Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain space fears, the shapes that fried dough can
take, gravitron related skull damage, and strict dip and dot meal plan restrictions.
All this plus Ashley Crystal Hairston joins us to talk wild waves on today's podcast, The
Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast hosted by three men who love lazy rivers
so much they zoned out in school when learning about more productive rivers like the Mississippi
or the Euphrates.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always Scott Gairdner.
How productive could it have been if it didn't help anyone to relax?
That's what I'm always saying.
Jason Sheridan, do you agree?
I would say so.
I haven't thought about the Euphrates in a while.
Yeah, what a poll.
I wrote Euphrates last night and I was like, is this a Dennis Miller-like reference?
It's not so obscure, I guess, so it's not classic Miller.
He would have gone with something much more obscure, but it was still in the zone of like,
I'm really like fancy reference boy here.
Yeah, it made everyone believe for a second that you knew about history unless they've
heard every other episode of this podcast.
Yes, then they would know that I only know about like X-Men history and different like
historical places that things have happened in the X-Men universe.
That's really more-
We all do.
I know the history of various malls that I've never even been to.
Where do you know where Sail on Sailor was recorded?
Well, that was on Holland albums, so it was probably done in Holland.
It wasn't just a name, they did the whole record in Holland.
So Holland is the answer.
Holland is, that's pretty good.
Yeah, hey, I did get it.
Jason, do you know where Devil Dogs are manufactured?
Oh, usually I think there's like regional baking facilities for freshness sake.
Okay, so you think there are multiple different locations where Devil Dogs are-
I think so.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's less impressive.
Our guest, go ahead.
I was just gonna say, still pretty good.
He gave a specific, it's funny, our guest was asking what is the format of the show
right before we started.
And now, I guess we have to break it to you.
The format of the show is quiz.
We'll be asking you a series of questions.
No!
We may not, we won't unlock the room.
It's gonna be location-based questions based on whatever micro niche stuff you're into
is what the topics of the show are.
You can also take a little nap if we go off too much about snack cakes and the beach boys.
Oh, good, because yeah, I didn't know anything you were referencing just now.
We went straight to deep cuts.
You woke up very quickly.
You're a real pro.
Like, oh shit, what is this?
Let's bring her in though.
From Tiny Toons Loonaversity and the upcoming show Fairly Oddparents, A New Wish,
it's Ashley Crystal Hairston.
I don't know why I'm so excited.
Yeah, we're excited.
We're loving it.
It's the best, it's the biased energy anyone's coming with.
Despite us trying to put you to sleep.
Oh gosh, great.
Good, good, good.
Happy to be here.
Thanks for having me.
Of course, thank you for doing it.
I guess I was gonna ask any famous rivers you like.
We don't have to talk about that.
Thank God we do.
The Nile.
Yeah, the Nile's a great river.
The Nile, yeah.
We're getting, if we're doing the Family Feud,
the board of kind of like the rivers you think of,
I think nobody got X'd.
Maybe Euphrates.
No.
Euphrates might be too.
Well, usually it goes, I think it's like Tigris and Euphrates.
They go together usually.
So that would be probably a combined answer on Family Feud.
I'm guessing.
Show me Tigris and Euphrates.
Nile and Mississippi are jockeying for one and two.
So you would have been up there.
Oh, Mississippi, right.
M-I-S-S-I-S-S-I-P-P-I.
One of the main points of the American education system
is teaching that little memory.
That's all I remember.
Any word that doesn't have one of those, I'm screwed.
I got this pile of five that I'm wrong every single time.
And I'm not coming up with them, but.
I can't think of it either.
How old are you?
How do you not know that?
There are words that I will spell wrong every single time
and will not take an extra five minutes to learn.
Same, same.
So like Cincinnati is probably jealous right now,
because Cincinnati, I don't believe, had one.
And I always get confused about how many N's
and how many T's there are.
Yeah, I don't know what offends.
I don't want to try.
I don't want to.
There's this really bonkers, you know Babes in Toyland,
the old Disney movie.
Oh my gosh.
There's that, but then there's this weird one from the 80s
with a very young Drew Barrymore and Keanu Reeves.
Oh my gosh.
And they're from Cincinnati, and there's a song
where they spell it.
But it's very unmemorable, and it doesn't help that it's
Drew Barrymore and Keanu Reeves singing it,
because maybe they're a little pitchy, right?
They're not known for their singing,
so it doesn't help me keep the melody in my head.
Well Keanu doesn't sing in Dog Star, right?
I don't think in his band.
Is he the bass player of Dog Star?
Oh, it's his band.
Yeah.
I'm like, I've not seen that movie.
I'm sorry.
You'll discover that I'm terrible with references.
This is when we all discover.
But throwback me, I love it.
You should know Dog Star.
Oh no.
Not just because, look, Keanu's, I feel like the film
is called Keanussance, which has nothing to do with his band
Dog Star.
I love that.
But they're back.
They were on Kimmel a couple of weeks ago.
Dog Star Band.
The band, he was just on for the band.
Oh my gosh.
They have a newer album, yeah.
So he's having kind of a moment in movies,
and he's also having a music moment.
And he's motorcycle enthusiast.
Oh.
And is that new?
He loves, well, I just watched John Wick for a few years ago.
A few years ago.
A few days ago.
And there is very clearly, he gets on like a racing bike,
or a speed, John Wick at some point gets, I'm like, oh,
of course he gets on a very cool motorcycle.
So were you basing his motorcycle moment on this movie you watched?
Or do you know other information?
No, I believe he was helping design ones.
Oh, that's cool.
And he helps restored ones, and sells them and stuff.
I love that.
Well, that's great.
I think we all love Keanu Reeves at this point.
We all can agree.
Yes, yes.
And we love everything he does.
Yeah.
From motorcycles to music.
He's the motorcycle character in, he's Duke Kaboom in Toy Story 4.
Oh my gosh.
So he's having an animated motorcycle moment.
And Scott loosely ties it back to Disney and theme parks.
Sort of.
Not that, well I tied it back to characters who you might need at a theme park,
but I don't know if there's any characters at the theme park we're talking about.
Maybe you can correct us on that.
I know, I was looking around.
But yeah, so we're talking today about a place that you've been, Ashley.
Yes, yes.
Wild waves.
Yes.
But yeah, we could real quick just kind of feel out,
what's your general theme park interests, where they lie, how often you go to them.
Right, right.
Do you like them now as an adult?
Oh my gosh, I love theme parks, yes.
Grew up going, we're like a theme park family.
I'm from Seattle, Washington, so not much to do.
That's a question, yeah.
So theme park, we go to Disneyland and Disney World to get away for our vacations often.
That's my childhood vacation memories, we're like going to California for Disney and Universal
Studios and Florida, all that stuff.
And then, yeah, oh I had family in St.
Louis, Missouri, and I remember going to Six Flags
there when I was a kid a few times, yeah.
And that was scary because there was always like twisters happening.
Oh god, really?
Yeah, I remember my first tornado, well first, my only.
Thank god, thank god.
I've not been in many tornadoes.
I hope it stays that way.
That's good.
But that was our first tornado hurricane situation was at Six Flags in Missouri,
and I remember the sirens went off.
I don't remember how old I was, I was probably like, I know I was 10 or under
because my sister was around that age and we're four years apart,
but I just remember them like parading everyone into one of their like auditoriums,
and we all had to stand along a wall, along like just like lying the wall of the hole,
and I remember just looking out at everyone stuck against the wall in case, I don't know,
I guess that's how you hold up a structure or something.
That's what they had us, because I'm from Illinois, so we would have a tornado warning
once in a while, and they would take us out in the hall and you just line up against the wall.
What is that?
I don't know, because I think in the old days it was under the desk,
but then I think they determined that that was bad.
I mean, that was also what they would do if like you got the like nuclear bomb warning
in those old videos, you get on your desk and like this, and you're like,
I don't think that's gonna.
What they think that's gonna do.
If there's a nuclear bomb heading for Schaumburg and Illinois,
I don't think that's gonna stop it, but I guess, yeah, I guess the feeling was like you go near
the strongest wall.
Yeah, for support maybe, like the wind will push your back up against and you'll just be stuck
to the wall maybe.
It'll be like a gravitron, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, it's fun.
Yeah.
And then he's all, we'll all start sliding up.
If you're in the eye of the storm, yeah, then you actually, maybe it's a little funny.
Oh, gosh.
You get a ride out of it.
I didn't even think about the eye of the storm.
Just spinning.
You got it.
Wait, isn't the eye of the storm?
No, the eye is the peaceful part.
The eye is where it never ends.
Where it slows down.
Oh, right.
I don't know about science, weather, or history.
The eye is where the teenager working the ride would stand in the middle and watch as you were
on the outside of the gravitron having a fun time getting smashed up against the wall.
Sure.
Yeah, which was the worst ride.
I'm sure you all probably talk about that a ton on the show.
I liked that ride as a kid.
You did?
Yeah, yeah.
I had so many head injuries from that.
It's dangerous.
Because it would just fling you up.
So the cylindrical, just kidding.
No, what's the word?
The force?
Whatever's pulling.
You're talking about a couple of science heads here.
The cylindrical force.
We've been like, yes, you know what I'm talking about.
It's a cylindrical force.
Believe the equation for that is, it was awful.
Yeah, and you just like, it shoots you up to the ceiling and bang your head all the time.
Yeah, no, I could see how that would happen.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I probably was very, I probably moved very conservatively in there.
So I just, I remember kind of just being pressed against the wall and kind of just trying to turn
upside down and not trying to like.
You're also really tall.
Yeah.
So that probably, you didn't have as much of a distance to travel.
If I hit my head on the metal, it wasn't with like five feet of distance.
Exactly.
It was one foot.
Yeah.
Yeah, that could play into it.
I think my parents described that ride to me and I was already freaked out and they're like,
yeah, it's called a hell hole.
Oh, God.
Later on, I would see the signs that said Gravitron, but they're like, yeah,
and it throws up against wall.
There's no seat belts or anything.
Sometimes a floor drops out.
Sometimes floor lovers can't stand.
Oh my God.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to go to the hell hole.
Get on, try it, son.
I didn't know it was called a hell hole.
I've never heard of that either.
I've seen Devil's Hole too.
Oh.
That's way worse.
You're really bad in your life on Earth.
You have to go live in the Devil's Hole.
When you're a nervous child and you are told you're thrown against the wall,
the floor drops out, and it's called a hell hole, I was just like, well, I'll never go on that.
Yeah, good.
Smart.
Ashley, were you into more thrill rides or more like robots rides?
Oh, definitely thrill rides.
OK.
Yeah.
I feel like I love roller coasters.
I love drops.
I love swings.
Big swings, I assume.
Yes, yes.
Although regular swings are good.
Like the ones that swing, yeah.
I don't like feeling dizzy though.
So the Gravitron one I didn't like.
I'm fine if it's like the regular swings that you, it's like, oh, this is whimsical and I can see
everything, but I don't like fast spinning.
Like, have you ever been on that ride at Epcot that is called?
Mission Space.
Which is, that's a round and around so fast that you get zero Gs and you get,
it's close to actual NASA flight training.
Yeah, that's a similar energy, I guess, the cylindrical pool.
Yeah, we didn't like that.
We were very mean to it when we did an episode about it.
It was a, it's a ride.
They had to tone it down really quickly because it killed a couple people right out of the gate.
I know.
All right.
That's all crazy.
And it's still awful.
I don't even walk over to it.
I don't want to look at it when I'm there.
No, you got to save yourself some walking at some point.
I don't need to go near that building.
I liked it when I was younger, like a teenager, and my body was like, could just be punished
constantly.
But I remember, I'm just recalling when we did that episode, I was in isolation with COVID.
So I was like, oh yeah, I feel like I just rode mission space.
I feel like garbage.
Did you, Jason, I don't know if we talked about this, did you have fun doing it when
you were a teenager?
Did like the forces, like the G force feel good?
I think I liked it, but when I rode it in my mid or late twenties, I walk off,
really nauseous and dizzy.
And I'm like, I don't want to do that.
I just can't imagine that feeling fun.
Because I can sometimes, if I get a little dizzy on something, I can imagine the, like
I go, okay, I could see how if I was maybe like, like more sleep or something, that would
have been fun.
Right.
But I can't imagine the feeling, the pressure I felt in my skull, that that would ever just
be a fun feeling.
Right.
And then on top of that, like the claustrophobia.
Yeah.
Part of it was stressful as well.
And there's nothing fun to look at.
It's just a little screen of like graphics from 2001.
It's claustrophobic when you walk in already.
So like, all right, I will be feeling claustrophobic.
Then they start it and then a whole panel comes towards you.
Yeah.
Like, oh wait, it is twice as claustrophobic as I thought.
Exactly.
It's like an inch away from your face.
Yeah.
Right.
There's not a single fun part of it.
Which is unfortunate because I would like to go to space one day.
But how would I get there?
Right.
You can't do that, you mean?
At some point you got to do it.
I bet it's worse.
I bet mission space is worse than going to space.
OK.
Because like William Shatner went into space on Blue Origin on the Amazon on Jeff Bezos'
rocket and he was fine.
He did it a year or two ago already.
He's 92 years old.
Oh my gosh.
But he might have gotten dizzy.
We don't know that.
I understand that.
But I'm just saying like you put 92 year old William Shatner in mission space, he's croaking.
Right, right, right.
And I shouldn't say that on this show on broadcast, right?
Because this happens all the time.
But I just mean like how much training could he have gotten to go on Blue Origin?
But is it, do you feel that sensation when you're lifting off and then you end up in
zero gravity and it's pleasant?
Maybe.
That's what I hope.
Because when you do it in Florida, you are in a simulation of a lift off and then you
walk into Florida humidity.
Or pouring rain.
So you're saying at least there's a pay, maybe that's just the payoff is the reason
that you put up with the horrible skull pain.
Maybe.
And that's kind of like life, you know?
OK, I have a real question for all of you.
Yeah, go ahead.
Sure.
Would you go to space?
That's a good question.
In like the sort of touristy way that it's like a brief, like you're in zero G for like
20 minutes and then you go down?
Yeah, if like we got to a point where it's regular, normal, everybody can go.
But you do have to, you know, get there.
Which, you know, whatever all that entails.
So it's like, OK, I'm going to ask, flesh out this question more.
Sorry.
So it's like cheap as an airline ticket, perhaps multiple companies have been doing
it for a long time, multiple years.
And it seems like very few explosions.
Right.
Check those yellow reviews.
And the one stars are done on behalf of they're written by the widows of the people who passed
away.
Yeah.
Get over it.
It's not like super elitist anymore.
Yeah.
It's not like.
But there is like a spirit airlines of space travel, too.
But if you do these, this one's better.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm kind of interested.
Right now I'm hesitating because I'm a little afraid of blowing up.
OK.
But if it is like multiple years.
Geez, Mike has these crazy fears.
Of blowing up in space.
I've written some pretty janky roller coasters and some pretty janky cross country flights.
So I like fly though.
How much worse can space be?
Turbulence and all that.
Could be like a lot worse.
It could be a lot worse.
But like maybe I don't know.
I've rode in some bad Southwest flights.
He's a pro.
He's basically sign him up.
Jason, go tomorrow.
You don't even get to pick your seat.
You're fighting for seats when you get on.
It made me check my bag.
I had to put my bag.
I wanted I needed here though.
I'm trying to get trail mix out of there.
Actually, that's a perk.
They still have the two bags free.
Like not a lot of places have that.
OK.
I could do like an hour of turbulence without losing my mind.
Then after we get into that hour on the plane, like second hour of turbulence,
I start to go, oh, here comes the Joker.
All the dark spots.
I'm turning to the Joker.
So I think it's a shorter trip just to get to the like the atmosphere,
like whatever the part of the atmosphere where you are weightless.
So I think I could handle that.
I think so.
OK.
So yeah.
So like if we're talking like going to space and then like kind of live in a hotel on Mars
or something, maybe I am a little more intrigued because you get the fun of zero
gravity, but then also you're like living on a planet or moon or something.
I would.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would.
I think it would be cool to, you know, traverse the terrain of a planet.
Yeah.
You're getting out.
You're getting out of this.
Yeah.
Going to wherever you're going.
That's that sounds more because like I was when I was a kid, I loved Star Trek The Next
Generation and I would in the same way, I think they like when I was a kid, you loved it.
Well, I only had it then.
No, no, I only had a qualifier to say what I was about to say next, because obviously
I talk about how much I love it all the time on this show.
But I just only say that in the same way that like kids would read a Harry Potter or read
X-Men and like fantasize about going to a place, I would like dream of like living in a little
room on the ship and like going from planet to planet.
Uh huh.
You wanted a cabin is what you wanted.
I wanted a cabin on the Enterprise, yes.
Because you had, there was a replicator on it that could make you any food item you wanted.
And you'd have like, it was like, I mean, it's a one bedroom apartment.
I wanted a bachelor pad as an 11 year old.
There wouldn't be room for a second person to sleep.
I didn't even worry about having a girl.
No, I didn't want to.
Where would they go?
When I was 10 or 11, I was like, I would just love to have like
a big room with everything in it and a fridge and all my stuff.
And like, eventually I realized like, oh, I'm describing a studio apartment.
Did you ever get one?
No.
Oh, dang.
Still time.
There's still time.
Yeah.
Still time.
Some sad changes in my life.
I can still make it happen.
Yeah.
So, so yeah, space.
It will be, unless the planet blows up, I feel like it will be easier to do.
Yeah.
In a decade or so.
Whoa, which is crazy.
I don't think I weighed in.
I feel like I got to be honest with myself.
It sounds fine to me, but I'm not going to count a bumpy flight as
people know I have problems with coasters.
I'm just like, I'm being honest with myself.
I would just need to like hear some information.
What is this going to do to my body and stomach?
How long are you going to be like blasting off or, you know?
Give me some kind of thrill meter.
Right.
Let's put, you know, rock and roller coaster.
Where's rock?
How many, how many numbers, how many rocket ships is, or novas is rock and roller coaster on the
meter and then what's actual space?
Okay.
Because I fear that, well, rock and roller coaster is a 0.
00025 and space is 100.
So, but I don't know, but Shatner does.
I see what you're saying.
Shatner gives me hope.
So yeah.
And he came back very depressed too.
Oh, no.
Oh, fun.
Oh my God.
Oh my gosh.
And he just was having like a freak out moment.
It does not sound so fun.
Maybe I don't need to fantasize it so much because yeah, it does feel like,
it feels like space and the galaxy, you know, planets is like some cool thing.
Like humans made up in their minds, you know, like the biggest like concept we can imagine,
but it really exists, you know?
So why wouldn't we want to go and explore it?
Yes.
Because it might make rumblies in my tumbleys.
That's fine.
Jason, do you say you would go?
I think I would go.
Look, I would also go to Federal Way, Washington.
Oh, is that a hell of a segue?
he can also handle the twists and turns of space.
I would go to space, but every time we do like a regional or a smaller neighborhood theme park,
I'm like, I could go to Iowa.
Go to Seattle area.
You could go to Iowa.
But like, I'm not like, I'd like to see this, you know?
I would.
It did feel to go in the direction you're going.
It felt like I was going very, traveling very far away because it's like I'm from,
well, so technically I'm from Bellevue, which is like 10 minutes outside of Seattle.
So like getting to go to Wild Waves was like this, oh my gosh, we're going, you know,
it was like maybe 25 minutes away, 30 minute drive.
Which feels long when you're a little kid.
Especially on a bus, like you're taking a cheese bus there.
It's like, oh my gosh, we're going.
A cheese bus?
Far, yeah.
Like a school bus.
Oh, you call it cheese buses?
Yeah.
Because of the yellow?
Yes.
Oh, that's nice.
That's cool.
Yeah, take a cheese bus there.
Oh wow.
So you would do like school trips also to Wild Waves.
Yeah, so.
This is in the, okay, it's in the Sea-Tac area.
Correct.
And it's kind of between sea and tac.
It's sort of equidistant.
Yes, Seattle, Tacoma.
And it is a, it's kind of half theme park and half water park, is that accurate?
Yeah.
Because it was like both, like it was in the past called, like Wild Waves is the water park part,
but the theme park had been called Enchanted Village at some point.
Correct.
Now it's just kind of all one thing.
Pretty recently they've combined it, and so it's just called Wild Waves theme and water park.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Okay.
They used to be clunkier with like, no, it's two things.
Yes.
Remember two names.
And I'll tell you what happened probably, is that no one liked Enchanted Village.
Like as kids we all hated Enchanted Village because the rides were boring and dumb and
for little kiddies, and no one ever wanted to go to Enchanted Village.
Everyone was always like thrilled and excited to go see, to go to Wild Waves,
because that's where the fun rides were like the freaking wave pool that like drowned people,
and then all the cool slides and stuff like that.
So yeah, we all were like, forget Enchanted Village is the boring part.
What age are we talking?
When's the first like trip or two?
How old are you?
So I was thinking about this on the way here, and like my earliest memories
were elementary school.
And I don't remember, so I know for a fact that the math Olympiad team got to go for
their end of the year.
Oh cool.
But then I was thinking, I was like, was I on math Olympiad?
Which seems very far off.
Seems like that would be unbelievable.
But I do, you know what I know it was.
I went with my patrol team.
I got to go.
I was on patrol in elementary school.
What's patrol?
Patrol is like the kids who wear the yellow vest, and you get to like
guide kids, students in between classes, you know, to like go that way, go this way.
I don't think I know that.
Was the school complicated enough?
You needed that?
I don't know.
I guess.
It's just something to do.
Like we need kids need jobs.
This is going to be one.
Put them to work.
Then we got to like leave class a little bit early to go and like be at your station.
Our school, which was Sunset Elementary, Puesta del Sol, is Spanish immersion and English.
It was like outside, you know, like so like the classrooms were separate.
And like to go to each classroom you go outside outdoors.
And so it was kind of like amazing that way because all of the pathways connected
to each outdoor, to each like building.
If that makes sense.
You didn't need to.
And it was like older kids usually, right?
It wasn't like you wouldn't put like first graders in it.
You had to be like fourth or fifth grade, I remember.
But there would be like a kid or two in my class that would have to leave like
10 minutes early to suit up in uniform.
To go direct traffic.
Right, right, right.
Why didn't I have this?
They deputized the child.
Was it just kind of
Fairly self-explanatory, I guess.
Did you have hall monitors?
Like that's what
Yeah, that's basically sort of what it is.
I'm not sure that I did have hall monitors.
I don't know.
That always felt like a TV invention to me.
I know they're real, but I didn't, I never had like
That's sort of what this is.
Yeah, basically.
But yeah, it would just be like to get, yeah, one kid to feel like superior to the other kids.
To get to go and tell the other kids what to do.
Friggin' wild waves at the end of the day.
You were superior because you made it to wild waves.
Yeah, that is actually a real victory.
So you're being sold the idea that Enchanted Village is supposed to be for you, but it's lame.
So this is what I'm confused about because there are coasters and stuff.
Was that part of Enchanted Village, or is Enchanted Village purely
There were some rides for kids because it sounds very kid-oriented.
Yeah, I don't remember any big roller coasters being there.
I remember a train ride situation, maybe a carousel thing, or some boring outdoor gymnasium thing.
I remember that.
And then there was some boring theme of the Enchanted Village that nobody cared about,
about bears and bear fairy tale land, whatever.
And they had characters, I remember.
And it was all just so kiddy-like.
No one cared about going to Enchanted Village.
It just made me think how upset I'm going to be when my son doesn't
I have a three-year-old, and when he starts thinking rides are boring,
what am I going to do?
The entire way we pass the time is go on various trains that show you nothing.
Oh, when the word boring enters his lexicon, I'm so screwed.
They don't want to go on.
There are a few roller coasters at Wild Waves now.
Oh, great.
They've added stuff in the last decade or so.
They've changed owners and stuff.
They haven't added a lot recently.
No, they have not.
But there is the
What is the coaster called?
Are you talking about Timber Axe?
Yeah, Timber Axe in 2018.
They added something called Timber Axe.
Oh my God.
No, is that the spinner that looks like a big axe?
Oh, you're right.
Yeah, that's not a roller coaster.
Excuse me.
That is a big axe that spins around.
Oh, no.
Watch out.
Boring, we'll show you.
The most violent ride possible.
Timber Hawk is the wooden coaster that kind of goes through the woods a little.
Oh, that sounds fun.
So, and those are always fun.
It's like a good old clunk.
That's a 2003
Timber Hawk, Ride of Prey.
Ride of Prey.
Prey doesn't mean anything.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, watch a ride through whatever.
That'd be the boringest thing.
Sometimes we'll play clips of rides and shows.
Oh, that's fun.
All right, now here, let's just listen to Ride of Prey.
Listen to it.
Let me just hear glug glug glug glug.
All right, well, I think we got a sense of it.
It's interesting.
This park, because it does feel like a smaller neighborhood park to the point that in the
aerial photograph you can see online, you can see on Wikipedia, there are houses up in the
corner by the parking lot.
But then there are a couple of larger coasters.
Okay, let me see.
Yeah, this seems decent.
Like, you know, just the good old clunky wooden
This is the
Timber Hawk is the tallest roller coaster in Washington.
And that is not
It sounds more impressive than it is because that's a technicality,
because Washington, as you probably know, does not have a lot of roller coasters.
I think that's our only park, like our only theme park to Washington.
Other than the State Fair, which has rides.
Puyallup Fair, we have, I think.
Well, at least that's the one I grew up going to.
When Puyallup, Washington smells terrible.
Getting weird with these names.
That's in that Keogh Cook family.
I knew someone from Puyallup.
And then a friend from high school went to Evergreen College, designed his own major,
sort of like
I feel like a lot of cartoon
Matt Groening?
Was he involved in Evergreen at some point or went to school there for a little while?
Was Matt Groening involved in it?
No, I couldn't remember if he taught there or if he was a student there or something.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
But when Mike said you wanted to do this one, I was like, oh yeah, I don't know a lot about
the Pacific Northwest parks.
There's another park a little further away.
And then there's Enchanted Forest in Oregon, which is not related to Enchanted Village.
Kind of has the bush gardens.
Like, all right, there's the little town.
There's the little old West Street.
There's a little variety.
I like that one.
People tell us to do that one.
Enchanted Forest?
Yeah.
You know what?
When this came up during this episode with you, Ashley, I thought, well, that's interesting.
I've never heard of that one.
And yet it felt familiar to me.
Then I realized, oh, I have heard of this because several years ago,
I did.
And I'm going to enter a differing opinion.
I don't know.
Totally some of your feelings about this place.
But here's what I did.
I did a call a couple of years ago on Twitter for some topics you might want us to do on
the main feed or on our Patreon.
And there was one that stuck with me so much.
I took a screenshot.
It was on my desktop for the longest time.
I think the user was Diddy Thump.
And the-
Diddy Thump.
Shout out, Diddy Thump.
Who seems to not have been expelled from Twitter or something.
I hope it was not a bad situation.
But Diddy Thump said, just this very blunt, here's-
All right.
What should we do on the show next year?
Wild Waves in Washington.
Suck shit.
It's funny.
It's funny?
Suck shit.
It's funny.
That was the full review.
And it really called to me.
I thought about pulling the trigger on this with you guys a long time ago.
I'm glad I didn't so we could do it with you, who's actually been.
But now that I've thrown out kind of the like negative opinion, and I don't know.
I was just so like entranced by the-
The way that was.
Of the spray show.
Oh, for sure.
All right.
Diddy Thump is right and I hope they're out there listening today because wow.
Suck shit.
This one's for you, Diddy Thump.
What calls- what jumps out when you hear that someone thinks that it sucks shit?
What might that be for?
Well, literally, well, I'm again, I know they're probably referencing the Enchanted
Village part is like such a waste of a park on the side.
The Wild Waves Parkside was so fun, but it was also just so like you have to know about what
and I don't want to rag on my own hometown, but where it's located is like Tacoma is always gets,
you know, chitted on because
um and no offense to Tacoma people, but it does it like smells bad.
The city like actually smells bad because of like the uh there's like uh
Some sort of plant or something?
Yes, it's a plant.
I was gonna say an oil plant, but I don't know if it's oil.
It's like old refinery plant that's there and the smell is like sulfur that they use to crush.
Ashley, there is a Wikipedia referring to this syndrome.
This is extremely sourced and the Wikipedia title is Aroma of Tacoma.
There you go, yes.
It is a- yes.
Yeah, they did Tacoma.
A putrid and unpleasant odor that is sulfury.
Why is it?
Is a rendering plant, a pulp and paper mill.
Pulp and paper mill.
An oil refinery.
It's a lot of stuff.
I think it's better now maybe than when you were growing up, but it's still bad.
Mike's listening.
Oh yeah.
During a concert stop at the Tacoma Dome in the mid 80s,
Bruce Springsteen reported that the odor was so overwhelming he was forced to leave the town early.
Oh, what is that?
I thought it was gonna be the show.
Oh no.
Bruce wouldn't have to leave the show early.
I agree.
I'm taking- I'm just gonna chill out for a week in Tacoma.
Oh my gosh.
Just real hardworking American like nope never mind out.
This afternoon, give me a plate.
Just find me a Marriott in Seattle.
Bruce would not.
He'd still do a four hour show, but he put like the clothespin on it.
Their lives are so hard with this aroma.
He should have written a song about the smell.
Yeah.
You know who did?
Wait, sorry Jason.
Oh, please.
You know who did?
Frank Zappa.
The 1979 Frank Zappa song, Jewish Princess, mentions a garlic aroma that could level Tacoma.
Oh my gosh.
You guys know all of this history.
Me neither.
This is your hearing it real time.
I'm glad you brought this.
I have no idea that Tacoma smells.
Apologies to everyone in Tacoma.
Would there be a bigger theme park presence in Tacoma?
Possibly.
The pros like cheap land, cheap real estate, a large population, cunts, stinky.
Smells like eggs.
And that's what it literally smells like eggs.
Like soon you'll be driving in your car.
You'll be normal, listening to music, having a good time.
And then bam, suddenly eggs in your nose, in your throat.
And you're like, oh god.
And then you like immediately want to turn around.
Nothing good's happening in this city.
Gary, Indiana is like that too.
There's a smell?
Yeah.
Oh boy.
Just because of the different like whatever like plants again, like whatever.
This is also there's Google results on this.
This must have fooled the Jackson family too.
Aren't they from there?
We gotta get out.
I grew up outside of Philadelphia and all along the Delaware River there were refineries and
chemical plants and stuff.
So occasionally get a bad smell.
And then once or twice in childhood, I lived pretty far away from it.
But like the people who lived close, so it's like, okay, we're doing indoor recess today.
Do not spend extended periods of time outside.
There was a leak.
Oh gosh.
The Tesco plants.
Everything is under control, but you may smell a pungent odor and do not be outside for too long.
And it's like, oh, okay.
What does Tesco do?
Why are they stinking up your town?
I don't know.
There were so many.
Boeing and what's the, not Lockheed Martin.
DuPont had a lot of plants in Pennsylvania and Delaware, different facilities and stuff.
But yeah, reading about this park was interesting.
It's had a lot of owners over the years.
Foster child kicked around.
Kicked around.
A lot of the reviews are either four or five stars, like really fun going with manager
expectations or one star review.
They are plagued by staffing issues and half the park is closed.
Yep.
A lot of reviews of like go to drive a little further, go to Silverwood.
That was the other.
Silverwood.
Is Silverdale?
Maybe Silverwood.
I don't know.
Silverwood in Boulder Beach.
I don't even know where that is.
That one.
Yeah.
It's farther away.
I have to check that out.
So morale's a little low because it's getting at least a half of that Tacoma stink.
Yes.
The water park's fine, but.
Yeah.
Water park was fine.
And then I feel like there was like teens working.
Of course.
No adult presence really.
So you got grimy teens working these rides and monitoring safety.
And yeah, the people that the park attracted, they're from all over.
I feel like no one ever really felt safe there.
So everyone's looking around, making sure their kids are there,
belongings are there, all that stuff.
You got to go there, yeah, manage your expectations basically.
But my favorite ride on Wild Waves, well, I shouldn't even say ride,
but it was the wave pool.
Kids went for the wave pool.
That was the big draw to Wild Waves, was the insane wave pool that like,
there's probably deaths listed for that too.
There is.
Okay, yep.
Yes.
Yeah, I drowned a couple times, not fully drowned, but like.
You needed help?
Yes, I needed.
Well, first of all, I'm 4'11 for the listeners out there.
And then I can't swim also.
Well, and I should say I can swim over water or underwater.
But when you put the between.
But the between water is not safe for me to.
It's also hard to swim when you're getting pummeled by waves.
That too.
Yes, I'm right there with you.
I'm 5'1.
I've got my ass kicked by some wave pools.
It's so scary.
Where the actual Atlantic Ocean has not beat me up as much as like artificial wave.
Yes, yeah, same.
I have so many memories of like, I remember we got in trouble once
because I was further out than I should have been.
And our or whatever the lifeguard person was like, had to dive in and.
Oh, they did?
Yeah.
Get me out.
Was that like a situation where you could not breathe as well?
Like, is it that scary?
Just like, you know, clamoring in the water and like, catch a breath,
that kind of situation where they see you physically struggling and know that,
hey, this girl doesn't know how to swim.
She should not be this far out.
But it's hard to not be that far out because the waves are pulling in, you know?
So it's tricky.
It's a very tricky thing to navigate.
This was one of my mother's big fears.
And I was not allowed to do this for many, many years in any sort of way.
Wisconsin Dells was yours, correct?
Yes.
We haven't talked a lot about wave pools, I guess.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
The regularity, I guess, of like the machine driven, constant, giant big wave is a little bit.
James Bond villain torture device.
Just like throw Mr.
Bond in the pool and we'll pummel him with waves.
And see how when he like his like muscles give out.
Yeah.
And then he just goes sinks and that's it.
It's so bizarre.
I mean, that's so bizarre, but like it is you think you're safe one moment.
And then once the way, and I think there was like a sound or an alarm that would go off
whenever the waves, we knew the waves were coming.
So kids would like rush out as far as they could and wait.
Yeah.
And just wait for them.
The big wave could go farther out.
And then they're gradual.
So like the waves would start small and then everyone, all the kids are like,
and then they get more and more and then suddenly it's like
the biggest wave of life.
And you're like, like dying immediately sucked under water.
That would alarm me.
Like you were saying, a partial drowning.
Yeah.
They believe they say the panicking.
Right.
Is a big part of it.
Yes.
As a kid, those alarms that big waves are coming would stress me out so much.
Sure.
But like every now and then the alarm would sound.
I'm like, I don't like that.
Like, yeah, it's thrilling, but also terrifying.
Yeah.
It's kind of fun when you're at the beach and it's like, oh, big wave suddenly.
Right.
A little surprise.
That's kind of like, oh, here's a big one.
Now a smaller one.
As opposed to the just drilling of I have the sire.
I feel like I must have been somewhere with a siren, but is this like an error rate?
Yeah, it sounds usually like it's like a nuclear bomb is coming.
Get under your desk.
Yeah.
Backing up from Mike, does anyone want to try it?
And is anyone haunted enough by one of the air raids where you feel like you know what it sounds?
Is it like Godzilla style?
It's like, maaa.
Yeah.
That was horrible.
That's good, yeah.
I feel like he really is nailed that.
All the moan of that.
That's really, these are all terrible for different reasons.
That is what you would hear too in the Midwest, like, because we were, we lived right by my school
and they would, there was the tornado alarm.
Yes.
It would blare through the town.
Yeah, that's so scary.
And it was like that because it would go.
And it would just last for a half hour.
And that's what, yeah, you would hear in the wave pool.
That's the story you own.
In the fun place.
Everybody was afraid of you on your trips and you where you live, afraid of tornado sirens.
And then for fun, you'd go to places with fun sirens.
Yeah.
Which sound identical to the scary sirens.
Yes.
Okay.
Than the tornadoes necessarily.
Yeah, scary.
I don't like, okay, I don't want to like delve into this, into the death though.
We try to avoid those, but there's just an aspect of the death that happened here that is like,
well, that's what happens when teens are in charge.
Oh no.
Where it's.
life grid said, I don't believe you.
I know kids are pranking me.
And not to meditate on it, but isn't that bonkers?
It is, but it's also like.
And then the 31st kid was like, somebody's drowning and he's like, yeah, right.
I fell for it 30 times and then I would have a little more sympathy.
Squidward is not in the pool.
I know that for a fact.
Your dad does not work for Nintendo.
I went on a computer and I looked it up, play the secret games that the other kids don't get to play.
That's not a real thing.
I've been lying to you by kids all day.
I see another and I watched some videos of rides at the park and stuff.
And a lot of parks, even at the six flags level, will do like for 20 extra bucks or something,
you do the sky coaster or whatever, or a zip line or like, sky coast is the thing where they like
raise you up in like a vinyl tarp and like drop you.
So I, someone had a GoPro clearly like strapped to them and was being lifted up.
And that the way that there's like a mix of the way they get people down is like,
there's kind of a cherry picker, like a thing that rises up to meet it.
But then they also just kind of like hook you with a long pole.
The workers that were walking out to do the hooking part, one of them was just looking at
the whole time while they were like lifting the person up and they didn't have anything to do.
But I'm like, if I was being lifted that many stories in the air, I would prefer the employees
to be alert and not playing Tetris.
The theme park should be like the set of a Christopher Nolan movie.
No phones, no sitting down, always alert and making sure that kids are okay or people are okay.
Yeah.
I love the stories of sets like that because it's like, okay, that is a director who is not also
an actor because most of the job is sitting around.
That's true.
Yes.
Let's make it very clear.
Jason Sheridan refuses to be in a Christopher Nolan film.
If you were thinking if anyone was filling out an email to try,
are you curious for a self-tape for Jason?
He's out.
I'm bringing like a Coleman chair.
I'm bringing a folding camping chair, Chris.
Jason was set to play Alfred in the Batman movie.
And he turned it down.
And he turned it down and they went with Michael Caine instead.
I can put my little phone in the trailer, but I need like at least a tiny little chair.
I need a little stool or something.
So you will accept the role of the elevator attendant.
Yeah, elevator attendant.
I will demand rows where I am sitting.
I'll be a Bonville.
I would be Blofeld if I can spin around in a chair.
Asha, do you remember specific slides at all?
Were they memorable enough where you were like, oh, I'm going on this and you knew the name of it?
I don't remember the name of it, but there was one.
It was closest to the freeway.
I remember because you would be at the top of the slide and you could look to your left and the
I-5 was next to you.
Oh, yeah.
I saw something about the I-5 in one of the Wikipedia.
It's just this park is literally just off of the I-5.
Like it's right there.
Oh, one of the thrill rides is called I-5 Skydive.
Oh, is that the sky coaster?
Yeah, that's new.
Is that one new?
That's 2017.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they're just naming it now because it's so close.
Yeah.
So there was a slide that was right there.
And it was a water slide.
And I remember there being like two.
So one was like really higher, like higher and steeper.
And then there was one like they ran right next to each other.
And then the shorter one was like for the wusses.
And yeah, that was like one of the other big attractions.
So like, yeah, there's like Congo slides, they say on the like, I'm just looking at the website.
And then there's Pacific Plunge, which has like a couple of different slides.
Oh, I remember that thing.
And Zuma Falls.
Maybe that's it.
And that was when you were in a big tube.
Oh, no, that's not it.
So it's a family.
It's a family.
I mean, it's there's something.
Warming tubs, they say.
Well, Scott, I have questions about the warming tubs.
Warming tubs.
What is a warming?
That phrase kind of hurt my head.
Is that a hot, just like a gentle hot tub?
It looks like a hot tub.
It's bigger.
On the website, they call it warming tubs and it says thrill level mild.
It could not jump to moderate or severe if you get stuck in the jet.
So Scott can go in the warming tub.
Has anyone seen Scott?
Oh, he's posted up in the warming tub.
He's probably getting some mild thrills somewhere.
Now, here's my question is that it says on the Wikipedia,
former rides warming tubs closed 2020.
So it's unclear if they've reopened the warming tubs
and just haven't updated the Wikipedia, which I guess is more likely.
They close it because of COVID.
People are getting COVID in the warming tubs.
You can't have that.
So they close it, but maybe they just haven't put it back on the
operating rides on the Wikipedia.
Somebody get on there.
We got to let the world know that the warming tubs are available.
Assuming when does this place open?
I don't know.
In the morning?
Oh, I see what you're saying.
May through October.
That's kind of like some times only on the weekends.
I think October a lot.
They also do a fright fest.
I don't think you could trademark the phrase fright fest.
No.
But I'm sure started
I was little
I've not been able to quite suss out because I kept seeing conflicting things.
Because Six Flags at least had partial ownership.
But some reviews I read or watched or read about this park was like,
well, it never got official Six Flags branding.
Okay.
A former owner sold their shares to Six Flags.
Seven years of Six Flags.
And then Six Flags, like, no, they were good.
They're on wild waves.
I think they got out of Six Flags probably at good timing because it was during
When Dan Snyder, who used to own the
Is it the Washington Commanders now?
Formerly the Washington football team.
Formerly a much more unpleasant name.
He kind of ran Six Flags into the ground for a while.
And so they like just missed like that.
No, I think he did.
I think he was the owner then.
And this was part of like getting rid of their massive debt was selling off a bunch at that time.
Because they owned a bunch of odd like
This is one.
Frontier City in Oklahoma City.
Elitch Gardens in Denver, which is a place I was thinking about going to.
Can I do a quick little mini rant here?
Because there's that.
And then there is the main attraction to me, the newly reopened Casa Bonita.
Do you know about Casa Bonita?
It was in a South Park episode.
It's this crazy giant Mexican restaurant that's kind of a theme park too.
That has cliff divers and little human beings that jump into the cliff diving site.
And it was so specific in the South Park episode 20 years ago
that everyone was like, but did they make that up?
What is it?
Yeah, it is real.
It's real.
It's this big Denver fix.
And I'm like, oh, if we could go.
And maybe I even do my anniversary, my 10 year wedding anniversary at Casa Bonita.
Yes.
It was purchased by the way by Matt and Trey from South Park.
Okay.
They bought it and renovated it.
I love that.
Yeah, they bought the restaurant.
They saved the restaurant.
Yeah, because it was going to close.
Good.
Then I started that.
So I even bought plane tickets.
I'm going Denver.
We're going to Elitch Gardens and we're going to let's go baby.
Yeah.
But then I realized then I saw somebody, a friend of mine, Joe say, all right,
at last my year long wait in the Casa Bonita lottery has finished.
Oh my word.
Now just to scramble and get plane tickets so I can be in the city.
And I checked with a couple people about this.
Doug Jones, you went to Casa Bonita.
Right.
Now I've gotten the answer.
It is an insane lottery that takes a year to play out.
There's no way to know when they'll tell you you're up.
Oh.
And then you might never hear anything again.
Really?
I almost went to the city and then just walked up to the door.
Hello, I'm ready to be here now.
You have a year of waiting to do.
This might be, I complain about Disney booking and reservations and all this.
Yeah.
Casa Bonita might be the most difficult place to get into in the world.
That's cool.
In the world.
More than Club 33.
All of it.
I hate to burst your bubble even more, but LH Gardens days might be numbered as well.
It's one that's changed.
They're open this summer.
Changed.
They are open this summer.
of course, like apartments and mixed-use shopping and all that.
Silver plants.
I think it's kind of falling apart, but it does have, do you know about Beowulf, Ashley?
It's kind of like a theme parky art group.
They have installations in, I think, Texas and Vegas.
We went to the Omega Martin Vegas and they were given like free rain.
They and a ride company redid a ride at LH Gardens.
So there's like an oddball psychedelic ride in the middle of a theme park that is kind of seen better date.
I know.
That's the other thing.
I'm looking at this website like this doesn't seem that good.
And if I can't even go to the greatest restaurant on earth, then what am I doing?
So I'm curious if any of-
Do you think there's like a underground, you know, market situation?
I don't know.
Maybe an email.
Saying, you know, I'm a influencer in the theme park podcast space.
I love that idea.
I don't think it'd help me one bit.
I sent the cockiest email, like happy to tell you more about our listenership, how many people.
I don't think anything's happening here.
Listeners and people have asked, like do a Casabonita episode.
I'm like, if only it were that simple.
This is a whole process.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
No, that's cool.
I'm going to have to go leave and mope for about 15 minutes.
I want to see these cliff divers so bad.
Yeah.
Anyway.
That's a bummer to hear.
It sucks.
Apologies.
I saw the word Elitch Gardens and things.
And you were sad you were triggered.
I had to complain about this.
And your anniversary is this year.
Yeah.
Dang it.
Get another 10 year anniversary.
I have to spend it at an annoying restaurant for children.
I hear you.
What am I doing if I don't do that?
You got to do 15.
It's going to have to wait for 15.
Tell your partner we got it.
10 year doesn't matter.
15's a new.
Ashley, so when you were there, do you remember, was there a teacher present when you would take
a field trip?
What were the ways in which you were allowed to explore?
They just said go have fun.
Would kids break off into little groups as well?
Yes.
I remember it would always be we'd go with our groups.
We'd have our adult in charge, our chaperone or whatever.
And then we'd get there and then we'd immediately have to go put our belongings in a locker.
And then I remember we were free to roam the park.
And then we'd have to come back by whatever time for lunch.
And then we'd get to roam the park again.
And when we were roaming though, I remember breaking off into our subgroups,
little friend groups, which was always kind of nerve wracking because you want to,
well, I don't know, for me, I was always like, am I going to be in the cool kids friend group?
Because they seem like they're having the most fun at the park.
Well, there's politics to it.
For sure.
When you're a kid.
And then it's also like maybe you're friends with a couple people,
but they're not in the same friend group either.
And then you're like, kids want status.
You're like, I'd rather go with my friend who's in the cooler group.
But then you might be letting another person down.
You're absolutely right.
So it's stressful in that way because that would always, you would run into that.
Yeah.
I remember that exact situation numerous times because I was pretty, you know, fun kid.
I had lots of different friends, all different kinds of friends.
But there were the cool kids, quote unquote, which were usually like the rich kids.
That's what makes you cool.
Money makes you cool.
But were they really that cool, you know, now that I think about it?
They're actually pretty boring.
But we would like, you know, once I had my like set group of friends, we like weren't worried.
But I did have one friend who was like liked by the cool kids.
So she would get pulled off into the cool kids group.
And then like she'd be leaving our like BFF group, our subgroup, you know.
And splitting the time.
Then we'd get like lost and separated.
And then it was always, yeah, it was weird like passing your friend at the park who you're like,
hey, are you not with us?
Isn't that cool?
We're not going to the warming tubs.
Just all go to the warming tubs.
Yeah.
But yeah, I had my set, my BFFs.
Like I've had the same friends since sixth grade.
Oh, yeah.
Like my, yeah.
So that's interesting.
Well, sort of.
Well, I won't get into that.
Anyway, I had the same friends for about 25 years, over 25 years, the same like group of friends.
That's cool.
So that was very long.
But yeah, we would.
Yeah, it was like there was a there was a social component to it.
Yeah, it is makes me cringe sometimes when I think about it.
Yeah, like I think I was like upset people.
Like, because I don't know that I ever acted honorably in those situations.
I don't know if I ever was like, hey, we can all just hang out together.
I was more like, I want to go with the Pritz and Kula.
I always chose the worst option.
I think I always just gave in to whatever.
Well, yeah, on some level, I guess, betrayed, but always like, feel like I probably was a coward
and didn't try to.
It's hard to speak up and do that at that age.
It's like everything's on the line.
Yeah, I remember I have really weird stuff will hit me at five.
I wake up at five a.
m.
And I'll just be like, remember when you accidentally called a kid's name
and you thought you wanted to hang out in like the playground?
And then he like you told him, no, you met these other kids.
And he looks so sad.
And he was a kid who walked around alone at recess.
Oh, my gosh.
Why didn't you just say like, hey, we can play.
Don't worry about it.
Like, let's have a good like that.
Like stuff like that will haunt me once in a while.
Sure, sure, sure.
And I'll be like, oh, God, like it's always five a.
m.
too.
You're mixing things up.
That happened with us.
No, I met the other Jason.
No, I met Jason Aldean.
What I would sell you off for Jason Aldean in two seconds.
Son of a bitch.
I knew it.
It's just reality, man.
He's the coolest singer, country singer.
I know it goes rock.
I'm never going to Nashville with you now.
I would give up this podcast to hang out with Springsteen.
I'm sorry.
He already has a podcast partner.
I know former president Barack Obama.
I know.
But if they would add me to that podcast, I will.
Three renegades.
The three renegades, Barack, Bruce and Michael.
Did I ever tell you my Bruce story?
No, no, I wouldn't do this.
So off topic.
No, please.
Ron is on the topic.
I'm so sorry to give it.
So my ex-boyfriend went on stage with Bruce Springsteen.
He's like a huge Springsteen fan.
He has been to countless, like every concert he tries to make.
And so when he was here, this had to have been, I guess, 2017,
right, or 18 or something.
And he had three concerts right before the LA dome closed.
He was like the last person to perform.
The sports arena.
Yes, yes.
I was at two of those.
Yes.
Might have seen this dancing.
Maybe I did.
You probably did.
So we went for our anniversary, and then he went again the next night.
So the night that I went, I touched Bruce Springsteen and held his hand
because he came out around and my ex-boyfriend lifted me up to reach and grab his hand.
And I touched and we held hands for a little bit.
And he sang to me.
Looked you in the eyes?
Looked me in the eyes.
Sweaty face and all.
And then he went back the next night and brought a sign that said,
dancing is a man's man's job or something like that.
Okay.
It had his face in the center.
A man's man's job.
Oh, maybe it's dancing is a
Well, because during that song, dancing in the dark, he usually brings up a lady on stage.
Like the Courtney Cox video.
Courtney Cox video, yeah.
And so he was saying that he could be also somewhat different.
Right.
Doesn't need to just be a girl.
I'll dance with you, Bruce.
I'll think I can be Courtney.
I love that.
Exactly.
And he went to the front.
And so this is where I learned all about the how to get to the pool, the front section,
all that stuff.
You have to be in the lottery.
And we did that.
But so he got pulled up by Bruce Springsteen.
And not only that, he gave him a guitar to play.
Wow.
And they played together.
Did he play guitar?
No.
He doesn't play guitar, but he is a comedian and an improviser.
And so he just pretended to play.
And then Bruce looked at him and goes, you're good.
And then
Is it on YouTube?
If you figured that out?
It has to be on YouTube.
I'm sure it's on YouTube.
I have seen this.
And I can't remember if it was the one show I didn't go to or I saw it
because it was probably just on Instagram and I saw it.
Probably.
It kind of went medium viral a little bit.
He got interviewed by some news stations after.
He's from New Jersey and his whole family is Big Bruce people.
And so this was a huge, huge deal for him.
He was sick for days afterwards, just on a high, so excited.
This is everything to him.
And then you kicked him to the curb.
That's what ended it.
All right.
Well, just kidding.
No, I was so happy for him, but we did break up later, but not right away.
Way later.
Sure.
It wasn't that he was
It was with Bruce related.
Just to be clear.
It wasn't.
Yeah, he only called you Bruce from then on.
Bruce or me.
He was sick at work the next day, I remember.
Just so elevated.
Didn't sleep by that.
It was too much to
Like a kid getting too excited and then just throwing up out of work.
Yeah, he threw up at work.
I don't blame him.
It was so great.
Do you think that happens with the character Courtney Cox played in the music video?
That's the epilogue that you don't get to see of the post-high vomit.
Yeah, you are in withdrawal.
He's got so much charisma when you get away from it.
Yeah, that's what happened when Jason and I met him at the book signing.
We threw up the next day.
Depression, it's real.
It was depression.
You need to get treated for it.
There's no shame in it.
There's no stigma.
It wasn't the eight hours in the chaotic, poorly managed groove.
No, we've talked about that part.
Oh, what happened there?
No, it's a long
We waited for like eight hours.
Say it again, you motherfucker.
Fluctuating temp picture.
Mine was a joke.
This was for the book.
I appreciate it because it was a joke.
He wanted to retell the story.
It's Jason's fault.
He had a book signing at the Grove.
Yeah, he went in his memoir.
And it was sort of just a photo op.
It's like a Pooh Bear.
It was at Disneyland.
And you just kind of walked in there.
You walked in and took a photo with him.
The most, maybe the most security I've ever been around.
Wow.
Is that true?
In terms of like, keep moving, watch out.
They were, yeah, his handlers, they had real handlers.
The handlers were really intense.
So, how long has it been actually since you went to Wild Waves?
Oh my gosh.
When was the last year?
No, I don't even.
So, I would go with school numerous times, I remember.
And then some friends had birthday parties at Wild Waves.
So, that was a thing too.
So, I'd been for a few birthday parties there.
Which were, those were easier, I will say.
But yeah, I don't, I would not even remember.
It's been a while.
It's been years, years and years.
Yeah.
My question, and I don't know when this was implemented,
but I was looking at the website and you can buy,
I wonder if this is for birthdays or what,
you can buy, as if it's a Las Vegas pool,
you can buy cabanas and rent them.
Fancy.
At Wild Waves, I don't know if this is.
Where are they located?
I think this is common for water parks.
Is it?
No.
But I don't know, I mean, I think there's probably a dozen of them.
When I say common, there's a handful of parks that have that.
Well, it looks like there are 19 according to this map.
Oh my gosh, how much are they?
How much is this?
Well, you have to call for pricing apparently.
Yeah, yeah.
It's probably dynamic.
They don't want to say what the bottle service costs.
Yeah.
But they do give you 25 or 50% off if you're a season pass holder.
Really?
Yes.
And they're all around this wave pool.
Oh, gosh.
So.
Nightmares.
And probably you can see a little bit of I-5 too.
Prime I-5 view.
Maybe you don't want a cabana because the walls
block the I-5 view.
So yeah, it sounds like you were not having a birthday in the cabana.
No, we didn't do.
I would be interested to know how many of these are filled on any day.
I'm curious how much a ticket is these days.
Oh, well that I think you can find on here.
That is one where it seems like by the season pass because it's the same or less than one day.
We don't have that many days of sunshine in Seattle.
It seems like the park alternates between really empty and understaffed or totally packed
and also understaffed.
That sounds accurate.
There's a lot of to this sucks shit end that Diddy Thump referred to.
Where you'll end up waiting in a food line for an hour.
Barely moves and then you get up to the front and like one hot dog.
Sorry, we are out of hot dogs.
I don't remember the food being good at all.
Yeah.
Is there any.
That's not what you're there for, I guess.
These days or back then, do you have like a go to like of crappy theme park food,
like a corn dog or like is there a thing you gravitate towards?
I'm a I'm a plain old chicken tenders gal.
I love barbecue sauce and I love french fries.
It's my favorite food as an adult woman.
So, you know, take me to a park and give me fries and nuggies and I am a happy camper.
Very reliable, but also very sick.
Like I don't think nuggies have ever made me sick.
Oh, right.
Nuggies.
I don't think it ever fucked me up.
This is a virus you've passed on.
This is what it's going to be on the park as forever now, isn't it?
Tendies and nuggies.
Yeah.
It's so cute though.
Nothing.
God, you're the weird one.
Yeah, they're so good and you can always like if you're dizzy, like they'll it'll sit in your
stomach.
They will calm.
It'll calm it.
Give you a little protein.
Comfort food.
Comfort food for sure.
They seem to have something at Wild Waves that I've never heard of before that might be like a
fair thing or a theme park thing.
I've just never seen it, which is elephant ears.
Oh, yeah.
I was going to ask about elephant ears.
Is that a Pacific Northwest thing?
I don't know.
Is it?
Because a lot of the things, I looked at a couple of the area theme parks and they all
mentioned elephant ears, which is flat fry bread, usually cinnamon sugar, sometimes fruit
topping or whipped cream or stuff.
That was like a highlight.
We'd be like, oh, yeah, let's get elephant ears.
You know, that kind of thing.
But I don't remember them being at Wild Waves, but maybe it is a Pacific Northwest thing.
But it's they're so good.
It's just like, yeah, like you said, fried dough with cinnamon sugar, freaking.
It looks like it's in like the non zone, but like, but like a non funnel cake.
It's like funnel cake.
Yeah, I was just gonna say funnel cake, beignet territory.
I'd like to try it.
Looks like a beignet.
Like funnel cake is often like, I can't finish.
Like this is too much.
But beignets or like elephant ears.
Similarly, it's like this feels very manageable.
I think I could put one or two of these down pretty easy.
Funnel cake is the size of like a human brain.
Yeah.
And these seem like they're a little more like a pop tart.
Right.
Or are they bigger?
I remember bigger, like at least a plate full of them.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm also finding maybe these are the same as beaver tails.
And I feel like beaver tails has come up before.
Perhaps what's in my head is lagoon with Stephen Ray Morris, a Utah park.
So maybe we do different.
Beaver tails is very popular in Canada.
Used to be in Epcot, the Canada Pavilion in Epcot.
Right.
And they think occasionally come back.
I don't know if they're back at the moment.
It's like, what shape do you want your fried dough in?
Yeah.
Depending on what part of America you live in.
See this picture how it takes up the whole plate.
Oh, it is bigger than I thought.
Yeah.
The candy.
It's like a plate's worth of dough.
You're showing us some pretty big elephant ears.
But that might be deceptive then because if it's like three,
it's more three dimensional with a funnel cake.
And then this is almost like the size of a loose leaf sheet of paper.
Yeah.
But thicker.
Right.
So you might be getting a similar amount of dough.
Oh, I see.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I could.
I guess it depends because obviously there's probably different size funnel cakes.
You can probably depending on what machine you have,
what funnel cake making machine.
OK.
I'm looking at funnel cake.
You have recommendations.
I assume you both have funnel cake machines.
OK.
Look at this image of funnel cake.
Sony XR27 I think is the strongest right now.
I was just comparing funnel cake versus elephant ear.
OK.
And it's basically like just a flat version of a funnel cake.
Like funnel cake is I didn't realize or process really.
It's a bunch of dough like squiggled around.
Squiggly squiggled around.
So rises a little more.
Squirt it out.
Like kind of.
Yeah.
I don't actually know how it's made.
I should know that.
But yeah, it's I guess it's just whatever.
I don't know who invented these brilliant food inventions,
but it is just the shape.
Yeah.
Those losers we have now.
Well, it should be a Mount Rushmore made out of funnel cake.
Take a bite out of the founding fathers.
The other thing I saw that Wild Waves had obviously, yeah,
we were saying pizza, hot dogs, dip and dots as a present.
They also have Korean style.
Yeah, they do.
It surprised me.
Those are really fun.
Because they put things on the outside like potato flakes or like hunks of stuff.
The picture makes it look like it's completely plastic fake food,
but that might just be the way they photographed it.
But yes, I was that everything else is pretty standard theme park stuff.
I read reviews saying that that seemed to be an outside vendor,
and thus the superior quality to everything else.
Okay.
You could eat in the park.
So there's a tip if you end up in Wild Waves.
It is very funny with most theme parks.
Outside vendor either means you're in luck, it's going to be a lot better,
or it's like, oh, that's really shitty,
and the park has plausible detiability because they can go outside vendor, outside vendor.
Are they even here?
We didn't even see them set up.
Yeah.
So it looks, yeah, everything else, not that these are that interesting.
There's Carousel Cafe, there's Lumberjack Burgers, there's The Wharf, there's Disco.
The Wharf, what specifically says hamburgers and chicken.
It's not a fish restaurant.
What do you assume?
The Wharf says chicken tenders, burgers, and hot dogs.
Yeah, that's easy.
No, dad doesn't want that.
Disco eats and cool treats.
What?
Disco.
All over the place.
The theming is not necessarily rooted in the concept.
I think they sell, there's a place called Sharky's Bar.
And there is a fun, I don't think I have it.
Oh, Shakey's, nevermind.
No, there's Sharky's.
There is Sharky's and Shakey's.
I think it's kind of a generic.
And there is a fun shark on the outside, but I can't blow up the photo to show everyone.
But trust me, he's cool.
He's fine.
The other thing I have to, I built into a hill, right, this park.
And so like the amusement park side is kind of there's stuff like in wooded areas.
Yes, it's all wooded.
And that's very pleasing and then very, very nice.
But also due to the hill part, I noticed some pictures or videos where people just like
put their towels down on some grass strips and just like we're hanging out.
And I'm like, I see the appeal of that, but it also just seems a little sleazy.
Feel like there's a line between like, oh, this is pleasant using the landscaping.
But then it's also just like, we couldn't get a chance.
Throw the towel in the cooler.
The cabanas are for the elites.
They're not cost effective.
I think man of the people, Jason Sheridan would be all for the towel on the grass.
Well, I am.
I think what it is, the lagoon like at the entrance doesn't have any, like the plants
are very small.
Like it looks a little like they just put it in, which is not the case.
Yeah.
If I can bring a little towel and put it on the grass, I will be in your movie, Mr.
Noe.
Oh, Chris.
Yeah, Chris, I'm bringing something.
I need to crash a little.
They have a, I don't know if they had this when we were kids.
They have a season pass dining plan.
Which is very similar to the thing they stopped kind of doing at Six Flags where you can pay
$75 for the year.
What?
It's maybe, yeah, you know, there was a thing where Six Flags Magic Mountain offered
something like this and there was somebody out there who was like, great, that will be
how I have every meal from now on.
Bro.
And they wish, you know, if you're purely financially, you know, if you could do that
here, if you could spend, if you had to go back and live in stinky Tacoma, I don't know
what picture I'm painting of your life.
You got to be in Tacoma.
That would, oh, I feel like you would.
This.
What would happen to your body?
Oh, gosh.
What deposits would start forming in your.
I read this dining plan, though.
It's a lot of research.
You read the fine print on the contract.
I read the fine print.
What is that?
I believe it's one meal and one snack a day.
And there's like, cannot be used.
One?
Yeah.
So what's about the rest of the family?
No, no, one per person.
Oh, okay.
If each person had the dining plan, they can get like one meal, one snack because they're
like, they're not camping out for multiple meals.
So you're saying one plan per person for $75 for the year.
So I'd have to buy one for my three kids as well.
Yes, you would.
Yeah.
Robbery.
But then also like, cannot be used at Soul Corn Dogs, cannot be used here.
You can't get Dippin' Dots with it either.
You can't get Dippin' Dots.
That's a vendor.
That's an outside vendor.
Oh.
Espresso on the go coffee truck?
No.
Where are my kids going to get their needed dots?
My kids can't get dots.
They can't get espresso.
What's going on here?
This is not a good dining plan.
I wonder if maybe I should buy this by Wild Waves.
Buy the park?
Yeah.
It seems good.
Well, not now, obviously, but in the future, invest in the amusement park.
Industry in general?
Yeah.
And see, granted, most of the previous owners have sold this place after several years,
but maybe you're the one to take it all the way.
You can get like earlier, as we're recording this, a few days ago it was announced,
oh, this historic theater in Westwood, 30 filmmakers banded together and are taking it over,
which I'm not quite sure of the economics of that.
I saw that.
I just read that.
Well, Quentin Tarantino has bought two theaters himself at this point,
and this is 30 people buying one.
He bought the Vista too, right?
He bought the Vista and he bought the New Beverly here in Los Angeles.
You'd think Nolan wouldn't want to buy a movie theater.
There's so many seats in there.
Maybe he's got a plan.
Standing room only.
You don't know how to appreciate film.
I don't think he can apply that to film viewing.
He's on top of his game.
He's probably going to win best picture.
He could start saying whatever he wants.
We stand in movies from now on.
Real quick, I want to say that there's a guy who,
a couple of guys owned the park for a couple of years,
Michael Moodenbaugh and Jeff Stock, and we're not going to talk too much about it
because I looked into it a little bit.
They also owned a place called Boblo Island Adventure Park.
I just caught a little look of this story.
Apparently, they were putting a lot of money into that park
and they were getting bands to play and very ambitious plans for it.
This gentleman, Michael Moodenbaugh, got into a bad car accident and went into a coma.
His partner and everyone completely abandoned the plans
and switched it while he was basically out of it.
And then he ended up suing his partners for that
for all the things they were doing while he was in a coma.
It was a complete huge trial thing.
These are the two guys that owned this at one point.
He ended up having Michael sell his shares.
It just seems like an interesting story that we'll maybe investigate at a different time.
That's very traumatic.
It's very, no, it seems very traumatic.
But I then found a picture of Michael.
I think he made a full recovery, luckily.
Here he is in a suit on a water ride.
The dream.
Go Michael.
So I was like, okay, well, that's maybe we look into the place in a Boblo Island.
Let's make a pact with each other if one of us goes into a coma,
that the others will not bail on the podcast and leave town.
I would think business as usual until the party gets out of the coma is the respectful way to go.
If Scott goes into a coma, we're telling the Bruce Springsteen story every episode.
Oh, no, you can finally do the show you want to do.
Springsteen story, Buffett Plains story.
Randy talk, Randy Gerber talk.
Once a month, Tendi and Nungi review.
Scott has been holding us back from putting whys on every single word
and little before every other word.
I'm looking through here.
There's a vaguely patriotic zipline.
Did we say this?
It's called the Soaring Eagle zipline.
Okay.
And it's got the bald eagle on the top of the
Our state mascot, I believe.
Oh, the bald eagle is.
This ties into
All right.
I believe so.
Okay.
I believe that zipline goes from the one side of the park to the other side of the park,
so you get a cool view.
So that is positive.
It's an add-on, but you get to see the water park and the amusement park.
Scott, you'll love this.
A number of videos I watch refer to the water park and the dry park.
Now that's nice.
So that's, I guess, more of a
And a jerk is fine.
It's play.
A term.
We've discovered a word
There's water playgrounds in theme parks,
and that has led to us finding the words wet play and dry play.
Thank you.
The correct response.
Wet play.
This is for parents.
If you're bringing a family, just say,
okay, there's wet play and there's dry play.
No, families should
Now we're pulling families into these disgusting jerks?
No.
Imagine asking your child
I want it less than ever.
You're a wet player.
You're a dry player.
Hey, little boy.
You're into wet play, dry play.
Why don't you come with me?
I'll take you over to the wet player.
Okay.
We have to leave the park.
That's going off to jail.
Everybody wants wet play.
Surprise, surprise.
Can't you just a weirdo that's into dry play?
I don't know why it's their thing.
But I had in her dry park before.
Dry park is fine.
I'm fine with park.
Wet park.
Yeah, there's something that's not the same as
It should be wet park, but not even when that's still uncomfortable.
Yeah, right?
That is just like, yeah.
No, it's a water park.
We have the phrase already.
We don't need to reinvent the wheel.
And I guess dry park, if it's
Doherty Park, two great parks, one great price.
Doherty Park and Wild Water Kingdom.
Wet park, dry park.
Did they give you money to do an ad in the middle of the show?
No, it's unfortunately glued in my subconsciousness
from watching the commercial too many times
when there was only cable television, no computer.
Child Jason Sheridan, though, on the way to a park
that he's never been would be like,
excuse me, mother of
Is it mostly primarily dry play today or wet play?
Well, this is child Jason Sheridan got to hang out
with some good friends at Hershey Park
when the chorus of band went to do a competition
or something there.
And the first year discovered that his close friend
was very scared of big rides.
So childhood Jason was pretty pissed by that.
So the second year, I said, see ya, and did a lot by myself,
which you were not supposed to go off on your own.
But enough kids were
If I saw a teacher, I would just look for other students
and say, hey guys, what's going on?
We're all in the group.
And then the teacher would walk away.
I was like, all right, see ya.
You briefly pretend to have friends as cover.
I was a pretty social guy.
I had a lot of friends.
I had a lot of places and friends.
But in these days, you don't want to
Like friends only slow you down from getting them.
No, I wouldn't ride a big wooden roller coaster
and eat a chili dog.
I was like Sonic the Hedgehog in that way, I suppose.
I wanted to go fast.
Well, I wanted to go fast.
You wanted to go fast, but you weren't.
Just be a roller coaster.
I was like a chubby Sonic the Hedgehog at 12.
Cute.
That is cute.
Yeah, I was cute.
I didn't know the power I had of being cute at the time.
Chubby, isn't it?
I should have been telling my peers,
I'm actually a little cutie.
It's kind of adorable.
With other kids your age,
make fun of me if you want,
but I'm actually a little cutie.
Do you realize that?
I'm a little cutie.
Let's try to beat me up now.
But it'd be all you'd like.
I'm a big chubby and these glasses are from Sears.
But I think when I get older, this will be pretty endearing.
I love this, Jason.
Little cutie.
He's a little cutie.
So I guess as we sort of wind down,
Ashley, do you have any big stories,
big memories of any of this stuff?
You don't have to have a big story.
Or do you want to go make some new ones
now that you've revived it?
Yeah, I kind of do want to go back now,
but I'm like, wow, wait, what if, okay, the wet park idea,
what if they made an amusement park for only adults?
Sure.
Only adults and it's all wet stuff.
Yeah, you into it?
I just want to know what definition wet is.
It's just called wet park and it's for you specifically only.
I'm uncomfortable on the surface.
This is getting more and more popular in the dry play.
In Vegas, I think Luxor has an adult playground with bars inside.
You consider that dry play?
An adult bar in a casino you would refer to as dry play.
I agree.
If there's a pool within 100 feet.
The day clubs and the pools are wet play.
But there's an adult playground with bars
and then Manloy Bay I think is building a very elaborate
miniature golf with bars.
A miniature golf.
It's too boring.
These are the loosest definitions.
Right now we're doing a dry podcast because we're not
being liquid while we're doing it.
So this is very popular now.
It's dry podcast.
Okay, okay.
Well, yeah, wet play.
Wet podcast is dangerous due to electrocution.
You got to do those with satellite microphones
that are outside of the pool,
pointed into the pool to record that sound.
But that's not what we're doing.
To be clear, listeners, this is a dry podcast.
We're not drunk currently yet.
I have water.
Yes, just water.
But I don't know.
Are you dissuaded by anything that we've told you about?
Are there people's opinions about this?
Or if you end up up there,
what are the odds you ever go back to Wild Waves?
Well, I go back home like probably three, four times a year.
But yeah, I'm curious to go back now
and just see all of the updates.
Everything that's changed.
See if I could put my bid in to purchase the park.
And yeah, I'll be Mrs.
Waves.
Oh, you'll change your name.
Yeah, I'll change my name to Ashley Waves.
I think you could use that
because we've said there's not a clear cohesive theme.
That's what I'm saying.
They need a theme.
They need someone to come in and really tie things together.
Give it a nice concept.
It could be the face of it.
The way you hear Dollywood, Dolly Parton's name,
the person you think of Dolly.
That's what I'm saying.
Can you be the Dolly for this?
I'd be Mrs.
Waves.
Yeah.
Are you just on signs or the restaurant's named after?
It's Mrs.
Waves, fine fried nuggies.
Yeah, Mrs.
Waves, cabana, house.
Just everything's named after you now.
That does make it more appealing for you especially.
Yeah, it's my face.
And then you can Google it and you'll find fun facts
that I didn't even know how to swim
and I still conquered purchasing a bottle, a wet play pot.
You'd think Mrs.
Waves could never, from those starts,
you'd think she'd never become the queen of wet play.
Exactly.
Mrs.
Waves, the queen of wet play.
That's what it says on the sign outside.
Oh, yes.
It says, come wet play with me.
That's my slogan.
You've got a comfort with the term, I feel like.
I feel like you've got a plan for this place too.
I think maybe this is what it takes to move it,
to pass it forward to the next generation of sea tackers.
Which, so I mean, with that, I believe,
Ashley Crystal Hairston, you survived podcast The Ride.
Thank you so much for taking us to this bizarre neck of the woods
and to space and to the Bruce show and everywhere.
Let's exit through the gift shop because I believe there's some stuff to plug.
Yes, what's going on in your world?
Hey, well, you can watch Tiny Toons Luniversity.
It's out on Macs right now.
And keep an eye out for Fairly Odd Parents.
Yeah.
The reboot.
This is just announced.
It happens to be the morning that you're recording this with us.
Yeah, my phone's blowing up.
You ran this show and you're the main voice in the show.
All right.
Well, there's four of us that created it.
And I was fortunate to be a writer on it and also lend some voice acting to
the new God kid.
So very exciting.
That's great.
Also involved in the show.
My love.
I thought you said my mom.
Ever since we had a daughter, I haven't called like a Mike Pence style.
I call her mother.
Mother is also involved in the show.
Yes, yes.
Lindsay Kata, yes.
We're both Geminis.
So you can imagine how wacky this this little kid will be.
That's very exciting.
You've been working on this for I don't know.
Are you allowed to say a while?
A long time.
I posted that it's been two years.
So it just takes forever.
Yeah.
And today this will be out fairly soon.
A few weeks.
So yeah, very exciting.
Fairly soon.
You're also Babs Bunny on Tiny Toons, I want to say.
I know.
And our former guest Eric Bauza is Buster.
Oh great.
Oh, were you on it?
I mean, was he on it?
Yeah, he's on here, yeah.
Oh cool.
Wow, we've had Buster and Babs.
You've had Buster and Babs.
Pretty cool.
Maybe the most starstruck when I realize you two were Buster and Babs.
That's crazy.
My friends from childhood?
Yeah, from our mod days.
Yeah.
For the listeners, Jason and I were on a mod team together at UCB Theater.
She had a sketch knife for a number of years.
Now we're on this podcast.
Yeah.
Pretty good.
Come a long way.
I was expelled from university due to plagiarism.
Oh no.
Oh dang.
The dean, Taz, beat the shit out of me.
He just spun me around.
So you had no clothes at the end?
You know what?
I deserved it.
They didn't know you were a little cutie.
I was trying to tell him.
I'm a little cutie.
I don't think you realize that.
You try to plead your case and they just respond with.
It's me and Devils.
You can't reason with them.
Ashley, such a pleasure.
So fun talking to you.
I can't imagine cartoons that come from your mind and have your voice.
I'm excited to check it out.
Hey, thanks.
Absolutely.
Thanks for having me.
So fun.
For sure.
As for us, you can find us on the socials at podcast, The Ride,
Merchant, or T Public Store for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate, or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier
Club 3 where we're currently in the process of re-releasing the City Walk Saga.
The original, we are believe now, or one week out from the new City Walk Saga,
the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
Let's commit to it further by me saying it right now.
So anyway, if you want to be that re-releaser to get that full experience of the Orlando Saga,
all of that at patreon.
com slash podcast, The Ride.
There we go.
And then right.
So my notes are all the usual plugs that I say.
And then right under that is a review I didn't read from the park that says it's one star.
This place gave my dad a concussion.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to
our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.