Forever.
Dog.
Guys, Mike, Jason, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Yeah, Jason, are you there?
I'm here.
Oh, good.
But why can't I see you guys?
What's happening?
It's like we're still in some weird muck zone between ends of the multiverse.
Is that what you're seeing too?
I'm also seeing weird muck.
Yes.
Anyway, we gotta find each other again.
How do we make our physical forms land in a physical place,
specifically at City Walk Orlando?
God, it's like we need some kind of new jump point, you know?
A place where we can reunite.
Like, where is a place of unity?
A place that brings together the best and brightest from far different ends,
from miles and miles apart, with a spirit of cooperation, celebration,
and yes, perhaps, delicious food.
Gentlemen, I know exactly where to go.
A place we have not been to yet,
that brings people together despite minor differences.
Gentlemen, meet me at the Hot Dog Hall of Fame.
When your town has made you frown,
When your swear has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch,
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge,
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol,
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks,
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk,
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the City Walk Orlando Saga Multiverse of Madness.
We are back together in one place again.
Me, Scott Gardner, you, Mike Carlson, and you, Jason Sheridan.
Hello, I'm here.
Jason!
Hi, Mike!
I'm so happy.
We could finally, it was tough being split apart,
but we did what we had to do, but now we're back together stronger than ever.
This is like when Kiss did their solo albums, and then the next album they were back together,
this must be what they felt like.
Yeah, having conquered the world.
Each, how many, 12 songs on all of those?
So, what, 48, or something, maybe I'm at it wrong, like 48 classic songs.
Let's just say 48 classic songs that we all remember.
No notes, no problems.
But now we are, we have become, we're back together, the regular group,
but I feel that we are now a super group because we're joined by a great guest,
who coincidentally, perfectly, for today's topic, one of America's leading hot dog voices,
the writer of the New York Times bestseller Raw Dog, the Naked Truth About Hot Dogs, Jamie Loftus.
Wow, it's just really great to see you guys back together after this whole journey.
You have no idea.
Perhaps at this point we have no idea what we've been through separately.
It's all a fog to us, but yeah, yeah, we made it just in time to host you, to have you.
So excited to have you here.
The first non-Chucky Cheese-oriented episode.
I know, I was thinking that.
I kept, like, I knew we were talking about the Hot Dog Hall of Fame,
but there were several times this week where I was like, I gotta get, I gotta brush up on Chuck.
I had to like tamp down that anxiety, because I'm like, I'm behind, I'm behind on Fector,
I muted Fector, I don't know what's going on.
That's the correct move, is to mute.
I feel showbiz pizzas, or wait, no, he's the Rock of Our Explosion creator.
Yeah.
Right.
If you're out there and you aren't following him, don't, or if you are, then mute.
Crazy things happening.
I do have one question.
I don't know if you know about this recent,
these happenings in Chuck E.
Cheese world.
The somewhat mixed bag of news that the animatronics
are officially going away, yet they will have one committed to residency near us in Northridge,
California.
There is one place where the robots will not disappear.
It feels very dark to be like there's one location where you can, like, because it's that Chuck E.
Cheese
was just a, is just a museum basically at that point, right?
Like, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to go, like, I'm going to go the second it's, is it, has it already happened?
It has happened.
I have not been, my wife and child went separately.
And here's what it is.
They just, they, they did something, I don't understand why they don't just, why didn't they do this at all of them?
Because, you know, all right, let me step it out a little longer.
Here's the deal.
Like, I've been to,
I've been to that one with my son.
I took him specifically, like, we got to go to one of the old school ones with the full munch,
with the full robot band.
We went, he had no interest in the robots.
I have failed to instill this in him.
Just a three-year-old with no context has no interest.
What he has been really interested in at other Chuck E.
Cheese's are
the light up dance floors that they are replacing the robots with.
I'm looking at this in my own family,
and I'm seeing that like, boy, it works.
They figured out something with these dance floors.
So in Northridge, it's both.
They split the room.
So it's the best of both worlds.
And yes, why not do that?
Yeah, I guess, I guess possibly because the kids don't like the robots.
But specifically with no, because it's entirely context with us.
I might, I don't know if I liked them when I was a kid.
I might not have started to like them until high school.
I don't know.
Yeah, I was afraid of them.
Yeah, but I did like them.
I definitely, I think I liked them.
But yeah, I liked them, but I feared them.
They're kind of like, like aunts and uncles in that way.
I like these people, but I don't want to like touch them or be close to them.
But I like that they're here.
See them once a year.
Uh huh.
If you're good.
And I don't know.
Do you, I wonder not to like pathologize your son's got, but I wonder if he, because I feel like I have like a clear memory of the first time.
I'm like, oh, I think my, my dad is disappointed for something.
And I wonder if that, if this will lock into, he's like, I don't know what I did wrong, but I know I was supposed to feel a different way about these robots.
After the very tense car ride, because there's a little bit of a drive.
That's like half an hour for where I am.
Yeah.
When the icy silence set in.
Did you punch the dashboard?
Broke his hand.
Delightly.
Yes.
No, it did more damage to me than to the, than to the mirror.
Okay.
It'll be fine.
No, I, you know, I try to be as open ended with these things as possible.
I try to not like, you know, I, I, of course I want him to, I'm just glad he likes being a Chuck E cheese at all.
And then within that, I'm not going to guide him.
I like that he likes being at Disneyland or Universal Studios.
I'm not going to, I don't, I don't need him.
I have plenty of like of eighties animatronics for the entire family from, from multiple entire families.
So he doesn't need to have this too, as long as he likes being in the places.
Yeah.
Everyone gets what they want.
You guys were driving back and you did put on the Chuck E cheese cover of cats in the cradle though.
We did, I will say a year and a half ago, Scott and I and his son went to see Chuck E live on the Santa Monica pier.
Rocks.
Yeah.
How was it?
It was pretty good.
It was loud as hell.
It was very, very loud.
Great show.
Great set.
Only new stuff though.
They weren't playing like together.
We got it.
Like they didn't do.
Did they, did they at least throw in a happy birthday?
Like they didn't do happy birthday.
I don't think, or there was a different type of birthday song.
The point of it was summer.
The point of it was having an awesome summer.
Yeah.
Okay.
So he's doing his theme shows.
I respect it.
Wait, where was the concert in Santa Monica?
It's on the pier.
On the pier.
Next to the park.
Next to the arcade.
Yeah.
I was like, wow, that's real.
You gotta let me know when this stuff's happening.
I didn't, wow.
That's the last time I went to the Santa Monica pier was to see Joey Chestnut eat, win a pistachio eating contest.
Whoa.
A non-hot dog.
I don't think I realized that.
Yeah.
I know Joey Chestnut is the hot dog competitive champion, but I didn't know he did other food.
He does other foods.
He's not general.
I don't think he's the champion of other foods.
He was neck and neck for wings for a while, but he's been pretty, pretty square-legged.
He's got really eclipsed in wings, I think.
But he was doing it for Spawn.
He is the guy for, I forget what brand of pistachio, but he's like, he has two strong sponsorships that I know of.
He has his own brand of bespoke mustard, which I do have in my home.
Whoa.
It's $14 for a thing of mustard.
It's a huge ripoff, but he is the spokesman for pistachio nuts, and he is the spokesman for Dude Wipes, which I think is the best match from, because is there a messier guy on the face of the planet than our Joey?
Yeah.
Are Dude Wipes for your face, or are they for the end of the process as well?
I think they're for the-
Based on the commercial Joey did for them, they're squarely for your ass.
Okay, okay.
100%.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
I'm looking at the-
They're like ass wipe-
Google says, for your butt.
Butt wipes.
That was my thought.
You said messy, and maybe I was hoping you meant face, but you're right.
I guess I never really, because I'm thinking of his face when I say that.
I'm not thinking of his ass, but maybe they are, which adds to the great-
Yeah.
You have to assume.
I like that he's being accountable for the end of the process.
I think that that indicates growth on his part.
I don't think he always was really open.
The year I saw him, well, the first time I saw him, he was doing some bounty spawn, which also makes sense.
He's a messy guy.
Right.
He was wearing a bounty robe and slippers.
It was pretty awesome.
Oh, wow.
Jason, you got to get out of the mat.
Oh, the dream.
Yeah.
Wow.
Him having these endorsements.
I hadn't thought about this dimension of-
Dude wipes were created because some men felt, what, that using a baby wipe was not masculine enough?
That's why I get it, because I was like, there's not really a feminine equivalent that I can think of.
They're not-
Yeah.
This seems like a needless macho branding.
I guess maybe not if it's successful.
I don't know that it is.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
I know that they, dude wipes, at some point, they donated a block of dude wipes, individually packaged things of dude wipes to the homeless coalition I volunteer with.
Everyone was like, I don't think we're going to give this to anybody.
This is for no one.
This sucks.
Are dude wipes, do they have a scent?
Is it cedar or something?
They smell very strong, because I ended up, because we were like, we're not going to give these out, I brought some home just to test them out, see what they're, and yeah, they reek.
So they're, yeah.
They smell so strong.
Cigars?
They smell like a skimmed, chemical musk.
Cool water.
Just automatically, if women try to use them, they just make them sick.
Rashes and ill, yeah.
They find a way to chemically.
Yeah.
It's not for, yeah, you have to have tough skin to use it.
I'm just like, who is it for?
Like in the smell element, I find fascinating.
I'm like, is it for, like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I feel like the guys who are using it don't have people near their ass often.
I don't think so, yes.
The desire to, I can't see them having the desire to make their ass smell like a specific, to have an ass cologne.
I think it's just a vibe based product.
I hope they paid Joey well.
The pistachio thing, I'm a little more confused by.
It was very underwhelming.
We just like, I went, I took the bus to the San Monica Pier.
It was at 10 a.
m.
on a Saturday.
It was raining.
And he just, boop, boop, boop, boop.
I mean, it was like, you know, he, he won against the other guy and then they gave away free pistachios.
Was it like fixed though?
Was it, it was kind of a show, like a.
I feel like it was.
The other guy threw the fight, threw the contest.
I mean, it's only fair.
He won, he was on, god, I don't know anything about sports.
He was on a basketball game the other night, eating pierogies.
Really?
Yeah.
I didn't know that he was like just eats if you pay him.
Makes sense, but.
Yeah, he's very eat for pay.
What did you have?
The dream?
The Joey Chestnut texture to your book, I feel like is big.
It's a big turning point.
I wrote down something too, because I wrote down like a thought about Tommy's and then I flashed back to your book and I'm like, oh, Tommy's a very kind of pivotal moment as well.
I think it was a LA chain Tommy's chili dogs and chili burgers and fries and stuff.
Was it big in popularizing chili dogs or at least here?
What's the turning point nature of it?
I don't want to ruin the end of your book.
It's more, I learned about myself there.
Oh yeah, not history.
Not in Hot Dog.
Your journey.
Jamie's book, there's a personal odyssey.
We got it too.
That's very stirring.
Thank you so much.
I went to Tommy's by myself on Christmas Eve.
I know.
I know my stomach just tightened saying that out loud.
But it's true.
I think in a just world, Tommy's would be as successful as Pink's is as an LA Hot Dog institution, because I think Pink's sucks.
Yeah.
Yes.
It's a scourge on Universal City Walk.
It's a waste.
It's a fake thing.
Especially growing up in LA, as I did, you hear about that forever.
The big line.
It's kind of put next to in and out.
But then when you go.
It's either unremarkable or fully bad.
It's a bummer.
The first time I went to Pink's, it was years and years ago, I stood in the line.
I did the line thing.
And I ordered something that there was no there wasn't a picture of it, but I accidentally just ordered like a little cup full of meat and sour cream.
Like I didn't even order a hot dog.
I was furious.
It's like, how did this happen?
What was it called?
I don't.
It was called like Sunday.
But I.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'll take accountability for I shouldn't have ordered something from a hot dog place called Sunday.
But it was like a cup of meat and sour cream.
It was pretty gnarly.
So don't just like start saying those celebrity names.
Don't go up and order the Tom Bergeron.
Oh, yeah.
You might just get it might be like a hot dog smoothie.
Styrofoam cup with.
And then you should know that's what the Tom Bergeron is.
By the way, before any further discussion, I think we know where we're going.
But let's officially confirm.
Oh, yeah.
What is the what are the contents of today's sector with the sector keeper?
Boys, boys and Jamie, phase seven, sector one is the hot dog hall of fame.
Good luck, boys and Jamie.
And keep an eye on Jason.
All right.
Well, as assumed.
I mean, we we knew and, you know, this this I feel is very serendipitous.
This worked out perfectly because, Jamie, I just asked you to be on the show for whatever purpose,
not affiliated with the saga.
And you organically brought up the hot dog hall of fame, not even knowing what was not even knowing it was a crucial piece of what is now a series in its 19th day.
I can't find the original city walk saga.
Still don't know.
We don't know how long ago.
We don't know how much more we have.
We will see.
My luck.
Just to toss that out.
And then like, oh, you have no idea.
OK, hold that thought.
I think we didn't then it was we held onto that for like a year.
And now we're here to do it, to fulfill a really crucial function.
Right.
Thank God.
Yes.
And what better place to have all met?
I think so.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's a read to reconvene here.
So you have and OK, so you you you wrote this book about hot dogs and well, I'm sure things about that will factor into this conversation.
But also you you have been to the hot dog hall of fame.
I've been twice.
Twice.
Oh, my gosh.
Twice in 2022.
Same.
Wow.
He returned that.
That speaks well of it.
I came back from any other while we're on the city because you were talking about having done a solo city walk, Orlando excursion.
Anything else from that experience you want to name check before we narrow focus on not talk all of them?
Well, I was I so I was yeah, I feel like I've given so many experiences of things that you're supposed to do with people by yourself.
The last five years.
And I like made time to stay at like a cheap hotel and go because I wanted to go to the hot dog hall of fame.
That was the thing luring you.
It wasn't even just city walk.
It'd be interesting and not the parks.
It doesn't sound like I well, I didn't have time for the parks.
I would have loved to go to the parks, but I was like, I only have time for one.
I'm going to walk.
And so I went I yeah, I love it was great.
I went at night.
I walked over.
I walked over for my hotel at night.
I was so overwhelmed by the hot dog hall of fame.
It's sheer size.
I have so many thoughts about the menu.
I tried to tell the person working there that I was like, I'm writing a book about hot dogs.
This is really exciting.
They could not have cared less.
I asked tourists to take my picture alone in front of the hot dog hall of fame.
It was really awesome.
I yeah.
So I loved the hot dog hall of fame.
I considered because I was like, this is you know, like when you reach the threshold of like personal humiliation where you're like, let's just keep going.
I considered going to like the dance club next to the hot dog.
Oh, yeah.
There's a few of those.
Margarita.
Clothes.
I don't even know which one it would have been.
The groove.
Yeah.
I read that.
Coconut.
There's a coconut club.
Yeah.
The coconut club.
That's what it was.
Yeah.
And it was Saturday night.
And I was like, should I maybe I'll meet the love of my life tonight.
I go to the coconut club.
But I didn't.
And yeah, it wasn't during Halloween, was it?
Because you could have met a sexy Frankenstein.
It was this.
OK.
It's about to get the stories.
It was on Valentine's Day.
So better, actually.
It was my first encounter with the like scary chocolate restaurant.
I still I know that you guys understand the scary chocolate restaurant.
I don't.
It was my first time encountering it.
I don't know if we've we've we've discussed it at this point.
I think we may we're possibly more baffled than ever having meditated.
It only unravels.
Baffling.
Do we like it?
How do we where do we land?
Oh, it's it's unpleasant in many ways.
There's a lot of ways to go wrong.
I'm sure there's one.
Maybe there's only one formula to get it right.
And it's like it's like a maze where there's only one path and then lots of dead ends and pitfalls and traps.
You know, you'll probably get into one of those.
But I'm sure someone out there has had a good time.
I somehow had a decent meal.
And it's because I got like the power green salad and just it's it's was shocking to like, well, this is all really fresh.
And the vinaigrette is flavorful.
It sounds like an anomaly.
Very strange thing for them to get right.
Yes.
And not any well, Hollywood, which is a more limited menu, I feel like probably.
Yeah, because the one in Orlando is huge.
Yeah, it's really big.
Like looming, bizarrely big restaurant.
Next to right next to the biggest Hard Rock Cafe.
Yes.
This the scope of everything.
Hot dog, hot dog, all fame included.
There is scale to everything.
Yeah, I was impressed that they really gave the hot dog Hall of Fame some breathing room.
And so then I went by myself and then I came back with my mom several months later.
And because she has a biannual timeshare and she really wanted to go.
This was on the fourth of July, another holiday.
She wanted to go see the new Minions movie that came out in 2022 on City Walk.
The day like on the fourth of July.
And I was like, all right, we're going.
And so we like pregame to the hot dog Hall of Fame.
And she was great.
That's an American day.
It was a very American.
Incredible.
What do we need to what picture do we need to paint of the hot dog Hall of Fame before we get into specifics about it?
It is it's like a walk up window.
Yes, so much so much more than that.
It is not an indoor sit down restaurant, but there are plenty of places to sit.
Great places to sit.
Bleacherous.
It's bleacherous.
It's basically like a they took this space.
I don't know what it was before because this wasn't there at the inception of City Walk.
But you like it's it's this like outdoor terrace on a corner that kind of like it just utilizes what would just be a weird awkward space.
I don't know what that would be without it.
But it turns it into this wonderful little mini stadium corner with like baseball stadium seating, baseball stadium seats, literal seats from our seats from OK.
Yes.
Right.
From old stadiums.
There is a kind of the you know, not just the window that you order from, but that keeps going up into this mighty wall, which has a big screen where you can watch baseball games.
It's got many trophies that are have like a gold fork that is spearing hot dogs.
I want one of those so badly.
I was zooming in on all the many pictures I have of those trophies, and I don't think that they say anything, unfortunately.
I wish that they had they had taken the time.
It's not like individual jokes.
Yeah.
Here's my two Polaroids that I have at the at the Hot Dog Hall of Fame.
The stuff in the windows is genuinely cool.
I think.
Which things in the windows?
I mean, OK, there's the trophies.
But then what else are you referring to?
There's like I mean, I feel like it's a combination of sports memorabilia and vaguely hot dog related things.
But my guess is I don't I don't know.
I mean, how long has it been there?
OK, I have some materials from the opening.
Do the videos say that?
I mean, it's like it's last 10 years, I want to say, or maybe last like 12.
So like fairly recent part of maybe like the second wave of stuff at this city walk.
I have some materials from the opening ceremony, but I'll say that.
Yes, if I didn't if I didn't cover that, what kind of did they get any like hot dog celebs at the?
No, no, no, no, no, no celebs.
Nobody known for hot dog.
No, there was not really a star studded affair other than the founder of the restaurant.
But again, I'm going to deal with that separately.
But it's you know, maybe they don't want to distract from the hot dogs, the hot dogs of the stars.
Sure.
It is also funny that they didn't like like make a baseball restaurant.
That's what it seems like it kind of wants to be.
Right.
When it was playing, they were playing a hockey game on the TV.
It's not called like sports dogs or something.
No, which they could have gotten away with.
Yeah, I kind of wish that they had leaned more.
I mean, I like the sports angle is great.
I like the bleachers, but it's a little yeah, I feel like hot dog Hall of Fame.
Maybe I guess sports has Hall of Fame.
I was expecting more of like Hollywood hot dogs, which would make more sense at Universal anyways.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, it's kind of splitting the difference between hot dogs are associated with baseball and here's hot dogs from around the country.
But it's still not.
Yeah, you would want like like like an imprint of a hot dog in cement outside like famous hot dogs.
Oh my God.
That have put an idea immortalized.
Yes, from different movie hot dogs.
Movie hot dogs.
That would be really special.
Different types brought.
Yeah, whatever.
I guess brought worsts you can even do.
Would you be able to tell the difference like a regular wiener and then a and then a broad was like something with more of a curve and then a foot long.
Are you talking about and I feel like in your version of it, correct me if I'm wrong, it's not even buns.
It is purely the wiener.
It is probably the wiener.
Yes, I'm trying to think.
Yeah, I'm not against the bun also being part of the cement.
Yeah, if it's a crucial piece of that particular hot dog.
Yeah, but I do like the idea of just the meat.
Yeah, it's it's spot on.
So I'm just saying, yeah, that's if you're really if the concept is really being like fulfilled, I think it's more like that.
And then yeah, cases and like different buns, buns throughout the years, how they've changed.
You know, you're really.
Types of buns, high toast.
They're steamed.
There's so many ways.
Wow.
I would I love this restaurant you're describing earlier in the series.
We made the sector keeper.
Somebody made Jason say a full list of ways to prepare hot dogs.
Wasn't that?
Yes.
Yes, that was again.
It's a fog, but you made it to 10.
I think you've and also I think it bears mentioning Jamie.
I don't know if you know, but I feel like the association with I think our show has an association with hot dogs to some extent.
But Jason, especially, I feel like maybe since the original city walk saga, there's really a lot of talk cemented about my home preparation of hot dog.
Yes.
I just really listen to this because I was curious.
I was I wanted to relive the mythology.
One is that I don't think you said this in your list of hot dog preparations, but one that really stuck with us was Jason in a hurry needs somewhere to go.
I would forget to eat.
So he takes just the just the wiener, puts it in a napkin, puts it in the microwave for a minute and steams that.
And then takes it in the car with him to go.
Wow.
I've done something similar.
Not quite.
But yeah, you need you need to wrap it in a wet paper towel.
So that's true.
Say that part of it.
What was your similar iteration there?
I mean, I've Mike, I have microwave hot dogs made microwave or boil.
I feel like you get similar results.
But the wet paper towel is crucial.
Yeah.
Because then it like is basically food.
If you do it, it's basically food.
And it's it's less likely to kind of like explode in the way that makes a mess.
Are you doing any condiments in that iteration?
Oh, yeah.
No, I got to get some mustard.
They're eating the mustard relish.
But how do you feel like?
No, I don't like to eat and drive.
I feel like I just eat it really quick.
Well, I can't drive.
I live with a vegetarian now, so I had already been eating less meat for the sake of my health.
So I feel like I've scaled back on my hot dog consumption.
This was this was a five years ago thing.
You're a different man.
You're a different.
I was a different.
It was that is very much a single man's diet.
No offense, Jamie.
No, that's fine.
It's true.
When was the last time everyone here bought a package of hot dogs?
Two weeks ago.
Two weeks, Jason.
I think it's been a while.
What do you think?
More than six months?
I think a few months.
I don't think since I moved.
OK.
Yeah, I think it's been a few months.
I bought, you know, sausages, like the like Kielbasa sausage.
Because then I can chop that up, freeze some of it, cook some of it, you know.
OK.
I feel like maybe the Fourth of July last year.
Maybe.
That's a respectable answer.
I bought a hot dog for a bachelor party eight years ago.
Whoa, really?
Yeah, I know.
I'm outnumbered.
It's not a good day to be, Scott.
But that's all direct traffic to Jason.
The other thing I, you know, actually, I feel like listeners in I'd forgotten this specific
quote and we re-released the original City Walk Saga on Club 3 on our highest Patreon
channel.
forgot, which is this phrase.
Hot dog buns are the lowest form of bread.
Well, yeah.
So I knew this would come up.
I'm thinking if you're like buying it at Rausser Kroger's and you're buying like a
one dollar pack of hot dog buns.
Yeah.
If it's like a real
You can get a bunch for one dollar.
Occasionally.
It's probably going up now.
Even in Biden's America?
I don't know what Biden
It might be 139 in Biden's America.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, that kind of bread is
I feel like there's not a good way to prepare it.
It kind of just turns a glue in your mouth a little bit.
It gums really quickly.
They usually have better buns, split top buns in some of the parts of New England where you're
from.
I love a split top bun.
Yeah.
Wait, describe a split top bun.
It's a little taller.
It's a little breadier.
Yeah, you get to nestle your hot dog in there.
It's more of, yeah, like a little bean bag chair.
It almost falls inside, right?
Is that right?
It's a little cute.
I've weirdly watched a kitchen staff preparation training video for Skyline, the Cincinnati
chain.
spaghetti stuff.
And I remember part of it was making a little boat, like you're trying to make.
Oh, yeah.
Which that sounds like what the, so you need the height to be able to make a hot dog.
That's cute.
Lobster rolls, you see split top.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Right, we're right.
What do you make, though, do you, Jamie, agree with Jason's assessment about lowest form
of bread?
I think it's a little harsh, I'll be honest.
It's a little harsh, but I was talking about, like, home preparation.
Yeah.
Because, like, then if you're cooking for one and you end up with a pack and everyone's
like, oh, yeah, there's more hot dogs or more buns than hot dogs.
And you're like, what do I do with the rest of these?
You know?
I don't like when, yeah, when a bun is overly, like, chewy.
I don't know.
I've gone both ways in this because, like, cost factor is always something that hot dog
consumers are keeping in mind.
But I feel like if you're making a home hot dog, you can't have a bad hot dog and a bad
bun.
But if you have a kind of bad hot dog or a kind of bad bun, you can still have a decent
meal.
Like, if you had a spectacular, like, Hebrew national nestled in a kind of shitty bun,
I feel like the Hebrew national will win the day, even if the bun isn't great and vice
versa.
If you got a nice bun, it's crispy, it's great, but the hot dog inside is, like, mid.
Huh.
You'll be all right.
It's just one of those components.
What about if both are mid, but condiments, can condiments rescue an all mid?
Ooh.
Jason, what do you think?
I think kind of no.
Yeah, I think kind of no, too.
Unless it's, like, really flavorful, like, red relish or stewed onions.
Yeah, like a real special occasion condiment.
A real special?
Yeah, but then in what scenario do you have bad hot dog ingredients but really good stewed
onions?
Yeah, so that's so much work.
You have a bizarre shopping regimen.
But, like, again, I think if you're going to, like, a hot dog place and they're, like,
really proud of, like, their condiments, that might elevate it.
I feel like I've had multiple hot dog sellers be very enthusiastic about
There was a guy my senior year, my last semester at Ithaca, and he set up grills in, like, the
Commons, like, the downtown pedestrian mall, and he would be making red hots and white
hot dogs.
I mean, well, yeah, that's a great area.
That's a great hot dog area.
Yeah, it's a great hot dog area.
And he was so enthusiastic.
He's like, oh, I get these.
I got a butcher who makes these.
It's really great company.
And then once I was at Zuma Beach and there was a hot dog guy, and he's very enthusiastic.
He's like, hey, do you want some?
I have this red relish.
I get this flunid from these goats.
And he was so excited about it in the same way.
And it's just infectious.
But like, I don't have this stuff at home.
Like, like, Ralph's is not super, you know, they don't have this type of red relish.
Not fun.
Yeah, it's infectious.
You're describing an interaction from a long time ago, and this is the most energy to
interaction.
They're all for these are old stories for you, but you are.
You're the most beaming of senior.
I they they just it was so endearing both times.
It was so charming and so endearing.
Wow.
I think it's even more fun when like I there's this place Hye talk about in the book, but
like there's a place in Connecticut where like they had a house relish.
Everyone there was losing it over this house relish.
It did taste good, but it was like gray.
It was like the color gray.
It looked scary and like the whole vibe of the building was like scary.
It was like a place that had burned down a bunch of times.
It was like a hundred years old.
There was a sign inside that said no dancing.
What year was that important to put up?
And their house relish was gray.
And how it but like everyone was like, this is like the best thing that ever happened
to Cheshire, Connecticut.
This is our legacy.
This is and it's like it was gray.
And that said to any Cheshire heads listening, it was good, but it also was gray and the
building was menacing.
And it's really nice to see someone get like extremely hyped for something.
You're like, well, I don't get it, but I'm glad that the gray relish means a lot.
I'm sure you get into this in the book and I need to read the book and listeners need
to read the book.
I don't know.
As we in this within this conversation, I certainly want to I want to keep it going
at home myself.
But the your personal hot dog journey, where does it tip into full on fascination?
Where does the love come from?
I mean, it was just like my my dad.
It was like divorce meals.
Like that was like I associated hot dogs with like hanging out with my dad because they
were the things that he knew how to make.
And we like boiled them, which I can't believe that we boiled them.
I have a lot of nostalgia for a boiled hot dog.
But I just like I think the rationalization down the line because I was like, dad, like
why did you boil them?
He's like, we were poor.
I was like, we had a grill like we like, what are you talking about?
You sound so stupid.
We had a pan.
We could have pan fried them.
We had all the tools.
You don't need like a rig to make a decent hot dog.
But he was like, no, it's just it was an income issue.
It's like it wasn't.
It was lack of interest and lack of dedication.
So he anyway, so that was how I got in.
And then also just like, I don't know, like I got really into the 7-Eleven hot dog for
a while.
That was like a real point of fascination.
7-Eleven hot dog and sushi in college.
The sushi is going strong at 7-Eleven.
I saw some this morning.
Wow.
Have you had it at this?
This isn't a regional thing.
You've had it out here.
Yeah.
They've got it.
They've got no, but it's never like made me sick, which is honestly what I expected
to happen.
But it's like all like, it's just, you know, like old rice and imitation crab.
Yeah.
But you know, it did the trick.
My, when I like was in college and then when I first moved here and was broke, but was
like, but I want to feel expensive.
I want to have sushi.
It was great.
And then the hot dogs at 7-Eleven are genuinely, I mean, it depends.
They can get pretty old, but.
Uh-huh.
But pretty good if it's like a fresh one.
If it's a fresh one, I think genuinely good.
I don't know where they, if the, where they source the meat from is consistent, like
across the board.
Uh, but the last time I haven't had one in a while because it was my regular 7-Eleven.
I was like, picking it up with the tongs and the guy working there was like, you definitely
don't want that.
Oh, man.
Cause he was like basically caught, I think it was cause I was a regular and he, but he
was like, that's been there for 12 hours.
Like it had been there for so long.
I'm glad it wasn't longer.
I mean, that's long, but I wonder if they can cross.
I mean, I don't think that honestly, like a two day old 7-Eleven hot dog has been left
out at 7-Eleven for two days.
I think it's like not meaningfully different from how it started.
Um, yeah, I guess.
It's just kind of been out for a long time.
Would the person at 7-Eleven, cause you come in so often, if it was just a stranger, would
it like, he would just been like ringing them up.
No problem.
I don't know.
I guess I'm, I want to believe that.
I want to believe that my local 7-Eleven feels some loyalty to me and my health, but I'm
not totally sure.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Um, uh, it's a localize it for a second.
What's the hot dog destination in Los Angeles for you at this point?
Or are you, uh, a little, have you, has the hot dog consumption gone down post book or,
uh, it's gone down, but it's still pretty consistent.
I, I, it's a bar cause there were like a lot of places I like in LA that I didn't, that
didn't make it into the book, but the places I like around here are Walt's, uh, Eagle Rock.
That's a rare recent hot dog I've had.
Yeah.
Really good.
So good.
And they have a great vegetarian hot dog, which is like almost impossible to find anywhere.
So big Walt's proponent, uh, which has like, uh, if you're not from around here or haven't
been here and I like also like pinball games, cool patty recommended.
It's really cool.
Yeah.
And, and so I like, I like going to Walt's, uh, I like for chili dogs, I feel like Tommy's
is genuinely like very, very good.
And there's a couple of those around here and then they reopened.
I'm wearing the pin right now because I feel such loyalty to them.
Uh, they reopened a classic hot dog stand in West Hollywood on Santa Monica called tail
of the pup.
Oh yeah.
Oh, the one that was the hot dog.
It's like a hot dog.
Is that back?
Yeah.
they had, I knew about the hot dog stick because it was this hot dog stand that used to be
somewhere else.
It's shaped like a hot dog.
It was originally just the stand.
There's a really famous picture of Sigourney Weaver eating a hot dog in front of it.
Whoa.
Um, and it's like a really hot picture.
It's kind of nuts.
Uh, it's, she's going for it.
Um, but that, like that stand was in storage for years and I got put in contact with the
guy who owned the storage unit and I was like, what are you guys going to do with it?
And he was like, we're going to reopen.
So now it's like the stand is out front.
You order in the stand, but then there's like a full kitchen and stuff.
Oh, so that there's still the, all right.
There's not the pressure to keep it all in the little box, but you get the fun, you get
what you want.
There's one with a really mini stand, but, and then just full food court kitchen, uh,
in Topanga social, which is, uh, in Woodland Hills.
They fancified the mall I used to go to as a kid with, it has like outposts of like cool
local chains and there is a, there's a tale of the pup there.
Tale of the pup at the start of the movie LA story.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's carried by a helicopter.
It's like a nod to a Fellini movie, but instead of like the Virgin Mary statue being carried,
it's the hot dog, uh, stand.
It's a really special moment.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
It's a very comforting shot.
Wow.
Um, okay.
So we'll take, to get it back to Florida, uh, to where, where the, where the ultimate
game of hot dog is played.
Um, I mean, where did we get first?
I mean, I just, again, that this environment is great.
The like theme parkiness of it, the, the, the, like the, the prop design and just, I,
the placement, I don't know.
I just like it spatially a lot.
And then you order from, you order from the bases basically.
Yeah.
Uh, I forget if, I forget if that lines up where then like home plate is now you're up.
I don't quite recall.
Um, but that's really charming.
The only thing I would take away, and maybe you could speak to this from Valentine's Day
or, or maybe it was not at all crowded on Valentine's Day at night.
You order from the outfield.
Oh, it's the opposite way.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So it's like that.
Oh, totally.
Okay.
Or second base, I guess.
You begin your line experience at home plate.
Yes, exactly.
Um, the only thing I would say, like, um, I really liked being here and getting to just
walk through the empty turnstiles.
I also saw this during the summer one time where the entire thing was full and I had
friends in the line who were not happy.
This seems like, as with probably a lot of things in this Orlando city walk, we had a
great time due to emptiness.
This thing's full and you're hot dog all-fame experience is an hour and a half.
That I don't know.
But was that the case when you were there?
I was, it was not for whatever.
I think it was just cause it was like February and it just like was not a super busy weekend.
And I went towards the end of the night, I want to say.
So I feel like more people were there for the coconut club than were there for the hot
dog all-fame.
But yeah, I mean, I feel like that is any time.
That's why, that's part of why I think pinks, I mean, well, I think pink sucks for a lot
of reasons, but the fact that it's like you, you're standing in a line and at the end,
it's like a pretty humble, like a pretty, a pretty small meal.
Like you should be able to get a hot dog quickly.
That should be the, that's part of the point.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
It's no fault of the people who were, I mean, they're, and I feel like you do get, if you're
into hot dogs, you get a lot of cool stuff.
I was very impressed by the mustard cart.
Yes, yes.
They're like, they have, they, they know what they're doing.
And there's so many different, I just, I don't know if we're talking about the menu yet.
I found the menu thrilling.
I love it.
You're basically, it's like, it is like an all-star game where regional hot dogs have
come to play and you have your choice of great hot dogs from around our great nation.
I feel like, I don't know, I have some from a list, but please, Jamie, whatever, what
you ordered or what call that to you.
Yeah, it's the starting lineup, right?
Yeah.
There's, I generally at hot dog places, especially regionally, but like generally in hot dog
places, you'll only have one provider.
So like at this hot dog place, it's all Nathan's or it's all Vienna beef.
It's all kind.
This has like regionally appropriate meat vendors.
It's so cool.
Like, yeah, we've got.
That's kind of nuts.
You could see them like, and maybe I, hopefully they haven't just like, it's not just like
in the menu only and then for real they'd, but I don't think so.
I think you can like, we've all had different types of hot dogs there.
You feel it would be, there would be lawsuits.
There would be.
This is in the Simpsons, like, you know, pleasure where they're just, there's a grave
that they're spearing stuff out of.
And it's like, this is going to this restaurant.
This would be a scandal pretty quickly.
Yeah.
No, but it's like, just in scanning the menu, there's at least four or five regions.
That's incredible.
And for the most part, and I guess I can't speak to, I haven't eaten a hot dog in all
of these cities, but for the, I mean, Chicago being Vienna beef makes total sense.
Nathan's and Sabret in New York makes total sense.
Kaim in Boston, the Boston one's so good.
Kaim all beef hot dog, toasted New England style bun, spicy brown mustard, diced onions
and relish.
Incredible.
That sounds really good.
I didn't get it.
But now if I, if I was going back, maybe that'd be, that's what I would.
And you, like in working on the book, did you know, are all these names called out to
you?
You know Kaim, you know Sabret.
Yeah.
Wow.
And I have rankings and preferences.
Yes.
But for the most part, I mean, I think the only ones that I cannot speak to are the,
like the Kansas city and that might be it.
And also the, having the Milwaukee bratwurst that I thought was like a really cool touch.
That's what I got.
I kind of, cause again, I don't have the, my, I don't love just regular hot dogs.
I was like, what's something different I could do so that it is, yeah, it's bratwurst, hoagie
roll, grilled onions, spicy brown mustard.
And then, but not so much of that, that I didn't, wasn't able to then sample each and
every mustard from the mustard lineup.
I love the mustard.
Yeah.
I, I, when I went the second time I got the Boston dog, I wish I'd gotten the Arizona
dog just cause it's one of my favorites.
All beef, smoked bacon, pinto beans, grilled onions, peppers and cheese.
Always great.
That's unique.
The beans, interesting.
I will say that they do have vegan dogs, but like with considerably fewer options.
I feel like you should be able, I wonder if you could just be like, can I have a vegan
version of the like Colorado dog if they would just do that for you?
But there's like pretty limited vegan, which I know is a challenge for the hot dog community.
When I went the first time though, I, they had a special that I got, the shrimp po'boy
dog.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
I can't even pronounce everything on this.
Smoked andouille?
Andouille, yeah.
Andouille?
Okay.
Smoked andouille, fried shrimp, lemon aioli, Louisiana hot sosh on a hoagie roll.
And it was pretty good.
I'd never had anything like it.
And then of course I went nuts at the mustard cart.
I like that they cycle in and out like other regions that aren't on the permanent menu.
Do they change them?
Like, yeah.
Or are you looking at one, like if I went through mine, are they going to be what's
on yours?
Because you were there years before.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I can.
Is it a curate?
Yeah.
Is it a curated?
Oh yeah.
There it is.
Yeah.
I went through, I did rankings of all of them.
And by the way, this is one of the joys of that we're going without theme park pressure
to just do everything at CityWalk, that I had time to just leisurely try every mustard
in a place with a lot of nice mustards.
Yeah.
Because this is a component I do.
I do like, you know, I do like spicy mustards and brown mustards and mustards with the seed
and it let you kind of do everything.
I'm going to do a quick ranking and then tell me if any of these weren't on your.
I did one, I set out to do one to 10, but I didn't even go below five because I thought
a lot of these were fantastic.
This, okay.
I'm going to get the last name wrong, I'm sure.
But it's like boat, boat, boat, jeez.
Like Dutch mustard or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a guy, a guy's recipe from 1889 that he made in his garage.
Fred.
Yes, yes.
Stone ground Dutch mustard in his garage in Rock, Illinois.
This was my lowest at six, but I still kind of find food and wine, spicy jalapeno, nine.
I loved a spicy kick on that one.
House bar height, smoky garlic.
Be warned, this mustard is not for part-time garlic lovers.
It shouts summer, baseball and picnic.
Shouts these things.
I love copywriting so much.
Somebody did copywriting for this?
I don't think there is more than one hot dog hall of fame today.
I think there have been in the past.
That means that we are getting this, however, you don't want to see signs changed out at
giant chains at Burger King or whatever.
This one restaurant took the time to write all this stuff and do mustard pairings.
It's beautiful.
Wonderful.
Committed to.
They're keeping up with the promise of the name.
I gave this one a seven.
Silver Spring Beer and Brat, I gave an eight.
And Burtman Original Ballpark, I couldn't find, so it was not ranked.
We went back to this place with the level keeper and he was trying to do the same thing,
try them all and I think he found some ketchups and many more missing.
I don't think he found the full menu at all.
So in that ranking, Food and Wine Spicy Alpeno wins at nine.
If it's still there, when you go check it out, I was like, is this something I could
buy at home?
I could not find any Google results imprint for this.
It makes me wonder if they got the name wrong.
Food and Wine is not a brand.
If that was the section they bought it from.
I don't know, the winner, I can't have it home.
Well, help Scott find that mustard people.
That is the thing I think I would, you were talking about Joey Chestnut's special mustard
that's expensive.
I don't do a lot of the special ordering.
It's a very shark tank that people pay 20 bucks for one bottle or something.
I think I might with spicy mustard.
That's the one thing maybe I'll splurge into.
You could become a mustard guy.
Sounds very cool.
This sounds like a great identity for me a dad.
That's a dad thing to do.
Kind of a mustard guy.
But I do like it.
Can I say this?
We did an episode a couple years ago at this point where we went around Disneyland and
tried all the hot dogs.
Effort here is just a hundred times more than Disney.
Because Disney they would put different toppings but all the hot dogs are the exact same hot
dog.
What is the Disneyland Hollywood themed hot dog place?
Award Wieners.
Excellent name, I was disappointed.
Jason's a defender I feel.
I really like the film strip fries.
I like those.
You're pro film strip fries?
I like the film strip fries.
I was let down by the hot dog.
I also went there shortly after I got vaccinated.
I was like alright hot dog book we've got to go to Disneyland stat.
I was looking forward to it because it looked like there was a pretty comprehensive menu
there.
But then when I went it was just corn dogs and hot dogs.
The menu was diminished.
Sometimes when the other corn dog places closed they'll bring the corn dogs over to award
wieners.
I've learned that I know that.
Yes.
They'll bring it over.
We've got to put them somewhere.
When corn dog castle is closed.
Yes it was closed when we went.
We ate at Grand Californian and we ordered their special hot dog of the month and it
was the same hot dog that was in every other spot in the park.
I got one really good hot dog at Disneyland before my hot dog era even.
But it was like a cocoa hot dog.
And it had street corn on it.
And it was long.
It had a toasted bun.
It was good.
That's interesting.
I already don't remember what won.
Was it the main street?
I think we won with the one at Casey's Corn.
Is that the one?
I think I voted for it because it was just smothered in fake cheese and neon relish.
And that's sport pepper.
It was that one.
It was a limited time.
The ingredients is what, the ingredients, or the toppings, excuse me, were what won
it.
Because the hot dog and the bun itself was not much different than any other ones we
had.
Well back to that original thing of can condiments elevate.
We were really leaning on that at Disneyland.
As opposed to, it feels like you could go really condiment minimal at the hot dog hall
fame and still have a great experience.
Which I think is, I haven't spent a lot of time in the park at Universal in years.
So I can't really speak to their current hot dog thing.
But as a seasoned pass holder here, I think that the hot dogs are not doing much inside
the park there.
No.
In fact, multiple ones have.
This is a recurring story on this saga.
Got me sick.
The in the park ones.
Yeah.
The one of the ones.
Pink's used to be in the park.
And now I think it's just a generic in that central plaza.
Do we still got Dodger dogs there?
I forget what happened to the Dodger.
I think the Dodger store is still there.
Yeah.
I don't think there's dogs anymore.
At City Walk.
Yeah.
I don't know if the dogs are there.
Did Pink get you sick?
Pink's got me sick.
How bad?
And Mel's like Mel's Diner.
I think they were both chilly dogs.
And looking back, I think like they were both probably the same dog.
I think it was bullshit.
Probably.
It was probably just like lying in bed, like getting up to.
Pukesick?
No, I'm not.
I was a pukey kid.
I'm not really a pukey adult.
You're not a pukey man.
Yeah.
I would get so nervous as a kid.
I would like throw up.
Because of the anxiety.
Because of anxiety.
So hot dogs don't put any of that blame on hot dogs.
Yeah, hot dogs weren't doing it.
Well, as a child, no.
But Universal Studios Hollywood, yeah, I don't know that food.
Because they have that.
I was excited about it.
They had like a hot dog stand in the Simpsons area.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Again, there's only like two types of hot dogs, and they're the same hot dog.
And the hot dog wasn't good.
Because hot dogs are something you might want to expect to have at a theme park, but they're
clearly not reliable at all.
But all you got to do is go right outside to this nice spacious setting, where they
actually do it with quality and with different.
Curated.
More types there than Disneyland has in the entire park.
I think that's the thing in theme parks.
It's the emphasis is on making a lot of them quickly, you know, to feed a lot of people.
But this philosophy is still in CityWalk in places.
At other places.
But the Hot Dog Hall of Fame, it's a little more effort put in.
I was so, I hope it stays that level of effort because I was sort of expecting because by
the time I went to Hot Dog Hall of Fame, I was excited because I knew what it looked
like.
But I was like, I feel like we're going to be in for another award wiener situation
because I was devastated by what the events took place at award wieners.
I also feel like this one is like if any listeners knew when we started, here's the things that
are at CityWalk.
It doesn't seem, from the name, you might expect this to be like a disaster point for
us.
Like, oh, and then we all went to the Hot Dog Hall of Fame and got sick.
But it seems like not to just cut to the chase too much.
I don't think anyone's had a bad experience here.
I think this is a reliable place to get elevated hot dogs, right?
I feel like we're all pretty positive.
I think so.
I would say the time I ate there, I was also alone.
Good for you.
An ally.
Yeah.
It was like 2017.
I was down with my dad and brother.
And it was a night where we're like all just like, parks are closed, everyone's different
levels of hungry.
We all just split up.
So I was just walking around CityWalk and I was like, what do I eat?
And I was like, oh, the Hot Dog Hall of Fame and got a Chicago dog, liked it.
You know, I had my customary before bed Sunday from Toothsome.
Customary.
Even though Toothsome started that year.
I meant customary ice cream.
Oh, Sunday in general.
I see.
Sunday.
Yeah.
To make something customary.
The first time.
On the first time.
No, not Toothsome in particular.
I was just like, and it, yeah, it was filling.
I think Chicago dogs are deceptive because a lot of it is the garden.
Well, I, so it tastes, it all tastes good.
You know, I don't know.
Portillo's wise.
You remember when we had Portillo's?
We've had Portillo's a couple times.
Do you find it deceptive then?
No, no, I like, or in terms of keeping you full, like the pickled, pickled stuff is like
you get the kick of salt, you know, but it's not the most filling, you know,
pickles and relish and that sort of thing.
You're saying that it looks like a large amount of food, but once you eat it,
it's pretty manageable.
It's manageable and it's not necessarily that you're going to be like packed full.
That sport pepper spice might fill you up a little.
Yeah, I feel, yeah, I guess the Chicago dog like markets itself as like two meals in one.
And you're like, well, no, it isn't.
It's a bit, if so, it's a piece of shit salad on top of a really good hot dog.
I like a bit.
I mean, I like Portillo's.
I'm look, I was raised in Chicago.
Portillo's.
Yeah.
Do you like the big pickle?
I like the big like pickle slice on the hot dog.
I like the big pick.
I prefer the big pickle to the sport pepper, but I also like, I just am not a sport pepper guy.
I don't know.
I come down pretty hard on the Chicago dog.
I got booed at my own book release event in Chicago.
They're there for you.
And you still manage.
That's great.
And the whole Q and A was just person after person being like, so what was it?
What was wrong with it?
Wow.
Deep dish pizza and Chicago hot dogs.
Are you probably like you were a wrestling heel in Chicago?
I mean, they did show up, but it was to confront.
I read your book.
Are you upset?
Are you upset about this though?
Very upset.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's going to be a seething tension.
What is the Chicago dog?
I have no dog in this fight.
It's Vienna beef, poppy.
It's basically the thing they have.
Poppy seed bun.
Like that neon relish?
Neon relish.
Neon relish raw.
Yeah.
But what's the, why do you come down hard on it?
Not to get our Chicago audience upset at you.
Well, no, I feel like my reasoning is going to make people even madder.
I think it's a fine hot dog.
I don't buy the whole two meals in one historical marketing.
And just that people are so adamant that it's the best hot dog when it's
demonstrably untrue if you go outside Dodger Stadium.
There's so many anyways.
Oh, sure.
Wait.
So then favorite general preparation for you.
What is your personal ranking number one?
Ooh, I love, I mean, on my top five list is like the carts outside any LA
sports stadium, never inside.
Is this, yeah, because I haven't done this in a long time, but boy, leaving a
concert, I do love the smell of those carts that are sitting there.
So good.
Is that generally, I haven't done it forever.
Is that a reliable area?
Those are pretty great.
Yeah.
And they take Venmo now.
It's great.
I got a great danger dog after going to WrestleMania last year.
And it was one of the most saddest, because I was like, I was so hungry,
but I'm like, don't get it in the stadium.
Wait, you'll feel, and it was incredible.
That's really good.
I really, I like a lot of Southwestern hot dogs.
There's the Arizona prep, which is on this menu is really, really good.
And I like something that I don't think, I guess it would technically be a New
Jersey hot dog.
Cause I think that, and like New York and Chicago, I think are too cocky
about their hot dog prep.
And like, it's actually Tucson and Jersey that's holding it down and in
Michigan as well.
But, but yeah, there's a, it's everyone's favorite hot dog places in New Jersey.
And it's called Rutz Hut.
And they have a hot dog called the Ripper, which is lightly deep fried.
Oh, wow.
They deep fry it for like five to 10 seconds.
You can get different levels of deep fry.
There's whole lore attached to it, but it gives like the perfect, like little,
not, not crunch, but just like the perfect snap.
Yeah.
As you're, as you're riding into it.
And, and it's just like kind of a shithole on the side of the highway, but
like has the best hot dogs in the world.
I think that's the one, did Anthony Bourdain talk about Rutz Hut?
Yeah.
It's, and it really is like hanging over the highway.
It could, the location would not be weirder.
There's a lot of wonderful food in New Jersey that have been there
for like 50 to 80 years.
It looks like a death trap, but it might be one of the best things you've ever eaten.
Yeah.
It's like does, again, we were traveling like shortly out of lockdown.
So, but like it did feel like, oh, this is where you would go if you just killed
somebody and then you would come to Rutz Hut and get two hot dogs.
Wow.
It is like a crooked building.
It's strange looking.
I don't know if you addressed the, have you talked about this before?
Have you ever had at Disney a Ronto wrap?
Yes.
Yeah.
We're all big fans of that.
I was, I was expecting to be a hater of the Ronto wrap, but I was pleasantly
surprised.
Okay.
A good serving size.
Good serving size.
That fills you for sure.
Yeah.
I forget what the lore is, but I appreciated that they get, they attributed somewhere.
There's like attributed lore to the Ronto wrap.
Yeah.
The Ronto is a character you can see in the movies and you're eating it.
So it's being cooked by a pod racer.
And being cooked on the engine of the pod racer.
So that is all.
The most successful part of Galaxy's Edge.
It very well could be.
I had one a week ago.
I want to return to the Ronto.
The Ronto wrap might've been, I mean, I tried to like stay out of the corn dog zone
because I feel like it's almost a whole different discussion, but like the corn dogs
are great.
But the Ronto wrap, I think took it for, for Disney.
Above the corn dog.
We left it out of the hot dog competition as we end corn dogs, because it felt like
if we put those in, one of those is going to win.
I like that the hot dog hall of fame also seems to subscribe to this.
They're like, we're not fucking with corn dogs.
That's the same thing.
Yeah, different thing.
Different thing.
This might be a good time to, Jimmy, you've referred to like whoever put this together.
You know, you did well for this reason, that reason.
And I'm, it could, to me, it could not be a better answer of who put it together because
it is, it is one guy and it's a guy who we talked about recently and who's come up on
the show here and there because this is, he's becoming a legend to me quickly.
Steven Schussler.
Steven Schussler is the inventor of the Rainforest Cafe.
Whoa.
He personally developed that concept.
And as we've discussed recently, in order to prove it, created a demo Rainforest Cafe,
not just in some industrial space, in his suburban home.
He turned his house next to other houses with neighbors into a fully functioning rainforest.
His house was so humid to prove the point of, that a rainforest inside a building would
be a good idea.
That rocks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is a guy, this is a, this is a practice what he preaches, like a big swings guy.
I've learned a little, I've, sometimes we do an episode and I do the prep for it and
then I never think about it again.
Steve Schussler has stuck with me, especially given that we're going to talk about him a
little more with this.
I've watched some like motivational speeches that he's done.
What order do I go in?
There's so much here.
Also, okay, so T-Rex Cafe is also him, if you're a T-Rex Cafe.
This all makes sense.
It all feels like a part of the same.
Great whimsical, weird premises, concepts.
You don't need the premise to enjoy the place, but it sure makes it fun.
Impossible to uninstall kind of.
Oh yeah, you can't flip them easily.
You can't like do the 2020s blandify of these places.
I went to the, what's the huge, I was reading a story about malls and I went to this huge
mall in Phoenix where there's a huge.
The Scottsdale one, there's a massive one.
Yeah, yeah, kind of right on the border.
Yeah, yeah.
There was a gigantic rainforest cafe inside and it was quiet.
And I went, I was talking to the waiter who was very candid and I was just like, I'm
like, surprise, this is still open.
He's like, yeah, honestly, like it would be more expensive to uninstall it and to
just like leave it here unsuccessfully.
I was like, wow.
That's so cool.
I love that.
I read the story you're talking about and I love that malls now are stuff like that.
And then a lot of stores that sell.
Heath Ledger Joker.
Yes, it was.
I couldn't tell how much of that was just like being in Arizona, but it was all like,
yeah, gigantic theme restaurants and then like think like stores that look like they
could be like cleaned out within 20 minutes.
That was all like cosplay gear and like, yeah, Joker Joker is Naruto in one piece.
And yeah, and and probably some Scarface and then maybe hopefully fingers crossed
something where all of the Jokers are meeting.
I think there's some there's some playing poker poker.
Yeah, I think maybe there's one where they're all in a car like taking a joy ride.
Oh, yeah, I've seen that one.
It reminds me of the image of Paul Walker driving Brian the dog to heaven.
That's what the.
It's like the same angel of the car should be a standard mall shirt as well.
I think about that.
Oh, yeah, because Brian the dog died at some point.
Unlike Paul Walker, he came back and he came back.
Yeah, he did come back.
But you have so Schussler.
There's so much extra Schussler lore, including even just about the rainforest cafe
thing, which we're talking about.
But I watched this long, like motivational speech that he gave
where he talked about the the making of it was so hard.
I posted this on our on our Twitter and it's worth playing on the show.
This is like this is an ad for the event that you can buy where he'll come
and motivate your company with his speech called 800 Pound Gorilla.
Hundred Pound Gorilla package includes five thousand books, an inspirational
speech, customized podcast on creativity, innovation,
the five P's and the eleven commandments.
A one day personalized consultation where I actually go to your office
and speak with your employees and your staff to our ideation and lunch.
I didn't have before me at one of my restaurants and autographed party
and you support a smile.
The value of this investment is priceless.
This is the ultimate 800 Pound Gorilla package.
Did he say autograph party?
Autograph.
Yeah, he's got five thousand books to sell.
It's a party when you're signing.
This is promoting his book called It's a Jungle in there.
Inspiring lessons, hard won insights and other acts of entrepreneurial daring,
which has endorsements by both Lee Iacocca and at the time it was written
President Elect Donald Trump.
Wow.
And he mentioned the five P's personality, product,
persistence, people and philanthropy.
But the book also preaches the value of passion and caring for like, wait,
you said five P's and then immediately added a sixth P.
But that is not one of the five P's.
No, not canonically a P.
I mean, it's a P alphabetically,
but it's not officially one of his.
This guy thinks outside the box, you know.
Is it is it like self published?
Does it look like I don't think he could publish it like I love.
I love an entrepreneurial self published book.
Oh, yeah.
I've never thought about this dimension because that implies that nobody's asking.
It's like part of building their own mythology to just do it yourself.
My favorite.
I have one.
Oh, my God.
To mind immediately.
It is the guy who has since passed the creator of one Pollo,
the chicken restaurant.
It's just like a rotisserie chicken chain.
And I for some reason, he like bought the original McDonald's on Route 66.
He really was into McDonald's history.
He wanted to preserve it.
So they're at that like location.
It's a weird mix of like McDonald's stuff and then this guy's stuff,
including his book, which I bought called Albert Okura,
the chicken man with a 50 year plan.
And it's got an incredible cover.
Wow.
Guy with sunglasses and then just like a regular shirt,
like a shirt from the from the restaurant in front of 20 rotisserie chickens on fire.
Sorry.
Can I stare at that again for a second?
Oh, my.
Oh, my God.
It was I was just confused by the pattern.
I didn't even know what I was looking at.
Whoa.
He's in front of a wall of chickens.
Geez, we got a lot to post.
Sigourney Weaver, this Ruts Hut.
Oh, my God.
Have you have you read it?
Have you looked through it or just aware of it?
I've skimmed I've skimmed the chicken man with a 50 year plan.
And it seems like, you know, I don't know.
I mean, he executed it.
He was like, I will have a successful restaurant chain in 50 years.
And it's just kind of like a reasonable ish goal.
Yeah.
So it's an easygoing.
That's yeah.
Yeah.
You still got time to have fun.
He did it.
See friends plan achieved for him.
But I think they share some kind of common DNA.
I think so.
Well, in their in their graphic design, I think this this guy makes
so many crazy claims about the founding of Rainforest Cafe.
He says that his neighbors
demanded that he get a psychiatric evaluation
due after that, but once there were the sheer volume of like that,
everything's vines and jungle and like a monkey.
He has monkeys in the house now and that a psychologist called him
and like, your neighbors have paid for me to do this.
And it's somehow I forget he waved him.
He waved it off somehow.
Then he he all the money from Rainforest Cafe.
We addressed this was it was put up by one of the most successful poker
players of all time named Lyle Berman.
And he claims in his speech that his father went under velvet
ropes at a poker at the World Series of Poker.
When this guy went up to go to the bathroom, his
this guy's father went and sat in the guy's chair
so that when he came back, a stranger was there.
And he's like, what are you doing?
Don't you see the security?
You're crazy.
You have to leave right now.
And he said, no, first, you need to hear about my son's rainforest restaurant.
I don't know if I believe this, because how is how are you
walking up to the rain for it?
And then it goes on.
And he says how this poker player, he had to get to the rainforest
house 28 times or something.
And that the final piece of it to get him to sign up to sign off
and do it was that he said, listen, Lyle, here's what I'm going to do.
I'm getting a big sandwich board that I'm going to wear in the sea.
And it's going to say Lyle made me do it.
And then I'm going to jump off a bridge.
That's what I'm going to do.
If you don't give me the money for the rainforest cafe.
And he said, here's three million dollars.
I believe that.
I believe that this man said, I will kill myself
unless you give me the money for rainforest cafe.
I do believe that.
That makes sense to me.
The first story that adds up.
Just the tone of his speech in that sales pitch he makes.
So you order this guy to your company and he'll tell you that story.
Right.
And that's priceless.
I can't tell you he brings five thousand books.
Do you regardless of how many people are there?
I'm bringing five thousand books.
This is an autograph party.
I ordered a million.
Does that mean if you have the 800 pound gorilla package,
have you purchased the books or did he just the part of the package?
Did he just bring them?
It's the presence of the books and the possibility to get them.
But then the book is extra and the autograph is extra.
He provides the autograph party, but the autograph itself
you have to customize an atom.
It makes sense.
I'm not sure.
He just drive a U-haul up to the party with all the books.
A lot of books.
Yeah.
Five thousand books.
It does sound like I mean, this guy seems like a nice guy.
He seems like a benign version of this kind of very rich.
Yeah, I think so.
The guys that we've talked about yet.
The five thousand books does sound like the conservative publishing racket.
Yeah.
A best selling book.
And they just buy it for all these insane conferences.
He may have bought a million books to send it up the charts.
And now he has to get rid of them.
It's got a really hopeful.
I love reading about like scams like that, because then you're like,
what the fuck is this?
You're like, oh, it's a liar.
Like, it's just like it's a liar lying about the rainforest cafe.
Yeah.
It's really it's no way that it became this brand that has major placement
in every major city that did at one point, and then it came out of a guy going,
I'm going to kill myself.
I got a jungle house.
The psychiatrist calls me on the phone.
If that bridge is high enough, first off, the mechanics of a sandwich board.
I feel like that sandwich board is flying off.
Like they might not.
It might just be a blur for photographers.
What's the sign that that is 20 feet from the body?
I don't know.
And I can't read the text anymore.
Throw it in the garbage truck.
God, my day is so much harder than normal.
I was earlier here before we started recording, saying sometimes you maybe
you don't want to like dig in and interview certain people.
But maybe we want to interview this guy.
Yeah.
Well, if we I think the price of you think you'll charge us.
Five thousand books.
You think you would charge us?
But we're promoting him.
We are outlets.
How much is it for you to be on the show?
Five thousand bucks?
No, five thousand books.
I need you to take I know there's three of you
and only a couple of heads of your network.
But I'm bringing one thousand seven hundred books off my hands
and then I will do your podcast.
The fact that there is no music in that ad was making my head hurt.
You could hear him taking ragged breaths as it continued.
I just put the music under it.
That's like the Chris Farley El Nino sketch.
Or he's just like yelling.
It was a red.
It was his final sketch.
Yeah.
That shows you the wrestling promo.
So anyway, he also now we know what his speeches are like and what they promise.
And he gave an opening day speech at the opening of his newest concept.
Hot dog Hall of Fame.
How amazing is it to now know this is who did it?
So here this this might be this might be a full minute or so,
but I think it's worth it.
How many here love hot dogs?
Yeah, almost everyone here.
Almost is an American food, obviously.
Where the fuck is something that we have a great deal of pride in.
We've been experimenting with hot dogs for the last seven years,
seven years going all over the world to eating some of the best hot dogs.
I promise you that hot dog Hall of Fame here at Universal Studios
will be the best hot dog experience you've ever had.
We're going to serve five different beers, nine different hot dogs,
12 different kinds of mustard.
We're going to have one of the most exclusive mustard bars you've ever seen.
The things that we're going to be known for is some of the little stuff.
For instance, our two foot hot dogs.
I can imagine a two foot hot dog.
That big.
Two people can pull it from both sides.
We have special hot dog hats.
We have all kinds of things for the family and for children and
paint your own wiener.
Oh, bring that back.
Yeah.
It's your home of paint your own wiener.
You can buy these hot dogs inside and they get they get painted.
They get collected.
They get saved.
And I am the commissioner of hot dog Hall of Fame.
The commissioner.
Wow.
This predates a certain Mr.
Susser.
Wow.
Maybe this guy's got a lawsuit on it.
I think so.
Yeah.
There is like a surprising amount of crossover between like
hot dog, like celebrities and like professional wrestling cadences.
Yeah.
This does feel like like he's kind of issuing a threat to no one.
It's confrontational.
But to what today to like any other restaurant that doesn't do any of this
to somebody wouldn't want to come in.
I feel challenged by that.
I think this has to be like the attitude you have to like
convince someone to give you millions of dollars.
Yeah.
There's no way you're like, excuse me, could I have three million dollars?
I have a rainforest idea for like that's not happening.
You have to come in aggressively.
And that makes either people scared, annoyed
or just like convinced, you know, you're doing.
Or we'll give you three million dollars to stop talking to them.
That's also true, too.
I've got poker games to play.
Yeah.
Stop badgering me.
And maybe it'll work.
God, I feel OK.
That speech was great.
Yeah.
It did feel like he was yelling at them.
I OK.
He said he went he traveled worldwide for what he has already admitted
is a very domestic event.
Yeah.
But he has traveled worldwide.
And there's less mustards now.
There were 12 mustards at inception.
That's heartbreaking.
Five mustards.
I've never seen the collectible wieners either.
Or even hot dog hats.
I was like, I surely would have gotten a hat if they had one.
Well, they've also betrayed his original vision in another way, which is so,
you know, they've got the big screen.
You can watch games there.
Just this morning, texting a friend of the show, Kevin Tully.
He said he went and just sat in the grandstands.
He didn't even get a hot dog.
Watched an entire baseball game there and said it was wonderful.
Very pleasant time.
So that's good.
They created this great environment to watch baseball games.
But that's not what Steve wanted.
He goes on in this interview to say he wanted the big screen at all times
to be playing videos of people eating hot dogs.
Oh, that's great.
Are you going to find a long enough loop of that?
You're going to make it.
I guess so.
It's going to be custom done from the ground up.
Hire a famous director to travel the country for months.
Or a collection like they should have made like the.
Oh, every director makes their own little.
Yes.
Like there was that run of like New York, I love you.
Paris, they should make an anthology of just like hot dog shit.
Shit.
Yeah.
God, I would love that.
So he was he maybe wanted this thing to be a little bit more of what I was saying
at the start, a little more hot dog centric versus baseball centric.
Sporty.
That's really good to know.
I mean, I wonder.
I mean, I guess I know why they were like, we're not going to do that.
But it's already even still we've lost some of this,
but it's still like kind of an unusual for just a counter restaurant.
It's unusual and as weird gimmicks.
And he wanted there to be twice as many gimmicks.
The buy in to be here is so much.
God bless.
This is that.
Yeah.
Like rare businessman who is a eccentric creative.
Not always like not usually it's too practical.
The thinking for these type of guys.
But no, this guy is an artist.
I feel like in this guy, you know, if you go in the rainforest cafe now,
of course, they're selling Tillman for Tito's very aggressive self-help.
Sure.
Yeah.
Motivational book.
The now owner.
The now.
ownership.
Yeah.
Now it's owned by Landry's, which owns Bubba Gump.
Right.
And he's not a creative guy in this way.
No.
He just purchased.
Just mean numbers.
Yeah.
But I feel like his book,
I mean, they're not my cup of tea, those business motivation books.
I feel like his book is probably less like intent.
Tillman for D is this book starts with warning you that a paddle is coming
for your ass and you must be aware of that at any given time.
And that is his like five steps.
You know, I don't know.
His book has death threats.
And they sell it.
They have it like at the cash register.
There's a sack of them.
A black and white in the most colorful environment.
What could stand out and get your attention for us?
It was being in the Schomburg mall and seeing this black and white photo
of the meanest man ever seen amidst all the friendly frogs and birds
and whatever that really jumped out.
I would like to read it.
I love business books are like so demented.
And the target audience, I don't think, recognizes that all of the time.
But if you're just like reading one for fun, yeah, like that
self mythologizing, you're like, how how are you going to tell me
this book would survive a fact check?
Like it's.
Yeah.
And if you're putting it out yourself there, then nobody's ever.
Maybe God, these are books I should I should read.
We've never read.
Yeah, we should.
How come for your ass book?
No, I tried to get when we were talking about it initially when it came up,
like it was it was on hold.
Oh, there was too much demand.
And the library there was too much demand.
It was already out so I could only see a sample.
And that's how I found the paddle coming from your ass.
Well, I think I think you got a paddle coming from your ass.
If you don't put down your heart and money and buy it,
how do you expect to make money if you won't pay me money?
Yeah, my paddle stories.
I'm sure that guy,
I'm sure that guy shows up on like cable news
and was like, no one wants to work anymore.
Oh, yeah, 100 percent.
I'm sure he owns the Houston Rockets.
Yeah.
As well, in addition to Landry's restaurants.
Well, I might have to.
Yeah, these are probably all good areas for episodes for us.
These crazy books.
I bet they're like that.
Maybe I don't know if you've read anything in this genre, Jamie,
but it seems like it's I bet it's like so boring for 100 pages
and then the craziest thing.
And then they really starts to kick in.
That was how I found the Chicken Man with the 50 Year Plan to be.
Where like it's a very like sort of, you know, generic upbringing.
And then but then when he gets the chicken idea, you're like, well,
you know, that he's really locking into business speak and like real
manifest destiny sort of talk about the chicken idea.
Yeah, you can get Tillman for T to shut up and listen for eight dollars.
Thirty cents used on eBay.
Wow.
All right.
Shut up and listen.
So imagine you just had like you met Cha Cha the Frog.
You had like a tropical drink and you're walking through the gift shop.
You're like, oh, I'm going to get a panda for my my nephew or niece.
And then you're like, what?
He shut up and listen.
Like, why is it in the restaurant that where there's a thunderstorm
every 20, 30 minutes?
Wait, this has like a really good Goodreads rating.
Wow, really?
Yeah.
Is this awesome?
It's got a three point nine one on Goodreads.
That's solid.
Oh, wow.
Scott, look at this Tillman for Tita.
It's six ninety nine on eBay.
It's a copy of the magazine Wine Spectator and Tillman.
There he is.
Maybe in his house.
It's a whole cover story on him.
Tillman for Tita with six hundred plus restaurants.
He's betting big on wine.
Wow.
Legacy.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
I've only had crap wine at his restaurant.
I guess he saves it for himself.
Have you ever read Wine Spectator magazine?
Oh, I can't say I am curious who else is on the cover of Wine Spectator magazine.
I'll try to gather that here.
Well, maybe I need to.
These are all future episodes.
Wine Spectator.
It's less self-help book.
Less goofy than a cigar aficionado.
I think so.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like everyone on it is boring so far.
Oh, yeah.
There's wine.
Yeah, there's usually it's just a bottle.
It's just a picture of a bottle.
That sucks.
I want I want some doofus getting my lips wet with or red with the.
Here's just a person on the front just looking at wines.
Like, it's not as exciting as Tillman.
Could we do an episode with listeners be into an episode where we just
review cigar aficionado covers?
We just like because there's got to be a lot of good ones.
Yeah.
Let's rank them.
Acroid, Jim Belushi are on, you know, for sure.
They're on there every three months.
Yeah, I feel like they didn't know they were such aficionados.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
We got a few Bon Jovi's been on.
Oh, yeah.
Hampton, Hampton Water.
Oh, he has Hampton.
Oh, God, that's an annoying water.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
And and then and Carmelo Anthony, we got.
OK.
But that's a good cover.
That is cool.
Oh, wow.
He's so happy to be drinking that wine.
I'm expecting you on the cover of this.
Oh, sure.
I like that.
I like that he's not Carmelo Anthony is not drinking the wine
and he is just spectating it.
Oh, yeah.
Can't drink.
Why is that the name?
Wine Spectator Wine Drinker.
Yeah, that sounds bad.
Oh, let me ask while we're talking about beverages, what do you think?
Is the best company
beverage to accompany hot dogs?
Oh, good question.
Oh, I mean, if you're going
for like booze, I do feel like a cheap light beer.
You can't feel don't pair it with an IPA.
Don't mess around.
Do you want anything that's going to dominate the dog?
Or a or like honestly any any soda, any soda that's not fruity.
Like, no, I I'm I would discourage an orange soda with a hot dog.
Again, just a familiar, a familiar flavor.
I don't know what it's Dr.
Pepper a Coke.
Yeah, not water.
I think it's so weird when you see someone like
I've got a hot dog and a water bottle like I not it can't be water.
It has to like not appear naturally in the world.
In order to be an appropriate drink for the hot dog.
I don't know.
What's your preference?
I drink a lot of water and I'm only starting to drink more.
I don't want to say I'm drinking more soda, but I'm a little more like,
oh, if I'm having a burger and fries or I'm having pizza,
you want soda with that?
Yeah.
It sounds like you're drinking more soda.
I don't want to say the phrase I'm drinking more soda.
You want to say it out loud.
I think if I drink more, I'm drinking more soda,
but then I am cognizant of like, oh, I need to drink more water
the rest of the day to flush it.
The flush.
As long as I be disturbed if you said I've been trying to drink more.
That's where the problem is.
I drink more soda, but then it's just like, OK, that's my sugar for the like.
I can't like have ice cream or cookies or something.
Oh, that's heartbreaking.
I look like I'm you know what?
I hate to do this around this episode because I don't want to get in the whole thing.
But the last City Walk Saga five years ago, there's a long stretch
where I just question you about how many times a month you're eating cookies and milk.
Yes.
And I said like five.
And you said like five or six.
That's a lot of times.
Yeah, it is.
And can we just check in here five years later?
How many times a month are you sitting down with a big glass of milk
and dunking Oreos in it?
Whole milk, by the way.
Whole milk.
Yes.
OK.
Go hard or go home.
Well, look.
This is important.
Less because I've decreased my cookies, milk and increase my anxiety medication.
OK, OK.
Those don't pair.
I yeah, I feel like we usually keep oat milk or like almond milk in the house.
And I think I'm less likely to.
I just need it.
I know.
I need a number, though.
You haven't said a number.
Once or twice.
OK.
Yeah, he's still in the game.
Still there.
So I am not I have left my old self behind totally.
But you know, we all grow up single at some point.
Growing up, I guess this is growing up means two times a month.
Sitting down with a big glass and dunking.
Sitting down with cookies and milk.
And wearing a propeller beanie, but not necessarily making a point to spin it.
Right.
No, no.
Buying it for live shows at the beautiful Dynasty typewriter.
You know, yes, I do.
Complimenting the beauty of theaters.
That's the yeah, live theater.
You know, the carpet you see.
OK, actually, one more thing about Schussler, he in his little
interview is the rounds of press he was doing when this place opened.
Something that he said about the philosophy of this place.
He's talking about the mustard selection.
And then he then he says we're talking about his challenging nature, he says.
And never ketchup.
Never, ever, ever ketchup.
What's the what's the room's feeling about?
Well, that's technically the Chicago thing.
Yeah, that's the Chicago.
It's very they're very aggressive about that there.
I will say I don't completely agree with that.
And I do like ketchup sometimes on it.
It's always nice to spend time with an open minded Chicago.
I'm a little progressive.
I'm a little more progressive in that way, in my beliefs.
I grew up with I didn't I didn't I wasn't aware that ketchup was not allowed
until I went to Chicago for the first time.
And I find that that is actually a big part of why I got put off
by the Chicago dog, for I was it was so aggrieved.
Like there are places where they threaten to cut your hand off.
If you put ketchup on like it's really intense.
I'm pro.
I don't know.
Yeah, seems like an odd thing to be.
I'm pro to growing up.
I was, you know, always doing ketchup, mustard, relish.
Yeah.
If I go to like Costco, if I get the famous Costco hot dog soda combo,
I think I'm relish mustard onions like the Boston dog here.
I think it's fine without ketchup.
I just get I just I'm like, but it's not generally worse for it being there.
Is it does he explain why no ketchup?
No.
12 mustards, no ketchup.
He just believes maybe in just that old.
Yeah.
Feeling or whatever.
Minnesota guy.
So I don't know how that factors into this whole philosophy,
because I don't see that represented in Milwaukee.
But I understand the ketchup.
So like, especially if you put a lot on it or it's like a specific catch up,
like it can't overtake the taste of everything.
Right.
It's a very like strong taste.
But I don't know.
It's fun to have ketchup, mustard and relish on it.
I feel like.
Yeah.
So it makes me feel seven.
That's what it's.
Yes.
Ketchup is a childhood thing.
I think it's an infantilizing thing.
I get like a fancy ketchup now to sort of like take the edge off.
I'm like, sure.
This is adult ketchup.
Ketchup and white bread, though, is still like, you know,
a silver fondness for the flavor combination.
Ketchup and white bread, like white bread or hot dog bun.
You know.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
Not just the two together.
That's what I was asking.
You're not just having a ketchup.
Oh, no, I'm not just having a ketchup.
No, I don't live in the depression.
Not anymore.
Yeah.
Not since the time.
Not since.
Yeah.
Not since you got here.
In the time machine.
Um, maybe one last question.
You've you've sampled.
I know Steve talked a big game about his hot dog tour
to get everything he needed to bring to this base.
But I feel like it's very possible you've had more hot dogs.
I don't.
I don't say that I have.
I'll say that I have.
I think.
I'm willing to bet that.
I'm sorry if he ends up shouting at you in some later form for having said that.
Shut up and listen.
But if you could bring if there's something missing from the hot dog
hall of fame that you've experienced in your travels, they cover a lot of ground.
But what what is not represented that should be?
Gosh, I'd have to look at the menu.
I think that honestly, the menu is surprisingly comprehensive.
And that but that seems like that's Steve's whole thing.
Like you wouldn't think there would be so much rainforest at the rainforest cafe.
You wouldn't think that there would be a million options.
I think honestly, that for vegetarian hot dog fans,
there's not enough here.
That's my main thing.
They got one vegan field dog.
Yeah.
Micro cilantro.
This sounds like I don't know.
Don't you want like still kind of base?
I feel like they overthought.
That that I think is a newer menu addition,
because I have an older menu and there's no vegan on this.
It's a micro cilantro.
What is micro?
Is it like micro plastics or like it's so tiny?
And they invade the blood, brain, the blood, brain barrier is penetrated
by these micro cilantro.
What does that mean?
Not sure.
Yeah, it's like I've never had a complaint about the size of cilantro.
Yeah.
Is that a vegan thing?
They can have cilantro.
It's got to be micro.
Just got to be little.
It's got to be little.
Yeah, I feel like if at the Hot Dog Hall of Fame,
if you could get any of the meat hot dogs with a good vegan alternative,
it would be it would be great.
I also I haven't tried enough of them.
I'm not seeing.
There's no LA street dog.
There's no danger dog.
Yeah, there's no danger dog.
And there's no they have two Washington dogs.
I don't know what Washington they're really referring to.
They have blue cheese dressing on this dog.
I'm looking for the cream cheese dog in Washington state,
which I don't believe is represented on this menu for some reason.
But yeah, the danger dog is missing.
The the cream cheese dog from the Pacific Northwest is missing
and good vegan alternatives.
But like there's still like more hot.
Did he say there were nine?
There's way more now.
Well, that is standard boy.
They're like, they're, you know, and also, of course, I want all 12 mustards back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Back all 12.
Yeah, we were impressed by six, but imagine 12.
12.
I can't even conceive of 12.
After Jamie, after doing all this work, a hot dog based work, how how many days?
If I said here's three million dollars, you were going to put together
your own Hot Dog Hall of Fame.
How fast do you think you could draw up the plans for your own version of this?
Oh, I think I who I think pretty quickly menu wise,
the menu I could bring together in a couple of hours.
Oh, OK.
But the vision.
What would it look like?
Yeah.
I I would love a gosh, a medieval times kind of hot dog thing.
I don't know.
I would want to combine the elements of Chuck E.
Cheese that I like with a hot dog themed restaurant.
But every time that's been attempted, it hasn't gone over very well.
Like, there's not really a lot of hot dog chains for that reason.
Because there's one of the I wanted to write about more in the book,
but it's just like almost impossible to learn about.
I happened to read a biography of Mickey Rooney ten years ago,
which is the only reason I have this information.
Wow.
Here's some podcast.
We've been talking about Mickey recently.
He has come up on.
Yeah, yeah.
He's I mean, he's he's he really lived.
I was I was working at a bookstore at the time.
I was just like reading this over the course of weeks.
But it was in his bad investments era.
And and during that.
And I think there was just one, maybe two.
They were not open for a long, but it was called like Mickey Rooney's Weenie World.
And the special dish they would serve was like
a circular hot dog, like an Ouroboros
style hot dog served on the hot dog eating its own tail.
It wasn't successful.
It only survives in like a few newspaper clippings.
So I don't think it would have been in the 70s.
Like I've had a really hard time.
Again, because here's the thing.
Some that we've been sent this and we've I think fallen for this.
Yes.
There's something called that helped inspire our celebrity
where our celebrity owned restaurant.
Right.
That's there's something.
Sometimes you'll see something go around called Mickey Rooney's potato fantasy.
But that is a parody, a very well done parody.
Just yeah, you should know it's a fake.
But so I'm shocked to now discover right next to that.
That's a real there was a real one.
I didn't know that the sillier sounding one is.
Yeah.
Whoa.
It's OK.
I'm seeing there's there's been a new article written about it since I last checked.
This is great.
A meandering journey in a search for a restaurant that may or may not exist.
I mean, God, I hope it exists.
Yes.
No, wait.
Potato fantasy.
That's the fake one.
But we need world seems to be.
I mean, if it's in his book, it's got to be.
But also, like, I don't I.
Maybe he made it up.
Is that what people are speculating?
I need to I own the Mickey Rooney book.
I'll go back and check, because if I'm remembering correctly,
there was like a newspaper clipping like printed in the book.
That's someone's got what I'm looking at.
There's also and then it's this picture and it's and it's a quote.
Hi, Long Island, you're number one.
The Mick wants you to come to his grand opening.
And then does anyone want to take a quick guess at what the
the themed French fries are called at Mickey Rooney's Weenie World?
Oh, boy.
It is weenie.
Well, it's really it's very I love this answer.
Anything about any pun he might like turn it into.
Oh, a small fries.
Oh, that's good.
That's very good.
He wishes.
Yes.
The answer is Mickey Rooney French fries.
Free Mickey Rooney French fries with this Mickey Rooney French fries.
Rooney French fries.
That's right up there with my favorite every week.
My favorite bad menu item name was at
was that it was at Universal.
I don't know if it's still there, but it's at the Minions Cafe
and it's just called Evil Mac and Cheese.
And it's disgusting.
Was that Hollywood?
Was that at the Hollywood?
Yeah.
Well, this is why, because guests of this saga,
Evan Susser and Van Roeber Show wrote the menu items for the one in Florida.
So clearly they needed some professional comedy
and some funny people to get a little more clever than Evil Mac and Cheese.
Yeah.
I was doing the writer's strike.
I'm like, maybe people were taking a stand.
Scabs are writing this.
Right.
Anyway, I mean, what I there's so much we could.
Now I just want to spin it off.
The Mickey Rooney's weenie world.
It's the Mickey.
There was a tweet going around.
Is it real where it's like the Property Brothers said
Mickey Rooney kept trying to steal food on this set?
Yeah, I saw that too.
Celebrity.
Somebody said that was a picture of them with Leslie Jordan.
Oh, I'm not sure.
I actually I just don't know.
I didn't look at it very closely too much.
So I like the idea.
Anyway, that's so I mean, the world was very real.
I'm looking at this.
OK, good.
Him at the opening.
Oh, great.
He's beaming.
Oh, that makes me happy.
That makes me really.
I'm looking at it.
The picture is so small.
His smile just like shouts through it somehow.
He's a star.
Wow.
Was the biggest star in the world.
How did we miss this during?
Yeah, really?
It's this on the website snack stack.
Yeah.
How did we miss that?
Geez.
I mean, we still have more.
I mentioned in the article that's exciting.
Oh, wow.
You're in this article.
Wow.
I just thought as Loftus mentioned before, I was like, what?
Whoa.
Damn.
We just what a great.
It's so nice to be a part of something bigger than yourself.
To be associated with the mixture, to have your name even in his
in the same breath.
Well, it's it's well deserved.
As I see you, you've more than earned
my earlier poll quote about you being one of America's leading hot dog voices.
And this this was so it's saying a lot.
We've a lot of these have been very fun.
This is this might be the most fun I've had doing one of these.
Jamie Loftus, he survived podcast, The Ride, The City
Rock, Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
Let's exit through the plug portal.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Besides this article that mentions you.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like to I'd like to plug this snack.
I'm really looking forward to reading this whole thing.
This this writer did a very thorough investigation and confirmed
the circular hot dog.
Wow.
Wait, and you're in your quote, it's a failed franchise of 52 hot.
They did there were many.
I don't remember what I said in the book.
I I'm assuming I had reason to do it in a relish called McLeish.
Yes.
No way.
I wish I had known about making really fresh fries.
Oh, not even Andy Hardee's.
No.
Where was this?
Do we know where this was?
This was in Jersey City.
OK.
Yeah, but there were multiple locations.
Does the audience want celebrity to let us know just generally?
If I would never know what to bring back, if you want more celebrity,
I think we could do it.
Especially this.
This makes me want to do this.
I went to the gym.
Oh, but anyway, plugs officially.
Oh, yeah.
Read raw dog.
That feels like the thing to plug.
Yeah, I need to.
I'm sold.
It's every it's everywhere.
I think I don't know.
I think it'll be I don't think it'll be back everywhere closer to hot dog season
to what's hot dog season.
Oh, well, I'm going on there.
I it's my publisher has started being like, well, we're going to put you
on the road for a little bit during hot dog season.
Cool.
Is that line up with the paperback release?
Maybe it will.
The paperback releases next year, but they're like,
we're still going to send you out during the peak season.
Wow.
Yes.
Great.
So like, you know, June into July, the summer, there's a great
I don't know if hopefully this will like have been announced by the time
this episode comes out.
But there's going to be like a 60 foot long
Times Square hot dog sculpture opening in the spring.
Oh, my God.
And all the hot dog heads are going out.
So I'll be I'll be there.
So find find me there.
I'll be right now.
The plan is I'll be giving a speech in front of the big hot dog.
Wow.
I can't wait.
It shoots out.
It also raises up
every couple of hours and shoots out confetti.
What?
I know this is the this is a throwback to like fun 90s.
The David Copperfield restaurant that never opened.
Like, this is some silly stuff.
Wow.
I won't believe it until I see it.
But it is there.
They're like booking the hot dog.
They're booking people to do stuff at the hot dog.
Wow.
You got a big summer.
If it all ends perfectly.
Congratulations.
Well learned.
Oh, and wait a minute.
The sector stone.
Oh, there it is.
Sector stone is appearing.
And I think it's huh.
It looks like a sandwich.
What's in it's hard to say.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's got a little like pink style label of what's in it.
Wow.
This is called the Jason
Sarah Sheridan sandwich.
Oh, wow.
And look what's in it.
It's OK.
Ketchup, white bread and anxiety medication.
Oh, that really brings out the oomph of the Lexapro.
All right.
Well, that'll do it.
Jamie, thank you for being here.
We're going to let you go so that we can check in and see where we're at
at this point, if we're getting anywhere close to the finish line with the sector
keeper.
So let's see if we can call to him.
Boys, boys.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Oh, it's good.
It's good to hear from you.
I mean, you were kind of keeping tabs on that episode, right?
With Jamie Hot Dog, all of fame.
That was really that was a blast.
I thought that was wonderful, boys.
Thank you.
Oh, boys.
Things are not good.
What?
How could they?
I mean, isn't that like that's one of the last things we had to do.
We've been doing this for more days now than the original.
Like, we got to be close to the end, right?
Yeah, we've covered everything.
No, boys.
The rift is stronger than ever.
The worst part, it's it's because of me.
What?
How can that be true?
What did you do?
That doesn't make sense.
The entire multiverse is crumbling because of because of my actions.
Many, many years ago, boys.
My.
Yeah, that's something you are.
That you did.
You don't do bad stuff.
Yeah, I know.
Sometimes it's smoke or whatever.
I'd like to be bad.
But that's a cheeky thing you usually say.
Sometimes it feels good to be bad.
Yeah.
But this isn't one of those times.
No, no, this is not bad to be bad.
No, this time it feels bad to be bad.
This time it's bad to be.
OK, well, then what are we?
All right.
So how do we fix it?
Where do we go?
What do we do?
Just tell us where.
If I tell you directly, the evil forces will find us.
I can't guide you or the listeners, boys, to the to the next jump point.
It's it's too dicey.
It's cosmically dicey.
Dicey.
So we have to do another episode,
but we don't know where or what.
No, it might it might be in front of you.
Like like Fassbender, Mr.
Policeman, I gave you all the clues.
Oh, it's like a podcast puzzle.
OK, let me think.
I'm racking my brain.
Wait a minute.
Think.
Wait, wait a minute.
I have the I'm looking at the logo
for the Sharon's logo for for the multiverse.
The great logo.
Yes, yes.
Mr.
Scott, look, yes.
I don't think I've ever called you Mr.
Scott.
Mr.
I appreciate it.
It feels very professional.
It's not my last name, but it sounded cool.
Wait a minute.
I'm looking.
OK, yeah, I mean, I'm zooming way in on the hemisphere dancer.
Playing with a very interesting story behind it.
Of course.
Yes, there's something I've never noticed in this.
From afar, it looks like windows.
But if you look really closely, right, there's numbers.
Zoom, zoom.
I'm zooming.
Yeah, I see.
OK, I'm looking at it.
Michael, what do you see?
Do you see it?
Michael, you know this plane better than anyone.
I do, but that's yeah, it does.
No, those are the official numbers of the plane.
Yeah, the plane doesn't have that in for in real life.
I would know about it.
But on the image, it says is it an S and a 16?
S16.
Oh, my God.
What?
What is it, Jason?
We have to go back.
Go back where?
What do you mean?
Go.
We have to go back.
Oh, wait, S6.
Hang on a second.
Is this the fucking the food court sector
that is that we never did in the city walk original saga?
And it was my fault.
You told us.
I know.
You told us not to.
Which way?
Hang on.
We can't do this.
We can't gang up on him.
I was just a boy.
He was just a boy and he still is.
Clearly, he's wracked with regret over this whole thing.
I'm just frustrated because like at the time, it seemed like a fun break
after 19 days in a row.
And now all it's doing is adding time to this.
So we have to.
Well, you're not adding time if you're not adding time.
If you know what I mean.
That's dense.
I don't know if I do.
Let me see if I can.
And again, we'll try to do this while evading the evil forces.
Yeah.
We'll try to speak in code.
But hopefully what I.
OK, so there's been new sectors every day of the saga.
I guess tomorrow people can go on the main feed
and hear an episode that covers city food or whatever.
City food, the thing that we didn't do five and a half years ago.
Yeah.
So we'll do it.
So that'll be all right.
That'll be up whatever midnight tonight, whatever.
Yeah.
Right.
No, no.
The timeline can only be corrected in the exact spot
where the original sin occurred.
Oh, my God.
Mr.
Scott, I can't say anymore.
Scott, Mr.
Scott, you don't.
I know what he means.
We have to go back.
That's right, Mr.
Jason.
Yes.
You hearing this have to go back.
Have to go back.
They.
Oh, they have.
They have to go back.
This series so far has only moved forward.
But in this case, the only way to hear tomorrow's sector is to go back.
That's right.
It's like I've always said the end is in the beginning and the beginning is in the end.
You're always saying that, you know, everything you need is there.
I can't say anymore.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
OK.
But it's all right.
If we've gone back and fixed what the mistake was, then in theory,
they don't have to wait till tomorrow.
Everything you need, you have.
Everything you have right now.
Wow.
And stay paired up.
You're the ghost.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett
Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDog Team and liking our page on Facebook.