When your town has made you frown, When your square has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch, You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge,
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol, A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks, A place where you can tattoo your lower back,
So let's go take a walk, let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight, tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness, a daily,
extremely necessary series, exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder that make up Universal
City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to the first ever saga episode on Club 3.
Club 3, a new invention
since sagas, yes, since the dawn of sagas.
We podcast scientists invented Club 3, but not
only for this new saga, was it available.
It really is history, I would say, and you know,
we start these things casually, we don't always introduce ourselves, but we have to introduce
a special guest who you know we had to bring to visit the Club 3, the VIP supporters of this show,
Sector Keeper in the building.
Boys, boys, Club 3, let me hear you in the balcony.
Wow, he's revving the crowd up.
I love that.
You know, this is the party people here.
That's that Club 3 treatment.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow.
Club 3 should have been a place at City Walk.
It would have been at least three stories.
Yeah, of course.
Massive sprawling failure, yes.
Yeah,
it would have failed for sure.
It also, it would have been called Club 3, but it would have been
four stories.
Yeah.
And so everything.
Not perfectly just not clean.
A good amount of
conversations between guests and wait staff.
Like, so there are three, well, there's actually
we do this every day.
Yeah.
It's good to see you Sector Keeper.
You know, you sent us to the
Land of Fallen Brothers and Never Built as like a punishment, but we ended up, it's weird to say,
I kind of liked the Sector Creeper a little bit.
You saw the Creeper?
We met the Sector Creeper,
he looked exactly like you, but with a Chris Gaines soul patch.
Yes, exactly.
I mean,
sort of like this chill fun Bealejuice kind of deal.
Yeah.
I mean, it's wild down there, right?
It is wild.
Yeah, but there's like a lot of cool places.
You guys liked it.
We kind of liked it,
actually.
Other than some of the things popping out and like threatening to hurt us.
The potential
to be crushed to death or to be impaled while taking a shit.
Yes.
Yeah, we didn't want that.
I did stick around for a little while and I lost a lot of money in those poker games
because he kept getting five kings.
Yeah.
Oh, Jason.
Yeah, that's my fault.
That's my fault.
There's only four in a deck.
Yeah, I know.
I feel like we're in a comic strip.
Look, my.
Just this episode you felt that way?
He said, you sure you don't want to play?
I got a three card Monte table
and then I was like, all right, I know how to win three card Monte.
And then he started
dealing five card Texas Hold'em.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry about that.
Yeah.
Did you get anything
like any free swag?
I know he's got boxes of it.
I got a couple boxes of very pungent Stoegies.
Really?
He just he's always looking for him.
He's always looking for me.
He said, oh, take those.
They're empty.
And I tried to tell them they're not.
And then he forced me out with like force
powers.
That's he didn't display those powers to us.
I guess he also had force.
But wow.
Wow.
I mean,
it's kind of like Leia, like suddenly flying through space.
Some force powers that's true.
Come out of nowhere.
They come out later.
Sometimes they come out later.
And the more
fuel rod kiosks that pop up, his force grows.
His force grows.
Yeah.
All the energy of the unused fuel rods.
All kind of like gives him the force of a
iPhone.
Yeah.
It gives it gives each one gives him the force to power a phone for 35 minutes.
If he gets enough of those kiosks, he'll be able to charge a fuel rod battery
all so much it will get a phone to 80 percent.
Oh, I'm glad you got out of there.
Yeah.
For the best.
And you know, and we're happy to be here on like, you know, in a place we understand
in Club 3.
So you have you have climbed the paywall if you're hearing this.
And that means that you
get an episode about a wall.
You know, I know the usual rigmarole here is that the Sector Keeper
does the reveal, which we can do.
However, you listening to this have known already for a while
what this topic was going to be, because for the first time ever in a saga, there was a power
more powerful than the Sector Keeper.
And that's the power of democracy.
Thank you all for picking
today's topic, which we will still let the Sector Keeper.
Yes, boys, boys, audience,
poll takers.
Phase four sector two is the piece of the Berlin Wall behind the Hard Rock Cafe.
Good luck, boys.
So there you go.
That's again, that kind of stuff we get up to here that people
want to hear here in crazy Club 3.
Yesterday, we handled everything.
We cleared out everything
about the Hard Rock Cafe besides this.
Yeah.
And I like it because it took it off the plate.
Let that
be a leaner episode.
And now we can just really meditate on this wall.
Some other things didn't
quite get there.
I really liked all these suggestions.
Fallen Brothers, we ended up taking
care of in a different way.
The idea, there was the idea floated of a mini saga in the Knotts
marketplace, a little shopping center outside of Knotts.
And I'm of two minds there.
One,
on one hand, I'm kind of happy we didn't have to go do the work.
But on the other hand,
it's a very, it's a fun place.
I'm sure we would have met some sort of colorful,
I am her character or brought along a favorite keeper from the past.
I am a little shocked,
impressed that the audience would rather talk about the Berlin Wall piece than have us do a
full mini saga in one episode.
Yeah, that was mini saga, I think was the key word there.
Yeah,
it would have like, imagine.
I mean, that could have been a five hour thing.
Could have been.
Somebody said, somebody's rationale in everybody's kind of campaigning for what they want there.
And somebody had the rationale, come on, mini saga, we got to put the boys to work.
Another rationale that I saw in pushing what we did end up do.
Oh, no, actually, no, this was
open ended.
Actually, this was like, you know, just general strategy.
Somebody, Eric said,
you know, it's possible that all these topics will be covered.
It's just a matter of which
one is behind the double paywall.
If that's the case, pick the one that will help the good boys
drum up the most new Club 3 subscribers.
That's very kind of it.
It is very nice.
Now,
the answer to that is not this one.
Yeah, no, I picked the least interesting.
No, it's interesting.
It's interesting.
Pick the cement wall.
Sorry, Eric.
Eric's wishes were not fulfilled just in
terms of, but I think this will excite everybody.
Look, it won and I'm excited about it.
You know,
this would have gotten a big chunk of core in the other one.
And it's you know, what we're
talking about here is like, oh, it is like a big walk.
And then behind something, it is like the
double paywall.
It's secret.
It's a secret.
It feels secret.
It is.
It's like I think I walked
by before when I was just kind of exploring, totally forgot about it.
And I mentioned to
someone who worked at Universal, we were going to do a bunch of city well stuff.
And they said,
don't forget about that piece of the Berlin wall behind Hard Rock Cafe.
And I was like,
I simultaneously know exactly what they mean and not.
And then sure enough,
when we just kept going, it's right there.
It really, it's kind of the I like that don't forget
rationale because it kind of is the like dotting of the I, the crossing of the T.
Yeah, I know
we're doing a lot of days of this still unclear on how many at this point.
Who knows?
You're almost
halfway.
Oh, God.
Almost.
I'm gonna crunch some numbers on that.
What does that mean?
But it's a number halfway to eternity is like, you know, I live in a different real Cheshire
cat smile.
As you say that there is no halfway when we're talking an infinite loop.
Yes.
Oh,
God.
OK, well, we'll see.
But anyway, it is, you know, it's possible that we could have forgot if
we were to do an exhaustive, I'd have to think the only exhaustive covering of City Walk,
Orlando, we had to hit this.
We had to give it ample time.
So here we are.
This topic suggested
by multiple people, Miguel Sandoval, Melanie and Chad H.
I had the question of how to say your name
before.
E.
I just don't know.
It's H.
A.
E.
F.
L.
and I'm going to fuck it up.
I'm not going to.
I owe
you more respect than that, Chad, than to bungle your name.
You spelled it.
That's Chad Havlach.
That's a way to at least pay respect.
Yes.
Yeah, absolutely.
So he's given full credit.
So we are here.
We're at the.
Why don't we describe what happened, how you get here?
Yes, because Jason alluded to this as we covered yesterday, the giant Hard Rock Cafe with a concert
venue, huge footprint.
And then so just even if there was nothing in the back to take a walk all
the way to the back.
Yeah.
Be kind of a long journey.
And I only did this at night.
So I have
kind of like the mysterious air.
I did do it twice.
I did go back here twice.
I was there.
Yeah.
But like it's, you know, it's shadowy, it's dimly lit, there's bushes.
What's in the bushes?
You're on the outskirts of the park and there's very much a vibe.
Like, you know, as you're walking,
the hard, the rock part kind of stops.
You're not seeing a bunch of like guitar pillars or
sprinkler heads that look like speakers or drum pedals.
I don't know.
It feels like you're going
in a place like a part of like a maintenance entrance or something.
This is not for the public
to walk down.
It feels like you got like, oh, we walk around here because like we're like, we have
to give a bunch of like containers of soda syrup or something to load into the six flags like
similar to six flags.
When you're just suddenly in what you suspect might be a delivery road.
A back entrance in the Hard Rock Cafe.
You could go through the restaurant.
Yes.
I'm describing
the specific way where you're not even in the restaurant.
Yeah.
It just doesn't feel like an
image.
It doesn't feel like they want you back there.
It's kind of near that weird side entrance
that Universal uses sometimes for overflow or if you were going to the old Blue Man Group show,
like it's kind of in that neck of the woods.
Yes.
Yeah.
Kind of an alternate way to get into
the park.
But there's a point in the middle there where you're it's almost like, am I supposed to
be here?
Yes.
Is this correct?
Yeah.
Is this the right way?
And no one is there.
No one's there.
If you go back there and there's other people there, I think it'd feel very strange.
It would
feel like an accident.
Yes.
Yeah.
Or like you're about to get jumped or something.
Like there's
something like going on a secret meeting here.
You know what?
Nowhere.
We don't bear responsibility
for any robberies that occur when you're on the way to the Markable Berlin Wall.
There is.
Okay.
Once you get back there and you stand and stare at the piece of Berlin Wall, you look to one side.
You jump to the right to the end of the story.
Oh, what?
You get all the way back and there's
a piece of Berlin Wall standing there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That we already said that.
I was weaving
a tale.
But anyway.
Oh, okay.
It really feels like a college student dissertation on like the 20th
century because there's a Berlin Wall.
There's a theme park to your right.
And if you look to your
left, there's a Hard Rock Cafe with a replica CBGBs on it.
You're saying these are like important
things for American culture.
It's a random sampling.
Important things or like important
things in the language of Hard Rock Cafe where it's like, you know, 20th century big events,
rock and roll, CBGBs, Berlin Wall, you know?
Big studios.
You know?
Love all serval.
Like a verse from We Didn't Start the Fire.
I was about to say how many of these things are in
We Didn't Start the Fire already?
Some of them.
Berlin Wall.
When did it come out?
Was Berlin Wall still standing?
Yeah, good question.
The next verse sequentially would have
been Nickelodeon Studios.
The list of all the double dare Hard Rock Cafe.
What else do I have to say?
We Didn't Start.
Where they filmed Gullah Gullah Island.
Barbecue menu.
They push it really hard.
Yeah, but it's like, it really doesn't feel like you're like, I mean, it feels like you're like,
you're on the outskirts of a stadium or something.
Yeah.
And then and it and then like,
and then you're just looking at a gate.
You almost have to like, just like peer to,
you're gonna like go even a little further out of your way to get to this odd little,
it's a planter.
It's a planter that then has a cement block.
You would think it would be like,
obviously there were lights back there, but you would think it would be like a thing that's fully
like just a straight shot.
And then there's like kind of a like a circle, like you walk around it,
maybe on a sidewalk and it's well lit.
And like you go, oh, I see they've made a real like piece
out of this thing.
They've made a real like, it's a real presentation versus what you're saying,
it's like, you kind of go around a little bit and it's like, it's kind of quiet back here.
Okay.
Yeah.
Maybe there's some like, like really muffled speakers are playing like,
and you're really, I know what it's like.
25 year old song.
Radio after you radio after you.
Yeah, that's right.
Yes.
But then, but you get there and you get to a, to a planter
and you see this, this piece in its glory.
Yeah.
Now, all right.
It makes, I guess it makes you
think, it makes you think about, about history and you know, and where we've been as a nation
and all the significance of, but it's also just, it's a wall.
It's also a wall.
It's kind of,
it's kind of unremarkable in and of itself.
Remember the famous quote, Mr.
Gorbachev,
tear down that wall and put it behind a hard left.
Of course you forget about the second.
You forget.
Yeah.
So yeah.
There's a little, there's some writing there, but yeah, it's not,
you don't, it's not an impressive thing on its own.
It's big.
It's a big piece,
but it's like without again, like a museum with a big like backdrop that maybe shows you what it
like it, which part of it it was like pointing out a big picture of it.
Maybe here, this is the
part or something.
You know where it stood, you know what part of town and any like kind of local
news articles about it are very much like an interesting fact about universal Orlando behind
the hard rock cafe.
There's a piece of the Berlin wall and then just a paragraph of the Berlin wall
erected in such and such today torn down in 1980, November, 1989, checkpoint Charlie,
like every article mentions.
And of course, checkpoint Charlie to go between East and West
Berlin.
And I know article answered the why.
So you're mad that they said,
give me the info I'm here for.
Give me the real history.
Get here.
Charlie Soviet this
bridge of spies.
Did I come park bid for it?
There was some people on Reddit.
Someone said it used to be more centrally located by the old
hard rock cafe.
Oh, I was wondering if that was part of the old one, but wait, because yeah,
as we addressed it moved from across the park over by the old by the psycho house,
by the fake psycho house.
Yeah.
Because now it feels like you're keeping us up with this.
Sorry, boys.
I dozed off.
Oh no.
No, no, it's all right.
No, we used to be a secret creeper.
What a love doll.
Yeah, you would have been down an old crumbling wall.
That's where he lives.
He loves everything in his world.
The rest of the walls down there.
All the parts that weren't saved for all right.
Yeah.
There used to be a very weird section of
universal Florida where you would go past five was playground, see a recreation of the psycho house
and next door was the hard rock cafe, which you could leave the park to go to or enter it from
outside the park.
Yeah.
Pretty awesome.
Now, you know, I mean, he knew we'd sector keeper knew
already, of course, but you know, and where does checkpoint Charlie come into play?
Well before this on the other side of the world.
Well, but you do have to consider, I think the
those checkpoints between restaurant and theme park, those are kind of miniature
checkpoint Charlies in their own right.
Right.
And there's sort of tend as there was tension
between the West and the East, there's tension between restaurants and paying customers.
There are now checkpoint Charlies as a part of the South.
Oh, in the multiverse.
Oh, so we're gonna have to get out of here via checkpoint.
OK, portals, gates, wormholes,
checkpoint Charlies, jump points, checkpoint Charlies.
Makes sense.
Galactic ones.
Well, you know, I do think that to understand everything about this, I think it is time to
dive into our deep lengthy analysis of the Cold War, the causes of it, the effects,
ongoing effects of it.
And what I mean, like, OK, you could we could read what's on the thing.
That's boring to do, I guess.
I'll do it.
But it tells you it does.
They do.
It's a tidy explanation
on the plaque of what it is.
You know, I guess in 1961, this infamous symbol of the Cold War
was erected to keep the East Germans from fleeing in order to wait in order to the way.
All right.
Well, I don't think they wrote down all the words on this.
What I copy pasted has
some weird in order to fill it in, make it up.
C.
The sick S.
I.
when there's a yeah.
Yeah.
A blue state, three blue men picked up the piece of wall and carried it across the ocean on a
steamship, used it as a silly drum.
Yeah.
The Soviets built a wall between the West.
Fucking this up is why I don't just swear this is an history podcast.
So it's built a wall between the East and West sections of Berlin for the next 28 years.
The
Cold War raged on and checkpoint Charlie.
There you go.
Take a shot.
Govern passage.
The wall stood
as a harsh reminder of the chasm between the non-communist West and communist East.
On November
9th, 1989, the wall was symbolically brought down.
Only a few parts of the wall remain.
The Hard Rock
Cafe is proud to display this piece of history that symbolizes the wall of oppression.
The wall
stood as a harsh reminder of the chasm between the non-communist West and communist East.
On
November 9th, 1989, the wall was symbolically brought down.
Only a few parts of the wall remain.
The Hard Rock Cafe is proud to display this piece of history that symbolizes the wall of oppression.
Yeah.
I mean, this and they know the weight is on them because they know that they would have had
to start building walls like this to keep planet Hollywood away.
If that if those tensions had grown
and they started building next door everywhere, they already had a hard rock.
Yeah.
Why does anybody
ever propose doing a world history cafe that's full of just like, you know, old stuff and I don't
know, pieces of walls and different, I don't know, tanks, different history, historical artifacts.
That's true.
It's the only way you're going to get us to learn about anything.
Yeah.
If you name a
terrible burger, they've got Napoleon's hat in the world history cafe.
Wow.
John Wilkes Booth
chicken tenders.
Yeah.
Cause like that there's got to be something close to it in like a museum
somewhere.
The Bill of Rights rice bowl.
The Bill of Rice.
That's good.
It should, they should do it.
Yeah.
History.
This is the way, the only way to get people to learn nowadays.
By that we mean us.
I'll write a little paragraph and like send it to Robert Earl and all the other different
restaurateurs, Tillman Fertitta and stuff.
Shaq.
Shaq?
Sure.
Uh huh.
Shaq will sign off on anything.
Oh and Shaq will be dressed up as all the, like the historical figures.
Oh, Shaq in a powdered wig.
That's right.
That's fun.
General Shaq Washington.
But then the general will sue him for a general
thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's muddy if there's other generals involved.
Seeing Shaq as Napoleon
would be funny and confusing as Napoleon was short.
That's true.
He'd have to get on his knees,
put little shoes on like Dorf.
Yeah.
Which would be a Dorf on, Shaq doing a new, an updated Dorf.
That's what I was about to say.
Shaq bought Dorf and it's, and his, he goes on his knees and now he's just a regular
size person.
Sector Cuber, do you know who Dorf is?
I remember.
I made a reference to it and forgot,
I forgot who it was and then you were like, no, that's who I'm talking about.
It was Tim.
Tim Conway.
I remember the VHS as Dorf goes fishing.
Yeah.
Even as a kid, I thought this just feels off.
It's an early sign that not everything is good.
I think that's right.
Yeah.
We just got Dorf as a club three suggestion and it was like a, like,
wait, okay, we had to stop recording because Jason like coughed and I thought it was just a
coughing and water thing.
But then you said, you said it was, it was caused by you not knowing what
Dorf is.
It was a combination.
I started laughing and then choking water and coughing.
And I was trying to get out.
I don't know what Dorf is.
I was sitting here going like,
why are you all like, I don't think we should be saying that.
What are you talking about?
I don't think we should be saying that.
We weren't saying Dorf.
No, no, no.
I was like,
is that the term?
Dorf is not a slur.
It's not that we are not taking anything away from any
group or it's one that I don't, it's so obscure.
I don't know about it.
Do I remember his name is
spelled D-O-R-F.
Yeah.
I had no idea.
I was so confused.
Well, you know what I was about to
say is that it was suggested on club three and the person is like Dorf, which was a series of
Tim Conway did where he's and I'm like, I know what Dorf is, but Jason did not know what Dorf is.
And thisDP is not the kind of thing it is.
Probably it's, it's probably reasonable and better
that you don't know what Dorf is.
There was all these home videos in like the home video
initial rage in the eighties where he, he, he, he gall.
He was like a German guy or like Dutch
or something.
Like, cause he had an accent.
That's part of it.
And then I love getting explained
from the ground up, but he was, he did instructional videos, mostly golf,
but he would go on his knees and put little shoes on his knees.
These were like very short person,
no money.
Yeah.
Really?
Like you get the vibe from it.
You were like, this feels like a bootleg
tape of some kind, but it was literally, they just, no one had put any money.
I don't know
how much Tim Conway may probably made a decent amount.
I would think, but maybe not.
So maybe
probably nobody was exploiting that, that area, the home video market.
But then also there'd be
things like if he's on a golf course, they would dig little holes for his legs to go so that then
he could like tip around and like go back and forth, like a blow up doll or like an inflatable,
you know, like outside of cardio.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
But still with the
little shoes seems like second rate earnest.
That's, that's pretty right on.
Yeah.
And it never got, it stayed second rate because there was never a door film.
Well, I didn't really have plans for the rest of the day and I guess they will be taken up by
searching door on YouTube, obtaining the rights to door.
So you can take the mantle.
Here's what I
think.
I think you'll have the most, like, I think you will be just like doubled over laughing for
six minutes and then it'll just kind of like turn to silence and like, huh, huh, how much more
for two?
I was going to hit you so hard and then just taper off.
I'm going to be begging for like
the thing Griffin told us about where Popeye meets all the King features syndicate characters.
That's really something that he, he proposed that in the last club three, he proposed that to us
and that he was like, even for you guys, this is too boring.
This is too unremarkable for you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Where were we?
Dorf.
Cold war.
Let's see.
Where were we?
Checkpoint Charlie.
Dorf.
Um, dude, we are immediately pop by Russian soldiers.
They see dwarf come and they're not
fucking around.
I can't make heads or tails of what that is.
Shoot him.
Um, anyway, but your, um,
dwarf was a communist.
Um, so you gave me, you had a question when we shut down for a second, which was
why would the, the hard rock cafe end up with this and put it behind their restaurant?
Yeah.
Um,
and you, and you said like, why would it, wouldn't a museum want this?
Um, and I think I'm sure that
I know that there are many pieces of the Berlin wall in museums.
Uh, that's definitely true,
but they, they seem to be sorta up for grabs for a little while.
Yes.
Cause a lot of odd places
have them.
Uh, my film school had one, Loyola Marymount university.
Uh, it was, uh, as I recall,
across from the Jamba juice.
Um, so I passed that a lot.
Yeah.
Uh, Chapman of film school.
I, I
liked it not to go to also has one.
I remember when I was deciding between the two, uh, Berlin wall
holding film schools in Southern California.
Um, the Reagan library has one.
Makes sense.
She said
the thing.
Um, the Nixon library has one and that, that covers a lot of, there is a website where
you can track where they all are across the world and in California.
I was curious about the
California ones.
Um, but mainly I was going through the website a little bit and like, okay,
if it's not somewhere stupid, I don't want to hear it.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
There's like museums and
stuff.
Of course.
When I was a kid, I saw one in DC at the new Zium.
If you remember the new Zium,
that was kind of the news and reporting journalism museum.
And then parts of the big stretches of it
are still up in Berlin.
And I went to one when I studied abroad there.
Um, and it was, uh, cool
and powerful to see, but have I thought about the Orlando one behind the Hard Rock cafe more?
Probably.
Yeah.
And that's why I'm done.
That's why I'm as dumb as Dorff.
But, uh, there's also, it's not the only Berlin wall segment in Orlando.
There is another one
elsewhere in the city.
Uh, that is at, there's a 10 foot by 10 foot panel in the Ripley auditorium
on international drive.
Ripley entertainment purchased 16 panels of the wall in the days
after it came down for $48,000 plus shipping.
Wow.
I didn't see how much it was.
That is not
a lot of money.
I feel like.
How much would you pay for a Berlin wall, Jason, if you had a pretty
big bank account?
Well, I thought, I thought $48,000 would be for one chunk of the wall.
Oh, 16.
How big is that?
10 by 10 is what they said.
10 by 10.
Yeah.
That's, that's because
the other ones are, I usually you see them as rectangles.
How big would you say this one is?
Like 10 by five or 10 by four?
Six maybe.
Yeah.
It's a little wider than that, but yeah.
And a little taller and a little, it might be like 12.
Chopped up maybe.
One by six.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Second market.
It's a little bit like a 2001 monolith.
Like a smaller white 2001
monolith.
It looks like the crystals in, or it looks kind of like it would be in the, um,
space or something by like a Zordon or something.
Yeah.
It looks, that's the shape of it.
I'm not
saying it's a crystal like that.
Yeah.
Uh, um, what do you notice when you look at it?
Let's
talk about what's on the wall.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
What's, what do you see on the piece itself?
Um,
dirt.
Yeah.
Nothing, right?
Nothing.
Yeah.
The one in my film school had some interesting
graffiti and, and, uh, a lot of them have just like pieces, like, uh, you know, just like, like
art and people expressing themselves and sending messages to people.
And the one back there just
has nothing.
And Chad H whose name I don't want to butcher claims in the comments, the Berlin wall
has no graffiti on it because a well-meaning maintenance employee didn't know the historic
value and power washed it.
Really?
Oh man.
Isn't that interesting?
That rules.
Oh no, better clean this wall.
This wall is full of, that's a kind of goof Dorf would make.
Yeah.
Dorf on maintenance.
Dorf in a museum, like a racing the Mona Lisa.
This, uh, I would encourage him to turn that power washer 10 feet to the left and get the hard rock
cafe a little more.
Torben museum is a good, I think.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Well, yeah.
A couple, well, you know, you know what he'd do is, and, uh, again, how uncultured I am, I can't name
the artist who did, whose piece was the urinal.
Um, but you're like, that's Duchamp.
Okay.
Uh,
you know, he'd be peeing in that Duchamp photo.
Yeah.
Perfect thing for Dorf to do.
Oh yeah.
He's covering up, uh, Michelangelo's David, of course.
Oh, he's a penis.
Yeah.
He's covering it up.
Oh yeah.
He just, he has, he just goes and gets a pair of underwear and then he can't figure out how
to, uh, get them on him because the feet, he's very heavy and the feet are stuck on the ground.
So he ends up in trying to put, uh, underwear on David.
He knocks it over, falls in.
And then
he's got to try to put it all back together.
Yeah.
I might put it in like some, some like
it knocks over a trash can and then there's like cups and wrappers that, sorry, what are you saying?
No, I was just gonna say he pokes his eye out with his dick.
Oh, well you can do both.
You can do both.
That happens first.
And now he knows it's a nuisance to children.
So he has to put underwear on him.
So he knocks it over, gets mixed up with trash can pieces.
And then a weird big trash David gets.
That might be a little lewd for the tapes.
I don't know what rating they were.
Plenty of room on that VHS.
Kids need to learn about art.
It's not pornographic.
It's, it's,
it's art.
And they, you know, if the way they need to learn that is by seeing
Dorf get poked in the eye by David's dick.
Dorf on, it's like Dorf on golf, Dorf on baseball,
whatever.
Dorf on David's dick.
Dorf would vector.
I, I, I'm amazed.
To be your Pluto have not made a call to like, we want Dorf.
You, you should be Dorf.
You should just start doing Dorf and don't even get the rights.
Oh, sure.
Just Jason as Dorf.
And you just do it.
And let's just see if something like the widow,
Katim Conway's widow comes after us.
They're, they're cheap to make.
It wouldn't take long.
I guess so.
Do you think there's, do you think it's important name recognition or would he get the
Dorf or Zorf?
Dorf.
Yeah, why not?
Well, that's, that happens if the widow sues us or if that's
the estate sues us.
Oh, then you just repackage all of it.
Yeah.
I mean all the, how many YouTubers
or whatever got famous just doing Jim Carrey's voices?
Uh, that one fucking idiot who just did
Shanaynay the Martin character, uh, just stole it whole cloth.
Yeah.
Uh, so that, you know,
yeah, just that, that's your way to YouTube fame is just start doing.
Yeah.
Dorf goes to the Bob's
Big Boy and Burbank with all the classic cars.
Mr.
Beast, Hunst, Dorf.
Well, that's a crossover
for later.
Yeah, I know.
That's once you're doing Mr.
Beast numbers, which is probably two, three
months away.
Yeah.
Um, if I could circle back around, I brought up the, the, there's a piece of
it at Ripley's.
Remember Ripley's in that same complex where we did our live show.
That was a
perfect, now that we've discovered that that place was sued by Universal because they wanted to call
it I walk.
And that's where the, uh, if you were going on a national treasure style hunt to put
the Berlin wall back up here, you could, that's where those are.
These are the two places you
stop in Orlando.
That is, that should be in, if they do a third national treasure, which are always
talking about, they just try to find a hunk of the wall that has like a codex or a secret message.
Hidden in it.
Oh yeah.
You have to search every hard rock to find it.
Every Mills outlet mall.
Uh, I was trying to fit that stumbling upon finding the hard rock piece
reminded me when I went to, uh, my old college roommate Jack's wedding in Staten Island.
Uh,
the wedding hotel was a Hampton Inn back kind of next to an office park.
So there was a few offices,
buildings, Hampton Inn, Hilton garden in with a cabaret that had a big sold out Joe Piscopo side.
So couldn't have stuck around from his cabal, but I was just went for a walk one day and was
walking around this like parking lot, some pathways and stumbled upon this giant like
chunk of metal and it was steel beams from the twin towers in the back of this office park.
And I
think it was, uh, you know, the plaque was a tribute that some hook and ladder companies from
Staten Island had responded.
It was like a plaque and this was a little.
Yeah, the plaque and then like a
piece.
Foot tall, like, um, you know, chunk of metal from the building.
I wonder if that's common.
It was just such an odd, it, it much like the Berlin wall piece was just kind of like so off the beat
and bare.
Why are they hiding all these things?
I don't know.
What's the agenda?
We hide, we hide
parts of our history.
Right.
And maybe that is what it is.
Maybe that's what we're getting.
I, where is, do we know where the Ripley's is, uh, where the wall is displayed in the Ripley's?
Is it first?
Is it end?
I think you, I think you got to pay to that's, that's past the paywall.
Oh, right.
Cause they don't want you.
Yeah.
Um, I think I'm not sure.
That's not just in an
office park.
Uh, um, I believe by the way, I believe Ripley's believe it or not.
I believe the wall.
I believe they had a wall.
Yeah.
It's not like a thing.
Oh, I believe it.
Like I believe it.
Denial of this, of all the things that are denied things in Ripley should really make me go, I don't
believe it.
Oh yeah.
Well, that's for other things.
That's for, you know, when there's like a statue
of a man who was nine feet tall or whatever.
Right.
I prove that.
But I, maybe, I don't know.
Maybe I don't believe it.
Those proportions seem strange.
There was, there was a wall that, uh,
divided Berlin.
I do believe it.
That's the believe it section.
The Cardiff giant drawing was like,
or not.
Yeah.
All right.
So they have a mix.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's what they give you the choice.
Unlike the multiverse right now.
We're trying to do is restore the balance.
Yes.
That's right.
Uh, um, I feel like I have an idea that I want to run.
Yeah, please remember guts.
I loved guts.
Yeah.
Instead of getting a glowing piece of the aggro crack, you should have gotten a little
piece of the wall of the Berlin wall or the aggro Berlin.
Oh, the Berlin wall.
Okay.
Well,
it was recent history then it had just been torn.
And like, what better way to, you know, we had a
lot of fun here on guts, but like, maybe you need to think about, uh, or put it at the base of the
crack and you had to climb over it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
Would have been a good, also a good
thing on legends of the hidden temple.
Like the, you know, yeah, make it talk like, oh, Mac,
could I, could I, could I also suggest that maybe there was a historical guts where at the end of
the show, kids would have to climb the Berlin wall.
Yeah.
What else would you have to do?
Well, you'd have to cross the Gettysburg, I think for sure.
Cross the Gettysburg.
No, no, what
12 miles of battlefield.
Like it's about folks.
You don't come to us for the history.
The what you know, you could recreate the crossing already.
Are you trying to say cross the Delaware?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cross the Gettysburg address.
The kids, the kids have to give, recite the address.
Maybe.
Well, right on the back of a train.
Yes.
Right.
But like that's like a Douglas debate
on the back of a train.
This is a good painting though is, is Washington crossing the Gettysburg
and then it's so the address is in on papers on the ground and it's just him stepping over it.
There's been some colossal blunders in the last few episodes.
Let's go to Moe.
Moe.
She's in a powder wig and we're subtracting points from all the boys.
All of them are mealy
mouthed, misremembering everything.
I don't think any of them have what it takes to go all the way.
That's right.
Back to you, sect to keep it.
And then whoever wins global history guts,
they get to enjoy being serenaded by Mr.
David Hasselhoff.
He once did a musical performance of
the wall.
Oh, okay.
Death defying segways.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh no, I got the tag.
I got the tab
open.
Oh, it's here.
You know, I'm thinking about the Hoff.
Of course.
Yeah.
Is it worth?
Yeah, of course.
It's always worth hearing.
Gasoloff sing.
Yeah, please.
The main thing is, yeah, he's wearing a light up jacket and then the like the tie is piano.
No,
it's a scarf that's piano keys.
You know, that that's stuff with him in Germany is definitely
true.
Really?
Yeah.
Lose their fucking mind.
I just saw some with it was some weird like opera
or classical performance where he made a surprise appearance and everybody lost their fucking minds.
It was an audience of entirely 60, 70 year olds.
I forget where maybe in Belgium or something.
Yeah.
And they I've never seen a crowd while out like this.
Fucking bananas other than the
half an hour earlier in the concert when Los del Rio showed up and did the Macarena.
Wow.
I don't
know what this is.
This I was thinking this might be there's also like a like this, like a some like
big hippo chase or something through again, this is a classical music concert and all of this happens
and we all look up what this is.
How recent?
I don't know last seven years or so.
Yeah,
it's really good.
Fairly recent.
Again, we will get cultured if you make historical restaurants,
if you if Haseloff shows up at our opera.
Only option we have now to remember anything about
American or world history.
We're too dumb.
We think you crossed the Gettysburg.
Club three knows how
dumb we are.
Fun fact about Gettysburg, I grew up Pennsylvania.
I've been to Gettysburg multiple
times.
Sure.
Just outside Gettysburg, the farm where they retired Dwighton Mamie Eisenhower.
You can tour the Eisenhower farm.
So that'll be something that would be on the global
history guts.
It's tour.
You have to go through the Eisenhower farm.
You got to leap over cows
at Dwighton Mamie Eisenhower.
That sounds good.
That sounds fun.
That's great.
Yeah, we're like
a basketball like while in a kayak next to his house.
Yeah, I think so.
And then the next step
becomes like, what if we don't do it on the farm?
What if history is not part of it?
What if it's
just a basketball kayak show?
Forget the history.
OK, here's OK.
So I think we all find this
kind of odd that it's there.
It's not what hard rock does.
Hard rock is about, you know, having
you know, like receipts that Fred Durst's you like that he got from clothing purchases, 30%
a real one from yesterday.
But, you know, so why do they have this piece here?
Why are they tied
into this?
What I have found is that Hard Rock Cafe has made a concerted effort to align their
brand with the brand Berlin Wall.
But there's a couple of steps to this one.
Of course, it
follows that there is a restaurant in Berlin.
There is a Hard Rock Cafe there in West Berlin,
less than three miles from where the wall stood.
That makes sense.
You have one of those in Berlin.
It's a major city.
What I didn't realize till a couple hours ago, one of the things they have
is a guitar that is made from one of the pieces of the Berlin Wall.
That's a real thing.
They
shaped some of it into a guitar shape.
Seems a bit impractical, but it is cool.
It was probably a real challenge for whatever
stone artisan and it, you know, it ended up looking like a prop from the Flintstones.
Definitely very silly.
But nonetheless, it's there.
Now, as we've discussed, Berlin is kind of in the
shadow of this, of the Cold War, of its division.
There's pieces of it that are still up to remember.
Then there is Checkpoint Charlie, after mentioned by Jason.
That is still a primary
tourist spot to remember the Cold War and reflect on it.
As of 2020,
literally there's the booth.
Checkpoint Charlie, which was a little booth where somebody stood,
where they try to keep people from crossing.
Here is, there's the booth and right behind it is
something called the Hard Rock Rock Shop.
It is literally at Checkpoint Charlie.
I kept double checking this.
Am I crazy?
It's at Checkpoint Charlie?
Yes, it is.
They have a rock shop right there and there's a ton
of touristy crap there, so it's not the only thing.
There's a coffee place, there's a McDonald's.
Checkpoint Charlie actually is kind of a stupid tourist trap place now.
This was a spot where
there was a showdown between US and Soviet tanks that lasted for several days, in which there was
genuine concern that nukes would be launched and a true nuclear war would begin because of what's
happening at this spot.
Now there's a Hard Rock Rock Shop at it.
It's like the ultimate capitalist twist of the knife.
Yeah, yeah, like Jason was saying, all of it combining in this weird confluence.
And can I just confirm that is a standalone Hard Rock gift shop.
It's not the restaurant.
It is only the shop.
The restaurant is two to three miles away and they only have,
it's pretty narrow, it is just a rock shop and it says Checkpoint Charlie on the window.
The only other place I've seen that was when Disney MGM Studios on the way to Tower Tower
had a standalone Planet Hollywood shop.
Oh yeah.
Even though the Planet Hollywood, the giant globe
one was miles away at then downtown Disney.
Hold on, hold on, help me out with this one.
A-bombs didn't drop, now it's a Hard Rock Shop.
If you could fit in the phone.
There's a couple more in there.
Now it's a Hard Rock Rock Shop.
Hard Rock Rock Shop.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that actually worked better.
That's great.
It fits right in.
It tells you everything you need to know in a way.
We didn't power wash the rock.
The new version.
99 Hard Rock Shops floating in the summer sun.
Anyway, they even, again, the desperation of Hard Rock Cafe to be aligned with the
Berlin Wall and the Cold War, they wanted to build a Hard Rock hotel there.
They ended up
getting rejected for that due to historical significance.
Okay, but could we build just
like a little shop though?
Yeah, yeah, sounds good.
You could do that.
They really want you,
when you hear Hard Rock Cafe, to think of Berlin Wall.
Because it's the most famous piece of Hard
Rock.
Whoa.
That's what I'm thinking.
Wow, wow.
Because they can't get a piece.
The original
Hard Rock.
The wall predated the existence of Hard Rock music.
Right.
Wow.
So they have all
your favorite artists of rock and Hard Rock.
And now this is literally a famous piece of Hard Rock.
What else would they want?
Great Wall of China, but that's not, they're not.
They'd want a piece
of that for sure.
That's more famous.
I feel like that's the more famous wall.
Maybe more famous.
Stonehenge.
It's not really a wall though, but they're famous pieces of rock.
It's Hard Rock.
Yeah, you're right.
No, you're right.
Sorry.
What are we arguing here?
We're saying that they want
Hard Rock.
You're right.
They would want Stonehenge.
They'd want
the Ten Commandments.
They want to track down the actual true Moses held Ten Commandments.
Right.
Well, now we're actually,
wait a minute.
We don't even need a new brand that's the History Cafe.
If they would just branch out
definition of Hard Rock to be important historical Hard Rocks.
Yes.
Yeah.
This has to be part
of it.
This is good.
What about like rocks that stoned people to death?
Well, can you name a famous
one?
I know I was trying to, I don't know.
I mean, it's the one that slayed Goliath.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm in a little bit of a church peril.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
You've been,
you've been going to church.
Yeah.
Jason's been letting you say all the church stuff too.
Thanks, Jason.
He's testing.
Well, he's testing.
Yeah.
My catechism home.
You guys aligning on the, you guys staying with each other has been great
because I was worried I would have to put you up for a while.
I got a kid in there.
It just makes
sense for you to stay with Jason.
It makes a lot of sense.
And I'm glad you've been doing it for so many days.
Yeah.
Me crashing with Jason's for sure.
And I got, I got you, man.
I know I owe you rent for a couple
months now.
Well, you know, yeah, you do what you can.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thank you.
So I didn't mean
nothing, but you did win the Powerball.
Sure.
Yeah.
You did win the Powerball.
As
soon as the Venice Beach Boardwalk keeper Venmo's me, I'll Venmo you.
You might be waiting for a while.
He's got a, you know, pay you in Maserati paintings that man, Michael Ferrari,
Michael Ferrari, excuse me.
Maserati.
It's close.
It's the Maserati of paintings for sure.
But yeah.
Well, as we search for significance here, do they want hard rocks because that's in their name?
What is the greater meaning?
Why the why?
I, I, and I'm about to read a listener comment,
but I also want to, I also want to read Chad Kinsell Mo in his voting for this topic.
He said
you had me at behind the hard rock cafe.
He's right.
That is definitely, that's a big,
that's a big part of the why it's really strange.
The mystery of it, the journey
that you have to take.
I actually honestly loved as I talked about yesterday, because there's so
much space in the hard rock cafe that there's many giant empty rooms.
I kind of had some moments of
peace there.
Yeah.
It was otherwise a very hectic trip and I felt the same way.
Just like getting a
little stroll and no one's back here in the calm of night and I can't hear the imagined dragons that
much.
And then you go back and you reflect on history, but not really because you got to get
back to the NBC sports grills and meet Mike to get some bad chicken sliders.
But anyway, I, I think
the behind is a big part of it, but here's the other one.
I was so, by the time this comment was
written, I was like, it has to win.
And this is another comment from Chad H whose name I will not
butcher.
After he revealed that it has no graffiti because it was power washed.
He kept discussing
his love of this spot and why it's not on any map and has no signage pointing to it.
This is almost
like the, like, but he was, but a humble carpenter.
Yeah.
Not a care did he have, not a penny to his
name.
It has no signage pointing to it.
To see it, you have to walk so far that it feels like you've
gone somewhere you're not supposed to be.
I ripped off your point, Chad.
Your reward is a blank slab
of concrete.
It's my favorite place in all of City Walk.
My own personal hemisphere dancer story to
tell people.
I would be forever delighted to have it immortalized in a saga and appreciate any support.
And while Chad, isn't that beautiful?
And where we've had so much like disappointment and
sickness and borderline food poisoning and all of that, that can't happen here.
There's no food
available here.
All there is to do is take a quiet walk and look at a blank slab of concrete.
Chad,
I think really put it in context.
I think that is beautiful.
And I think, yeah, I think anybody who
goes down there, go and check it out and take a couple of minutes and appreciate it because
I think it's very soon where the plant life will completely overtake it.
The way it looks like things are going.
They're letting some, I don't know, tree or bushes sort of
start to get in the way.
Yeah.
So I just appreciate it while you can.
That's what I'm
saying.
Not be available to see soon enough.
Yeah.
And do you, one of you have pictures?
We took some pictures, but I didn't find them on my phone.
I think I might have them on my
phone.
Yeah, we took some very somber photos.
So you will see us paying our tributes, but honestly,
the face that we're making, it's less about what happened now.
And I think more about what Chad
said about it.
When you see the pictures, think of us paying homage to that, these sentiments.
Yeah.
You know what?
I think this was a nice little bit of calm.
Yeah.
And we got,
there's less people listening now.
I feel the calm of that too.
Smaller audience.
We're only
friends here.
Yes.
An intimate moment.
Wow.
You know, we do always sign off with that,
the optimist prime line.
And I guess we, yeah, we are providing a moment of intimacy.
We should
all, let's take the voices down.
A moment of intimacy with you, the listeners from us.
That's what you want.
And then the sector keeper is always a little soft.
Yeah.
Wait.
You
like, is there something, actually, is there something special that we can do for the listeners
that's like that the sector keeper showing his appreciation just for only the club three
subscribers?
I don't know.
Whatever you want to make that if you want to just like tell them you
love them or that they, they, and they alone give you strength or yeah.
Club three listeners,
you give me strength and I'm proud of you.
Wow.
That was gorgeous.
That was beautiful.
Yeah.
I was going to ask what the stone is.
Oh yeah.
Oh, after all that, what's the stone?
The stone
is appearing in front of you.
You see it's a beautiful painting of Shaq as door in a powdered
wig crossing the Gettysburg.
Wow.
Finally some art and history worth caring about.
Oh my God.
You've given it.
You've given us such a gift here.
You gave the listeners such a gift sector keeper.
We thank you and we honor you.
We thank you.
The club three audience for selecting this topic,
for surviving this episode of podcast, the ride, the city walk, Orlando saga,
multiverse of madness here on club three.
Your bravery has saved the city walk,
Orlando saga, multiverse of madness.
Well done freedom fighters.
Thanks Aaron for the art.
Thanks to Mike and Zach for the theme music.
Keep it subscribed here where you always get to pick
the topic and where all of the episodes will be coming out ad free.
Hasn't that been nice too?
No intrusion.
Yeah.
It's really just trying to give you, give you a calm.
Like heaven plus.
Yes.
This is, this is your own personal heaven plus.
And tomorrow we'll go back across the lake and we'll see who we find over there.