Forever.
Dog.
Audience, audience, when we last left the Good Boys, they were ripped apart from each other and scattered into different corners of the multiverse.
The only way they can fix the dimensional rift and reunite is to record separate solo podcasts about stuff at malls next to theme parks.
We take you now to Jason's End of the Multiverse.
We hear.
Welcome to the Pepcast, the number one Bucca de Pepo fancast.
I'm your host, the Baron of Breadsticks, the Maestro of Marinara, Jason Sheridan.
Today we're talking baked CD and I've got two great guests.
My first guest, she's a writer for the blog Carian, a part of Unorque magazine.
Pethys Squires is here.
Pethy, how are you?
It's great to be here.
I'm full of pep.
Oh, thanks.
Great.
That's what we want here at the Pepcast.
My other guest, you know her.
She's a stylist.
She's also my love, my girlfriend, Claire Jane.
How are you, Claire?
I'm good.
I'm doing good.
I'm also happy to be here.
I put our cat Odie in the bedroom just so like, you know, he wouldn't escape.
Yeah, Odie is a real handful.
So how are you all doing a couple days after a lovely Bucca meal?
I'm feeling pretty good, pretty level.
Yeah, it was a nice time, you know.
It was a time.
Oh, it was quite a time, all right.
Now, I'm learning that next to Bucca, not only is there a theme park,
there's this outdoor shopping and dining destination called City Walk.
And I had you both on because I figured maybe you could educate me.
You both spent a lot of time up there at City Walk, correct?
Yeah, definitely.
I've hit some of the shops there, some of the,
I guess you could call it food establishments up there.
You don't know anything about it, OK?
I don't know anything.
Yeah, you used to work at the theme park.
Now, how did you hide this in our relationship for so long?
Well, I'm an actor, and that's why I worked at Universal Studios Hollywood,
because I'm an actor.
Like, I don't want to, you know, the first time guest, longtime listener.
Jason, you talk about Bucca de Pepo a lot, and I think maybe it just,
you're so focused on the Pepo that some details of other people's lives don't come through.
Well, yeah, that's true.
And, you know, I usually get out of a taxi in front of Bucca.
I go right in to the Pepo and I come right out.
And I've often asked myself, like, what's all that racket over there?
All that sound and light.
But I had never really investigated until we went up there.
Bright lights, big city, baby.
Oh, yes.
Good.
Pethy, you said you were wearing some items from this location.
Yeah, I know it's weird, but I like theme parks.
I mean, I'm just weird like that, I guess.
And yeah, I go there a lot.
I'm an annual pass holder.
And I do, I just happen to be wearing my old Hard Rock pendant from when there used to be a Hard Rock there.
It's, of course, now a Wonka's Emporium.
And then I have socks on from the Los Angeles sock exchange.
They have a store there that's just socks.
It's great.
Oh, wow.
You should go.
Yeah, I can't say I've ever heard anything like that.
But enough of talking about other establishments.
Let's get into our Pepo meal.
Now, we had kind of a mix of stuff, you know, we tried a variety of items.
Pethy, you had a Martini?
I see vodka on the receipt.
I had an espresso martini.
How was that?
It was fine when it got there.
I don't, look, I know this restaurant means a lot to you and I don't want to come in hot.
Oh, please be honest.
Don't hold anything back.
We are no holds barred here.
Okay.
I worry that Bucatepepo is a dark nexus in the American culture.
Interesting take.
Have not heard that one before.
Please go on.
So the espresso martini, it took a long time to get there because we were sat upstairs.
And it seems like maybe the people who have to work upstairs don't like it.
Because as I was walking up the stairs, I heard a server stomping down and said,
I'm not running shit up there.
And then see me and deer in the headlights, fear in her eyes and just she is zoomed past me.
Okay.
That's the first time I've ever heard anyone talk negative about the area that I call the bird's nest.
And so, yeah, we, Claire and I took the elevator because I, you know, have little difficulty getting around sometimes.
What did you think about that elevator, Claire?
Well, it was interesting because it was very small, windowless.
And as you were using it and going up or down, there were boot, boot, boot.
It's okay.
It's called Boca de Pepo.
Yeah, yeah, that's okay.
And there were.
There were Boca ads.
We were laughing about that.
Like we're already here in the restaurant, Robert Earl.
You don't have to sell the restaurant to us.
To entice us, I guess, to get to our table upstairs.
And it kind of smelled, but it also took a long time.
It was pretty fun.
It was a long elevator.
It almost seemed like a large dumb waiter that we were told to go into.
We also could not operate it ourselves.
Someone had to begrudgingly get us in and out of it.
Yeah.
And then meanwhile, the stairs just has the ugliest murals you've seen in your life.
Just faces that are so close to looking like human faces.
Okay.
All right.
Well, this is again.
This is a unique episode 99 and we're finally getting some criticism.
So that's great.
That's great.
Like the the people on the Reddit will be happy about the Pepo Reddit.
And check that out, everyone.
Also, please check out our drip page.
That's the crowdfunding website started by Kickstarter.
It's a big hit.
Our drip keeps growing and growing.
Soon it'll be what's bigger than a drip.
Anyone?
I don't know.
Drizzle.
Oh, soon it'll be a drizzle.
I like that a lot.
Well, I'm going to have to say that more often.
So keep keep giving to that drip account.
And as you know, I don't even have to keep saying it.
It's a website we all visit on a daily basis.
It's a huge hit.
So let's get into our meal.
We started off with a small mixed green salad.
What did you both think about this?
I thought it was it was fine.
A lot of iceberg lettuce.
I got really excited about the olives and realized there were only like two.
And then the one I got also had a piece of a pit in it, which was a surprise.
But, yeah, you know, a nice little little starter white salad.
Yeah, you know, normal, normal salad.
Olive garden ask.
I don't know if we can't mention other Italian chains here, but it's about this.
I mean, that's OK.
That's OK.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry.
I, you know, fine.
We did say fine a lot this meal in for a mixed green salad.
And it did have an awful lot of iceberg lettuce.
Yeah, one green, one green salad.
Yeah, that's pretty funny.
Yeah, it is a one green salad.
It wasn't really mixed at all.
And yeah, there wasn't a lot of olives.
I ate one of the two.
I do not like olives.
I kind of didn't realize I was eating it.
You took a precious olive away and you didn't mean to or you didn't enjoy it.
And you took it away.
That's a slap in the freaking face, man.
Why did you do that?
It's a salad for three people and there's on pit.
You will.
OK.
Exactly.
And you took one.
Oh, I'm kind of mad.
Look, that's fine.
I was at the meal kind of it kind of threw me off my game.
Honestly, I have the you you had said like, oh, we have to try the giant meatballs.
We have to try the kind of a signature there.
And if I can get in on the criticism game a little, these were the driest meatballs
I've ever eaten in my in my life.
But it was very fun.
And you took one home to your husband.
How did they feel about it?
I think they felt it was fine.
You know, we had to cut it in half to get it into the container
because they didn't have a container big enough for the giant meatballs.
Yeah, it was a little surprising to not get a custom meatball container because it's kind of a signature there.
Like you could use like those boxes, corsages come in and then everyone could see the beautiful meatball.
I think that would really elevate the take home presentation.
I mean, I can put that in my next letter to Robert Earl.
He hasn't answered any of the other ones, but I can certainly try.
Also, looking at our bill at the end, I've got the receipt here to go in my scrapbook of Bucca receipts.
Those three giant meatballs worth thirty dollars, which breaks down to roughly ten dollars a meatball.
And I'm not quite sure about the economics of that.
Yeah, I wanted to get the meatballs because some of my favorite pictures ever taken are of
Vigara holding giant meatballs at Bucca di Beppo.
And that's what I wanted to show these to you.
I mean, I'm sure as an old hand, you've probably seen them before.
But specifically, this one of her doing a sort of what I think of as Larry David in whatever works hand gesture.
Oh, my God.
She's got a whole table full of giant meatballs.
Hundreds of dollars of meatballs.
It was a fundraiser that she would do there called Meatballs for Ni単os.
I'm not sure what it raised money for.
But she did it a couple of times.
Look, celebrity fundraisers, that money doesn't just disappear or anything.
So I'm assuming it probably went to the Ni単os.
The Ni単os.
Shit out of luck, I'm guessing.
Ripped to the Ni単os.
God, it's such a man's world.
Women can't have anything.
I swear to God.
But is this a good time for me to bring up the other pictures of celebrities at Bucca di Beppo?
Yes, please.
So at my work at Cariann, I have access to like a big Getty database.
And so one day I just searched Bucca di Beppo and there is, I think, 47 pages of people getting their picture taken.
Forty seven pictures?
No, 47 pages.
Wow.
Fifty pictures per page.
What?
This is my dream.
Of people getting their picture taken at the Times Square, Bucca di Beppo.
And it's, okay, here is a woman who I'm told is famous.
Oh, is this Angie from Jersey Shore or Gina or whatever?
I don't know, but that's quite a picture.
She's holding meatballs in her hands over her boobs, like on them.
Oh, as if they were breasts.
I see.
It's a sort of simulacrum, yeah.
And then here's Snooki and Jwoww.
And they do the thing that a lot of people do there where, so when you're a celebrity and you go to Bucca di Beppo,
hopefully this will happen for you someday,
they present a bowl of marinara and you dip your hands in it like Grauman's Chinese theater.
And then you put it on the wall.
You put your hands on a piece of paper.
Then they frame just rotting tomato sauce with your signature on it.
And that's just up there now.
I mean, I've done this recreationally and they don't seem to like it any time I do it.
And there's three types of people who seem to go do the handprint thing at the Bucca di Beppo Times Square.
It's Miss Universe or Miss USA.
Wait.
Sorry, I'll add it out later.
Professional poker, like World Series of Poker Champion.
And underage Disney stars.
And that's it.
The trifecta of fame.
Oh my God.
Well, sorry I had interrupted you, but I did like two pageants when I was younger in Florida, like in my 20s, not like baby.
But I remember like the girl who won, they would often do like events at the Bucca.
And I just thought it was like, oh, that's just where like in town they like whatever.
I feel like there is like a legit like maybe corporation something kind of tie in.
Because it's not the first time I've heard about like pageantry and Bucca.
I'm not kidding you.
No, that tracks me right because I think Robert Earl has his hands in a lot of pizza pies.
Is this a good time to bring up the housewives of it all?
Yes, you also mentioned Housewife Connection.
Yeah, Robert Earl shows up on Real Housewives of Beverly Hills and Vanderpump roles like some like more than I would assume a chain restaurateur would.
I mean, he's a star.
After Miss Universe, World Series of Poker Players and Child Actors, Robert Earl is like number four or number one, like above all those people in terms of the fame game, at least my fame game.
Sure.
And so he the first time I noticed him was I was watching an episode of Vanderpump Rules and he goes with Lisa Vanderpump to check out what will eventually become Pump Restaurant in WeHo, which is since closed during Scandival.
But he's just like, it's going to be fabulous here.
And Lisa Vanderpump of course makes some joke that like the gay waiters are going to blow him and he's like, oh you and it's very like that energy.
Oh my God.
Lisa always has.
And then in an episode of Real Housewives of Beverly Hills, there was a whole arc where he had Dorit decorate a room in the Encino Bucatipepo.
Oh, I've always wanted to go there.
Yeah, my dream.
Okay, we're going to talk about the other thing that the Encino Bucatipepo is famous for near the end.
Let's get through some happiness first.
Okay.
We can't wait.
But yeah, so there's a there was a huge fight at the Encino Bucatipepo in the Capri room when
it was this whole thing where where Brandi Glanville said that she had slept with Denise Richards and Denise Richards said that they didn't even really know each other and blah blah blah blah blah.
But if you've ever wanted to see a woman having like full body sobs claiming that she ate somebody out in a Bucatipepo
season 10 finale of Real Housewives of Beverly Hills.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time I experienced something like that.
But, you know, you do a podcast long enough you've seen everything.
And I mean restaurants.
It's this, you know, it's a very event heavy restaurant and, you know, tensions are running high.
People are stressed out about whether the party is going to happen while we were there.
There was a book publishing.
Okay, so from what I can gather, it was like maybe also a birthday party, but it was also like very clearly very like, you know, a group of religious people.
They did all do a mass prayer together.
And this was a pretty big long table.
And then at one point it was just us in there with them.
So I caught a woman going, okay, Jeremy, this is why I'm grateful for you.
I never really had a brother like you because my real brothers didn't do it.
And I believe God brought you to me.
And I was like, we got to get the fuck out of here.
And I was scooting out of a very, the very tight booth we were sitting in.
And I'm like, oh, someone is giving a very heartfelt toast.
I should get out of here.
And then we got around the corner and Claire here was like, those people were very religious.
And I was like, this is probably not the best time to bring up.
I bought two copies of those books.
So but one for each of us, dear.
Thank you.
You got to commemorate every.
That's true.
Yeah.
So just kind of off my game now.
I almost said, who could the Beppo earlier?
Like, I know you said it's OK.
It's very common.
It's very common mistake.
But BDP, that doesn't even make sense as an abbreviation.
Let's get to the big CD.
The reason we're all here today.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's fine.
Yeah, it was.
It was fine.
I liked the the Rosa sauce, which I think they just mix the red sauce and the white sauce together,
like in a pitcher and then pour it over the CD.
The sauce pitcher.
Yeah.
OK.
So that's like a known thing.
The sauce pitcher.
You know, you walk through the kitchen and you can see a little bit of how it's being made.
I I did realize that the I guess chef's table, you might call it,
when we were leaving was actually just the workers eating their food at that table.
It was just the workers table.
So I thought that was interesting because I thought it was like a, you know,
a special experience, more just like a little break room that's invisible to everybody.
Yeah, I was kind of disappointed by that.
That's supposed to be a whole experience and appeared to be two men all in black having their like family meal.
Yeah, their shift meal.
Yeah.
What a shift meal to have.
Dorit spoke lovingly of eating at the chef's table at the Encino Bucatipepo.
We must go.
That Capri room makes you feel like you're on the island of Capri.
And I don't know how they manage that with just a bunch of false lemons.
And white enamel.
Hey, very good.
Oh, wow.
White enamel.
Nice.
Fake lemons and white enamel.
I will say the the chef's table at the CityWalk Pep is very close to the bathrooms and also obviously like kitchen adjacent.
So while we were leaving, it was getting closer to close time.
And so I think they were breaking down the kitchen and that whole area just smelled like bleach.
So maybe like so, you know, good on them for staying sanitary, you know, keep that A rating.
Love it.
Work it, girl.
But not the most pleasurable eating experience if they just douse the whole place in bleach.
I agree.
I didn't love that the just me personally, sound a little bit of a germaphobe.
I didn't love that the bathrooms were like literally like right basically like in the kitchen.
Like, I don't know, it just kind of weirded me out because it also a little bit felt like maybe it was like the employee restroom.
Like you're in the back of the kitchen.
This might just be a me thing.
I do have bathroom like OCD.
But I was like, what did it love in our area?
There was like an upstairs like chef or not chef, like waiters station.
And it was like adjoining our room because, you know, like all all buka de pepo's have sort of like warren's of little intimate dining rooms.
Oh, yes.
Ours was next to like their prep area, which also meant it was next to their like throw away trash area.
So near the end of the night also, I did get a whiff of just the trash from that room coming into our dining area.
Yikes.
Yeah, I think we're starting to see like a good 30 plus years of this place being open.
Maybe they should knock some walls down.
Maybe they've taken the intimate Italian restaurant thing as far as one can take it.
But you don't enjoy being in a really nice intimate room with multiple screaming toddlers running around as well and having meltdowns.
I mean, I think it built to the ambiance.
It certainly adds to the ambiance of every wall surface being covered in pictures.
And going from that to very loud prayer gatherings was was a bit of a shock.
But, you know, hey, let's let's go to something else positive every time I go to buka de pep.
I got to order the Buddy V's cake slices and we we did two.
We restrained ourselves.
We didn't get three.
So this time we did the rainbow cake and the black and white cake.
What did you all think of these cakes?
They were very pretty.
But the second you like put a fork near them, the levels just all kind of split apart.
But the contrast of the colors was really nice.
It was it was, you know, it was cake and the fudge frosting on the chocolate one, like in between the layers.
That was pretty good.
It tastes like chocolate.
The cake didn't really taste a lot like chocolate, but the fudge in between, I will say that icing was quite good.
I don't want to be like a weird conspiracy theorist or anything, but I kind of got you to be.
I got the sense that maybe they added extra oil to the cake to make it seem moist for longer.
I don't want to be like insane here, but it did say a little oily.
Oh, that's a really good point.
That's interesting because the parts I got like the meatballs were very dry.
Hmm.
It is.
Well, the icing, I mean, hey, something positive.
You always want to hear the chocolate icing tastes like chocolate.
That's a positive.
It was the in between the layers because the top there was still white icing, right?
Yeah, there was the white icing and like the little jimmies on the end.
And that tasted like nothing.
Yeah, it really didn't taste like anything.
It barely tasted like sugar, you know?
Sometimes you can taste frosting and it's like, oh, this is just clearly sugar.
It kind of just tastes like paste.
Like it just was like paste.
So I think I said that night that it kind of had the feeling of eating food in a dream where your brain kind of knows you're not tasting anything.
I still don't know if we really eat that cake.
I agree with you.
I totally get what you're saying.
Buddy Valestro like Robert Earl.
I'm shocked with let something be seemingly less than stellar quality.
You know what?
You're probably right.
Just, you know, I think but speaking of Buddy Valestro, Robert Earl and 30 years of Buka, I know you try to focus on the food and stay out of the politics.
OK.
On the show.
You don't like bringing up, you know, dark stuff randomly.
No, I'm scared of it.
I'm scared of most things on topic.
100 percent.
That's the Jason Sheridan promise.
Yes.
But I do feel like I have to talk a little bit about the history of Buka Di Peppo.
OK.
So it was founded by not Robert Earl, but a different guy who's Phil Roberts, different Robert, Phil Roberts, who not Italian in the slightest.
He said that he wanted to make a restaurant that people could look down on.
That's a direct quote.
Oh, my God.
We don't.
I like I kind of reword that quote sometimes of something people could look up on.
OK.
He wouldn't love that, but that's OK.
So his idea was he wanted to do like a parody of Italian red sauce joints and put all of the trashiest like Italian stereotyping he could find on the walls.
Oh, my God.
But he hired a Milanese chef to make the food.
So the food was not a joke, but the walls and he wanted in the wine list, he wanted to make sure that people felt superior while they were dining there.
He said that he knew that he had he had done a good job when he was walking by a couple and a couple pointed to his statues that I would never have that thing in my house.
And he was like, yes, I did it.
Oh, my God.
So that it starts becoming a larger chain and they hire a new CEO who's actually Italian American Joseph Micotrato from Cleveland, who he goes he starts saying that Bucatipeppo is named after.
I'm so sorry.
I did it again.
Bucatipeppo is named after.
Peppo, Peppo.
Like you got some pep in your step after eating a couple pounds of pasta.
The story just doesn't make me feel peppy.
He says that his his that the place is named after his grandpa Peppo and that all of the recipes that the Milanese chef had created were his grandmother's recipe book.
OK, yeah, I didn't know a lot of this story.
I did know about Grandpa Peppo.
Yeah, I mean, Grandpa Peppo becomes like a huge part of the mythology even after this guy later leaves because he was charged with stealing more than two hundred thousand dollars from the company to buy an Italian villa.
OK, well, that's all of our dreams.
Because, you know, I've been working pretty diligently my day job, of course, at the Los Angeles Hazardous Waste Disposal site, and I've been trying to save up money for years now to get that villa.
You know, I'm very passionate.
My two passions in life, Bucatipeppo and proper hazardous waste disposal.
It's more important now than ever.
Don't throw out your batteries.
You certainly don't throw out your lithium ion batteries.
Properly dispose of them, folks.
So then it's bought by Robert Earl, who combines it with Planet Hollywood.
The Bucatipeppo in New York is also Planet Hollywood.
And that's why, OK, all of those Disney stars were there, I guess.
I hope.
Yeah, that makes a little more sense.
But like, yeah, that's still OK.
All right.
Continue, continue.
And then the last thing and then we can we can wrap up on a nice note.
I just have to get this out there because it's my first thought.
Anytime I see a Bucatipeppo is the Encino Bucatipeppo, the one with Dorit's Capri room was also where Phil Hartman's wife had her last meal before, you know.
Oh my God.
OK.
This is.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I know you don't like bummer.
Yeah, no.
Weird history.
And I'm really sorry to do this to you.
That's that's like that Vitello Studio City Italian restaurant that I don't even want to set foot in because last meal where Robert Blake and his wife shared a meal before the murder.
Yeah, I don't know.
Did she get to finish that meal?
Anyway, let's talk about the dessert.
So not the best buddy V-cakes I've ever had, but that's OK, because, hey, we bought the picture.
You know, I got to get the picture.
We went for the black and white one, which, you know, as we're in a criticism mood today does make us look like we all died in a plane crash.
But that's OK.
It's in a frame.
And I it was like a flat picture frame, like, you know, thick paper.
But then I opened the back so you can actually make it like look propped up.
And it does really kind of look like that.
But also it's really cute.
It is a pretty cute picture.
And we all kind of work work together to choose a lovely photographer actually got to us before our food.
We are seated at an largely empty table.
We have some waters and an iced tea.
I don't have my martini.
Excuse me.
I almost called you Bethy.
Yeah, you didn't even have your martini yet.
So but a great picture quality.
And they gave us three to choose from.
And I guess they just you know, I was wondering this.
So do they just throw those ones away?
I mean, I guess maybe obviously, but also that is so many pictures to waste.
And like, you know, do they maybe go somewhere else?
Is it at some restaurant somewhere in another place where they're just like, we'll give you pictures of people that, you know, like, I don't know where they maybe Robert Earl has a large surveillance network.
And this is a record of everyone has been there.
And they're doing they're doing training face recognition AI on all of our discarded Buka picks.
Look, I spent 99 episodes trying to figure out where all the other photos go.
And, you know, Occam's Razor, the simplest solution is likely the right one.
So they probably just end up in a garbage dump.
But also, they could be training AI.
Who knows?
Where do the pictures go, Robert?
What's going on?
Oh, man, this really gives me a lot to think about that.
Hey, let's let's get to our rating.
Of course, every episode, we rate our meal on a scale from Robert Earl to Robert Earl.
Clary, what do you what do you think?
Let's start with you.
You know, I think I'm going to split the difference and just give it a Robert.
Great.
Middle of the road.
Pethy.
Yeah, I would I would go with just a across the board Robert.
Yeah.
Like a yeah.
A Robert E.
One more than that.
OK.
Slightly above.
All right.
And I'm going to give it a Robert E.
A.
because I just can't bring myself to call it anything lower.
This was a hard one.
OK.
Now let's, you know, head for the pasta portal.
Who's got some plugs?
The pasta plug portal.
Yeah, I have a zine that I just finished making called Girlzine.
It's about all the girl stuff from last year.
For some reason, it's under Bethy Squires, not Pethy Squires.
That's also my Twitter is at Bethy B.
Q.
S.
You and Instagram, Bethy Squires.
And, you know, you can always find me at Carrie and blog at Unorak Mag.
Great.
Claire, anything you want to talk about or plug?
I just want to say I think Pethy is like so cool and like genuinely.
I just want to give her like props because she rocks.
But I am a stylist.
So if you have any events coming up or you just want to closet refresh
or you just want a little consultation, you can hit me up.
I'm at Jane Claire styling because at Claire Jane styling was taken.
So I had to like do the stupid swap thing.
So you can find me there and say hi.
Great.
As for me, folks, next episode, very exciting episode 100,
we're finally tackling spaghetti and meatballs.
Little Meatball Talk today to get everyone fired up.
You know, and our guest, we had to get a big guest for this episode.
And folks, it's a big get.
It's like a big giant meatball size get.
It's the totally epic former vice president, Tim Kaine.
That's right.
Tim Kaine in the membrane.
Tim Kaine in the brain.
We're going to talk about a totally epic term as VP under President Clinton,
a term that happened just before the event.
But we're not here to talk about sad stuff like the event.
We're here to talk.
Peppo, Boogie the Peppo, to be precise.
None of that Peppo nonsense.
No, it's Boogie the Peppo.
I've been your host, Jason Sheridan.
Thank you so much for joining me and we'll see you next week on the Pepcast.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production, executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.
Thank you.