Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a dough that's soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll.
With alcohol, a place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where seam-punk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando.
Tonight, tonight.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride presents the City Walk Saga Orlando.
Multiverse of madness.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And Scott Gardner.
Happy Sunday.
It's just a, it's a podcast that comes out on a Sunday when you've already,
it has already been one, the two previous days, a full week.
And it's not the only full weekend of podcasts coming your way.
I assume you're in church right now, quietly listening to this,
hoping that like your wife or husband don't notice that you have the headphones in or the earphone,
like a little like Bluetooth earpiece in.
Just one AirPod, which I, I got AirPods a few months ago.
I have lost my left AirPod somewhere in my apartment and it's driving me crazy.
Have you gone?
Post move.
So it's, you know, it came with you.
And also the fine by was telling me like it is in this place,
but there's not enough battery to make a sound to ping it.
So, yeah.
Have you gone to church with it though recently?
Well, that's usually my right one.
Oh, you only bring one to church.
I bring one.
So I hold the Bible with the left or the hymnal book,
hold that with the left hand.
And then I've got like, you know,
you insist on Isle so that nobody you're with can look down, you know, you like,
I'll take the, you know, I kind of like, you know,
so I can get up to the bathroom if I need to.
And then nobody sees that.
Yeah, no one sees except the offering collectors.
Those I got to pay them off for the rat on me.
Yeah.
I try to pull it out really quick, then give them the money, but do not give them.
You're sure you didn't know it's in the apartments.
You did not give it to.
I did not give it to them this time.
Okay.
And what are you what are you usually listening to?
Huh?
What are you usually listening to?
Oh, the game.
The big game.
Okay.
Whatever the biggest game is on.
The biggest game that's on.
Yeah.
We're recording this before the biggest game.
It hasn't happened yet.
And I only say that I don't say the real name of it because as with commercials,
you're not allowed to say I don't want I don't know how that applies on podcasts,
but I don't want any trouble.
Well, every game.
So I call it the biggest game.
Every game is a big game when good sportsmanship is involved.
That's the spirit.
Yeah, that is.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
Speaking of spirit, though, you know, we do have we're being joined by one of our favorite
spirits, maybe our favorites next to well, Casamigos is my favorite spirit, I would say.
But second is the sector keeper who is returning.
Boys, boys, thank you for having me back.
Good to see you.
And the Holy Spirit.
Don't forget.
Sector keeper.
Are you with Jason and Church sort of just like in the background?
Always.
Yes, I go to church on Sundays with Jason.
We do the 10 a.
m.
Mass, sometimes the five p.
Mass if he's sleepy.
Sure.
And then a show is in between.
Oh, well, you go to both of them.
Huh?
Oh, wow.
With a long show.
He's break.
Jason calls it the double holy header.
Oh, wow.
There's two places of worship.
Yeah, that's nice.
I didn't realize you guys were so religious.
Well, you know, it's good to keep in touch.
Something to do.
Keep in touch with my old pal, God.
Yeah, that is.
Have we talked about this that the sector keeper existing is proof that God exists?
I don't think we have.
We have.
We actually.
Well, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, because you've been to hell and everything.
He doesn't want to go to hell.
That's one of the first things he told us that if we didn't complete the first city
walk, that his soul would burn in hell.
It's well, you know, it's a little more complicated that you guys have written it out here on Earth.
But, you know, heaven, hell, jump portals.
Oh, OK.
This is this is all.
I'm glad you're this is why I'm glad you're filling us in because the Bible left all that stuff out.
They like the Bible, very clean, very precise.
Right.
You're to fill us in on how the universe really works.
It came close.
Matthew came close to keeping it in his Bible, but he opted out.
So he had an editor that took it out because it was too convoluted.
And the book was Matthew's editor.
Oh, I know the writers of the book.
You've met the people who wrote the Bible.
It's more of a collaboration.
It's like a writer's room.
Oh, interesting.
So it's like a mini room or something like they have in Hollywood these days.
All of Jesus's work.
Oh, a lot of consult of the disciples were consultants, producers.
Right.
Yeah.
So they didn't get their credit.
They deserved no, no residuals on any of the Bibles you've read.
Luke and Matthew haven't seen a sin.
Really?
Oh, that's Luke's family and descendants are not profited on recent sales of the Bible.
No, no.
And they had a chance to renegotiate with the new when they wrote the new test.
Right.
That makes sense.
Unlike David Schwimmer and friends holding out for favored nations.
Right.
Disciples couldn't get it together.
Oh, that's a bummer.
This is a different time too.
Lately, it's been kind of a more pro strike era.
But, you know, this is a different time.
This was the year 1200.
Those things are not friendly.
Right.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, that's that's too bad.
Pontius Pilate was the Zaslav of his time.
So we did wear like a vest, one of those big wool like kind of vest things.
Sunglasses.
He had a puffy vest.
Oh, he did.
He would wear a puffy vest.
Patagonia puffy vest.
That's what made him relatable, though.
He's just a regular guy.
Just wears a Patagonia.
Yeah.
Jason, I have to apologize.
You're missing AirPod.
Yeah.
I ate it.
Oh.
When you were watching me this weekend.
Yeah.
Wait, I was going to say I wasn't sure where things landed.
You ended up because you were shifting.
You maybe wanted to stay at Mike's because of his toys.
You ended up going home with Jason.
Yeah.
I stay with Jason most of the time.
Me and Garfield are tight.
Jason's got the best snacks.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Because he found all those different gold like those like cookie goldfish crackers that exist.
Have you heard about you saw?
I mean, obviously you saw them, but I hadn't heard about.
Yeah.
Goldfish makes a bunch of cookies now.
Damn.
Talk about playing God.
Yeah, no, they're they're getting crazy with their experiments.
Yeah.
And you've had them?
Oh, yeah, I had a few kinds.
Still make my way through the elf maple flavored ones.
You call them.
Yeah, that's why the church just smells forever like maple.
Yeah.
Artifit like a real artificial maple, too.
If you get it on your hands, you're going to smell it for a while.
Yeah, we tried them in December and they really the smell doesn't come off your hands easy.
Oh, yeah.
Which is why which is why we found Jason licking his little fingers.
Yeah.
I was like what you said is purely to get the stickiness off.
It was not the reason.
Sweet maple.
Of course.
Utilitarian.
Yeah.
Father, son and Holy Spirit.
James Khan, Will Ferrell, so he did Chanel, you know, trying to get the beginning of that.
Well, James Khan is buddy.
The father.
Father.
Right.
No, you're right.
Where I guess is Bob Newhart.
Well, no, but he's the head elf.
Yeah.
He's not in the family.
He's kind of the adopted father, though.
That's true.
Yeah.
Where's Scott confidence?
Jason, real world linear Jason's Hawaii five goldfish cookies.
They're in like they're fish, but they're the fish that like the boat would find.
Yes.
Yeah.
Scott, I assume they have like a boat.
Yeah, they probably have boat.
Hey, where's Scott confident?
Probably where there's a DJ booth.
You can get in there spinning the ones and twos.
You know, it's got kind of DJ.
I'm assuming if he's a famous guy's son, probably a DJ.
I think it's got a leap that he's got.
Scott, are you looking up if Scott Khan is a DJ?
Oh, wait, I'm seeing that somebody there's a rap group called the Hooligans, consisting of Scott Khan and Alan.
Yeah, it is.
That's oh, my God.
Wait.
Yes.
He was a rapper and a DJ.
He I don't know which is which.
It was Scott Khan and Alan Mammon.
And they went by Mad Skills and Mudfoot.
What?
So, yes, before even his acting fame.
Wow.
Did you have any idea about that?
Jason, I fully guessed.
He's kind of rolling the dice and open for lucky number seven.
They were on Tommy Boy Records.
They really caught the attention of Be Real from Cypress Hill.
Wow.
He's wow.
Geez.
And then he followed his father, James Khan, into a successful acting career.
I, geez, actually, now I'm like, maybe he's more rapper than actor.
Wow.
Look, Jason's got the glow like he just hit a grand slam, like playing a big game or something.
Sure.
Knowing that.
You pointed before you hit it.
I did.
Scott Khan, DJ.
Boom.
Right out of the park.
I pointed that Scott's like big head like decal of Scott Khan that he keeps on the wall.
Oh, yeah.
Fat head.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Scott Khan.
Well, look, I'm tempted to keep looking up all this.
I'm seeing that maybe Scott Khan killed Action Bronson on a verse.
Really?
Maybe.
Yeah.
So now you know Scott Khan from Hawaii Five-O is a better rapper than Action Bronson.
But we can't get caught in all this.
We need to keep moving forward, figure out what the plan is.
Set your keeper.
Where are we going today?
Boys, boys, today is a very special.
You all right?
Are you okay?
Sorry.
My spirit phone locked and I had to open up.
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
I understand.
I had to reopen the time.
Boys, boys, today's phase one, sector three, waterfront kiosks south, a.
a.
k.
Emerald.
Oh, okay.
And don't get it confused with Lagasse.
We're all right.
Well, you know what?
Actually, that's kind of applicable here.
So yeah, we'll get into that.
Yes, yes, of course.
Water taxis, dancing fountains.
Oh, God.
Wait, that's a mess.
We should have cut that.
We should have cut that from the list.
Oh, NBC Sports Grill and Brew Alpha, NBC Sports Grill and Brew Omega.
Good luck, boys.
Sorry, can I back you up there?
Okay, so NBC Sports Grill and Brew apparently, and that's like a restaurant that's a bit
a couple of the city walks now.
But you said it twice.
You said, but with what were those again?
Oh, Alpha and Omega.
Okay.
So there's two different ones.
They're two different.
Yes.
Yes, boys, boys.
Don't you see this rift in the space time continuum?
These many wormholes, portals, these gates, these jump points.
Yes.
This is your first jump point, boys.
This is the first.
We're at the first jump point.
Because you see, Alpha is Orlando and Omega is City Walk Hollywood.
Welcome back to Tinseltown, boys.
Scott Cunn's waiting with the beer.
Well, that sounds good.
He's sitting in the booth at NBC Sports Grill with Al Michaels.
I mean, I'd be happy to walk in anywhere and see one of the hooligans with a Z.
But okay, wait.
But the, all right.
Look, there's locations that are, like there's an NBC Sports Grill at both of them.
I know, but I kind of thought maybe like, okay, so if you do one, it kind of covers both.
You're saying that.
No, no, but there's two.
So Alpha is the first one in Orlando and Omega, boys.
Oh, no, you're getting sick.
Oh, I'm feeling it.
Because we're asking.
Oh, oh.
I need a Carlton 100 menthol.
We're stressing him out.
I don't want him to keep smoking because we're asking too many questions.
They cost so much.
Jason lent me $12 just to get a peg.
Oh, man.
They are pretty expensive now.
Jason can't be happy about the price of cigarettes.
That seems like the kind of thing he'd be mad about.
That's right, boys.
But like.
You're starting to put it together, the puzzle.
You see that these are connected.
What ends begins, what begins ends.
The Alpha in Orlando, the Omega in City Walk Hollywood.
Right.
Perfect.
You see, there's portals, boys.
There's gates.
There's unlatched galactic fences, if you will, Scott.
Unlatched galactic fences.
Wait a minute.
Front doors, back doors, screen doors, boys.
Trap doors.
Oh, no.
Okay, okay.
So there's, I get it.
There's this bevy of all of these things that connect all of the malls and the multiverse.
at City Walk Hollywood again.
I couldn't have put it better, boys.
So it sounds like we have to, all the new stuff that's happened since the last saga,
we have to now go and rate and review.
You're up against dark forces grander than you could ever imagine.
Oh, man.
No, I know, I know.
But there's a lot already.
We also now have to go do the things in Hollywood that are, that's been a lot of years too.
I mean, there's not, at the same time, there's a lot.
Enough to add, I'm scared of how many days to this.
But then also.
That's adding a lot, yeah.
That's adding some days.
It's adding some days.
Okay.
Well, you know, take comfort.
Some behind a paywall, some not behind a paywall.
Okay, well, this part I can get on board with.
Maybe you can make a mall in front of the paywall.
I don't know, Jason, what were you going to say?
Let's just shift over to whatever Jason's point.
Interesting thought, Sector Keeper, but Jason, you were saying.
Well, I was just up at City Walk Hollywood recently, and I was excited to see that nature was healing
in the sense that while the Skechers shoe store is gone,
there is a store selling celebrity autographed knickknacks.
Yes.
Like big gaudy frame things.
Jason's locked in, he's getting in.
An autographed Robert Pattinson Funko box.
Yes, what else, Jason?
Oh, there's a big Harley Quinn poster right when you're walking out of the parking garage.
Oh no, steam is coming out of Jason's ears when he said that.
I mean, she's outrageous in that there's a Margot Robbie and a Lady Gaga version coming.
I don't know if we're going to be able to handle that as a country.
Jason, add a third mass to Sundays because you've been bad.
Father, father, for Jason has sinned.
He went to Celebrity Authentics too many times to check out the Harley Quinn posters.
Getting a personal line of credit to buy that big poster.
Jason calling his credit card company.
I need $10,000 freed up on my credit cards.
You don't understand.
This one signed by Margot Robbie and Jared Leto.
Okay, sir, you have horny protection set up on your account.
Disable it.
No, it's just to make sure that you don't, if in case something happens, in case you ejaculate all over your new belongings, that those would be protected and replaced.
Very well.
It just makes sense.
Well, look at that.
It seems like that one we kind of covered already, right?
Celebrity Authentics.
I think we took care of it.
Kind of, sort of.
We'll get back to it.
We'll figure that out.
Okay, all right.
Well, you know what?
I guess the longer I complain, the longer this will take.
So why don't we get into the things that we know.
Okay, the first one was, sorry, waterfront kiosks.
Okay, because last time we did waterfront kiosks, North, which was Sapphire.
And now we are doing waterfront kiosks.
No way.
That was, yeah, okay, this is South.
Yeah, yeah.
Confusingly not an S.
South is Emerald?
Emerald.
Okay.
You know what you said at the beginning was interesting because actually not only did Emerald have a restaurant at CityWalk Orlando, Fallen Brother, but also Emerald did a week of shows.
Not far from where these particular waterfront kiosks are in Sector Emerald.
His sitcom or?
No, I wish.
Oh, if it was the sitcom, and let me just encourage any, like Future Club 3's, I would love to cover the Emerald sitcom very much.
This is just his regular cooking show, but he, you know, what was his thing?
Bam.
Bam, yeah.
What was Blank It Up, though?
Kick It Up?
Kick It Up a notch.
Yeah.
He kicked it up a notch right at the beautiful CityWalk Bayfront or Lagoonfront or whatever you want to call it.
So that's serendipitous that you said it.
Yes, yes.
There was something in the air, a waft of spice.
Yeah, yeah.
Emerald spammy spice.
His trademark spice.
Creole spices.
Yes, please, this one.
Just tell me about this.
You know, I don't have much about these.
I feel like I might have to kick it to you guys.
Do you guys have any experiences?
Well, I did.
I will say somebody stole a shirt I had made that I had a shirt made at one of the kiosks.
Stole?
Stole, yeah.
It says, I love CityWalk on it, and I just don't, I don't know where it went, but I got a shirt made.
It was like 20 bucks.
It was a very kind of graffiti style shirt.
What's that?
When?
When did you have it made?
Oh, when I was in Orlando.
Just, oh.
Recently, yeah.
So I just said, excuse me, can I get a shirt and like a graffiti style that says, I love CityWalk.
And someone stole it?
Yeah, somebody stole it.
I'm not sure who.
I hope we find it during the saga.
Hmm, okay.
Yeah, that's all.
Very curious.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Very curious.
I was going to go over and get one of those made too.
They're very, like, they, it's not expensive.
It is not, I didn't realize.
And the guy was really nice.
He seemed a little like not busy, not nothing against him.
It just didn't seem like this was the highest trafficked booth.
No voodoo donuts.
It was not like voodoo donuts, but they had a lot of different styles of things.
What were you going to get?
I was going to get one that said a phrase that I saw all the time at TVs at the hotel.
I was going to get one with blue and one it said water theme park.
What?
What does that mean?
Like volcano bay is the third gate at universal Orlando.
It's a water theme park.
Oh, is that what they say?
That's what they say.
I know they say it's a third gate.
I understand.
One with blue, the velociraptor or one that's in the color blue?
The color blue because water often looks to be the color blue.
I was thinking of my friend David's friend blue.
Yeah, I thought you might be talking about blue 32.
Well, yeah, we don't really want to talk about him right now.
There's a lot going on with it.
I don't know.
I don't know how much you've been paying attention to the news.
Oh, not blue blues.
Fine.
But as far as I know, blue was not on any recent list.
Good.
I've only been watching TV land.
It's the only channel on adjacent.
He pays for TV land only.
I don't have cable.
He pays for the TV land package.
And I'm pissed.
It's like up to 90 shows.
I was like, come on, I want like a Beretta or, you know, I think there's a cheaper channel.
You could buy.
Yeah, I think this is where this is where what you need is an antenna and antenna to get antenna TV.
Yeah.
Rewind TV.
I don't remember what those are all called.
Like just like mom likes it.
TV.
That's right.
I don't think that's one, but it should be.
Laugh.
Oh, yes.
I've seen L.
F.
A.
Laugh is the place to be.
So well, there's more kiosk stuff.
That's where we're going.
Oh, did you cover other kiosks?
Oh, of course I did.
Yes.
So they don't have a sock market in Orlando like they do out here, which is a full sock store, but they have a sock kiosk sock and sandals.
Now, we looked at the, you know, the website last time and there's some aggressive socks, if you recall last time.
But these are much these are much nicer.
They're not as naughty.
But, you know, there are like there are some things for like mom and dad.
Like you can buy something called wine socks and it's socks crammed in a package that looks like it's a glass of wine.
But I think it's just sort of the plastic is molded to look like that.
Then once they're out, then it's not like socks.
Yeah, they look like regular socks.
You just get you open the socks from a not very realistic looking wine glass.
Yes.
And there's also beer socks in a similar way to make it look like you got a little pint there of beer.
And again, yeah, they're just the regular socks.
Is there a straw?
There is not a straw.
No, not that I see.
I thought I saw a straw.
Yeah, I thought I saw a straw.
You know, just the way you like a straw and a beer.
I would have never had beer, but I would have a straw.
Some of the cigarettes.
There's some more.
There's like there's socks that say life happens.
Vodka helps.
So that's just a little like another mom and dad sock.
You'd wear that on your sock.
On your socks.
And you have to put your feet together to make the whole sentence legible or to make it make sense.
There's one next to it that says this.
Maybe like the way you like put your legs together if somebody's trying to cuff them.
Yes.
If you had leg restraints that were being placed on you.
Yeah, if you're being held down.
Like in your like in a prison yard and they got the big ball, the big weighted ball like you're like an old time like Joker was in jail in the 60s Batman or something.
And they don't want him to like be able to go very far.
So if vodka helped you a little too much.
That it says there's one that says this seniorita needs a margarita.
Pretty similar.
To be that seniorita.
And this is not this is close to the margarita but it is not at Margaritaville.
So it's different.
I don't know if they know about it.
I should send Margaritaville like a little bit of like a letter or something to let them know that somebody's infringing on their brand.
Not far from the door.
Yeah.
And then there's a couple there was one just says dog walking socks.
And that's not you don't have to.
I'm not really sure what the point of that one is.
And then one says peace, love and therapy.
Oh, I'm not afraid I've ever heard before.
I like that one.
Me a man in touch with his emotions in 2024.
Those socks are for me.
Yes.
So I should have gotten them for you.
I'm sorry.
Now that I know you are yourself.
You know what?
Do it for yourself, Michael.
And then what I think I like the best is one that just says damn I love this town.
So it doesn't say a specific town on it.
It's just you know where you're supposed to wear them.
You don't want to wear those around here.
Do it in a town you love like Orlando, like Orlando, like City Beautiful or like Nona maybe to Jason's favorite place like Nona.
Can anything be a business?
What is that?
Those socks?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
Do you want to like brains?
You probably could start your own like novelty sock company right now.
You could fire off 10 things.
I don't know if I force you to do it, but maybe I would.
No, no, no.
Just give me a couple.
Sure, sure.
In God we trust.
That's great.
Oh, yeah.
That's good for Americans and religious people.
What if God was one of us?
Okay, yeah.
Oh, goodness.
This is harder than I thought.
Got a lot of respect for Ryan Styles right now.
Oh, what if one sock says, Peace be with you, and the other one says, and also with you.
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh, the body of Christ on one foot and then Amen on the other foot.
Okay, yeah, that's good.
Oh, oh, or the blood of Christ and it comes in a chalice like a plastic chalice.
Once you open it like the wine glass, you're done with it.
But then one of the socks is the wine, and then the other sock in the package is the
dirty cloth the priest uses to wipe the chalice with.
It's a good other use of these socks as a church wine cleaner.
Wow, yeah.
Never mind, it is a good idea.
Yeah, I'm looking.
I mean, there are a few religious sock companies already, but I think you have a good handle
on what the public might want.
Oh, or some of them can come with like pre torn and you can say these are my holy socks.
Oh, that's a good maybe that trend like how actually Ryan's thousand.
I have a lot of that is like, you know, jeans are pre ripped now just for the style.
So you're selling pre hold.
You know, it's a thing the kids are doing.
I read have you heard ripped like they want the holes in it.
Have you heard?
Affliction sucks.
Yeah.
But that that impression remind me of maybe denim socks.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah.
If you could do it.
I mean, socks are really particular texture.
But yeah, if you could give that a denim feel, we know at least one customer.
He lives in Burbank.
We don't have to say we're allowed car driving around and toss them his way.
Maybe we can put some socks in the tea public store.
Oh, I don't think we do offer any socks right now.
Oh, that's not a bad.
I don't know if they offer any.
Maybe we just need to start a separate sock company.
I don't know if that should be podcast, the right affiliated or we shouldn't sully it with it.
It just should be a fully.
We just should all start a religious sock company.
Yeah.
You're willing to end.
You know what?
I know somebody who's got some seed money.
Sector keeper.
I don't want to start edging in on your cousin's territory and asking you for money, but they ask you money for money for bad stuff.
We want this.
This is a can't miss idea.
This is a slam dunk, man.
This is spend money to make money.
Oh, that's good.
Spend money on one sock.
Make money on the other.
Oh, yeah.
So like just to start it like I don't know how much you got like I don't know like 100 K lying around.
I want to be gross.
We can cut.
Let's cut this because it's gross.
I don't mind talking money, man.
It's twenty twenty four.
You got to be open about this stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
With like some of my V.
C.
contacts up in as the yeah, I could probably get us a hundred K by next weekend.
Oh, wow.
OK.
We're going to have to check in with you on this then.
Mm hmm.
Maybe as this thing goes, because we're going to have a lot of time and you're like crashing with different ones of us, I guess.
Yeah.
Why not start a business?
Maybe Scottie Khan will get involved.
I can only hope.
If you're lucky.
But now I've straightened up fire and I only wear religious socks.
Wow.
Yeah.
One sock says I killed and the other says action Bronson.
Great.
OK.
Well, this is great.
We might as well entrepreneur your eyes, being realized while we're all hanging out.
But what else is going on?
Kiosk wise.
There's an M.
A.
some Dragon Ball.
You stop floating around.
That was in the other.
There's more.
We can't cross Sapphire and Emerald.
But then there's like a jewelry kiosk.
Well, and you can just get like glassware, much like the Six Flags kiosk that Anthony
Geo and I came upon during Fright Fest last year.
You can get like kind of like jewelry in a kiosk, which again, that's another one that
didn't seem like it was very well attended or well, I don't know, bought from.
So, yeah, I didn't buy anything from there.
But we've talked about how they cycle through different businesses here.
And this one felt like this can't last.
For too long.
But maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe somebody from Orlando.
Tell me, do they always have this like jewelry, like seemingly not super expensive, but like
not cheap?
It's not just like cheap.
By your special lady and necklace with a little like cubic zirconia minion on it.
Did you think about doing that?
No.
OK.
You got to watch out for some of that cheap stuff.
Like it might give someone a rash or it might start to tarnish and get green.
Have you?
If you.
So you're saying if you buy cheap jewelry.
My neck got torn up by a crystal zirconia minion.
Why are you all bruised?
Did someone hurt you?
Well, yes, but just with a necklace.
Well, love hurts sometimes, you know.
Jason bought his prom date a cubic zirconia and she had like a huge rash by the end of
the night from it.
It's a big it said my special girl.
And by the end of the night, those words were they were going to be stuck in her body for
two years.
They were in the hospital that night.
Yeah, you know, cheap, cheap jewelry can do that.
That's true, I think.
But I don't know.
We're saying that about this business.
I don't know that they're selling stuff that's going to like make your skin puff up.
I'm not sure.
I'm not using them of that.
No, this might be the finest jewelry on Earth.
Right.
So I wouldn't.
Yes.
Since I didn't purchase from there.
Yeah, you're right.
What am I saying?
Charms.
Well, we covered charms in downtown Disney.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So so they have this here and it's an interesting selection of things that they've got in these
kiosks.
And was it Sapphire Sapphire?
This one?
No.
Emerald Emerald.
Damn it.
Hey, OK.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
All right.
Well, interesting, I guess, is the vert.
I mean, we can move on to things.
I don't know.
I think so.
Water taxis is the next one.
Water taxis.
And you know what?
OK, here's where when you compare the two, think about all the trips we've made up to
Hollywood.
Yeah.
We like sequestered ourselves in this kind of like ultimately a little bit.
Sorry to say, like depressing, narrow strip of stores.
It's, you know, like you can feel a little claustrophobic.
Right.
But the fact that CityWalk Orlando is on this lagoon, that there are these waterways and
this is my first experience with them because I hadn't stayed on that property before.
Right.
So I hadn't taken these water taxis, boats, you might call them, but properly water taxis.
Yeah.
Seems to be the term.
That just has not been part of my Orlando vacation experience.
You know what?
This is it for me.
I don't think I'm staying at Disney World anymore.
I love these.
Yeah.
And it's such a triumph.
It's like no matter how sick.
I don't know if you guys felt the same.
No matter how sick we were getting of CityWalk and the things to do there and the things
to eat there, you still, you would like get this genuinely kind of stunning view out onto
the waterfront.
Yeah.
That was, I don't know.
This is, I think this is the whole thing is like a triumph.
The water taxis included.
Yeah.
It's just a great system.
Very relaxing, very convenient.
The view is, I would even call it refreshing.
Very refreshing.
I would say it's refreshing.
There's so much water there.
I actually didn't.
I've been on these water taxis before.
I didn't do it on this trip.
I was staying by bus ride away.
Not as good as these, I don't think.
Pavement taxi?
What's that?
Oh yeah.
Pavement taxi.
Yeah.
So.
That's not what we're talking about.
Yeah.
I got on the wrong pavement taxi as well.
And I got, I went to the third, the third gate accidentally.
The water theme park.
Yeah.
I kept saying like, this isn't where I'm, yeah it is.
Yeah, it's where it's supposed to be.
I was told the wrong things by two people over and over again.
I go, well I'm not supposed to be here.
Can I just get on this bus?
No, you can't get on that bus back.
I go, but doesn't it take you back to City Walk?
No.
It's just going to, you have to go back to your hotel.
And I go, but it says it goes to Hard Rock, which is right on City Walk.
No, there's no way you can take that.
And I go, well what if I did take it?
And I go, all right.
And then the bus driver who told me the wrong things.
The bus driver told me the wrong things.
Took the whole bus of people to the wrong hotel.
And then he goes, hey you, off here.
I go, this isn't Hard Rock.
And he goes, yeah, no, this is where City Walk, you wanted to go to City Walk, right?
I go, it's at the hotel across the street.
He goes, you're right.
And I was like, oh man.
A lot of attitude from the
He gave me a lot of attitude, yes.
It feels like everyone did along the way.
This was the only part of the trip where I feel like I was getting attitude from people.
And I knew I was right.
Everybody else seemed nice.
They worked everywhere.
He wasn't even not nice.
He was just like sure he was right.
Until it all crystallized him.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Well we got a little bit of attitude the one night.
Because we went to Hard Rock just to walk around and get some ice cream.
And then we came back out and we went to go through the gate.
And the tents were closed.
And we're like, hello, is anyone there?
And they're like, oh yeah, we're closed.
And we're like, we need to get to a water taxi.
This water taxi was running for another hour and 90 minutes or something.
And they're like, well if you take a bus and he couldn't even finish it.
I was like, come on, it's right there.
And he's like, okay, just come through the metal detector.
And I'm like, I'm in a scooter, man.
You want me to take a bus to go longer?
Like what are you talking about?
Was it that quick where you were just like, can I?
And they were like, all right.
Yeah, basically.
Slight pressure.
I mean it was later.
It was like pushing midnight.
But we had been assured that the water taxis were running until like 1 or 1.
30.
I see.
So somebody maybe didn't know?
I think we were just getting mixed messages.
I think people were on different pages.
It's possible that person got fired for letting you through though.
I mean, you never know.
We got one.
You're remorseless about that.
I am remorseless.
You're been assured.
CityWalk's not closed yet.
You shouldn't be closing one of the main entrances.
I agree.
No, no.
This is why we're on this journey.
Everyone's a little galactically shaken up.
Yeah.
You can be employees.
Yeah, you're right.
The tides, the moon, the cosmos.
You can feel the rift.
Yes, guys.
Everybody can feel the rift.
Everyone can feel it.
Pavement taxis going to the wrong places.
The pavement taxi man might have been from a different part of the multiverse.
Now you're understanding, Michael.
Oh, OK.
Pavement taxis are buses, but taxis are still taxis.
He could have traveled through the timeline.
He could have been driving in his timeline.
He was driving to the new Stella Nova and Daruluna resorts.
They're not even open yet in our timeline.
We don't have to cover those yet, do we?
Unfamiliar, but I know all about it.
Yeah.
Wow.
No, we don't because they're not open, but reservations are available.
But they're open in a different part of the multiverse.
I can see that they're open and they're flourishing.
Oh, wow.
They've got those reflective tiles.
It's very soothing.
That's all everyone's talking about.
Beautiful colors of the rainbow.
Secretary Keefer knows all about the tiles.
But boys, please, please stay in this timeline.
Oh, we better.
Yes, thank you, Secretary Keefer.
Of course.
We were riding the multi-taxi Scott and I are the water taxi.
The multi-taxi.
No, that's right.
Jason's getting it.
Your brain leveled up as well.
My brain leveled up by playing 12 dimensional chess like the world's politicians.
So Scott and I, we were utilizing the water taxis.
But Mike, every time I talk to you when we were out and about, you were writing down another water taxi name, I feel like.
Yeah, so they have names.
I mean, you guys probably caught a couple of them.
I don't know.
Please talk about that.
But the first one I saw in the back.
So on the back of the water taxis, they have a name.
They each are specifically named like a Mr.
Toad's Wild Ride or something, which has different characters.
That has characters, but this has a different name.
The first one I saw here is says movie magic on the back.
Wow.
So that's one of them.
I'm loving it.
That's what you go there for.
Right.
Learn how they make it.
One of them says Chow.
Oh, I like that.
Very, very Hollywood.
Very Scott Khan.
Yeah, Chow.
C.
O.
I.
A.
Is that right?
C.
O.
I.
A.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, hold on.
And now I got to find the rest of them.
You were thinking like eat like Chow down.
Well, you certainly could do that plenty at CityWalk.
One of them.
This is the back of the years when it says Chow.
One of them just says Hard Rock.
Okay.
Yeah, something you hear at CityWalk with the Rolling Stones song.
I heard them the first night.
Yes, of course.
And then hold on.
I got to find the
I don't know why my pictures are out of order.
Hold on.
Here we go.
It's all part of the rift.
Oh, when we fix it, your pictures will all be in order.
Okay.
And then this is the last one I have for unless I'm missing some.
Silver Screen.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's what we love as creators and dreamers is that we love the blank page and we love
the Silver Screen.
Wow.
Because it's meant to be filled up with the movie magic.
That's right.
That's for the memories.
These seem like definitely named early on in the creation of CityWalk.
Sure.
Much more when the ride the movies was the tagline for all of Universal.
I'm guessing.
It was just movie?
Well, it's a movie terms and this is like movie terms or grandparents.
Universal movie.
Well, they was ride the movies for a while, but it was very much that's the the genesis
of Universal because it obviously was from the actual studio.
And even when Universal Orlando opened, it was still like learn about movies and that's
the whole thing.
And now it's it's away from that.
It's much more like a Disney or whatever.
There's still the movie like DNA in there making movies DNA.
But now that's why I'm assuming these were named 20 years ago.
Well, so they've they've decommissioned some of the boats like Let's Do Lunch.
Right.
Bofo.
You look marvelous, darling or something like one of the Gabor.
I know that's also Billy Crystal's character.
Another cappuccino, please.
Right.
The water taxis, too.
A lot of them were running like I don't think we ever waited longer than like 10, 50 minutes.
And they were really communicative of like if one fills up, they're like, one will be
here in five minutes.
And like if you take it all the way to Sapphire Falls, you pass Roe Pacific and you also pass
the boat dock with all the drop like ones that are docked, not running that day.
How many did you see there?
Do you think I think there was like five or six docked?
So they could really have a full fleet.
Yes, because then they were on the other end.
They go to Hard Rock and Portofino as well.
Right.
So I only went the other way.
But you know what?
Really, like the way that it pumps you up in the morning or chills you out in the evening.
Yeah.
And I thought they're playing good like music for everybody.
You know, I was on one with some bye bye bye plan and oh, everybody's grooving on Y2K
vibes and memories.
And it's good.
Just good feelings.
I feel like.
I think notches CityWalk Orlando above Hollywood in quality.
Yeah.
Well, Hollywood, any really I'm trying to think Disney.
There's anything where you can take like a boat from a mall to a hotel because you can
do that in Disney.
Go to Port Orleans down to Disney Springs.
Yes.
And that's delightful.
Anytime a mall has a waterway leading to a hotel, it's great.
And they don't think they can do that.
There's probably no way to build a lake in Anaheim right now that makes sense for Disney,
nor is there a spot in Universal Hollywood for it.
But so that's Orlando is always going to have a leg up in general because of water and waterways.
Yeah.
Just from yeah, just the transportation aspect and just from a beautiful view aspect.
There's a little trough of water outside the billabong.
Oh, yeah.
It's a little wave.
Yeah, that's true.
You're right.
I shouldn't discount that.
Yeah.
Well, and of course, the dancing fountains.
Well, right.
Right.
Also have here.
Yes.
I mean, it's not nearly what it is.
You got no color.
Yeah.
Call them like shows.
Per se.
I mean, and I for one think it's egregious that they would build one.
They'd build a new city walk and do this.
But triggering what it is.
Yeah, it's well, you know what?
You actually describe what it is.
OK.
So.
All right.
Oh, OK.
So the fountains are going in and Scott is Scott is juking in and out of it like a like a like a child.
You ran through the fountain.
Sky ran through the fat and he made it.
Oh, I made it through the fat.
You ran through.
I made it.
I was feeling lucky that night.
You know what?
I was holding a drink while holding a drink.
Was it open?
I don't remember that part.
What am I?
Covered.
Can you tell what I'm holding?
You I think you're actually just holding like a Coca Cola cup of some kind.
You're also just be a water.
You're also holding a box of kind bars that I bought at Target for you.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yes, you dropped off my supplies.
Thank you.
So, yeah, you may you may just have a cup of water in a six kind bars in a box.
Look at that kind bars undamaged.
You know what?
I was just sucking up to you saying I didn't like the fountains.
I loved running through these fountains.
I don't you know what?
It's the we can't blame.
Yeah, you're right.
What am I saying?
Yeah, and it could have been me.
It could have been me just as easily as you.
Of course.
I didn't mean to blame you or say I was feeling like a daredevil that night.
If you're just listening to this side and you haven't heard any of the other
sagas, I just I apologize.
I have to explain what happened.
The sector keeper was playing in the fountains when he was a human and he caught
staff from the water in the fountains here at City Walk Hollywood.
And then he knows to Scott's credits.
He wasn't eight years old and wasn't left unattended by his parents for.
Yeah, that's true.
He was an adult man for a while.
Right.
I forgot this that they weren't around.
They weren't watching.
No, they weren't watching.
Do we remember?
We probably talked about this forever ago, but they were there in another store or
they were just like, here, knock yourself out.
And I think that they were at the Raiders.
I can't remember.
It's a little it's a little fuzzy.
But I'm sure we explored it thoroughly, though.
I just forgot these.
I shouldn't speak ill of your parents.
And I'm sure they've had it very hard because where have they I mean, did they just
they just don't know what happened to you.
They don't know that you've been having all these adventures.
And I don't know what happened to them.
Yeah.
You haven't even it's like it's probably too painful to go visit your parents again.
Right.
Yeah.
So but seeing you have a delightful time and really, I think getting a box of kind bars,
that was a good night.
Yeah.
You know, it was good and it kind of brings me happy memories.
And I don't mean to now bum you out, but like, do you think they had a funeral for you?
I mean, you got to say goodbye to your.
I would hope so.
Damn, I never really consider you can't really go to your own.
It's not like Huck Finn rules where you can go to your own.
Anyway, I just it's just represents a lot of fans.
You know, did they have another child?
Do they adopt another child?
I know we don't know.
You haven't.
It's all blocked out, boys.
But maybe you can help me.
Maybe you can help me discover that eventually.
All we can help you with is we can go into stores and point out stuff on the walls and say if we like the store or not.
Hey, that's all I can ask.
OK.
And that's that is and I mean this, that is all we are capable of doing.
Like not for you in the world.
That's that's this is what we do.
Of course, of course.
Well, again, I hate to like, you know, bring parental emotion into it, but this is kind of what we're what we're dealing with.
But like, you know, this this waterfront area, I spoke broadly about this in like a trip report episode.
But one thing that I thought was funny is that we went down here to do a bunch of city walk Orlando stuff.
This like silly mission.
And then where it leaves me is Jason and Jane and I hung out for a little bit doing one of the things we had to do.
And you guys left.
And then I stood at the waterfront and I had my first ever phone conversation with my son because we're never apart.
We don't talk on the phone.
And the last time I've been I was away from him.
He wasn't capable of that.
So now this is the first time we can like actually talk and I could find out how his day was and I could tell him about being on the airplane.
He could say, I miss you and I love you.
And this happened overlooking the shimmering waters with tooth some and hard rock live in the background.
Chow streaming down my face.
Genuinely, I love you too, dad.
It was like incredibly emotional.
And I'm staring at tooth some chocolate and pouring a chow boat rolls right by.
It's pumping sugar every morning.
Give me a mini necklace.
Just bring me back Minions or Coney.
I hope it doesn't make me break out.
Yeah, but if it does, then you'll know that I love you for longer than if you just wore it just for a day.
You'll know that you'll know that I love you for six to eight weeks until the rash.
I'll give you the necklace and the rash and drive you to one of Burbank's many urgent care locations.
Wow, that's beautiful.
That's nice.
It was really something like a genuine touching thing that happened because of this and because we did this trip.
And I find it kind of funny also that like that happened to say, you know, we didn't talk about this.
It wasn't in the sector list.
But like if you're incorporating the whole like water complex into our discussion here, you know,
it's like a big open area with terrorist steps.
And I think you technically call that the waterfront plaza.
And that's where they did the emerald taping.
I think Ellen did a week of shows there as well.
And the so that's that's where I was basically.
And I discovered another great father son family kind of moment that happened right in that spot,
which was the shooting of a movie that involves family legacy and lineage.
And that is a movie called Ace Ventura, Junior Pet Detective.
Oh, yeah.
Filmed partially around the the Universal Orlando Resort.
It's not Ace Ventura, Junior Pet Detective.
So it's not a prequel.
He's not a junior.
He is Ace Ventura, Junior, colon, period colon, Pet Detective.
This is a straight to video masterpiece.
So Ace Ventura's son.
It is about Ace Ventura's son.
And there's a part where I didn't get to watch this entire film, regrettably.
But there's a part where he says, I love you, Mom.
And his mom says, I love you, too, Ace.
And then you I'm like, wait, so who is she?
And she is her character's name is Melissa Robinson Ventura.
And she is supposed to be Courtney Cox from Ace Ventura one.
Wow.
And though she is now played by Anne Cusack, who is a great actress, who was Chuck's ex wife on Better Call Saul.
Oh, yeah.
Now you're supposed to believe that this is the fun Courtney Cox character from the first.
And so the so next time you watch this Ventura, just keep in mind that after the events of the film, they got married.
They had a child and then Ace disappeared forever, leaving his son to many years, having never met him or spent any serious time.
With him.
He went and adopted not only his profession, but also his hair and penchant for Hawaiian shirts.
Oh, wow.
It's kind of dark.
Like stepping into your father's corpse.
Son of the masks should meet son of Ace Ventura.
Oh, yes.
Like an aliens versus predators.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
You know what?
I don't like either individual film, but if they teamed up, that's enough for me.
What about that?
That's a blockbuster.
What about the young dumb and dumbers?
Well, that's tricky because that is still always them.
Oh, yeah.
They're not the kids.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Son of Mask, the Mask son, Mask Jr.
No, actually, that is the man.
I believe that the mask itself floated elsewhere and was picked up by Jamie Kennedy, who gave it to his son.
And he's not related to any of the events of the first film.
Okay, so they would do anything to do a Jim Carrey sequel.
Any crazy loops and wormholes they had to go through to make one.
Is there anything past those firsts?
Is there like a majestic junior or Simon Birch?
Simon Birch.
Little old Truman show.
Little Truman.
Like Truman.
Yeah, something.
If that's fun.
If after the, you know, like the very uplifting ending of Truman show where he gets a fresh beginning, if Truman had a son who was once again trapped and ensnared in a giant sound.
Oh, it's the guy gets his revenge.
Is Christoph the name of it?
Christoph.
Yeah, Harris.
Christoph gets his revenge.
Kidnaps Truman Jr.
Oh, yeah.
But then he would say, well, how have I've given him an amazing life better than you ever could.
You couldn't give him a multimillion dollar world to explore the real world.
It's not safe for Truman Burbank Jr.
And it's all over the phone because Jim Carrey doesn't do the movie.
Yeah, yeah.
Stop yelling at me, Truman.
Why don't you come here and say that to me in person?
Oh, yeah.
Too much of a coward.
Everyone's doing returns and reboots and stuff nowadays.
So we should come back.
Honestly, you should make a super movie where like the super movie like where the mask fights a spandora and he plays both.
Yeah.
And they stand and they crash through a wall and they land in the soundstage of Truman Jr.
The Truman Jr.
show.
Bruce Almighty's there.
Well, interesting.
OK, so you definitely Bruce.
Little Bruce is good.
Young Bruce.
So Jason's definition of a super movie is an actor's entire filmography in play in one movie.
Well, I mostly meant to.
I mostly meant like two of the most successful.
But I was really starts wandering into fray.
So like a Tom Hanks super movie, it's Forrest Gump.
It's the Cloud Atlas characters.
It's the terminal Express.
Anything is in game.
But not necessarily Tom Hanks.
The him.
So he himself.
It's like how much can we parse off its force?
It doesn't have to be Tom Hanks.
Right.
Yes.
Uh huh.
But it could be all his characters.
David S.
Pumpkins.
Yes.
And they all get caught on the bridge of spies.
Big showdown between over here.
16 relatives of Tom Hanks characters over here.
Another over here.
The wall has risen again.
What do you think?
Jerry Crown.
Let's get him.
Get him.
It's on the moped.
Yeah.
And Booty's riding on back and they're flying down the road to Perdition.
You know, wow, it's the movie that teaches you that the road of Perdition hooks up to the bridge of spies.
How did you know?
Forrest Gump ran across all of it.
How did you know I would be here?
I checked your location on the circle app.
Wow.
Why perhaps an actor who appears briefly in the circle or some shit could be terrific.
That counts.
Jason, whatever the hell that is in the circle.
I don't quite remember.
Aren't you doing improv in the circle?
Me and Drew Droga are doing fake improv.
Yes.
Well, fake in not in the fake in when you were performing.
I initially started improvising and then I felt bad.
There was a line of extras who could not talk or tag in because they were not paid for that.
Right.
All right.
So you could be in that.
You count for that.
Have listeners ever found you in the circle?
Because there was that and then there's the thing.
What's the thing where you're in a soccer audience?
I'm in the squeakle.
They didn't find me in the squeakle.
You were found in the squeakle.
Yes.
I while the circle while a bestselling Dave Eggers novel, I don't know if enough people have seen the movie adaptation to find me.
Now watch the circle.
Yeah, we issue you the circle challenge.
Please.
What was the modern?
Oh, that's part of the mission.
Oh, OK.
Please.
I need this listeners.
Wow.
OK.
So not only we know.
It's not just that you should make your X.
Please find Jason in the circle.
OK, so we'll work on that.
Anything that we should probably start making it to since we got two NBC sports girls.
I'll find Omega and bruised him.
That's four places to get through.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Alpha.
Do we go over this?
Alpha and Omega.
What's the difference?
Alpha is in Orlando.
OK.
Alpha is in Orlando in this case.
But is that because is Alpha always Orlando or?
No, it might switch up here and there.
Oh, Alpha is like it's the first.
First.
Yeah.
OK.
That NBC sports grill and brew open much earlier.
So if there's another one that we encounter where CityWalk Hollywood open first, that will be Alpha.
That would be Alpha.
OK.
Very clear.
Great.
Well, I know Omega, the creator and the end.
That's right.
The creator and the end.
As I've been saying, all beginning, you learn about in the circle.
This really this whole series is kind of like a big circle.
All a big circle.
Yeah.
In fact, if you watch the Dave Eggers, the circle.
What is it?
Well, Dave Eggers wrote the novel.
A heartbreaking work of staggering genius.
And then he's written.
If you watch this and you sync it up to Margaritaville, all of your all of your answer questions will be answered.
Yeah.
The song on a loop.
Yes, that's right.
It's just that's just that.
Yeah.
John Boyega enters that looking for my life.
That's where you hit play.
Yeah.
Can I get is your character in the book, your improv character?
I don't know.
I that is I've read a few Dave Eggers books, but I don't think I've read the circle.
Two ruggedly handsome men have the room and stitches.
How could this be made up off the top of their head?
The audience thinks.
All of them at once in unison having the same collective thought.
It is as if they were touched by the hand of God.
One word.
It's all they asked for.
It certainly couldn't be that the one of the actors was the director's improv teacher and then he asked,
We need another guy.
Do you know anyone from this list?
It's like, I know Jason.
Wow.
That's how he got the gig.
Yeah.
That's how the scenes info.
So, wow, Hollywood stuff.
That's how magic.
And then Charlie.
Yeah.
Let's do lunch.
Let's do lunch at the silver screen.
Is here.
Let's do lunch at NBC Sports Grill and Brew Alpha Alpha.
That is OK.
So it opened in Orlando in 2015.
That makes it alpha.
That's right.
You know, I think we've got a lot of experience with both.
We could probably go back and forth here.
You know what?
A little like again, a little little peek behind the scenes.
You know, we were talking about the city walk saga Orlando a long time ago, and we thought,
Oh, maybe some of these locations that are both would be good to visit.
So we went up to NBC Sports Grill and Brew Omega in L.
A.
with Griffin Newman with this in mind.
And that was in December twenty twenty one.
That is how long we have been trying to do this.
That's right.
There is a photo of us, which we can post.
You could tell when it was taken because we're there are masks on all of our chins.
That's right.
My memory from that is that Griffin, I think Griffin had a really runny broccoli and cheddar mac and cheese.
Like it was just pure liquid at the end.
I don't think it left a good taste in his mouth.
The whole thing about city walker.
Now I don't know if Griffin will be in the saga.
They would never let that happen at Alpha.
They're in a tight ship at Alpha.
It's an Omega problem.
Well, you know, because there's differences like in at Alpha, they have grip at sandwiches, but Omega, they have home run handhelds.
So there is a difference.
They are different.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
You said that was so much base in your voice.
What was it?
Handhelds.
Home run handheld.
Home run handhelds.
Like a like a Scott Kahn DJ sample.
Yeah.
I like it.
Where'd you find this handheld?
Handheld is really weird to call your sandwich a handheld.
That is a thing.
That is a thing now that restaurants.
Where?
I know what he's saying.
Yeah, no, this is like on restaurants or if you watch food reviewers online, they'll talk about mains and handhelds.
I hate mains.
I also really hate when people like you hate the term mains.
You love main.
Yeah, I like an entree.
But when when someone like someone online refers to something as very delicious or so delicious, it's like nails on a chalkboard to me.
Like, I don't know why.
Very delicious.
Someone saying, oh, it's so delicious or it's very delicious.
I like I don't know why.
It just gives me the willies.
The word delicious.
No, no, it's the modifier.
Like delicious should be enough.
What about what about so delicious?
No, you just that's why I'm saying very delicious or so delicious.
I've got one.
What about so delicious?
Jason, Steve is steaming again.
I hate.
I'm just bad.
I'm just what about ultra ultra ultra delicious?
I actually don't mind ultra delicious.
OK, I think it's kind of that's that might be the plus.
So wait, like a super movie, super delicious, super.
Yeah, I think I'm OK with that.
Maybe it's just more oomph in ultra and super.
Huh?
So so and very aren't enough, but super and ultra are just right.
Yeah, that that first off, it better be really good if you're using those.
What about Alpha Delicious?
Well, that's OK.
Yeah, because I respect the multiverse.
Listen up, vloggers, get creative, bloggers and vloggers.
Get creative with your words or Jason's got a paddle coming for you.
I don't care how many seconds you got on Tic Tac.
You know, you don't need to waste it.
So delicious and very delicious.
I was you know what I was looking through and that's why I didn't hear him say so.
I was trying to find my meal from twenty twenty one and I found it.
I had a chicken like salad of some kind.
Well, you had the hot chicken salad.
I had a hot chicken sandwich and mine was noticeably better.
Yeah, mine was very good, but I did get a Manhattan with it.
Wow.
So I remember that and then get it.
And I looked at this foosball table that they have at the Hollywood location.
And having just seen this foosball table a few days ago, it is so much cleaner and nice.
Oh, that's a photo from twenty twenty one.
Yes.
And that.
Wow.
You're right.
Because yes, we ended up doing this just a few days ago.
Mike and I were up there with friend of the show, Kevin Tully from the band, Telethon.
And that we I requested to sit at the oh, there you were at it with masks.
Wow.
Oh, wild.
Well, anyway, this time we went up there and it was pretty slow and slow enough that I was like, I'm going to get greedy here.
Yeah.
Can we can we sit at one of the foosball tables?
Because if you don't know, they have long tables that are foosball tables as well as dining tables.
Yes.
This is, you know, because it's like that we haven't said really what the restaurant is.
This is the ultimate sports bar sports fan location where the prize are called Bases Loaded and his TV is playing all the games you can imagine.
And then you've got you can sit at a foosball table.
And I've never gotten to do it because I've only been there in, you know, stupid, dumb groups of five or less.
And we were only three.
But there was nobody at the table.
And I was like, I'm going to take a swing.
Let me see if I can load these bases.
We're in sports Xanadu after all.
And she kind of grimaced.
I was like, oh, it's OK if you get the hostess.
And then she's like, you know what?
It's slow.
You can do it.
Yes.
Yeah.
The victory of even though we are only a little corner that we got the foosball table felt so great.
So there's like, you know, there's a couple of layers of glass up on top, but you can use cans.
You do still have access to the top to like put the ball in and play.
And the only issue becomes that if you're going to eat some handhelds and you've been touching, you know, really markedly dirty balls, much the dirtiest balls, visibly dirty, not just you know, people have dirty balls.
I'm just saying it looks like it's decaying.
It looks like you can see the germs that have grown on it.
Yeah, there's food.
There's greasy hands.
It's just very scratched up.
I mean, a foosball is going to get lots of wear and tear regardless of where.
But then the handles, it's such a touchy game.
Yeah.
And that kind of hadn't occurred to me till we were sitting down and then we had the dance the entire time of like, well, do you want to wash your hands now?
Yeah, I'll wash your hands.
Well, you know, why don't we?
OK, let's play a little foosball.
Then we'll wash our hands.
It was like when we went bowling at downtown Disney.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
You were there for that.
Yeah.
These things are maybe not.
That was very handled to like sushi.
Buffalo sauce on the lane pepperoni grease on the.
Yeah, but that pepperoni grease added to you getting all those strikes.
That's right.
Yeah, sure.
Jason bowled a turkey, then ate a turkey.
Your full turkey.
I only just learned that the what I ordered when we went out there all those years ago seems to have been removed from the menu.
The drink I ordered, which was a float.
It was a black cherry soda float.
Oh, yeah.
So it was a big scoop of vanilla ice cream.
And then they poured like IBC or Hanks black cherry in it.
I was wondering because I wrote down I guessed off of the current menu what you got.
My guess was a chocolate cherry cordial float.
We're seeing you order that with dinner.
I believe not alcohol.
Unless it's spiked.
Is that on the current menu?
That is on the current menu.
Is that possibly what you got?
That is I believe what I got.
Or maybe that was the you know what?
Maybe that was the menu.
Maybe I took a picture of the menu in twenty twenty one.
I'm all confused.
Alpha Omega twenty twenty one twenty twenty four.
I don't know.
You're learning, Scott.
You're learning.
Embrace the confusion.
It might have had a hint.
Yeah.
Little chocolate syrup.
It was delicious.
But it was also a little chilly out to be drinking.
It was a cold night.
Yeah.
Can you what is a cherry cordial?
Well, like a cherry cordial is like, you know, like a sweet cherry.
It's a cherry covered in chocolate.
You would get it in like a Russell Stover's or a Whitman sampler.
Got it.
So what is cordial?
What is the actual word mean?
Before Jason eats it, he says, please and thank you.
It's a polite thing.
Sort of an old formality kind of a thing.
I'm not a chocolate.
All right.
Because like, could you have like a strawberry cordial?
Would that just be a chocolate covered strawberry or anything?
Yeah.
What is the cordialing process?
It is not.
It says warm and friendly.
Well, that's true.
You're looking up the definition.
Yeah.
Yes.
No, dessert definition, dessert cordial definition.
Define chocolate cordial.
Liquid filling is placed within a chocolate shell.
So it needs yes, because the cross sections I'm looking at, there's like a little goo that comes out.
Yes.
That little goo makes all the difference.
I love cherry cordials.
I love.
So when I saw that on the menu, I got very excited.
Is it milk chocolate generally?
Do we know?
I think it can vary.
But usually it's milk chocolate goo that's injected probably with a syringe.
Well, I think it's like a variation of like a maraschino cherry.
Right.
But it would have to be injected.
It would have to be administered by some sort of professional.
Yeah, it could be injected by a machine.
Well, what else would it be?
Like a tooth sum?
Yeah, sure.
Like a doctor's tooth sum.
By Professor Dr.
Tooth Sum.
Yeah.
I went in Philadelphia.
There used to be a soda company that had a black cherry Wishniac soda.
And for years, I didn't know what that was.
Wishniac specifically?
Wishniac.
I believe it's an Eastern European like dessert or treat.
And when this company was trying different flavors, the immigrant owner was like, oh, it tastes like a Wishniac.
So that is how that soda got its name.
But I think.
Oh, OK.
Wishniac.
Well, here it is.
This must be a.
Because here it is in one of the top Google results, Philadelphia magazine, and they call it the cheesesteak of beverages.
Yeah, yeah.
So I think Frank's was the original soda company.
I think they're out of business.
You know who wrote the article.
Yeah.
The Car Cub reporter wrote it.
He wrote it on.
He wrote it at great expense to himself.
He brought ten Wishniacs to write it.
Chopping on some Wishniacs and a big cheesesteak in an Amarosa's roll, you know.
One Wishniac equals one cheesesteak.
That's the Philadelphia exchange rate.
Just to make sure that we are covering Alpha and Omega, we've been talking about a lot of a lot of Omega, which I've you know what?
Actually, just to say a little more about that really quick.
I this has become for me the place that at CityWalk Hollywood that is not awful because we had a big debate with Kevin.
Yeah.
Where do we go that isn't terrible?
And we were running through things on list things we're going to have to face in this saga later.
And we kept going.
Tad it didn't like it.
Gave me food poisoning.
And I think now and actually somebody did just ask me where should where do I get a drink after a movie at CityWalk Hollywood?
And I said, well, you know, I don't want to give it away.
There was another place where I was like, don't get food there, but just a drink might be fine.
Right.
This has become my like this is OK.
I'm not going to give it higher than OK.
Yeah.
I'm no Nashville hot chicken sandwich experts.
You might like you might bristle at my opinions.
They have been fine when I've had them.
Jason, I think I did it at Omega or no.
Sorry.
Alpha.
I did.
I think like a slider equivalent, right, which was not nearly as good.
But also I tend to like their beers.
I tend to like a good IPA, a good old fashioned.
That's all I need.
And this place offers that and is so far not offered me a horrible night's sleep because of indigestion.
So that's my general review of the franchise.
High praise.
This place feels like and I it's not taking any swings.
A sport reference there.
Thank you.
It's not taking any big swings.
Yes, Mike, you give me.
It's very much food that your dad won't bat an eyelash at.
Dad is going to be comfortable there.
No dad.
And I think like even because I like Antequitos and I won't talk about it yet.
But like there's you're going to find a couple weirder things on that menu here.
I feel like they were they made a very conscious choice.
Simple stuff on the menu.
The basics.
They don't try to do anything fancy.
Potato skin.
It's consistent.
It's a very consistent place.
I don't know if I would say it's my favorite, but I do know where you're coming from because I would reliably suggest.
Well, that you won't be upset probably going there.
That would be what I would say.
Where we're at.
High praise.
Wall of TVs.
This is really you guys ever stop and think about when in if if any of us ever go to like an actually good restaurant and you're having an actually good meal and then you think about how much time we've spent.
And it's not all because of the podcast.
I can't blame the audience of the sector keeper.
That one with Kevin.
That was just like let's go to city walk.
We do it on purpose.
Yeah, it was not for the show.
And this is and our highest praise to offer any restaurant is won't make you unhappy.
You won't be upset.
Dad would be fine with it.
Won't make you ill.
That's all you can ask for from these places.
It's really insane.
Another thing about Alpha.
I ended up there with you, Mike, just kind of for a drink and a little bit of food there.
I went upstate.
It is a massive footprint.
This huge two stories.
It's a little here in Hollywood.
It replaced fallen brother Tony Roma's and fit into that space.
But it's two stories in Alpha.
It's it could fit 900 people.
It's so massive.
How big it is.
Why?
It's an arena.
Yes.
High school gym.
I remember an amount of people where you might require like a special ops to feed all of them.
Like a disaster has happened.
It's the first place I went getting off the plane after I got went to the hotel and I was like, oh, where's the bathroom?
And then somebody told me and the bathroom was so far.
I remember walking and walking upstairs and walking over.
I mean, it's not that far.
You take that.
No, this doesn't get you to the bathroom.
And I was like, I couldn't believe when I got used to it, it was fine.
But one the first trip, I went, oh, my God, this place.
This is huge.
I know.
And I had just seen you after a day of plane debacle.
After you missing your flight.
I just seen you as excited to see you.
And then like, I'm going to go to the bathroom and you're gone for a while.
And then I had to go.
And I remember nearly broke my foot, very nearly broke my foot.
So I'm hot.
And this is the worst that it was of the trip.
So I'm hobbling up many, many flights of stairs.
Right.
I would say it like it keeps getting longer and longer.
I look, I'm going to make this very brief.
When I'm on a plane, I don't want to go to the bathroom.
And when I say go, I mean, go to the bathroom.
So I think this was the first time my body relaxed was at the NBC sports bar and grill.
So I had to go to the bathroom there.
Oh, the longer go means.
And I didn't come back.
I'm not crass.
I would be crass on this mic for shock value sometimes like I'm going to be right now.
But I'm not going to tell Scott.
Oh, by the way, I got to go take a shit.
Like we're at a Six Flags or something.
I'm not going to say that.
Yeah.
You're not going to say you will not say take a shit on this show.
No, no, I won't do.
I said I'll say it on the show, but I was going to say it in person.
I wasn't going to build when we were sitting there.
You didn't tell me at the time that this is my show persona and I would not bring that into the real world.
Wait, so you're more uptight in person is what you're saying.
A lot more uptight in person.
Yeah.
You thought I was my character on the show is uptight.
Mm hmm.
Haven't seen anything until you've hung out with me.
I have to go.
And then you write down on a napkin asterisk.
Oh, asterisk.
Oh, I couldn't even say the word fill in.
I couldn't even say the words bathroom to the person working there to ask.
Where are the rooms?
This the special room.
The watcher closets.
The rooms with sinks.
Could we know?
I need to powder my nose.
If you know what I'm saying.
You want a bump?
I got that.
When I went up there, my bathroom experience once I got there is that after, again, foot as bad as it could be, then I almost slipped.
There was like as there was a spill up there and I'm not.
I think it's maybe something that just happened from a sink or a urinal.
I don't think I'm not saying that the bathrooms are particularly dirty.
Foosball rolled off the table.
Waiter went flying into the bath.
All his drinks spilled.
No, you know, just, you know, a spill that could happen.
It did happen.
But I slipped a little bit and like, oh, that's the last thing I need.
And it was bad enough that I was like, maybe I should warn the guy next to me at the urinal.
Next to me.
And I and like, you know, I should be nice and just make sure he and then I turn and look and he is the kind of teetery drunk where he might just like collapse against the wall and be there for.
He doesn't need a spill to slip.
No, anything.
Anything could do it.
You might need my help more than anybody.
But so I'm weighing that versus like I might maybe I don't want to talk to this person eventually like should be should do the right thing here.
And I'm tired now and I've had a couple of drinks, so I kind of like not gracefully like there's just about didn't want to bother.
There's like a spill there and I almost I also I just want to make sure you don't.
So I'm just letting you know, there's just slip there.
And then he gruffed at me like a horse and turned and stared at the wall again.
Truly should like like I'm in a like I'm in an old saloon in a Western.
I've been happier to see that menu.
Let me ask you this.
Were there screens or anything above the urinals?
I don't remember.
Don't you might have been trying to watch the big game?
Maybe it was 10 p.
m.
Or whatever was on something.
I mean, we're racing or the horse racing with the cart.
There were people in there watching various big games.
Tell me more about the theming boys.
It's kind of a boring theme wall of general yellow stories of not a lot.
It's like black with white text and the white text will say like a year when NBC did something important.
And they'll be like these like kind of like art pieces on the wall.
I don't even know.
This seems like it's like some scribbly like scribbly.
I'm not sure if that's like a sock to soccer players.
I think it's like kind of a yellow background.
And the style is very like sketchy and it's like they're not hard lines that just outline.
It's like almost like you were just doing a rough sketch.
It's a gastropug.
Just get it up.
We got people in here and drinking.
They don't care about cool art.
Yeah.
They didn't commemorate the trade of Al Michaels with Oswald.
Not that we saw, but you talked about that before on the show.
Yeah.
Yes.
In order to get the rights back to Walt's original character.
Yeah.
They had to give up Al Michaels football announcer.
But I think that's the only that's the only shake of hands between Mickey's glove and Woody Woodpecker's.
I'll say love again.
It'll never happen again.
One thing that they have something that Mike and I noticed there.
This is only in Alpha, not Omega.
There's a big sign next to a booth and it says, Do you have a sports topic you feel passionate about?
Pick up this phone and get ready to share your thoughts on the radio.
Our producers will get you ready and our hosts will bring you on the air.
And it's in quotes.
So that that implies like a backtracking.
This this seemed it was locked, right?
Well, it was it was not locked.
What it what it was is they put two like children's booster seats in the way to block you from getting into the actual booth.
So no one could actually get in there because they're they're just or whatever you would call them like the high chairs for children.
I need to tell everyone Aaron Rogers is a true teller and he's got the real scoop.
He's the only guy brave enough to tell the truth.
That's almost like the way Six Flags would say this riot is down.
Yeah, they just put like a folding chair, like lean it up against the entrance.
Say it without saying it.
It was still lit up and it said on air, though.
I think maybe they couldn't turn it off.
Maybe there's no way to do it.
The house lights.
They can't.
They lost the remote.
Turn that off if we wanted to.
Yep.
And that's that's really what ultimately if we're comparing them, that wasn't part of the mission.
But I do got to give it up to Alpha bigger, more inexplicable stranger.
I don't know.
I had a good time there.
Yeah, I think it's and again, it's like I really felt like this is a hangout for people in a way that and that's in general with with Orlando versus Hollywood.
That was my feeling that people had just come to watch a game.
And so the bar was very active even as the place was closing.
So I was like, oh, this is just I was like that was the first night even be I was just like this place alive.
I felt like this place so much more alive than Hollywood is.
And you said that about a place with a booth that had booster chairs inside where I encountered a horse man peeing.
And that was I think there were probably like 20 people in there after what they've done to our beloved city walk Hollywood taken out how the moon taken out saddle ranch.
There's no nightlife there anymore.
They've gotten rid of all the bars we hated.
It's not alive.
It's dead.
You know, so so I was like, oh, this is where the energy still is.
This is where the action is.
It's Orlando.
OK, so if we have to make the ruling, I think that I think Alpha is better.
I would like to get that booth open again.
So maybe that gruff urinating man gruff gruff on the radio.
Yeah.
What do you see?
Just said, I don't know.
It was like a bunch of it was just a bunch of guttural noises.
And I'm worried that 20 percent of it was racist.
Oh, OK.
And then he beat the shit out of that urinal.
I pretended you're the world.
This is what I want to do to you.
Well, I think I feel like that's that's getting us there.
I think.
Do we do good?
Boys, boys, you did it.
You completed phase one, sector three.
Yay.
Wow.
Well, you know what?
I think I see the I see the stone.
Yes.
And it looks like.
Wait, it's it's a circle, but it's blank.
It's blank.
You know what?
I bet this means I'm just going to take a wild stab here.
I think that this is only half of a sector stone and that you, the listeners, have to
complete it.
We can't truly change the rift in the multiverse unless you fill a circle with Jason Sheridan
in the circle.
You have to go into the movie and find Jason and then cut it out, put a circle, put it
in a circle shape.
And only then will we have the stone for phase one, sector three.
And if you happen to be in Europe and you watch it, maybe this year I'll get another
eleven dollar check in the mail.
Who knows?
OK, so do it in Europe if you can.
Be sure to note that you are in Europe and prove it like a red.
Angela Merkel, I know you're listening.
Show us your screen name and then like you in front of a European landmark or just a
sign with a different language on it.
Sure.
And that should work.
Well, OK, so, you know, our mission is not fully complete, but the phase is complete.
This is our first phase.
Yeah.
Wow.
It feels so much different than than the other than just a regular sector happens.
Right.
Yeah.
Is there anything else different we should know about one of phase ends?
Well, yeah.
OK, so, boys, you should you should know that tomorrow begins phase two, obviously.
OK, OK.
We got to like kick it into gear.
This is going to we got to step it up somehow.
You're sensing right.
Everyone's brain is on a multi-level plane at this point.
OK.
Boys, this phase requires a very special mission for this phase.
You must not just talk about Orlando.
You must go to Orlando.
Yeah, but we like I feel like we did it already.
I mean, we we went to Orlando and we talked about all this stuff and we came back.
Yes, you know, you've talked about it, but this this one must be recorded in Orlando
before a live audience.
Oh, OK.
Wow.
OK.
Well, that's it.
Whoa.
We've never we haven't brought an audience in.
Never on the on a on a on a saga before.
This is a big challenge.
This is a big step up for phase two.
And I'm just you know, I'm just glad I got you guys to to to back me up.
I think we're going to I think we can do this thing.
We can do great.
And Secretary Kuper, I'm so glad you'll be there with us, too.
Oh, yeah.
So about that, I mean, you know, like the multiverse is vast and mysterious.
And I can't be at all parts of it at once.
All right.
So you're not OK.
So you're not going to be fine.
All right.
That's a fancy way of saying you're not going to be there.
That is it.
But that's a fancier way of saying you might need a little help from some different keepers.
Oh, interesting.
Whoa.
There's other.
I mean, we've met.
We know we've met keepers.
But we wow, we might have to encounter one there.
Yes, there'll be one there and he'll guide you.
OK, one that I actually have a good relationship with and has not taken money from me since I won the power.
Oh, wow.
One of the good ones.
Yes, one of the good keepers.
Oh, this.
Oh, blessed today, there will be one of the good keepers waiting for us in Orlando.
And I guess waiting waiting for you tomorrow.
Listeners to hear this.
OK, great.
Well, thank you for thank you for preparing us.
Thank you for getting another keeper ready.
You got it.
Thank you, boys.
Jason, I just have one question.
Jason, can I get a ride to church?
You know it, buddy.
You know it.
You did the morning.
You're going to go to another.
We're going back.
Shonies on the way.
Yeah, we got to hit one of the less than 20 Shonies remaining.
One of them is in California.
Oh, God.
I don't know if they are.
Well, again, that's probably where some of these like gates and the doors and everything.
Shonies plays heavily in all of this.
Oh, maybe in the toilet at Sizzler, there's a gateway to Shonies.
You're learning.
Now you're thinking multiversal.
Yes.
OK, great.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner.
Oh, wait, you survived the CityWalk Orlando Saga Multiverse of Madness.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for the art, our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the theme music.
Multiverse of Madness Merch in our T-Public store for the full multiverse experience.
Subscribe to podcast the ride the second gate or join Club 3 to get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector.
All of that at Patreon.
com slash podcast the ride tomorrow.
A new day, a new phase, a newly reenlightened and reaffirmed in their faith.
Jason and sector keeper.
But not he'll be.
He stays at home.
A different keeper in Orlando.
Wow.
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.