Forever…
…
dog.
There was a boy, a boy like any other boy, who loved to romp and play.
Until one fateful day and one fateful play in the dancing fountains at Universal City Walk Hollywood.
As his parents departed to put in their names at Bubba Gump, the boy got a staph infection, and he died.
He remained in a permanent limbo state without hope until the year of our Lord 2018.
It was then that he encountered three brave podcasters.
They, and only they, could set his spirit free by reviewing every store and restaurant at City Walk.
These heroes were known as Mike, Scott, and Jason.
Their ghostly friend, the Sector Keeper.
Their trials and tribulations were captured in a tidy, 19-part podcast series simply titled,
The City Walk Saga, that you can go back and listen to right now if you scroll through Podcast The Ride's back catalogue.
Now, with a terrible cosmic rift sowing galactic chaos, the Sector Keeper has again called upon the heroes three
to face a challenge beyond their comprehension.
Yes, the boys have conquered a single Algonquin Mall.
But will they be any match for…
The Multiverse!
When your town has made you frown
When your square has made you swear
When life gives you one more punch
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Crunch
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall
Where seam-punk robots sell chocolate snacks
A place where you can tattoo your lower back
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight
Podcast The Ride presents, The City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
A daily, infinite, extremely necessary series, exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder
that make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride presents, The City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
My god, we've made it.
After all this time, we've made it.
I'm Scott Gerdner.
Mike Carlson has made it as well.
I made it here.
I'm standing, I'm looking at the top of a mountain, a beautiful mountain full of very familiar places and some not so familiar.
You're right, a number of extremely familiar, perhaps covered once before, perhaps covered several times before.
Yeah, perhaps, and maybe will be covered for many years.
Doesn't it make it the biggest challenge in a way to have to cover certain somewhat bland establishments for going on the fourth or fifth time?
It wouldn't be a saga without Jason Sheridan.
That's right.
It feels like home, you know?
Not just being back in the saga, but City Walk Orlando holds a special place in my heart.
Yeah, this one, no chore for you.
This is not a big, nothing about this is like, I have to go spend a bunch of time at City Walk Orlando.
No, if anything, got a new appreciation.
When Jason goes to these places, he doesn't say, Chewy, we're home.
He says, Chewing, we're home.
Because he's excited to chew on all the different treats that he could, that he has an option to.
He speaks to an act.
Yeah, yeah.
Anything to get that Cheshire grin back on Mike's face, you know?
That's his famous, that's the phrase.
He said it to me, there's a GIF of Jason and I like Chewy and Han, and he says it, and you just write it.
You're going to have to film that.
We didn't do it there, but we'll do it in front of a green serene.
We'll make it seem like you're in Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom, and he's going to start chewing on some plantains.
Yeah, so here we are, and we're going to start explaining what we're doing, but there's an empty fourth chair.
There's a chair that is not filled, and we can't really do this.
We might have to just cut and stop and not use what we're doing right now, unless we're able to get really the presence who we all know.
We can't fully do a daily multi-part saga without.
There's no set way to summon this being, but I did have an idea, something that I think might work.
There's a sacred old phrase that means something to us that was a part of the last time we did one of these daily mall-focused sagas.
I got a feeling, I got a hunch that if we were to say it three times altogether, that maybe who we need might appear.
I'll kick it off, and you guys join me.
Okay, Basin is now Sanuk.
Basin is now Sanuk.
Boys, boys, chewing, I'm home.
Wow.
Here he is for the first time for an extended sit-down in our physical presence.
In ghostly form, yeah.
For the first time in four years, over four years, the Sector Keeper.
Oh, feels good to be back.
I'm back.
Oh, wow.
He's got a great, he's got his usual toot.
Yeah, that's right.
How are you boys?
How are you?
Oh, fine.
I mean, we feel refreshed from going to the City Walk Orlando.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a little, as we said, a little different.
Of course, of course.
I'm feeling fine, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, there's kind of a more vacation vibe, too.
You know, it's very like, it's picturesque, it's scenic.
You know, there's kind of a breezier feel almost, and I'm almost at this point, like this might be, this juncture, it feels like a little easier potentially than City Walk.
Less like annoying, mundane.
Wouldn't you say, Jason?
I would say so.
I mean, there's all that extra greenery and wateries, too.
This is like a couple of clubs and restaurants.
I think, I actually, I feel like we're, this might be in a way like a little bit of a simpler endeavor than the previous City Walk Saga.
Uh, uh, uh.
I'm sorry to say, Orlando simplicity is nothing but smoke and mirrors, boys.
It's nothing but Orlando magic, like the name of the basketball team.
It's Orlando magic.
It's Shaq, Dennis Scott, all of our favorite Orlando magic players.
Dennis Scott.
Horace Grant briefly, after he left the Bulls and he wore blue goggles instead of red.
Yeah, it felt weird.
It felt weird.
You kept up with your stats, you kept getting your Sports Illustrated delivered to you for kids, even though you weren't even in limbo.
Yeah.
I remember there was a Sports Illustrated issue that said a kid beats Scottie Pippen one on one in horse.
What?
I always doubted that, but we're off track, sorry.
I always doubted that.
That's fine.
I don't know, maybe something like, and I don't know exactly what we're getting up to here, but maybe there's some way that we can, you know, whatever shackles you're currently dealing with, maybe there's a way that we can free you, get you to go play a game on horse with Scottie Pippen.
Yes, yes.
Well, you know, like you said, it seems like Orlando is a simple place, but in fact, beneath that simplicity is something much more complex.
Orlando is very much a hub.
Oh, really?
Of the city walks that unite us all.
Okay.
You refer to this sort of multiverse, these many malls that make up the universe of city walks.
There's Universal City Walk, obviously, here in Los Angeles.
Right.
City Walk in Orlando.
Yeah.
You want to name all the other ones too?
You know, there's a…
Oh no, he's getting weak.
I won't make him do that.
Japan, Japan.
There's one in Japan.
Osaka, yeah.
There's one in Japan as well.
Thank you, Jason.
And so, I just want to let you know that you're not embarking on a simple journey.
This is going to be the most difficult one yet.
Because there is a rift in the multiverse.
And that's all I can say at this moment.
Oh, well…
Unless you need me to say more.
Oh, I mean, I wouldn't mind hearing more.
What are we doing here?
We have to fix a rift, but we don't get to know what the rift is?
Well, I mean, it's how you usually fix things.
I need you to cover all of City Walk Orlando.
Right.
So, like, we rate it and review.
We rate it, we review it.
Talk about our experiences in different ways.
Experiences, yes.
Okay.
And don't skip any of it.
No skipping any of it.
All the sectors must be covered.
Well, but, like, I mean, okay, some of the things, you know, we went there, we spent a sizable amount of time there.
Some of the things are like a little, you know, it's like something we could go to down the street.
Do we have to have done everything there in order for this to lose rift?
Everything, every square foot.
What feels thinner is actually thicker.
Oh, okay.
So that's opposite too.
It, like, expands out, like, dimensionally.
Just like the sign at Cinnabon says, what feels thinner is actually thicker.
They're icing.
Oh, right.
That's the way that they've justified watering down their thick layers of icing.
Deceptively thin looking icing from Cinnabon.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, we should have known we were in for some fucking shit.
So I'm just interested, I'm interested to know because, like, Orlando, so.
And I'm growing weak because of the rift.
Oh, no.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I mean.
I'm just, this is a, it's like, you know how multiverse is like there's so many infinite number of worlds and options.
I didn't realize that we traveled essentially to part of the multiverse.
I just thought it was another mall that was built after this mall out here was.
It's a hub, damn it.
Okay.
How much any time is left?
I'm so sorry.
I'm just, I just really.
It's a hub.
I'm just trying to wrap my head around it that it's such a, that it's sort of important.
Think of all the sectors within it.
And then those sectors also have gates and those gates have doors and those doorways lead to portals and there's jump points.
Right.
So it's like when like.
Wait, wait, whoa.
Jump points.
I'm writing it down, actually.
Oh, it's a lot of terms.
Sectors, gate, portals and jump points.
Yes, Scott.
I sent you a Google Doc.
Go to the.
Yeah, no.
We're all shared.
These are long.
Oh my God.
These are long, long definitions.
You've written like quantum physics theory here.
You're going to have to boil it down for us.
So what like jump points is like a way to like get from hub to hub in the multiverse?
That's right.
Well, I'll be your guide through it, but I'm also who you need to help as always.
So, you know, I'm guiding you, but I also need your help.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, that dramatic archetype where the kind of the victim of the story is also the Obi Wan.
Yes.
It's like Obi Wan was.
And Princess Leia are the same.
Yeah, he was ill.
Right.
And he needed help.
He needed.
He was.
He needed help.
You're like if they took every Star Wars character and mushed them all up into one.
That's the.
That's how what a great character you are and what quality you bring to a narrative.
I couldn't have put it better.
It's like with the Yoda death scene, right?
Yoda's dying, but he's also guiding.
Right.
He is dying and guiding at the same time.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, thank God you don't have some like complicated backwards way of speaking because you've just delivered a lot of complication to what we're doing already.
So we have to OK, we have to call it.
We have to solve a rift.
We have to do it by reviewing everything at CityWalk Orlando.
There's going to be sectors, gates, portals and jump points.
Right.
So we got to be aware.
And those might yank us.
What like to other places or something?
Phases.
Oh, in phase?
OK.
But it's still sectors though.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
I'm the sector keeper.
OK.
Yes.
It would have to be sectors, but also then the sectors are they're grouped into phases.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
And phases.
And is there is is there a way to know when a phase is done?
Is that like one of the things you listed?
Yes, yes.
You'll know.
You'll know when a phase will feel it.
You'll feel it.
It will feel like the universe, like the multiverse will kind of make us have like a warm feeling
in our bellies.
Like a warmth.
It'll feel like you're waking up on Christmas morning or having your first kiss or on the
same day, eating your first Cinnabon on Christmas morning.
All in the same morning.
Wow.
What a morning.
Jason might be the only person here whose first Cinnabon and first kiss gave him the
same feeling.
Well, yeah, I'd lay it over the counter and give the like a little friendly pack like,
thank you.
Thank you.
This 13 year old is going to be very happy.
Ah, Cinnabon and an RC Cola.
Jason's like Richard Dawson from the Family Feud at Cinnabon.
Double kisses on every boy.
But it's sweet.
It's charming.
It's sweet.
What a modern reference.
All right.
We got Richard Dawson.
We got jump points.
We got a lot to look forward to here.
All right.
Well, I feel like-
And don't forget about the rift.
Okay, and the rift.
We know, yeah.
The rift figured out.
Because that's what's making me grow weak and weary.
Oh, okay.
I know, I know.
Speaking of weak and weariness though, one thing, I mean, we haven't done this altogether.
It's been over four years since the Downtown Disney ordeal.
We first met, you know, we've known each other now, Sector Keeper, for five and a half years.
Yeah, wow.
That's when the City Walk Saga original was-
Human years?
Yes, our Earth years.
I guess it's different for you having been in kind of a pretty free limbo.
Every year for you is an eternity for me.
Oh my God.
So five and a half eternities then?
Five and a half eternities, yes, that's right.
That's right.
And wait, and also there's a thing here where like, I get fuzzy on, it's been a long time,
but we save you and we set your spirit free and it seems like every time you just fall
back into, if I remember correctly, we checked in with you, we did like, let's let this cat
out of the bag if the audience doesn't know.
There was a secret Sector 20 of the original Universal Hollywood Saga, which we disguised,
we called it Universal Cruise Line as you helped us play a little fun joke.
Yes, that's a little naughty joke.
And in that one you were still with Cricket Wireless, but then you were like, you were
on some kind of like compound, you were like, there was like a, it was a corporate retreat,
but it felt more like a cult.
And like, is that in the rear view?
You're not going to care from that?
That's technically in the rear view.
I can't say much because I did sign an NDA.
So you're just back in regular society now, you're just hanging out basically?
Yeah, I'm re-assimilating, yeah.
And I try to, we try to unionize at Cricket Wireless, but they put the, I stopped that
out, so, but I won the Powerball.
Whoa, what?
You won the Powerball?
You know, one of the billion dollar Powerballs?
Yeah.
Did you make billion dollars?
Yeah, I hit billion a couple times in the past few years.
But you didn't win a billion.
No, well, after taxes, no.
Oh, okay.
You did the, you hit the big Powerball.
I hit one of the big Powerballs, yeah, yeah.
And we're helping you?
Well, you know, you quote one of our good friends, you know, you had enough money to
buy Miami, but you piss it away so fast.
No, we're never meant to last.
Who are you quoting there?
Jimmy Buffett from Piper, oh, okay.
A Piper that looks at 40.
Mike knew what I was talking about.
Yeah, it took a second, I figured it out.
It took a second for Mike.
You know, you come in on money and then suddenly you're looking at your phone and you're getting
a call from, you know, Hoboken, New Jersey, and you're answering and suddenly the domain
keeper's calling, and you haven't talked to him in 20 years, but he's coming out of the
woodwork and…
Everyone's gone.
Wait, we met a bunch of your cousins and stuff the last time, all these other keepers, so
they've all like…
Mooches.
They all jumped on, oh my God.
They're mooches.
That's disgusting.
Not all of them, not all of them.
I don't want to throw everyone, but yeah, there was some mooching, so…
Yeah, that American Dream Mall, always having money troubles, I'm sure.
Are you propping it up?
Yes, and so, yeah, pretty much.
Okay.
Oh, so you're giving all these people, all these ghosts and keepers money, right?
Yeah, it's hard to say no.
Oh, so you probably don't even have much.
No, I don't have much left.
Does anyone have a lighter?
A lighter?
For cigarettes?
Whoa.
Like a lighter?
I don't know, he switched his cigarettes?
Oh, jeez, that indicates some stress.
You were juuling last time with these cigarettes.
No, I'm rolling my own now.
You're rolling cigarettes, not joints?
Just tobacco.
Spliffs, baby.
Oh, you have a little tin of tobacco there.
Okay.
I was going to say, you stink.
That was one thing, when you appeared, I didn't want to say anything.
Just tobacco and stems and seeds for you, huh?
Yeah, well Jason has a cigarette once in a while, so you maybe could light up with him.
We'll bring one next time, if you don't have one now.
Yeah, there's the long parliaments, you know, Jane accidentally bought, I'm still coming through.
Oh yeah, on the trip, Jason's preferred cigarette is big, long parliaments.
Like Cruella de Vil.
Not intentionally, but…
Like Virginia Slims?
Well, sort of.
How long?
Like too much, too much for one to smoke.
You just showed like three times.
I caught a fish this day.
Even with the recessed filter, it's too long, you know.
Taking in between bites of Cinnabon, taking a big, long hit of a three foot cigarette.
That's in the park.
In the smoke zone?
Yeah, in the smoke zone.
And a port entry.
That's in the park, so thank god we don't have to review the smoking areas.
They're not part of what we have to do.
This is crazy though, that we, like, the last one was entirely about, we had to go rescue all of your friends and cousins or brothers or whatever they were.
And then there were so many.
You only said one, and then there were so many.
Now you see why the money went so quick.
Your family is, we should have known when we heard you had so many relatives that they're all like,
You have like a, just like a gigantic, I don't want to say this, but like backwoodsy family that all needs stuff out of you now that you've hit it rich?
Yeah, they just came a call in and you know, a little here, a little there, and you know, you buy, you know, whatever the guy is that watches over the Gurney Mall and,
Oh, Gurney Keeper, yeah.
The goddamn Gurney, goddamn Gurney Keeper, and then he's got a dozen kids and he's,
Oh yeah, I didn't even think that they all have families.
Stay in your guest house.
You lit up a second cigarette when you already had one in your mouth.
Yeah, I did too.
I think you're just like really frazzled.
Oh, that's really a sad sound.
That's a sad exhale.
Uh oh.
Is he, is he, well, like he's always been ill, but this might be ill the way like people are ill.
Yeah, this is this the toll of anxiety and stress and the world's the weary, world weariness is what I feel like is happening.
That's right.
So, you know, that's why I went as soon as I knew something was a foot.
I almost feel like all this turmoil, you know, it's, you know, it's playing into the journey you're about to go on.
It's like maybe why I, you know, when you started saying Mason is Sanuk, I realized like this is the right time, man.
Like I need my, I need my boys.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
And Sanuk is now California soul.
Oh, wow.
We missed the last, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course.
Well, we missed the final part of the prayer.
Maybe we need to say that towards the end or.
Mm hmm.
You knew you had to come.
But what I'm wondering now is like, okay, because I was thinking at the top, initially I'm like, maybe we can get through this in like a breezy, like a,
like a 12 day, 13 day.
Oh, right, right.
Okay.
I don't want to accuse.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not saying this.
Someone might accuse you of like, did you come in and give us a bunch of like new rules and other stuff to do just to like have somewhere to be?
Because you're stressed and sick of your family.
Oh, I am.
No, like I'm just like coming to like, I'm hanging out and like.
Like you're giving us a bunch of work and then it's, it gives you an excuse to show up and hang out.
Just sit up and hang out and like.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
No, no, I mean I brought pizza, man.
So that was cool.
Oh, sweet.
Oh, okay.
You have a.
Oh, then you know what?
All is forgiven then.
You do have like a big suitcase full of clothes as well.
Ghost clothes.
In my ghost suitcase?
Yeah.
If I can see through it, that's why I know what's in there.
Can I, can I crash here tonight?
In my garage?
Well, maybe like if you guys like, you know, split, split me up, right?
Like I'll stay with you on Sundays.
I thought you meant like your arm would go with me and then your legs would go with Jason.
Well, the thing is, you know, I get to like, catch you up on things like Mike and I've had children since last.
Oh, that's awesome.
But Jason, Jason has just moved to a new place and I don't really, I think you got like an office, but an office can really work.
Jason would be perfect actually.
Yeah, but you know, I got a lot of health stuff going on right now.
So I don't know if I'm exactly right.
Yeah, but don't you want a buddy though?
I think it really, really helped by.
Hang on, hang on.
I'm not going to impose.
I'll stay with Scott Saturdays and Sundays.
Okay.
Stay with Jason's Mondays, Tuesdays, Wednesday afternoon.
Jason will drop me off at Mike's.
Mike, hey man, you know, it's be around.
I'll hang out with Lindsay and the baby.
All right.
When I'm not there, you're going to be hanging out?
Yeah, of course.
It's like, what's the thought into this?
I'll hang out with Lindsay through Friday and with Mike and then Mike Friday evening,
maybe Saturday morning.
You'll do another drop at Scott's.
Yeah.
You don't got to be there, man.
I'll hang out there and the baby.
All right.
It's cool.
We're all green.
So I can get like childcare out of it potentially.
Actually, I prefer if your son watched me.
I mean, he's gotten his faculties about.
He's pretty together.
He's a pretty mature kid at this point.
Okay.
Cool.
So yeah, I mean, I'm pretty.
You're going to start going for electrical outlets.
I don't know whether there's the portals or something.
You need to travel between them.
Hey, that's an idea.
That's pretty cool.
Outlets.
That's another way.
Outlets, portals, gates.
Okay.
So, all right.
Well, we'll figure out this arrangement.
Well, maybe we'll divvy up, you know, who gets that third night or whatever.
So what you're saying is not only are we for many days in a row.
I don't think we've defined how many days.
I'm a little nervous to ask.
But for however long this goes, we have to do all these records.
We're also going to be all living together.
That's right.
Okay.
That sounds kind of phony, put it that way, right?
Yeah.
Like a big, what's the lock-in, like the high school and everybody.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
They would do that too if your parents paid a little extra.
I think it was official.
I didn't mean to say it was like a thing.
No, no, of course.
You'd like slip the guy some cash.
Yeah, they'd slip a little cash.
And he'd give you the keys.
Or you had a friend that went to church and you act like you liked church for a weekend
so you could go with him.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
I hear that.
The church was going to Discovery Zone.
Little suburban understandings.
Yeah, so cool.
Your rap name.
So.
It's a piece in the neighborhood, not fake.
Yeah.
A Cinnabon opened on the nearest block.
I can't put down that block.
I was in shock.
They had Cinnabons and I couldn't miss, leaned over the counter and I gave them a kiss.
Yeah, a little kiss.
Doesn't do aggressive.
I think I could get us started.
Yeah.
I have an artifact.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, okay.
About CityWalk Orlando.
It's like, Cheebrie, you kind of seem like down bad, so maybe this will make you feel
a little better.
Oh my God.
An artifact?
Yes, yes.
This gives me strength.
Now, I knew this would come because I went back in my eBay purchases.
Okay.
I bought this in November 2020.
Yeah, it's a while ago.
So, this is, well, how to set this up.
This is an 8x10 glossy photo of a press photo of CityWalk concept art.
What?
Wow.
Oh my God.
I think it's from a press kit.
Oh, this could be a real guide as we get into kind of the nitty-gritty, the big picture
stuff about CityWalk Orlando.
This is the first maybe worthwhile thing said so far.
You're looking for information, sure, but I didn't want to know what's up with us and
our sleeping information as well.
Do you want me to read the info?
You tell us.
You're the only one who knows what's on there.
I'm sure it's said it's a watercolor.
So, this is a photograph of a watercolor of about what the one corner of CityWalk Orlando
looks like.
I mean, it looks maybe a little nicer.
Concept art gives me strength.
Oh, wow, you're like the colors coming back into your face when you see that.
Yeah, they might look like my suitcase is becoming more corporeal.
Oh, yeah, and I can't see your clothes as well.
They're not kind of falling apart.
I'm feeling a little better.
Go ahead, Jason.
OK, Orlando, Florida, scheduled to open in late 1998.
That didn't happen.
It opened in February 1999.
Universal CityWalk will be the first major entertainment venue in the evolving global
destination resort Universal Studios Escape.
The expansive 30 acre complex will feature a must-see gathering of innovators and originators
of some of the world's most popular entertainment.
Venues announced to date include Jimmy Buffett's Margarita, Margaritaville, E Entertainment
Television, Bob Marley, Attribute to Freedom, still hanging on, Motown Cafe, Fallen Brother,
Emerald's Restaurant Orlando, Fallen Brother, NASCAR Cafe, Fallen Brother, a 20 seat, 5,000
seat Universal Cineplex Cinemas offering the cutting edge in projection and sound systems.
But not the cutting edge of posters.
I would say the same posters they had when they opened.
We'll get into it.
The world's largest Hard Rock Cafe and Hard Rock Live, their first dedicated live concert
venue.
Additionally, Hard Rock has recently teamed up with the National Basketball Association
to create the first other NBA themed restaurant which will premiere at CityWalk in early 1999.
Wow.
Fallen Brother as well?
Yeah, Fallen Brother as well.
I was going to say, boy, that's an exciting little press release.
It might whet your appetite for what we're going to talk about in this series, but most
of it has closed.
We went and we did what they have there now today.
I think something that bears mentioning is that when we first did the CityWalk Hollywood
Saga, the very first saga five and a half years ago, CityWalk Hollywood was at the time
of the former Jason and I were living less than 10 minutes away.
Mike had to hoof it.
Mike had to do an entire 16 or 17 minutes drive to get up there.
This time, you know, in downtown Disney, we went a little further.
That's an hour away or so.
This time, for the first time, we traveled across the country to gather the contents
for a daily podcast mall oriented series.
I believe that we are the only people ever to travel across the nation just to go to
CityWalk Orlando.
And I think that when the series is over, we will also we will remain the only people
who will ever do that.
Yeah, we should get like a presidential medal of freedom or something for that kind of
dedication to what we're doing to our jobs and our livelihood.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe you could fool Biden into thinking that's the kind of thing you should give a medal
for.
Maybe get the right somebody get in the right advisor's ear.
Folks, Smoketown Cafe.
Friend of the show.
Friend of the show, Anthony Gio.
And I always talk about how if we just hang out in the lobby of a D.
C.
bar, we could be
working for Biden within three months.
It would not be.
I'm dead serious.
Young go getters.
Yeah, there would be.
I truly I could do it in three months.
I swear.
Three months, a quarter of an eternity.
It would be exactly your quarter of an eternity.
I so Jason, that was some very good back story just a little since this is the first one
to kick us in a little bit and then and then we can find out what what our sector and I
guess phase are today.
This is kind of a crucial part of the big expansion that Universal Orlando did in the
When Universal Orlando opened, it was one theme park, a great theme park, an innovative
theme park, but just a theme park.
It wasn't a resort.
And it's really what do you need to make a resort?
You need hotels.
In this case, you need a vast series of interconnected waterways.
And then you need a shopping and dining and retail destination where you can drink and
dance the night away.
That's right.
And you know, it felt like a throwback to the old city walk saga because the heart of
the city was like, oh, I'm going to be there in 10 minutes away by boat from like Sapphire
Falls or Aventura.
This is true.
It was very relaxed in the in the getting there day to day, moment to moment, getting
there in general involved Mike missing a flight and I fucked up my toe.
There was a lot.
It's already been we started at a deficit, I would say.
But we went we did it and we found so much fantastic stuff to do.
And I guess with that, you should tell us.
Wow, this will this will take us back.
Tell us what our sector assignment is today.
Boys, boys, we're back, baby.
It's phase one, sector one, Universal Studios Store, Jason Cinnabon.
Quiet flight, quiet flight surf shop rolls off the tongue.
Yeah, you got it.
You know you love it.
And Coke icon.
Boys, boys, please complete this phase and sector and good luck, boys.
Can do.
Thank you.
Off to the races.
You might also bear mention that way.
You said February 4th, 1999 was the opening of this.
So we're not far, I guess, from the 25th anniversary.
This this really lined up very nicely.
This is when we're on an auspicious occasion that everyone across the nation is celebrating.
Yeah, celebrate with our sidewalk brothers.
It's been down there.
We've been Bob Marley spirit.
We tribute freedom every day.
He's been on the cow fish in front of the cow fish.
American innovation led to the combination of burgers and sushi.
That's the spirit we can never lose sight of.
Well, he's got to do it soon if he hasn't.
It also opens as part of when the resort was renamed Universal Studios Escape.
Yes.
This bizarre.
That is one of the weirdest things they decided on.
Yes, I like the logo.
I got some pins.
Yellow words.
Yeah.
And blue.
I look around the time of me buying vintage press photos.
I was also buying vintage like escape pinsets.
OK, so specifically of the escape.
It's like one escape, one Island of Adventure, one city walk logo.
So that was like your Taylor Swift era.
It's the universal era.
Yeah, yeah.
Jason's escape era.
Yeah, that was the escape era.
I was trying to escape my house, so I was buying theme park merchandise.
That was the marketing.
The marketing was escape your horrible life and come here.
They didn't know Universal didn't know how bad the world would get.
Yeah, from February to March, you can only do the one park and city walk.
Islands isn't ready till May.
Oh, is that right?
Oh, what an awkward time.
That's odd.
Yeah, their way of announcing like how Disney has more than one thing to do, they call it a resort.
Universal was like, we got a new theme park.
What are we going to do?
Let's call it escape.
This single move confused the public so much that Islands of Adventure was considered somewhat of a disappointment when it opened.
Naming your hotel escape was not a slam dunk.
Well, no, the hotels had additional names and they didn't even open all at the same time.
Escape noun, a collection of hotels and retail districts and theme parks.
That's what one escape is.
I don't think they called it an escape or the escape, just escape.
No articles for that.
What a strange time.
And we'll at some point delve a little back into like some of the things that they did have when this place opened.
But the first assignment, I believe, was the hey, where better to start than with the basics with Universal Studios store, the big store with over 2000 items.
That is all things that you maybe forgot to get while you were in the theme park.
So more you didn't pay for theme park admission so you can get it there.
Or you didn't go to the little tiny store at the very turnstiles when you are leaving each park.
You missed seven opportunities.
This is your your opportunity.
Did you guys spend any quality time in Universal Studios store?
Sure.
I did.
Yeah, I have another artifact.
Jason's like Felix the cat with this magic bag.
I was going to say like Indiana Jones with this with the artifacts.
Oh, when he's going to replace the artifact with a big bag of sand.
Yes, Jason, Jason replaces the the idol with the hoagie.
Reverse, reverse.
He puts the idol down and takes the hoagie.
I put the idol down, take the hoagie.
Then I do the bag.
I grow and then I do the bag of sand because I'm like, I gotta get the idol.
This is by me.
Many hoagies.
OK, I have not built this yet.
Clear.
This is a 3D metal model kit of the Universal Studios Florida entrance arch.
Oh, wow.
It is no no glue or solder needed.
Realizing you don't need to solder it with a solder it.
You you just pin back tabs on it, although it does show that tweezers or pliers would be helpful.
So slightly less.
You're going to cut up your hands.
I'm going to cut up my hand.
So I have a little bookshelf decoration.
And of course, I asked the workers, hey, do you have one of these of the Islands of Adventure lighthouse?
And I probably got multiple.
Oh, huh.
Yeah, we do.
That's weird, right?
We probably should.
And I'm like, yeah, I I agree.
But maybe it might be a big deal.
I might just complete somebody's life over here.
Just give me something to do that'll bring me joy.
So only the 25th anniversary coming up.
Jason, do they have what other ones do they have of that?
OK, they had on the globe and they had a shark.
The shark hoisted up.
Oh, the shark.
The car.
Yeah.
Which I considered getting.
And then I thought the effigy of like a dead shark in my house.
That seemed like bad vibes.
You thought that would like summon some sort of hell spawn?
I mean, sector keeper could answer the question.
Would a effigy to a dead shark?
Oh, yes, that's 100 percent.
That's opening up a gate.
Yeah, it's not even the right shark.
It's not even jaws.
It's the other shark.
The devil loves shark effigies.
What really quickly, what does it say in green on there at the in the corner?
If it's not too much to.
Oh, yeah, I mean.
Oh, it says Metal Earth.
That's the company that makes the metal earth.
Is that part of the multiverse or that sounds like it?
It sounds like it would be like going to Metal Earth where everything's made of metal.
Metal Earth will be a stop.
I don't want to go there.
We might become metal.
We'll freeze into metal and never get to.
I'm following the line of is it meant to be a plan?
Middle Earth, you think?
Confusingly.
Jason, let me ask a question.
Would it be possible for you to assemble that while we're doing the podcast?
Well, who knows how many days we have?
So I can certainly get started.
This podcast right now?
Oh, right now?
No, I got to transfer to home and I'm going to cut off my hands for sure a little bit.
I'll tell you what, when I stay with you and Jane, we'll do it together.
Oh, great.
OK.
Hey, are you going to walking dogs?
You got that Doberman.
You can really help us out if you could take the dog out.
You actually should go with him.
I'll hang with Garfield, man.
But here's the thing.
Garfield's got to watch me.
Well, do you like to sleep?
Great.
I think you'll work out just fine.
So that was your big souvenir purchase from that place.
Yeah, from there.
A little arch that will be assumedly irritating to put together.
That's the most last minute gift I've ever seen.
A last minute gift for myself.
Jason puts no thought into his own gifts.
I didn't buy the five dollar generic chocolate bar with the meat on it.
That feels more thoughtless.
That is a thing they have.
Yeah, they'll sucker in.
You know what this place has is like they have this in Hollywood, too.
They'll be like a bunch of stuff with the old logo, with the old Neon Universal Studios logo, which I love.
I've bought stuff with that on it.
But I noticed they'll have like retro universal chocolates.
And you flip it around like it's just chocolates.
Those don't have the logo.
And most chocolates aren't nine dollars for no reason.
It's a trick.
Utterly generic.
Yeah, yeah.
Almost worked on me.
I do love the logo that much.
Yeah.
I mean, they've got the like the slight amount of retro stuff that is attractive to men of a certain age's eyes.
But, you know, it's this is the store, which is generally this is what you get.
Grandma, if you go to Universal.
Yeah, this is the sort of standard stuff.
Obviously, there's like more hardcore Harry Potter stuff because they've got some of the in-park merchandise here.
There's a big Harry Potter wing.
Yeah.
And it's very creative, whatever you call it.
I guess you say imagineered.
Yeah.
It's a Disney word.
But we know a better word escaped.
It's very escaped.
Yeah.
It escaped their brains.
Get away.
A lot of the kind of notices across the board, a lot of the merchandise, a lot more standardized than the last time we were at Universal.
I feel like there's a lot of minions, a lot of Fast Furious.
Certainly a lot of Jurassic World.
Yeah, that's always the shift.
Sometimes you go, oh, they're doing a lot more stuff for me.
And then a couple months later, it's all gone.
And it's just a thick sweatshirt in its place that just says Universal Studios.
Like, that's the stuff that sell.
Like, look, this is we're in the minority here.
I shouldn't be going in these places going, come on, give me something for Michael.
Like, give me something that I want specifically.
What do you want specifically?
Is there an item that we all would especially like any bit of universal lore?
They do.
In Tokyo Disney, they do have like a lot of ride vehicle toys and stuff.
Yeah, they're way better.
There's so much better about the type of thing that we would want.
So, yeah, like they don't sell a scoop, a Spider-Man scoop or something, or they don't sell like that type of thing is more what I'm looking for.
Yeah, shirts like with Optimus Prime or something saying, your bravery saved the planet.
Like, obviously, that's specifically for me.
But yeah, I want more toys.
Forget about the shirt or, you know, actually do it as a shirt, but it should do it backwards that you can look at yourself in the mirror and that message is bouncing back at you.
You get to start every day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My bravery?
And it's got a little cut out of like his helmet area.
So it looks like you're wearing it too on the mirror.
Or they should sell those like mirrors that used to be carnival game prizes that have like the designs on the outside.
That's kind of what I didn't know until I was a grown adult that those were very popular as cocaine mirrors.
What?
The ones where it's like the mirror would say like Led Zeppelin along that people would try to get it because then they could do coke off it.
How did you find this out?
I don't know.
I feel like I just learned about it like through osmosis.
Like, oh yeah.
So wait, wait, wait.
I remember these mirrors.
Yeah.
When I was very young, you would like try to win the ring toss game or pop the balloon.
You had like a clown wig and you look in the mirror and you had like a clown wig.
Is that what you're talking about?
No, no.
Like the outside would have like.
Oh, just a band's name.
Yeah, a band's name and like maybe some stripes or something.
Okay.
I looked up Led Zeppelin Coke mirror and there is a listing for that.
That phrase is in there and it says has that marvelous cocaine era look.
So a coke mirror in quotes.
I don't doubt that there's there's something to this.
I just think that it's funny that you're a kid playing carnival games.
You're like, I don't know, you're you're doing ring tossing as a guy next to you.
Like, it's like, oh, damn it, I'm out of rings already.
Okay, another round, another round.
Someone won the pink Floyd one.
Can I get up like 700 at a time?
How much is the yes one?
Is that the same level of the yes mirror?
Can I just pay out of pocket for it?
Can I just have the secret life of Pat's Coke mirror?
I'm just saying if they repurpose those old surplus mirrors,
you put Optimus Prime saying I'm proud of you on it.
There's so many old surplus mirrors sticking around.
Wait, you know what?
No, this is you know, this is completely a thing.
I'll give I will absolutely give you that, Jason, because now I've just found Black Sabbath Coke mirror.
These were usually found at carnivals.
So I guess the band has never heard of this.
As a kid, I was like, wow, if you like that band, you could get a mirror with their logo on it.
That's cool.
So the band aspect is what made it cool to do the Coke off the mirror.
The fact that the rock and roll aspect because it was rock and roll.
So that's probably why.
Universal thing.
No, I guess.
No, no.
The people doing it would definitely always say like, hey, you're ready to do this cocaine.
What are you expecting?
Some normal boring mirror.
Guess what?
This one's got rock and roll.
Yeah, then we get everyone excited.
My mirror that says rat.
My dare officer, Kevin, said, have you see a Coke mirror run?
Oh, wow.
It's probably.
They were still referring to it.
I feel like I feel like he was speaking from experience.
Maybe McGruff.
McGruff never did a commercial about that.
As far as I remember, McGruff never did a song about Coke mirrors.
No, Coke mirrors.
Don't don't win Coke mirrors.
Don't play ring toss.
Nothing but trickery to get paraphernalia out into the world.
Jump for two smaller stuffed animals instead of one Coke mirror.
Pick two of the smaller plush instead of the larger mirror for cocaine.
The fluffier a plush is, the less likely it is it could be used for cocaine usage.
Now, you could carry cocaine across state lines in the back of a plush if you cut it open, but you shouldn't do it.
And whatever you do, keep those plushes away from open flames or else this house is going up like a tinderbox.
The only thing worse than Coke, your batteries, right, McGruff?
Counterfeit batteries.
Make sure you buy Duracell.
If not, they may be just a bunch of newspaper in an outer ceramic shell.
You could get fooled very easily.
Plenty of artists are talking about cocaine.
White lines.
That song is out there.
No one else is doing music about not buying counterfeit batteries.
Criminals are always sculpting batteries out of Play-Doh and putting them into a 7-Eleven and making people buy them.
You got to make sure they're not doing that.
That common thing people do.
Watch out.
Re-soldering the packaging so that it can be sold.
Using tweezers, tiny tweezers to construct counterfeit batteries.
Metal Earth batteries.
An approximation.
A little model of a battery.
Does that pretty much cover Universal Studios store?
Can I ask what you guys would want?
Your dream Universal.
Oh yeah, I was going to say, yeah, wait.
You know what?
I was veering to ET Adventure.
I was thinking something with Botanicus, but no, wrong.
I want a little talking Steven Spielberg action figure that you press.
You press his director's hat and he says, we haven't got much time, so I'll be brief.
Truly.
Scott recently sent around some pictures of, I think they're companies overseas that make these ultra realistic dolls.
In fact, we talked about it on the show before.
We talked about it on the show.
There's a third party, somebody made a Spielberg, but it's not a licensed Spielberg.
It's like Mr.
Director Man, they call it that.
And yeah, but you can't get it.
It's sold out and it's like very hard to find.
But there's new ice.
There was a Michael, somebody's making a Michael Jackson and there's a video of them putting in the realistic eyeballs into the head.
So I just wonder what level of realism do you want on your Steven Spielberg doll?
Do you want it to be what size?
Quarter scale, sixth scale, one 12th scale, which is like the normal size of an action figure.
And what kind of do you want a cartoon, Steven, or do you want it as realistic as possible?
I want it to look like an old Return of the Jedi when they didn't have this technology yet.
This stuff creeps me out.
I don't want my I don't want to see every molecule.
Yeah, Michael Jackson's eyeballs.
Nobody should have ever wanted to see that.
So yeah, I like I like I'm like blunter and worse, less articulation, chitier, old school.
And I want that voice box to sound like shit.
Yeah, it won't be.
It won't be him doing the voice.
It'll be a higher.
Yeah, his brother Jim Spielberg Spielberg Spielberg Spielberg.
Recording all the lines in Cantonese or Mandarin every language.
Yeah, Jason, I asked I asked the question to you, but I'm not going to let you answer.
And I'm going to answer for you and see if this is correct.
If you would do this, would you buy let's say it's a two hundred and fifty dollar really perfect recreation of sort of the open like the entrance area, the port of entry and the lighthouse.
It's a really nice looking model that looks like a lot of work was put into it.
It's two hundred and fifty dollars.
Yeah, we consider that consider.
OK, that doesn't sound like a slam dunk.
I think I would.
It looks great.
It looks exactly like it.
Yeah, I'd love some port of entry merch.
All right.
You can answer.
I'd love more islands of adventure merch in general, because I thought it was kind of lacking.
You know, would you?
What if that what if you're the lighthouse that my brain will not allow me to retain the name of?
If the lighthouse was that shape was fashioned into big old bong, I that's got to be a third party company.
Yeah, that's a mixed director, man.
I also I have no idea how to use a bong.
I've never used a bong.
Oh, wow.
I'll show you when I stay with you.
Oh, OK, thanks.
I guess I can see one in your see through ghost suitcase.
It's a water bomb.
You just drifted this whole is this whole thing.
I shouldn't say that.
You're our guest and I want to be nice.
It's just it makes you think if you're just doing this to have a place to crash and do drugs, I'm just couch surfing.
It's a little bit what it's this all this multiverse stuff.
It's all gates, portals, holes, wormholes, wormholes.
That was a new one.
I feel like I didn't mention wormholes.
Oh, there's wormholes too.
Sectorkeeper, do you have a piece of a dream piece of merch from Universal?
Oh, good.
Let me think about what was yours.
What would yours be?
Oh, I was saying like sort of really good ride vehicle toys.
Oh, right.
The scoop.
Yeah.
Scoop or anything.
Oh, goodness.
The rip ride rocket roller coaster vehicle.
I can't I know I can't think of one of the time if they said thick sweatshirts, right?
Yeah, they have those.
Okay, so they have those already.
Okay.
Yeah.
And also this Universal Studios has got like a collection of the characters on it.
Thicker sweatshirts.
Yeah, sweatshirts.
One thing to note is that.
Or maybe like a Hermione Coke mirror.
So she's on it.
So it looks like when you're like that you're like putting your face like on her while you're doing it.
Yeah.
And it says like, you know, levioso, bro.
Well, that's good.
They're not going to make that official third party again.
Third party.
They'll magical magical girl multi use mirror.
That's the name.
Yeah.
Because, oh, yeah, they'll have one of those surplus warehouses with all the mirrors.
They'll just put that on it.
Slap it on there.
I was going to say one thing about this, you know, like you gave us the heads up that this was coming cause we could just go go down there.
Get ready because then we're going to have to explore the multiverse.
You didn't go.
You didn't go with us.
I couldn't make it.
You couldn't make it.
It was something very, I mean, I'll probably dealing with, you know, the zone keeper or whatever it is.
Yeah.
Serving papers to the zone keeper.
Serving paper?
Like a restraining order or something?
I'm in it bad, man.
Oh, man.
Trying to get your family away from you.
I'm just noticing now your bag looks like, is it crypto.
com merch?
Is it?
Did you get involved in like the Sandbank been freed scandal?
Big time.
Were you in that polycule?
I was in the polycule, but I flipped.
What?
What does that mean?
I flipped, man.
I'm a fucking red, man.
You ratted on the polycule.
I'm in it.
A plea bargain, man.
My God.
Well, he was probably, he was after your money too then.
Not only ghosts are getting after your money, but then the real world.
He came in and he was like, I'm the crypto keeper and you know, and like.
I'm the crypto keeper.
I'm three sheets to the fucking wind, man.
So he owes you.
So you were open to maybe get some like.
He said we're going to rename Staples Center.
We're doing it all, man.
That sounds legit.
Yeah.
There was a time where it seemed like we're still, we're going to have to live with that arena name for a long time.
Bookline and sinker.
Yeah.
Geez.
Did you get any like reward money for ratting out the polycule?
Yeah.
The reward was not going to jail.
Well, that's good.
I mean, that's something.
Yeah.
But hey, at least it'd be a place to crash.
I don't know.
Yeah.
You're guessing at a good point there.
Three hots and a cot, you know.
Jason stared down the barrel of jail before.
I wouldn't be so bad.
Jail the army.
You know, the judge gives you a choice if you're young enough, you know.
If I ever get wrongfully busted for one of these, for this white snake coke mirror.
Yeah.
I just, I didn't even know what I meant.
I thought a white snake was cool.
I was a kid.
I always forget.
We only can record because it's Fleet Week, right?
You're in for.
You're just in for a little bit, right?
Well, I'm still.
At ease, sir.
At ease, boys.
Sector Cuper, can you transform your body into like wearing a little navy suit for us?
It matches what Jason's wearing.
I know.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I got the big lolly and you don't.
My usual recording big lolly.
You know that we're done.
But like we need to end the episode when it's out.
Yeah, when it's out.
Two and a half hours.
It's magic, yeah.
This was, this place just moved.
It was built, it was four stores before.
These are our first fallen brothers, I think.
They kicked all of these tenants out so that they could open a big store full of their stuff.
Yes, and this used to be where the Legacy Store is now.
Okay.
In the time between being there and recording and releasing the Legacy Store is now a fallen brother.
Oh, yeah.
So Sector Cuper, I'm sure as you know, there was something called the Legacy Store.
There was a bunch of like old school Universal stuff, but it's not there anymore.
So we don't have to cover it now, right?
No, that sounds about right.
I mean, get into it a little bit.
Just a little.
Okay.
Get into it a little bit.
Oh, great.
We're off the hook.
Thank God.
Okay, this place, this entire big space used to be the Island Clothing Company, respects to fallen brother.
Something called PIC, which was spelled P exclamation point Q.
It's a bunch of Funko Pops and shit.
Fossil.
We lost a fossil.
This was a long fossil.
A long fossil?
Yeah, I mean, this is like a long store.
Like a long cigarette.
The store is very wide.
Oh, that's what you're saying.
They were a long time.
Like it was in the spot for long.
It was a long, a very narrow fossil, like a dinosaur spine.
Like a dog run.
Your dog could go nuts in that fossil.
Yeah, up and down.
Watches.
Yeah, watch out.
He's going to eat every watch.
And then there was a store, there was something called Fresh Produce, probably a place to get vegetables, healthy snacks.
No, this was a clothing store.
I saw a listing that said that it had clothing with which came in vegetable colors.
What store doesn't have vegetable colors?
There was a green shirt?
Yeah.
And this brother fell.
I guess maybe Fresh Produce was as confusing as calling a resort escape.
Yeah, yeah.
If you need to like Google what the store means before you go in, that's a bad sign.
Yeah.
So anything else?
Do we move on?
I think so.
Wow, that is our first thing completed.
Oh my God.
Hey, we're breezing now.
Oh my God, it's almost over.
I think I earned this one.
I'm going to light it up.
Have to keep a cigarette count, a rolled cigarette count.
Wait a minute.
I think you, did you plan this for, because you know what, I detect a little flavor on it.
I feel like I get a whiff of cinnamon.
That's right.
I think our next.
Each of my cigarettes is themed.
Wow.
So let me.
Hit that Cinnabon, boys.
All right, all right.
That's how you transition us.
Okay, so Cinnabon, this, we're back to Cinnabon.
This was part of the original one.
And now we're tasked with talking about Cinnabon again.
Did anybody go there?
I did.
You did.
Yes, I did.
I had an iced coffee in the morning.
Yeah.
And I said, Oh, look at these mini Cinnabons.
There's, there's like.
The sleeve.
Well, they have a sleeve.
Yes, they have a sleeve of Cinnabons.
I said, Oh, could I purchase one?
They said, no, you have to buy six.
And I said, I'm not going to get them right now.
What size of the.
Six sleeves.
No, no, six in a sleeve, essentially, or at least the sleeve I was looking at.
Jason might have been looking at a different sleeve of cinnamon rolls.
I ate the sleeve at Port Ventry.
I did eat the sleeve.
But it doesn't count.
But you bought it in.
You bought it in.
It was an adventure.
Cause there's a Cinnabon when you walk in Thailand's adventure as well.
Yes, right at the end.
That's not what we're talking about.
It's next to the star boat.
Jason was looking at his own sleeve where he keeps a little cinnamon one hidden.
Like a card shark.
You remember taxi driver when he like.
He gets like a hinge.
He like rigs up something to wear under his shirt so we can real quick, you know, get
the hand gun slide into his hand.
I did that.
And I practiced.
I practiced in the mirror.
A Coke mirror.
Yeah, a Coke mirror.
You practiced it in an Oreo Speedwagon Coke mirror.
The mirror might seem, say boss hit, but you just walked into hell.
If you're in a store and you're stressed about a lack of Islands of Adventure metal.
What is it?
Yeah, it's a little metal model.
Metal model.
Metal Earth.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like, all right, getting a little stressed.
Bang.
Cinnamon hit.
Yeah.
So wait.
So then.
Sorry.
You wanted one single cinnamon.
I wanted to get a small Cinnabon.
Just a small little one.
One small.
They would sell you a big full size Cinnabon, which is the size of like a dog's head, a
medium sized dog's head.
Oh, Mike's famous method of measurements.
Like not a Great Danes head.
Well, Great Danes is a smaller head, I guess.
So maybe it is similar to a Great Danes head.
Did you try, there was like a stand up sign.
Did you try the breakfast sandwich with a half a Cinnabon and put sausage and egg in
it?
I don't think I even saw that.
Okay.
But those flavors don't fit together.
Well, but I don't think it has the icing.
Well, they do, they fit together.
Okay, wait.
Salt and sweet.
Oh, okay.
Without icing, yeah, I guess so.
I mean, those are all things that might be on a breakfast plate.
It's kind of like a McGriddle.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's a McGriddle.
There you go.
You got some embedded sweetness, I suppose.
Oh, but the caked in chemical sweet, I don't know.
I don't know about this.
Yeah, I mean, it could taste good, but it's going to be gross.
There's no way around that.
Some aspect of it, yeah.
So they denied you…
They would not allow me to single purchase a small Cinnabon.
Okay.
Even if I asked nicely.
But I got a sweet, they only sell like sweet coffee as well.
You can't just get a regular iced coffee.
It has to also contain like 200 calories.
Of course, they're…
They have the ingredients somewhere.
The ingredients are there.
They couldn't have sweet coffee if they didn't have regular coffee.
If they let me behind the counter, I think I could have figured it out,
but maybe it's possible it's not.
Maybe it's premixed and they wouldn't know.
They wouldn't let you behind the counter.
They probably wouldn't.
They let Jason, but not me.
They know he knows what he's doing.
No, I think they would have if you would have…
Oh, maybe, yeah.
So I had the coffee.
I will say, I mean, it was a delicious dessert coffee in the morning.
It was just like a vanilla sort of iced coffee.
Yeah, get your 39 grams of sugar out of the way.
Get it put in there before 10 a.
m.
Uh-huh.
So I started my day one day with a Cinnabon coffee.
Usually it would be like a Starbucks or Epcot.
I just went to one of the kiosks.
So sorry for bringing Epcot up, but…
Oh.
He hates theme parks.
I know, I know.
Just a possible mention of Joffrey's.
He's shaken.
Yeah, yeah.
Did it have any impact on you?
You felt like starting your day with a sweeter coffee?
Here's what I'll say about myself just in general.
I think as I age, and maybe I've brought this up before.
I know I have, is that I do think my stomach is becoming a little less tolerant to attacking it with sugar and chemicals.
I think that that is not as good and not as easy a cell for my stomach as I age.
And yet I, who had this problem from the beginning of this podcast, was mocked.
You are no fun.
You're not a little treat boy like us, the little treat boys.
Ow, my stomach.
It's like there's razors in it.
You didn't drink coffee for a long time.
I started drinking coffee when I was about 36 years old.
36 or 37.
You are 37.
I feel like I mistake you for 16, 17 all the time.
Oh, thank you so much.
You hit 36?
I actually am, yeah, around 36.
I thought you were a junior in high school, Ben.
Hey, thank you so much for saying that.
Yeah.
He wears band t-shirts of who was popular when you were in your era of middle school.
You were telling me that you thought Olivia Rodrigo and I were like peers.
Yeah.
So yeah, I appreciate that.
But yeah, so.
Half peers.
So I'm not saying I threw up.
I'm not saying I had a nasty shit at CityWalk.
I'm not saying any of that.
I'm just saying right off the bat in the morning, I'm less tolerant of a crazy sugar
bomb in my stomach than I used to be.
I can still, as usual, can still hang.
I can still go.
You put a fucking cupcake in front of me.
I'll eat it.
Doesn't matter how big it is.
And I won't shit immediately.
I can still handle it.
I'll snort so much frosting off of a.
I'll sprinkle sprinkles.
I'll snort sprinkles.
Off of a foreigner Coke mirror.
Jimmy?
Whatever they call it.
They call them Jimmy's sometimes?
Sprinkles?
Back where I came from, it was like rainbow sprinkles and chocolate jimmies.
Chocolate jimmies.
That's how I knew them growing up.
Chocolate jimmies?
But I think it depends on what part of Pennsylvania or Jersey or New York you wear.
Chocolate Sectorkeeper, have you ever had a cupcake sprinkled with chocolate jimmies?
I can't say I have.
But we only call them sprinkles.
But Jason I think is the one who showed me the jimmies.
And it's just sprinkles?
Yeah, it's just sprinkles.
Sprinkles are jimmies?
Some areas of the country.
Sprinkles are jimmies depending on where you live.
So it's a regional thing.
As usual, it's a regional thing.
So yeah, I had that and I liked it.
But it's not my preference as far as an empty stomach right away.
It's not mine either.
I didn't do anything from the Cinnabon.
I brought the gift of information.
Information such as that the recipe of the original Cinnabon recipe came from somebody named Jerelyn Brousseau who ran a restaurant in the Seattle area called Brousseau's.
There were people who were looking to start a cinnamon bun place that would go into malls that would take down the prominent one at the time, which I think might have been called PJ Cinnamons.
They had PJ Cinnamons in the crosshairs.
It's time to snipe them.
And they were looking for the most delicious Cinnabon, cinnamon bun they could find.
Jerelyn Brousseau was the source.
She is still with us.
She's referred to today as the Cinnamom.
And she seems very nice.
Oh yeah, we call her the Cinnamommy?
Cinnamommy.
I don't want to do this to this nice person.
I don't want to add creepiness to it.
Jason's glasses are fogging up.
I'm imagining a literal mommy made of cinnamon.
Yeah.
Not this Jerelyn.
No, she now spends the inventor of the Cinnabon is still with us and spends her life removing landmines in Vietnam and planting trees in their place.
Cinnamon?
That is what the Cinnamom does.
Cinnamon trees?
Cinnamon bun trees?
McDonald land-esque magical cinnamon bun trees.
Wow.
You could just lick the bark and you'd get a sweet treat.
That's nice.
She's like a Jimmy Carter or something out of office.
She's doing a lot more good even, I would say, in the world.
That's nice.
More good than Cinnabon?
Yeah.
Oh, that's interesting.
And then what was the old place called?
Cinnamon?
I think it's PJ's.
PJ's Cinnamons.
A now defunct.
I hope I'm not making that up.
Oh, maybe I do.
I credit myself for creativity.
Have we ever said the name?
TJ Cinnamons.
Apologies.
Have we ever said TJ Cinnamons on this show?
I don't think.
I am amazed that we have not come across TJ Cinnamons.
Again, a regional thing, depending on where you were.
Perhaps Missouri, it looks like.
Wow.
Your place might have been TJ Cinnamons.
Eventually, TJ Cinnamons was bought out by Arby's, which I think killed the brand.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait.
Hold on.
I'm reading that Arby's locations continue to feature TJ Cinnamons.
TJ Cinnamons is a Cinnamon Bun brand within Arby's now.
Whoa, is TJ, is there a representation, like a character of them?
No, it's just kind of like a ribbon in a circle.
Yeah.
So that's up to us to use our imagination to, you know, the Wonka-esque hat with a cinnamon
bun swirl and a cinnamon stick cane.
TJ Cinnamon, I feel like he is a, not a stork, because that's the Velastic Pickle stork,
but he's like, let's say he is a mule of some kind.
Yeah.
TJ Cinnamon.
A mule?
But he's got a sash also.
Yeah, yeah.
And his saddlebags are filled with cinnamon and icing.
Yeah.
And he goes through, like he kind of gallops into different towns and decorates cinnamon
buns.
Like a Johnny Appleseed type.
Yes.
From coast to coast.
Yeah.
Does he sound like a friendly guy or does he just still like, bray like a mule?
He braes.
Yeah.
He just braes.
It's unpleasant.
Yeah.
He spits a bunch of cinnamon.
That's right.
He spits the frosting.
It comes from him.
He's a little too caustic to catch on nationally.
The frosting is his bile.
And the sprinkles and jimmies come out his rear.
Batsy couldn't even say butt.
His rear.
His asshole.
The mule's asshole sprays sprinkles.
That's what I wanted to say.
And that's the phrase I was looking for.
The mule's asshole sprays sprinkles.
And I would have accepted jimmies.
And I think that brings us to the end of Cinnabon.
Hold on.
Can I bring this up real quick?
This is the thing that's on the wall in the Cinnabon.
And it says, love baked into every bite.
Well, that's nice.
Do you like, do we like this?
Yeah.
I mean, you know, it brings to mind that motherly feeling of Cinnamon.
Maybe that was the secret ingredient.
Even if she didn't say it, I wish they just put it in quotes and attribute it to.
Yeah, yeah.
It would have made it feel more meaningful.
What was her name?
Jerrolyn Brousseau.
The inventor of.
Yeah.
That's my plus up.
Make it whether or not she said it.
Just misattribute it.
Yeah.
It just makes it feel more important.
I think every store should have its own mommy.
Like a designated mommy.
You've thought that for years.
Well, yeah, every store at all.
Kmart should have had designated mommies.
They'd still be in business.
The K mommy.
The K.
Yeah.
So what?
Like a store that sells military supplies.
Yeah, for sure.
Yes.
Military military mommy.
Yeah.
Milla mommy.
So I salute you.
Boys, boys, did anyone else get Cinnabon?
Well, now I got it out of bounds.
Jason made a big fucking mistake here and didn't buy Cinnabon in City Walk.
You should have bought it there because now you can't talk about it.
I was paying off other threads where I promised to take more advantage of Ford Adventure.
You should have had both.
I can't believe this.
Only one Cinnabon sitting on his vacation.
Well, when you summoned me and you the moment you summoned me, if you would have told me only one of the boys got a Cinnabon.
And it was a coffee.
I would have fell back and tipped right back into hell.
That means no actual Cinnabon.
No Cinnabons were consumed.
Is there some punishment for that?
Are there minus points?
Hold on.
Would you allow Jason to talk about the consumption of the port of entry Cinnabon?
Well, does he have something up his sleeve?
Well, I mobile ordered from about 10 feet away and I could see the one team member mostly standing doing nothing as I was watching the progress on my phone.
Not update and him also not make it for about 15 minutes or so.
As opposed to if they were looking a person in the eye and felt the pressure to, I better go make the thing that that person told me with their mouth to make.
I do want to say there was no line.
And I was just trying out the app for mobile ordering and then about 15 minutes later, it did start to move and I did get the notification that it was ready.
So when it says like baking up cinnamon goodness, that isn't them putting all 15 minutes of putting love in it.
Mommy is saying every mommy is kissing every little cinnamon bun.
But look, I eventually got it and it was delicious, you know, and I feel like we were eating it at the fake rock work, you know, in the smoking section and we kept like reaching in and it was like a never ending.
I guess there was probably six.
How about a remake of rear window where Jason watches the Cinnabon employee make his Cinnabon over the course of an hour?
I'm not getting anywhere near it.
Just standing there.
You'll be packing it full of sin of goodness.
He's really not giving me all the all the icing I need.
I got to tell the police.
The chain still in Starbucks.
She's been in there a while.
I sent her over there to investigate.
They're going to smother her in frosting.
Dear God, I don't know how much batteries left in this scooter.
Oh, permitted.
That gave me strength.
Yeah.
All right.
Great.
You know what?
Then I'm glad you asked light up another cig.
This should taste like an ocean breeze because boys, it's time for quiet flight surf shot.
Oh, man.
I'm so glad that was another cigarette flavor that does have a flavor.
Eventually, we're going to hit a wall.
Sure.
It's kind of a stretch, but that one's great.
Oh, I do smell the ocean breeze.
We're here at Quiet Flight Surf Shop.
Why?
This is a place where you can stock up on beach and skate essentials from brands like Quiet Flight, Billabong, Vans, Quicksilver, Roxy, Ray-Ban, Oakley, Billabong, and or choose from an awesome assortment of surfboards and skateboards.
That might that might tap it out for me.
Gentlemen, Quiet Flight Surf Shop thoughts.
We walked through it.
Yeah, we did.
We did.
We looked around at the shorts.
Mm hmm.
This felt like Billabong.
Everything's very expensive.
It's not.
Keep in mind, it's not Billabong.
Billabong is at City Walk Hollywood.
Yeah.
Quiet Flight Surf Shop at Orlando.
Don't get them mixed up.
Skate shop, surf shop, kind of a go to for these outdoor malls.
Yes.
And to get the tweens and getting the parents credit cards because those are MSRP.
You know, those are suggested prices.
You know, what do you mean?
You're not getting many clearance items in skate shops.
You know, you're paying a lot for those board shorts.
MSRP stands for what again?
Manufacturers suggested retail price.
Right.
Got it.
So you're getting that for the $50 recommended from the retailer.
It's not like a Ross or a TJ Maxx where they've got that stuff on discount now.
Yeah.
You're getting a $50 pair of shorts for $10.
Right, right.
Like that's their souvenir for the trip.
There's a pair of shorts.
They don't want any stupid million stuff.
Yeah.
Or a full surfboard.
That was a question I had is if you can buy a surfboard at City Walk and walk out of there.
Yeah.
And go on to the water.
Go right there.
What was the answer?
Surf past some boats.
I can't tell exactly.
If you can imagine nobody's documenting this surf shop too well, including myself.
I was there.
I saw it.
I looked at it.
We saw every short.
Every short there was.
But I can't tell you if you can buy surfboards there.
I did read a review that was mad that said, as this should be a family-friendly place,
a couple of the staff looked red-eyed and out of it.
I certainly hope that random drug tests are performed.
Oh, wow.
That's harsh, man.
Various skate and surf shops are always drug testing the employees.
To make sure the vibe remains chill.
Yeah, it's a very important job, though, so I agree with that.
They're selling those things that Bart Simpson ride.
The nutty boy.
Also, then I think it's the end of that same review.
PS, I know the name of the cashier and sales associate who had horrible customer service,
but I ain't no snitch.
So you're not a snitch, but you do want them drug tested.
Just drug tested.
That's not snitching.
That's just being aware of…
You want to know what's in your body.
You want to know…
It's for their own health, you see.
Snitch it.
Put a review online.
Yeah, I do.
Do I want anyone to go into this filthy drug-addled store again?
No.
Am I ratting out the specific employee?
Also, no.
And do I want them drug tested on the hour every hour?
Absolutely.
Yeah, and keeping it general, too, makes the manager suspicious of everyone.
So really, what they're doing is maybe worse.
Cricket Wireless never drug tested.
Well, that's good.
We also didn't have time cards.
Well…
Oh, no.
That's not good.
Was it all day channel?
That's not in a way that an employee can amble in when they want.
That's just like they just weren't keeping track.
No, just weren't keeping track.
Oh, man.
So it wasn't like a fingerprint paperless system?
No.
Oh, God, no.
I don't even know why I asked.
Their phones are that level of tech.
A lot of credit, yeah.
Well, at least you're doing great financially now, right?
So…
I mean, man…
I'm all right, man.
Oh, no, he got sad again.
My suitcase is fading again.
Oh, no.
You're going to lose your things?
That's part of it now, too.
Lose what you own if we don't get through all these things.
Well, maybe we should keep going to…
Yeah, let's get to the last one here.
I know you just lit up that cigarette, but you got another one.
Yeah, I don't have to finish one to start another.
Tumble up.
This should taste like or smell like…
Coca-Cola Classic.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
You can smell it, too, though, right?
Someone wrote in the comments, I smell it through tasting.
Like, you go, mm, the air is thick.
Like a Yankee candle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So this is…
The best I could find of a name of this is Coke Icon.
And don't get confused.
This is not one giant mirror.
Right.
Although there is a rock and roll component to it.
Basically, this is like kind of a Coke refreshment stand.
But not just some boring little stand.
It looks like a giant Coke bottle.
The biggest you've ever seen unless you've been to maybe another theme park or the Coke Museum in Atlanta.
But besides that, for sure, this red Coke bottle has got to be in the top 10 or 15 biggest Coke bottles you've ever seen.
Yeah, for sure.
And I feel like it should be more prominently displayed on advertising for CityWalk.
Like, you're going to not come here?
In that case, you're not going to get to see this Megaball?
It's an icon.
It's a public art.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a sculpture.
Think of it more as a sculpture.
My little ghost brain forgets.
Is there Coke sloshing around in it or is it just…
No, it's just red.
Just like metal.
Yeah, oh, metal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's not like, yeah, full of liquid.
Not like the classic.
Classic glass bottle.
Right.
Yeah, it doesn't look like that.
And then it's not like a fountain or a geyser or anything.
Right.
No, it's not that cool, but it's pretty big.
And I think that if you have a cup that's meant for Coke freestyle machines, you could
just take that up to any location in the parks or this place.
I like that.
I've done that.
There was a summer in Disneyland where I had a reusable plastic cup that I paid for, and
then you'd get a refill for a dollar and you could go anywhere you wanted, refill.
I had a lot of lemonade that summer.
I'll tell you that.
This is not one of my memories that implanted into you.
Oh, wait.
I just feel like I was possessed for a second.
What was that?
What was I saying?
You're talking about your summer of lemonade.
Did Jason just throw his being into my being?
I'm telling you, weird things happen in the multiverse, man.
Oh, that's what I think happened there.
Jason just threw his whole brain and his experiences into mine and I started speaking for him.
Wait, let's see if something like that could happen again.
Hey, how would you describe the little things up on the top of cupcakes?
Chocolate jimmies, I'd call them.
Jimmies?
That's what I…
From my boyhood in sweets.
Come back, come back.
Mike, what would you call the things on the top of the cupcakes?
Rainbow sprinkles.
Wow, wow.
I might have guessed that you might have said like sprinklies or something weird like that,
but sprinkles does sound more like Mike.
That's what I said.
That's what I called them as a boy.
Why?
Why do you even bring it up?
Wow, geez.
There are odd things amiss here in the multiverse.
Yeah.
Who knows what any of us could become.
That's a good point.
Shape shifting and holes and wormholes and…
Gates.
And gates too.
So many gates.
Oh boy, there's going to be a lot of these things, aren't there?
This thing also has a big screen, a big…
Not the clearest screen.
Look, it's a pretty pixelated screen.
I'm going to be honest.
It's not the most updated screen.
Are there better screens at most stadiums and sporting events?
Yes.
But I thought it was exciting.
One thing I hadn't done was go on YouTube and watch the new Rolling Stones video, which
was from their album Hackney Diamonds, which Mike of course finished before finishing the
entire Liberty Rodrigo album.
But I finished them both.
I finished them both.
I did finish them both.
She ultimately did finish them both.
But I watched the full music video called Angry with Sydney Sweeney in it, where she's
a classic sunset strip babe riding on the sunroof of a car.
Yeah.
And it was pretty exciting to see.
Sector Keeper's face is incredulous, I would say, right now listening to the description
of this video.
You know, a sunset strip.
It makes you think of the Rolling Stones.
And you know, seeing a piece of content for the first time on a big Coke bottle.
That was the first time you saw that video?
No, I had not.
It had been kind of in my mental queue.
I was not maybe rushing to watch a new Rolling Stones video in at that time.
I forgot that that's the first time because we talked about the video on this trip.
That's where I caught up.
So it allows you to catch up on the newest, coolest music videos like Angry.
Yeah.
Wow.
Interesting.
Pretty cool.
So at least we know they're updating it.
Yes.
Yeah.
It is not content that is…
Although, I mean, I wish it was like…
I wish that they had never…
That it's all like ever last or whatever.
It's changed since early 2000.
Three doors down.
Yeah.
I was going to say like from the Rolling Stones album, A Bigger Bang, the last one,
I think it was 10, 15 years ago.
I mean, in terms of recent Rolling Stones, all I ever want to hear is that Mick Jagger's solo song about COVID ending.
Oh, yeah.
Well.
We're going to get back to having a blast.
Pandemic.
Shmandemic.
I don't want to remember any better what that was.
Yeah.
In my head, it's Mick Jagger presents Pandemic Shmandemic.
Dr.
Fetchy, get lost!
So that's my experience there.
I mean, is that…
Maybe we're there.
We took Fallen Brothers.
Yeah, I like the Coke bottle.
Uh-huh.
So, yeah, I don't know.
I think that's it.
I mean, as far as my thoughts on the bottle and the videos, I think that, yeah.
Wow.
What else could I say?
I think we made it.
This is…
Wow.
It's hard to know what it's even supposed to feel like, but I guess, like we were saying,
it's just like a…
It's a feeling we'll get, and I'm getting a nice feeling.
I'm feeling like I'm full of lemonade.
I don't feel angry like the Rolling Stones.
I feel good.
You feel more like Sydney Sweeney out of that sunroof.
Having a ball.
Mike, do you feel like Sydney Sweeney?
If you've seen that video, I've never felt like Sydney Sweeney before in my life.
But she's young in your peer.
Well, on that aspect, yes.
She's in the poster for that movie and the trailer with the guy from Top Gun.
Glenn Powell?
Yeah, Glenn Powell.
That thing from many months ago, yeah.
Do you at least feel like Glenn Powell?
He looks like Glenn Powell, I'll tell you that.
Thank you, yeah.
In that way, yeah, I do feel just like Glenn Powell.
Wow.
Well, I think we all feel like Glenn Powell.
We feel victorious.
I think we made it through phase one, sector one, and wait a minute.
Oh, it still happens, I guess.
There's a magical glow.
Is it a stone or is it some other new thing that we're calling it?
That's right, boys.
Boys, you give me strength.
You give me such strength.
Phase one, sector one is complete.
Wow, there it is.
So it's still for now a stone, but we'll see where things go.
Things might get kooky.
Yes, it's a stone if you look closely.
It's not just a stone, it's also a mirror.
Oh, a mirror.
We can see ourselves in it.
I can see it now.
That's right.
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
And there's a little, there's something next to it.
Is that the famous, is that the Rolling Stones tongue?
Oh, wow, yeah.
Wait, no, it's not.
No, it's Jason's little puckered lips.
It's Jason's little puckered lips from his first kiss on Christmas morning at the Cinnabon.
At the Cinnabon.
Thanks for opening, everyone.
Happy Christmas.
Wow, it's little Jason hoping that the powder all over that mirror, that Motley Crue mirror
is powdered sugar and not something else.
Happy Christmas, he says.
Wow.
Happy Christmas, everyone.
Oh my God.
Well, we'll take this, we'll value it.
Maybe we'll need it down the road.
But thank you for guiding us.
And hey, I'm just, I'm happy to be back, Sector Keeper.
Great to be back.
So what's today?
Today's Friday.
Yeah.
So what do we decide?
So I'm with Mike tonight and then he's going to drop you off at your place tomorrow.
That sounds good.
Yeah, Friday nights are going to, Friday nights are a night for Mike.
It's a night when you guys rock out, Sidney Sweeney style.
TGIF.
Hey Mike, can we go to City Walk tonight?
Tonight?
You got to go back.
Maybe, yeah.
Can we go to the Sunset Strip first?
Yeah, top down, Sidney Sweeney style.
Yeah, we'll sit on the car.
Careful, don't blow away.
Let's do that.
And then we're going to get me a Raiders jersey.
Oh boy, wow, wow.
Okay, well, big plans.
But hey, don't hit it too hard, okay?
Not too much lemonade, not too much cinnamon bun frosting, because we got a big episode tomorrow.
I think our first guest of the saga will be joining us.
That's something to mention really quick too.
Are we the only maniacs who made a point of going just to City Walk in Orlando?
Well, yes, and we made other people do it.
We made some of your podcasts the right guest favorites.
Demanded, you might say, that they go spend a little time there.
Took up valuable time of some of the comedy world's best and brightest.
That's right.
And so that's going to be part of this too.
So who will it be tomorrow?
Who will it be every day?
How much fun will we have overnighting with the Sector Keeper?
Only one way to find out.
But for now, you survived Podcast the Ride, the City Walk Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for the art, our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the new theme music.
Multiverse of Madness, merch is in our T-Public store.
For the full Multiverse experience, subscribe to Podcast the Ride, The Second Gate,
or join Club 3 to get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector that you yourselves, the Club 3 VIPs, selected.
You will find all of that at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
We're in it now.
We're not just recording it.
We're living it.
Thanks for taking this one, Mike.
I'll handle it tomorrow.
Cool if I smoke in your car.
Just roll the window down.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehme, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram, at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.