Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride.
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
And I just want to say, folks,
mama always said,
podcasting is as podcasting does.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Scott Gierdner also here.
Yeah.
And life is like a box of podcasts.
Life is like a box of podcasts.
What does that even mean?
You could put it in a box of CD-ROMs.
I suppose it had a bunch of episodes on them.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Do we need to do like a physical media release at some point?
The box set?
Could we do like a high end Jack White's, whatever,
third man records,
like vinyl pressing of some of our greatest episodes of all time?
Well, you could do like a split, like a seven inch,
one side is City Walk Hollywood theme.
One side is City Walk Orlando theme.
That's true.
We could do that.
Would it be full episodes or would it just be like greatest hits?
Would it just be like Jason said,
no one gives a fuck about grapefruit.
And that's like one track.
Is it more of like…
Well, let's get it straight.
It's who gives a shit about grapefruit.
Let's get the profanity right.
I'm sorry.
But this is why we need an archivist of our own material
to correct us on our own points.
So whoever out there feels qualified to be our keeper of the vault.
Well, maybe it's our guest.
Maybe he's ready to sign up for this unpaid job that we've just created
and he wants to do it.
He's returning to the show from Ring of Honor, from AEW, Ian Rickabani.
Welcome back to Podcast The Ride.
Oh, thanks everyone.
Yeah, I downloaded all of the City Walk episodes during the pandemic.
And so during the first Ring of Honor bubble tapings,
I got really into Podcast The Ride.
I got really into the program,
which led to me aggressively sending Mike DMs
because I confused Mike and Scott at one point about all this beat boys minutia.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so I was feeling the fever.
I could feel it building up.
So we drove down to Florida over Christmas this year,
and I made my wife listen to most of the original City Walk saga.
And she had a lot of questions about Nick Mundy, who's become a friend of mine,
and about some of the accusations that led me back and forth in that episode.
But it was a really good time.
And I explained to her, I said, hey, we're on a mission.
It's almost like the Blues Brothers who come into play in this, by the way.
It's like we're on a mission from God.
Yes, we're going to see my parents.
Yes, we're going down for Christmas, but we got to get to City Walk.
We absolutely have to get to City Walk.
Wow, that inspires me.
By the way, Mike and I both just saw Nick Mundy for the first time
since the deepest throes of pandemic at Disneyland and in my case, downtown Disney.
Wait, what were the designations there?
It was not.
It was OK.
It's phases now.
What was it?
It was Worlds.
So that was World 1-3, which is the Napoli Italian restaurant.
So I'm happy to say that I got to see Nick Mundy on fertile soil.
And sorry to say nothing has changed.
He is still a bad man.
Yeah, very good.
He was rooting.
We went on Rise of the Resistance, and he was rooting for Kylo Ren.
Whoa.
I saw him in Utah, of all places.
We were in Salt Lake City together.
And he had a Houston Astros hat on, which I thought was very disrespectful
because everybody knows I'm a Philadelphia Phillies fan.
And unfortunately, the Astros beat them two years ago in the World Series.
So we had a little rough start, but I agreed with all of his Bo Jackson takes
when it was all said and done.
I'm glad you found common ground.
That's great.
Well, being that I myself, there's confusion about past profanities that we've said in past sagas.
There's confusion about are we are we worlds or phases or what is it?
Why don't we set the record straight by quickly checking in with the Sector Keeper
and getting today's official phase and sector assignment.
Boys, boys and Ian, phase two, sector three is Bubba Gump,
Starbucks, Cold Stone Creamery, and Red Oven Pizza.
Good luck, boys and Ian.
All right, there we go.
All of these.
OK, look on the surface, some of these things are fairly perfunctory.
Some of them are things that we have covered in previous sagas before.
But the thing that is different here is Ian and Ian's excitement,
seemingly about your time in City Walk, about past memories in City Walk.
So, Ian, if you would like to calibrate us to your feelings about City Walk
or even anything in this particular sector.
Absolutely.
I think what everybody needs to know is that the Sector Keeper sent me here
and it was through a Beetlejuice like function.
Anytime anyone mentions Allentown or anything related to Allentown three times, I appear.
And so when Jason mentioned Dorney Park and then Christine Taylor,
Allentown legend was mentioned, and then Tim Heidecker was mentioned,
that's what drew me to the City Walk saga.
And that's why I'm here today.
When was all those?
These are all just recent things that we've we've talked about.
I have vague memories of some of it.
The Tunnel of Love, Dorney Park came up a bunch because they had a mill chute ride for many years
that was called Mill Chute and then later journeyed to the center of the earth.
But it was essentially a dark tunnel of love that ended in a shoot the chute drop.
Right.
And I was researching all that very late the night before and we recorded it in the morning the next day.
And as I was like heading home, I was like, oh, I should have asked Ian if he had any memories about this.
And sure enough, when it came out, I woke up to messages from Ian about the trout fishery.
The trout ponds are still there.
Just move down the road.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
When when the discussion of famous rivers was happening, I was yelling at my phone, the Lehigh River, the Lehigh River,
because that's where the trout hatchery and fishery is in in Allentown, Pennsylvania.
So they just kind of shifted them up the river and over into a smaller place.
It's on Fish Hatchery Road for those that would like.
That follows.
Yeah.
Is there anything about the fish hatchery or fishery that is themed that would warrant an episode?
There is actually.
So it so the Native Americans, the Lenape are that was a fertile ground for them to fish.
And it also was the site of turtles and things like that.
And Lenape culture, they believe that the turtle that the universe was created on the back of a turtle.
And so there's really cool markers along the it's called the Little Lehigh that feeds into the Lehigh and explains some of the Lenape culture.
But it's also through a grant from PBS or the Explorer, not the Explorer.
One of the characters from from PBS leads you through leads you down.
Really?
Yes.
So the PBS intellectual property.
Wow.
Yeah.
And I'll try and I'll try and find that.
But it's PBS 39.
They do a lot of great stuff through the through the community.
They yeah, they're wonderful, wonderful organization.
So but yeah, they've they've continued to keep that fish hatchery portion alive and doing well.
And my kids love to go and feed the fish.
And it's a family friendly activity.
That's great.
Can I ask a question?
Jason brought I've said this.
We just talked about this again for the 100th time.
But just I did I ask you, have you ever fished for pond eels?
Oh, geez, I've never I don't know what pond eels are.
OK, never.
OK.
Yeah.
Nuff said.
Got it.
Yeah.
It feels like something I should know from my journeys to Bubba Gump shrimp, though.
That feels like yes, it does feel like part of that world for sure.
Yeah, yeah.
We're in that zone.
But you were part of why you.
OK, so you were you were summoned here by the keeper.
The sacred words were said, which we didn't know Christine Taylor was one of them.
But now we know for the future.
But in you, you had talked a little about we were DMing about your fond memories of City Walk, Orlando.
Is that a good way to weave us in just like what you know, some City Walk glory years that you because not every guest has.
A lot of the guests are people who were like, please go down to this place because we don't know a lot of guests who've ever been here.
But you, in fact, have a history here.
Absolutely.
My brothers lived in Orlando since 2003.
And so as soon as I hit college age, I'd go down and visit quite a bit.
And I even lived in Orlando for a summer.
I was a legal resident of Florida because at one point my parents had also moved down as well.
So I changed my license and everything.
And my brother and I, we'd go to City Walk to kill time with his wife and just hang out.
And I have a lot of fond memories of just walking around, hanging out.
And then my association with wrestling, they used to tape total nonstop action there.
And so in addition to Ring of Honor, which we filmed a couple of times there last year, I used to go down during those summers and see TNA wrestling.
And now I've worked with a lot of people that since that were on those TNA tapings like Samoa Joe, Christopher Daniels, AJ Styles, whether it be for prolonged periods or short periods.
But I think my most embarrassing story was one of the only times I had the courage to actually talk to a woman outside of a school situation or anything like that was at the beautiful Starbucks.
Right when you walk in the nice open air area and it would later be someone that I'd work with quite a bit.
So I don't want to finish that story, but please let it be known that I asked her if she'd like to go see wrestling that night.
And she said, yeah, I'll be there.
And she certainly was.
She was part of the event.
So wow, it was a it was a wrestler is who you were attempting.
Yeah, it was somebody that that ended up being on television.
She wasn't on TV at the time yet, but she would be making her her debut that evening.
So, yeah, I didn't I didn't get turned down and it all worked out because I met my wife about eight weeks later.
So, oh, wow.
All good.
Geez.
Okay.
All right.
So it's a happy story and you got to you got to meet a future co-worker.
This is great because the fact that you have anything resembling a moment or a story in a Starbucks is huge for us because this is our third saga.
We have we've had to deal with Starbucks in some cases several times within a series.
And I don't know what else there is to say.
You characterize it as beautiful.
It seems it may have moved since the one that you this is something we have to be on the ball about to is tracking where the location of start because Starbucks is one of those flux locations.
It kind of moves within city walk establishments.
I remember it being in the same place.
I remember it being when you walked in as you kind of walk down.
It's open air.
I don't remember it initially being that big.
And that could be the difference.
I think it is more real estate now than it did.
This would have been 2006.
I have a ton of really fond memories, too.
In 2020, we needed to get out of the house and Universal Studios said, we're opening up, baby.
We're going to be the first.
We're going to beat Disney to the punch.
We COVID who cares?
Wear a mask.
Come on in.
And my brother's down in Orlando.
My parents, my parents were probably the most at risk in terms of COVID.
We check with them.
We said, hey, can we bring the kids down?
We're going crazy.
It's been four or five months.
They said, sure.
My brother said, sure.
And then we snuck off the Universal Studios.
And I'll never forget the fun we had on that trip.
It was about 100 degrees because it was in July 2020.
And we had a ton of fun.
I felt so bad for the Grinch.
The Grinch must have just been sweating profusely.
Grinch out.
He doesn't even that's not the season for him.
No, no.
And he was out waving.
And the Starbucks.
I just we taking taking my daughter in who was who just turned one.
My son, who our son, who's about to turn four, just the joy on their face to do something.
And then they had figured out what cake pops were.
And those are those are relatively safe for kids and good portions.
So just the joy of them being able to walk around and see the Grinch wave at them as they came into the city walk area and then go into Starbucks.
It felt like that's when things were kind of getting back to normal, even though in my head I was like, do not do this.
You're going to get COVID.
You're going to not be able to work for a ring of honor.
You're going to get pulled off the tapings.
But it was a calculated risk worth taking.
And that trip in particular was so much fun.
And it started with Starbucks.
Wow.
Geez.
This is far more than I thought anybody would have to say.
Thank God you've really come through because I feel like we're kind of obliged to do more than 60 seconds on all of these places.
And speaking of obligations, let me get this out, because now that we've discovered at this point in the saga,
we've realized that we are responsible for some material about City Walk Hollywood that updates things since the last time that we did it.
And so this seems like probably we've got to get this out for the sector keeper's sake.
Since the last City Walk saga, the Starbucks moved from what I think was Sector 14.
I could be wrong.
It moved up to a part of a space up top some stairs that was formerly occupied by Karl Strauss Brewery.
And it was there for a year or two.
And then it moved back to the original location where it was the first time.
Which I believe expanded the original location.
I think it took over part of the Blaze Pizza, too.
Okay.
Yes.
Blaze Pizza.
Okay.
I knew there was something up over there.
All right.
There has been a change.
I think it moved to the top of those stairs so they could redo the original space.
Because I could not figure out that when it was at the top of those stairs, I'm like, you have to walk up a flight of stairs and then walk down the flight of stairs with your piping.
You know how you like to get a piping hot cup of coffee and go down a full flight of stairs surrounded by strangers?
I just couldn't figure out why it moved.
And then when it moved back to this bigger space, I was like, okay, this makes more sense.
Well, and Jason, also the word Starbucks never left the original location.
So that was always confusing, too.
Why is there a giant, huge, empty space that says Starbucks and then you walk up to it and nothing happens.
And instead you got to go somewhere else, walk up a flight of stairs that where you can't necessarily fully see the word Starbucks.
And as I learned one time, a stroller could not clear the aisle.
I couldn't get my stroller all the way through after I took an elevator up with it.
This was a very frustrating situation.
Thank God rectified Starbucks backs back where it belongs.
Yeah, but for now, for now.
But who knows?
Yeah, these Starbucks, they're wily and all of these outdoor malls.
You never know where they're going to pop up.
They might show up underground.
They might show up in the sky.
We don't know.
Toothsome could just close and become a big Starbucks.
That seems like the most likely prediction.
It's possible.
In Hollywood.
Orlando.
Oh, I don't know.
Orlando is doing perfect.
Toothsome seems there to stay.
And feel free to toss in other Starbucks memories if you have them.
I'm also going to maybe point the direction towards one that I'm worried about content wise.
Maybe we just need to get a bare minimum done.
Cold Stone Creamery.
This is in your sector.
Does anyone have anything about the fairly nondescript Cold Stone Creamery?
I do.
Good.
Thank God.
I put this on the list for my wife, who's an amazing trooper.
She goes through all these wacky missions.
She has lived with me long enough to know that if there was a Kmart or an Ollies or anything on a road trip, we were likely stopping to check.
Oftentimes, I didn't buy anything, even if I found what I was checking for, which is my wife's least favorite thing that I do, which includes clearance out video games and action figures and things like that.
I just need to check and see if they're there.
But the Cold Stone, this is the thing that made my children maybe the happiest.
And we had this for dessert.
It also served as a refuge for my soaking wet children who decided it was going to be fun to run through the journey into your imagination style water shooters that they have out in the water fountain.
Yeah, we didn't have a lot to say about that either.
So this is actually cool.
How did those, as opposed to the Hollywood ones, which have caused all manner of trouble in our mythology, did your kids like those?
They did.
They loved them.
My wife and I, before the trip, decided that we were going to be a little less hands on, that we are too much no, no, no, and that this was the trip where we were going to let the kids make a little mistakes here and there.
And it cost us about one hundred dollars because we had to buy them dry clothes.
They ran through the fountains.
They had the time of their life.
Unfortunately, the sun went down by that point and it was maybe forty five to fifty degrees that day.
So they were there, brother.
We were not going to let them get sick.
You know, but the fountains were very cool.
They were a little less predictable.
It was kind of like and it's going to be a far out reference that the game show Press Your Luck, Michael Larson was the greatest Press Your Luck competitor of all time.
He figured out there were three patterns on the board to get the big bucks.
And all he had to do was figure out which one it went on and he could time it.
And he won one hundred and ten thousand dollars on Press Your Luck back when the highest base was only five thousand.
Right.
Oh, wait, there's documentaries about that.
Yeah, this is a big story.
The guy who like who games the system.
Yeah.
And he did it perfectly legally.
He just figured out where the lights went.
So then they figured out how to randomize it.
And so that people couldn't do it.
I think that's what CityWalk did.
Because when you're at imagination, you can kind of figure out the pattern.
I was looking at this thing for all 10 or 15 minutes when my kids were running back and forth through it.
I couldn't figure out where the water was jumping.
There was more than one outcome for each fountain.
It was crazy.
It was it was awesome.
So I think maybe a kid Michael Larson did and figured it out and they had to change it, make it completely random.
Larson did.
OK, so they come in soaking wet.
So you're you are you're operating at a financial loss.
But now now cold ice cream is there a reward with we had promised them ice cream.
And yeah, I mean, it is what it is.
I'll say this.
It was as cheap as it is in Allentown.
So among theme park desserts, it ranks relatively inexpensive because the portions are still gigantic.
They're still as big as I remember it at Coldstone.
It was good.
It was quality.
And I think each of the kids things were like seven bucks.
And I think mine was like eight.
They gouge on the soda.
I think the soda was like, you know, four.
But right.
Yeah.
But the ice cream, you know, we got we got decently sized stuff for what you'd expect to pay in the suburbs.
So can I ask a quick question as far as far as kid preference?
Because oftentimes I Jason or I, but oftentimes myself, I choose something on a menu that might be aimed at seven, six year old, five year olds,
because it has a lot of colors, sprinkles or jimmies, as Jason might say.
How do your kids do?
Do they do they order like a birthday cake remix or do they go for something more sophisticated?
Yeah.
My son figured out that you don't have to color in the lines.
And it's dangerous because we let him at Dairy Queen, for instance, go and mix the Reese's and Snickers.
And the one time he did Reese's Snickers brownie and we and that's like I mean, it was almost to the point where they couldn't spin the thing because just OK.
There's too much stuff in it.
Plus, it added like an extra dollar fifty or two bucks or whatever.
So, you know, we we've encouraged him to be creative.
But now that he can read, he reads well, he could figure out what's on the on the menu.
My daughter, Nora, she just wants chocolate and sprinkles.
If it's chocolate and it's got sprinkles, that's that's for her.
So little mix of both.
I'm a I'm a strawberry boy.
If it's got strawberry, I like the strawberry shortcake.
So that's usually what I get at places like Coldstone.
I am also a strawberry boy.
If we're talking about the core three, the Holy Trinity of ice cream flavors, I am strawberry boy.
Absolutely.
And I'm a person who thinks that strawberry shouldn't be in the Trinity.
I don't think it's I don't know why it's a primary.
I it's fine.
I'll have some strawberry ice cream.
Jason, what do you think?
You think that's the Trinity?
I think chocolate vanilla strawberry is usually we're talking the appaltine.
That's the Trinity.
I like the what is it?
It's pistachio cherry chocolate.
That's another that's spum.
Yeah, that's been money.
That's not that's a different religion.
That's a different but I prefer that.
I like you know, I do like chocolate ice cream.
I think I like, you know, fudge and chocolate chips more.
Thank God you're clarifying this, Jason.
I think the audience was concerned.
It is different.
But like so if I like chocolate or not, if I can get a good quality vanilla
and then get some fudge and some chocolate chunks in there, you're not okay.
Long story short, you are not like Ian and I and you're not a strawberry boy.
Not a strawberry boy.
That's fine.
I did learn recently of a fudge boy that Cold Stone Creamery, they default to the sweet cream a lot,
which I saw someone were like making a short video working at Cold Stone and they're like,
well, sweet cream is just basically plain.
Like it's just the default ice cream, but there's no, you know, vanilla beans or vanilla extract, you know.
It's a vanilla without even vanilla in it.
That's right.
Flavor.
Now that sounds godless to me.
That sounds like I don't know how you even do that.
Well, I think I think at Cold Stone, it's just a base to put a lot of toppings in.
Oh, it's almost like they're creating their own ice cream.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah.
Depending on the toppings, the fixin, whatever, fixins or whatever they call them.
Jimmy's.
I'm glad you're putting this in religious terms, though.
You've kept that consistent, Mike.
Thank you.
Ice cream, the religion of the show.
I well, let me see.
Now I can't decide whether to veer to because I just feel like, you know, we should give,
if we need to shortchange one, we can, but it feels like we should give ample time to the real star of the sector,
which has been the previous star of a sector, and that is Bubba Gump.
And you, Ian, jumped at that.
You seemed like, OK, you're in town.
You're going to go do a family night.
You were more than willing to have Bubba Gump be the main feature of your city walk evening.
Absolutely.
Something strange happened.
My wife got really into it.
And it was, you know, we're sitting at my parents who live in the middle of the Ocala National Forest,
which is like, you know, seventy five to ninety minutes away.
And we were we had a lot of fun and we were going to, you know, we were going to see him a lot that week.
And I looked at my wife and I said, you want to go to Universal tonight?
She said, sure.
And so we loaded the kids up and we realized the city walk parking was more than we remembered.
And so we made the decision to see if there was any hotels at the in the area,
because in my mind, if I'm going to pay 40 or 50 bucks for parking and the hotel is 100 or 125,
might as well just do it instead of driving back late at night with the kids.
So is that what we're talking parking wise?
By the way, we don't really know what we didn't park there.
So we don't really know what we're dealing with.
Yeah, it got up to Disney levels.
It's pretty high and it didn't used to be that was that was one of the big reasons I used to see wrestling there,
because it was a easy night out wrestling.
The TNA wrestling was free and parking at city walk.
I think after five or six at some point was free.
And that wasn't the case anymore.
So we I think maybe the free parking starts at like nine o'clock now or eight.
It's like very late.
And the kids the kids bedtime is usually, you know, on a on a vacation night, it's eight o'clock or nine o'clock.
So we couldn't wait to have dinner until then.
So we figured, you know, if we're putting 40 percent of that toward a toward a room, why not?
So we got a room at Endless Summer, which is this is where I segue all the Beach Boys talk into.
Oh, sweet.
Yes.
Yeah.
And that's a phrase in their world that they use all the time for titles of lots of things.
And I thought earlier it was a big parable for using biblical terms, a parable for summer in paradise.
We were discussing all of the the failed expectations and things like that in the previous conversation.
But got an awesome room.
Very nice premise.
And I'm sure you'll go over this in the hotel section.
Well, this now look, OK, we clarify this in a later sector.
We did make the choice.
The other sector keeper made the choice.
Right.
You know what?
It was never it was never said.
So we just didn't because something has to be out and hotels had to be out because this is OK.
We've we don't know how long this is going to go.
So I don't know.
I guess if I sound defensively and it's because you've now if the audience is now wishing and hoping for a hotel sector, I don't know what to say.
Hotels were out of downtown Disney ordeal.
So this is in keeping with tradition.
Well, that's I can I'll keep it quick.
We had a beautiful view of an abandoned hotel that is probably going to get demolished and bought by Universal Studios and for another resort.
And we had a good to do.
Dunkin Donuts that were fully operating.
And but the hotel itself was actually beautiful.
It was nice.
It was Disney quality.
It was bright colors, you know, beautifully clean head to toe.
It felt it felt like an experience.
And the kids really got a kick out of it.
Super high ceilings.
Awesome.
You know, check in the.
Checking counter again, something comparable to what you'd see at the Disney Resort.
So they were pumped up right then because they had no idea.
And they didn't even care if we were going.
They just love hotels.
So they didn't care if we were going to the park.
They didn't care.
We're going to city walk.
They were just there's a big Christmas tree because it was like there too after Christmas.
So they were they were jacked up and we take them into the room.
We get them kind of dressed around.
We get them in some warmer clothes because we know we're going to be walking.
And then we hop on the bus.
The transportation is awesome.
It's like a two minute ride.
It's right outside.
It's more convenient than almost any Disney resort, maybe besides Polynesian contemporary.
You know, those Magic Kingdom ones like it is hop, skip and a jump.
You're maybe a mile away entrance to entrance.
So already this is this is great that, by the way, bodes well for the epic universe situation where there's been the concern about
will the transportation be complicated sending people a little further away?
But if you had a good, pretty sound situation, maybe that bodes well for the future.
Yeah.
And the road design over there.
So the endless summer used to be wet and wild and wet and wild.
You know, it was isn't a relative.
It seems kind of relatively inconvenient.
It's off I drive it or was.
But the way they siphon the traffic and create a new traffic patterns actually worked out really well.
So it's right off I for you know, if you go left, you're at the summer.
If you go right, you're at Universal.
You know, can't recommend it enough.
And it was affordable.
I think it was only for a room Christmas week.
It was like, you know, one twenty five or one forty nine or something around there.
Yeah.
And so we got the kids ready.
We told them we were going for dinner.
And I'm telling my wife, I said, I don't know if they're going to like this.
It's you know, I looked at the menu and there's a lot of Cajuny things.
And it's about the movie Forrest Gump and which which came out.
Let me just do some quick math here.
I think forty nine years before they were born.
That's right.
And then the irony of it is that I saw it in the theater in Florida with my parents and my brother.
So this is all coming full circle.
I'm having like a crazy like, you know, every everything setting off a memory.
Even driving from my parents' house, we stopped at the Turkey Lake Service Plaza, which used to have an awesome kind of
retro Burger King that has since been remodeled to Wendy's and a Dunkin Donuts.
But it's still there.
So all those memories, like the time I shot my dad with ketchup and I thought I was going to die because it's the maddest I've ever seen him.
Whoa, whoa.
Yeah.
So I'm just like, this is beyond belief and everything's going wonderful.
So we get there and they couldn't have been nicer.
And you walk in and it it feels like you're in the movie.
I can't stress enough the attention to detail, you know, within Bubba Gump Shrimp.
Now, is anybody going to talk about the parking garage?
Because I have some fond memories of that as well.
I believe that is the plan.
You know, the Sector Keeper hasn't divined it all for us.
But I think it's I think it's worth mentioning here.
Yeah, you were alluding to this, like the the fond feelings just in the buildup of the garage.
I say go for it.
Yeah, it's again.
I didn't know this was kind of in me, but I kind of flashbacked when I was the first time I went to Universal was 1995.
I was sort of an eight.
And I just remember seeing all the different monster movie characters and Jaws.
And they just started to put up like a Jurassic Park parking section.
If it wasn't that trip, it was the trip after.
But you start to hear all the scores from the different Universal movies.
So they drop you off on the bus just under the parking garage and you take an escalator up to the garage where they security and your ticketing and stuff like that.
So you go through security and then there it is.
The beauty of that city walk and Bubba Gump is on the left.
And I'm still feeling this.
I have endorphins and nostalgia and stuff I haven't felt in years, which I didn't know I had for Universal.
I knew I'm addicted to Disney.
Like I have it for Disney.
Absolutely.
But this experience unlocked it.
I'm almost sitting here thinking like there must be like years and years of built up.
But it's almost yeah, they like unlocked it.
Yeah, because we only as a family went to Universal maybe two or three times.
I mean, ninety five, two thousand.
And, you know, I've gone I've gone with my wife on kind of a solo trip like 13 or 2013 or 14.
So, yeah, with the kids and then we 2020.
So, yeah, there wasn't a whole lot of memories, but this time it was just like, there it is.
And it was really cool, but I never I'd never eaten a single Bubba Gump shrimp.
I lived in New York City for four years.
I never went to the one in Times Square.
I had always been kind of curious.
But Bubba Gump's the kind of place where you can't really say like, hey, guys, you want to go to that hot new restaurant, Bubba Gump?
Like, it's never something that could be suggested.
But now I had an excuse and I'm so glad I did.
You have to.
You could tell your family a ghost child's life depends on it.
Yeah.
And they they were fully understand they from the jump when they heard the sector keeper was involved, they knew.
And so we walked down, we went to the left and it's right there.
It's one of the one of if not the first things you see.
And it's I think physically the first thing you can choose to do.
It's right on the aisle.
It is a dramatic.
It's like it's a prime position in the city.
Well, for sure.
Yeah, it is.
This whole stretch is like stuff tempting you.
Like early in the day, it's Starbucks and Bubba Gump.
And then when you're leaving, it's like, oh, do we need another meal?
Should we go to Bubba Gump or should we get ice cream on the way out?
You know, yeah, in a lot of ways, these are like the sirens on the cliff calling to the sailors.
Are there dangers that lie in these places sometimes?
Yes.
Yeah.
And there was nothing, no danger involved in Bubba Gump.
I mean, we walked in, you know, there it had the cool.
I don't know if you guys remember the old school Long John Silver's that used to have all the details.
Yeah.
So it was it was that but better.
You know, the wood floors, wood panels, the ropes, the the safety buoys on the wall,
the pictures of a forest with different folks, license plates across the walls from the different spots that he was in the movie.
There was just left and right.
Everything was detailed.
Pictures of Jenny everywhere.
So you know what I'd forgotten about was like the the folksiness,
like I'm looking at photos where there's a lot of like kind of grandma knickknacks,
like that, you know, pots and little ceramics and, you know, whatever.
There's like metal, those platters or whatever that you put up on the wall.
You know, things reminiscent of mama.
I think mama's spirit is especially strong in this location.
Yeah, I would I would have to agree with that.
And it was I'm trying to put my finger on it.
It's almost this is going to sound like the craziest thing that's ever come out of my mouth.
It's almost indescribable.
It's it's just it made me really happy to be there.
They treated and I think it was, you know, they treated my kids really nice.
They made a big deal about making sure that they were taken care of.
Well, there was there's this cool thing.
It's it's almost like Foa de Chow where instead of where they have the green and the red for the meat,
they have a thing you can flip over if you need service or if you need help,
which made it really convenient, especially with kids,
because you didn't have to flag anybody down and chase them down.
And my kids really got a kick out of just everything involved.
They had a they had a menu.
And I'm going through my pictures now where you could draw yourself next to Forrest Gump.
And for some reason, both my son and my daughter just gravitated.
They wanted to put themselves next to Forrest.
What is what is Forrest to them, though?
Did you have to explain and is the explanation because the explanation is complicated?
Well, he sort of he's this like cipher who appears in all of history.
And, you know, and you got to be careful with certain aspects of it,
given that it's an actor playing a type of person that he is not, which we don't see as much these days.
Was there any difficulty in explaining to children what the hell this franchise is?
Say like, you remember the Polar Express?
Is that where you start from?
Is it an easier explanation?
Well, he's kind of that guy.
We we explained Forrest as a nice character from the movies that really wanted to help his friend.
And he made a restaurant in the movie to commemorate his friend that he had a boat with.
And that was that's really sweet.
That is.
Yeah.
You didn't have to get in the hole.
Like, well, he kind of journeys through the second half of the 20th century and represents a lot.
And encounters a lot.
Yeah.
There's a weird sequel book where he meets Tom Hanks and it's kind of a metathagos.
That's not that's not an important thing to tell your children at all.
There's a script.
There was a script.
They were going to make a sequel and then some events occur that kind of made it like inappropriate.
And a lot of people kind of agree.
It probably should have been pulp fiction.
So history doesn't look too kindly on it because that was like the new Daring movie.
But it's still I don't know.
Wait, wait, did it did it really get delayed because the 9-11?
Supposedly the legend now is that like, oh, yeah, we had a script ready to go and then we were going to go of meeting about it on September 11, 2001.
Oh, my goodness.
But who knows how much that's apocryphal, like how much that's like it just seems a little too perfect.
Well, this is I'm seeing it.
Eric Roth screenwriter did say he turned it in the day before 9-11 and that it had.
Wait, I saw what happens in it like OJ's in it.
Oh, my God.
He's he had Forrest in the back of OJ's.
No, no.
What do you mean?
He was in there.
OJ's in the back.
He can't be in the back.
That's where OJ is.
Al Cowlings is driving.
AC.
Yeah.
Does he?
I don't we're getting close because he said I think he may have been in the federal building in Oklahoma.
No, no.
Yeah, that's what this is.
This is bonkers.
This is so not now.
We got to read this.
He danced with Princess Diana.
Not on the night of he wasn't like in a tragedy.
It's all far as wandering.
So is the first everybody dies.
That's true.
Everyone has topical illnesses and illnesses or wars.
Yeah, boy.
Oh, oh, oh, Jay's Bronco makes no sense, though.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, hang on.
I had forced in the back of his Bronco.
He would look up occasionally, but they didn't see him in the rear view mirror and then he'd pop down.
He was back there and they didn't know what events would possibly transpire.
And they were going to play a murder as a site gag.
Like, yeah, Peter's.
He was he was a gun to his head in that moment.
Right.
If he misfired, he's like, OK, I won't kill myself accidentally pulls trigger while putting gun down, goes right through the seat into forest gum skull.
Well, was what was that?
Was he hanging out with OJ that night?
Then like, why was he there?
He like just stumbled into the car.
Maybe he do Kato.
You think I think he was friends with Kato Kailin.
Oh, I could see that.
Maybe he's trying to start an acting or modeling career.
Yeah.
And his buddy has like, I'm staying in this guest house right now.
OK, what are the odds?
Do they cast Kato or do they get an actor to play Kato?
I think if his price is right, you just get him, get the real guy.
Yeah, nothing has ever had a lot of trouble getting Kato Kailin if they want him.
If you Irishman Kato Kailin, so he's more era appropriate, I think it would be fine.
So you age him down at this point.
Yeah, Dial of Destiny face thing to Kato Kailin.
And I think you use them.
I think it's because it's the technology is perfect now.
So you may as well.
So nuts.
I'm really glad I know about this now.
I just don't.
I feel like we could spend the rest of the time trying to figure out what
what logical way for us could end up in this car.
But we can't do that.
We've now distracted from what was a nice meal.
Yeah, I know.
Sorry.
No, it's wonderful.
I didn't explain.
I haven't yet broached the topic of OJ with my kids or, you know, Jenny's untimely demise.
And, you know, it's crazy because as I get older, I almost appreciate my parents or things
like that, because they did take me to see Forrest Gump when it came out.
And they did give me reasonable explanations that weren't outright lies.
And so I think one of the parenting skills over time, I think that is super valuable,
is the ability to not not lie to children in you don't have to tell them everything.
But if you start to explain something and give them enough, like this was a man who was
in the army with someone and they had a shrimp boat.
And then his friend passed away and he started a restaurant like that.
You can kind of leave it there.
And my dad always seemed to be really good at that, you know, just giving you just enough
information.
And the one thing I couldn't explain was why they gave my kids light up flashing
glasses because they heard the kids drink.
But by the end of the trip, which is only a day and a half, we did.
We ended up doing the park the next day.
We ended up with six total light up glasses.
Wow.
That's like Mike's kitchen.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I mean, yeah, my kitchen five to seven years ago, maybe.
Well, yeah, because now you have a lot of catching up to do is what I'm saying.
What's the new what's the latest in your kitchen?
My you're talking about me?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I don't actually know.
I think we have two spaghetti factory glasses from San Diego that are fairly recent.
They're kind of nice glasses, too.
They're not plastic, but they don't light up.
They don't light up.
Sorry.
But they are novelty restaurant glasses.
We just got some nice Disney on ice ones when we saw the number two Calypso artist of all time, Sebastian performance.
It's not just the girl.
Oh, what a callback.
Yes.
Yeah.
Buffett number one.
Sebastian the crab number two.
You're the archivist.
Wow.
That's right.
That'll go on the record.
Let me ask you, when you went to Bubba Gum, did you guys meet the mascot?
I wish I if you go through my Instagram pictures at any length, you will see that it is either me and my family with mascots, me and my family at theme parks or me at a wrestling event.
Those are your three choices.
And unfortunately, we did not meet the mascot.
I was aware of the mascot existing.
We did meet Bumblebee, the transformer the next day.
Oh, wow.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, we met the Blues Brothers.
So we did.
How do you begin to explain that to your children?
That's tougher than 9-11.
Yeah, there are two guys that came out of jail and they hated Nazis.
And then they had to raise money.
Yeah, I don't think I could simplify that.
No, it's too complicated.
Daddy, was this did they think this was funny or cool?
Well, both both kids.
Well, it's like when you do get around to explaining, oh, yeah, you you know, do it gradually and you start with the dancing Edo's.
I'd forgotten about that.
Yeah.
What led to this?
So what inspired this for this classic sketch, Dad?
Okay, I'm going to jump to one of the naked gun movies as I buy some time to think about how to explain this.
I do need to jump in.
I when reading about public, I figured out I had once again convinced myself of something incorrect.
The mascot's name is not scampi.
It is Shrimp Louie.
It is a different dish that I was confusing with Shrimp Scampi.
Whoa.
Okay.
Scampi.
Yeah, I know.
It came up.
It's come up recently.
Now we couldn't remember it.
And then we all believed it was scampi.
And look, if you maybe you might hear episodes where different names are used in different sectors, depending on when these come up.
So let's I get the confusion about this is never going to end.
No one's.
Yeah.
Let's just keep making up names for him to change it every time and then never mention it from here on out.
Yeah, because he's in he's in a top hat.
So, you know, I would.
What is that?
You know, the fancy, fancy lad, our friend fra Diablo.
Everyone, everyone loves it.
Call him Pinky.
I guess his name is Pinky.
It is surprising.
Pinky is simpler than Shamp Louie.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, maybe like Hat and Tails, you know, because he's these fancies got both.
Mr.
Hat and Tails.
But he brings the tail no matter what.
Yeah, that's good.
All right.
From here on out, we'll be we'll just try to add more confusion.
Yeah, no, different, different name every time.
That's the rules of a name.
I already shrimp shrimp Louie you're saying, but we may bail on Louie.
Huh?
It's really for that.
It's it's an impossible mythology to find.
Really?
Like nobody's I don't know.
Maybe there's maybe there were some like coloring pages for kids to clarify.
But I think there's a reason they have not like hammered this into our heads.
Yeah.
I'm looking at I've just blown up on my screen a picture of my son coloring in the coloring guide.
He colored in forest and he put himself they have a box of chocolates that you can color in, which is pretty neat.
You can circle the Bubba Gumps that you've been to in the United States.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Well, that's pretty neat.
And then it has all the locations from the movie, which is pretty cool.
And what was neat about that?
We like to drive down.
It's cheaper, but also it's fun.
The kids play their switches and tablets.
And so that map was kind of cool, too.
My my son realized what the states looked like on the map because they're and so he said, Daddy, when you said Georgia, where is it?
And so I pointed to Georgia.
And so we had a brief geography lesson about some of the states that we just drove through earlier that week.
Oh, geez.
It was an educational man.
Wow.
That's that's great.
Yeah.
This is informative and fun.
What did everybody think of the food?
Because you had the risk of like Cajun.
Does that not make any sense?
Right.
So the kids, thankfully, and again, we had a server that was terrific on top of the kids drinks and everything.
And they got the special drink, which was kind of a Shirley Temple thing, but not really.
I think they did it custom that night.
It went in the collectible cup.
So I think what they did, they put the cherry ice with Sprite and did like a little mixer thing that wasn't on the menu.
So we got like a secret menu item.
And yeah.
And they got Zach got the chicken strips and Nora got the I'm sorry.
Let me look here.
Nora got the chicken.
Zach got the mac and cheese, which is fine.
Like no Cajun.
What you default to is the parents bread and butter right there.
Yeah.
And our literal bread and butter also.
You can't go wrong with that.
And I got the what was it called?
Of course, we have scampi.
I think is the official name of it.
I wrote it down here and I love the menu.
But not of course, the character's name is scampi.
Right.
It's not an of course.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's called Of Course We Have Scampi and my wife got the jambalaya.
So we both really liked it.
We again, it was it was crowd.
It was busy, but we were able to kind of eat at our own pace.
We didn't feel rushed.
The service was great.
Everything about it.
I took a picture of so this is how to the detail this restaurant is.
I took a picture of an Ed Hardy thing to send to my brother and laugh because Ed Hardy is objectively hilarious at this point.
And 2024.
However, I didn't realize that Ed Hardy designs were in the Forrest Gump movie because of the year at Hardy started designing things.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
So if you look up at Hardy, Ed Hardy design stuff came out.
Where is it?
It came out in the in the 70s and it would have been around the time that Forrest Gump was in was doing his thing coming out of the coming out of the armed services.
And there was Ed Hardy stuff and Ed Hardy tattoos and things in the movie.
And like there's little Easter eggs like that.
And then there's the restaurant where seemingly untied together things.
The attention to detail is so great that if you look at the license plates, they're all from places that he was at.
If you look at the the end, Hardy stuff, it's all from something that was tied in the movie.
Like if you were if you were a super fan of AEW and you had an AEW restaurant, you would you'd want this level of detail.
I'm sure there is a Forrest Gump super fan somewhere.
And I don't think they'd be disappointed.
They just every like everywhere he went in this place was just little Easter eggs.
And if if I'd seen the movie within the last 10 years, I probably would have picked up even more.
It was it was nuts.
It's really weird that there's there's just not any equivalent to like, you know, it's it is a it was a huge movie and an Oscar winning movie and a big box office box office success, too.
But there isn't like it's not a franchise and franchises are like the only thing that inspire any physical spaces.
So it's so unique because there isn't like I'm trying to think of like an equivalent hit like this is weird.
It's similar tonally, but of course it wouldn't make a good restaurant.
Like I'm thinking about the Shawshank Redemption.
There's no maybe it would.
I don't know.
It might be interesting being Shawshank.
But like it just if you were just told again, this is whole chain and they don't know.
And it's like you're like you're in a prison.
But it's fun, though.
And this fact's about making the movie and, you know, like Tim Robbins shirt and whatever.
It's just like you buy that almost as much.
It's just it's it's so singular and strange, the existence of this place.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really why it's like I'm a big Joe's Crab Shack fan.
And this is like basically you could it's like a more detailed Joe's Crab Shack.
Now, I haven't been to every Joe's Crab Shack, but the one in San Diego, it feels like, oh, like Joe's Crab Shack is the unlicensed for a scump restaurant.
They just don't have the they don't have the attention to detail.
They don't have the little touches.
Who's Joe?
We don't know anything about him.
Did Joe ever meet any presidents or inspire any famous rock stars moves?
Right.
Joe is no one and nothing.
So so yeah, I guess my point is just that like it's so weird because it's the movie and then it also just feels like it's almost like a better version of an existing chain restaurant or a more specific version of it, I should say.
Yeah, I think the only time in history that's happened was was Arby's and Roy Rogers, right?
I think we all agree Arby's is the punched out version of Roy Rogers.
Oh, I don't know about Roy Rogers to weigh in.
I've never had Roy Rogers.
It's good.
But in my opinion, Arby's is better.
Really, Jason, what do you think?
I there used to be a Roy Rogers up the street from where I grew up that eventually flipped to a McDonald's and then Roy Rogers became like only president at East Coast rest stops, much like the famous Allentown, Pennsylvania rest stop.
Very centrally located off of I-95.
Is that right?
Four seventy six.
Okay.
So I was always excited to eat at Roy Rogers because it was like a rare white elk.
You'd only see them at rest stops.
Right.
Interesting.
But do you think it's better?
What do you think about it?
First is Arby's.
I think Arby's is probably more consistent.
Sure.
I know Roy Rogers has gotten me sick a few times.
Oh my god.
More fondness about places that get you sick.
I don't think Arby's has.
I think I've been okay.
I've not eaten Arby's in a long time, but definitely at the end I was eating the chicken strips a lot more than the roast beef, which I always liked.
At the end.
At the end of your Arby's?
At the end of my Arby's run.
Towards the end.
That's what you're talking about.
A parent.
And you know, and at the end, you know, there were some rough times, but also a lot of perspective.
Well, because.
And a lot of roast beef.
Arby's would go on to open up the street from where I lived.
And so in high school it was often a quick go-to spot.
Right.
The glory days.
Let me bring up something that I've learned about Bubba Gump that we didn't get into the first time we did it in the first sector.
And that is the founder of the person who we have to thank for this chain.
Do you mean Tom Hanks or Robert Zemeckis?
I mean in some way, yes.
But no, I'm talking about environmentalist, entrepreneur, consultant, author, motivational speaker, and of course restaurant founder Anthony Zelezzi.
I'm going to share my screen and show you this.
This this info is all courtesy of friend of the show, BugmaneBuzzBuzz.
Here I'm going to share my screen and you will see something from his website.
And there's a picture of him putting his finger to his temple next to a Bubba Gump sign as if to say that I thought of it.
I thought it up.
Anthony Zelezzi was a like worked in food in all manner like packaged food, frozen food.
And then he got a job for something called Meridian Products, the world's largest shrimp lobster and crab consolidation company.
Sounds good, right?
Wrong.
Meridian Products fortunes were dwindling.
Their sales and margins were declining.
So they brought in Zelezzi, a genius from other companies, to help them find new growth vehicles.
And he had seven months of very little traction or change.
Things were not working out at Meridian.
And then one day he put on the movie Forrest Gump and had the aha moment as seen in that picture.
When this is where his own website gets confusing.
When he saw the character nicknamed Bubba Gump reciting a list of the well, that's not true.
No, Bubba Gump is the two names.
Even he doesn't get it right on his site.
Anyway, the part where Bubba is doing the big list of all the shrimp, all the ways that you can cook shrimp.
He reminiscent of what Jason did the other day with hot dogs when Sector Keeper put him on the spot.
Anyway, that big list happened and he's like, wait a minute, we could do all those kinds of shrimp.
And the next morning he headed straight to Paramount Pictures where he's, I assume he just walked up to the gate and knocked on it.
Anthony Zalazze here.
But he did secure the licensing deal for both shrimp and chocolates, all of it.
So for a while, and I don't remember this era that Bubba Gump was frozen shrimp.
It was a grocery item first.
And then the California restaurant, the Rusty Pelican, he worked with them to create the brick and mortar establishment, which was a tremendous success.
So now we know we have a guy here.
I think this is a guy, but a guy for good.
Wow.
Thank you, Mr.
Zalazze.
We now we know who specifically to thank for your nice meal.
You can thank Zalazze.
I have a lot of respect for his tan, but also his apparent care for eye care because he has a tremendous tan, but he has like the aviator block out around his eyes.
So that tells me this is a man that he knows how to look sharp, but then also got to protect those eyes.
Got to protect the eyes.
Maybe he was pointing to his eyes in that photo, actually.
I'm protecting them.
Check once or twice a year.
Get them checked.
We can all take a cue from Zalazze, his creativity, his self-care.
In telling that story, we missed before we move on to the last restaurant of the sector, do we miss anything about your very wonderful experience?
Sounds really nice.
I can't stress enough.
Again, this was also reasonable.
We got the big sampler.
Let me look up the official name here.
It is the and it was plenty of food for every for all four of us run across America.
It had shrimp, hush puppies, chicken tenders, Bubba's far out dip, chip sauce.
And it was really good.
And it was what you'd expect from that level of restaurant.
Yeah, I think I have an idea of what it would be like.
Yeah.
And then the kids meals came in boats and little paper boats.
So it was really neat.
Again, if you have kids, the kids stuff in particular was very reasonably priced.
It helps really balance out the meal.
The portions were pretty gigantic.
So don't go on anything but an empty stomach because you will get a lot of food.
And it just overall.
Yeah, just a really, really great time.
And that was the point where my wife and I looked at each other and said, we have to take the kids to the park tomorrow because we thought that by walking around City Walk, they realized there was a giant theme park.
But they didn't because they got too into the water fountain.
So we probably could have let we probably could have went to the hotel and just drove back.
But I think it was my wife and I at that point that were like, yeah, we're in for tomorrow.
We better make sure there's tickets.
Wow.
You like us had a whole world of fun, not even involving the theme park.
And the main thing is there's a recurring thing with guests of this saga.
A lot of guests have been having trouble with food and or getting sick.
Yesterday was Eva, who we haven't revealed what happened to her and where yet.
But there's a real bad pattern forming.
So, Ian, please tell me that you and your family made it through your City Walk experience without our curse.
Oh, yeah, it was.
Yeah, we were fine.
Yeah, yeah, we we ended up stopping at Turkey Lake back on the way home from the theme park the next day.
Again, we got Dunkin Donuts there.
It was just every everything went well.
We got to see my brother briefly even before we, you know, before we left Orlando, he came down to Ocala.
It was a great trip.
But really, the the exclamation, the kicking it off at City Walk with the convenient transportation,
just the the nicely priced and good food.
Yeah, that really set the tone.
Wow.
It's well, that's beautiful.
And this this might provide rationale of why this this fact I'm about to say is true.
And I don't know if everybody realizes this.
Bubba Gump is the only restaurant that is present at every single City Walk across the globe.
Oh, wow.
The only thing this was a lot of things are a lot of establishments are at three.
But Bubba Gump's the only one which is at Hollywood, Orlando, Osaka and Beijing.
So it's really this is kind of this is our this this restaurant has been our gift to the world, our gift to Asia.
And it has to serve as an ambassador of American culture.
And it seems like Ian thinks that that is justified.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I do.
It did leave me with some regrets, though.
You know, you reflect on your life as you get older.
Like I said, I lived in New York for four years.
I had bad meals at the TGI Fridays in Times Square.
I had bad meals at Hard Rock.
There Bubba Gump was there the whole time.
I could have just went to Bubba Gump and and save myself the gastroenteritis, you know, the gastropane that came from the other meals and probably save some money, too.
I mean, you could that's that's something that will haunt you.
But I don't want you to beat yourself up too badly about it.
Just a little bit.
I appreciate that.
It's you know, a lot of it was resolved by good memories going to the Toys R Us across the way in Times Square and and and check checking the wrestling action figures.
Yeah, those were never on discount, though, were they?
At that point?
Yeah, not in the Times Square.
Yeah, that was not a discount heavy location.
No, no, no, they clearanced out the game.
They clearance out GameCube games, though, right as I got to college.
So I had a big score of a couple of games for four dollars there.
But wow, that's pretty good.
Yeah, something.
All right.
Those are bad memories that outweigh the years of the loss of Bubba Gump.
Well, you know, probably the nice thing would have been to like, you know, go soaring out on this high note of Bubba Gump.
We do have to address red oven pizza.
Let's put at least a minute on the clock.
Red oven pizza.
OK, I've been there on two trips and it has been fine.
It's fine.
And you know what?
Fine is saying a lot given some of the other things that we experienced during this saga.
I've had pizza there, salad there.
It is fine.
Jason, agree?
Yeah, I ate a mushroom pizza.
It's like a larger personal pizza.
I don't know.
I like 12 inches across.
I was headed into the airport.
I ate some of it there and then I took some of it with me and ate it at the gate.
Wow.
Oh, you took it through security.
You took a pizza through security.
Well, it was in like a tiny box at that point.
We might have to bump up the rating.
I find it's my delineation whether or not I pack it in the bag to go through security.
I think that's probably better than fine.
I bet you and Jason have a different scale when it comes to saving food, if it's based on how good it is.
Well, this was pretty good.
I mean, the Orlando airport is certainly not lacking in culinary options, but I was like, this was good.
And it was pretty easy on the stomach.
So good for flying because, you know, I have a question.
This is actually I don't know if I've ever done this.
Do you have you ever taken leftovers on a plane?
Yes.
Did you travel a lot?
I do.
So I've snuck things out of AEW catering and other others have as well.
So I've taken some cookies.
They have these nice boxes because at AEW you could you could be there just to have an interview.
And then you might be able to just sit back and watch the show for the night.
You might be there to have a match.
It might not be later earlier.
So they have these nice boxes that as they're putting the catering away, they'll kind of give a last call.
You can fill up a box to take back to your room or to hang out, watch the rest of the event.
So when I'm there for dynamite or for anything like that, I will normally fill up a box because I don't know if I'm done.
But the time for dynamite or if I have to go in for a ring of honor or whatnot.
So I'll have something and there's good enough desserts where I've snuck that that's not but I've taken the desserts back on.
Checked it through, not checked it through, had it on my carry on, got it through security.
And would this food be accessible if like, I don't know, a friend or podcaster came to visit you?
You shared fond memories of Allentown.
Would that would that particular person maybe be able to also sneak away with a box or two or five?
Could you say, Ian, could you just say like, I need an intern?
It doesn't have to be college age.
I just need a guy to help me out.
And then he's just going to kind of come with me backstage and have access to all the areas, especially the areas sort of with all the layout, the food and stuff.
Are we trying to get Jason to smuggle some food out?
Yeah, look, I just saying hypothetically, I don't want to say who specifically.
I'm just saying, is that a possibility?
Sometimes in wrestling, getting stuck in catering, that's a negative connotation.
I'm like begging, like just drop me in catering.
I also like Jason Sheridan, food smuggler and Indiana Jones type adventure.
That's cool.
With the plane, the plane line going from dot to dot internationally freeing food to its rightful owner, him.
Smugglers run, Jason Sheridan, smugglers run.
Some of my coolest wrestling memories have been in AEW catering.
That's how I met Ric Flair and talked to Ric Flair.
Whoa.
By the way, is the most amazing smelling person you'll ever meet.
What?
He smells like a it's kind of like a like a fireplace mango.
And it's wonderful.
And I don't have the nerve.
I didn't have the nerve to ask him, hey, where do you get that cologne?
Because I don't wear cologne, but I'd wear that because it was it was pleasant.
It was welcoming.
But it was also like it had like a it had like a hey, I'm here.
The kind of vibe to it.
So.
Okay.
Yeah.
But, you know, I've gotten to, you know, I've sat and eat, you know, I don't want to drop too many names, but.
Go ahead.
Oh, yeah.
You know, Paul White has become a friend of mine when we've done commentary together, the big show.
And so it's fun to sit and have some more private moments with with folks that otherwise I just kind of work with here and there and just kind of move on.
So, you know, the A.
K.
W.
room is a fun place to be.
And yeah, I've still I've still a lot of cookies.
I'll be honest.
Let's come clean.
Yeah, I've still cookies and brownies.
My cheesecake.
Yeah.
Wow.
They got a full.
They got how many cheesecakes are back there?
Oh, geez.
These are people that can eat a lot.
These are these are very strong people that can consume a lot of calories, I assume.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
You know, they they watch what they eat in a lot of ways.
But in other times, you know, depending on where you are in your diet, you want carbohydrates to make your make you look more vascular.
So, sure.
Yeah.
There's a lot of cheese when there's cheesecake.
There's a lot of it.
This is the place to be.
I got to get in there.
God, I mean, I don't want to brag.
I'm in a web A.
W.
web series.
I play a dog's agent.
I'm Johnny loves tie.
I want to look at that.
Right.
Well, you haven't plugged that properly.
May as well get me back.
I may as well be back there.
I'm basically on the roster.
Let's let's throw that plug at the at the end to after the just tag that on.
So, yeah, I know people can find that.
Sure.
But for now, we probably should head to that point, especially because, oh, my God, now the stone is appearing.
There it is.
My God.
It's it's incredible.
Well, this one looks like.
Wait.
OK.
I think it's OJ Simpson.
But he's wearing an Ed Hardy shirt and light up flashing glasses.
Wow.
Well, that may seem so much more fun that way.
What a great tribute to the great time that you had in and in Rick Bani.
Oh, my God.
You survived podcast, the ride, the city walker, Orlando Saga, multiverse of madness.
Let's exit through the plug portal.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, Mike mentioned Johnny TV, who was recently on Ring of Honor.
He's been on a W's been on Ring of Honor.
He recently won custody of Dalton Castle's boys.
It was one of the most heartbreaking moments that we've ever seen in Ring of Honor history.
So we have a big, huge event called Supercard of Honor.
It's on April the 5th.
It's at the Leah Kora Center.
It's going to be that Friday night.
There's a big weekend that weekend.
And we're a part of it.
It's on Temple University's campus.
Tickets are moving real fast.
Mike, you were you were able to come to last year's version in Hollywood.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So this year, tickets are moving just as fast.
So if you go to our R.
dot com, you can get your tickets there.
And I have a feeling that Johnny TV is not going to be let off the hook and that Mr.
Castle might, you know, be willing to try and punch his face in again.
Seems likely.
And any details released about the catering, the catering situation back there?
What's the access going to be like?
What's the cheesecake scenario?
Yeah.
Strawberries on the top of the cheesecake.
Oh, yeah.
For the strawberry boys.
Yeah, we've had that.
Yeah.
So.
Hell yes.
Just to screw Jason, I'm doing the internship.
All right.
Boy, I had the idea.
That's my idea.
It's going to be it's going to be a blast, though.
And then, yeah, every Thursday, myself, Caprice Coleman, where the voices of Ring of Honor, I pop up on A.
W.
from time to time.
Little Matt Excalibur, he beat me again in the Wrestling Observer Newsletter voting for announcer of the year.
But but that's all in good fun until I steal his mask and then he won't be able to do it anymore.
That's right.
I'm coming for you Excalibur.
But yeah, we're but we have a blast and I hope everyone can join us on for Supercard of Honor.
It's going to be live on Honor Club.
So if you got the Honor Club subscription, it's only nine ninety nine.
It's yeah, it's one of our biggest events of the year.
It's fantastic.
Well, yeah, that that sounds great.
And so glad you could join us for this.
Somebody with some true city walk affection and nostalgia and recent memories seeming like the best ones.
That's great.
And I'm happy we didn't make your family sick.
OK, thanks, Darren Gardner for the art, our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the theme music.
Multiverse of madness.
Merch in our T public store for the full saga experience.
Subscribe to podcast the ride, the second gate or get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector on Club 3.
That's all at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
I believe this closes out this phase.
We'll see where we end up going tomorrow as we head into the I believe the seventh of these.
We're almost at the full week.
Mark, I hope you're keeping up with us and and not to throw more stuff at you.
But again, what is the Web series, Mike?
Oh, Johnny loves Ty.
It's on the official A.
W.
YouTube channel.
It's a reality show, reality show.
But I play the dog Johnny and Ty as dogs agents.
Wow.
Show.
So we should put we should put like somehow tie our universe to that universe so that sure the next episode only makes sense if you go watch that.
Oh, that's smart.
Yeah.
Mitch is on an episode as well.
Mike Mitchell is on from Doughboy's on an episode as well.
Wow.
Sweet.
OK.
Head there.
Check it.
Do that and then come back to us tomorrow because we got more coming in for a lot of days still.
So we'll see you then.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.