Forever!
Dog!
Audience, audience, when we last left the Good Boys, they were ripped apart from each other and scattered into different corners of the multiverse.
The only way they can fix the dimensional rift and reunite is to record separate solo podcasts about stuff at malls next to theme parks.
We take you now to Scott's End of the Multiverse.
La Nuba Boys.
Bonjour and welcome to La Nuba Boys, the only podcast that offers weekly analysis of Cirque du Soleil's 1998 to 2017 show at downtown Disney Orlando, La Nuba.
I am your ringmaster, Scott Gardner, joined as always by Le Fou, the Fool.
Just kidding, just messing around with you, you know I love you.
Buzz, buzz, buzz, the Prince of Jesters here, the Bugmane.
You walked right into it, you proved my point.
Bugmane is here, back for more La Nuba talk, it's us the La Nuba Boys, what's going on?
Welcome back, obviously La Nuba is an unforgettable journey through our universe, at once threatening and exhilarating, frightening and familiar, La Nuba is the story of all stories.
You know we talk about it every week, the site of all mysteries is La Nuba, that is within the theater.
The site of La Nuba is where dreams and nightmares for a brief period of time, 19 years, slept side by side in this theater, nightly, dazzling audiences.
Absolutely, not only nightly but dazzling.
There was never a night that it didn't dazzle.
If that ever happened, I'm sure they would have shut this thing down in a heartbeat, but they kept that standard up, it never didn't dazzle.
And the thing about it is it beckons to us, it beckons to us, it challenges us to uncover passions we thought we'd lost long ago.
Basically, if you're imagining you're in Orlando and you've never even seen something so earth shattering.
You maybe have never seen a circus, you've maybe never been to an art gallery.
You've never left America, you don't know about these cultural things that are happening, you don't know about the Blue Man Group, you don't know about David Fincher commercials,
the movie Toys with Robin Williams, you don't know about these very artistic things until Disney through the lens of Cirque du Soleil delivered it to you in La Nuba and with the DVD delivered it in mass.
Then to the world.
I don't like these podcasts that become this dense web of references that you don't really understand and you don't really have an in on so it's hard for new people to come in.
So I do like to explain the basics of La Nuba, which of course from 1998 to 2017 performed at downtown Disney.
And I became first aware of it on a trip to Walt Disney World, which was fine.
I'm not particularly interested in theme parks, but I remember being bored in the hotel room thinking I go there's more of this Disney World trip to get through.
And then there's an ad for the things that you can go do at downtown Disney at downtown Disney's west side.
And it's this clip.
I like to replay this whenever I can just to recall how La Nuba first spoke to me.
The Cirque du Soleil show La Nuba is a remarkably unique family experience unlike any other on the planet.
Where feats of physical bearing and acrobatics meet the artistry of live music, magical effects and awesome design.
You've got to see it to believe it.
I mean, that says it all.
I mean, you get so much in that 22 seconds you get if we just analyze it first, you're going to be in the big tent and the free standing structure that they built just for this at downtown Disney.
Disney has its castle, whatever with its spires.
But if that doesn't speak to you, then what is your version of the castle going to be?
And for me, the just the gleaming white of the La Nuba tent.
That was my cat.
It's sort of a euro minded artistically minded alternative for the Disney castle was the La Nuba tent, which spoke to like the kids who were weird.
You know, if you felt like a weird kid, kind of more interested in culture and nuance and enrichment.
I mean, I was a kid that grew up loving Renee Magritte.
And to finally reach that age where, OK, enough with the kids toys and the Cinderella's and the Peter Pan's.
It's time to get cultural.
It's time to.
I was such a Magritte kid.
We talked about this the first day before the podcast, and we were just doing the podcast just for fun out loud.
And we hadn't actually started the thing yet.
And who could have dreamed of the success that we would end up having?
I mean, you know, so many so much so much great support.
So many people subscribing to the La Nuba boys do play on the Patreon.
Still Nation.
And in that space where La Nuba briefly existed and on October 22nd, 2004,
they filmed the staged live performance for the DVD, probably one of the most banner and finest sites in French artistic and experimental theater.
Yes, of course.
And as always, we suggest and encourage you to consult your own copy of the La Nuba Pro Shot DVD from October 2004.
And we'll be reflecting on a particular element of that.
And again, not to be redundant is this episode 48.
So you know what we do.
But every week on this show, we do rate and review a different sequence, moment or act from La Nuba Cirque du Soleil's finest show.
There's a quote in this commercial.
This was the TV ad for La Nuba, which has a quote that is that is really striking.
And I just want to get, you know, get your thoughts on this.
Cirque du Soleil presents La Nuba.
Now astounding audiences at the downtown Disney West Side to see it is to know the color of imagination to see it is to know the color of imagination.
Is that not how it makes you feel?
Even just watching the DVD.
So La Nuba is almost a new color.
It's a new kind of and the thing you can watch La Nuba.
Let's just be a little respectful.
Obviously, you don't want to wear your Disney Mickey ears to La Nuba when you're going to see it.
We're in an artist's world, but we're not so stuffy.
That was what was so beautiful about it and the performance in 2004.
It's not so stuffy.
You're not going to, you know, some actual European art exhibition with tuxedos and champagne.
No, it's not elite.
It's extremely accessible.
Yes, exactly.
It's inclusive.
Basically, just kind of wear a collared shirt.
Wear your nicest collared shirt.
And that's what you see when you watch the DVD.
And as always, we encourage you to watch the DVD or if for some reason you don't have a copy of the DVD, you can go on YouTube.
There is the video Cirque du Soleil La Nuba, Subtitulada, then space and then AVI.
I guess that was the that was the file name.
But if you, you know, if you're just coming into the show for the first time, go look it up.
It's about 90 minutes.
It's a breezy 90 minutes.
Just watch the full pro shot version of La Nuba from 2004.
And in that you're going to see these audience members see what they were wearing at the time.
You'll see their nice collared shirts.
You'll see their golf resort hats, their band in dune hats, their van dykes.
Yeah.
A few van dykes, tiny spectacles, tiny glasses.
James Taylor post 1999 glasses.
It is they cut to audience members of at least the older men in the audience all look like plaid era eagles.
They all look like hell freezes over hell freezes over eagles or better.
Ben Affleck and Chasing Amy and in their heads, plaids, bowling shirts.
Every one of their heads holds the memories of 9-11 in the 2004 DVD.
Even the children.
And guess what?
Like I was saying, they are their bowling shirts are nice bowling shirts that they're wearing.
They chose their best bowling shirt.
They're choosing at this time.
You have to remember in the early 2000s bowling shirt penetration is full.
So these young men are looking at a closet of probably a dozen bowling shirts.
They pick their finest one.
And they yeah and they do they know this.
Yeah, this is I can't do like the silly yellow one with the Hawaiian pattern.
This has to be kind of an austere maroon and black.
Something that shows a little bit of respect to these Frenchmen and their artistry and their dignitaries.
They come ambassadors, ambassadors I was going to say of culture.
Of culture to us.
But we also have to show up and give our best.
You know, these are our best applause, our best smiles, our best laughs at the clowns.
Our best Van Dykes, our best bowling shirts.
Always our best Van Dykes.
And you know, these are people in the audience that are fans of hitman comedies.
The year is 2004 and they and they you know, they love lucky number seven and they love you know,
They love to get shorty and they can't wait for be cool.
They can't wait for.
Yeah, they even saw Big Trouble.
Yeah.
To be perfectly honest.
Yeah, even despite.
They even saw Big Trouble after the delay.
Big Trouble showed fear where La Nubia showed bravery.
Big Trouble changed their ending.
They didn't back down.
Yeah, they didn't.
And they kept going.
You know, there was La Nubia was performing on September 10th and then I don't know when they came back after September 11th.
But I bet it was by the end of the month.
That much I know.
You know, they didn't say we're done.
We're going back to France.
They stayed in Florida because that's what Giuliani wanted.
That's what George W.
Bush wanted.
And, you know, our finest cultural institutions had to keep going.
And La Nubia, the finest, did.
There's old men in Orlando, Florida, who have just paid $500 and drank a double Jack and Coke,
wearing Hellfreeses over plaid shirts and James Taylor tiny glasses with their brother in a Van Dyke and bowling shirt.
Inside of their brains are the memories of 9-11 and Barry Sonnenfeld hitman comedies.
And they're going to get their mind blown and exposed to European sensibilities on that night of October 22nd in 2004.
And they're going to like it.
Also, an olive branch to the French people in general.
At the time, we're talking about freedom fries, not French fries, because of their perceived cowardice.
It's a cliche.
Yeah, it's a cliche.
Wow.
We are rejecting French culture in a big way.
And what better way as an ambassador to France than their other great cliche art?
You know, Scott, La Nubia takes you to a new realm where dreams and nightmares collide and your fantasies reach new heights.
Another way to reach new heights is with today's sponsor, Bluechew.
Absolutely, Bug.
Increase your performance and get that extra confidence in bed with Bluechew,
the first chewable with the same FDA approved active ingredients as Viagra and Cialis.
You can take them any time, day or night, even on a full stomach.
And since they're chewable, they work up to twice as fast as pill.
So you can be ready whenever an opportunity arises.
Bluechew is prescribed online by licensed physicians.
So you don't have to go to the doctor's office or wait in line at the pharmacy.
And it ships right to your door in a discreet package.
They're made in the USA and since Bluechew prepares and ships direct, they're cheaper than a pharmacy.
Right now we've got a special deal for our La Nubia boy listeners.
Visit Bluechew.
com and get your first shipment free when you use our special promo code NUBACHEW.
That's B-L-U-E-CHEW.
COM.
Promo code NUBACHEW.
N-O-U-B-A-C-H-E-W.
NUBACHEW.
To try it free.
Bluechew is the better, cheaper, faster choice.
And we thank them for sponsoring La Nubia boys.
S'il ménifique.
You know, I shudder to think of if there was an alternate universe where La Nubia hadn't hit as hard as it did in ours.
I shudder to imagine a world where La Nubia doesn't get the respect that it deserves.
And people listen to podcasts not about this, but about trash.
Just like garbage.
Yeah, exactly.
It's infinitely dissecting subjects that no one can care less about, to be perfectly honest.
That are fluff, that are hollow, as opposed to what we get to do, which is revisit La Nubia again and again.
And, you know, some fools, le-fooze, think that it might get bore-ele-foo.
I said it.
I'm not afraid to say it.
You might think that this podcast would run its course.
That you could only do one of these and then you'd be done.
But we keep finding new angles on La Nubia, new information about it.
Bug, I've been dying to tell you about this.
I finally, I've been meaning to.
I watched the 1999 Bravo hour-long profile of Cirque du Soleil, which is of course called Run Before You Fly.
And I learned a little bit of information about how La Nubia came to be and how it showed up at the Walt Disney World.
Oh, wow.
Now, you know, we're a little, we're kind of invested in full Cirque du Soleil history.
And this was, of course, you know, the mid-90s where they had just done their big show by the Santa Monica Pier at the pop-up tent.
And that was causing all kinds of Hollywood interest.
And we've been through this before.
But, you know, that's when they almost signed the deal with Columbia Pictures that Columbia Pictures was going to make a full Cirque du Soleil movie.
When they showed up on our shores, it was with a bang to be perfectly honest.
Honestly, in a nonviolent way, the equivalent of Godzilla showing up on the shore in Tokyo.
Exactly.
Or Pearl Harbor.
Yes.
Yeah.
It was like an inverse Pearl Harbor that was for good.
Yeah, that was for good.
And that they didn't cower and run away from the fight.
They were the ones bringing it.
But artistically and culturally.
Yes.
Yeah.
So, of course, who catches wind of Cirque du Soleil?
We got to do something with Cirque du Soleil, the Walt Disney Company.
Michael Eisner, full context, since we never really talked about him on this show, he at the time was the CEO and chairman of the Walt Disney Company, like through the 90s and 2000s.
You might have heard of him.
So he saw Cirque du Soleil in Santa Monica.
We have to lock this down.
Can we get this a presence in Walt Disney World?
They were interested.
Guy LaLiberté, who again, just to orient people, just so this podcast is always accessible.
Guy LaLiberté, the founder of Cirque du Soleil, who was a homeless busker and stilt walker and fire eater and is today, due to his Cirque du Soleil profits, the 11th richest Canadian worth $1.
2 billion in Canada's first space tourist.
I'm sorry to say all this again.
I know you know all this bug.
You know all about Guy LaLiberté.
No, what I didn't know though was I didn't really know to draw the direct line to Michael Eisner being the patient zero of the hell freezes over dad being completely inundated with culture and blowing his mind.
He was the ultimate hell freezes over dad.
He was the perfect patient zero.
If you look at him, if you look at a photo of him at that time, he does look like James Taylor, but with less wild hair.
He absolutely he was like maybe the most powerful James Taylor type.
Yeah, in Hollywood.
Yes.
First of all, never knew this.
He wanted to buy the company.
He almost bought Cirque du Soleil outright.
Guy LaLiberté said absolutely not.
Integrity.
Yes, he has integrity, as we know.
It's what made him the 11th richest Canadian.
So then it became all right.
Well, can we do a show?
Can we do something at Walt Disney World?
And you guys point there and the biggest sticking point in the negotiation was Disney not wanting to give over full creative control artistic freedom to Cirque and Guy.
And ultimately you have to take a leap of faith when you're dealing with Guy.
Why do the deal?
Don't even talk to Guy if you're not going to do the leap of faith.
And ultimately that is what Eisner realized.
And he personally intervened and said there's no reason to do this unless we give them it would be like asking Guy to not eat fire.
Absolutely.
You don't look at a fire eater and tell him today for breakfast is a bagel.
So listen to this quote from Michael Eisner again for context.
It's like asking Guy to not have oxygen in his in his lungs or fire in his belly.
His belly belongs on fire.
That is that's that's what Guy LaLiberté is about.
So here's this is quote Michael Eisner.
The Hollywood people are used to he was a pussycat.
Amen.
I'm glad a Hollywood great that he he compares correctly.
Finally, Guy LaLiberté to Lucas and Spielberg.
I'm glad he actually came to his senses.
Yeah.
And rationalized it with his friends.
And gave them the artistic freedom, which led to why we're sitting here today.
We wouldn't be sitting here today without James Taylor, Dad, patient zero, Michael Eisner taking a leap of faith.
Take it.
Taking a leap of faith after taking a double Jack and Coke and drinking it.
I also then there's this piece of footage from the Bravo documentary where this is going to as you as a fan, you're going to go nuts because I'll just ruin the first frame of it.
This is Guy LaLiberté on a motorcycle driving through downtown Disney.
And you can see you're not see you.
Hey, you could do whatever the fuck you want if you're Guy LaLiberté.
That's Guy for you.
He doesn't just ignore stop signs.
He ignores ignores every sign.
This guy, you know, he sees a sign.
He takes a gulp of fire from his fire belly and he burns that sign up.
Yeah.
Guy sees a stop sign.
He goes.
He reads it as he reads it as he has flipped his own brain.
So here he is.
And he's driving on a motorcycle past the Virgin Megastore, past the Disney Quest.
I mean, what a zone this was at this time.
I feel like this downtown Disney at this time is where the millennium happened.
The millennium happened early in 1998 and it happened with the incredible VR at Disney Quest and daily at the Virgin Megastore.
As people sampled Moby, as people put on their headphones, they listen to their Moby.
Then they went to Wolfgang Puck or Bongo's Cuban Cafe.
And then they capped off the night with a double Jack and Coke and Lanuba.
Yeah, they got they got they got themselves a butternut squash soup at Wolfgang Puck.
A new flavor.
A new.
That was nobody had that in America before 98.
No, no, no.
And then they had themselves a barbecue chicken pizza flatbread, a flatbread.
Now, not a not a we know this word now.
Now we're accustomed to this word, but a flatbread barbecue chicken with a butternut squash soup in 1998.
I mean, who but Disney and downtown Disney was even ushering the millennium in like I don't think any other company was saying it is coming.
You put the cookies out.
You welcome these holidays and no one else was even ushering the great millennium in with the respect that Disney was and with the face of Mickey's face,
facing the future, facing the future of the new millennium.
Obviously, there was a House of Blues deal with Cirque du Soleil.
There was a Wolfgang Puck deal.
You mean you're talking about the meal deals where you could you could pair it.
It was like, you know, you pair wine and cheese.
Well, Cirque and Puck Wolfgang Puck.
What now?
Now.
So perfect.
They're they're aesthetically of a piece, too.
You go into Wolfgang Puck and there's the beige or yellow right next to a checkerboard pattern.
And then that's all caught up.
Yeah, a kooky sun on an upside down pyramid light that has some some colored glass in there and and also mosaic tile.
There's a mosaic tile on a column over there.
I look over there.
There's not a mosaic.
There's not mosaic on that column.
Just on this column has a mosaic.
It's not about matching.
It's not about uniformity.
If you feel mosaics on this column, do it.
If you don't, if you just feel a goofy moon on this column, just do that.
And you imagine, imagine you're a James Taylor dad.
Tiny spectacles, a Rolex watch, collared shirt.
You're there with your bowling shirt, Van Dyke.
You're in Orlando.
You woke up in Orlando this morning.
You had an extra eight hundred dollars.
You're going to spend that eight hundred dollars.
You now find yourself at the brink of the millennium, tasting tastes like flatbreads and sushis and butternut squash soups before you go.
Sushi in America.
Did I wake up in the wrong country today?
Sushi in Orlando.
And now I'm going to go see a Frenchman on a tricycle while I'm drinking a Double Jack and Coke.
I just spent five hundred dollars.
My son is here.
He's going to.
This is the first time he's going to masturbate.
He just saw that girl's body right there.
This is the first time my son's going to masturbate.
I'm sitting here in Lanoe by my belly's filled with butternut squash soup.
And I'm drunk.
I'm drunk.
I'm watching a Frenchman.
I woke up in 1998 one way.
I'm leaving and I'm in the year 2000.
The next day that just happened because of Disney.
Michael Eisner funneled the vision of the millennium into all the like minded James Taylor's and Hell freezes over is like him.
It's what Eisner could see with his tiny glasses that other CEOs of companies couldn't.
He could see the synthesis of the millennium of butternut squash of your first masturbation.
He could he could triangulate all of it.
He saw through the matrix before even there was a matrix.
There wasn't that film yet.
You're Michael Eisner.
You're curating the idealized version of the millennium.
He told Dan Aykroyd put some Jack Daniels in that damn barbecue sauce for those ribs at the House of Blues.
Yeah.
And it paid off.
And guess what?
You can go and see social distortion or the cotton mouthed Kings.
Yes.
Usually the cotton mouthed Kings at the House of Blues.
You go from the cotton mouthed Kings at the House of Blues to a belly full of butternut squash and a Frenchman bouncing a tricycle on your lap in one night.
You come you you're from Minnesota.
You went into the culture matrix brought to you by Mr.
Eisner himself.
I got right.
Drive to my job.
All right.
Your fill in my data.
Go home.
All right.
Meal with the kids.
How was your day?
All right.
Fine.
It's the same thing every day.
To then break out of that.
Go to Orlando experience a cultural melting pot.
Something that combines Jack Daniels and cotton mouthed Kings and a Frenchman with a long nose.
It was hiding but then peering out and then saying hello and then doing strange gestures with their hands and little feathers up top.
You have a flatbread.
You're drunk.
You and yes your money is now in Michael Eisner's pocket that you brought to Orlando.
Did he not earn it?
But did he not earn it?
Yes.
It's tough to go back.
It is tough to go back after you go to La Nuba.
You're a dad.
You just had some great silent very silent drunk drunk sex.
You get back there.
You have a you have a belly full of Jack Daniels.
You're drunk.
You have butternut squash.
Now you're trying to have silent sex.
You're trying to have silent sex in the contemporary with memories of the rag dolls still dancing in your head.
And the walker there underneath your little hat that your top hat that you tipped up now there in your head.
The new but he brings his hat up and the the call dancing on there his head.
Now you're dancing in sugar plums dancing in your head.
You're there.
You you lost your money.
You have no more money.
You're leaving the contemporary tomorrow with no more money.
But you what you've gained what you've gained culturally.
Michael Eisner.
Wolfgang the millennium three days in Orlando.
And all of a sudden you've seen the best of what the world can offer in 1998.
You're sent back to Minnesota a better person because of Michael Eisner.
You're sent back better.
You're sent back.
He fixed you.
He was a cultural doctor.
He diagnosed everybody.
He saw what they were missing was Jack Daniels ribs.
Cottonmouth Kings and jesters.
He curated a medley dish the best of the world for you.
Yeah.
In the year 2004.
This is a pivotal moment for Eisner as captured by Bravo's cameras.
Here is Guy riding through downtown Disney and he picks up somebody along his way.
Hi Michael.
How are you?
Pretty good.
Where are you from?
Coming from the desert.
Wow.
This had a long ride.
You want to have a ride with me a little bit?
Absolutely.
Come on in.
Excellent.
Oh, he's getting on.
Yeah, Eisner's getting on.
See this is also artistically what he did.
Yeah.
Got him on the backseat.
He took him for.
We are right now are watching and we'll post this to our Twitter so everybody in Stilt
Nation can see this.
This is really the moment that makes it all happen where Michael Eisner hesitantly, you
know, he's not sure where to put his hands.
He's not on a motorcycle all the time, but that's the trust that he puts in Guy.
It's analogous to the artistic the artistic trip that he took.
He had to trust Guy.
He didn't know where to put his hands when he got on the back of Guy's motorcycle the
same way.
He didn't know exactly how to how do I put the financial box together for you to do.
Do I take creative control?
How do I?
But yeah, ultimately, he put his hesitant shaky hands on Guy La Liberté's midsection
and they rode off into the sunset or at least eight feet forward to where there was a cut
point and then Bravo went to commercial.
Seemingly he didn't fall off.
I don't think so.
At least not artistically.
At least not in this take.
This might tie us together nicely.
Why don't we take the tightrope over to la performance de la semaine, the performance
of the week.
The main thing we will be analyzing on Lanuba Boys.
My favorite segment.
La performance de la semaine.
The cycle sequence.
We're so lucky.
All this talk of motorcycle and Eisner on the motorcycle.
This is the part of the show where you know you think you're watching some stuffy like
Dad, what is this?
I should be back in my room listening to Everclear or Everlast.
I should be listening to one of the Evers.
I don't want to be here watching some stuffy French circus.
All right, well, what if we told you that this circus has BMX bikes in it?
A spoonful of sugar makes medicine go down, the cultural medicine.
You're also getting sonically the music.
You're also getting visually the costumes.
Now for a kid, BMX, that's a spoonful of sugar to get the cultural medicine go down.
They knew that.
Gee knew that too.
When you're up to that point, what's the number one coolest, newest, newest sport, action,
extreme, X games, X games, X games?
What is BMX?
That is incorporated.
Gee seamlessly incorporates BMX into his not just a circus, masterful, La Nubia piece of art.
It's going to get the dad.
It's going to get the kid.
Well, yes.
And as we've talked about a number of times, La Nubia was Cirque du Soleil's attempts to do something cool,
to do something for the teens.
If I could quote Franco Dragone, who was, of course, the director of La Nubia and who did pass away suspiciously shortly after doing the Chris Angel, a Mystica show.
All right.
You know, we don't ask too many questions about that.
We honor Franco Dragone and we say thank you for giving us La Nubia.
But you know, this is a quote from him.
After working on previous Cirque shows, I turned around one day and realized that life had gone by and I hadn't seen my children grow up.
I wanted to reconnect with youth to show my 19 year old son that I was still hip.
So that is what this you're reading exactly into it.
This is a show meant to pull in the 13 year olds, pull in the 19 year olds.
That's what I'm saying.
And it's the same thing that Eisner did by putting it in Orlando.
Look, at that point in time, Cirque du Soleil didn't just have to be performed in the marble palaces of the intellectual aughty out in Paris.
No, no, not just for the richest sheiks.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Guila Liberté flipped the whole system on its head.
He was on the streets breathing fire, eating fire.
There's the wealthiest of the wealthy and then there's fire eaters on the ground.
He flipped the system and now he's the 11th richest Canadian.
And I mean, imagine Lefou becomes the king.
It's almost a plot.
It's almost a plot from one of Guy's famous performances.
Yeah, they did do that.
Isn't that that?
That's the story of Mr.
A.
Yes, I believe I think so.
Obviously, we I'm more Lanuba favoring than Mr.
A.
Oh, no, of course.
But we acknowledge their other works.
We just don't like them.
Yeah.
Vertigo and Hitchcock, Guy and you know, you're going to put some of yourself into your work no matter what.
Quote, What helped us get through it was to make the show a tribute to all the teenagers in the world, which injected a lot of energy into it.
And that really reads when you watch the full 90 minute pro shot version of Lanuba, you definitely can tell that this is something that works for teenagers.
I mean, teenagers would love that.
It's a tribute to them.
Rock music.
There's BMX bikes.
They could have called the show Teen Tribute.
I mean, Lanuba is a perfect title, Lanuba, which, of course, means party, party, party, which it basically is.
I mean, it's not Lanuba being a teenager themed experience makes perfect sense.
It's also telling you, listen, this is kind of like a PG 13 show.
Yeah.
You know what?
Maybe keep the seven year old back in the room.
Well, the title tells you that.
How many?
There's children's birthday parties.
But who goes to parties?
Teenagers, teenagers, teen parties.
It's just also a recommendation for who the show's for.
And only a teenager could begin to synthesize and understand the beauty and the artistry of Lanuba.
You can't.
A child could not.
Possibly.
And we should strive for our entertainment to be smarter than a dumb little child could perceive.
At least start at Lanuba.
Yes.
I have a child and, you know, he's about to turn four, not quite Lanuba age yet.
I would say at five, I'm going to start adjusting.
That's a Lanuba boy.
Yeah.
A future Lanuba boy.
I guess he's going to be co-hosting with us in not too long, you know, because we know,
you know, this will be going for a while.
Isn't it nice to have come out of the gate with such audience response to know that we
got 15 years of this thing.
Hey, all you Lanu bots out there and Lanubians, I know that you guys have a little bit of
a feud going against each other.
I see them on the Reddit.
They argue.
I know.
The Lanubians and the Lanubians.
We don't get into it.
We let you decide.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're just happy that you guys are listening.
And honestly, for your son, I can only imagine the joy of putting on a Lanuba DVD shot in
2004, October 22nd on the Vision Pro.
Imagine that.
Oh, yeah.
That's almost as good.
They never would have dreamed of that.
Because he can't, you know, he'll never understand a world where you can just show up with $199
in your pocket to Orlando, Florida.
It takes $199.
And he will never know.
Did I have to make the calculation?
Do I want to bring a child into the world who can't go experience Lanuba live?
Because, of course, Lanuba was replaced in 2017 by a new show called Drawn to Life, I think.
I don't even, I don't, I'm so fucking pissed that they got rid of Lanuba.
I don't even, I'm not even sure what the name of the new show is.
And you can't even go to Gloria Estefan's Bongo's Cuban Cafe anymore.
No.
Why even go to this part of this place?
Why even go to Orlando at all?
I don't.
I don't like going to Orlando.
Because now they've made it, it's now a show that involves like Disney characters, Disney animation.
Fuck that.
That was not the vision of James Taylor's dad.
Or Guy.
This is, we're asking for it.
In terms of like any societal breakdown, climate change, we're asking for it, for spitting in Guy LaLiberté's face.
We deserve worse.
It would be like canceling Stranger Things and replacing it with some other show on Netflix, right?
Yeah.
If we ever get rid of Stranger Things just because the children are all now 26 years old, we would be quitting.
We'd be quitting culturally.
Those parts belong to them.
It's about their essences, not about whether they are still four foot five with their little backpacks.
Well, Liyama, the Peacock singer, Piero Acrobat, the devil, the lost ballerina, and Piero Clown never age in the dream world.
To bring it all back, just to say, I did, of course, My Child Deserves to Live, even though the only way he can experience La Nuba is by watching the DVD from 2004, the ProShot DVD.
And hopefully, fingers crossed, as soon as they work out the kinks with that Vision Pro, I'm going to strap that thing on him.
I don't know if it's too big for a toddler's head.
I don't care at this point.
I need to start getting one.
I would rather, I mean, exactly.
It would be like, I would rather them at least start with La Nuba on Vision Pro than Allegria or, you know.
I know.
I mean, I can't even imagine.
Winduuk?
No, no, no, no.
They're going to put out Winduuk first?
Come on.
Yeah, yeah.
When they, when Cirque starts going through the catalog, if La Nuba is not the first thing out of the gate, what are we even doing?
Shut the company down.
I'm showing my kids a new hope for Star Wars.
Yeah.
Let's just put it that way.
Yes.
Yeah, we can quibble with, we can make up these interesting orders to do it in, but you start where you start.
You start with new hope.
Whoa, whoa.
You know, Bug, Michael Eisner made some great decisions as CEO of the Walt Disney Company.
But if our listeners want to feel like the CEO of the bedroom, they should check out Bluechew.
You can take them any time, day or night, even on a full stomach.
And since they're chewable, they work up to twice as fast as pill.
So you can be ready whenever an opportunity arises.
Yes.
If you could benefit from more confidence where it counts, Bluechew is the fast and easy way to enhance your performance.
Right now, we've got a special deal for our La Nuba boy listeners.
Visit Bluechew.
com and get your first shipment free when you use our special promo code NUBACHEW.
That's B-L-U-E-CHEW.
COM.
Promo code NUBACHEW.
N-O-U-B-A-C-H-E-W.
NUBACHEW.
To try it free.
Bluechew is the better, cheaper, faster choice.
We thank them for sponsoring La Nuba Boys.
C'est magnifique.
So, the BMX sequence.
A couple of cool BMX bikers come out and they do awesome bike stunts.
They hop around, they hop through the audience, they land their bikes on different platforms.
Very precarious stunts.
But it's not just that.
They also tie into the broader theme of La Nuba.
We know that the characters in La Nuba are broken up into the Cirques, the Circus people,
and the Urbains, the Urbanites, and we know them because they wear the dark muted monochromatic colors.
And that theme of urbanism is really handily strung through all of La Nuba.
And here's quote Aguila-Liberté.
We wanted a very urban show that it had to be a modern kind of urban, not something out of Fritz Lang's Metropolis.
That's why you see dot com, shift, delete, barcodes, and so forth on the walls for the high tech element.
These BMX bikers come out about halfway through the, or not halfway, it's at the 30 minute mark, if you want to follow along with us.
And they are wearing skin tight bike suits that say shift and TM and there's a big at symbol.
A visionary.
I can't think of anything cooler than that.
You mentioned this earlier.
This was before the Matrix.
It predates, it predicts, it thematically is getting teenagers involved with the internet, BMX bikes.
You're mentioning these words today and it just completely sunk in.
I can't believe that after all these episodes, whatever episode we're on, I know you guys at home, La Nuba bots.
We let them keep track and you can check the La Nuba boys wiki.
Yeah, if you're counting the Patreon episodes, but basically.
They're dorks.
We love them though.
We love them.
And thanks for subscribing.
Subscribe to the Dublay.
Please just.
Stilt Nation.
Yeah, Stilt Nation out there.
Obviously all the green birds.
Green birds are getting a little crazy on the forums though.
But it's getting.
Well, the Reddit's getting a little toxic.
Honestly, I can't really check the comments anymore because those green birds are, you know, they're just so good.
There's always some complaint this or that.
You know, why are you so dismissive of Zumanity?
Because I, well, because they went too far showing the sensual side of Cirque du Soleil.
Exactly.
I want my son to masturbate after the show, not during the goddamn show.
Yes.
Keep it in your, no, you, you plant erotic visions for them to take home and then go hide in the bathroom, in the hotel room.
Obviously we've talked about this a million times.
We, Zumanity, we have a whole spiel about this, but like I said, La Nuba, visionary.
Gee, is prediction about teenagers now all they're looking at or at signs.
Yeah.
If you're thinking about it.
Because they're on social media.
This was in 1998.
This is before TikTok.
He's putting ads on the BMX bikers.
And now ads are attached.
We, people know our names with ads before them more than they know our real name.
And this is what was, this is what was given to a James Taylor dad in 1998 with his bowling shirt.
It's like Eisner and Gee wanted to give James Taylor dads everything they needed to know, a full toolbox.
Yeah, exactly.
They were giving, given a millennium toolbox from Michael Eisner in downtown Disney of what to expect, the new taste that you're going to get.
That your kids are going to be obsessed with the internet.
You are going to be eating flatbread soon.
You're going to have to get used to zucchini being a regular part of your diet.
Yes.
What if I put a walnut in a butternut squash soup with a little bit of goat cheese?
Wow.
What if I showed you a French clown?
What if a person was bald and pale and had a streak of blue paint next to their eyes?
Are you afraid of it?
You shouldn't be.
You should embrace it.
Embrace the difference.
Embrace change.
Yeah.
The tent in Lanouba was the ground zero for the very millennium itself.
For what was to come in the very millennium itself.
At signs on BMX bikes with a belly full of butternut squash, goat cheese soup.
How does the Lanouba tent being ground zero for the millennium, does this have any relation to your broader simulation theory?
Of course.
It all perfectly synthesizes into my 2001 theory.
My theory, of course, being that everything before 9-11 2001 was a data set memories implanted sort of like Dark City.
Dark City is what they call the city in Lanouba, by the way.
That's also the movie of which I based part of my theory on was Dark City.
Wow.
And the Matrix, obviously.
But basically, Dark City is these aliens replace people every day and they just data set their brains.
You think you wake up in a job and you're a CEO, but actually the day before you weren't, you just have the memories implanted that you're the CEO.
OK, same thing with 2001.
On 9-11 2001, we all woke up on 9-11.
It was the alarm clock data set of all the memories.
Now, what Lanouba fits in, it's the perfect data set of a memory or a dream.
It is within itself the meeting ground of dreams and reality inside of the tent.
Everything still stands.
Even if it was a dream, if it was a dream, a data set, a memory and it never happened, it all still stands because within that tent holds the clues of which this simulation has now been set in motion.
It still has all the clues.
When Steven Spielberg woke up on 9-11, he hadn't made Color Purple or Indiana Jones.
OK, that was just a memory in his head.
But that memory gave him the clues of which to then proceed and make Minority Report.
Yeah, whatever.
Anything afterward.
Now, was he the same Steven Spielberg after 2001?
Maybe not.
He was our Steven Spielberg.
No one was the same.
Yeah, exactly.
Who could be?
Yeah.
But he learned from his own false dream data set.
That's why this Lanouba Ted is perfect.
It actually was the ground zero of what was to become in the millennium after 2001, 9-11.
That's why we always return to this October 22, 2004 DVD taping.
But it still synthesizes, reinforces, reverberates in that little Lanouba tent in 2004 what they set up in 1998.
All those clues are still there.
We still can use those clues.
They still inform our understanding of what the simulation is.
So it fits perfectly in that it is a signature from the Mr.
Simulator up there who made all of this.
It's just a signature.
It's a way of saying, guess what, guys?
You found it.
You pinpointed the exact moment where dreams and reality, data set and reality all converge into one tent.
And guess what?
For this period of time after your existence, you can go back into that tent and watch exactly how I did it.
All the clues are still there for you, Mr.
Policeman.
They're all there.
It's a signature.
It's a way of saying, bug main, Scott, you figured it out.
I'm the simulator.
My crockpot for the millennium was the tent at Lanouba in downtown Disney.
The way I tested it was in this data set, this mishmash, transference world of dreams and realities in this tent.
That's where I put all the flavors of the new millennium into it.
So did you think the BMX stunts were cool?
Yes.
Okay, well, as always, we conclude the show by taking the act that we saw and giving it a rating.
Our rating is, of course, one to eight little shakes of a Jester's Hatbells.
What rating would we give the BMX bike portion of Lanouba?
That's a full eight shakes of Jester Hatbells for me.
Yes.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's a full eight.
You can't get better.
I mean, like we're saying, prescient.
It's written on their clothes.
I mean, Gi is working on a level that is…
Pure Gi.
Perfect Gi.
Yeah, contemporary act BMX bikes.
Contemporary act.
In a European circus, what are you talking about?
Totally surprise you, really like shakes you up just like a Jester's Bell.
And that's why I also got to give it eight shakes of a Jester's Hatbell.
Can't get any better.
Eight shakes of a Jester's Hatbell.
Well, then it goes in the Super Shake Club along with every other part of Lanouba
because we have always given eight shakes of a Jester's Hatbell to every single part.
We will determine next week if we give the same eight shake rating to the automatons.
We finally make it to the automatons.
Audience has been waiting for this one.
We'll see.
We have some hot takes coming for you.
This could be the one that doesn't go all the way.
We'll see.
This is where Stilt Nation is going to get mad at us.
Stilt Nation, this is the divisive one.
Be cool, Stilt Nation.
Relax.
All right.
Don't be haters, Stilt Nation.
Now, I don't know if Stilt Nation can not be haters, to be perfectly honest.
Oh, geez.
You're asking for it.
You're asking for their hot takes about our hot takes.
Buzz Buzz, Stilt Nation.
But hey, we love you and we thank you for supporting us.
And I guess with that, it's time for us to take our curtain call.
Thanks to Stilt Nation.
Join us on our Patreon, Lanuba Boys Duble.
You can join us on the Trapeze tier for $120 a month.
You get a bonus weekly comment there on the Lanuba DVD.
We do a different weekly bonus commentary on the same Lanuba DVD from 2004.
Or you can join us on the Highwire.
That's $500 a month where you get Discord access.
Bug, anything you want to plug this week?
Pudding sauce.
All right, Bug.
Until next week, the tent is closed.
So long from Lanuba Boys.
Biii.
Funky Ape.
Lanuba Boys is a Funky Ape production.
Executive produced by Bug Main, Scott Gerdner, Alice Foon, Byron Tain, Hank Vanquish,
Tony Sittles, Clark Cork, Roy Van Cleet, Morgan Belt, Reverend Andre Kirkland,
Heather Neck, and me, DJ Sam.
For more great shows from Funky Ape, visit Funky.
Ape slash Funky Ape Greats.
Funky Ape thanks our proud sponsor Bluechew.
Get 2% off with promo code NUBACHEW.
NUBACHEW.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gerdner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.