Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate, today covering a topic that resembles a live
feed of our brains.
I'm Scott Gardner, this is Mike Carlson.
I'm here and welcome to the Twisted Minds of the boys from the podcast.
Well, it's twisted, but it's also as wholesome as can be.
We just got thousands and thousands of Mickeys running through them, scampering plan.
When I said twisted, I meant more like twisted like a peppermint candy cane.
The twists in a candy cane, in a nice way.
Twisted back to the way things should be, wholesome.
If like gushers had a special kind of gushers that were like twisted gushers, like really
all that means is maybe there's a couple colors and it's fun.
That's what I meant by twisted, I didn't mean it like that.
And I can't see them putting this out, but you could deconstruct it, put a little booze
in there.
In gushers?
That's a twisted gusher.
Yikes.
There has to be a way scientifically, doesn't there?
Well yeah, you would just get a syringe and you fill it with something, tequila, and you
would inject the gusher with booze, yeah.
This is why you gotta check your kids Halloween candy.
Oh yeah, you're right, that's a very good point.
I had no reason to leave you out.
The gusher is hollow, am I wrong?
Sorry to bombard you with these questions, but you would know the answer I think.
Well, it's gotta be hollow if it's got juice, yeah.
So you could, I'm sure.
But is it not packed to the gills with juice?
I don't believe it's packed to the gills because the juice would leak out more, which honestly
occasionally does happen.
I haven't had gushers in a long time actually, but I believe there's only a little juice
in there.
I've had them in the last three months.
You've had gushers in the last three months?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you have any recollection?
Did you stop midway through, oh this is the kind of, actually this is a thing my son does
is like take a bite of a small candy, show me the inside, but not with a gusher, so he's
not helpful in this case.
Okay.
I'm gonna have to get him a gusher to find out.
Well there's only a handful in every package, so I feel like the way I eat them.
You mean there's not a hundred in every package?
What do you mean?
No, in every baggie.
You're saying there's not a lot.
Yeah, so I'm saying as I go through the baggie, I feel like I silently like, all right I bit
that one, I bit that one all the way, this one I'm gonna bite in half and take a look
and then eat the other half.
So you have taken a look.
You took a look?
Yeah, I've taken a look.
First of all, that you have taken a look, but that's now been superseded by the fact
that you have a mental process while eating a bag of gushers.
Yeah, it's fun.
It's fun.
Keeps it alive for you.
Wow.
Kind of a play-by-play commentary.
Do you ever do like sort of the sommelier, like you sniff the gusher, you bite into it,
you smell, you put it right under your nose, and then you eat the rest of it?
Michael, I have definitely done that.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my detect strawberry splash?
Bodacious blueberry perhaps?
You waft it into radical raspberry?
You waft the smell with your hands.
You get it up into the nasal passages.
But I think there's room in there.
That's my point.
I believe there's room in there.
I think it's kind of hollow still, even with the liquid.
What are you waiting for?
Get yourself a syringe and start making yourself alcoholic gushers.
All right.
But they do sell little chocolate-shaped like a Kahlua bottle or a Jack Daniels.
Yes, they do that.
They got a little bit of a hit of it.
I feel like every now and then, like, a parent would get them in like gift bags or gift baskets.
Something for mom and dad.
And it's like, oh, you can't have, or you can only have a little corner.
Because some of them, it's like fake liquor goo, and some of them, it's like a shot of
alcohol.
Yeah.
Like a full shot of alcohol?
I don't know if it's a full shot, but I feel like I've had one or two of these.
For the consistency of a chocolate shell, I don't know what's going to hold that.
You don't trust the 1.5 fluid ounces fitting in that single chocolate.
I just don't think it's going to hold.
I think you need such a hard shell.
I think that's fair.
Yeah.
I think you've got to eat that gusher fast, though, because maybe the alcohol will degrade
the surface or whatever it's made of, the gelatin or something.
Start to wear it down, like acid, just like melt the entire thing.
Well, this is something to try if anyone at home wants to and show us the results, or
don't.
Just have a good time for yourselves.
You don't owe us anything.
I agree.
Just have a fun alcohol and gusher night.
I started watching guys' videos on YouTube, and he just tries to make wine out of different
things.
Like, he made wine out of Mountain Dew, and he made-
This is an abomination.
I'm going to report this guy on YouTube.
Offensive content.
I think it's anything with sugar can-
Be fermented.
Sure.
I think he's working on Dr. Pepper right now.
Oh, you've got to make gusher's wine.
Jason, bathtub gusher's wine.
Come on.
Don't bathe for a few weeks.
All that will result is the Homer explosion.
I don't even get the wine.
I just get a damaged the glass shower door.
You're ranting.
Who gives a shit?
Come on.
Fuck that bathtub.
Make us gusher's wine.
It's made to experiment in.
Yeah.
You're sure you'll lose the security deposit.
What?
Now he looks like an explosion went off.
His hair got blown back.
But you'll make it back when you sell gusher's wine.
Oh, yeah.
That all becomes profit.
Oh, well.
Breaking even, eh?
Oh, mania's already overcoming us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's perfect.
With the talk of gusher's, we're kind of in the right zone because we are talking about
a very 90s Disney World event, parade, spectacular, whatever you want to call it, Mickey mania.
I believe this first came up in the episode we did about Disney World Resort TV with Ian
Riccobani where we sampled a nice helping of different videos that played in Disney
hotel rooms showing you what there was to do.
And I remember sparking to like, oh, right, Mickey mania, this thing, because just a couple
things about it.
This was a Magic Kingdom parade from June 94 to September 96.
There's a similar version in Tokyo that ran throughout 1995.
And OK, if you haven't seen this thing, maybe look at our little artwork or do a Google
image.
And I would say if you Google Mickey mania, Mickey mania parade, see if you can find any
clues that this was done in the mid 90s.
Just see if there's any hints that this is a mid 90s thing besides every single thing
that you see in the frame.
This might be the peak of Disney's Disney 90s.
It is the molten core, the molten gusher core of Disney in 90s colliding.
And I, well, I don't want to say my feelings about it.
We got to talk a little and then, you know, not not spoil our views.
But does that kind of accurately sum it up before we get into what specifically it looks
like?
It yes, it is.
I mean, I guess this is sort of tipping.
Well, I won't I won't tip.
I won't say either.
But it's like a Disney store like sprouted arms and legs.
And it started walking around like it's so 90s Disney.
It's unbelievable.
Every like every bumper on the Disney Channel, every Disney store came to life.
Anything like that.
Where, yes, like Mickey's gloves sprout and you go on some weird little like claymation
tunnel warp or whatever.
Absolutely.
Thousand percent.
Yes.
So yeah, it's it's it was wild.
It's a wild watch.
Yeah.
It's a lot of deconstructed.
Like it.
OK.
Granted, I watched three of these parades back to back.
Like one Tokyo to Florida.
That probably added to my media as I was writing some stuff down.
But yeah, just seeing the color scheme and the deconstructed like every little piece
BMX.
There's some bikes.
There's lots of weird bikes.
Yeah.
There's a little bit of rapping.
Mm hmm.
And there's a little bit of sampling very old audio in between the new audio.
I found a website that listed the lyrics of the song that plays and it is funny seeing
like in parentheses, Jimmy Dodd sample, the right name of the guide, the Jimmy, the Mousketeer,
the leader, the adult Mousketeer.
All the guys are sampling.
All the hip hop artists are sampling Jimmy Dodd.
Yeah.
No.
One of the biggest.
Like Godfather and Scarface and then Jimmy Dodd.
Of course.
The original Scarface.
Hey, kids.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, kids.
So the big thing that we haven't said about this, though you'll know this immediately
if you look at any photo of it, you'd have to describe this thing as a very intense Mickey
based fever dream, right?
It's just like, and it's hard to say, I don't think that there's like a story to this necessarily.
I think it's just a big Mickey themed party.
But visually, it's just like, let's put Mickey into some sort of like going haywire duplication
machine.
Yeah.
Out come thousands upon thousands of different visual interpretations of Mickey.
Some of them grotesque.
Yes.
Some of them very.
Some of them.
Some freaks came out.
Some are the fourth Michael Keaton in multiplicity.
There's some freaks.
This, too, that you're talking about the song, the song really captures a thing.
I don't know how to describe it, but this song, I think, is a way to do it where, like,
I was like walking around the house in between viewings of different braids.
I was singing like, Mickey mania, da, da, da, da, da, da, like da, da, da, da, da.
That's why I thought I didn't know that Goo Goo Dolls song that had been the subject of
much discussion.
What do you mean?
What's why you didn't think you knew?
That third Goo Goo Dolls song, because I realized every time I heard it on the radio, I would
go like, so, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da,
da, da, da, da, da.
Like I didn't know any of the lyrics.
The song's been more on my mind lately because of the controversy, and now I've listened
to the song, but I cannot retain those lyrics.
Coming down, the rustle, the rustle,
angels fall, the spell is made.
I was doing this, that, what I did to that said,
duh, duh, duh, I started doing about Mickey Mania.
As I was like-
It is an earworm, but not a fully effective earworm.
Yeah, that's a great way to put it.
You get the gist of it.
Okay.
So basically, as tempted as I am to talk about
Black Balloon for 35 minutes.
I didn't say anything.
And neither am I.
So we'll sit at a table this for another time.
We will dizzy up the Scott some other time.
Oh, when that episode's over,
I won't want the world to see me.
You will be like the album art of a person
lying stomach down on a bed.
Well, we're back to things I don't know.
So imagine I still don't know everything about-
Iconic album cover.
Poll, do you know this album cover?
Part of the poll is that you have to have looked at it.
Now that you've looked at it, do you know it?
Iconic, like Mickey's big yellow shoes.
I brought his pack, I brought his pack.
I need you more than ever for this.
So basically, in this parade, Mickey is deconstructed,
de-atomized, exploded, split into parts, big and small.
There's many small Mickeys, there's plush Mickeys,
as Mickey's done in every possible media.
I mean, maybe not literally,
I guess there aren't oil paintings or clay.
He's not made out of human feces,
but he's made out, there's like, I would say,
10 to 20 different forms of expressing Mickey.
There's no shit Mickey crawling his way down Main Street.
Or, in whatever process caused this parade to happen,
that did come out of the machine.
Oh yeah.
And they shot it in the head
before it could make it out to the public.
Right, but it took a while to get it.
The first one didn't work, it didn't put it down.
And it crawled a long way out.
They left a lot of perfect shit stains,
but in Mickey ear form.
And then they'd shoot it in the head,
and the blood splatters
would also form perfect Mickey ear shit.
Oh, like the soap dispenser you can get.
Oh right, that is a thing, yes.
It shoots it out, it shoots the three, yeah.
Does there really, on any Disney property,
is there, well obviously there's macaroni for kids
in Mickey ear shape, I assume,
but is there anything that can make long noodle strands?
There's gotta be a Play-Doh, whatever you call it,
play set that has the Mickey shape, or maybe.
Yeah, and I bet there's that,
but is there that for adults?
Can I order a $45 pasta that's in,
that are long, long Mickey strands,
that are an original Disney type of pasta?
Could you make pasta with just a Play-Doh play set?
If it's soft enough, potentially.
This guy on YouTube who could make Mountain Dew out of,
he could make wine out of Mountain Dew,
I'm sure he could make pasta out of Play-Doh.
Yeah, well I'll tell you what,
you definitely could put human shit in a Play-Doh play set.
Thanks, Mike.
Many a grizzly police scene has encountered
shit shapes made in Play-Doh.
Uh-oh, it's one of those again.
Yeah.
It's talking about normal stuff,
like Scott's grotesque long-hitting Mickey pasta.
But I, is that basically, it's just like,
it's Mickey iconography just like physicalized
into like five maybe parade floats,
and then like many kind of like,
I don't know the parade terminology,
but there's like little parade breakers essentially,
like not quite, but something that a bunch of people hold.
And just amidst all of this,
there's thousands upon thousands of Mickey.
It's a living Mickey nightmare.
But also, at the very end,
there's a big float and tucks and tails,
Mickey is riding a top.
Oh yes, you still get, yeah you get.
The real Mickey, yeah.
Yeah.
Primary Mickey, who is a,
sorry to keep you talking about this,
but a pig in shit.
Yeah.
He is like, imagine being him.
Yeah, yeah.
This is transpire.
He's made everybody.
Gazing upon horrors and horrors.
As he stands on top of simulations of all his past selves,
like Steamboat Willie, and like,
regular shirtless Mickey.
Regular shirtless, they always gotta represent
shirtless Mickey.
Yeah, Jack, Jack Mickey, beefcake Mickey.
Yeah.
This feels like, like in a cartoon,
Mickey would make someone,
let's say Pete, or Mortimer man.
Mortimer, what's the one with the big pants?
That tall mouse that hits on Minnie in the early days.
For yeah, Fresh Boy.
Fresh Boy, go suck your head, Fresh Boy.
Is it Mortimer?
Or is it, let's say it's Mortimer.
But like, if it was a cartoon,
and Mortimer was really upset with Mickey,
this is what he would see in his nightmare,
where he's cursing Mickey out,
he's like so upset with him.
And now all he can see is Mickey,
everything is Mickey, different versions,
and it's just infecting his brain.
Thousand percent.
It's almost like the kind of thing
that would happen more likely with like a Chip and Dale,
like characters who are pests more often.
Like Donald would see this like,
or you know what, it's very Pink Elephants on Parade.
Yes.
Or Heffalups and Woozles.
The character has a fear,
and then this manifests in this bizarre nightmare
where the character's represented
and the villain's represented in all these.
But in this case, it's Mickey,
the hero of the company.
Did it occur to them at any point
that they are using methodology,
usually reserved for nightmares,
but meant to be a fun 90s hip hop BMX party?
I don't think, I mean, I don't think so.
Maybe there was somebody like a lower tier Imagineer
that was like, hey, this is like,
this is too much, there's too much Mickey here.
The song, too, doesn't really change.
I feel like there's discussion about like,
oh, Small World, yeah, they play that
where people are trying to, you know,
in prison or get confessions out of.
But Small World has a lot of,
it's torture, or people just casually saying like,
oh, it's torture, I ride so long.
But that song changes a lot.
This song doesn't really,
Mickey Mania's song does not change for like 12 minutes.
You change genres, nationality, yeah.
This is the kind of the,
yeah, I know, because we're watching videos
where the parade does fully move through.
It's not like it suddenly,
it's not like Burrow Codown mainstream electrical parade
kind of like hits, all right,
now we're in like the Waltz part or whatever.
This is just the same thing over and over.
Should we get a hit of this song?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then in the course of doing this,
we could call out some of the things we see.
I don't think there's any particular order we need to go in
other than maybe saving the most,
maybe scarring imagery.
Building to that.
Sure, sure.
But here's a little touch of,
wait, and this song is called Rock the House with the Mouse.
There's two songs in it, at least maybe,
yeah, I think you end up with a second song at some point,
but this is Rock the House with the Mouse.
Mickey Mania.
["Rock the House with the Mouse"]
It is my town.
Mickey here, Mickey there, everywhere.
I'm meant to find mouse about time.
Many mouse Mickey's, you look kinda tricky,
but the way he's always hittin' around.
Just to break it up a little bit,
now you're hearing some sound,
that's not anybody's alarm going off while I play this,
there's a motif of clocks and time in this.
Common motif of nightmares as well.
Oh yes, yeah, yeah,
where you might get shaken out of one,
or you might have to adopt the alarm clock sound
into your dream, and that's a practical part of it.
In this case, there's big Mickey clocks,
that's an aspect of it,
you watch a giant Mickey watch go by,
those were kinda big around this time,
or even, maybe I'm wrong,
I feel like, at least this is what they were trying
to convey to a crowd going to Disney World,
is you can be an adult and own a fancy leather strap
Mickey Mouse watch.
Yeah, I had a fancy leather strap Goofy watch.
Wow, wow.
Backwards.
It went back, it was a silly watch?
It was a silly watch, I think I still have it,
I'd have to get it fixed, but yeah.
Did it work, was it like, you would see an eight,
but the eight was on the wrong side,
or was it literally the wrong time?
I think it was just, I think it was like,
the six was over here.
Okay.
Or no, I guess, no, I guess the nine was over here,
and the three was over here.
It's really confusing.
Yeah, difficult, as you were learning to tell time.
That's why it put me back five years.
I failed a grade.
You still, yeah, I do see you looking at clocks
and then kind of like pointing,
and then having to flip your arms, like wait, okay.
And then I got tangled, like I got my arms tangled
in my legs, like Goofy would, trying to tell time.
It'll still happen to me from time to time.
We're gonna do the test that they say to do
to like geriatric presidential candidates,
you're gonna have to draw a clock.
Yeah, good luck getting me to draw a clock.
I ain't putting myself on record with that.
I'm gonna get held back again from something.
I don't know what, but I'll get held back.
You won't be allowed to operate a podcast anymore.
It's funny that you say that, Jason.
It's such a, how insane is it that now it's like,
you know, when the presidential candidates
are so geriatric that we're concerned,
you know that new thing in the last six years
that will probably keep being a pattern.
Also, they refuse to draw the clocks.
Neither of them will draw, yeah.
Good for them, it shows strength.
Don't get bullied.
I'm trying to find the part where it gets into like,
can't get enough, can't.
Oh.
I remember watching it for the first,
the beat is all.
It's kind of a.
I try to do a good job of explaining this succinctly,
but now I've been thrown for,
I said a bunch of stuff, here's the premise of the parade,
and now I gotta go, and also clocks.
I don't know how to incorporate that.
This is, you know, look, there's, you know,
clocks have been incorporated in pop songs for years,
and they're kind of a weird, like a trippy little thing
to have in there, because you can kind of move in and out
of just the regular rhythm of a song
with the actual tick-tock of a clock.
So this is kind of more of an experimental thing
for a Disney parade, in a way,
compared to the average Disney song.
It's samples.
Yeah.
I think there is an understanding
of 90s hip-hop production.
Even if it's all to kind of an annoying end,
I don't think that they're so far off the mark.
Yeah.
I actually think, as I was comparing this
to something we talked about on the show
a couple years ago, Mickey Unwrapped, the album.
Oh, right, yeah.
The centerpiece is a tag team team-up
of whoop there it went.
And this is a pretty embarrassing attempt
to merge Disney and hip-hop,
mainly because Mickey's rapping.
And this, they leave, I don't know,
they leave the rap to, if not the professionals,
then people who aren't as annoying as Mickey Mouse.
Yeah.
So that gets you somewhere.
And Mickey is present just in the samples,
and in the samples of the 50s Mickey Mouse Club theme song.
Yeah.
But it's, you know, better than Mickey Unwrapped, right?
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
It is.
I don't know if it's the most successful
big parade crowd pleaser song,
but there are, you're like,
oh, it's a more interesting arrangement than normal.
You know what it is before, however,
some of these sweeping,
the ones that make you emotional in Japan,
they haven't built to those yet.
Probably parades around this time
are more just like either its greatest hits,
classic Disney song.
Maybe we haven't entered the era of the song
that moves you, that you can only hear in the parade.
Yes, that might be right.
I wonder when that starts.
I mean, it's interesting, hmm.
But yeah, no, still like nothing,
nothing touches the cool factor of Baroque hoedown,
but you know.
I don't know if I call it a cool factor, exactly, but.
Compared to everything else though?
Like all other Parks music?
All the other Parks music, parade music.
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
Cool's just not the word, I like it.
Cool, okay.
I don't know.
I feel like, let me use this thin excuse
to play this song, because it did remind me,
as a mildly successful mashup of 90s hip hop and Disney,
something I am very fond of
is the end credits music towards the,
well, they did it for, I think,
all the seasons of the Mickey Mouse Club,
but when we get into the later MMC era,
the song that played at the end of every show,
which would go for sometimes,
depending on how much time they had to kill
in the episode, two full minutes,
where the entire cast of like 22 cast members,
and then the whole audience comes out,
and they just dance while credits play for a long time,
and maybe just compare contrast.
You've heard Mickey Mania, do you know this song offhand?
Did you watch enough of this show?
I don't know, necessarily.
I think I know what you're saying,
but I don't know, I don't know it off the top of my head.
So, you know, old Mickey Mouse Club,
it's why because we like you,
M-O-E, and they still do that, there's still that,
but then they get to the E,
and things get a little more funky.
M-O-U-S-E.
Uh-oh.
The audience rushes the stage.
They all rush the stage.
You're allowed, go.
Time to see you later, never gonna fade you, though.
You wanna leave you with no plans.
This is pretty good, actually.
I genuinely, like a stressful day, a stressful week,
Aaron and I have like, you know, open a bottle of wine,
let's watch videos we like, we will sometimes land it.
M-O-C's got it goin' on funky style,
got it goin' on in a funky style,
like it's so effervescent.
It's so, it's cheesy, but man,
they're having so much fun.
I wonder how many different songs
in the history of the Disney company
have been a play on the Mickey Mouse Club theme,
because there's a song from the now,
I guess they did their last performance
of Mickey's Mix Magic,
which is the thing they do on Main Street
with no fireworks, just a kind of a light show.
And the song, of course, I've described before
as a cooler Disney song,
but it's come on everybody, get your ears on.
But in the lead up to the chorus,
they do go M-I-C, K-E-Y, M-O-U-S-E.
So like, how many times has this been,
like a version of this been made or sampled or whatever?
Somebody in the company has gotta be saying like,
think about it, that's saying all these letters,
that's rapping, we were doing rapping
in the 50s before anybody, that's like B-I-G, P-O, P-P-A.
Well before that, there was M-I-C, K-E-Y.
So let's take our birthright as the inventors of hip hop,
plus the Walt Disney Company, and let's own that area.
Can't argue with that.
So I wonder if anyone knows, probably no one does.
That is a very common thing, I guess.
They do it a lot, is my feeling,
but maybe we've just listed the three times they did it,
I don't know.
I don't think, I think it's a lot.
I think you're onto something.
There's been a lot of versions of just, yeah,
either little samples or references,
or just new version, updated versions,
for the era in which it was created.
It's not the one, it's not what Will Smith did
in that one special, that was zippy doo-dah.
Right, right, right.
Tracking, I think it's important that we track
all the kind of unironic attempts at Disney rap.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
But this one, hey, you know, I don't mind it.
I think where you get a little bit dicier
than the music itself is what happens at the beginning,
which before the song plays, did you guys happen to see,
or did you hear this bit of dialogue?
There is a, there's like a little scene, essentially,
that starts the thing.
You didn't think that was a fresh MC?
You didn't think that was really fresh?
Oh, I'm not saying it's not fresh.
I'm just saying, I don't know, plenty fresh,
a hell of fresh, but it's an interesting
little bit of dialogue.
Let me see if I can track this down.
Okay, so there's two versions of this.
One involves Roger Rabbit, and here is this,
as according to the script, woman rapper.
Yo there, listen up all you rad dudes.
Walt's house is rockin' with the mania
that's hit the street with the brand new beat.
Gar's sounds like a party, maybe I should make a cake.
Let me try to do Roger Rabbit.
Jeepers, Goofy, it's not that kind of party.
It's a Def Jam, and we're invited to groove
with the rest of the gang.
That's pretty good.
That's right, Roger, my main man Mickey Mouse
is bustin' fresh out of sight.
He wants you all to chill hard and bump the bump
while the mania cruiser moves.
Mickey Mania is taking control.
Then a sample of Mickey saying, oh boy, oh, oh, oh boy.
Oh my God.
Oh wow, that was fun, yeah.
Listen up all you rad dudes.
And then Roger Rabbit's saying, it's a Def Jam.
It's a Def Jam, this is, Def Jam Records is big
and culturally relevant has been for a while,
and now Roger Rabbit's.
Roger Rabbit's is saying it on Main Street,
or saying it in a Disney park, a reference.
Listen up B-Boys and B-Girls.
How many people did this reference have to be explained
to in management?
Like, no, no, no, this is a current thing,
and that's why Roger's referencing it.
Right, yeah, Roy Disney's in the meeting,
and like, well, first of all, I think you misspelled death.
Secondly, I don't know why we're saying death in a parade.
Don't you think that's gonna bring people down?
Yes, for sure.
Eisner, of course, had to approve it.
They had to explain it to him.
I mean, unless he's really, was really with it,
he knew everything about it.
Roy, let me take you through it.
Hip-hop is the sound of the streets.
There's a purposeful shortening of words,
reappropriation of them.
Taking old records and sampling and the scratching
is on purpose, that's not a mistake with the,
my kids, Breck has caught me up.
We are naming.
Big on the ghetto boys, he's taught me everything.
Ghetto is spelled on purpose.
Breck is extra fresh.
We're naming another entertainment company,
but we tried fitting the phrase Hollywood Records in there,
and it just didn't sound right.
So it is, yeah, that's the most,
it's always funny when Disney takes a chance
on being culturally relevant.
God bless him, it's really funny.
There's a few you gotta back up to there.
Walt's house is rocking.
Walt's house.
We're rocking the house.
The Homey Hills house, or the Burbank lot.
The Palm Springs house.
The Palm Springs, yeah, yeah, the ranch.
The smoke tree, which house are we talking about here?
We rocking the smoke tree lodge.
The one with the train in the backyard.
The one by the grocery store in Los Feliz.
One by the Grease High School in Los Feliz, California.
You're gonna have to be more specific.
Or they can't, surely they can't all be rocking.
I guess Walt's house is.
With the mania that's at the street.
Walt's house is the Magic Kingdom, I suppose.
I think that's what they're getting at.
Sure, uh-huh.
How do you do like the,
I don't think this was going at the time,
but the Izzle, Walt, Walt Dizzle.
Oh yeah, Walt, Walt Dizzle.
Is it just Dizzle?
Or would you. Maybe it's Dizzle, I guess.
Or do you add the Walt Dizzle, Dizzle-nee?
I think it's just Dizzle.
I think it's Dizzle. Yeah, Walt Dizzle.
What are the rules of the Dizzle language?
Yeah, I don't know, it's a good question.
Because the Disney company will dazzle.
Hello, I'm Michael Izz-Izzner,
President of the Walt Dizzle.
Oh, was there ever one where he was rapping?
President and CEO of the Walt Dizzle company.
Was there ever one where he rapped?
Man, I don't think so.
Oh man.
Because we'd know it, we'd know it.
And if we didn't know it,
and it suddenly popped up on somebody's YouTube channel,
we would have been sent it 30 times on that day.
You would think so.
Yeah.
You better, if.
Please do.
If there's anything with Michael Izzner rapping out there
and we're not aware of it,
please right this wrong.
And if not, let's see if we can get him to rap.
Even if it's about baseball cards.
Is he on cameo, is Michael Izzner on cameo?
Can we get him to rap something?
Great question.
Does he need like a hundred bucks for a personal greeting?
For a mere $100,000, I'll give you 30 seconds.
Sure, I will rap for 600,000.
Gotta make that money.
Gotta stack that cash, yo.
Now.
Izzner was more like Scarface, honestly.
There's a lot of young hip-hop guys that love Izzner.
They reference him in all their songs.
Yeah, there's gotta be some hello samples in there.
So this was redone then,
and theoretically because the presence of Roger Rabbit
was decreased in the parks
due to the Amblin relationship fraying,
and which makes it on some websites kind of oddly said,
they had to switch it from Roger Rabbit
to goofy son Max to not upset Steven Spielberg,
or like to prevent a problem with Steven Spielberg.
I read that phrase too on the fandom page for this parade
after I dismissed about three different ads,
like three different pop-up ads.
Yeah, that's it.
Just a few more rounds of layoffs and a few more pop-ups
and you'll be okay, fandom.
You'll be a solvent website, we believe in you.
There's a lot of weeds in that garden.
Yeah.
You got a lot of whacking to do if you go to fandom.com.
So Max is in, hey, I think they picked the right,
hey, you know what, Goof Troop completely, the vibe.
Yes, yeah, and the theme song as well.
Yeah, yeah.
I just learned that the guy who sings
the Goof Troop theme song is a guy named Phil Perry,
who is the singer on so many 80s, 90s smooth jazz songs
that I love. Oh really?
And I never put the connection together.
There's so many things like that where I'm like,
why do I love this music and I love these Disney theme songs?
Same fucking people. Wow.
Singer of Toto, singer of Gummy Bears.
Yeah, right. There's a ton of the same horn players
on DuckTales as play on King of Wishful Thinking,
everything I like. Yeah.
Shout out to Phil Perry.
I just did, I did a full hour long
Lucather interview last night
while I was doing stuff together.
Hell yeah, which one, Sunset Sound?
No, it was Rick, what's Rick's name?
Rick Beato. Beato, yeah.
I'm getting a lot of Rick Beato.
Yeah, I do a lot of Rick these days.
Rick pops up a lot.
Everyone seems to respect Rick also.
Yeah, I don't know from what, I don't know who he is,
but you know, puts a good interview together.
You get an aging rocker talking about how like,
yeah, that was how it was, man.
We just sat down, we didn't even have the track.
We had to sit down and figure it out by take two.
Yeah, you get a lot of like,
and Quincy Q called us into the studio, man,
and he was like, man, this is too metal.
When you're playing on Beat It, it's too metal.
This needs to be on pop or R&B radio, man.
This is not, this is too much.
And so I had to get back in there.
I knew what he meant.
Music to my ears, music to my ears.
I also like what Lucather's doing
with the hair and the beard.
Well, he's going gray, finally.
He's going gray. He's letting it go.
I think there might be, he might be doing something too.
Maybe let that be a lesson to you, Mike.
But I think he's doing something.
There's a different, like, it looks too cool.
The gray looks kind of like stylized gray,
and I don't know if it's his natural gray.
I think it looks good, though.
I think it's a dyed gray.
It might be a dyed gray, I don't know.
Could it just be like, you know, vitamin E and fish oil?
Or could it be supplements?
It could be Rick Beato or whatever his last name is.
He should ask him about the hair.
It's amazing that the old rock star interviews
on YouTube aren't just all about supplements.
Oh yeah.
And like, you know, like, colon health.
You know that's what they talk about
every second before and after the record.
Of course.
What are you drinking to start the day, my man?
You dump a collagen water?
You doing the athletic greens?
What are you doing?
How is it that our show here in late 30s, early 40s
is the one that has more talk about, like,
dribbling when you pee now?
How is that us and not Rick Beato?
We're more confessional, you know.
This is more into a look into our lives.
It's raw.
Yeah, it's unplugged.
It's more twisted in a lot of ways.
Yeah, raw look inside our pants that are dribbly dicks.
Sure.
I'm not gonna put myself in that.
I have no problem with the dribble.
Scott's very much that he's never dribbled in his life.
Jason and I are dribbling constantly.
I mean, yeah.
What's going on with Mike?
I got some health stuff going on that's understandable.
The doctor said it's a little bit, it's fine.
It's not normal.
A little bit.
He showed me on a diagram how it's normal.
You've talked to a doctor about this?
Of course.
Just wanna make sure.
He goes, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's all, he goes, and he showed me, like,
that the pee has to go over a certain part
of your anatomy to get to the hole to get out.
So he was just like, yeah, you see,
some of it gets kind of trapped up here.
It's normal to have a little bit.
You know, I'd honestly, I'd be more concerned
about somebody your age who doesn't dribble.
Actually, the dribble is more healthy.
He didn't go that far.
And if you're ever talking to a friend of yours
who claims that he doesn't dribble,
I'd get him in to see me soon,
because we gotta scrape that entire urethra out.
He did say that.
This is what the listeners demand.
We're back to what they're begging for.
Wait, we've gotten to the blood flow talk.
The pee tree's blood flow is age.
In your penis?
Oh, everywhere.
I just only started reading about it,
so I can't speak as an expert.
I don't know nothing about any of that.
I don't, we don't wanna bog this down.
People will give us nice compliments sometimes,
and you know, if we post a dry topic
or say we wanna talk about a dry thing,
people will say like, you know what, that's okay.
I'd listen to the boys talk about paint dry.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
They can, and that's a nice thing to see.
However, listeners, I would caution you, anything?
I'm not so sure.
Well, everyone.
When the blood health episode comes out.
Yeah, blood health, urological health.
You don't think about these things, you know,
but it's good, you know.
As you get older.
It mostly comes back to drinking lots of water,
like you're doing.
As I'm doing right now, yes.
I got water, too.
And we all got big waters.
I think I'd rather do the hydration episode,
the how you hydrate an episode,
than Wayland Flowers and Madam.
I think I would more, I would rather hear
about all of your bowel health, then.
I would be happy to talk about my bowel health in general,
but I will also say that every day,
a new little piece of Wayland Flowers and Madam
gets entered into my brain,
and it makes me want to discuss it with people more.
This is what you should be discussing with your doctor.
This is the biggest problem to your health,
and therefore mine.
Yeah, you should talk to someone
about eating all those Madam puppets,
slowly getting into, that can be good for your digestion.
No, well that's true.
Micro Madam puppets.
Micro.
From thrown away Madam.
It's, yeah, it's penetrating my blood-brain barrier.
That's for sure.
That's all I know, is that I have too much Madam.
I have too much Madam on the brain and in the gut.
My microbiome has too much Madam.
We scraped your stomach
and found little pieces of pink feather boa.
Oh, enough of that grotesquery.
Let's get out of here.
Back to these Mickey ones.
There is a, yeah, this is a cultural grotesquery.
So, Roger Abbott's out.
New dialogue with Goofy and his son Max, who is cool,
as we know from Goofy. Max is cool, yes.
Garsh, Max, sounds like a party.
Do you think I ought to bring some punch?
They changed that.
Max, response.
Aw, Dad, you're such a narfo.
It's a Def Jam and we're all gonna groove
with the rest of the gang.
Aw, Dad, you're such a narfo.
What is that even coming from?
It sounds like a 90s insult.
I think that it's one of those kinds of things.
Now I don't remember that this is something
that is very much in Kyle Mooney's wheelhouse,
something he did on our show, smashed a lot.
Some slang that completely sounds like
it would have been something the kid with attitude
would have said.
And I think that's what we're dealing with here.
I don't think there's a narfo in the world.
It sounds like you could, unless this is a missed,
unless the guy on this website was supposed to be,
no, it wouldn't have been NARC.
Goofy wants to party.
NARC wouldn't have been.
No, narfo I think is made up.
Narf is like pinky in the brain.
Yes, right, pinky says narf.
Yeah, well that's confusing.
He says narf, but he doesn't say narfo.
He doesn't say narfo.
So maybe somebody wrote narf.
Narfo is a zuzzy zazz.
It's a like, well, no one in the office
actually knows what one of the cool words,
and nobody could text at this time
so you couldn't check in with your niece
to see what cool kids are saying.
So you just had to go off the dome
and make up something like narfo.
You Google narfo, I don't find anything.
I find an organization which is
the National Association of Responsible Firearm Owners.
Oh wow.
Which you know what,
and that appears to maybe be in New Zealand.
I was gonna say, it doesn't sound like something
we'd have in America.
I was gonna say that's not right.
They're responsible.
That can't be a big group.
That's nothing you'd be proud of.
There's a different group that has a different
shorter, smaller amount of letters.
Yeah, it's the group whose motto is,
hey, come here, you wanna look in this drawer.
You know, those PSA cards.
Sure.
Please, uncle.
So yeah, I think Disney made up a phrase.
Narfo. And I encourage you at home
to try it out, you know, call a loved one.
Well, no, don't.
No, don't, it's an insult, yeah.
It's like calling your parents lame, I guess.
Lame, narfo means lame.
Something I could do, I could, you know,
because you sort of have control.
We have young children, they parrot our language.
I could convince my son that narfo
is something that you could call.
I would love if he started saying narfo.
Yeah, you're a narfo.
Yeah, I'm gonna try to steer him away
from the insults he's been using,
that's what you're thinking.
And I'm gonna change it into this more fun one.
Yeah, one that can't hurt me
because it doesn't actually mean anything.
It's not real.
We can start selling some T-shirts
like Frankie says, relax, those shirts were huge.
We can sell, don't be a narfo.
It's a major 90s throwback.
Boy, remember when you get home,
you'd open up your pack of gushers?
If your mom said, you have to have broccoli instead,
you'd say, mom, you're such a narfo.
This was part of being a 90s kid.
I guess we used to remember what it was like.
Yeah, we remember.
We remember every day for many hours.
What kind of kid were you in the 90s?
A totally rad dude or a total narfo?
I think we were all closer to being narfos.
Yeah, we were definitely narfos.
Some of the youngest narfos around.
Yeah, luckily we've grown out of it.
What if we're such narfos
that we don't even know that narfo was a word?
It's possible.
It was something the cool kids were saying
and the listeners are all going,
they don't even know narfo.
It's possible.
They're talking about their dribble dicks
and they didn't even know that all cool kids said narfo.
It was something they said on Single Out.
They probably weren't allowed to watch it.
Everyone who listens to this podcast hasn't told us
they listen because they want to make fun of us.
So that's just-
It seems like a few do.
Well, a few do, fair enough.
Statistically.
Fair enough, a few people do want to make fun of us
and they vocalize it, but everyone does actually,
they don't say it.
So I appreciate them being quiet about it.
It's being a listener bully.
Yes, right.
Which is, thank God there's a big gap between us and them
unless they come to a live show to beat us up.
We're making a big leap when we do these things
and we talk to people after that there's not,
someday there's gonna be the one who's like,
I've waited six years for this, suck.
So Living with the Land fan.
Living with the Land fan.
I don't know.
Let's see if it was, wait, Zach Ryder's on my side,
wasn't he?
Yes, he was, yes.
All right, yeah, I know.
I think I'm gonna help you.
He's on your side, but Matt Cardona's fury.
He's alter ego.
Yeah.
I don't think anyone's tried to beat him up though
for Living with the Land.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's what I'll just, you know,
let's just have him at any future shows if possible.
So anyways, that gets us into the parade.
We've got cool songs.
We've got an RFO talk.
Now I think it's time to just throw out
as many details as we can about the things
that occur in this parade.
Yeah.
Just call it like you see it.
There's a lot of rollerblading.
Pluto is on a skateboard.
And some of it is like, you know,
it's like the parade extras and they got backwards caps
and they're rollerblading, but it will also be like,
I don't, I can't, you know,
like the witch from Snow White or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's one, but you know what I mean?
It's a random Disney, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They're in rollerblades.
Yeah, well, I got one, I got a picture I took.
I was watching it on a TV.
I took, this is Alice, Wendy and Peter Pan.
I think Pinocchio's off screen on large adult tricycles.
Like, I don't know what to call it, three wheel bikes?
They're trikes, aren't they?
Yeah, they're, you know, they have elaborate costumes on.
So you probably don't want those caught in a standard bike.
You probably don't want them trying to balance
in a face character costume.
So the three wheels is probably easier to manage.
Yeah, maybe.
That's tough work that you got a Geppetto head on,
Smeez back there.
Yeah.
You gotta dress as Smee and ride a trike around.
Seems hard.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm more impressed by that in a way
than the actual BMX stunts, because there is one of the,
and this, I don't remember if I sat and watched this parade,
but I remember the existence of it at this time
and that there was a float with a slide and a bike rant
that kind of did a couple little humps,
and then you could go flying off them, and that's cool,
but those guys don't have Smee heads on.
No. Right.
There should be a Smee version of this parade.
Smee madness, Smee mania.
There's the-
Where everyone has Smee heads.
Captain Hook would be so mad.
Summer of Smee.
That's not the natural order of things.
I have to die for Smee to rise.
You remember the summer of 95 when the big six were
Mickey, Minnie, Donald, Pluto, Goofy, and Smee?
Summer of Smee. I remember.
Summer of Smee, yeah.
The summer of Smee.
I don't know what he sounds like.
I can't even think he sounds like that.
He sounds like kind of wimpy, like-
Yeah, does he have that voice?
I don't know about that, sir.
Does he, I was gonna say the slides float.
I didn't see this live as a 90s kid,
but this would have really gone,
holy shit, there's a slide on the parade route.
Wow.
And they make, they'll like push Donald Duck down it.
Yeah. And he has to like slowly,
that kind of slide, cause it's like a spiral slide.
Metal spiral slide, yeah. And metallic.
This is something my dad says every time
we're at a playground with my son.
It's like, boy, don't you miss the hot, hot metal?
Oh yeah.
You'd go past the, you'd like get caught on like the,
you know, the parts where they connect and the screws.
And it is funny.
That was more the case that they didn't make,
that playgrounds weren't very kid friendly
until about 20 years ago.
Yeah.
But yeah, you can just imagine, you know,
cause you've been on slides like that maybe as an adult
and like, boy, the slow scrape that you do.
So imagine being your Donald,
and then just like skunk, skunk, skunk,
just moving three inches at a time kind of painfully.
That's not an easy slide for Donald.
Seat gets caught.
There's some more stationary.
There's the float with Goofy on a BMX bike
that is attached to the float.
And it's attached, it's doing a wheelie,
but he doesn't really, he just moves the handlebars sometimes
and mostly waves and kind of dances sitting on the bike.
It's a perma wheelie.
It almost seems like they're,
like he's powering it himself with the pedaling.
I'm not sure if that's what they're trying to convey,
but you feel that way a little bit.
Also, by the way, style wise, okay,
so I've said that there's like thousands of Mickey shapes,
but also while it is a big, just insane mess of color,
there is a ton of Mickey's primaries, right?
It's Mickey's red from his pants.
Mickey's yellow from his, yeah.
Little red shorts.
I'm sorry, shorts, and I should say little too.
Yellow from his buttons.
His shoes.
Shoes, shoes.
Shoes and buttons, right?
Or are they white buttons?
And then black.
From his flesh.
His fur flesh.
His fur flesh, yeah.
From his hair.
And it is like, it is overwhelming,
this amount of red and black.
It's a real choice.
I would put this whole parade in the vibe,
a vibe that I love.
I would consider this an example of factory pomo,
which I'm sure I've talked about on the show at some point,
but it's this kinda, it's hard to explain.
You know it when you see it.
It's like a lot of circular logos,
and gears are part of it,
and I think clocks are related to gears,
and there's a little bit of art deco,
and big blocky fonts, and limited color palettes,
which is what this is, and hard contrast,
and a lot of basic shapes.
Squares, circles,
I was waiting, squares, circles, triangles,
and then a lot of zigzags.
Disney actually did a lot of factory pomo.
Basically, you'd see this at, besides Disney,
you'd see this, that SNL logo in the 90s where it's round,
and there's the little crosses between every word.
A lot of CD-ROM covers, a lot of food court logos,
but also, this is definitely very factory pomo.
Tomorrowland 94 has a lot of examples of it.
My favorite.
With its very art deco, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Innoventions, I think, is,
because you'd see that logo round,
and I feel like I could picture it on something shiny,
like a CD.
It's a type of 90s that I don't think is exploited enough.
I think it's fascinating and cool.
It's something I like because of the 90s,
because of being a child in the 90s,
but I don't, some of it I guess I like,
if I think about it.
I guess I like the Innoventions, but it feels.
It's like tackier.
It's tacky.
Yeah, I guess I don't want it everywhere.
There's a time and a place for factory pomo,
but that's another, if you do a Google image of that,
and then just kind of like soak up,
just like get yourself a hit of factory pomo.
I think it'll make you happy.
Here's a food court, here's a good food court one.
Oh yes, I've seen that one.
Yeah, yeah, any sign like that with like shish kebabs.
Beakman's World logo.
Beakman's World logo comes up.
A lot of 90s basketball team logo,
like if they did a 90s remake,
like Phoenix Suns, it looks like they had a factory pomo.
That is good, I like a lot of this, yeah.
I can't tell this is a modern reinterpretation,
but I'll call this Trapper Keepers Chic.
Totally.
This type of early CG, basic CG.
The main Tomorrowland sign, which is gone now,
but the one on the big.
With gears behind it.
Like the weird gear thing.
Somewhere in our Tomorrowland Explorator,
we should just like fully tribute Tomorrowland.
Let's try to carve out some space.
Oh yeah.
Just to gush, to bring up a word from this episode.
We'll all be gushers when we talk about that.
Beautiful, incredible Hulk lights, purples and greens.
Yeah, yeah, very cool.
Very soothing.
So anyway, that's on the cooler end of this.
On the less, on the weirder end is like,
when Minnie is, well there's two Minnie.
In Japan, Minnie is wearing like a head wrap or something.
She kind of looks, I thought she looked
kind of like Queen Latifah.
Oh yeah, okay, I could see that.
And then, but in America, she had a very different vibe,
which is that here's her two ears,
and then between them on the top of her head is a big bun.
And the bun is black, like Mickey's flesh,
and Minnie's flesh.
And so it's very disconcerting to see two big ears
and then an even bigger like hump.
Like she got hit on the head.
It looks like a cartoon, yeah,
the cartoon character getting hit on the head,
but without the little bald part.
It looks like Minnie has a massive, massive tumor.
It's really, I don't think it looks like a hair at all.
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
Why didn't they just like give her like blonde hairs
like she dyed it or something maybe?
That would have helped, yeah.
But she doesn't have.
They're going for Madonna a little bit with this,
but maybe they didn't wanna go too far.
Like I guess, can Minnie grow her fur out?
That's a question I have.
Does, yeah, does the top of her hair,
I mean, I don't know her situation follicly in general.
However, theoretically, yeah, you,
couldn't you grow like a human hairdo
from the top of your head?
Is it just a matter of taking the time growing it out
and then shaping it?
Has Mickey ever had like a mullet in anything?
Has Minnie ever had like shoulder length fur?
Cause mice don't have hair, they have fur.
But I don't think they're short.
So it would be a fur cut,
the first style of hairdo.
So I think she has to have a wig.
This has to be a wig.
She wanted a black wig that looks like a bun
and she stuck it in between her two ears.
Or they're going so logically that like,
well, no, if Minnie grew her hair out, it would be black.
It's fur.
So if she were to make a bun, it would be black.
There is, in the plain crazy,
Mickey like messes his hair up at some point.
That's true, he does have a little bit of a
messy growth there.
Like the black hair, flesh hair.
Okay, you're right.
He does have flesh hair.
Both of them could like get really shaggy like a dog.
And like shake it.
Yeah, cause yeah, like a short hair dog,
yeah, you can get a little of the fur to stick up,
but not enough for a bun.
We are deconstructing the characters
much in the same way this parade deconstructs Mickey.
It gets him down to the elements.
I mean, that's a good thing to bring up
that there is one of the more notable parts,
I think is that you will at some point see
just his gloves walking around with little legs.
And then just his hat.
And it's just like just a mousier hat.
And then the shoes being driven around
like they're the little bugs in the Main Street Electrical.
But so there's a part of the big stretch of this
where it's Mickey's body parts, giant and split apart.
A big shoe car.
You see a person driving it in the foothole.
I, this struck me when I was watching it.
I was like, oh my God, the shoes are being driven,
but the gloves are inflatable.
I think I'd like the inflatable gloves.
What do you mean?
Like I think the fingers of the hand
are natural to be like the walking legs.
You would like performing as the gloves?
No, no, I just liked like, oh that makes sense
being a big inflatable parade piece.
I see, I see.
The drivable shoes I had to think about longer
because there's people sticking out of them
and they have little hats on, kind of.
They gotta see.
But they're not like walking up and down like a shoe would.
You're saying it's not as a good of a representation
of what actually the hand would do as a walk.
Because the hands are walking with little human legs.
But they're walking like Cousin It would walk.
Oh, I guess so.
Using its fingers.
I think in cartoons, yeah, the hand or glove
turned into like a walking around Cousin It kind of thing.
A shoe wouldn't glide across.
If a shoe came to life,
it would not glide across the ground.
It would probably be jumping.
It would like heel, toe, heel, toe.
I see, you're right.
It is the finger, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Taking a little.
So you would need it to at least,
they should have built in something
like the Indiana Jones ride
that made it kind of go up and down, up and down
as it drove around Main Street.
And the more we talk about this,
the more horrifying it becomes.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Accurate footsteps seem scary to me.
The whole thing does just like,
I mean, what I flashed to is a version of this
where it was all laid out one day by Mickey
in some crazed energy burst.
Yeah.
I had a vision, bear with me.
Thanks a lot for coming in on no notice.
And for coming in on a Saturday.
Yeah, 11 PM, our Saturday.
I know it's a three day week.
With inspiration strikes, you gotta be here.
I got you all on call like Prince.
You gotta call 3AM, you gotta come.
So go with me.
All right, my body is huge.
Split up, man's chopped off, feet chopped off.
They're giant, they fill up all of Main Street.
And then behind that, 2,000 bees.
If I'm the star and you break me up into component pieces,
you two get more stars.
Stars in the sky, helps everybody.
You'll find a plush of me under each of your chairs
and you'll find a machete.
I want you to chop me up right now
and imagine what it looks like
if I'm flying down Main Street piece by piece.
No bad ideas, I won't be insulted.
We're in the blue sky phase.
Then they do it.
No, not the face, never the face.
Don't cut this face.
The company is built on this face, damn it.
That might, I want you to go, you sick rake.
Get out of here.
Mickey, we've mocked up your giant tongue.
We're gonna drag it, we're gonna have 10 people
drag your giant tongue down Main Street
and it's gonna be wet.
Ooh, I like this.
Okay, that's pretty good.
You're interesting, you're interesting.
Well, let's run it, let's rehearse it
as long as no children vomit when they see it.
We'll send it out.
Mickey, they all vomited.
Oh, God damn it.
Someone get Kronenberg on the phone.
Let's tell it to him.
It's also like one of the like.
That hack'll take any.
It also feels like one, if he was planning this out,
you get like your project lead on this
and you get a call from Mickey at 5 a.m., 3 a.m.
Oh yeah, you know those punching bags
with the sand on the bottom and they pop back up
when you punch them?
I want 50 of those, I want to see them tomorrow, okay?
Is that what that is?
I was trying, I was like, I think that's an oblong
old style punching bag, kind of.
I'm seeing me and inflatable, kind of like
the shape of grimace a little bit, but it's me.
And then, cherry on top, no limbs, no limbs.
They don't get them, that's what makes me different.
I get to wave, point my hands around, do a spell, not them.
Are you writing this down?
I don't hear a bit, so I'm writing this down.
Listening for instruction.
Donald, can you just talk to him?
I think the Lion King money is going to his head.
He's writing a high from the rock.
Can't do it still.
I want to be inflatable, like Superman flying through,
you know, you ever been in the circus
and they jump through those rings?
I want it to be like that, but wait.
Also, it's like my ears are the rings as well,
so my ears are on top of one of the rings.
Wait, Mickey, slow down, what are you talking about?
What do you mean, what am I talking about?
I made it fucking clear.
I'm Superman.
It's my job to think of it, it's your job
to write it down and do a drawing of my dreams.
Inflatable Superman through the rings
that are also my head and ears.
The top stomach down is what I'm saying,
permanent stomach down.
Hang up.
What, what was he saying?
We're gonna get our asses handed to us
if we don't have like 10 mock-ups of this.
Oval punch, did someone, oval punching bags?
Okay, well, a thing that stuck out to me
when you were showing clips, Scott, that hasn't come up,
the stilt walkers with staffs.
Oh yeah.
They look very similar to the Epcot.
Mickey's guards, yeah.
Guards.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, do you think those, Mickey,
do those ideas clash a little bit
because we already have a thing with big stilt walking,
Mickey guards with Mickey staff.
What do you think?
Answer your own question.
When's it magic kingdom, what is it Epcot?
Oh, uh.
Actually, I need these.
I need these for real.
Why do I ever get out of my own car
without 12 of these flaking me?
Bugs Bunny's gonna come and shoot me in the head one day.
Everybody's trying to steal my ideas.
They wanted to know why I wasn't in Lion King.
Why I wasn't the star of Lion King,
and they, what they bring up a good fucking question.
Why wasn't I in any of these movies?
Simba mania wouldn't make any sense.
No one would know what the shape was.
Just a regular lion's head.
In a lot of ways, the guards are there
to protect them from me.
The guards can form a prison around me.
They make bars with the staffs.
So when I say, let me at them,
they'll slam the staffs down and protect you from me.
You need to be thankful.
I've got these guards.
How about that?
That's an American tale.
Folk Fievel.
Wanna know why there's no more Fievel movies?
I killed him.
Shh, don't tell anyone.
Let's put Roger in this parade to make Steven upset.
Let's make Steven sad.
I don't care.
I want him to be mad.
Spielberg is such a narfo.
Is that a real word, Mickey?
It doesn't matter, it is now.
I thought of it so it's real.
It's real to me.
What are the vats that Goofy and Max are overseeing
in this parade?
Do you say vats or glats?
Vats or something to me.
Yellow vats and then like, what's coming out of them?
There's purple stuff?
There's a purple top with Mickey ears on it,
but they're in suits that look like they're trying
to contain, like they're working with hazardous chemicals
or something, and I can't tell what this float
is supposed to be.
There's a big Mickey inflatable hat on the back
that's actually pretty standard,
but then there are like four of these like drum,
like tall drums.
It's the dip.
Yellow drums.
I refined it.
It's a new iteration.
It could be the dip.
New formula you could tell because it's purple,
and this is how we're gonna generate
the thousands and thousands of me's
that we're gonna need for this.
He's gonna hit Mufasa with the dip.
Ha ha ha ha.
Too popular.
If you ever come back, it's gonna be for one of those
shitty straight to DVD sequels
or for some very unwatchable live action films
way in the future.
Stay in the sky, asshole.
Barry Jenkins wants to work with Mufasa.
That's his problem.
You can shoot the dip into the sky with a big gun.
I'll shoot your cloud for Mufasa.
I don't care.
It doesn't matter to me.
I got a big cannon.
Or I'll use one of the fireworks launchers at Disneyland.
I got, I bought staffs and bulk.
I'll just start launching them at you.
I think whenever Disney stopped getting sponsorship deals
from Dow Chemical.
Oh yeah.
On the way out the door, Mickey was like,
if you got anything lying around,
I gotta experiment with science on the side.
Pooh Bear, it's the five o'clock shadow Pooh Bear
in this parade where he has that like,
his snoot is colored brown
and it just looks like he's tired or he's been drinking
or he just hasn't shaved in a while.
He's getting a lot of five a.m. calls from Mickey.
I still don't know why that's the version
that they had for a while.
I don't know.
I think he's cute though.
Yeah, I like him.
I'd like to see him back on a throwback line or something
where it's all Max is gonna be there,
Darkwing Duck's gonna be there,
five o'clock shadow snoot Pooh is gonna be there
and that's exciting.
Well, he does this like crazy,
like kind of like swively worm kind of dance.
He does real hip hop in this.
So I'd like to see him at that,
the some 90s event doing that.
You know what?
Pitch entire Mickey Mania parade.
The whole thing's happening.
I genuinely think they could bust this thing out now
exactly and people would lose their minds.
I think so, yeah.
Part of the throwback night or whatever.
Yeah.
The only thing would be.
Oh no, regular park two.
Just during the day.
Oh yeah, probably.
Yep, send it out.
When is the majority of guests ever been mad at the parade?
Even in the version,
what's that one parade we did already an episode on
with the like.
Light magic with the pixies?
The pixies and stuff.
Yeah, that is probably the one.
That's the only time people are like.
Because they had terrifying scarred looking faces.
Yeah.
And replaced Main Street Electrical Parade.
That's maybe the only time.
Otherwise, yeah.
I think you just bring this thing back exactly.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess there are,
maybe some people are upset
about some of the deconstructions and the freaks.
And I guess if there was one,
and this is really the litmus test, I guess.
If there was one that was going to upset you,
maybe we've made it to this point.
I think we all know which one I'm going to bring up.
Yeah.
Because we've seen every type of Mickey.
There are weird inflatable limbless Mickeys
as if he grew them in a lab.
You know how KFC does the chickens without the,
without the arms and legs, without wings?
Let's do that.
Let's get that done.
But just, all right, do me a favor.
Just grow 10,000 of them
and the six most attractive ones we'll use in the parade.
The rest, you know what to do, hit them with a dip.
And I don't mean ranch or sour cream
or sweet and sour sauce.
I mean the dip.
You know, you get my drift.
So there's that.
And then there's other like inflatable looking ones
that just look like hulked out Mickeys.
Essentially looks just like a bigger, stronger Mickey,
just massive, more a street shark slash Jay Leno proportions.
Oh yeah.
But the one is an upside down Mickey,
like a fully distorted inverted Mickey
who walks on his hands and his feet are up in the air.
And also as part of this transformation,
his seat is massive.
So at the top of this Mickey is just a big wide butt,
let's just say it, with giant shoes.
So his whole, take Mickey, grow his entire lower half,
puff it up full of helium by 50%,
then flip it, make him walk around on his hands.
And then is the head big and weird?
No, head is normal.
Head is normal.
And depending on the photo or video you're looking at,
down at his crotch or down at his butt?
Yes.
I don't know if-
And the legs are real spread.
I don't know if,
even though you described it really accurately,
you're gonna have to go to social media or Google this
to find this.
I mean I love for a listener,
as the guy on the phone drawing Mickey's crazed visions,
I would love to see somebody draw it
based on my description.
That's a good idea.
I wonder if they'd get there.
Maybe they'd get close.
Yeah, it's weird.
And then it's the fact that his head
is then just like kinda looking at you straight,
like it would be if he was a regular Mickey.
But it's down at his butt.
And it doesn't kind of seem like his head
is trying to crawl out of his ass.
Like he, like Mickey ate himself.
That's what this whole thing is.
It's like Mickey ate himself.
It's a Mickey swallowing, so yes.
It's a Mickey Ouroboros.
It's not an alternate name, Mickey Ouroboros.
It's almost like the Lonesome Ghosts cartoon
where Goofy gets caught in the dresser drawers
and he sees his own butt and then he attacks his own butt.
He doesn't go inside his butt or anything.
But it does have that body horror thing
that I as a child, that part was a little disturbing to me
because Goofy's hurting himself really badly
and his body was contorted in such a crazy way.
This just takes it to another level
where Mickey has literally eaten his own head
and it's coming out as rectum.
This one good.
This is the best Freak We Grew.
This is my favorite movie.
I like this.
This is the, I look, not to call myself perfection,
but I'm a fan.
Look at me.
America's a fan.
The world's a fan.
It speaks for itself.
But maybe an improvement.
Maybe I want you to join me.
Imagine the world's first cartoon characters
and the head is coming out of its rectum.
It's breathtaking, isn't it?
It's, I don't, how, why?
Like there's a lot of other stuff in the parade.
Why this?
Why, how is it approved?
It's one of the weirdest things
that's ever been in the park.
Yes, there's not a lot of things
that you'd describe as disturbing.
But I'm also not, I also think it's awesome.
The guy, Disney Dan, did a video all about this
and he's like, I hate it, kill it.
I'm like, I feel the opposite.
I don't disagree with any adjectives you're using,
but I'm fascinated by this.
I'd get a toy of this, I think.
Well, we'd all get toys of that,
Mickey with his head coming out of his ass.
I think it's kind of like the legs and hands,
well the hands are the legs.
Ah, fuck.
He's not really square,
like it's not really stuck out like a starfish,
but I feel like there were some stuffed clowns
floating around like my house
and my grandma's house growing up.
And I feel like it's a version of that.
Yeah, so maybe that's where it comes from.
Lins spread way out.
Yeah, lins spread way out.
Right, and yeah, they weren't like, you couldn't.
Some Christmas ornament clowns, I feel like.
This is kind of, it's sort of like Sid from Toy Story
took a Mickey.
Oh yeah.
And did one of his little Sid operations on it.
But in this case, Mickey was like, approved, better.
Is it for sure the performer's ass
where Mickey's head is coming from?
I think I saw videos where it's up front
or he's where Mickey's head's packing up front.
Because that's sort of the first thing I see
is I can just see the person in it and essentially,
like I know, obviously there's legs are on the ground.
He's wearing gloves on his shoes.
And it just looks like Mickey is covering their genitals.
I think there is a version like that.
So yeah, imagine an inverse Mickey
who is dribbling his own head out of his dick.
Right, or it's like an Austin Powers joke
where he puts a Mickey head over
to cover himself or something.
That's sort of the way my brain goes, I don't know why.
Austin Powers in the brain like usual, but.
What a nightmare to like, imagine having a bad dream
where you're about to have sex with somebody
and then you unzip, you lower their pants
and then there's a big Mickey Mouse head there.
Oh God.
Play listener, tell me if I, first apologies,
second, tell me if I made you have that dream
by saying that.
Yeah, there's a few things.
I don't think that's ever happened.
I mean, people have maybe said
that they've had dreams about the show,
but if we ever provoked a nightmare with something in the,
this would be the episode, this is where it happened.
There's some ticking clocks in that.
Well, it doesn't even have to be,
it doesn't even have to be a sexual,
here, I'll widen the nightmare out.
It doesn't have to be a sexual thing.
Just imagine you're going.
I think that's like a weird, that's like if instead
there's like a big steak or something.
That's like something just, I don't know what to make of it.
Well, imagine you're in one of those situations
where you have to go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night and sometimes,
this happens to me, I don't know
if it happens to you, gentlemen,
I dream that I went to the bathroom
because I don't want to get up, I'm so tired,
so I kind of have a dream that I went.
I was sure that you were going to,
because that wind up and then you said,
I dribble a little bit and that's okay,
medically speaking, actually, it's encouraged.
It is, that was 100% correct things you just said,
but that's not where I was headed.
And you get up and you're actually dreaming,
but you're imagining you're doing the thing
that your brain is, have you ever had this?
Imagining, I was so distracted by the dribble.
Have you ever had a dream, you have an actual urge
to go to the bathroom, but you are so tired,
you're in the middle of sleep, that you kind of have
a dream that you're going to the bathroom
and you don't actually go.
And that takes you into some tangent, yeah, sure.
Yes, and it's still, like you wake up and you go,
I never, I didn't go to the bathroom, now I have to go.
I always find it interesting when the dreams hook up
to you trying to sleep, where it like stems,
instead of cutting to you somewhere completely different,
I like when it's like, the dream started with me in bed
at five a.m. and then I went on a little adventure
from there and I always find that interesting.
I only have that usually when I'm taking a nap,
where I almost have this weird like,
now we start literally where I am
and then weird stuff starts happening.
But it's usually nap, I don't know why.
Night, I don't have that.
Free from sleep, the dreams can get a little crazy.
Uh-huh.
But you remember them better.
But anyway, now we've lost the whole point,
so people have forgotten what I was talking about.
But I was over here.
If this was the Joe Rogan era.
The nightmare experience, that dream talk
would go for 120 more minutes.
That's true, and we would be making millions.
We'd be making millions of dollars.
DMT plus clips.
Ketamine, DMT.
DMT shit's fucking crazy, dude.
Yeah, ice baths or ice, cold plunges.
Is that a big thing with them?
Cold plunges are getting pretty popular.
Cold plunges are back with the celebs, too.
A lot of celebs doing cold plunges.
Steve Harvey, big cold plunge guy.
I listen to like an hour long thing
of what Steve Harvey does now for his health.
Cold plunge, a big part of it.
Now here, look, it's all to taste,
because I thought it was cool
you were listening to Rick Bito and Steve Lukather.
But then, so who am I to criticize?
You listening to an hour of Steve Harvey
talking about his health regimen?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know maybe it was 45 minutes.
In what form?
I'm trying to remember.
This is actually a few weeks ago,
so I can't remember what show it was.
But I don't remember how I got there.
I love Steve Harvey.
I think Steve Harvey's so funny.
So it was popping up in my algorithm.
And then he just started talking about his cold plunges
and this guy turned him on to a bunch of different things
like the whatever, some red light machine,
rich person's red light machine or something.
And I was fascinated by it.
Good start.
This was also said in last week's episode, too.
But you're gonna do every one of these things.
Yeah.
Cost permitting.
You are going to do every single
insane celebrity life extending thing.
I can't wait to see.
So Mike has this red machine.
What does it do?
I don't know, it blasts red at him.
I mean, that's the short version.
If you wanna hear the long version for Mike,
he will improvise an hour about every bit that the red bit.
You just lean back and it blasts red at you.
It blasts red.
Well, I think large infrared lights can get expensive.
But cold plunges, I was gonna say,
I think you make yourself with rubber meat,
but Mike's a tall guy.
So I don't know.
You'd have to get kind of a large rubber meat.
To be a too cold plunge,
it'd have to be a certain temperature.
And you'd have to bring ice in to get it that cold.
But you can do a version of it
if you really wanna fill the bath up
with really cold water.
So you can do versions of it.
Get some rubber made at Target.
And then you walk to the front of the store.
Hey, bags of ice?
Yeah, right there.
Sure.
What I do is, I mean, how do I look this good at 100?
Well, it's switching back and forth.
Cold and hot, cold and hot, cold and hot.
All night, and then I sleep from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m.
So I'm actually only up at night,
which is when creativity's better.
It's really when the best ideas come out
because you're in kind of this lucid state.
And I just make my employees also stay up with me
so they can transcribe my ideas.
I microdose DMT and ketamine.
I'm on a carnivore diet.
I'm listening to this Jordan Peterson book,
this self-help book.
It's really actually opening me up for a lot of things.
Yeah, Cleanser Room, something about lobsters.
I didn't follow it, so I've just been eating a lot of lobster.
Jordan just was responding to Mickey Mouse
Twitter accounts for about a few years,
and then I found he was on my radar.
He'll say like, fuck you, Yoda, and stuff.
And I was like, who's this guy?
But he actually has some interesting ideas.
It's actually pretty good.
You know, when I saw Shane Gillis saying the R-word
on SNL, I thought comedy is back.
It's like, it's legal again, folks.
Yeah, finally.
Finally legal.
I knew it coming, because I've been away, you know,
obviously in a hundred years, things come and go.
So I knew this woke era, you know,
that's gonna be a flash in the pan.
Just like Fievel, who I had killed.
It's actually, can you cut that part?
I don't really want that going out.
Since, I don't want to forget about that,
since we were talking about inflatable stuff,
can someone tell me what this is that I'm looking at?
That's the strap of an inflatable Mickey watch.
You're looking at, from your context and angle,
it looks kind of like a Caterpillar,
but you know, you were looking at a Mickey Mouse
watch strap turned to the side.
Okay, I see that, and it's a very specific,
I thought it was like a bandolier?
Like, I don't know what, I couldn't see.
Like watch straps are usually black, even Mickey watch strap,
I think of it as just a boring black leather watch strap.
Maybe they want it to be bright in the parade.
I suppose.
Yeah, but even though black's part of it,
there's obviously a lot of black in this.
There's also, in the last one, where he's,
like if you don't think you've seen enough Mickey,
then in the last float, the regular Mickey is up on top.
You don't even know what to make of,
I've been so, my vision's been so contorted now,
I don't know how to look at regular Mickey ever again.
But under him is a little like, you know,
twisting, turning factory of more little Mickey egg
type creatures. Oh yeah, I know.
It's kind of teeter and totter back and forth.
It's almost like, I wonder if it was supposed to be
a reference to Small World.
It's like a bunch of little like Small World Mickey dolls.
Or a reference to aliens.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's like his eggs.
Those are my eggs.
I laid those for the first time.
Please see my eggs.
We're gonna let Mickey, we're gonna let the fans in.
You guys didn't know that?
I lay eggs with little short patterns.
This final float with all of this Mickey design
and the little eggs and the little,
it almost looks like religious icons.
This whole thing is kind of this like false idol.
It's just like every possible,
let's worship every shape and size of this.
And it's somewhere between bizarre religious ceremony
and then also like something Kim Jong-un would make happen.
He would command that everybody do this
and people would be like pushed out of their homes
with big sticks to go start rehearsing this thing.
Yes, yeah, that's for sure.
Yeah, there's never been more,
Mickey is very celebrated.
There's been Mickey's birthday land, excuse me,
and these different shows, but none of those
are quite as grotesque as this whole package.
I don't know, that's an interesting thing
because I've never thought really on any of that stuff.
I go, well, Mickey's like the main character,
so obviously he's gonna get parades,
he's gonna get some of his own different lands, whatever,
but like this is maybe too much.
It's too much and I'm like at the end
of watching this parade a few times,
I'm like, what was the meaning of that?
What did that mean?
Then that's where you don't know in your awake state,
but when you're dreaming, that's when you'll figure it out.
Coming right at the same time,
this is not the only time they've used the phrase
Mickey mania, there was a Super Nintendo and Genesis game
that I remember, I watched a little of the play through
and similarly, I think the first level,
Mickey, modern yellow red, black Mickey runs through
Steamboat Willie, like you run by Willie driving the ship.
Well, also it's not so dissimilar to Epic Mickey as well
because that's sort of a deconstruction
of a lot of different Disney things
and you go through levels that are abstractions
of theme parks and of the shorts and stuff.
You gotta look at pictures of that Mickey mania game
because he looks so mad in them.
It's fun that Mickey, we're describing the brow
is so sharp and angular and he's with a bunch of bats,
he's kicking a sorcerer or something.
Yeah, the sorcerer, I remember it being a real menace.
That was one where I was like, this game is really fun,
the graphics are good, but I definitely stared
at that box art a lot.
There's another one called, this is a PlayStation one
called Mickey's Wild Adventure and it's him
looking again really angry, running at you behind him
or a bunch of ghosts and skeletons and hellfire.
Again, bats.
Boy, there's a lot of metal Mickey stuff out there.
Yeah, I mean that original, I guess,
I don't know if Mickey's face doesn't look angry,
but that original Epic Mickey art,
which looks so creepy and dystopian.
Some of the art still looks pretty scary, but yeah.
Mickey's really been through it in his long career.
He was willing to go dark, he was willing to go psychedelic,
he was willing to invert himself completely,
show us his eggs.
This is the most revealing personal thing he ever did.
Yeah, I would like to see his eggs again though.
Yeah. In some context.
Bring back Mickey's eggs.
The next time that there's an announcement
about something, and recently we have been getting
some announcements, we're recording this just as
there was an announcement of we're gonna do this stuff
in Paris, we're gonna change that park
and maybe some futures, hopefully some big stuff
coming this year, but anybody on our team
who listens to The Second Gate, you see some news
that even if it's news that you like,
just respond with bring back Mickey's eggs.
What if Disney started seeing this a decent amount
and the social media person has to go,
what is this, why are we getting this all the time?
I would love to see an event where Mickey lays
one of his eggs, and while he does that,
does like a Connor O'Malley kind of scream,
like an agonizing scream.
Well, cause it hurts to lay eggs.
It hurts, where's that coming out of?
It can't be that, the hole can't be that size all the time.
No, no.
The wider that thing gets, the tougher the effort is.
Of course, it's like a kidney stone,
like you're passing a kidney stone.
Yeah.
I've never had to drink enough water.
Right, and we got, that goes back to our hydration,
that goes back to our urethras.
I drank too much prime energy drink,
and they said I was super dehydrated,
passed an egg.
I made a deal with Logan Paul
to put prime energy on the castles.
They're all making deals with Logan Paul.
Castle now has a big prime energy logo on the side of it.
That's worth the money though.
We need that extra scratch.
Yeah, we're having hard times here at Disney.
We're worried about the Mufasa movie making box office.
What do we have coming out?
Daisy Ridley plays an accomplished woman swimmer.
Oh, shit.
Oh, there's a Yorg.
There was already a swimming movie at the Oscars,
and no one saw it.
Oh, wait, is that the Yorgos movie,
or is that a different one?
Oh, it's different.
There was standing up, and they'd have the full slate,
and on it was like Mufasa, Toy Story,
and then a Yorgos movie.
That's true.
Yeah, we go, Yorgos is doing Mickey Mania, the movie.
Oh, that would be great.
I'm gonna swear we're winning all the technical Oscars.
He's a weird guy, I love it.
That's Yorgos' house, Yorgos' house now.
That's what I call the studio.
He's doing it all.
Yes, Yorgos' house is about to get funky and fresh.
Yorgos is doing Smee.
The beat of the streets.
The Smee origins, the story.
Yorgos is doing the live action remakes.
Yorgos is giving them MCU.
Oh, Yorgos all the time.
I feel like we did it.
I guess, yeah, I think we did.
Yeah, hey, who was the trippy one?
The Yorgos movie of episodes.
That's true.
Well, what you said at the beginning about Twisted
was right.
It really was.
Yeah, boy, this was a trip to some weird places,
and I thank the Disney company for putting it on,
for loosening us up, for helping us all be
less big of narfos.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
If you wanna dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier, Club 3,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
And you know, you vote on the topics there,
so obviously we're gonna want it,
we're gonna see more urethra talk,
more anticipating when the kidney stones will,
yeah, the boys predict who will get kidney stones first,
and at what age.
Steve Harvey's just health in general
may be the topic for Club 3.
I think there's two ideas there.
One, the boys talk about Steve Harvey's health,
and how they can apply that to their own lives.
Two, Mike just holds up a laptop or a phone
to the microphone and plays that other thing that he heard,
and we pass that off as our own.
Sure.
That's a scam even I can get behind,
repackaging someone else's podcast for a profit.
I'm listening.