Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
My name is Michael Carlson and happy birthday to me, I want to say.
Very special day, very special birthday, I've decided, am I going to stop celebrating the number, much like a Leslie Mann character in a Judd Apatow movie, I'm not sure.
Which way, which movie?
I assume all of them is the same thing, right?
Uh huh, but are you referring to a specific movie, like with an age in the title?
Maybe I am, I don't want to say that one out loud, because I haven't decided how I'm going to address it, but Scott Garner is here.
Hi, hey, happy birthday to you.
Thank you very much, Jason Sharon here as well.
Hi.
How are you doing, Jason?
Oh, pretty good, how about you, big birthday boy?
Fine, fine.
I will admit, when we're talking about my birthday, I will admit that I was like always when I would see movie and TV where people would be like complaining about their birthday or like, oh, I'm getting so old or whatever, I was like, this is silly, this is ridiculous.
And I feel like worse, I feel the same way as all these people in like movies and TV historically.
Right, right.
Well, I mean, I mean, is it like, what is it about this one?
Is this a birthday that's like, I don't know, particularly notable?
Is it a birthday that, I don't know, changes more of the initial tagline and premise of the show?
Scott, you're trying to get me to say it and I don't want to say it.
I'm just asking questions.
That's all.
That's what this podcast is about, it's just asking questions.
So I understand and I appreciate what you're doing.
You're, Lindsay's brushing her teeth and you're sitting on the toilet with the iPad, like a poster.
Right, and she's like, why are you always hiding?
Some sort of poster, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you know what?
Maybe the end of this podcast, I'll reveal the number in case we haven't said it.
I think we have said it.
I mean, look, here's the thing.
If it's the number that I'm wondering about, I don't get what the problem would be.
Mike, everything that I know about you that I've experienced over years of doing this podcast leads me to believe that's a number you'll be fine to reach.
There's no, I can't imagine any complexes from you that would come from a certain...
I don't see you, I don't know, wearing your hats even more backwards to try to counter a certain number.
That backwards hat is not necessarily to make me look younger.
I will say that, but I have been doing that more, but that's more my...
I'm unhappy with my hair and not just the color of it, but that's more of that than it is me trying to appear younger.
You just need a full, maybe you need some makeover in general.
I've dressed like a child for a long time, so nothing has really changed as far as that's concerned.
But anyway...
And you know what else hasn't changed?
One day it hits midnight and it's another day, doesn't mean anything has to change.
It doesn't mean that your understanding of what teens like and the high probability of you being mistaken for a teen yourself, why would that happen just because it turned midnight one day?
Of course! It doesn't mean anything, Jason!
Jason!
Way in here!
Grabbing your wrist doesn't mean anything!
Al, you're hurting me!
Good! See, you agree with me.
So anyway, really, what this is not about me today, honestly. It's not about me.
It's about a thing I've chosen and it's about others.
Which is a surprise. This is for the first time, I think. I think previously we've announced what each other's birthday shots are going to be, but here is the second year of birthday shots. It is a true surprise to us.
And it's a true surprise mostly because I could not decide.
And I'll give you a quick look into what was happening.
Because even as of yesterday, I wasn't sure and I went through a lot of ideas.
There's things, and I'll give a couple examples of what I was thinking of.
First, I thought maybe we do an episode about Uncle Wiggly.
The Rabbit Gentleman.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, there you go. So Uncle Wiggly was a game we had growing up, a little game.
And Uncle Wiggly is a rabbit gentleman.
And he was elderly. Specifically, they would say he was an elderly rabbit who suffered from rheumatism.
You need to know this to play the game?
You don't need to know what to play the game.
You don't need to know this. Uncle Wiggly goes back to newspapers when millions of people are reading.
Like 1900.
Yeah, it's early 1900s pop culture.
We took out Uncle Wiggly books from the library and then found them at a yard sale.
So it's one of these sorts of...
Did they steal them from the library?
Hopefully not.
I'm on to them. I'm on to these guys.
They're trying to turn a profit.
Well, maybe they fled town to do it.
Yeah, it's possible.
And Uncle Wiggly, there were many, many books, many things written.
So there's a lot of material there.
But I thought, I don't know, I'm not feeling Uncle Wiggly right now.
Certainly in the future, there will be more Uncle Wiggly content.
I thought, hey, maybe Zubili Zoo.
You know, I've talked about that before.
And I did a little look into that.
And that's, you know, that's interesting.
And again, something we should probably talk about one day.
And then I was like, I don't know, this feels like these episodes would be something we would probably do anyway.
And then I thought, well, what if I did something that would make people mad?
And I thought, what if we did?
What if I just rolled in here today and said, Indiana Jones 2 right now, let's go.
We're doing Indiana Jones the Ride 2.
Yes. Yeah. Oh, that'd be an interesting move.
And I think like, I was like, Jason, Jason would be like, I wanted to prepare for the like, everybody would be like, I want to listen to the first one.
I was going to say exactly that, yeah.
Yes. Like, so I go, that would make everybody mad.
And I go, do I really want to do that? Do I feel like that right now? At least no.
I said, that would be funny, though.
I thought maybe we do a Disneyland app episode just about the app and how using the app is like.
Oh God, oh God.
And I said, well, that's pretty indulgent.
But then like, Jason's probably on board with that too.
You know, he's interested in apps.
He likes to talk apps with me.
I mean, I'm not interested in holding my very hot phone.
That always occurs when I load up.
Is your phone very hot?
No, my phone is not, except when I run the Disney apps.
I know what you mean.
Because you're out there, maybe not, because maybe that Wi-Fi is not working.
And it's a complicated little animations.
You got to get through a freaking figure out what they'll time to do a thing.
Yeah. And also just having it out a lot means the sun is hitting it.
Yeah. So it's working hard.
It's heating up and then the sun is hitting it and it traps the heat as well.
So I see what you're saying.
Yeah. But I thought, I don't really want to.
I started I started trying to figure out, well, what do we talk about?
And I go, I don't know. This isn't this isn't that fun.
But maybe maybe there's an angle on in the future. Yeah.
So I just want to call shots for all four of those things in the future, I think.
But I didn't feel right.
And then I said, OK, well, what stuff we've talked about before that?
I'm like, I'm not sure where it slots in or if it's its own episode.
And I was like, you know what?
We always like touch on certain actors singing careers.
And I said, yeah, they're oh, yeah, there's a lot of stuff in this grab bag.
So I said, you know what?
Let's do a second gate on the Actors Attempted Music Careers grab grab bag edition.
Part one. That's what that's what it is.
This isn't a false tee up. Wow. OK.
Nice little grab bag of things.
Some things we've talked about them, some things we have not talked about in regards to when an actor takes a swing,
a couple swings maybe and tries to have a music career as well. Wow.
All right. OK.
So I thought I'm fully on board here.
You know, I had a book called Hollywood Hi-Fi.
Yeah. That went into probably maybe some of what you're even going to talk about,
but especially because it was really tracking like old movie stars and sitcom people in there.
And like this is what I'm doing this at 10, 11.
I'm into this kind of thing. Sure.
As an of course, as a child would do, because I'm very curious because I felt here too,
because I was like, OK, because like I wanted it to hit everything.
I wanted to have stuff where we all go, oh, we like that.
And then I do want to punish you two with a few things.
You know what I'm saying?
So we get a grab bag.
Exactly. Wow. All right.
So I finally, I think I decided to do this at 9 p.m. last night.
OK. Wow.
And that had been after hours of researching and looking through the other stuff.
And I just wasn't feeling it. It didn't feel right.
Wow. And then I went, oh, this feels more right.
So it's going to be a little messy. I have a lot of tabs.
I don't know if we'll get to everything.
There might be some stuff where you're like, I want to hear more off that album.
Sure. We get like bogged down in it.
So that I just want you to remain flexible.
And that's why I've said part one here, because there's obviously more
than we can cover in a whatever, however long this is going to be.
You call it, I think, I think as much as you you you declare the end to your party,
you know, yeah, just just like just like you declare, all right,
it's time for everyone to message Prince to get him to come to my birthday.
In the same regard, you have control over it. Yes.
You say when it's. Well, thank you.
But also, if you guys are like, oh, there's more to this.
What is this? Can we hear a few more?
Like, please step in and it'll be it'll be a little bit chaotic.
But I think I think that'll be better unless I don't want to just give a book report
is what I'm saying. Great.
So let's start with something that I think maybe we've played on the show before,
but not for a while.
You know, what I'm going to do really quick is I'm going to say if we want to keep going longer,
you know what I'll say is enhance. Oh, OK.
That'll be the word. Sorry, we're going to go deeper.
Yeah, that's fun. Yes.
That's a word said by someone we're going to talk about today.
I'm sure one of the people has said it on his TV show and movies.
Yes, I think that's correct.
You probably know what you know what we're talking about, I think. OK.
But let's start here with Emanuel Lewis. Oh, boy.
TV's Webster. Yeah.
Have we have we done this on the show? I can't remember.
No, I don't think so. No.
He has a song called City Connection, which was released in Japan.
And there was I think it was just a single.
He did not have a full album.
But there was a trend in Japan to bring like American stars and give them a singing career.
Obviously, it was a trend here, too.
But sometimes it was like it only landed on certain celebrities like Emanuel Lewis
when he was a child, like when he was young.
I remember that I feel like they tried this with all of the you know, I think maybe Gary Coleman did something.
I think I think Rodney Allen Rippy ever heard that name? Of course.
Yes, of course. He's a jack in the box kid.
I think he did music. Yep. Yep.
But Emanuel Lewis, I don't remember. I don't know if I ever heard this.
And so this and this also I I've saw some people trashing this, which I I kind of like this one, I'll say,
because it's like very I really like like 80s like Japanese city pop and stuff.
And it's very dancey and disco and stuff.
This isn't the greatest song ever.
But I'm starting with something that I would say I like more than don't like when you got to like this cover.
Oh, I should show you. Yeah. Yeah. This this cover.
Well, I love what you're showing me.
There's another there.
It's just a close up of his face with kind of cool 80s Japanese text.
But then this one has that, too.
But he's he's a giant windup toy is a giant winder screwed into his back.
Yeah, that's pretty wild.
Now, a theme you'll see is when you're a theme that I hopefully has gone more away is like kids singing as if they're like 25
and like hanging out in cities at night or like hanging out like that's really weird.
And that trend, I think, has stopped, although I don't know.
I don't know if there's any recent examples of like 10 year olds having singles recently.
Is this kind of considered legit city pop?
Because I think it is.
It's on your J-Pop Wiki.
It's written by legit like city pop guy, I believe.
So, yeah, yeah.
I think it's from 1981.
So that's in that era.
That's in that like plastic glove zone.
I forget if plastic gloves 81.
But yeah, so here we go.
Let's just play a little one.
Yeah.
Let's make a connection, baby.
Weird, weird.
Yeah.
But music pretty good.
Very off the wall.
Yes.
Ring it, ring it, ring it, ring it, ring it tonight.
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance it tonight.
The telephone is gonna do, it's gonna do, it's gonna do.
I think I expected better singing than this.
Oh yeah.
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it tonight.
I mean, it's a child singing.
How old is he?
Yeah.
1981.
I don't have the age for it here.
He's 10.
I said 10.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wow.
No, he's not a good singer.
Oh my God.
It's a novelty song with cool music in it.
Yeah.
And background singers.
Wow.
Really bizarre find whenever I, I don't remember how I found this a couple years ago.
A really fun, like, and not, obviously not like some polished little Michael Jackson,
who was like an amazing singer at 10.
Yeah.
So I just, yeah, I, I, this is a weird novelty song.
You know what it really, you know what it's a cousin of is, do you know the, the, the
French pop artist, Geordie?
Yes, I've heard, yes.
Geordie is a, was a seven year old.
Yeah.
Who had a hit song with the translation is it's tough to be a baby.
It's a little like dance, like, but it's, but a song about complaining about being a
baby.
And then a big choir of babies all come in at some point.
I have to be Geordie talk down the road.
It really, a lot of this feels just like there was a song lying around and they're like,
I don't know.
Nobody wants to record this one.
So like, let's give it to Emmanuel Lewis.
What a way.
Cause that you'd put a real singer on that and something could happen.
But yeah, for sure.
But yeah.
So city, also city connection is a good title for a song.
Really is.
Yeah.
I'm not saying I'm like, oh my God, he's a great singer or any of her, but getting
hyped.
And then I'm sorry.
I think I helped it up too much in that regard.
I would say maybe nothing on this episode is going to be like, I'm not, I'm not going
to champion anything as hard as I like McGruff, smart kids.
It's not happening on this episode.
If you're thinking, I find like an amazing gem, but there's going to be stuff in here.
I like at least, I mean, I like the novelty of it and I like the music, but yes, he, he's
not such a dynamic singer.
Wow.
You got a live performance of this seemingly.
Did you check that out?
Is that any good?
I, you know what?
Actually I didn't look at that.
But I mean, I guess we could.
So little.
It's reminding me.
There's a video game from 1985 called city connection.
I'm.
Oh really?
Why does that, that phrase was bugging me?
Uh, cause I was like, I feel like there's something now.
Oh, cool logo.
America, North America.
It's, it just came at us.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like, there's a video.
My parents have me singing the rainbow connection.
Oh, which I guess I, now that I think about it, I should've brought that out.
Really?
Yes.
A different connection.
Uh huh.
Actually I sing the whole Muppet movie.
There's a video of me and I might've been maybe a little younger, maybe like eight.
And I'm doing like, can you picture that?
I'm doing, can you picture that?
And I'm doing all of it pretty good.
Like I know all the lyrics.
Wow.
I didn't want to do the Miss Piggy song cause it was slow.
Boring.
Yeah.
So.
Wow.
I'm going to jump around.
I'm already out of order of what I was going to do, but let me bring up a different artist.
And I didn't realize that, I didn't realize that this person had a career this young.
I knew she had a career later, but I didn't realize that Jennifer Love Hewitt had an album
that was released when she was 13.
Well, was she a kid incorporated?
Yes.
Okay.
But I didn't, I just either didn't know or didn't remember.
And she had some, but she was referred to, of course, as Love Hewitt and the album was
Love Songs.
And you're again, getting into the territory of like, were these songs written for like
a 13 year old to sing or were these lying around?
So there's a couple of things on here that's worth a little mention.
Let me play First Taste of Love, which is, I guess.
And this is where, again, you'll get into the music area where you go, hmm, some of
this music sounds like, I like some of it like, it's like Marauder or something.
Yeah.
Let's go.
It's like a big, rainy first song on 13 year old Jennifer Love Hewitt's album.
Oh, I like this.
Yeah, good.
I'm not scared anymore.
Little, little guitar there, little funk guitar there.
Can't be mad at that.
Not bad.
No, I think we're in the MMC zone.
I'm happy.
Yeah.
Yes.
So like, I don't know.
Good.
Pretty good.
Yes.
This instrument, like, and it's like, clearly like, you know, in the wake of Madonna and
there's a lot of like Janet Jackson, I feel like, influence on this album as well.
Sure.
And like, yeah, I don't know.
It's not, it's not like a revelation, but you're like, all right.
Yeah.
Things are all right.
Trying to track the producers of this.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not finding much.
Yeah.
Some of these, I have a couple, a couple of them, I have some credits that are interesting,
but I couldn't find anything that was so crazy here.
Let me.
This is, that's a Japan only also.
The single, there was a single released only in Japan, I believe.
Okay.
She has a 1995 album on Spotify called Let's Go Bang.
Is that from 95?
Yeah.
It says 95.
Whoa.
Okay.
Because I know she has like 2007, like there was that other like.
2002, Bare Naked.
That's 2002.
Okay.
1996 is just called Jennifer Love Hewitt.
And then in the, the video is very, I very much feel like they were trying to style her
after like an Avril.
Oh, sure.
In that Bare Naked period.
Because there's a couple of music videos there, but I was like, oh, maybe, maybe Jennifer Love
has to go back to sort of the retro, the retro vibe here, not chase the trends like in the
2000s, the 2000s, you know.
Let me put, let me play.
So this, this album seems to be a mix of songs, like just general love or infatuation songs
and then like calls to action for a better world.
Oh, great.
Good.
Yeah.
That's the world she's going to grow up in.
And there's a song called 90s Kids.
Oh, cool.
Which yes, that caught my eye and I don't want to over hype it, but yes, that is, it's probably
what you're thinking.
So I'll do a little 90s kids here.
Researchers say a newly discovered hole in the ozone layer is the cause of the world's
rainforest.
Now conditions worsen in Ethiopia, the worst nuclear disaster.
It was like talking to the radio.
It was like, that was just like it was.
And who better to address than a 13 year old Jennifer Love you or any 13 year old.
I shouldn't even say it like that.
I mean, these are all sounds I really like.
Yeah.
She's looking to the future.
Optimist.
Now we're going to be peace centered.
Jennifer, you have no idea.
The short and tall.
Will there ever be peace between the short and tall?
Yeah, I don't know.
We try to forge on this podcast.
Jason and I can be friends.
Your differences aside, see eye to eye despite not seeing eye to eye.
I've got to get a couple apple boxes.
Here we go.
90s kids.
We're going to teach the kids the world right from wrong.
Great.
Yeah.
Do it.
Wait, one more part.
Remember, I think it's the end where she says 90s kids over and over again.
Well, and they're making good on it now with like, you know, like actresses who were on sitcoms and CW shows in the 90s.
You know, nagging on Twitter about where we got to vote Democrat.
Oh, well, that's yeah.
Not Jennifer, but other.
Not her.
That's just that's the 90s kids generally.
They're really doing it now.
That is the 90s.
We're all adults now and these same ancient ghouls are still death gripping.
They still have a death grip on power.
So they will not release it.
If you stop buying avocado toast, you could have a house.
Yeah.
So this yeah.
But like so like the album is full of stuff like this.
And I'm like, you know what?
This maybe this is maybe this is one of the closest ones to being like, oh, maybe I champion this.
Yeah, yeah.
Album from now on.
You got a producer on this, Greg Porey, who seems to be among the has a lot of very legit credits, but also did a lot maybe even.
Oh, he wrote a famous celebrity song, Mr. T's Be Somebody.
Oh, yeah.
I have me.
I mean, I think I have a Mr. T in here.
Oh, really?
Somebody. Yeah.
It might be another one by this guy, though.
We might have a shared credit.
So there's a and also and worked on Eddie Murphy's music as well.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
The hits, I assume.
I don't know.
Well, you know, what was the one I saw?
C.O.N.
Confused.
Oh, from 1985.
That's a fun.
You really think about getting how unstoppable Eddie Murphy was and just like, God, the funniest man on earth and the best SNL run every movie has been.
And then like, well, he was not totally unstoppable.
I would say no one can name more than two Eddie Murphy songs and the ones you can name are not good.
Still a big.
Well, what?
Party all the time.
Yeah.
All the times.
Okay.
Yeah, like that.
But fine.
But still pretty good.
I guess he did have a hit.
That's what I mean.
I know.
It's true.
Yeah.
Just one hit.
And in addition to a huge stand up career and a huge acting career.
That's true.
But there are like he put out like in his last star run, he put out an album every year that no one remembers anything from.
Sure.
I'm just giving I'm like he got enough points on the board there.
That's true.
Yeah.
Michael Jackson one is not that one's rough.
Sure.
Yeah.
Now this I'm wondering if Scott, you have heard any of this because I did vaguely know this, but I hadn't actually listened to it before.
Now, most of the people on today's episode, I like.
Yeah.
In general.
This is maybe the guy I don't like as much personally, just from certain things he said and the way he is now.
But Scott Baio had a couple albums.
You know, I can't place anything from a Scott Baio album.
So first of all, there's two albums and the problem is there's going to be a couple songs I want to play.
Yeah.
Because again.
Do what we got to do.
Let me show you the cover of this.
Scott Baio, The Boys Are Out Tonight.
I mean, a great cover.
Do you have hits?
He feels like a guy who they would have gotten on American Bandstand and like.
He was on Dick Clark.
Yes, he was on.
I don't know if they were.
I don't think they were like big hits or anything, but they definitely made a big push for it.
Yeah.
And this is from 1983.
OK.
It's in the zone again of like they're using sounds we like.
I think that.
Yeah, I know.
I'll forgive a lot just by what the equipment that's in the studio.
He has.
There was a self-titled, I believe, Scott Baio album as well.
And there's a song on there called How Do You Talk to Girls?
So let me just play.
Let me give you like a little bit here.
Let's play.
I'll Take You Back First.
I mean, very cars of the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's fine.
It's serviceable.
He's going for that Rick Springfield money.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not a great singer.
You can feel the difference.
You can feel like the step down.
There's stuff you can't even qualify or quantify.
Sometimes when you're listening to a song, you're like, it sounds like the cars.
But you can feel it's like a full letter grade or two letter grades down from the songwriting.
Less umph.
Less.
Yeah, like there's just like it's missing a couple interesting choices.
Yeah.
Like it's hard to sometimes articulate why one song is great and one song is OK.
And I was trying to determine it because like the cars, the best car stuff is great.
I mean, the music on all of these are clearly made by very technically good.
Well, of course, yeah.
Or more like instrumentalists and stuff.
But I think only the Jennifer Love Hewitt song so far seem like.
I feel like one or two of those I had heard before.
Oh, really?
Like I think she's probably the best singer out of the three so far.
Well, she's in Hunchback of Notre Dame 2.
Sure.
I'm going to let you in there unless you get some pipes.
So, yeah, let me let's see here.
Let's do see how the love goes.
On my bedroom door.
It's very.
I find you rather shocking.
It's my best friend's girl.
Imagine my surprise.
There's a holy looking bride.
It's so generic.
A lot of like of the night, you know.
This is the real story.
The night in the night.
See how the love goes.
All this music where like nothing, nothing is happening.
Nothing wrong is happening.
But nothing right is happening.
Yeah.
A couple quick hits here and then we'll get digging a little more.
This is called some girls.
Maybe the best song on this album from the brief listen I did.
This sounds like.
Lobster.
Some girls lie.
Hillary.
I turn away.
It's OK.
Yeah.
So, by the way, I'm not endorsing any of the messages in any of these songs.
I just want to let you know, listener.
You know, this is bad, but that his Wikipedia doesn't have a discography section.
Well, I was actually kind of surprised that there were two full albums because I feel like this one isn't ever talked about.
Yeah.
As far as his music.
Obviously, he's maybe not the most popular guy at the moment because he's a unpleasant idiot.
But, you know.
So let me hear.
Hold on.
Let me get to maybe we'll get to the second one real quick here.
I didn't know he was in super babies, baby geniuses, too.
I didn't know that either.
So this is this.
This is the cover of Scott Baio self-titled.
He's in like a yellow sweatshirt, which is very.
So I have this kind of similar sweatshirt, which I wore to Comic Con one year and Matt Cardona made fun of me.
Hey, Scott Baio over here.
Yeah.
He did not say Scott.
You love doing that diagonal lean.
Oh, I was leaning.
That's maybe why he was funny.
OK.
This is called.
How do you talk to girls?
I have no idea.
Still, which is the maybe the anthem anthem of podcast, the ride usually talk less.
Listen, there might be a little more juice in this one, I think.
No way.
Talk to them for hours and hours about theme parks.
That's what you do.
Just a little bit of heat.
We're all sick of hanging out on the street.
Saturday night with the boys.
The boys.
Listen to the radio with big feet.
We're cracking just to hear the noise.
And yeah, we're talking about the girls, girls, girls.
We're talking, talking, talking all night.
We're showing off all we own.
We're passing over stuff we can't seem to get it right.
It seems to make it harder and harder.
Springfield.
Yes, yes.
The river.
How do you talk to girls?
Springfield wrote them too.
Lake and Tarr.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tell me how do you talk to girls?
How do you talk to girls?
That's what he's wondering now.
He wants to marry Marjorie Taylor Green.
How do you talk to red-pilled girls?
So this one, with a different singer, I think I would really like.
All of these, these are probably all songs that floated around on the song market.
And then like, good news, there was a sale.
Oh, good, who?
Scott Baio.
Oh, no.
Oh, good, who?
Scott Baio.
Oh, no.
Like, the music itself was pretty good.
But those were the best takes they could get with him saying, how do you talk to girls?
Like, really?
They couldn't dress it up a little more?
Sorry.
Look, it's very, you know.
Like, this is the case of some.
Actually, she was OK singing-wise.
But Hilary Duff, you go later into, like, let's give the pop career to the actress.
But there were some early ones where it was just like, now entirely other women come in
and sing the chorus.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that makes sense, at least.
They're trying to, like, if they're like, I don't know, the vocal isn't really strong
here.
At least prop.
Like, prop Baio up with some background singers.
Yeah.
A little more.
I got to watch out, though.
That's how Io got in trouble with JLo.
Oh, right.
I saw it on a podcast.
Here I am doing it.
That's what I heard.
It's my chance to work with Hilary Duff.
Oh, yeah.
It's behind the paywall.
Don't tell anyone.
Yeah, don't tell.
Don't tell on Scott.
I don't want to spend too much more time on Scott Baio.
But I did hear, I was like, I was re-listening to this on the car on the way over here, this
Scott Baio, the first one, actually.
And I was like, oh, maybe She's Trouble is good from the Boys Are Out Tonight album.
So let me just do She's Trouble and then we'll move on from Baio.
She believes in free health care.
Taylor Swift is a sire.
I was like, oh, I like that too.
Yeah.
Sleepy little dream, dreamy as you'd say, dreamy.
Again, the more we're singing we've had.
Yes.
Kind of whisper singing.
I'm embarrassed to be with Scott right now.
They are double tracking his voice, which that can sometimes hide a little bit of like a thin sound.
Sure.
And sometimes it's used, like Ozzy Osbourne does that a lot, but that's kind of a cool
effect that gives it kind of a scary sound.
That's not what's happening here.
I cannot get the image out of my mind of Eddie Murphy.
Is it the party all the time video where it's like he's in the studio at one point holding
the headphones, doing some great studio headphone acting.
Yeah.
A bit of rush that video out.
So MTV was like, yeah, we'll play it.
Do you have a video?
Yeah.
But I just imagine every one of these actors doing that.
Well, it's very it's all like actually he's a he's a lot like fucking Dirk Diggler.
Yeah.
So much like the Dirk Diggler music and Boogie Nights where it's like generic early 80s
like, yeah, it kind of has the attitude, but the singer just don't got it.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
Should we I don't know.
Should we record?
We record some of these.
How do you talk to girls podcast?
The ride version.
We could give it some.
Yeah.
If we could like bring I mean, I guess this is a good question.
If Bayo has like a writing credit, like I don't want to give Bayo any money.
But if the writers of it, yeah, if the writers of it would get, you know, when it becomes
a big hit, I mean, yeah.
Yeah.
When all the money we generate from our version of how do you talk to girls?
It's it's I don't mind giving money to Pat Robinson or Johnny Kid.
Yeah.
Johnny Kid.
Sue Schifrin.
I don't know any of these names.
Yeah.
So so that that's fine.
Randy Foot.
He backing vocals.
OK.
Got it.
Here's a couple.
Let me do a couple of quick hits here.
I have so many thoughts about them.
Tina Yothers has a song.
Sorry.
Tina Yothers is Family Ties.
Yes.
From Family Ties.
And she had a song called Baby I'm Back in Love Again.
And this is a great cover.
That like airbrushed like pastel.
What do you call this?
I got some weird treatment.
This is just a quick hit.
This is from 87.
I love you.
Boy.
That's the main element to it.
It's all right.
Yeah.
This is plenty serviceable.
Yeah, I agree.
A lot of the choruses for these like celebrity songs seem like they just repeat the same
line over.
I don't always hate in a chorus, but it definitely seems like if this song was written maybe
specifically for them, the songwriter is like, I don't know, just write it or like say I'm
in love again over and over again or say, how do you talk to girls four times for the
chorus?
Like, I don't feel like writing a chorus here.
How do you talk to girls?
We only need to get one good take.
We can just repeat it.
How do you talk to girls?
Yeah.
And kind of seems similar here.
But yeah, a perfectly serviceable song.
This did not light up the charts.
I'm seeing that that one is written by a writer of a video killed the radio star.
Oh, wow.
Bruce Woolley.
Great song.
It does feel a little elevated as far as some of the other stuff I'm playing.
Yeah.
That's one of the best for sure.
So that is interesting.
OK, so now we're let's do Mr. T's commandments, I think.
Oh, Mr. T, there we go.
OK.
So we're on to Mr. T here.
Yeah.
And this is called Mr. T's command, commandments, even though it's listed as commandment singular
on YouTube.
OK.
So this is Mr. T. He is hanging out with a bunch of kids on a baseball field and he's
got commandments to make.
Yeah.
How much time can we kill before he has to sing or rap or whatever?
But so far, so good.
Funny thing, listen and then along instrumentals.
The Bible makes it clear.
OK, so the first part of this, the first commandment, Mr. T has is just like your parents are going
to help you out.
Yeah, your parents are friends.
Don't worry about it.
Make sure to clue them in on your life.
Right.
And the Bible says, he also says, so this is a religious song.
Mr. T is religious.
This does seem like I'm surprised McGruff never mentioned the Bible in any of his songs.
Yeah, yeah, true.
The Bible.
Your parents are your friends.
The Lord Jesus says it's so.
There's one power higher than law enforcement.
And that's the Christian God.
When he puts his cuffs on you, it's forever.
They send you straight down.
So yeah, so the commandment so far is just a long explanation of like your parents are
there to support you.
So let's keep going.
This song is five minutes long.
For a minute.
Again, a lot of music in this.
It's from you.
You've got Mr. T. So so far, the commandments are just to your parents, right?
Yeah, it's a lot of parents stuff.
Give your dad a kiss.
For me.
So it's from Mr. T. Now there's one for me.
Next one's Mr. T. On and on and back and forth.
It's interesting.
You know, I feel like a lot of the media that connects with kids, it's made by adults treating
them as intelligent human creatures.
Sure.
Yes, go ahead.
So much of the Mr. T. and Hulk Hogan stuff.
It's like, all right, it's aimed at children.
They're morons.
We've got to spoon feed these babies.
There's two different approaches.
Some could say one is more successful than the others.
Some kids need to get scared straight.
So when big muscle men say, believe in God or I'll beat you up, it works sometimes.
Jason, I know you were a fearful child, you know, so sometimes if you were yelled at by a celebrity.
I was very always confused by like the human cartoon characters like Mr. T.
I love Mr. T. though.
I like Mr. T. He was a little more ridiculous.
But every now and then, who would intro or outro GI Joe episodes?
Was it Sergeant Slaughter?
Sergeant Slaughter, yeah, yeah.
I would be like, what is this guy?
Where are the cartoons?
Who is this live action man?
Sergeant Slaughter looks like, I mean, he was drawn into GI Joe, but he looks like a cartoon.
His head is more cartoonish than Leno's head.
I don't know if you can think of Sergeant Slaughter off the top of your head.
No, I know.
I don't remember him.
I was at Starcast, the wrestling convention in 2018 and he was just had a table.
And he was trying to get people to come over to get, you know, buy a picture or buy whatever.
Take a picture, buy a picture, get an autograph.
And all of a sudden I hear, hey, recruit, come over here and I'll put you in the camel clutch.
Or wait, actually, it's a different move.
But I look over and Sergeant Slaughter is yelling at me.
It's you?
He wants you?
I didn't do it.
Now, in hindsight, it's crazy that I didn't just go over and pay him $40 for a picture.
But I was like, my goodness, this man is a cartoon.
Like, it's so crazy.
Yeah.
He looks, the photos of him look like they are AI generated.
So, yeah.
Then I remember some people being like, did they cast Sergeant Slaughter after they drew him in GI Joe?
And people were like, no.
What?
How would that be possible?
They didn't get like plastic surgery on his skull to do that.
All right.
So let's listen to Sergeant Slaughter, Max Martin single.
If that exists, if that exists, that's for part two.
This song, by the way, produced and written by a guy named Patrick Henderson, I kept looking up.
Co-writer of some Doobie Brothers songs that I love.
Oh, really?
It's a song called Real Love, a song from Michael McDonald's wife, maybe at the time, called How Do I Survive?
What's the other one?
What's his name?
Patrick Henderson.
Open Your Eyes, another dude.
It's songs I really like.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Mr. T went.
Let's do a little more.
Give me a Doobie.
I really like the chorus on this.
I know.
I mean, we've heard two choruses, so that's when he talks about God.
But it's just a catchy situation.
Let's just see a little more.
Back to the scratches.
Good way to excuse to repeat material.
Book goes on him.
Don't send him out naked.
I didn't understand.
What did he say?
I don't know why the name of this song is Mr. T's Commandments.
It's only about one thing.
Didn't you?
When I heard this, I was like, oh, it'll be a list of things he says.
You know, drink your milk.
Yeah.
Say prayers.
All that stuff.
But no, it seems to be about kids and parents.
And then he's yelling at the parents here.
I'm not sure.
They came up with the hook, maybe, on the chorus.
And then they're like, what is the?
He says he wants to just talk to kids' parents.
It also seems like the commandments are essentially the same as the Christian commandments.
He didn't really customize the commandments too much.
That's probably right.
Because it would be blasphemous to come up with your own commandments if you were Christian, right?
That's got to be.
Yeah, you're not really supposed to.
Because you could have other rule, but calling them commandments.
I have no false god before me, so false commandments definitely seems like you're getting into the false god territory.
But he didn't do it.
But he did put his name on the commandments, and he's selling them, and that seems like something Jesus wouldn't like.
Right. Does the Bible say, I pity the fool who worships a false god?
Pull up Bible.com, do a little search.
Pity fool.
You know, I think what happened is they wrote the one commandment, and then lunch arrived.
And they forgot, and then they jumped to happy hour, and then the next day they're like, oh, shit, he's coming in.
All right, let's just stretch the one.
Scratch the record. That way we can have the same word said for 30 seconds.
Mr. T.
All right, look, he's coming in for recording, and then lunch is going to arrive, and then we'll just get him out of here afterwards.
We just got 40 minutes to worry about.
If we give him enough carbs, if we give him a big enough sub or enough rice as a side dish, he'll get sleepy and get out of here.
And we just mix whatever we get for the morning.
Yeah, I wish there was more Mr. T. stuff. I don't know. It's just Mr. T. such a fun character.
Yeah, well, I mean, as mentioned earlier, be somebody. Yeah, yeah.
And there's like a Scott Bale level.
Well, some of the songs maybe weren't released as records, but they're in some video because I also I have in my head the song like, treat your mother right.
Right, right, right.
Again, so much parents stuff.
Yeah, a lot of parents stuff.
I guess the generation of latchkey kids, they need to be reminded like other people live in the house.
Yeah.
You don't see them very often.
Do you pay for this place? I don't think so.
You got a rent check.
Reimburse your parents later in their life.
Add up all the food they bought.
You can't be trusted to make hamburger helper.
It's not safe.
So OK, there's so much here.
I think we have to get to this real quick because this has come up a couple of times.
And it's Robert Downey Jr.
OK, OK.
It's Robert Downey Jr.'s album, The Futurist.
Oh, no. Oh, we landed in it.
We've got to do a little of it for this episode.
I mean, I'm relieved it's not a full episode.
I did contemplate full episode about The Futurist.
Now, what is The Futurist? Just refresh me.
He came out with just a straight ahead album in like, let me see, is it 2001, I think?
And it was just mostly written by him and a couple other people.
And a very completely very earnest stab at having a music career.
This is around the time of his comeback on like Ally McBeal, is that right?
Yeah, I mean, in that zone.
But yeah, it's so it's not I've said this before where it's like I don't it's not like such a oh, I can't believe this or whatever.
It's it's like absurd or whatever.
But it is very much sounds like it's of its time, like sonically and vocally and everything.
Released in 2004 on Sony Classical.
Sony Classical.
I don't know why it's on Sony Classical.
I think his idea maybe was again, yeah, full music career.
And then I think this just did not do well or didn't really spark.
This is produced by a guy I saw on one of the other ones.
Maybe Jennifer Loughue, his name is Mark Hudson.
He's part of the Hudson family.
He's like Kate Hudson is his niece.
Oh, really?
He's in that family lineage.
He's a cook.
I've seen this guy like at a concert or something.
He's like a kooky guy with a dyed beard.
Uh huh.
He worked with Ringo and Cher and Aerosmith.
He's a legend.
And Nilsson.
That's where I've seen him.
And Nilsson died.
The Baja Men.
All the legends.
Nilsson and Baja Men.
And Robert Downey Jr. is the futurist.
There's two covers on the album.
Let me see here.
One of them is a Charlie Chaplin composition, of course, because he played Chaplin.
And then there's a song by Yes.
Okay.
The first half of the song, I've Seen All Good People by Yes.
Oh, John Anderson of Yes plays on the album.
Does background vocals on your move.
It's his song.
Yes.
Oh, and then Smile, the Charlie, which Michael Jackson did too.
Right.
Right, right, right.
So again, this isn't like, I don't think there's a ton of like haha or anything here.
But just because I've mentioned it on the show before and because this song has a very funny title.
And that's really all that's just scratching the itch of me playing it for everybody.
And the song is called Little Clowns, C-L-O-W-N-Z.
It's Clowns and G at once.
Yeah.
All of Scott's favorites today.
Little Wind Up Children and Clowns and Little Clowns.
It would only be better if it was like Little Clowns Boy or something.
That would be the only so.
I want to, parentheses, I want to be a.
I want to.
And so that's yeah, you saw the cover of it.
And he's got like he's like using a coin.
Working hard.
Writing my lyrics.
This is pre Tony Stark.
I can't.
Like if I couldn't paint an image of like, I don't know what music I'm going to hear.
That's what I was about to ask.
Can you even take a guess what it kind of sounds like?
No.
OK.
It's kind of like like synthy.
What do you think?
Does it sound like late sting?
Is he trying to be like later sting?
Scott, you're.
Wow.
Is that a good guess?
That might be.
OK.
I'm like, yeah, because we're like, what would he like?
He'd probably like that.
The mountains outlast the summer.
A father gave us your number.
Our very own.
All of my friends.
All of my so-called brothers.
I can hear you holding the headphones.
So when you're a star, that's how you sing.
And if you think that a simple solution is retribution, please.
The song is called Little Clowns.
Little Clowns.
Yes.
Freeze job.
Scarled in situations.
Why am I standing?
Is this my home?
All of my tears.
They're bound to be hurt.
Tell them it should be called Robert Downey Jr.
Sings Words Weird.
Is this called Driven to Tears, you said?
This is called Little Clowns.
Oh, this is called Little Clowns.
Jason.
Driven to Tears, there is video of him singing with sting.
Oh.
He's a big sting guy.
And I think that's a lot of.
Yeah, wow.
I get that from nowhere.
Yeah.
Seemed right around that time.
The vibe is correct.
Yeah, yeah, you were right about that vibe.
Wow.
So that's a little.
This is why when we talked about this a couple of years ago and I was like, I don't, it's
not.
I at least give him credit.
It's not like some like C, A minor, D minor, G like straight ahead.
Like he's trying something.
Yeah.
It's like a little free form and it's not like, oh, I'm just writing like a simple.
I bet he busted his ass making this.
Sure.
Yeah.
Here's a compilation of him singing in Ally McPeel.
Oh, okay.
So he had some musical numbers in the show too.
He seems like a guy who would jump up and play with that.
You know, he's up with Mac or whatever.
Yeah.
So.
That's boring though.
It is boring.
It's boring.
It's a boring song.
He's a futurist.
He imagines a world of boring music.
Yeah.
So there's that.
That's a scratch.
It's a niche again.
There's not so much to.
Does he ever say the words little clowns?
He did.
Hold on.
Let me.
There's the lyrics here.
He says little clowns later.
He says, hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on little clowns.
You might just turn the world around.
These are just words.
It's kind of the same idea as 90s kids.
I think it's exactly the same because it's unfit for evolution.
Silly and pure.
I think somebody called some critic called these lyrics obtuse.
I believe I read a nice way of saying it means nothing.
Uh huh.
So.
But you know, again, if you have the right kind of sounding words, it doesn't matter
if the music or the lyrics are so meaningful or they, they, they, the words take on other
meanings.
Sure.
I'm just saying.
They could.
Hypothetically.
In the history of music.
I wouldn't be shocked though if after all this, then the, the cherry on top of this
is that then you reveal and, uh, uh, uh, Robert Downey jr. is the futurist one best album
at the Grammys that year.
There is a world where, cause that, the Grammys always will throw, at least in the past we'll
throw that at you.
We're like, what?
One best album?
Yeah.
And it's like something that like.
I feel like Sting won many Grammys for those albums that no one listens to.
Yeah.
Yes.
Even though like one of them was a big hit.
The one with like desert rose probably was a big hit, but I've never listened to it.
Yeah.
So maybe that maybe it's popular, maybe that's got its audience.
Maybe people are yelling at the podcast right now and give desert rose a chance.
But yeah, I don't know.
Brand new days.
Okay.
I guess I'm getting older.
I guess the biggest sign I'm getting older is that I now think brand new day is okay.
That's the equivalent of the opinion equivalent of a gray hair.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, okay.
Let's see.
What are we doing here?
Um, so many tabs to choose, which will mark decided to click on.
Uh, okay.
Okay.
Let's get to one that I've said many times and just give it a little, give it a little,
uh, attention.
Uh, uh, my beloved Brent Spiner.
Oh, finally.
Lieutenant commander data from Star Trek.
The next generation.
Oh yeah.
Oh, he's data, right?
No, he's not data.
Data is data from.
I can't, I I've said it before.
I can't explain why it drives me nuts.
Cause you love it.
There's other stuff that doesn't drive me that crazy, but for some reason data drives
me nuts.
I can't, I would have to go to therapy to understand why.
But do you think that it's always, is it valid to call to use data at all?
Is it like, like you could call data.
You could use that for regular data, but when it's a character, it's gotta be data.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
Of course.
I wouldn't be so upset.
Unless that, unless that is wrong.
Maybe somebody could tell me.
I don't know.
I'm reeling still from going to the George Lucas talk show where George said that it's
pronounced, technically it should be short-lived.
Everybody jumped down his throat and then he was like, look it up.
And the audience was aghast.
I'm aghast hearing that.
Apparently, technically we should all be saying that things are not short-lived, but short-lived.
Yeah.
This shook me, I don't know, like finding out my dad had a secret wife.
I didn't know.
I'm really thrown by that.
That is weird.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
So Brent Spiner, Brent Spiner did musical theater.
I forget, he worked with Sondheim in like the seventies or eighties.
He's had a lot of stuff.
I found a clip of him in like 1776 playing John Adams and singing.
Also in that is Pat Hingle who played Commissioner Gordon in the first four Batman movies.
Oh, I like him.
I'd like to see him in something else.
He's in Talladega Nights too.
I think that's one of his last roles.
And then he like, he sings a lot.
He's in Out to Sea, of course, the Walter Mathau Jack Lemmon movie where they're on a cruise ship.
Oh, right.
And he's pretty funny in it.
He's like doing like a snooty character.
And he does, I'll give you a little of the comedic singing of Brent Spiner here from Out to Sea.
Have you ever seen Out to Sea?
I'm trying to think.
I think I've seen Grumpy Old Men or Grumpier Old Men.
This could be a miniseries pitch to Griffin in Blank Check.
I don't mean the entire filmography of Mathau and Lemmon, but the post-Grumpy Old Men Blank Check.
Odd Couple 2.
Yes, Odd Couple 2, Out to Sea, and I would count my fellow Americans in this.
Suddenly America had Lemmon, Mathau comedy theaters.
This is like the 90s revival.
Grumpier, obviously.
I wonder if Out to Sea would like, I would be like, this is the funniest movie of the last decade.
If it came out now.
Possibly. I don't know.
I don't know anything about it.
Well, this will be a test, won't it?
Well, you're going to get a little Spiner.
So he's a cruise ship director and he's had it up to here with these troublemakers, these 80 year old troublemakers.
That's the premise of it.
But here, this is just like 17 seconds of him doing singing.
He does a little dance.
A little dumb clap. That's funny.
Yeah, silly version of Oye Como Va.
He's got a sense of humor.
He has two albums, I realized last night.
Two albums.
He has, of course, Old Yellow Eyes is back, which is, of course, like a parody.
It's a cover. It's a great cover.
And it's a good, yeah.
And it's black and white and he's got, Data, of course, has yellow eyes.
That's the joke there.
And it's a play on Old Blue Eyes is back.
Was that a Sinatra?
Yes. And he also has an album that's newer that I, not newer, but like newer in the last 15 years, 20 years, called Dreamland, which is like old songs as well.
But it's also got like skits in the middle.
Ooh.
And Mark Hamill is in it doing a voice that I would say he shouldn't be doing.
Oh, no, no.
So we'll see what we have time for.
I still have a chunk at the end here.
But let me do a little of Old Yellow Eyes is back that also has Jonathan Frakes, Michael Dorn and Patrick Stewart on it, which is, of course, the big boys.
The boys are here.
I don't know why LaVar's not on it.
That feels wrong.
That's his best friend in real life and on the show.
More celebrity best friends to track.
Best friends on the show.
And then they seem to be best friends in real life.
But I don't know why he's not on this.
It's called It's a Sin to Tell a Lie.
Be sure it's true.
That's that boy singing in the background.
Jason, does it do anything for you?
I like this.
Have we finally gotten something you like on this episode?
The spider sings the old ones.
I'm playing because there's also something coming up that is worth listening to.
It's a perfectly serviceable song.
I don't even mean that to sound derogatory.
You're like, oh, yeah, this guy.
Good for him for going for it.
I might take some of this fame.
What is it for if not to do your own little project?
Little standards.
Like you'll be doing soon.
Hello, baby, hello.
Be sure it's true.
When you say I love you, darling.
Because you know it's a terrible sin to tell a lie.
I wish he had known, though.
Oh, so many hearts have been broken.
Oh, you know what I should do?
Hold on, let me cut him off here.
Actually, now, again, I'm going to call this on the fly here.
Enhance.
There's a great, there is a funny, I don't know if you've ever seen this.
He was they were doing like a birthday tribute to Gene Roddenberry before he had passed.
Okay.
And I don't know if you've ever seen this clip.
Mr. Crusher set course for Starbase.
He's on the set.
He's in the uniform.
Patrick Stewart, I'm talking about.
Gene, you're adorable.
B, you're so beautiful.
Jason, have you ever seen this?
C, you're a cutie full of charm.
D, you're a darling.
And E, you're exciting.
This is just like a shot of for Gene.
But what's the song?
Oh, Jason, you tell me.
G, you look good to me.
Oh, he's got his hair.
H, you're so heavenly.
I, you're the one.
Oh, he caught a cane.
He's got a cane.
Oh, he's got a bowder.
He's got a straw bowder.
He's got a cane.
He's dancing like skipping off the bridge.
A little bridge.
L, is the love light in your eyes.
M, N, O, P.
He's going to slide down the rail.
I could go on all day.
Q, Q, R, S, T, alphabetically speaking, you're okay.
You make my life complete.
V means you're very sweet.
Double V, X, Y, Z.
It's fun to wander through the alphabet with you
to tell you what you mean to engage.
Jason, do you think we can get you doing this exact song
in some context?
I just wish there were more people on the bridge.
Like, they should be looking at him, longing.
Like, they should be bouncing a little.
Yeah, it should be a number.
It is very bare, isn't it?
Very bare.
It's like dead quiet.
Yeah, yeah.
Here's my question.
If we're going to, if Jason's going to do this,
who would Jason want to film a tribute,
who would Jason want to sing that song to?
And it can't be Jane.
It can't be Jane.
We got to take Jane out.
It has to be.
Whose birthday is it?
Oh, wow.
Sunny Eclipse?
Oh, whose birthday is it?
The Toppings Bar Innovation.
The present you want is Jason singing that song.
That song.
The G.
I think that you're okay.
M is for Mike, and L is for like, and I like.
Mike.
Sure.
That's what I want.
That's my gift.
I think I deserve it, quite frankly.
I'll say that I've tried to,
I've tried to say, Scott,
that there's some Star Trek next gen that you would like.
And that, even though that's not how the show is,
it is also the energy of the show in a way.
And when they do their little,
their little like history side tracks.
They go to the holodeck and they dress up
like Robin Hood and stuff.
Yeah.
You get your like silly 80s, 90s.
There's a little silliness to it.
I think the Brent Spiner album, like that song,
you can hear their smiling.
He sings on the show too.
I'm sure he does.
As well.
There's blue,
he sings blue skies in one of the movies.
And they sing,
they all sing like a piece of like the HMS pinafore
in one episode.
Oh gosh.
To jog data's memory,
to get him to stop being evil,
they sing old songs.
Like that's the silliness.
That's what we would have to do if Jason turned evil.
Yeah.
I am the very modern version.
But that's Pirates of Penzance.
Isn't that part of it?
HMS Pinafore and Pirates of Penzance are different shows.
Oh my God.
Let's look into that.
Let's make sure you're right about that.
I do like very much.
All right.
I feel like, okay, I have to get a little of this.
I'm going to not play.
Well, all right.
Can I use Samantha?
No.
Sit down.
It's his birthday.
So all right.
Let's end part one here.
And I wanted to end strong with something
I think we can all agree on.
Cast members of Batman 66.
Great.
Again, I don't know if you guys have heard any of these.
I might know some of this.
Let's see.
Yeah.
So there's a couple things.
There's a couple different things here that I like.
Some of which was not recorded,
but I think is maybe worth just playing little snippets of it.
But it's funny because they did this,
and I know I don't have everything,
but they definitely were like, oh, this is a big hit.
Big hit show.
Let's spin off singing careers for many of the people.
Some of the villains, I feel like, had musical theater careers.
Absolutely.
And I don't have all of it here.
For now, I've left out the Burgess Meredith stuff.
But I can't picture.
Yeah.
But it seems like they wanted to do singles
that would reference Batman in a way,
either really directly or a little bit directly.
OK.
And then on the B side, you'd give a more straightforward song
as sort of like a backdoor pilot to a career.
Yeah.
That's the way I read it.
But so like, for instance, Frank Gorshin, who played the Riddler,
who I feel like, you know, maybe doesn't even get his props
for defining like how villains act in a lot of ways.
Yeah.
Like is the guy who kind of starts out,
and everybody's sort of been doing an impression maybe
of how he played the Riddler on Batman.
And I am realizing.
Yeah, that's the most consistent in a way that like nobody,
you know, Jim Carrey just kind of like took it to space.
Yes.
So Frank Gorshin did this on a variety show,
but also they released it as an album.
And I don't know if you've seen this,
or I showed this to you years ago, Scott.
I don't know.
Jason, I probably showed this to you.
He had a song just called The Riddler.
Yeah.
This was not subtle.
They knew what this was.
And the cover is fantastic.
It's just him with the mask and the gloves and the outfit on.
Not the suit, the full like body suit.
It's like a Herb Albert album cover, but just, you know,
basic good portrait.
Riddle me this.
What do you call a sleeping bull?
Answer.
A bulldozer.
Riddle me this.
What, tell me, what, tell me, what's the difference
between an elephant and the fleas?
Gee, we would sure like to know the difference
between an elephant and a flea.
Well, an elephant can have fleas,
but a flea can't have elephants.
Hey, can you tell us the home of the Riddler?
It's the home of the Riddler.
The Riddler.
You know, it feels like Nancy Sinatra
or like some, any of the cooler versions.
I feel like I've walked into multiple of your apartment.
apartment, multiple apartments you lived in
and you're playing this, and we're like,
hey, can I play you some?
That feels right.
So yeah, that's fun.
And then there was a B-side that has nothing to do
with the Riddler.
So, and here I'll show you this cover.
This is Frank, casual.
He's got the cigarette.
He's got sort of the, whatever, sport jacket on.
Handsome, cool.
Handsome, cool guy.
Frank Ocean on that Sullivan show
when the Beatles were on, I believe, same episode.
Really?
And this is, yes, and it like,
let's see if we can sneak in a real song
and see if it works.
And I guess it didn't, it didn't work.
But I feel like it's a pretty good song.
["Ridin' by David Gaetz & Redd"]
Pretty legit.
Written by David Gaetz and Redd.
Oh.
["Ridin' by David Gaetz & Redd"]
This is not the Riddler song, this is Frank.
It's okay.
I'm gonna say it's great.
["Ridin' by David Gaetz & Redd"]
That's Scott Walker.
That's where you like, you put this on
and you're paired for a little make-up sesh.
Yeah.
And it's like going, okay, once then the music starts
and then you're deep into the vocals
and then she kind of starts getting a little shifty
and like, what is it?
And then looks over your shoulder,
goes past you like, sorry, do you have an album,
did you just put on an album by the Riddler?
Oh, sorry, I thought I turned the album cover around.
No, you had it on Riddler's side.
I had it on Riddler's side.
You're describing something that would have happened
to us in the early, early 20s.
Your idea of make-out music is Frank Gorshin.
First of all, I don't know who that is.
I saw the word Riddler, which I remember
has something to do with Batman.
You remember Batman the F-
Yeah, I do, I don't, I didn't know the name of the guy.
Jim Garry plays the character in the movie.
My favorite movie.
Jim Garry, yeah.
The Riddler song reminds me of one of my favorite
old TV clips, which is Tennessee Ernie Ford,
who sang the song 16 Tons.
He is on like a variety show and he's like,
and you know, I thought this new music
the kids are listening to, it's so great.
And I thought I'd just, you know,
gussy up a classic or whatever.
And he just does 16 Tons,
but there is like a go-go backing track
and go-go dancers, but he's just going,
oh, I was born one morning when the sun didn't shine.
Well, we'll listen to that on your birthday.
Yeah, oh, cool.
Tennessee Jason Sheridan.
Pickled up my accent, I walked to the mine.
Let's real brief, Burt Ward, who played Robin,
a song written and produced by Frank Zappa.
Have you heard this?
Yeah, this I have heard.
Frank Zappa before, right before.
And he's still like, you know,
he looked like a square still.
So he could, you know, he could fit in with the normies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But what a weird, weird crossover.
Weird crossover.
And it says Burt Ward on the cover
of the Boy Wonder Sessions,
says produced by Frank Zappa.
Oh, it's going to taste good.
Boy Wonder, I love you.
Oh, Boy Wonder, I love you.
Hi, kids, it's me, your pal, the Boy Wonder.
Taking this opportunity to catch up on my fan mail.
Even as a boy wonder,
it's really hard to read all the tons of mail I get.
Here is a happy letter from someone just about your age.
Dear cute, wonderful, fabulous, magnificent,
exquisite boy wonder.
A cold chill runs up my spine
every time I see you sock a villain.
And oh, how I cry when you're even scratching.
Please don't send me a mimeograph copy
of interesting facts about you.
I want your handwriting.
I have a whole wall of my room dedicated to you.
Oh, Boy Wonder, I'm making a gum wrapper chain
to symbolize my love for you.
It's going to be as long as I am tall.
I'm fighting for 10 inches in stocking feet.
As long as I am tall, hick.
Please come next Saturday and sleep for a week or two.
I will feed you breakfast and bed.
I will make your bed for you.
And I like you so much,
but I want you to spend the whole summer with me.
It's like misery.
This is a girl's life.
It's like Stan.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the original, so it's letters.
You got the indifference.
Yeah.
Dear Boy Wonder is the original Stan.
What's the fan club sketch on SNL about?
Brock Toon?
Oh, the Mr. Belvedere fan club.
I do want to cook Mr. Belvedere a nice meal.
I do not want to keep in a giant glass jar in my basin.
He keeps saying Boy Wonder, which is funny.
And so I feel like he clocked it.
That's a funny way to describe Robin.
I was thinking it's almost like they didn't.
This is like a Super Bowl big game thing.
Could he not say Robin?
That's also possible, yes,
because this does not feel as official as the other releases.
Yes.
Hi, kids.
He's doing it with this reel.
I don't know if Burt Ward had the ability to be sexy sultry
and maybe be worse if it was,
but then it all has that gee whiz.
I made a gum wrapper chain.
It's too pipsqueak, you know?
I think, I mean, I don't know how much range Burt had.
I don't want to say he didn't have range,
but I feel like almost he got Robin
because maybe he had one thing he was good at,
you know, very specific energy.
Holy smokes, Batman.
So I think Frank Wisely wrote to his strength here.
Did he write the song?
That's what it says.
Maybe I have bad information.
Because that's kind of, now if you think of it
as like a weird parody of fandom,
it's kind of brilliant.
If that's all like kind of subtly,
there's a subversiveness to it.
Yeah, for sure you think so.
It's like he's playing a joke on,
I'm going to trap you in this, Burt Ward.
He's the villain.
I've seen couples, right.
He's in the Zappa's lair.
I've seen a couple sources say he wrote it as well.
Whoa.
And I think, yeah, let me see if I can just double.
Yeah, I mean, there's a couple places that say he wrote it,
so I assume that's right.
Is it worth finishing the song in this case?
There's only a little left.
Yeah, let's do it.
I remember this whole thing being funny.
25 seconds left.
Okay, oh, yeah, great.
What was the last statement?
Does the letter like sign off?
What's the last thing said?
I like you so much that I want you to spend the whole summer.
Make your bed so tight you won't be able to leave it.
I hope you know this is a girl writing.
That's right.
That's what I was going for.
I hope you know this is a girl writing.
Yeah, it's a really.
That was written by Frank Zappa.
For Burt Ward.
It's really weird.
I mean, yeah, as a real speak singy.
Song.
Yeah, I would say so.
It's mostly dialogue.
It seems like kind of like a little prologue to Frank Zappa's weirder stuff to come.
I would say certainly this is not the weirdest thing Frank Zappa would make.
No.
That is like, I was not suspicious about it not being a girl writing until that line.
Right.
Right, which I guess is me.
Maybe it is, I don't know.
Now I think it is a 75-year-old man.
Not for sure.
Oh, I better say I'm a girl or else start to think.
I don't know what Frank was thinking necessarily when he was writing this, but it seems to be some sort of mediation.
Kind of good.
I feel like he took a job.
Either he could have just turned in something as boring as the Scott Baio music or he's like, I'm going to get one.
I'm going to do a little prank.
It is funny.
Like, not that the monkey's movie head is amazing or anything, but it is interesting.
I admittedly struggle.
I know it's interesting, but I struggle with that.
That's what I'm getting at.
Because like Jack Nicholson is in there and they're like, they like sneak some weird counterculture stuff in like some of the most popular pop entertainment for teenagers.
Yeah.
I watched that when I was stuck inside with COVID and I'm like, what the fuck is this?
It's insane.
Yeah.
It'd be cooler to like it.
I'd rather that I like it, but I have to be honest with myself.
The soundtrack is good though.
The music is good.
Yes.
I think.
Is there a song called Porpoise?
Porpoise.
Yeah.
And they, I saw them do that.
I saw Mike Nesma's last concert.
Oh yeah.
That seemed kind of grim.
And it seemed like it was at the time.
Yeah.
Okay.
Is there a flip side to that song?
I don't think.
In my head there's, he does, he does something called, it's like orange colored sky.
Well.
He does kind of a sincere, am I confusing that with something else?
Batman Sings Orange Colored Sky.
Oh!
That's what I'm thinking.
On Hollywood Palace.
Is that what you're thinking of?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Or did Burt do that too?
Do we know the flip side of.
Interesting.
Boy Wonder, I Love You.
Oh, he does.
You're right.
I remember there being kind of a bizarre, like.
Yes, here it is.
More of a standard song, but he can't handle it at all singing this.
Here it is.
Yes.
Well, that's so weird that Adam doesn't.
I was walking alone, like in my business, out of that orange colored sky.
That is really unpleasant.
Well, I was going to say orange colored sky.
Did they play this at a memorial for Tony Scott?
But that dude is so, it's kind of a trademark in some of his 80's movies.
You mean Tony Scott had an orange colored sky in a lot of his L.A. set.
We'll look into songs that were played at celebrities' funerals.
That'll be another, that'll be your episode.
Oh boy.
For your birthday.
So that's a good transition to Adam West doing this same song.
Whoa!
In 1966.
I didn't know that.
On Hollywood Palace in full costume.
Whoa, yes!
Here is your host, the famous star of television's most talked about show, Batman.
Adam West!
Great Adam West.
And it's a big number with the playing out to the Batman theme.
Shit!
People are sliding, ladies are sliding down poles as if they were headed to the Batcave.
Adam West couldn't fool off right now.
You know what I'm saying?
Have you seen any unusual looking people around here?
I was walking along, minding my business, went out, of an orange colored sky, swam,
bam, zow in the land, more evil crooks came by.
I was singing a song, raping in sunshine, acting as good as could be.
Crunch, plop, crack, and plop, they threw their curves at me.
Somebody yelled, hey Batman, what are you waiting for?
With a zap and a crack, I began my attack.
After that, they were lapped on the floor.
So I'm walking along, carefully watching, in case they could make another try.
Zonk, pow, here they are now, out of an orange colored sky.
Sitting in the audience, this is a real theater audience.
They're kind of quiet so you can see it.
I'm in a nice, them dressed nice, I'm in a suit and I'm watching this.
Christian Bale should have done this.
Get Pattinson, get Pattinson doing now, I feel like he's got a sensation.
Absolutely.
Yeah, so we're in the West territory here, we're in the home stretch of what we got.
Adam West had a single, I don't know if you've heard this.
Adam West, Miranda, with the B-side, you only see her.
And again, Batman is on the cover just in case you forgot who this guy was.
So you have to know that this is Batman as well as Adam West.
And this is called Miranda.
Will tonight be the night that Bruce reveals himself to the magnificent Miranda?
What?
Zonk, pow.
I've never met a girl like you before, Miranda.
Miranda.
And I'd do anything for you if you'd just ask.
Ask me to do anything for you, Miranda.
This is always meant to be a sweet, silly grandpa is what he ended up as.
He was that at this age.
Don't ask him to remove his mask.
It's against the code of heroes.
That cover looks like they're going to do a duet.
What are you doing here?
Bruce, come right away.
There's a job to be done.
A giant octopus has run amuck in Washington.
My Lord.
Boy, genius, this is one time you'll see.
Boy, genius.
Like a big game situation.
An octopus isn't the kind of thing that happened on Batman.
Right.
Miranda.
Or someone powerful as me.
So again, it feels like they're not going to say the name specifically to try to get around some sort of thing.
Copyright avoiding.
I love him so much.
Yes.
Oh, I mean, my love for Adam West grows daily to this day.
Yep.
He's also, other than maybe Michelangelo, I think I have the most Adam West toys of any character.
That's the most representations of a human in your hand.
At least 10, I think.
Wow.
Adam West.
And I don't have the family guy.
I was going to ask, is there a family guy?
Did they do a Simpsons one?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
That's my prize.
Yeah.
Wow.
That was NECA made that like 10 years ago.
Geez.
Okay.
Let's just go real quick beside.
And here's what caught my eye.
And I don't think I've ever told this story on the show before.
Adam West's non-Batman part of the single was called You Only See Her.
And it's arranged and conducted by Stu Phillips, a man whose 50th anniversary wedding party I videotaped and edited in his house next to him.
Stu Phillips wrote the theme to Knight Rider.
What?
Whoa.
He worked on The Monkeys, composed like The Monkeys.
And just you look at the IMDB, it's nuts of how much TV and stuff he did.
I was called one day and was like, do you want to videotape Stu Phillips's anniversary party?
Which was somewhere I think in Beverly Hills.
And so I like videotaped this with a family friend named Gary.
And then it was like, well, he needs somebody to edit it.
And I go, yeah, okay.
So I went to his house for a few weeks, which was sort of off.
You edited it there?
I edited it sitting next to him.
Whoa.
And in his house.
And he was very nice.
And I only say this, and I have a copy of his book and he signed it to me.
And I only say this just because I don't think he's right.
He kept telling me that I was the best editor he ever worked with.
And I was like, that cannot be true.
I didn't say it to him, but I was like, oh, thank you, whatever.
And he kept being like, you're so quick when you edit.
And I'm like, yeah, I guess.
Is this a digital thing?
Just by virtue, sheer virtue of digital?
I guess, yeah, right.
I was like, I wonder if he just hasn't worked with an editor forever.
He doesn't know what Final Cut can do.
And he wasn't like, he's still around, but he was an old guy.
But he wasn't like, I was like, oh, no, he's slipping away.
He was with it and everything.
But he kept saying, and I think he wrote it in the book.
I should go, actually, you know what?
I should have brought the book.
Shoot.
I'll do it.
And he will post what he wrote to me in the book.
I was like, one of the best editors I've ever worked with.
And then he said, my son-in-law works for the NFL network.
Do you want a job editing with the NFL network?
And I said, no.
I don't want to be an editor.
I quickly learned that, yes, you were very fast at editing video
because you usually didn't want to be doing it.
Oh, it's to get it off your plate.
I mean, I would go on to edit for a few more years here and there,
but I would try to figure out ways to get it done in four hours
and go over to UCB and go to Bird's and drink and see improv or do improv.
I remember leaving Culver City for my editing job, not done,
going to do an improv show at like 10 p.m. or 9 p.m.
and then driving, like that's in Hollywood, driving back to Culver City
and then finishing at like 4 a.m. or something.
Like the weird, stupid stuff that was not worth it.
So anyway, he, Stu, arranged and conducted this.
You Only See Her by Adam West.
Look at this guy. But yeah, look, his credits are nuts.
Yeah, geez.
Jason looks like he's being taken away.
The day is almost through.
What was the last time that you noticed that her eyes were blue?
It's so weird, that beat and then the snaps.
Yeah.
It's unsettling.
Have you forgotten?
It's kind of drunken.
Laurie, I was going to say, I have a bottle of Seagram 7 whiskey,
seven grand whiskey in it.
This was recorded, just the recorded line down.
Yeah.
Sounds like Barney.
I mean, that's the gist of it.
So yeah, they did kind of ballads for Gorshin and for West here.
Wow.
This formula that they kept, like, let's sneak in kind of a real one.
Right, right.
Wow.
You know, I do wish that I could give him more credit as just a great,
sincere singer.
Maybe that's not one of the top tools in his arsenal,
but I think he figured out what he was good at.
Yes.
Did it better than anybody.
Yeah. And you wanted Miranda is a little more jaunty and you don't have to
maybe be as good of a singer for that type of music.
I think that, look, I didn't even touch Shatner on this episode.
Oh, yeah.
He's made 20 plus albums and I feel like that's, it's somewhat well-worn territory.
I would want to really dig in and find the obscure ones there.
Some of it's because, I mean, of course I love Tambourine Man and like the,
I think it's going to be a long, long, but it's sort of done a little.
There's got to be more.
There's so much.
I mean, there's like Shatner claws and like there's new Christmas.
He's made multiple Christmas albums.
Has been the Ben Folds one, which I do really like.
I think there's a lot of good stuff on has been.
Yeah.
I remember when that came out.
And it's interesting.
And he, Ben, I feel like you figured out exactly what to do with him.
Yeah.
And I feel like nobody got to now, but nobody got to do that with an Adam West album.
Another one where it was before the full has been album and it was just that
where it was that would, there was like a monologue through it,
like what we've listened to now.
I forget the name of this, but there's that song.
There's a monologue of this like an awful man confessing how he ruined the relationship.
And they did it live on Conan.
Yes, yes.
And he said, it's kind of cool on the album, but live, he just does it full Shatner.
And he says, it builds his story.
And he says, you say, I can't commit.
You're right.
I can't commit to you.
To you.
And the audience laughs.
They laugh during a completely sincere, because what else are you supposed to do?
It's William Shatner yelling, I can't commit to you.
Yes, it is.
And I like that song.
Yeah.
It's really good.
And it's really like, but yes, he, I, there's a live on Len, a live on tonight show performance
of him doing common people with Joe Jackson.
It's like, it's kind of a cool version of it.
Yeah.
And he is definitely, he's not on time to do whatever common people do.
He is not.
He is off with the band and that performance and he's doing his best.
He's trying to catch up.
He's never really has the rhythm to perform live.
But yeah, that album, I think is cool.
And I've listened to it not long ago and I was like, this is still pretty good.
This is kind of interesting.
As obvious and referenced as it seems, the Shatner rocket man is, I feel like once a
year I go back and like, I just can't believe it's real.
I can't believe it's so, how did they get, how did they possibly land on, then he's going
to split into three and the third is going to be a party guy with a loose tie.
It's so good.
Go to be a long, long time.
It's, it's bonkers.
It's so good.
And yeah.
And that one almost, yeah.
When you watch it, you go, oh, this holds a better even than sort of like people joking
about it or the hacky Shatner impressions.
Can you imagine the era where like there wasn't YouTube and you just had to know someone with
a tape of the sci-fi award show to have seen that?
Yeah.
A big tape or something.
That's a TV station.
Yeah.
And by the way, he didn't even put in Nimoy.
There's multiple Nimoy albums.
Yeah.
Is that, no, Shatner is transformed man, right?
What Nimoy is Nimoy does.
Bilbo Baggins.
Oh, right.
Bilbo.
And if I had a hammer.
If I had a hammer.
I do have a hammer.
The hammer of justice.
He also does one of the best Rainey Newman songs on a different album that I didn't know
existed until last night.
I think it's going to rain today, which is one of the saddest songs ever written.
And his version is not as sad, but it's all right.
We didn't even touch on that.
I want to say something in general.
Yeah.
I think that when that era, like records, records are new and we just need shit on records.
Fill them up.
It can be crazy.
It could be novelty.
It could be weird.
There's a reason why I love all that.
And then I love the VHS era where like, doesn't matter.
Any crap can be on VHS.
We're still every day finding new wonders of the VHS era.
I know.
And I think it's horrible that the streaming era is like infinite and should provide endless
funny crap.
And instead it's all bore.
It's like, and we're like seeing now, now it's scaling back and it's only going to become
more predictable and more safe.
I wish that streaming at any of the vigor of crazy old record era or crazy old VHS era.
That's a great, great point.
And the closest like I can even find to stuff like that now is just niche YouTube.
That's really where it lives.
But it's the bummer is you get like, you can't, people can't make money doing it.
You just have to be like, I sort of, I guess people make money on YouTube, but like, but
I missed it.
Like Leonard Nimoy, you're making an album.
Why I don't sing.
Who cares?
I don't know.
Or get Zappa in there.
Like these things, these like made at gunpoint albums that we're still just picking apart
for decades.
You get your renters.
You do get here and there.
Just requires the initiative of somebody to anyone.
All of us could make an album.
We can make Jason sings the old ones tomorrow.
Should we make it tomorrow?
Yes.
You got plans tomorrow?
Tomorrow we're doing it.
So yeah, we have plumber coming into handyman.
All right.
Well, let's write a song about that.
Yeah.
You can use the plumber of the banging of the wrenches as the percussion.
We can do it.
Plumber woes.
Yeah.
I just, I like with Adam West.
I just, I do.
I'm just regret.
I wished Shatner treatment got put on West more.
I don't think West fully got is enough chances like Shatner did and Shatner's made a ton
of crap, but is in enough stuff that I think people really like.
And it's got really got to show that he's funny and interesting on multiple shows and
movies.
And Adam did not get the chance, which bumps me out though.
There's a timing.
There's a lot out there.
And you got to give it, you know, honestly, family guy at this point, it became like such
a big part of the lineage.
Really funny.
That rest.
Yes.
I've just been like, he didn't get his Boston legal where he got to be like a mainstream
star.
They sure.
Yeah.
Maybe he was never meant to be like, and now a serious actor at him.
Cause I love everything he did.
I love like became the, like the post look well.
Deploying of him is so brilliant.
Yeah.
Why?
I just want more.
That's all I'm saying.
Yes.
I just wanted more.
Yeah.
And then Shatner, some might argue too much.
They got him too much.
Yes.
Yeah.
And he's still going.
God bless him.
Yeah.
But anyway, happy whatever birthday to me.
Who knows?
Whatever age I am.
Who's keeping track?
Who can track?
I don't know.
29 yet again.
29.
That's what I'll call myself.
And then to play us out.
Can I throw out something before you play us out?
Please.
I will wish you a sincere happy birthday as well.
Thanks for taking a very fun birthday shot.
But because it, look, it might be a big one, it might be a big birthday.
It might be.
Yeah.
And I don't think that we should celebrate with only this.
And this is, I've been saying this for a while and we aren't ready to do this yet, but I
just want to like, there's a shot I want to call on your behalf.
Something I've been wanting to do.
We'll do this in Club 3 as soon as we can.
There's other Club 3 plans.
Right.
But, you know, I'll say you survived podcast The Ride, Mike's birthday shot.
Thanks for subscribing.
And if you want to go all the way to the VIP tier, Club 3, basically, if you don't know,
audience picks the topics.
There's these polls.
And very frequently, something is suggested that becomes Mike's pick for the poll that
month.
This always has a very long title.
It usually has like, the one that's in my head is like, Legends of the Superheroes Roast,
1978.
Adam West and Ed McMahon.
And there's so many details you can't even put them all in the poll.
Right.
What is this?
So at some point when we feel like we're free and clear to do it, but at some point this
year, I'm calling the shot of the Club 3 poll where all of the Mike last place finishers
go up against each other and they finally, one will finally get their day in the sun.
So that's coming.
It won't necessarily be next month, but there's the list.
It says I've just enjoyed how much like, well, the length of that and the year of it, it
can only be Mike.
HR Puff and Stuff and Jabberjaw and Rip Taylor and Shields but not Yarnell.
Don Knotts.
Yep, yep, yep.
Don Knotts, yeah.
That'd be one of those.
There was a Don Knotts one in there.
So we will set that up on your behalf in the next couple months.
But anyway, now to play us out.
So yeah, to play us out and the reason I'm playing it out is just because it's the same
song that Martin sings at the end of the pool episode on The Simpsons.
Oh, what a stirring moment.
Adam West singing.
Really?
Summer Wind.
Oh.
Summer wind came blowing in from across the sea.
He's not dressed as Batman.
And he's not naked like Martin.
Does he have a little abscott on?
What was that shadow?
Of course.
Handsome man.
All summer long we sang a song and then we strode the golden sands.
I feel like he sounds better on this.
Yeah, this is good.
Two sweethearts and a summer wind.
Hell yeah, King.
Like painted kites, the days and nights they went flying by.
Any of our dads made an album.
The world was new, beneath a blue umbrella sky.
And softer than a piper man, one day it called to you.
I lost you, I lost you to the summer wind.
It really makes you reflect about life and whatever birthday it is you're celebrating.
I know.
I'm feeling wistful.
He's probably 40 years old.
Still the days, the lonely days, they go on and on.
And guess who sighs?
Yeah, I like it.
Okay.
Through nights that never end.
A little too modern for you.
I think he's having a lot of fun.
And I mean that sincerely.
That's not as fun.
The summer wind.
I'm sure he played the Batman interstitial music.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So good.
I'm back to business.
Hello.
Oh, it's you.
It's the Riddler again.
You want to tell about the next Hollywood Palace show, Riddler?
The hostess will be Miss America?
Oh, not Miss America, Mess America.
Well, everyone knows who Mess America is.
The hilarious Phyllis Diller.
Next week at this time, ABC will present one of the big specials of the season, Lerner and Lowe's Brigadoon.
And two weeks from tonight, the Hollywood Palace with Phyllis Diller.
You know, I've met some wonderful people here tonight, including you.
Thank you.
Good night.