Forever!
Dog!
Warning!
The following podcasts may contain
Mickey's Hand Sparks,
Teacher Angering Green Ink,
favorite Mark Twain deck positions,
Boat Ghosts,
and a thrilling look at Disney's water-based
spectacular, Fantasmic.
You'll definitely be humming the theme
for the rest of the day.
It's Podcast The Ride!
Music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
a podcast that is once again
about theme parks after a month-long
diversion into a different topic,
food poisoning. I'm Scott Gardner,
joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hi, I just narrowly avoided
to the measles outbreak,
Bucatipepo.
Oh, Bucatipepo did, yeah.
Bethy said me this,
Bucatipepo, a place where
people may have been exposed
to measles at the end of March.
Now I assume from that that we're still
living in the alternate universe
in which it is Bucatipepo.
Yes, that seems like
that's what we are doing.
Okay, so canonically from this point on,
Mike Carlson, hi. I'm here and I was also
sent a list of city walk places
that might have been the epicenter
of a measles outbreak.
Okay, I don't know anything about this.
No, I've missed this entirely.
If you can imagine that I'm not exactly staying up on
city walk news now. We should keep doing
more city walk, but I think we have to do this
because there was a press release
April 13th, 2024,
Public Health confirms measles case
in Los Angeles County health officials
identify locations for possible measles exposure.
And if you go down the list,
Bucatipepo,
if we're playing
Bucatipepo in a different universe,
Cletus' Chicken Shack is on the list.
Yeah, Universal Studios is also.
Lardlad Donuts and
EC Food Truck is on the list.
Sheraton Gateway
Hotel is on the list.
Oh no, the hotels too.
So yes, I was sent this yesterday
as well.
And so yeah, city walk, we just,
I think narrowly avoided
a measles outbreak. Wow, we got out just in time.
My god. Yeah.
Especially because the two of you
would have been like, oh it was probably from somewhere.
Probably both of our cases of
measles. Surely it can't have been city walk.
Yeah, well we wouldn't have blamed city walk if we
caught the measles in our
30s and 40s. If it had started up there,
then it must have flown down
from the famously windy food court
all the way down to the bottom of the hill
and we caught it there.
The conditions can't have been such up there.
Unless they were like ancient
measles unlocked from some old, from like
a Wampoppers or something, from the old
restaurant outside city walk. I mean it's possible.
Oh yeah, they were doing construction on this
new roller coaster. They unearthed
some meat. Oh, and they unearthed a bunch of meat?
A 30 year old strain of measles that was
in the ground. A group of
early California settlers.
Like a Donner family type group.
Right. A group that succumbed to the
measles on the Cahuenga Hills.
Right. And now it's been this living
in amber, some sort of amber casing
like Jurassic Park.
And then yes, as they were, the bulldozers
were just knocking down parts of the hill.
The amber was broken.
And measles were unleashed on the Buca
de Beppo. Pepo.
Was it on purpose
or not, Jason?
No, I just got too excited about
I have news about a measles
outbreak. And I said Pepo
so many times during the series.
After that entire thing, you still haven't figured it out.
You know what? I hope it never
changes. Ain't I a stinker?
You just keep doing you, Jason.
Well yeah, I didn't mean
to do a whole reprisal. This is important
news. And I'd like to thank my
friends for not texting me
about this. For knowing that I was
emotionally done. And we didn't text you about
it either. Everyone made the correct
calculation. Because while that was
a lot of fun, I'm
done. I'd say that I'm done.
And I'm excited to be veering back this way.
That said, listeners, this is the
first main feed since the City Walk
Orlando Saga. Thank you for all the kind
words about that. For the support of that.
I did have a blast. And I would
like to just make sure at
the top here to dedicate this and every
episode from now on to our friend
Stephen Kepner. Just the podcast
from this point on. I agree.
Now Mr. Kepner,
in his infinite wisdom,
during the saga in one of the final
episodes, he asked us
is this still a theme park podcast?
And I think
this episode we will attempt
to answer that question
to be yes. Yes.
Measles Diversion or no.
That's part of it though. We're still
on topic. Yes. Well, yeah, of
course. If it came from the
Bumblebee food truck itself,
then Cletus the Chicken Jack is in the theme park.
Cletus the Chicken Jack is in the theme park.
Emphatically, yes is what I'm saying
to the question. And that's why I
am covered in measles. Oh,
no. All right. Well, it's, you know,
if it's a thing at theme parks, then
it is our obligation to try it.
So let's try, let's find out what having
theme park specific measles is like.
Jason, I thank you for bringing it here today.
Absolutely. It's time. We're doing the
old chicken pox party.
Universal's
new tagline is get infected
by the movies.
And that's what
we're doing. That ties together because
there are, there is an unfortunate
tagline involved in today's
topic. Yeah, there is.
All right. Well, why don't we check in with
the, oh, wait, that's not how it works
anymore. We have to say it
ourselves. Today's topic,
phantasmic. And we,
asking ourselves, where do
we go from here? A big
question post saga. We landed
at this. We landed at, you know, wanted
to do something primary theme
parky Disney, which got no love
for a month. And they've got to be hurting
and not getting the love from us, the
boys. So we're back to
Disneyland. We're back to a big theme parky
thing, something that's
pretty epic, historic,
timeless that
we hope, I mean, it's on
hiatus now, but we hope that it
never leaves the park otherwise.
And that
I assume for all the things
that have been embattled in the recent past that
we've talked about, I'm going to take a guess here
and say that the three of us are all very passionate
about phantasmic.
If not passionate, then we like it.
I was going to say I like it. I don't know where
my, when we discuss my passion,
when we discuss my passions,
which we do often on this show,
I don't know that it's, yeah, passion, but I do,
I like it. I really like it. Yeah, well, I backed up.
I didn't mean to overdo it. No, it's okay.
Passion is a big word. Passion you say for your love,
you give that to your love, but not necessarily
But you've, you've exposed now that you're
passionate for phantasmic, which I appreciate it.
Okay. I don't know if that's a
correct calculation, but
I do, I do really love it.
Um, you know,
I haven't, I haven't gone to see it
in a long time. So that's why I think I'd be
misbilling it, calling
myself passionate about it. Yeah.
But you know what I associate it with
is growing up here and going
to Disneyland as my home park more
than you guys. I obviously loved
Disneyland every time that I went
and I must have been three or four times before
phantasmic, but there was something
about when this kicked in,
like, wow, we are cooking
now. In 1992, May
1992, this thing premieres
and we're still
in Disney decade era. It's
before they decided there is no Disney
decade. It was right after the debut
of Disneyland Paris,
if you're at Disneyland, which killed
the ambition of everything for a while. So
this was still very much
in ambition era.
Um, you know, we're getting to an eight.
I must have seen it for the first time when I was
seven years old. And
now I'm getting to stay
up late. Now it's not these quick
little kid pop-ins, which now
you've done, Mike, I think since the last
record. Uh, or
I don't remember when you did it,
but we'll get into that at some point. Sure.
Your child's first Disneyland happened.
But you know, you do these things a little bit
low ambition. You get out of there
early. You get them to bed at a fairly regular
time. Uh, and that's the kind of Disneyland
I was doing. And now
there's a big nighttime spectacular.
I'm old enough to stay up
for it. Every new thing
they add is killer.
Like, what did this, what did this come
after? Was it post Toontown
or was it on the way to, I think
it's post. I think it's on the way. It's
post Star Tours, definitely. Yeah, yeah,
for sure. And on the way to Toontown,
on the way to Indiana Jones,
and you just feel like they're in a streak.
They're in an incredible streak that this
thing, uh, keeps up
and just adds something. They, I guess
Splash Mountain is one that I'm missing.
Not that I've done it by that point.
Um, but what a killer time.
Between Splash Mountain and Indiana Jones
and Toontown,
all killers in this era,
and they add something that's not just
some nighttime show. It's a show
that expands the scope
of what a nighttime show can be,
the ambition, technology
you've never seen before that is now
a part of any
nighttime show
worth its, uh, worth its salt.
Do you, do you have
a memory of, like, just, I, just the idea
that they're using for Disneyland
the, like, the rivers
and, like, just that whole
area now is a stage for a crazy
show. To me, I feel like as a kid, if I was like
they didn't have a show there before and now
there's a show happening in what used to
just be, like, a river way, or
a river and just, like, Tom Sawyer Island.
Absolutely. Like, that must have been pretty
crazy to be like, holy shit, you can do
a show anywhere? Anywhere could be a show.
Anywhere, yeah, you don't know,
well, and that's, and that's before, you know,
the, the, the jammeters. Sure.
That's before now, even with, oh,
that's just the custodians going by, wait a
minute, hang on, they're banging on, now
really a show can be anywhere. Now we're used
to the idea. Yeah, absolutely. It
adds to, it, it adds to the magic
that, like, they didn't add new
space, they didn't buy new property
and yet they opened up a
space where a lot of magic can happen
and I think it adds to the magic
day to day at the park, where, yeah, you're looking
at, like, during the day, that's some
rusty old shack, but at night
it explodes with Mickey's
imagination. Yeah. And the boats,
the Mark Twain. Yeah, I was going to say,
adding on to that, it uses both
boats. Right, and the day, Mark Twain
is a shitty, boring old boat.
Yeah, just a real
creeker, just a seasickness
machine. Yeah, but then at night
that's when it really shines, that's
when I like it. During the day, get the hell
out of here, I wish it would sink. You gave me a ride
here and now you have to get me a ride home and I'm
going to be bawling.
In the car?
Just sobbing
in Mike's car.
Why did you say that? I kept it together during
the record. I kept it together, I'm a
professional.
Now that it's you and me,
I want you to see my hurt.
I've never asked you to edit comments
out of a show before.
That's a lie. You've insulted
me hundreds of times
and I've never asked, but this one time
you've gone too far, sir. Any
MAGA thing you want to say, that's fine,
feel free, but you
insult my boat. Don't insult my boat,
sir. That's right, Mike, we cut a lot of
Mike's MAGA rants.
That's right.
They all go three hours and we cut an hour
ten every time. Yeah, I take a little
nap touring them.
Look, this is one of my criticisms
of Fantastic,
is, I love a peaceful
nighttime Mark Twain ride.
Ooh,
interesting. And it's taking that away
from you. Me and the three little pigs,
they get to ride nighttime Mark Twain,
but not Jason.
Yeah, Buzz Lightyear
gets to go on it. He's from space.
He shouldn't even be in an old timey
steamboat. That doesn't make sense.
He's hanging out
at infinity and beyond
and I can't even ride the
little boat in the little rivers
of America. He has everything he could ever dream
of. He has everything. This is like, what are you
being jealous of, Buzz? I don't want to be controversial
here, but right away, let me ask a question,
Jason. If,
okay, how many, Fantasmic doesn't run every night,
but would you prefer Fantasmic
to go away so you always have the option
to ride the Mark Twain?
No, I don't think I would
go that far. Okay, but how far
would you go?
I don't mind being close for a year
plus.
Has the year, wait here,
continue your line of questioning. I was just going to say, once a
week, how many times do you think would be acceptable
for Fantasmic to run? Oh, I think
half and a half would be fair.
Well, what gets the four days, though?
What gets the three? What gets the four?
Mark Twain gets four days.
Okay, would you prefer weekends
for the Mark Twain or weekends
for the Mark Twain? This is a custody battle now.
I think a lot of, during
slower times, I think Fantasmic
mostly runs
Friday through Sunday. I would think
because it's a high capacity show and
that's when more people are there. It might want it that
way. They probably want to do less
shows. They like it. They actually like it.
They like the breaks to recharge
and maybe some of them, maybe the people who work so hard
on Fantasmic can take a break,
take a little moonlight boat ride
as long as they don't get in Jason's way.
Do you have a spot on there
if you're doing it late? Do you want to be on top?
Are you a top or a bottom?
Mark Twain wise?
Definitely tops. I think second or
third. At least second
if not third level
than Mark Twain.
Now,
Fantasmic going down
for a year and we are still, and actually, you know
we picked this topic, didn't even realize
that we are, this week
is a year since
the fire which took down
the dragon that factors
that's the main part of the climax
of the show. I mean, well, Jason would call the climax
the boat going by. Unless
it makes you mad. Unless it ends
the boat goes by and
you're just in a jealous rage.
They usually have to pry me off the fence.
Yeah, because I'm like, okay, if I really
leap
I can get on there.
And you come equipped with, you bring
your own little Cogsworth costume
so that you can maybe blend in as one of the characters.
Just bring streamers
dress up like a little clock and then maybe
they'll let you just be on it. Yeah, I'm multitasking.
I'm climbing the fence.
I'm putting my Cogsworth outfit on.
It's like that scene in The Fugitive where Harrison
Ford's in the St. Patrick's Day parade
and he kind of slips into a costume and he goes right
on. So Jason puts the Cogsworth hat on
and slips right on the Mark Twain
finale. Or like the Joker being
in the group of all the policemen
at the funeral.
But you're not after any Joker activity.
You just want a nice little boat ride. Anyway,
I was saying
this week is a year since
The Dragon fell, thus creating
a year of No
Fantasmic. Do we know, has
that opened up more nighttime
Mark Twain abilities? Or do they
stop running that at a certain point?
I don't know specifically
the schedule of the Mark Twain. I am sure
that on certain nights, if not all
nights, they run Mark Twain later.
But I could be wrong. I don't know
actually. This is something I should have looked into.
But I didn't even think about what
would happen to Jason's beloved Mark Twain.
And I believe Fantasmic coming
back at the end of May.
Yes, for sure. So we are
about to break the
hiatus and see
what they have cooked up
in the meantime. And we'll talk about
some of what the show was before
before we get into the changes.
But here's something that I didn't realize.
I thought, show coming
back, so that means we get Dragon
Mach 3. We get to the
third Fantasmic Dragon.
But now I'm looking into it.
It's coming back. No Dragon. Didn't
realize that. Yeah.
I don't know. I don't know.
This is like a primary facet
of it, of the billboards, of any
imagery of it that there's ever been over
these many decades. This is one of
those things where I start to get
conspiratorial. I start to get
like conspiracy brain.
Where I go, well what is the...
Did they set the dragon on fire?
For insurance money?
We are back to one of the
things, this ranking that we kind of
stopped doing, the burning things down for insurance
money. This is, yeah, it could be a
possible version of that.
Why wouldn't it be back? Why wouldn't they just build a new one?
It's pretty convenient that that's something
they don't want to bring back.
Maybe they don't want to bring it back because it almost
shot a bunch of flames into people.
Well, I'm just saying though, it was
spectacular, and you just make the flame safer
somehow. I don't know.
But the conspiracy brain,
here's where, I think the conspiracy
brain gets into dangerous territory
when you start
accusing the company of
like, well you realize if we
light it on fire on purpose, it could shoot
jets of flame from its mouth,
and if it's not angled just right,
it might go into the crowd. And you're saying
like, I don't know if it was Eiger or
Chapek at that point, but somebody's like,
maybe. And then just turns and leaves
the room. Well, it'll save us a hundred thousand
dollars.
It would only have torched
a couple of human souls. It would have only put the cost on top
of that. I guess it would have torched Mickey, not
the audience, because it's pretty far away from the audience.
I suppose it could have shot across
the rivers. It is
probably the most convenient place
where something's going to burst
into flames at
Disneyland. Because it's far
away from the audience. Yeah, it's far away from everyone.
Most performers
and stagehands even
are pretty far away from it.
Except for that Mickey. Thank God.
This is another story
entirely, if anything happens
to Mickey that night. Maybe
we don't cover it as a topic. I think
probably we don't cover it as a topic.
But just the
tenor of Disneyland changes forever
if a dragon torches Mickey
one night. I think that's correct. And maybe
I don't say it's a conspiracy theory if that happened
either. But
it is funny when this happens
because it's like the King Kong thing. Where it's
like, oh yeah, King Kong burned up.
And we have a new King Kong thing ready.
And you're like, well, what's the chances?
Sometimes the stuff lines up. Now, I think
oftentimes when something breaks,
everybody reassesses it. And
whatever their feeling about it was before,
now it's just a good excuse
to change it up.
So I watched a couple
of videos
of this show.
One from 2023,
4K,
crystal clear. And one from
1992, like
converted high
millimeter film.
Which was still pretty good
quality for that
format. And
it is funny that
the dragon caught on
fire in 2023.
Because 1992,
lots of
the interesting thing was seeing
how many beats of the show are already
in place. A lot of big moments of the
show are in place. The majority of it.
To some extent. But the
thing that was surprising to me
is how much the original version of
the show relied on
sparks. Sparks and fireworks
shooting out of things.
And sparklers. And that
did not cause the slightly
goofier looking dragon
to catch on fire. Instead of
the art, you know,
redone multiple times dragon
is the thing that exploded.
I mean, it did.
I think it was, you'd have to put it
in the sparks and fireworks category.
What ultimately did it. Because it wasn't
the flame breathing. It was the
the beat that did it, I think, was when
fireworks go off
in his brain.
And
which does always happen.
That does happen every night.
Which is crazy. They do
light it on fire from
the top, essentially.
And it seems like that's the one that
did it in. Yeah.
I mean, I remember
the night it happened,
within minutes, there
were multiple angles of it online.
People live streaming
or people who happened to be there
and got their phones out.
You could see it.
And it was badass.
Admittedly, one of the most badass
things Dizzy had done, and they didn't
need to. It looked awesome.
Admittedly, and again
we could say it, because nobody got hurt.
And you know, it's not like
if the trees had caught on
fire, if the island was torched.
But the fact that it was just a
watching a dragon burn up, it was admittedly
it's very compelling.
It's very cool. Yeah.
What happens if, say,
no one was on the Mark Twain, but the Mark Twain just
went up in flames, and there's a flaming
Mark Twain going around the
Rivers of America, as if it's on
a river to hell.
Well, I think
I think if Buzz Lightyear
is burning up, that'd be less funny.
No, I said empty. Yeah, empty boat.
If it's empty,
I mean, that
would also be a sight to behold.
It would, yeah. But I think you would have to rebuild
it. Would they rebuild
it, though? I bet they wouldn't.
For history's sake. I don't know.
You'd have to rebuild it by hand, I think.
Oh, jeez.
Or you would, if the boat was
on fire, you'd be like, take me, take me to hell,
Mark, and try to swim
across onto it. Grand Circle Tour to
hell. This is the way I want to go,
you said. Look, it's been
in my will. I wrote this
14 years ago.
Light the Mark Twain on
fire with me in it. And take me to hell.
It's in
your will that it be hell.
If this part of it, if anybody ever sees
the will who can make that decision,
just let you know. Because Jason
blazes up blunts, and where are you
going to get to do that? Hell.
Plenty of fire, plenty of sinful
weed smokers down there.
Oh, okay. Yeah, weed is the devil's
drug. Most people in hell are
there from even just one marijuana
used. From singular possession
and usage?
If you've been near it, actually,
if you've been near it and you didn't report it to the
authorities immediately, that's hell for you.
Listeners, you can do your own
reflection on it by my rules if you're
going to hell or not. Like most
are. Although I don't know
with this audience. I'm not sure.
I don't know either. Have you seen, do you know
what weed looks like? If so, hell.
No, this is making people uncomfortable listening
to anything. I'm sorry. We apologize.
We're going to leave it in, though.
Well, it looks slightly like Sour Patch
Kids or Reese's Peanut Butter Cups.
It's what everyone's concerned about.
Sour Patch Kids? What? The weed
looks like Sour Patch Kids? I mean, no, I mean
like edible packaging. That's very
clearly like a ripoff.
Oh, you're saying that? Well, this is something that Scott
and I don't even know that there's just constant
ripoff packaging or
there's constant ripoff packaging.
These are the things. You've got to give us the context
here. We aren't always extorting out.
This is taking you right down to Satan's
Chamber, Jason, knowing all
this. That's such an evil
Sour Patch Kids have been tainted? That's a
pure thing from my childhood. They're kids.
Right. Get kids off of drugs.
Oh, my God. You're going to sit at his right hand.
Low-nose accent is at his left hand.
If the
word shows are any indication. The three of you
will be unstoppable. Yeah. You'll
take over Earth.
Little J-Sex.
Okay, so let's get into some
basics about this thing. May
13th, 1992.
A year ago,
went away, but on and off.
It's been going for a long
time.
History of it. They
were using the rivers
and the space across the river
for shows.
There is somebody named Barnett Richie
who was named a Disney legend last
year, and she put on
a lot of the nighttime entertainment
that existed before this thing.
There's a show called Kids of the
Kingdom. She was one of
the Kids of the Kingdom. I'm not
prepared with a lot of information about Kids
of the Kingdom. Either
that will be an episode or we start looking into
it, and that's the blandest thing you've ever
heard of and we don't do it. I don't
know. Research
remains to be done. It sounds good, though.
It sounds like a good episode. It sounds up Mike
Sally, for sure.
We're back to wholesome territory. Yeah, yeah.
It just sounds nice. That's all
it is. I'm sure it was.
There was also something called the
Rolling River Review, where
jazz bands went by. I think for a long time
jazz bands played on the
Tom Sawyer Island rafts.
So they were utilizing this area
for nighttime entertainment a decent amount.
I think at grad nights, I think they had bands
play over there. I remember reading forever ago
that Cheap Trick played across
the rivers of America. That sounds
fucking cool. But
at some point, it's like...
Are Cheap Trick replacing the dragon permanently?
I hope so.
I don't know how wise of an investment that is
for the future. I'm not sure their age
is in health, but
just one summer at Cheap Trick
and I'm happy.
On fire-based fireworks,
rock and roll fireworks, that's what I say.
And most importantly,
over 60-year-old guys
playing rock and roll.
It would have to be. Those are the only
people who play rock and roll.
They're trying to flip a coin. Are they going to
play Tom Sawyer Island or are they going to
play The Sphere in Las Vegas?
That's
probably where The Sphere is heading,
I would imagine, given the recent bookings.
So anyways,
but we can't just keep
booking bands
who demand salaries
and run out the door.
There's got to be something permanent
that we can place here and something that uses
a little more imagineering magic.
So they start planning, oh wait,
and on top of that, Barnett
Ricci takes a trip to France
and she discovers that there is a French company
that does something quite incredible,
which is mist screens,
water screens that allow
you to project visual images
onto them. They have that
copyright.
Disney, as in
great Walt tradition, Disney sees something
and says, us too.
Now
this is, in terms of
fundamentals of Fantasmic,
this blew my mind
when I was seven years old. This is so cool
and now we almost take it for granted. There's a lot
of things of this nature
and this is a part of a lot of
Disney nighttime water shows,
but this was the first.
So cool. I strongly remember
being up close
and not even that up close and you still get the
mist on you, even if you don't stake out
those front row positions.
Love this.
Haven't done it in a long time, but as I talk about it
now I'm kind of craving that screen mist.
Screen mist is so interesting
because the term now
makes me go, uh oh,
in 2024, because there was
a lot of talk of the Tiana ride coming out.
Now they've just released videos of all
these robots and the robots look spectacular.
So perhaps any of my fears
are stupid or whatever. They look
amazing. But they were mentioning
a lot of projections on mist
a few months ago or a year or two ago
and I was like, uh oh,
I don't like the sound of that. But I
remember when
projecting on mist was new, because
we had it at our local indoor
swimming pool
slash mild water park
where I grew up. And I've said this before,
there was a hologram
projected on some mist as we
went down a water slide.
This wasn't your choice for
the parks that made us, this was something different?
Uh, it was not my choice.
This was just a low,
for some reason, like the
park district had some money, so they upgraded a
pool when I was in like fifth grade into an
indoor pool that was, like,
you could go year round. And for whatever
reason, they had a water slide that had a mist
and, like, had a projection of some
kind on it. I don't even remember what the projection
was, but it was all the talk
of, like, oh my god, you
could, like, place something on, like,
water and mist. Mike, what you're describing
is the greatest use of taxpayer
money I've ever heard of. Oh, it's
a ridiculous, I don't know why.
What was the point of it? It probably
cost a million dollars at the time.
To cheer up all the kids in
town. We never think about morale
when we make our budget decisions.
You don't get to go to the public pool generally
in the Midwest in the middle of winter,
but going to now branded
Waterworks, it's of course called
Waterworks, and I believe it still is,
they spent money on
some sort of mist projection. What was on
the mist? I'm telling you, I don't remember.
But we were excited about
it nonetheless. It didn't look very
good as my memory, but you'd
kind of, like, try to make it out of what it was
as you were going through it. And it
was not, again, it was nothing spectacular, but
for whatever reason, they sold the Schomburg
Park District on this, and
we got to experience, that's the first time I
ever saw it, and it was cool,
even though I can't remember what the projection
was. So you're,
when you finally then find out about
Fantasmic, you're like, oh, so they're doing
like a Waterworks thing. Right, it's basically, they ripped us off
of Waterworks. The Schomburg Park District
did this first, as far as I know. This
is just Disneyland copying Schomburg
as usual.
It might have. You grew up
in a wild experimental town.
Yes, of course. Rainforest
Cafe, Mars 2112,
Waterworks, the Little
Caesars, but the play area,
a big play area.
I am, look, I'm mildly
jealous whenever this list
comes up. I know, and I didn't realize
how good I had it. Why'd you move?
I moved back.
Alright, I will.
All that stuff is gone, except for Waterworks,
but I'll move back. You're right.
Maybe there'll be a new restaurant coming to Woodfield soon.
Hopefully.
For the legacy fans.
Anyway, they,
I never heard any of this history.
This was all news to me that there were premises for what this
would be before Fantasmic.
The first pitch was something called
River Haunt, and they did a whole
bunch of imagery of this that
you can look up. River Haunt
was supposed to combine
the mythologies of haunted
mansion and Pirates of the Caribbean
nearby this spot, the
Rivers of America, so it makes sense.
It's just artwork,
so you can't exactly make heads
or tails of the plot, but it's a bunch
of ghosts and a bunch of pirates, and
maybe ghost pirates, and maybe
a big leota. Sounds
kind of good. Do you think we missed out?
Should it have been River Haunt?
I think the name is bad.
Sure, but the concept
is cool. They might have, maybe
they would have gotten it there. They might have
buffed that name. So I don't know. If they said
Fantasmic's going away and we have a new version
of River Haunt, maybe
I'm in. I don't know.
There's that scary,
remember they repurposed, was it in,
it was in Disneyland Paris, they repurposed
the Mark Twain as a big scary boat.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
Let me see if I can find it.
But it looked crazy, and I'm like,
oh, that looks really cool.
Hold on, let me find it.
I mean, maybe the issue with that show is they're kind of
limiting themselves by making it
a fully scary show.
Now it does not attract the broad
Disneyland audience.
For example, me, I would have heard
those words and been out and never
seen River Haunt until I turned 21.
Yeah, oh, this is,
okay, it's the thing that was
tugging the Mark Twain. It's this
big scary ghost.
Oh, I've seen that before.
Okay, weird hooded creature with no
face. Like a giant tugging
the Mark Twain, like a tugboat,
not tugging it, like, you know what I'm saying?
Like Ghosts of Christmas
Yet to Come, Time Grim Reaper.
It is the
ball and chain that's been put on this
creature. His destiny in life
is to tug this boat away. Now if Jason
that was his destiny, there'd be a big
smile on this guy's face. Oh yeah,
the hoodies keep the sun out of my eyes.
And the smile,
the big smile would be reflecting
and hitting people in the eye because
the big smile constantly.
But yeah, something like this.
I don't know. Obviously, Fantasmic
definitely a crowd pleaser.
So probably the better choice.
But yeah, they got to something
that is, it's only scary at times.
There's some scary parts of Fantasmic. Maybe like
a scary Fantasmic around Halloween time.
That would be awesome. Sure.
Something like this. It would be awesome. The only
problem with like entertainment
that could potentially scare
you, there are active walkways
that people are walking on.
So there's suddenly a jump scare.
Maybe not.
People would be jumping into each other's arms constantly
like in an old cartoon or movie.
Someone's arms are going to break at some point.
That crowd would look like a popcorn machine.
Constantly.
Yeah, we don't want
that. So they end
up with probably at some point in this
development, they realize that involving
classic characters in Mickey Mouse would
be a good idea. And they put together
somewhat what we know
today. But they initially call
it Imagination. And I think it's
far down the road as Imagination.
That's the song. I bet
the song was written. Because Fantasmic
is never said in the
song.
So there's posters
of that. Maybe even advertisements
outside of Disneyland saying come see our
new show Imagination. And Imagination
is in the song. They say that word. Yes.
Imagination.
It's not in a night that's Fantasmic.
Because the name.
Here's something that we have missed.
First things first. Exclamation point.
I should have said it out loud when we said
the topic.
The name. How has this name
always struck us our whole
lives? Did it ever hit the ears
weird? No, I always liked
it. It's
funny because I was
just saying this the other day. All the things that Disney
decides to name things these days. There's a
blandness often times.
It's not that Fantasmic is so amazing.
But it's just enough of a twist
to make you go okay
that's memorable and somewhat unique. Yeah.
It's strange.
They made up a word. Yeah.
And it's in my I guess I always
thought it was so wait so it's
fantastic but Fantasmic
is what I what I always
thought was the entomology and how
they landed there. But then you're changing more than
right. It's fantastic.
Oh yeah. No. It's TIC
becomes MIC.
But that's not how they got there.
What it is
is a shortening of Fantasmagoria.
Because it involves
ghost stories. Yes.
Yeah. But I never figured that out
because it doesn't have most
of that word in it. And it's not
a pH. It's an F.
And who someone
says it in the show. Maleficent
says it. Really? Is it the words in old?
Oh. When she's the old
crone she goes I will
turn this into a Fantasmic.
I love how you said the old crone. I forget
her official. Is that her official
name? I think I've heard that character
referred to as the old crone.
But I do wish it would be. That's why I'm saying it.
I'd like it to be said more.
I mean we're coming up on a
presidential campaign that is old
crone versus old crone. That's
true. I think it's time to get that phrase
back on the book. And I think if we push
them at these conventions they could get
VPs who are even older.
I hope so. I hope so.
Yes.
My complaint about both of these guys
is they can technically still speak.
Let's get a real, let's get
a guy who's like a cut to in a
Laurel and Hardy movie.
Just a guy who looks like the craziest looking
old man. Just don't ask him to say anything.
The last surviving Civil
War soldier, I think they could be
VPs come January
2025.
That's the era they want everybody
to go back to so why not have somebody serve
who was in that era.
Now I'm looking up,
I don't know if she does say Phantasmagora
because I do have the
score she was like in
a rant. Like before she
turned into a dragon. And the old crones rant.
She rants and raves
cronishly. We talked about the price of groceries.
But then if you try to engage her
of like, well don't you think all these
conglomerates merging grocery store
change is a bad thing? She just
like writes you off entirely.
It came pretty naturally Jason.
Who's the old crone now?
I don't think it's any argument that
I'm not an old crone.
He's 38.
He sounds like he's 68.
What I found
that was funny is how they landed
on Phantasmagoria. So the show
is in rehearsals. It's going great.
Where he's like wow this is going to
this is really going to land huge.
We like everything about that name.
Imagination, it's not proprietary. You can't really
put it on merchandise because it's just
a word. So according to
Disneyland president Jack Lindquist,
we got a dictionary down from Michael
Eisner's bookshelf and started going
through it page by page.
We both kept throwing out names and rejecting them.
Finally we reached the P's and Michael
threw out Phantasmagoria.
It immediately intrigued us both.
It had the right feel. They took it to
our team who
I rightfully said
it's a lot. It's long though. And they
put Mickey in there and that's it.
So kind of comes from Eisner.
Comes from Eisner.
It's all good things do. Yeah.
We land there
over and over again.
If he had anything
to do with City Walk we never would have gotten
sick there. Oh that's a very good point.
No measles. No we didn't touch that
with his hands. Golden touch.
All he did was go there and change the name
of one place. If he had named
the wind up store
that would have left a legacy that would have ensured
no measles forever.
Old Hag
I ever credited as
in the script I'm looking at.
And she at one point says
and she at one point says now I'll turn
that little mouse's dream into
a nightmare phantasmic.
Okay yes.
Okay.
I mean she's an old hag. She could be
sundowning and just making up words.
Who knows.
Is crone gender specific?
And can it not be?
I always think of it as
enable everybody to be a crone.
Supposedly an ugly old woman. That's what
a crone's definition is on
this when I look it up.
Hag sounds so much worse
though. Crone just sounds like an old crank.
Yeah. Yeah. Oddly
maybe a little softer
in a way. And I
just like it. I want men to have the
ability to be old crones.
This is my dream.
Yeah.
Well you know. Well there's folklore
too. We can really get into the history
of crones I suppose. In
folklore a crone is an old woman who maybe
characterizes disagreeable, malicious, or sinister
in manner. Often with magical
or supernatural associations
that can make her either helpful or
obstructive. So
the crone is also an archetypal figure
or a wise woman. As a character
type the crone shares characteristics with
the hag.
So there's a little bit of a history lesson here.
That implies that they are different.
That does imply that. Not the same thing.
Yes. The word becomes
further specialized as the third aspect
of the triple goddess. Popularized
by Robert Graves.
Subsequently in some forms of
neo-paganism. Particularly
Wicca in which she symbolizes the
dark goddess. The dark of the moon.
The end of the cycle. Together with
the mother crone. The light
goddess. And the crone
maiden. Wow we really stumbled on some
fun stuff here. This sounds great. This sounds
like not negative crones at all.
This is fun crones. Mike you start
reading it from a dusty old book
that appeared in your hands.
That sounds like the work of
some old crone to me.
All I'm saying is we
get working on the script for
crone versus hag.
And then eventually down the line you do
crone x hag. A new empire.
Because eventually
you just want to see them be friends. You want to
see them hang out. Oh sure.
Best way you terminate her too. You flip it
at some point. The work becomes good.
I was curious if anybody
has called Trump an old crone.
And I did find the headline from this year.
Crone backs former president
Donald Trump. What?
An old crone? No.
Camden County Republican Chairman
Tom Crone. No.
Oh no. Doesn't count.
That's not quite yeah. That's not
something related to
neo paganism. That's not
mother crone or the light goddess.
Yeah that's not fun. Yeah it's not
as fun. Anyway
well yeah more crone and photocom.
But so anyway they land on
Phantasmagoria. They do so much
stuff to this area to
prepare it to do a big nighttime
spectacular. They drain the rivers
of America. They finally
replace the clay
that was at the bottom of the
rivers of America since 55.
When they filled it
first and then it drained. So
they put a bunch of clay in there which drained
much more slowly. We just
found this out about submarine voyage too that
the leaking of submarine voyage is unbelievable.
Rivers of America I don't think as bad
but still pretty bad.
And it was during that time that they replaced
the clay with gunite.
So next time you're there
no that's what's down there. Gunite.
Gunite.
More facts to bore your group with.
You know that's gunite.
Then you get pushed
into the river.
So they fixed the river. Less
draining. They build that
entire that facility was not
there. The shack or whatever you call
it. Because what I didn't
realize is that that's this giant
high tech facility
that goes five stories down.
Oh my god. That's like a crazy
vault there even though we think
it looks like a musty old shack.
Every inch of it is
different you know is computer
equipment and lighting grids.
And also space to put the massive
massive show pieces.
And elevators
that bring them up.
You talk about this dragon thing and you know
there were dragon problems
from the beginning and problems with other things.
The show used to have these big Pinocchio
marionettes that they stopped
using because sometimes wires would snap
and they'd just plummet down
into their grave at the bottom
of the like. This show
I mean
amazing that there weren't more
problems in a way but the problems that did
occur are so massive in
scale. You got to give them credit for
plowing through and getting it done
night after night even though it's
this is a destructive show. These
are props that could like crush dozens
of people under them. I was going to mention
the Pinocchio marionettes because
marionettes. I've never seen those
I feel like in the versions
of Phantasmag that I see
and I think they were gone by the like
mid 2000s when I started
going to Disneyland.
But in the newer version
there is a little
the genie makes a little
like Mickey.
He turns Mickey into one
and it's the same style and very Pinocchio
marionette and it's a nice little nod
without having to build
these potentially rigorous
props. They were kind of scary.
I remember they scared me because they have that
day glow vibe as
a lot of things did in this show.
Everything like that
I can go back into history but like
if we just talk about like
things that resonate with us about the show
the big
claw, the snake that walks
around. The snake is pretty intense
always. Yes. Yeah.
That shoots like
it's got laser eyes.
Maybe not lasers but like big light eyes
that kind of scope the crowd.
Kind of hypnotic in the movie.
Hypnotizes people.
I don't think it's laser. It's not blinding
everyone in the audience.
They don't fry audiences with lasers each night.
A lucky family. Every night
there's a lucky family that will be
horribly scarred by our new
nighttime production, Fantasmic.
Unless it gives them super powers.
They could get
Fantastic Ford.
That would be fun.
That stuff's cool.
The King Louie
and the apes that go by
at some point.
All this day glow stuff because that also felt like
look it wasn't new
in the 90s. Obviously
day glow was technology
that we had. But with
Batman Forever
and the Buster
Rhymes Put Your Hands Over My Eyes Can See
music video. It felt like we
were living in a great time day glow wise.
And not to discount
Cosmic Bowling. To leave that out of it too.
Blacklight. Right?
Blacklight and blacklight paint.
See I loved that as a kid. I loved
all blacklight stuff.
Day glow might not even be the correct
term. Is day glow right?
That's a good question. I know what you meant.
But maybe it isn't.
I don't know. I'm seeing day glow paint
that glows in the dark.
I guess blacklight's probably an important
word to say. An element of it.
I feel like it's just gotten more
elaborate as the
show is like seeing
different iterations.
Day glow paint looks like that's what you're talking about.
Yeah. Totally.
I was obsessed with this type of thing.
Glowing in the dark and neon colors.
Forget about it. That's one of my top
five things I liked as a kid.
Neon in general. Whenever you
got a box of crayons. I'm sure I've said this before on the show.
Whenever they added like five
neon colors to your box of crayola
crayons. I lost my mind.
I loved it.
I feel like that was 90s when all of a sudden
you know what kids? You got neon colors now.
We found new colors between
the colors. They're brighter colors.
They have names with attitude.
This is a gift to your generation.
Our scientists, our crayola scientists
have uncovered new colors.
They've been researching. They've been in the mountains.
The crayola mountains.
And they found them. And now we're
making them into your crayons.
I definitely would use those colors
first when I was
coloring or drawing.
Let me ask you this.
Did you like it as you aged
and people started getting different colored
pens?
Like not just black or blue
ink but like green or purple
ink? Of course I did.
I recently mentioned this when Griffin
was here for a Club 3 episode that I had one of those
pens with the four different colors on it.
But then when I was a kid I would have a pen
that had the ten colors and it was a big
thick pen. Do you ever see these
Scott? Do you remember these? I guess so.
And it would be like ten colors and you just put like
click down which color you wanted.
But the pen would obviously have to be big because it had all those
different things of ink in there.
Incredibly easy to destroy.
Like they would break if you looked at them too hard.
I had a big purple
like metal one of these and it was like
my prized possession in like third or fourth
grade. I don't know what happened to
it. I know I had a space
pen at some point in like middle school
that I lost and I was heart broken.
Space pen because you could write
sleeping down. Well yeah you could write
upside down. Yeah I
was dead asleep. I
would lucid dream right.
Lying down is what I meant to say.
I think I said sleeping down. Sleeping down.
Yeah in that case
if it gives you the ability to write while
sleeping. While sleeping down.
When you're sleeping down. Which is because I don't think
they're sleepwalking but who in their
sleep writes? And that ability
comes from the pen. Yeah.
Was that fun colors though?
No it was just black and pink.
So you weren't a fan of the fun colors?
No I like the fun colors. Therefore process
of elimination. You don't like fun colors
Jason. He's a Nazi. Let's see what he says.
Did you have I specifically
remember teachers though like
losing their shit on kids.
You can't use like
green ink. Yeah there would be
sometimes like always like specifically
you shouldn't use anything fun.
As a kid I was like what's going on
what's going on with them? What's their
problem? If you can read it what's
the problem? From a practical standpoint I
suppose pink ink is hard
to read. Yellow ink also hard to read.
So I could see if you're grading
like 30 papers and there's a bunch of pink
ink on it. Sure. Or kids
are writing in red ink and teachers
like no I use the red ink.
Yes that's another legit concern if
they're writing with red ink because you're not going to know
because yeah you could be a kid.
What if you just tried to fool the teacher and did the whole
test and then just did the red and just gave yourself
a hundred percent and an A plus.
I definitely fooled some teachers.
That would for sure work.
Yeah. Well you know.
That's the way to get them. Just put that grade on yourself.
They'll get them every time. Yeah.
So yeah try that. If you're in
school right now if you're in elementary school
try that. Grade your own test with a red
pen and see what happens.
Or in college. I don't know
try it in college. A parent turning off
the podcast. I thought these were good boys.
They're giving cheating
ideas. Yeah.
I
back to the history of the show a little bit.
The show cost 30
million at the time.
To compare Star Tours I think cost
like 32 to 35
million. Wow. So we're spending attraction
money on a show.
There's also all this infrastructure
stuff to do because they have to tier
and kind of like the terrace
where you watch it. I've never looked
at numbers of how many people watch
or can watch Fantasmic.
The area is meant for
6,000 people but I think can sometimes
attract eight.
And I was trying to. It feels like
it some nights I'll say that. Yeah.
Yes and that's the biggest deterrent to
not going to this or
trying to you know what I like is like
can I find some little corner kind of see
some of it from the edge but then
get out of there. Yeah. Beat the crowd
out of there because yeah that is and you
got to get their way early to scope
out. Though I love the show
it's not something I'm
willing to put the time into doing
that often. Yeah.
I'll say that it's
much more pleasant if you were staying
in Anaheim.
Because then you can kind of like
easily kind of slowly
let the crowds pass a little
then gradually make your way back. Make your way
to a hotel or whatever.
But dealing with crowds
dealing with Southern
California has some pretty cold nights
a lot of the year. Some pretty
like chilly nights.
And so dealing with that
and then to get back to the parking
garage and then drive back to
Burbank. It is such a Jason concern
though. It is. It's tiring.
I think though Southern California
we're really like
we have it so good weather wise
now we're going to it's chilly some
nights. It is chilly it's too dry out
here the chilliness.
And it's not exactly a phantasmic problem.
It's chilly at night in Orlando too sometimes.
Yeah but it's humid and it's warmer.
Is it warmer
you think? Well they say
there was an LA Times infographic
about this where it's like oh
50 degrees out here feels a lot
colder because it's drier.
There's not as much of a
moisture in the air.
I'm willing to entertain that.
Say Jason you want to see phantasmic tonight?
I don't know the dry cold.
If I were
a wet cold maybe
but maybe some of that mist will
get on me. But that mist is going to be cold if it
gets on you. That's not really.
Are you saying that because you have to stop and
stand or just in general
at Disneyland are you concerned with the
chilly nights? Is it just because you're
stationary? Chilly nights this summer
at Disneyland. You get colder if you're
standing. That's a good point.
But if you're roaming through Disneyland
at night generally it's not so bad.
I think if you're roaming through and you're going on
indoor attractions
you probably don't notice it as much.
If you're just standing outside
in the middle of all these people
you know.
It can get chilly.
Do you think it's chillier though seeing
a world of color?
I bet it is because there's more
open air. There's a lot of mist off
world of color. A lot of mist, a lot of
projections. But then I feel like there's more
things in the way of the full
windy gusts that you might
get. I feel like yeah DCA
is gustier. I think DCA
is gustier. That's my premise
that I share with Jason.
What is with you guys in wind
these days? The food court
at City Walk is so windy.
It is crazy windy. Can I ask you this?
Sorry we're going back to City Walk.
I've never experienced this wind in my life.
I let it slide in the episode.
Are you sure you wasn't just windy that day?
Did you see his mouth open like mine?
It's always windy up there.
It's always windy. No matter
what time of year. City food is always
windy. Or 90% of the
time. It's alright.
I shouldn't be opening it up now but as it was
happening in the moment I'm like here's a very
Mike and Jason old crone
kind of thing. I'm shocked by this.
If this is old crone behavior
consider me the oldest crone.
It's always windy up at City
Food. I don't know why. I used to go out there for
dollar fish taco Tuesday nights
and it was so cold
up there eating those dollar fish tacos.
That's a five
timer and sometimes you go up and there's
people working up there. That's another
five timer. Working up there.
You talk about how there's people
who go up on business lunches.
That's something that's come up a zillion times.
Well there's plenty of business travelers
staying at those fine hotels.
When he's right he's right.
Chilliness at Disneyland.
I've also gone up there
and done creative work in the past.
I'm not as concerned with chilliness at
Disneyland as Jason is but we
are in lockstep on the windiness of
City Food. It seems like you're a little bit
concerned with DCA gustiness.
Well I'm just saying it is gustier
and I think you could probably get chillier
and get hit with the gusts more aggressively
at Disney's California Adventure during
World of Color than
Fantasmic. But that's just
honestly that's a guess. That's something we're going to need to test out
in the next year. It's a gust guest.
It's a gust guest. I'm gust
guesting on gusts here.
I think I said it right.
Our guest today is gust guest
who's going to take
some guesses about gusts.
Look we need to do more
work in year what is it? Seven
of this podcast on the gustiest
parts of the parks.
We don't have good gust
maps when it comes to our home
parks like Disneyland, Disney's California Adventure.
People leave. They go to these parks unequipped.
They don't come with the proper gust breakers.
Exactly. They're thrown out to the
elements. They need that. The chilly
California nights.
That is a big change
from Orlando light.
Just throw a light sweater in your bag.
Day and night not that different
much in the year.
It's one of these coastal
things because I go to
Disney World and I'm like this weather is
bonkers. But you guys grew
up on that side of the country.
It's perfect. Florida weather
notoriously perfect.
Nothing more comforting than some old
fashioned hurricane weather.
I've been there where it's been on and off
rain and ten minute stints
for the entire day. Just bring a
sweater. Duck in a shop.
That's the fun of it.
Check out the wares.
Now that's fun but gustiness
this you must come equipped. You must plan
what clothes will
protect me from the gusts.
Now you must
deal with the power of California
gusts. Oh my god what if the new
there's a new I guess not a dragon but the new
bad guy or character is gusting
at the audience not shooting flames.
The gusts are
hitting the audience now. I mean that'd be evil
and it would probably also hit the
standby line when that Tiana ride
opens. Oh you know what it's also
like an ingenious thing too because you
would sell light sweaters in all
the gift shops around the rivers of America.
So everybody would race into the gift
shops to get a little light sweater and purchase
a Disneyland light sweater. So now
they're making hand over fist money
with the different people that
are just a little chilly. They're exploiting
people running into the brand new Critter
co-op store. Critter co-op.
They're running into the Tiana's general store.
The new Haunted Mansion gift shop that will
open this year. All these new places are just designed
to sell new Disneyland light sweaters.
These motherfuckers.
Did you guys age 28 years
since the City Walk Saga ended?
Now we're concerned
with shawls.
Well Disney is concerned by
selling us shawls. But it
is always, look it's just practical to have a light
sweater when you go anywhere. Or a sweatshirt. It could be
a sweatshirt as well. It could be a sweatshirt if
you're going to be a young person. If you're going to be
younger it's a sweatshirt.
If you're, are you
saying that sweatshirt is a young
person's term? Well it's
cooler than a cardigan.
Sweatshirt
and sneaker and
blue jeans.
What's his name? What's that basketball player?
I couldn't tell you. I can't keep up with
the kids. If you're sort of in college
you wear blue jeans and you wear
your sneakers and stuff. But after a
certain point you become an adult and
switch to slacks.
Blue jeans?
Do you wear your loafers? Blue jeans is a college
term? Like dungarees.
Hang on. As an adult
I'm supposed to start saying the
brand names. Blue jeans is a
phrase I retire as a young man.
I don't know what's being said
anymore. Look, if you don't
understand it I'm not going to explain it
at this point. Because that's just a difference
of, I don't know, how we were raised
or how we are
with morals. In a lot of ways it's just
differences in how we're maturing as adults
I think. The way in which we speak. Abandoning
childish things like the phrase blue
jeans and sweatshirt.
That's right. Sweatshirts and blue jeans
are for young people. That's
all I know. That's what I know.
As an adult.
An adult man.
Podcast The Riot hosted by one
man in his late thirties and
two who are mentally in their mid
eighties.
But mostly the two
mostly wear joggers. For some
reason they switch from slacks
to that.
They haven't worn blue jeans in
years.
Alright.
I'm going to play, how about we play a clip?
You guys want to see a clip?
When the
show is on its way to
opening they tease it on what I would
have to imagine is an Easter special.
And there is a tour
being given to a group
by one of the Disneyland
plaid wearing tour guides.
And one of the kids
in the tour group is
Home Improvement's Taryn Noah Smith.
This is one that
I strongly remember seeing.
Didn't see it for decades but remembered it
in a scared
way and I think you'll understand why when I
play the clip. So know that
the scene as it begins
is between
youngest Home Improvement child
Taryn Noah Smith.
Who today is a submersible expert
apparently. Now you know that.
He gives his life to submarines
now. And this
tour guide. But will she remain a tour guide
for long?
I can't. I wish I could see it now.
Oh careful.
Wishes do come true at Disneyland.
I didn't come here to be
careful.
Oh my god she turned into Maleficent.
Very well.
You have been warned.
She turned into Disney's sing-along
Maleficent with like the shinier
face. Not as shiny as the Disney sing-along
Maleficent but close. It is
a little bit shiny. It's definitely
in that family. Yeah yeah. Was I
particularly afraid of Maleficent
in the cartoon? No. But you live
actioned this Maleficent.
You give her shiny green.
And then digital red
eyes. Yes. This sequence is
terrifying. I definitely
remember watching this.
He does a
big McAuley
I said it wrong. How is it? McAuley.
Everybody yelled at me about this one. You said like McAuley.
McAuley or something you said.
McAuley or something.
You got McAuley there.
That's sort of how you say it. Like Mater would say it.
Hey McAuley cock.
I turned into.
Scott's such a hick.
Listen to him say McAuley.
Hey McAuley there. He's got the same
vocal tics as Mater the Toe Trunk.
Toe Mater.
Finally got an angle on Scott. Scott is such a
dumb fuck hick.
He thinks you say McAuley.
Hey McAuley cock. He don't eat.
Well yeehaw.
Scratches his butt. Scratches his
rear and says McAuley all day.
Get her done.
Get her done Scott.
McAuley I believe. McAuley.
So
anyway then
he go. It becomes night.
And he's like all
of phantasmic is happening to him.
And then Maleficent chases him around
the park. It's
a terrifying little scene. If you
take these park specials at their word
and you think this is what's actually going to happen
this is
a nightmare. And I did. I took every
single
Splash Mountain is going to take a full
two minutes to do
the drop like Ernest. And
I'm going to be hunted down
for sport by Maleficent.
Yeah. No I didn't see this when I was a
kid. Thank goodness. Because
it would have really colored my feelings
about the show. But anytime
and what's weird also
about it is these specials feel
they don't feel like a movie.
They're shot kind of like
they're not like a home video. But they're not
shot on like some film. They look
like it's shot on video. So that almost
lends itself to feeling like it's real
more so even than a movie
which you can even you can
articulate it as a kid that you know what a movie
looks like and feels like. But almost
there's some distance between you and
a movie versus this which is shot on
video which to me as a
kid would make stuff like that feel more real.
Like the news.
Like the news. Yeah. Right.
They just pointed a camera at this.
They didn't do anything.
We were thankful. We're like
I'm glad on the East Coast and the Midwest
far away from this hell park
where child actors
keep getting comeuppance after comeuppance.
Yeah. Yeah.
Individual kids might be victimized
by specific Disney villains.
It could happen to you. So yeah.
I'm just glad.
I think they have targets on their back because they're
celebrity kids. I was always hoping that the
anonymity would make it so
Maleficent wouldn't even see me. Yeah
maybe. Maybe. And she didn't
attack you when you went to Disneyland. No
I can't unless I ever pressed this
greatly. I don't remember Maleficent
attacking me. Okay that's good. You were
comforted in early
one thing about early
Fantasmic the old hag
had like a pretty comical
like character head on.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. She
transforms from having a regular face
to having like a big muppet face
for sure.
Hopefully fire. Like it's
mostly fireproof. Yeah.
I hope that's a concern with all
the wardrobe in this show. They used to
soak all the costumes in gasoline but they had to stop
doing it. So
It's fun if it catches on fire. Yeah.
There is a point
where the Mickey
I believe it's when he confronts the
dragon and the very old
version holds up a sword
and you can see the
hose of sparks.
You can see the hose that is probably
filled with sparks.
Sparks fluid.
He's always you know there's been
God knows how many Mickey's
are actually on that island but
A thousand.
Oh God. There's so many.
They keep coming. They keep reproducing. The one has
the gloves. The spark gloves.
That has been a main stay I feel like
on this show. You know what you bring up
Mikey mentioned the sing along songs
video. The Disneyland fun sing along
songs. Which is our first club three
episode. And I think that ends
with a pre-Fantasmic
Mickey shoot of
the sparks from his fingers.
Right. I think this was something they had.
This is something they could do
maybe for commercials or
very special events. But
they made it part of nightly entertainment.
And as we're talking I mean we can start getting into
the show and just call out moments that we love.
I mean this is great.
And the music builds
to it perfectly where it's like the music
is so many like great like it's dynamics
and hits. And I like that that's like
dun dun dun.
And it lets you go one arm two arm.
They go up one more time.
Sparks. And Mickey
shoots sparks. And we discover that
Mickey is a god. Yeah that's right.
It always delights me.
The spark gloves.
No matter how much
they like change the lighting
or the projection to be like
crisper and brighter. Like spark
gloves still
is as great as when the show started
I feel like. The two things that I
like. Well I like seeing Mickey do a lot of things.
But the two things that always pop out
in my mind of what I like to see the costumed
Disneyland Mickey do is shoot
sparks and drum for
real. And he does
that. He hasn't done that in a parade lately
but when there's a performer that's
the drummer and they're wearing the Mickey outfit
and they just go crazy on the drums on a big
float. I am delighted
and it's pretty equal with the sparks.
Well let me throw something at you.
Both. That's
how they up the game.
Oh wow. They're shooting. He's drumming
and shooting sparks
while he does it. Now is that
safe? No.
Let's give it a try.
Only one way to find out.
And it should be one of those like Neil Peart
like a hundred
different drum crazy drum sets.
I think Tommy Lee
had a mechanism where he'd like float above
the audience.
It's like he's trapped in a drum cage.
Travis Barker did it on a blink tour
once maybe. Well so all the great
drummers have done it so why not include
the greatest drummer Mickey. Wow that would
rule. Let me ask you this
Mike. Do you like
the walk around Mickey? Do you like
the one that can blink?
Do I like? Yes. You like blinking
Mickey? Yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't know that there's a
Mickey I don't like that walks around.
Sure. Even blinking. Remember
I went to the talking Mickey.
The one with his arm around Minnie.
Well I don't like it as
much. I like him as much but
yeah, yeah. I like the blinking one fine.
I wish the talking one was back. They retired
the talking Mickey. For some reason.
Yeah they retired him.
They put him on that island with all the Mickeys.
We don't know how many are out there.
They put him out there to pasture.
Welcome to Mickey Island.
How do you eat you ask?
Well rats,
squirrels and perhaps
other Mickeys. Good luck.
The original like nightmare mice
that were from like the ice skating show
that Wal just bought a mouse costume from
with the holes in the face. Those are out
on Tom Sawyer Island. They're still out there.
They're on the island. We've been trying to find a way
to kill ourselves.
They skitter if you go out there in the daytime
and you see something just in the corner
of your eye but you look and there's nothing
there. Right. That's the mutant ones.
Right. Mickey's birthday land. Mickey's
out there. Yeah. They're all out there.
But yeah it's
basic. Yeah so they retired the one that
I talked that I met in Disney World
where I met him in his dressing room.
Wow. Yeah.
So I'm glad you caught him in that window then.
Well right because I was
upset when I went to the city hall to complain
that initially you didn't get
the talking Mickey yes.
So yeah I like blinking. I like talking.
I like stationary face as well.
Dear city hall, Mickey doesn't
drum while shooting sparks.
Well how am I supposed
to keep coming to the park until this is
a reality? Yeah. Yeah. I would
complain about any sort of thing.
Can I ask this? I meant to bring this up earlier.
Were you guys's family
because I was texting with my dad
about like
were we did we camp
out a lot for shows or
parades. You know what
I mean like setting up well before
because he's like oh your mother
was always
on like getting a good spot for
the parade getting a good and I
was like but we wouldn't be there like an hour
or 90 minutes before. He's like
no like half hour. That was the
most we ever. I think I'm similar.
I feel like my mom would be willing
to do it and if it was something new like
this I bet we camped out for a little bit for this.
And only
my mom, dad and sister out.
I think there was the
other time you remembered was
and we'll talk about the Fantasmic
in Florida down the line.
But that loading in
the early days I think took a
lot of time
to really load in and
out people as they were getting up to
speed on that one. I'll tell you what
it is a thing that I do not ever do
today. This is
will I get back there if there's shows
that I feel like my son would
really enjoy then possibly I
could see getting back to that point. But
for now a camp out it's
been decades. Oh yeah.
I don't know. Well I mean like
they have the thing where you upcharge
like we did the Main Street
Electrical. Yeah.
So you eat at Blue Byte. You know you pay a
bunch of money and then you have like a little spot
they give you. Oh sure. So that's sometimes
a little treat you can do. They do that
with World of Color and stuff.
I don't think we that's not
especially when you go so often it's not something
I make a point to
do. Okay. But
once in a while and if it's like
a Mickey and the Magical Map or whatever that show
was called that was in the theater with seats
that's more of a like well we go
and we can go early and sit down for
45 minutes. Now that's a different story. Yeah easier with
seats but those seated
venues they may not open.
Well it depends. For much longer.
It depends if they're doing like three or four
shows in the day. I feel like you can get in there
a little early but if they're like
I forget what's the Little Mermaid show at Hollywood
Studios. I feel like that's running
so many shows per day. Well that's been down for
a while too. Sure but I'm just saying I think they run
that show more often. Oh yeah they run that
a lot. Than some other shows so it depends
but yeah no especially in a home park
you always have that feeling
well I can always do it next time and maybe
that's wrong. Maybe that's a wrong instinct
but I do feel like I have it with a lot of things.
You never know when something will catch on
fire. Right and then they'll change it forever.
Go down for a year. Yeah. Somehow
Waterworld hasn't caught on fire that much.
Sure that's true.
Just one character on
purpose every show.
Let's talk about some stuff
that we like in
the show.
Speaking of fire. Fire on
water. Now they didn't invent
this. This is possible. This has happened
in the movies but had it ever
happened in front of me I don't
know. And at that scale
it's pretty unbelievable. I mean
it's second only to the projections
on the water in terms of like that's
possible
blew my kid mind. Really loved it. And you
could feel that mystery. You could feel that heat. Very cool.
Feeling the heat yeah. I mean I'm trying to
remember when I even maybe it was like Six Flags
stunt show or something when you feel the
heat. Like as the Batman stunt
show I saw in the early 90s where it's like
they blew up a barrel of gasoline
or something and it was like oh my
god. Like that really will
scare the shit out of you as a kid. Yeah
we want our shows to stink.
Yes. Our shows should smell the
high heaven or it's barely a show.
But yeah that's the
flames on the water is pretty crazy.
That feels like
that feels like end times to me. That feels
like hell is on earth now.
Like it shouldn't be possible. I
understand how it works. I think I do at
least but it doesn't feel right.
It feels magical. I'm not saved from fire
when in water. My god.
Yes. I know that the oil
tankers spill oil and it catches
on fire. I know how that works but I'm just
saying. It's like seeing a live oil
tanker. It shouldn't be right. It must have been tough
in the wake of Exxon Valdez.
Right yes.
They had to get so much dawn soap
up there to clean off those animals.
Yeah I just
I will even I guess
I should have said this earlier back. I also
like when I went to Disneyland for the first time because
in Disney World this is its own thing.
Yes. So when I was a kid that's
what we saw it in its own like little theater
thing. In an amphitheater that they specially
built. Yeah so they did create a new
area for this and the plan I believe
is to talk about this down the road
second gate question mark.
Yes I'm just I'm just saying it for
context so like part of it was
just almost when I was going
here for the first time like noticing
all of the fun like oh
this shit all these lights are here
and they're hidden here and I didn't notice that that
was a big rig for the whole show.
Oh yeah. So like later like almost
like putting it together after the fact
not realizing maybe when I
first went that Fantasmic is just it's right here
and all this stuff is kind of hidden
in the background. So you're there like
much older and not even realizing that's
how they did thinking like it's you know you know
it is this like sectioned off amphitheater.
Right. And then you're in it you're everybody's walking
through that amphitheater all day and walking
on the show pieces you're on the ships.
It's all happening and then they in a matter
of hours they convert it. So I should have said earlier but yeah
even just before any of the actual scenes
itself it's just like I was I thought
that was cool that it's all like
hiding in plain sight. I have a question
on a similar note to that. Yeah.
The when
the okay there's like King Louis
and then there is a portion of the show
that I call Rafts
of Love and that is when the
romantic sequences go
it's Beauty and the Beast and
I think at various times been Little
Mermaid or Tangled.
Tangled. And you hear
very adult contemporary versions of
the love songs from the movies. Yes.
Are those
converted Tom Sawyer
Island rafts or are those their own
vehicles because they certainly resemble
them. So do they switch those
out during the day
or not. That is a good
question. I hadn't even thought of that but maybe
I mean they repurpose so much stuff.
Yeah. But is that a big
headache to flip those
and like put glowy
roses on them or whatever.
They have a lot of fiber optics on them
now I feel like. I feel like I always
saw those as separate barges.
They might be and maybe the I can't picture
the Tom Sawyer Island ones maybe those look
woodsier, folksier.
So I might be wrong on that.
That's just one of those like is it
in plain sight questions I had
that I don't know. Another one that I was
like wow this was
in here pretty early.
In the old old
video Ariel
is sitting on a rock with
flippers. I don't know in
the new one she is still doing that.
Uh huh.
I don't know. I saw
there's yeah is that in the
that's a good question. Or is it just Ariel
with legs. She has
flippers I think. I'm pretty sure she has flippers.
But I'd have to go double check that.
I like the
it's in the newer one
Aladdin and Jasmine with the carpet.
Yes. And the mist and stuff like
a mist on the lake. That is
really cool. That looks great.
I think especially when they flip
it to
less projection.
Like almost like the mist goes
away and there's more
like stuff on the island.
Oh I see what you're saying. Yeah
it's like a good reveal almost. It's not really
revealing anything but it's like
it's putting more focus on
the carpet and the performers I suppose.
But yeah that looks really cool.
I really
like the pink elephants
sequence.
I like that we have kind of a
scary psychedelic
moment in the show.
It's maybe the coolest use of the
mist screens because they think you know
if you're it's like you're not meant to like
stare at anything on the mist screens for a long
time so it's better if it's more abstract
and cutty or
crazy designs and patterns and that's
what that sequence is completely. But what
I really like about it
I've always really loved
the music in that
section because I
find it to be such like
funny meat head
90s prog.
It's so like the version of
pink elephants they play which is very
guitar heavy.
I mean you'll see it's just like so bright
it feels very like Pro Tools
core.
Let me give you a taste to see what I mean.
Look out!
They're like guitar like guitar
harmonies the guitars are playing.
I'm going to go through a little solo and get
to this one little part.
Pack of derbs!
That's really funny yeah.
Silly the dumbest like guy thinks he's
cool right. That's a real dad playing guitar
moment. I'm busting out
this rockin version of
pink elephants.
Same aesthetic as all the Marvel
superhero island music.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Double guitar.
Yeah you're in the zone of like power rangers
rock. I think it's kind of it kind of
sounds in a way like like kind of like
Steve Vai
type like
you know get to say Triani like
guitar 90s guitar
virtuoso music.
It's like really technically
impressive but it's also like generic.
Yes.
Everybody playing
is fantastic but it is produced like
so blandly.
But it also sounds like stuff that I listen to
to like with the express purpose of
like take me back to 1992.
So I kind of
love here and I love that it's never gotten fully
fully
90s.
And on that note the music.
Let's talk music
a little bit.
I love I love this theme.
I love hearing it.
You know in the Esplanade
I've I listen
to it like specifically
if you get it as the exit music
on Spotify
because you can listen to the you could
go to Spotify and get the entire 25
minutes score of the entire show.
There's a lot to get through.
But I like playing just the exit
music which I guess is as people walk out
that's what the word exit means.
And I just
it's just such a
it's got some inherent 90s
but also very classic.
So bombastic and
if you're talking instrumental music
in the parks it's one of the pieces that
moves me and transports me there the most.
Yeah it's one of those songs
that maybe I'm
misremembering or I've implanted
a memory in my brain that doesn't actually
that shouldn't be there. But I remember
hearing this seeing the show for the first
time and then us humming the song
the whole trip. I don't remember which
year it was which trip it was where we
saw this for the first time. But
it was one of those where we were like
humming the phantasmag theme.
And it's just I don't know
top five
top ten of any of these
instrumental maybe pieces of music
in general I would say.
Made for theme parks.
I mean maybe then Soren after this and then
after that music that like you
hear but Soren I don't even think the first
time we did it we were like humming it in the park
even though it's really memorable.
The only other time now in recent memory
is Sinbad in Tokyo
Disney Sea where
we were like humming the song
the rest of the trip.
It was immediately memorable
and we were just like singing it
for the rest. Yeah all those so
many days or whatever we were there. How many
was it? Was it three and a half? Was it four?
I don't remember. How many days we spent.
Well however many it was.
We were singing the song. Let's not go back to that.
We don't want to go back to that. But yeah
so but I'm pretty sure
phantasmag and that are the two things
I remember the most when music
that we're hearing for the first time in the park
like just sticks with you immediately.
And it's like
it just like makes you feel like I'm on
an adventure. Yeah. This is the little
theme of my adventure. Right.
It's just the star of the show.
Yeah. It's the it's the best
thing in the whole show.
Full of good stuff. Yes. I don't think
this anymore. Not going to anything else but if it wasn't
tied together by that magical
fanfare. Yeah I don't think
I don't think phantasmag is phantasmag
and maybe doesn't last
as long without the music. Yeah. I think
you're right because they've done other like they've
done other great shows where there's not
necessarily where the music's fine but it's not as
as memorable as that. But like
nothing I mean maybe years before we were doing
this podcast and I hadn't seen fully phantasmag
the only the thing I build is a dragon
or Mickey. Yeah. Yeah. But the
song that's the big
that's the fireworks of the show is the sound
of the song what the song makes
you feel a certain way. Yeah. With incredible
speaker I mean the sound setup
of this thing is unbelievable especially
that it stays hidden all day. Right. And comes
out at night. Let's just get a little hit
of it. Bruce Healy is the composer. Yeah.
It's funny because out of context
too especially that the kind of like
chiller version of it which is that
the exit music it does feel like
it could be in some sort of like industrial
tape to teach fast food workers
how to clean the equipment.
One thousand percent and that's what I love about it.
I chase that kind of music. I know I understand.
That's what I want to hear all
the time. It relaxes me so much.
When cleaning the fry cooker at McDonald's
make sure
You will often find
find some old video just some
arbitrary thing. It's just
yeah it's for Kmart internal use only
and you're like damn that song what is
up with it. It goes hard. Yeah. Yes.
It's such a common occurrence.
When you're working at Kmart make sure not
to wear your blue jeans. Make sure to wear
loafers and khaki pants.
Leave your young person clothes at home.
You want to be treated as an adult. Bring a light
sweater as well because sometimes at Kmart gets
chilly but we like to keep our guests on their toes
by keeping the temperature. Leave the blue jeans at home
the blue light is what's
the focus here at Kmart.
The exciting world of Kmart.
So let me say this without
saying the name there is
I had a conversation once that
changed my that kind of warped
me on Fantasmic forever.
When I was talking
to somebody who is
a music industry person and also
a big Disney parks fan
and when talking to
a music industry person I want to ask
stories about David Foster
who's come up on the show.
80's mega producer
why did he come up because of his Alan Thicke
collaborations a couple months ago.
Some people have reached out like really wanting
to nerd out about David
Foster with me and I appreciate you
do it anytime. I am available for David
Foster talk.
Any and all times. But I
asked about David Foster
and this person said boy well if I were
David Foster I would be pissed about Fantasmic.
And I said
what does that mean and he said
Winter Games and I said
of course know what you mean Winter Games
the 1988 Winter
Olympics theme performed by
David Foster for his beloved
Canada as they were in Calgary
that year. What I'm going to play
this is not a rip off
but I think you could see
tell me if you disagree with me but
ever since I heard that I am like I think
we're at least in the same tone.
These are at least in the
same genre of music
I would say. Interesting. So here
is a little bit of David Foster's Winter
Games.
That's funny.
It's really
those hits.
The hits really a big dynamic
and then kind of like glistening
like the river of piano
going through it. And if I played the whole thing
I think like the movements of it.
I'm not making any rip off
accusations. I'm happy that there's
room in this world for both of these pieces
of music. I just wonder if they were inspired
by. It feels like a demo of Fantasmic
or something. Yeah.
Well that's a knock on the
lush orchestration of Winter Games.
I apologize to the
song Winter Games. What I would
recommend either way whether or not
you see musical similarities there
here's what I'm going to recommend to any
and all listeners and to you guys. You go on
a road trip. You're on a little getaway that
you're really amped for. You start that
road trip with this playlist.
Fantasmic exit music. Bruce
Healy. David Foster Winter Games.
And then I
believe. See if you go with me
that I think that this is of the same
maybe. I don't know what to call this. I was
thinking on the way maybe is it like triumph
rock. Is that maybe the genre
of this music. It's kind of
athletics. Yeah. I mean Mickey isn't
in the Olympics but it's Olympic level feats.
And I think part of
all that I think number three of that playlist
could be a very famous sports song.
Well.
John Tesh.
I mean you're
it's got the hits. It's more hits.
It reminds you of the
the glory of victory
of the defeat
of enemies like old
crones and I don't know the
trailblazers if you're rooting against
them.
Great SNL sketch about
this song. Yes.
Tim Robinson sketch.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So
anyway. Put that playlist
together. That's good.
Yeah. And also you know if you
get the John Tesh live version
on Spotify then you get a little bit of the
basketball sample at the beginning.
Because you know he tells the story of how he
Oh I've seen it. Yeah. Yes. Of course.
He left himself an answering machine
message. He plays it stirring
to hear round ball rock live.
I think that's all part.
Whatever the genre is called Triumph Rock
I love it.
So there's my little musical terror.
What have we missed?
The big changes
I want to highlight like
one moment from
the old old version of the show
that I don't know that I've ever seen
live. There was a
giant Ursula
float puppet
thing. Like a bitch. She was a big
barge. She was a big barge.
She was an Ursula barge. She was lit up for maybe
40 seconds.
And it looked expensive.
You know what is she inflatable
because the arms wave but it might be
like where it's kind of being
the arms are being selectively blown
so it looks like she's like singing or casting
a spell. I thought it was cool.
I mean she was a big
that was a big villain at
the time. A recent villain.
And you know what some of the magic
of Phantasmic and for me at that
age is we're getting
my movie the recent
movies that have hit me as a kid
so I grew up in this Disney
Renaissance era but they weren't able
to put in permanent attractions yet so we're
getting Beauty and the Beast Little Mermaid.
Beauty and the Beast gets in there fast.
And it didn't in
like significant permanent ways
for a long time so
so yes that's
great. I think that was gone by
97. That's in the Phantasmic
problems category.
Continuously broke down.
Ultimately was
replaced by not replaced
because it took a long time but
as kind of a spiritual
replacement they did
big flotsam and jetsams
her
eels. Is that what they are?
And which
I never knew how they worked but I
saw like a kind of
a diagram of it
that those were run on
jet skis.
It was like a big mask
that they put over a jet ski.
I guess similar to that
scary thing pulling the Disneyland Paris
boat. And
I mean imagine that's your job. You're
driving gigantic eels
around via jet ski.
Cool. Yeah. Well the jet ski I mean I
recently we saw the purge
show at Universal at Horror Nights
with like neon jet skis.
And I would imagine I mean that's cool
too because that you get to be more showcased
now. You're the guy or whoever the
person driving a neon
jet ski. But be hauling
an eel behind you or next
to you. That'd be awesome.
Anyway
I mean in the cross section I'll try to post
that somewhere is so crazy.
These however
capsized all the time, bumped into
each other all the time. These do not last
very long. Yeah. It's saying
something though that like
they've always tried very
ambitious stuff
in like limited space
for Fantastic. And there's
been technically a lot of
troublesome stuff. Be it like
the pyro or
the dragon or Ursula
or the
eels. But it is
it's good that they keep trying
new things and iterating new
things. I think
one of the
interesting
things might be a short
as the show is going on
I feel like more and more is
taken over by missed
projection. Yeah true.
And all of and the like
you know the
whatever. What is the
projecting perfectly onto the wall?
What is the
projection mapping?
Yeah thank you.
There's a lot of that and I don't
I mean I'm just like
tired of it.
It's been used a lot. Yeah.
I think it's a little bit of clutter
in the Fantasmic context.
You'll be happy to know that
the Pirates of the Caribbean was on the
sailing ship Columbia for a while.
I believe Peter Pan
coming back in the
in the new version.
The Return of Peter.
Pinocchio is still the McKets
are still going. The Marionettes are still
going. We haven't seen the new show.
Maybe there's Pans back.
The McKets are back. My little puppet
boys are back.
Little boys that
don't want to grow up are back and puppet boys
are back. That should be the tag
because of the billboards going down the anus.
Puppet boys and boys that
don't want to grow up are back.
Thank God. What can we do?
Certainly we can't move on from this.
I get, look
other people don't feel this way. Other people are not
creeped out by Peter Pan as I am.
They just added a new area in Disney
Sea.
I just, I don't know.
But I guess I'm being very
age picky. Here I am upset with you
guys for being obsessed with
pussies and shawls. I guess I don't want you
to be, I just want you to be your age.
Just enjoy the age that you're at.
Yeah, but you're the boy who never
grew up.
How are we?
I am not that.
We're like Peter Pan's
parents. That's really what Jason
and I are like. We're Peter, what's Robin
Williams' name in Hook?
Peter Panning.
Banning with a B.
But he's Peter.
He's not the parents, right?
He's Peter. Yes, he is Peter.
He is Peter. Does he have parents?
Did we see his parents in that movie? I don't remember.
I don't know. I don't think so. No, I don't think you do.
Here's my question. This is, it's called
Fantasmic, and this is
the closest you have to a Fantasia
show or ride. Oh, I forgot
to say, and that was an idea
kind of, there was Riverhaunt,
then it was, is there some like we do
Fantasia live,
show clips, play live music, and it kind
of grew out of that. So that's at the base of it.
But yeah, they show,
you know, there's clips from Fantasia,
there's the Chernobog stuff, but it's kind of mixed in
with like Monstro,
there's a clip of Monstro, whatever, it's all in the projection.
But you get Mickey in his
Fantasia Sorcerer's Apprentice
outfit. And that's the closest,
yeah, that's like, there's never been a,
I mean, there's really never been a Mickey ride,
but you do, it's, I guess that's
probably, it's like the closest thing
is a mashup of Sleeping
Beauty and Fantasia in some ways.
That's like the kind of climax of it
in a lot of ways. And it's kind of interesting,
like I kind of think it's interesting to mash two movies
up. Steve and Willy
too, in their pioneering Mark
Twain. Yeah, and obviously there's a ton of movies, but also
like this, in my mind,
my mind, I think of those two, the things
you think of are Mickey in his outfit
and Maleficent Dragon,
which are from two separate
Disney movies. So I think more mashup
shows like that are good ideas
potentially. Sure. I don't know, we could
brainstorm real quick. I don't know,
two things, Peter Pan
and Pinocchio perhaps.
Aye, there used to be a lot more.
Send that back to the cardboard.
I don't know, take this song, there's
Peter Pan and he's fighting,
like, Monstro is fighting Peter Pan.
That's interesting.
I just want, can we, let's just mash
up. Yeah. Peter gets
turned into a puppet boy.
How about that? Peter Pan
we found a way to
worsen the...
And he's got strings,
but he still wants to fly. All you gotta do is
draw those ventriloquist lines
under his mouth and now I'm
even more out than usual. That's pretty good.
There used to be a lot more Pinocchio
in this show, admittedly.
How about this for a mashup?
Go ahead. Going really
small characters,
the rescuers
meet
the great mouse detective.
So, kind of around
the same time periods,
I feel like, at least at first.
More realistic mice meeting
up. Well, let me ask you this question.
Will the mice be to scale?
Will they be tiny
mice? Cause it'll be hard
cause the rescuers and the great mouse detective are
actually the sizes of
mice in the movies.
Mickey's more of an anthropomorphic. For a live theme park
show, it might be hard if they were to
scale. That's a good thought.
Alright, you're thinking, yeah, and if you're
at a distance, like across the river, great.
But for a motion picture where you can zoom in
and do some close ups.
So you're talking about a movie, maybe, too.
Oh, this is a whole franchise.
The great mouse detective
meets the rescuers.
Okay, alright.
Do they save somebody, or I guess
there's some sort of a mystery to be solved
and a rescue that need to be enacted
at the same time. Well, somehow, Rattigan
has returned.
And that's the opening crawl.
Yeah, that's the opening. That's the opening crawl.
Did they kill Rattigan at the end of the great mouse detective?
I feel like he gets tossed off, much like
Moriarty in
the. It's like a Gaston, it's like a generic
piece. But again, as with
Palpatine, that was a fault
of the death that turned out to not be true.
So, yes, we could be in
somehow territory. They do kill a lot of the
villains off at the end of these
movies. Yeah, but in a way that you don't
see. Right. You don't see the
splat. The kids don't see the splat.
Yeah, which isn't too satisfying. If you really,
if you hate Gaston, if you hate
Rattigan, I want to know.
I want to see a corpse.
Scar gets eaten at the end of Lion King
by the hyenas, right?
That's sort of what's implied. But you meet
his son later on.
You meet Scar's son later? Isn't that
like a TV show or
directed DVD? Oh, maybe. I don't know.
Scar's son? I don't believe it.
Scar's bastard child?
Oh, that's the title. Great. Yes, that rings a bell
now. Yeah, Scar's bastard child.
Does he talk about how he plays?
I don't know. I got to look into all of this.
I was going to keep talking, but I had to
sneeze, and then it didn't come in. I think it's coming again.
I may have to sneeze anyway.
I'm trying to fight it. Okay, I'll just sneeze.
There it is.
It's fine. Everything's
fine. It's amazing that doesn't happen
more often. I was just thinking that
this is crazy that the
adrenaline is pumping so much during the
show that rarely do I ever have to sneeze.
Yeah, yeah. Because I'm in fight
mode or whatever. It's so high octane, yes.
Sneezes
are weakness, I say. Yeah, you would think
we were ending that. And we feel so strong.
Sure, yeah.
It's like we've all got, I mean,
we do, you know, Mickey doesn't
drum with spark gloves, but
we are podcasting and shooting
sparks out of our fingers
a lot.
We don't film it, actually.
It's pretty exciting.
What have we missed about this thing?
You know, we've, okay, so
yes, good.
We've already alluded to it,
but if you're not seeing the show,
it absolutely ruins
Disneyland at night.
If you're trying to get from point A to point
B that's around adventure land.
But then it
sucks a lot of people out of it. That is true, too.
But it is something,
if you are going to see it,
go early, see it, and stake out of place
or do some sort of dining package.
But if you are not seeing Fantasmic,
avoid at all costs.
Avoid New Orleans Square
area. It is hard to get around
this area. Make sure that you have done,
you know, Pirates Saundered Mansion,
anything in that direction, the entire
west of the park. Make sure that you
have cleared it out. Yes. And hopefully
Tomorrowland becomes a ghost town.
Stick to Batuu or Tomorrowland.
Stick to Batuu.
But don't exit that one way.
Batuu is empty at night.
No one's there. Despite the fact it looks
terrific. No performers, no people.
That's not the issue.
Supposedly Sabine
Wren or whatever is hanging out.
There's new characters around in Batuu.
I don't know if you're messing with us.
No, I'm not. I think I just said a name of
one of the characters. Sabine is the name?
Just put some arbitrary sounds together.
Sabine Wren, I think I actually got the name correct.
Yep. And she's going to be
in Galaxy's Edge or is already there.
What is she? What does she do? She's from a show.
She's not an old crone, I hope.
She's a Mandalorian warrior
and a graffiti artist.
And she's got a creative and rebellious
spirit. So is she gonna do
like airbrushed art of the kids?
She's gonna do, yes. You can get
a caricature of yourself painted
by Sabine Wren
in Batuu. Sabine Wren will draw you
with a baseball bat in your hand
eating Cracker Jacks. That's correct.
Will she like spray paint like Calvin
pissing on Snoke?
On his body?
Yeah, on his dead body. On Snoke's dead body?
Remember he died. I certainly do
remember. He didn't just go into a tunnel.
He didn't go into a tunnel of ambiguity.
Snoke hasn't returned yet.
Yes. But somehow
in episode 12, Snoke could return.
If they give me the keys to the Star Trek
Wars. No, do it.
If they give you the keys to Star Trek, get Snoke
in there. That'll surprise everybody.
You'd never see it coming. Snoke shows up.
Yeah. No, here she is.
Sabine Wren is now appearing
for a limited time in Galaxy's Edge.
How about that?
Okay. Well, took the helmet off.
It's on a phone far away from me.
No, right? Fair enough.
But, you know, maybe that'll
draw some people from Vandesmic. I don't
know. A question.
Will the dragon come back?
What is this going to be? So a really, really quick
history. Original dragon
was a big head on a cherry picker.
I kind of liked it. I kind of like
spindly, old school
dragon. I like it too.
Yeah, I don't know. I liked it.
He just kind of became abstract
and he was a wiry guy.
I almost found the second one like goofier
with his big pot belly.
What damage is
this guy going to do? If he has to take
one step, he's screwed. It's all about
fire breath. If Mickey runs 10 feet
away, that guy ain't running.
I think this is a perfect, I don't think
they can do it, but
I would love it if there was some drone
element at the end.
Some sort of drone thing.
And I don't know, because we've talked
about this before, there were patents filed by
Disney for drones to like
puppet giant marionettes down
Main Street, which I think are not
against, it's against the law to put drones
over the guest's head.
This is over the river.
That's what I'm saying. So this almost feels like
this is the perfect place in Disneyland to do it
because you don't have to have them
over the guest's head.
But what is that going to be?
How is it not just a bunch of drones?
Well, I don't, that's a
good question. I haven't really thought this through,
but it could be some
drones making the shape
of a head or a character, because they can do
that now. They have the technology
to do that. But if it's the
puppeting where like, you know, you have four
drones basically
acting as if they're a puppeteer hands,
just put a big Pinocchio at the
finale. Yeah, I was going to say, I have a really
famous puppet. Pinocchio gets puppeted at the end
and Mickey just kind of hangs out with them.
So the dragon is replaced by
Pinocchio? It's just a
fun dance? There's not a fight?
Well, it could be evil.
It could be evil, but I think it would be better if
they just have a nice dance. Pinocchio
and Mickey just have a nice dance.
You don't have the tension to get out of Fantasmic.
Yeah, it's too stressful is one of my
problems with Fantasmic. I just would like Mickey
and big Pinocchio. Big
Pinocchio. Like a two-story Pinocchio.
You make Pan a puppet and I hate him
more. You make Pinocchio big.
Big. Oh, God. Yeah.
And then the drones just sort of pilot him
kind of going up and down. I'm going to go light this
show on fire. I will
swim through the
balloon or whatever it's called.
I'll kill the drones. I'll kill this mega Pinocchio
before it kills us. Okay. Well, how about this?
How about a big, evil Stromboli?
And he tries to puppet Mickey.
So Mickey's got to shoot fire
at him and then Stromboli just goes
up like
kindling like a deep-fried turkey on
Thanksgiving, you know?
Flash, like what do they call it? Flash
frying? Flash fry, thank you.
Well, you know what? I love
that. I think Stromboli is a more
relevant villain
than most because
he is an evil
show business
character with a certain look
and does he not, you know, he's like the
warning to not get
to be very careful
if you're going into the show business direction.
Is he not the original Harvey
Weinstein? Absolutely.
So to see him go up in
flames, would that not
be, that might scare a lot
of kids out of child acting.
Future Tara Noah-Smiths,
who left the industry correctly
to follow his submersible passion.
You know, if anybody's
tugging on their mom's shoulders, I want to act.
You put a big Stromboli in front of
him, that'll send him running the other way.
Very good point. Sure. So yeah,
more Stromboli maybe just in general at
Disneyland then. He's everywhere.
Stromboli on Main Street.
Hey, you will come with me!
Around any turn, there
could be a giant Stromboli. Giant
honest John?
Yeah. Well, honest, yeah.
But put Stromboli in Galaxy's Edge
too. Yeah.
Now, all right, again,
I'm about IP Surprise.
Snoke and Star Trek. Stromboli
and Star Wars. Right. Now
I'm interested. Now we're innovating.
Unkar Plot was kind of Stromboli-esque.
Unkar, oh, Unkar Plot was not
a Stromboli, you think? I mean.
You don't, I don't think so. I think he had
roped Rey into like
kind of a shady business deal
for that inflatable bread.
Well. For that big, for that quarter
portion. Yeah, he wasn't on
the level, but I don't know that he was so
nefarious. I didn't get
that from Unkar Plot in his
brief time. You think so?
He's no Stromboli. I don't think Unkar
Plot is a Stromboli. They're odd areas
because neither of them are like
Satan, but. Right. But Stromboli
is a bad guy. Yeah. He's a bad
dude. Unkar Plot might have
a heart of gold. We just don't know. Does he have
anybody in, does he have a droid in a cage back
there? And does he tell the droid you'll never be
a real boy? I hope
not. I had a good feeling about Unkar
Plot, honestly, until Jason said that.
So he's really. I don't know why you'd have a good
feeling of it. Maybe like no feeling,
maybe neutral, but I don't think he's a good
guy. Well, I had a good feeling about,
I enjoyed him. You're behind the
scenes knowledge that Simon Pegg was
in that outfit.
Was he? Oh yeah. I think he might be
right. Yeah. I think he did play.
But that might have been coloring your reflection.
Maybe that's what it is. You know what's also coloring
my reflection is that one of the best parts
of the sequel trilogy, and I mean this sincerely,
is that bread. Oh yeah.
That bread is so fun
and good. Yeah. And is one of the
top five things in those sequel trilogies
maybe. Maybe top ten. So
being that you associate him with the
bread. I do. As far as you know, he might have invented the
bread. Yes. So. It's possible
he invented the bread. Who could be bad
if you invent magic bread? Yeah.
Hmm. So. All right. I'll give you that. He needs
to be in, put him in Batuu.
It's insane. Smack in your leg.
You're insistent on this. Well there's, it's fun.
Give me fun stuff. He's from
the sequel trilogy that's in the same timeline.
He didn't get killed in the movies. You know what, juice up
mobile pickup.
You know, mobile food ordering.
Juice up the pickup spot.
Have an Unkarplud animatronic
screaming at people. Oh, okay.
I see what you're saying. Faster. Yeah.
Well and then not selling the bread is a mistake too.
We've talked about this before on the show. Well I think they were
for a little while. Were they?
But as like, it was just a custard. What do you mean the bread's
made up though? You can't do
the bread really. I want the bread. You put some
green sponge cake on top of a custard.
I want the bread more than I want the milk. Yeah.
I want the bread from seven more than I want the blue
milk. I don't care about the milk anymore.
I'm never gonna try that milk again. I did it
opening weekend. No interest in having the
milk over again. Did you try the green milk?
I don't remember.
It's a little more herbal. I don't care.
I want the bread. Wow. We tried one
of it. You can get a little
you know, little. Oh you get a little.
Now we're talking. Now we're talking.
Little nip in there, you know.
I get my flask out. I put a little on the green milk.
I was about to say that you guys were recovering some of
the old person energy until
you called it a nip. Nip
took it for ten more years.
Of a little sip of alcohol. I want
to say also just on the way out
the door. I was
inspired by Mickey. I was starting to use my
imagination. And I thought
of a little show.
I don't know where it goes and
how we could do it. But I did start
conjuring a little show called Phantasmike.
It's a journey
into your imagination
Mike. Where you use
the power of your imagination
to get Prince and Bono to come to your
birthday.
In this world they have
very busy schedules. But when they
hear that a cool
youthful seeming guy with a really
chill vibe is having a birthday
they drop everything so they could come
be a part of it. You gotta
have villains as part of this.
Of course. So the villain
is me. It's a green version
of me. I show up and say
people don't really know the
song Black Balloon by the Goo Goo
Dolls. Oh yeah it's making me mad
hearing the dialogue. I know. As angry as you've
gotten every time this has come up.
But you Prince and Bono show
me you lead an all star
jam for 20
minutes of Black Balloon.
Olivia Rodrigo shows up for the first half
and she cuts out of there.
And I melt
and scream. And
Dr. Chase Meridian and Minnie come and
give you kisses on the cheek.
One each though makes like
I don't want it to be excessive. Hey
use your imagination. Wait your imagination
is to keep it limited?
Yes just one on each cheek.
Minnie on the right. Shit Dr.
Chase on the left. And then they leave.
Yeah yeah good. You
advise them, girls you look
a little chilly. Might want to throw on a light sweater.
Not a sweatshirt. Ladies do you have a light
sweater? Yes that's a good
plus up for the end of it. Watch out for drifts.
Okay yeah no I like all
of that. I think that's nice and wholesome.
Are you big? Are you a big
robot or some kind or? Yeah
I think I could be. Yeah yeah. Why not
a stromboli style. Okay.
Alright I'm all the villains.
We're mashing up villains like you were saying.
So I'm all the villains. I am massive.
I am green. And I
have a big stromboli beard. And you have
the puppet lines by your mouth as
well. You know what I'll give it. It's your show.
It's your imagination.
And since I'm the one
who's ruining this beloved song
for you. You can paint me any way that you
want. Can he have Chernabog wings?
Chernabog what? Wings. Oh I like
that. I don't mind this.
This is cool. You know
I was actually pretty old when I
learned the name Chernabog.
That seems like something I would be an
annoying 12 year old about. I think
I was pretty old by the time I heard
the name Chernabog and knew what it was.
I think I was an older man when I
knew what I learned. I was something
years old. I'm sure I definitely
told people who were not asking
that the wizard named Yen Sid
was Disney backwards.
That old crone.
Yen Sid. The famous old crone.
Mickey's mentor. The original
wizard.
That stops him from dreaming.
That's a real, that's a relevant
villain as well. If Stromboli's like Harvey Weinstein
Yen Sid
is the boss who doesn't want upward
mobility. Who probably doesn't pay
very well. Who doesn't like
you turn the other way while
the employee uses the
facilities to pursue their dreams.
You don't need a union.
We're all family here.
Normal healthy units.
Families.
Those brooms tried to unionize on me
and I took away their ability to talk.
Did you know like only four
months ago all the brooms could talk. One zap
that was the end of that.
Can't talk back when you can't talk.
So you knew that years before
you knew Chernobyl. I feel like that was like
did you know kind of fact
at the Disney hotel room channel
or around MGM studios
or something. And now you're
a professional did you know factologist.
That's really
isn't that what this is. The most beloved
kind of person on planet earth.
People love it. That's all
I know. The most likable type.
That's what we are.
Well did you know
that there is a whole
other world of Fantasmic
at Disney World in Florida.
Disney's Hollywood studios. And did you
know that if we talked about that
this episode would get much longer.
So here is my proposition
that after Fantasmic
finally returns after the by then
more than a year hiatus
when we determine what that
ending is
in the lack of a dragon. If it is a giant
flaming stromboli. If it is just
a nice Pinocchio made of drones.
We'll see. I propose
that the episode is we talk about that.
We say do we like that or not.
We talk about Disney World version.
We talk about Tokyo version.
Which I saw.
So you know just a big
old potpourri
of the rest of Fantasmic.
We like the sound of that. I think we love it.
Ok great. Well that will be coming
down the road. Which means we can
close out this one.
Unless there's any further thoughts about
temperatures, conditions
in which light shawls or sweaters
should be packed. I will say this.
I don't have any other thoughts about
windiness. But
ever since we talked about city food I've been
hungering for a firehouse sucks.
You can always go to the
North Hollywood location.
That's like $2 cheaper.
I know where that is. I think we should go there.
I will say this.
I don't. Ok.
The brand. If you want to try
the brand again.
That makes sense to me. But the idea that you would
specifically want to go back
to the city firehouse subs
post piece of plastic
in the sandwich. Which Jason described
online as just a little nub.
Just a little nub. One of the most disturbing
things you've ever said.
Saying a lot. That's
where I draw the line. There has
been a thing
nubbing at me since the city.
I let this pass. This was in the last
main feed episode which was the finale with
Weiger. There was a point. I don't know
maybe I was just like preparing for the next thing. Maybe
I wasn't listening to you carefully enough Mike.
But what the thing was
when I was editing I found it.
And you said well I have the strongest stomach
of all of us. You talking about yourself.
Because Jason gets tummy aches.
And Scott you know he gets sick.
And he throws up.
When I was watching it back in editing I was like
why didn't I say something. I don't.
I do not.
This only happens at two places.
City Walk Hollywood.
And City Walk Orlando. I do not
regularly have stomach
problems. And I let it happen.
I let you toss it all out.
Scott and his weak trembly stomach.
It's basically made of liquid.
It can't even retain anything.
Scott basically eats paste.
And even that he throws up a little bit.
Gosh. Look I wanted to be.
I shouldn't have said the fire off subs thing obviously in hindsight.
But I mean look.
There's no better place to test your metal.
As far as eating is concerned.
And your stomach is concerned than City Walk.
This clearly is the premise.
What I am saying. I don't want
my metal tested. This is the only
place where my metal is in question.
These are not regularly
problems. Now Jason. I feel like
sparkling water makes Jason sick.
Jason's all.
He's got his banana in the morning.
His stomach is an issue. I really
don't. It's a weird. So.
As you say I have the
strongest stomach. You know
Scott has. But this is not a problem. I don't want
to be cured of this. I don't
want it to be loosened up. I feel like
I'm Hercules. Hang on. Hang on. I'll let
you say that. But you can. I'll only if you call
yourself City Walk Hercules. I'm City
Walk Hercules. All right.
I'm City Walk
Hercules. I like
that. I like the weird dubbed movie
version of Hercules that you're doing. I can eat
a pound of candy from its sugar
and then a shake from
Dr. Toothsome and then three
pieces of plastic from Firehouse
Subs. An entire
nub Sunday.
I would laugh in its
face. I wish Harryhausen was still
with us to make City Walk Hercules.
One nub baked into each meatball
please.
Can I have it with nubs?
Whatever plastic you put around
your food leave it on.
Oh, you were already going to?
Wonderful. His only
weakness is flounder almondine.
That's the only weakness he has. And even
that didn't make him puke or throw up
or anything. It just made him bite his mouth.
Just made you bleed.
Yeah. But it's
stomach. No more City Walk for months.
We won't even say the word. I swear.
I don't swear. You know what?
But I swear. I don't swear.
All right. Well, with
that, tribute to City
Walk Hercules. We'll give you a victory
parade. As we say, you survived
Podcast the Ride.
Glad to be back in
Theme Park World. Although, you know, we might step
back a little nub at a time.
For three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride, The Second Gate. Or get
one more bonus episode on our VIP
tier, Club 3. Eventually
more phantasmic coming. You will find
all of that at patreon.com
slash Podcast the Ride.
I kind of want to
end it with Jason saying
wait here, I'll whisper it to you.
Mickey's last line.
Some imagination, huh?
Jason saying it as Mickey.
Forever
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott
Gardner, Brett Boehm,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe
to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever
you get your podcasts. Keep up
with the latest Forever Dog news by
following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page
on Facebook.
Thanks for watching.