Welcome to Podcast the Ride the Second Gate, the best podcast Patreon in all the land,
don't you deserve the best. I'm Sky Gardener, there's my Carlson. Hello, I'm my Carlson and
I'm sure that's the only time you're gonna hear the voice today. I won't promise it. Getting it
out of the way now. There's no way. I don't feel like I need to do the voice. Yes, but you don't
want to be sweaty or desperate. Oh no, there I am doing it again. Jason. Hi, I'm here too. Oh no,
Jason got extra timid. He went the other way. I got scared by the loud voices. Oh no, it's Jason,
Jason like slash, I don't know, like what's a fun like child character? What's the most famous child
character of all time? Oh, Lilo? Yeah, Jason mixed with Lilo. Lilo's not a coward. What about Cindy
Luhu? Was that a Cindy Luhu style voice perhaps? Mr. Grinch, whatever she says. I don't know if
any of these are the most famous child character of all time, though I'm struggling to come up with
a replacement. Kevin McAllister. Oh, the most famous child character of all time, Peter Pan,
the boy who doesn't grow up. But that wasn't a Peter Pan, that was more of like little Michael.
Yeah, the eighth most popular lost boy. Yeah. Yeah, one way towards the back. He's got like,
he's not even a key, he's not even a rabbit or a fox or you know what they wear on their heads.
I'll watch your flank or no, I'll watch your back. Oh God, guys, I'm starting to think I should grow
up. I like the cut of your jib kid. That's right. No more of this eternal kid. You're the least
creepy of the bunch, kiddo. I don't think I went around this island anymore. I just want to like
send emails, send an office and do email. That's right. We vilified Peter Banning and his big cell
phone, but I say get on the big cell phone. Start moving and shaking, getting things done in this
world. Yeah, I just want to send emails as a really interesting. It is kind of a good encapsulation
of adults in most of what being an adult is. Yeah. Yeah, either hard labor or email job. Those
are your two options. Right. We chose email job, I guess. Yeah, emails. Much closer to it. What it is,
I'd say, unless it is a performing job. And that's what we're talking about today is a particular
performing job. And I don't think we've settled yet as we recorded on what we're calling it,
but what we're focusing on is the Gaston face character in the parks. Right. Or I don't know
if we call it walk around Gaston. I don't know if we call it meet and greet Gaston.
There's versions of it. I met and greeted him years ago. I think it's Gret. I think Gret is the
met and greeted. You met and you met and you met and Gret. And then he beat the shit out of you.
Yes. Beat the shit out of you. Right, the shit. But then he walks around sometimes, too. So I
think it depends. So it's like, I was going to also for part of me was like, oh, yeah, they don't do
this in Disneyland. So we'll call it Walt Disney World Gaston or something. And I'm like, no,
they do do it in Disneyland. I've seen videos of it, but I've never seen him in Disneyland.
Yeah. And he's in the he's been in the shows perennially. That's another way to experience
Gaston is in the Beauty and the Beast musical. But that's not what this is. I mean, we're focusing,
I think, on the particular type that they started doing in 2012 with the new Fantasyland expansion,
where you can get in a line, have a moment with Gaston and, you know, who obviously is the
antagonist of Beauty and the Beast, who is a very barrel chested, egotist cheeseball.
Sure. And boy, have they encapsulated the character really well in these meet and greet
moments that you get that they have just gone full throttle and let these these fun park
performers go nuts. Yes. Let me ask this, though, because you came up with the phrase off-brand
Doc Brown. Do you think this is off-brand off-brand Gaston? I don't, because the rules
change when you are moving mediums from animation to a live person. I think what feels so weird
about another Doc Brown walking around is that we know that that's supposed to be Christopher Lloyd.
Right. And also they get the wig so wrong so often. Yeah. That's that's a separate aspect,
as opposed to this, where I think the wigs are immaculate, the wardrobe is immaculate. They get
the open chest right. They get the muscles right. Yes. And I also, Christopher Lloyd, I guess,
is just so specific of a performer. It's just you're always going to be like, that doesn't
really, that's not quite the character. Yeah. But I don't know, there's something about Gaston that
I feel like so many different people can play him. I've seen so many different videos of him being
played by different people. And I go, oh, that's good. And that's good. And that's right on. And
different flavors. Some people get, you know, some people get the look exactly right. Sometimes it's
attitude. Sometimes it's voice. Yeah. But it's always, yeah, I don't know, it's become a fun,
open-ended assignment for performers to put their stamp on. And I don't want to sidetrack.
And what I'm going to mention is going to be old news by the time the
listeners hearing this, but it's impossible for me to ignore. And I'm curious if it's the same
for you guys, because I guess what I'm asking is, is it tough for you guys on this particular
morning, Thursday, April 11th, to record this episode under the shadow of the surprise
announcement of the death of American icon OJ Simpson? Maybe, you know, to me, it is a massive
elephant in the room. To you guys, the elephant might not even be in the room. But I need to,
we didn't even talk about it as small talk on the way into record. I think I need to process a tiny
bit. Sure. On the Gaston episode specifically, you think? I do. Well, and you know, it tied
together in my head, I think, because I think there are some similarities between Gaston and
the dearly departed OJ Simpson. You know, a strapping guy, an incredible physical specimen. Yes.
Huge, imposing, muscular, you know, lives among all of his totems of his achievements. That's
true, yeah. You know, but also not great attitudes towards women. You know, wants them to be
subjugated and domesticated. And Gaston also, as we learn, is, I don't know if he doesn't get to do
it in the film ultimately, but he certainly desires to murder. Well, because a beast,
of course, you're referring to Gaston's attempted murder of the beast. Yes, yeah, yeah. He not only,
you know, he's got the dark charisma of OJ Simpson to where he can lead a group to, you know,
to all want to do this terrible thing together. I mean, if you, maybe, you know, the angle,
if you would come in with more of like a Here's Lucy guest star has passed away.
That's more of what I'm like, well, now I'm ready. Was he not? I feel like he, what is the,
I wonder what the most up your alley thing is. I mean, I've definitely seen OJ doing magic
as introduced by Bea Arthur. Well, he was on Here's Lucy. Yeah. And he was, oh, he was.
That's what I'm saying. He was on Here's Lucy. Yeah, yeah. Okay. Has this come up before?
It has. And does this qualify as a PTR curse? This might be the third time I've brought it
up on the show, actually. I'm pretty sure. I'd believe it. I'm pretty sure. Uh-huh. Here's Lucy
tends to be, that's just one of those like erasers for me. Here's Lucy, yeah, well, for the, for the
public. Not, I love Lucy, but you throw here's in there and then I immediately forget the fact. Well,
I love Lucy, Lucy Show, then Here's Lucy, which ran for like seven years. And it's full of. Like
more than the, are there more Here's Lucys? There might be. Yeah. I actually don't know that off,
but yeah, there were. OJ is in the episode with Ginger Rogers, right? And they all make a line
and they're like, well, I think I still got it. And they all do a little dance. That is right.
You're not making a joke. Huh? That's real, right? No, I am making a joke. Oh, okay. I don't know. I
believe it. Absolutely. OJ and Ginger Rogers. Except when did Ginger Rogers die? That'd be my
biggest question. Doesn't matter. She was on Here's Lucy after she is dead. You think, you think a
death is an obstacle to being booked on Here's Lucy? Also 1995, so she was alive. Here's Lucy,
you could be a ghost and appear on it. That's something you people don't know.
So that's why I was confused by Jason. What was so notable about the show is like it was the,
it was the first and only post-death appearance of many of the golden age of Hollywood's greats.
And Jason said that so confidently because I've seen the clip of OJ and Here's Lucy. I've not
seen the full episode. I didn't watch the full episode of Here's Lucy. No, I just said that
because there was a clip that went around a while ago. Oh, where she's dancing with her daughter
and Ginger Rogers. Yes. And Lucy LaValle and her daughter are dancing. Yes. And the crowd is loving
it. They're so excited to see the old, the old gang doing a little dance. Sure. Yeah. And I recently
brought up the, the Jackie Gleason appearance with, with Jack Benny on the Here's Lucy clip
that I just saw like a couple of weeks ago. OJ goes to speak. He's a guest speaker at a Beverly
Hills chamber of commerce luncheon planned by Lucy. Then there, then he helps him get into a USC
football game. Wow. He talks about his real life first wife, Marguerite, and his kids in it. Wow.
Which this website says gives it an eerie feel. But it all has an eerie feel now that we're,
now that we're talking about him having said goodbye to him. Sure. But anyway, well,
okay, obviously we got to do this then all of, we, we, we, we, we have to go through all of his
variety show sitcom appearances to properly send them off. Sure. Sure. Here, here's Lucy. Of course,
I first became aware of, uh, in the gift shop for Lucy attribute and there were all these DVDs.
I love Lucy, Lucy show. And I'm, I was standing there. I was like, what the fuck is this?
Here's Lucy. I think it's funny. I bring up like the, the death of a, like one of the most
memorable figures in history. And there's a little bit of interest in it, but here's Lucy
becomes, I'd like to talk about when I first saw it, here's Lucy DVD. Well, you're hosting
the show with two lunatics. I hate to tell you. Well, I was trying to try and tie back to Lucy
attribute. No, I'm on board with Jason. I'm back to Lucy attribute. We weren't on Lucy attribute.
Yeah. I'm Jason's right on my wavelength here. All right. Well then you, I'm sorry I interrupted.
Do you have anything to say about the first time that Jason learned about here's Lucy?
No, he wasn't done with his important story yet. Was, were you not? Was there more story?
Oh, no. I mean, I was pretty much done. Uh, the back of the DVD is explained. It was the show he
made, she made with her kids. Right. Yes. So I was like, oh, okay. That makes sense. I understand.
Now somebody calmed you down and said, no, no, read the back of the box. That makes sense. I
understand that. Yes. Before that you were livid. You were starting, you were foaming from the mouth.
I was. Get on compute. You thought you were going to seizure the death. I only knew two.
It was a Lucy show I don't know about. I'm not spending enough time with Mike Carlson, clearly.
Gail Gordon was on this too. I believe playing her brother, not Mr. Mooney, her boss. By the way,
club three subscribers, uh, get Gail, just somebody suggest Gail Gordon as a topic for the next poll
so that we can see it land right around 2%. Let's just watch it coast right in there.
One of these days I'm going to have a big victory with one of these and it's going to shock the
nation. That's why I stay consistent with it. I think. And, uh, you know, um, yeah, keep,
keep aiming in the right, the same direction. Somebody point, somebody pointed out the new
Beetlejuice trailer. A Beetlejuice says the juice is loose at the end of it, um, which yeah,
that's interesting. Yeah. And now he was the, OJ was the nickname was the juice. And now it's,
they obviously can't include this in the film, but now OJ could hang out with Beetlejuice.
That's true. They could do reshoots, I suppose. And do that. I mean, they can't, I mean more
like in the war, if we believe that Beetlejuice is real. And we do. Yeah. Yes. Yes. And we do.
Putting on daily graveyard reviews, uh, in, in, in where does he live? Does he live in hell? What
is Beetlejuice's afterlife? That's a good question. There's probably a name for it that I don't
remember. I haven't seen the movie in a long time. I like the movie. Uh, this movie also is
going to be very serious. It's just very serious. It feels, you know, the tone is the, I mean,
when I heard the serious day, Oh, it was the serious day. Oh, one thing I never liked about
Beetlejuice one is they, they took, they were so flippant about day. Oh, daylight come and me want
to go home. Right, right. Isn't it? Isn't that a joke? I don't know. Every real, every trailer does
serious versions of, I thought that was a parody of every trailer doing. I think you're giving
them a lot of credit. I'd like to believe that Jason, but I feel like I've seen it with dumber
songs. I have gone back and forth on it. There's also the same like Ecto one reveal dusty pull away
and it's the little town, the same like you remember this thing when you were little, here it is under
a dusty cloth, a dusty blanket. I don't remember if they did this, but I, I, I bet probably there
was like a, you know, an eerie sounding six year old girl saying an invisible man sleeping in your
bed and then it gets dubstep. That's another important thing about current trailers. We have
to do dubstep the 13 year old musical genre. We have to slow down songs, then dubstep them.
Yeah. Yeah, for sure. I hope we know this never changes. This is, this is trailers forever.
Anyway, sidetrack got us off the, I just wanted to, it's, it's on my mind. Sure. It just happened.
This whole time we're recording, it's like, I'm imagining a hulking OJ Simpson behind me. Right.
Upset if I don't acknowledge him. Well, again, like Jason, I want to remember the simpler times
when he was dancing with Ginger Rogers and Lucio Ball and her children, you know, that's the way
we're thinking. Yeah, a nice memory. We Mandela affected ourselves. From now on it was, it was
on the Ginger Rogers episode. Yeah, sure. And if, if that wasn't the case, then we can AI it very
easily. But again, you know, I, oh, I read the weirdest AI article about Don Knotts yesterday
that said Don Knotts shot himself in the head on Sullivan's show. AI prompts, come up with an
exact sentence that Mike Carlson would say. Yeah, I am AI, but literally the story was just, it was
like saying it was a history that Don Knotts had pulled a gun out on the stage at the Ed Sullivan
show and shot himself in the head on live TV. And I'm like, this did not happen. I know. Sorry. Wait,
who said Don Knotts shot himself? This AI article I was reading yesterday. Claimed that. Don Knotts
had killed himself on the Ed Sullivan show, live on the air.
Okay. Well, this is, I was reading about Don Knotts and going, I agree. Don Knotts was alive in the
nineties. This isn't true. Unless he went back to the, like, I don't, I don't exactly know how he
died. I don't think that he went to the David Letterman, now hosting a theater, the Ed Sullivan
theater and killed himself there. Well, I, I, I was reading this and I'm like, this is, it didn't
say it was AI, but I assumed it was AI. Unless there was a sick, twisted person trying to make
people think that this happened to Don Knotts. Is this close enough in your history, you could say
the name of the website that- You can take a look. A website that is a source of AI Don Knotts
articles. Yes. And why, how did you, what do you think was the Google prompt that led you
to an article that said Don Knotts killed himself? I think I was looking up with Don Knotts' death.
I think I was looking up- Well, Mike was looking at his favorite website. It's called ZergNet and
it's at the bottom of all websites. And he's like, wait a minute. You were just, just calming
yourself at the end of a long, busy day with reminding yourself how Don Knotts died. I swear
we'll talk about Gaston. We will, but I am curious. I do want to know, I want to know the history. I
want to know the search that led you here and then what is this so that we can all not trust
this website. Was it InsideTheMagic.net? I'm looking so far, the first Don Knotts results I've had
from yesterday is when I was looking up Don Knotts as Les Calhoun, his character from Matlock,
where he would join the show later and it was just Andy Griffith's neighbor.
And there's like a compilation of Les Calhoun clips that I was watching.
Uh-huh. How many hours a day of your life are devoted to Don Knotts?
Yesterday, 20 minutes or so, 22 minutes perhaps.
If you average that out, some days it's more like 40, some days are tough, you only get four.
Okay, here it is. It's RobotMonkeys.net.
So we can't trust RobotMonkeys.net anymore?
No. And then it said, on June 30th, 1963, comedic actor Don Knotts shot himself in the head with a
.38 caliber revolver during the live airing of the Ed Sullivan show. And I was like, that's,
that is not true. I know. I'm smart. I know what happened. And that did not happen. So then there's
a whole like, there's a decent amount of text here about this fake thing that didn't happen.
So this is, this is what you get up to when we aren't with you. We need to record more episodes
to try to stop you from going down these rabbit holes. Jason, we need to start committing to six
episodes a day to keep Mike away from dangerous ends of the internet, like RobotMonkeys.net.
This wasn't going to come up. This was for me. I didn't tell anyone about this.
I may have sent Andrew Grissom the less Calhoun compilation, but other than that,
I wasn't going to tell anybody about this. This just organically has come up.
Yo, you're so embarrassed and upset that suddenly you found yourself talking about Don Knotts's
I'm not embarrassed. I'm just explaining this was for me. This was not for-
I did not want to talk about this. Don't make me talk about it.
Don't make me sing. Yeah. Like this is a real, oh gosh, how embarrassed. Yeah.
Then I get to talk about less Calhoun, Don's famous character. That was not the,
what's Mr. Furly and then Barney. We were almost on our way to a particularly
tidy episode. We almost got there. Like the top of it was really tight. It was my fault.
I of course know that it was my fault. Oh wait, but now I'm like, any results for Don Knotts,
O.J. Simpson? I do, is this real? I'm looking at a photo of O.J. doing a stick up with a gun
in 1980 at Knotts Berry Farm. Oh my God, really?
Is this photoshopped or is this real? Whoa. I don't know.
Why would this be made up? I don't know.
Why would the Ed Sullivan show be made up? Yeah, that's true.
You think that's real? I don't know what to trust anymore.
It's hard to know what to trust on the internet. But unless you're like a real Don Knotts scholar
who really knows about his life, like I kind of am, an amateur scholar of Don Knotts' life,
but you're not going to be able to know. Now we're precariously in the zone of having
to declare a false start, which we could do, but I think we can veer it back. I think we can get
there. I just won't even try to do a tidy segue. Well, you know, Don Knotts is not the physical
specimen. That guest John is. No one fights like Don Knotts.
No one mugs like Don Knotts. No one stays on Mike Carlson's mind like Don Knotts.
Okay. 2012, new fantasy land expansion. An area opens called the Enchanted Forest,
and this is a bigger committed to Beauty and the Beast land within a mini land within an expansion.
And I kind of thought about how much real estate they gave Gaston.
Because you've got Gaston's tavern now. You can go into the bar where he has songs sung about
himself and he uses antlers in all of his decorating. There is a really fun statue out there,
which is him kind of holding a bunch of barrels that water is pouring out of using the area.
That's the fountain aspect. He's stepping on a very beleaguered LeFou, his constant companion.
The plaque, I think, says that the statue is twice polished by LeFou.
So this whole zone is very fun using the egotistical nature and the put upon nature of LeFou.
For a while, they had a variant of the turkey leg, which was a big pork shank.
You could get and eat as if you were Gaston eating a big pork shank. It doesn't appear
that is on the menu anymore. You think the pork shank is gone?
I think the pork shank is gone. What's on the menu at Gaston's? Because I think there was
like kind of a, they don't sell alcohol there, but you could get something that was kind of
like a kid's fun drink. Yeah, I thought it was funny. I do have this in front of me.
Meal period snack. And then the section is labeled quick bites. So if you want a Quibi,
go to Gaston's Tavern. And they have the gray stuff cupcake, which you can also get at Disneyland,
which is a pretty fun dessert. I did think it was weird that like, okay, so Gaston's Tavern,
they've got to have some big meaty like shanks. That makes sense to me that they started there,
but now it's a ham sandwich. You get a ham sandwich with chips.
Ham sandwich or wormson and roll. Or the cupcake.
And then non-alcoholic like fizzy apple juice, essentially, which is funny to imagine, you know,
the machismo of that tavern in the movie. And in real life, you can go there and drink apple juice
and have a ham sandwich and chips. Uh-huh. You know, it's like Jason's tavern.
I was going to say Jason, the worms, warm cinnamon roll and apple juice.
You kidding me? That's like your heaven. I honestly, I never really saw any like glowing
reviews of the pork shank. Pork also works. I never saw like that. I don't think caught on
like the turkey leg. For one thing, I feel like that is very greasy.
Yeah, it might not be. Well, I mean, turkey leg and they've, I feel like they've engineered
the turkey leg over time to be a tidier meal, even though it's not, it's still like a giant thing.
I'm looking at it on disneyfoodblog.com and this, what I'm looking at is pretty disgusting.
It doesn't look good. I know it looks like very fatty and kind of disconcertingly
white and then the, the big bone. Uh, unless this is AI generated, like, I don't know what
website, I can't research live on the air anymore. Right. I'm going to run into one of these monkey
situations. Right. Monkey robot. What is it? Monkey robot. And there's, wait a minute. They said they,
they served monkey shanks here once too. That can't be right. Right. It was a much more robust menu.
Yes. When I went the first time, I feel like it was more robust even. And yeah, they didn't,
yeah. You run into the problem, of course, where it's like a G rated movie and you can't like
serve beer in there. I guess I'm trying to think of an example of a place where was, is there anywhere
that's like technically themed to a G rated movie where they are selling alcohol at all?
Like, is that, is that the problem? Is there no precedent for that? Where isn't, um, I was going
to say Mario. There's no alcohol in Mario land. No, no alcohol in Mario. Um, you can, can't you get,
uh, in Toy Story land. Minions. Minions. Yeah. Minions cafe. You can get a beer in there or
something. You can get some tall boys. Yeah. And right across from Minions and Secret Life of Pets
is that dreaded, uh, tavern where you can, you can get hammered. A den of debauchery. A den of
debauchery. Yeah. You can have a puppet. You can add the, the puppet from Secret Life of Pets. The,
what? The puppy or puppet? There is a, there's a puppet sort of like the New York street actors.
Oh, there's one of the character from Secret Life of Pets in those facades that'll yell at you. Oh,
okay. So yeah, you can get hammered and get yelled at by a puppet. Yeah. Which is pretty fun. But is
there a Disney example of that? Probably not, right? Toy Story. I think you can, I think, yeah,
you can get beer in Toy Story. In Toy Story land. Mm-hmm. In Woody's, like, lunchbox. I think so. Is
that, or is that just the stand? I forget. I think so. I remember because it was brought up,
like, again, as all things alcohol are. This was brought up years ago by Jason, like,
and you can get beer in the Toy Story, but it's always brought up as if, like, you can watch a
live sex show in a theme park. It's always the tone. Oh, boy. Wait, so you'd be okay with that,
Jason? Well, after dark, you know, if it was, like, an after hours event. It's alcohol always
scandalous. Live sex at a theme park. This we're okay with. What if there was, after 9 p.m. on the
Great Movie Ride, they would switch one of the scenes out for just a porno. Or just, like,
yeah, rotate it around. Or something. Yeah. And Great Movie Ride would now just have one scene
that was a porno. Wow. Like, Footlight Parade isn't there anymore. It's just a porno in its place. No.
Oh, wait, sorry, sorry. The Great Spank Movie Ride. Okay, sure. Yeah, yeah. Well, even if they could
do it during hour, they should just have the Xenomorph has Little Mouth come out and Little
Mouth says, come up and see me sometime. Why? Oh, that, when you say live sex show, that's what you
mean. You want. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Maywest innuendo, yeah. I don't know if I can keep doing the episode.
I'm so aroused by that image. That's going to be in that new, that new Alien movie. I think that's
actually a scene in there. Whatever it's called, that Romulus, Alien Romulus, I believe is the
new Alien movie. Is there a TV show coming? I've lost track of the Alien. If there's a famous movie,
there's a TV show coming. It either was just canceled and they're doing a new one in two
years or it is coming. So I'm pretty sure there is like a Noah Hawley Alien show or something.
Yeah. They're doing, they're doing a, here's Lucy, like a prequel where it takes six seasons
to even get to Lucy. Right. Thank goodness. It will be so boring until. Yeah. Gail Gordon calls
herself Black Blood and then throws something in a river and that causes. It causes Lucy to be born?
Oh yeah. And then you see, you see a little shape form and then it sprouts a little bit of red hair.
Yeah. And you, if you listen close to him, it's very like guttural animal, but it sounds like
I want to be in that show. Okay. Who are we? I don't know. Gaston's Tavern.
Punchy one. Gaston's Tavern. Really? So yeah, they could, I guess, because of the Toy Story
precedent, they could have beer at Gaston's Tavern. I think like, well, I don't know what,
I don't know what the problem would be. Well, we're operating, we're operating.
They have wine in the Beauty and the Beast restaurant. What am I even saying?
Yeah. I think there actually may be many examples of alcohol in G rated movie places.
Why wouldn't you have a big stein of some kind and serve beer in Gaston's Tavern?
Because if Walt found out that there was, you know, Walt's intention was Castle Park. If there
is Castle, then alcohol can only be in three select places surrounding Castle. I guess it is
because it's in the Magic Kingdom and it can't walk around. No, you have to be seated and you
have to be served. So that's got to be what it is then. It's just that there's no seating at
Gaston's Tavern and they don't want you roaming like every other park where you're allowed to roam.
Because I don't know, you'll get it on, because Small World's too close by, I guess.
Like it's too, you'll dump it in, you'll dump the beer in the river.
The Small World's drugged out naked guy is what they've been fearing the entire time.
That's true, yeah.
That was Walt's vision. Walt actually saw all that in a vision with his last ounces of strength on
his deathbed. He drew exactly that naked guy.
Going into Small World.
And that's been in a vault at the studio. Like, I don't know, Walt saw something and I'm worried
that one day it'll happen. It's an apparition and we're going to see it someday.
Right.
And when that guy showed up on whatever he was on, all of Walt's worst nightmares came true.
The hand came out of the, Walt's hand came out of the grave.
I told you.
Give a big thumbs down.
Right. Yeah, no, he went right back in. He just was like, I wanted to see.
I'm going to be rolling down here, FYI.
But he said, the juice is loose.
Well, that's actually at Gaston's Tavern, the juice is loose.
The apple juice.
The apple juice, yeah.
And if you just, and if you like sugar highs, then the juice might get you a little juice.
Oh yeah. Have you been, have you been in there?
I think I just walked in, didn't buy anything. I just saw the Antler Room, which is great.
Which I, you know, I like that they have, as part of this expansion, that they gave Gaston
a big footprint because I do like Gaston. I always liked him in the movie. He's a great villain,
a fun villain. He turns so dark and murderous, but before that, he's a great love to hate
kind of character, a very funny blowhard that completely illustrates who Belle is,
that she is not like the three girls who together swoon over Gaston, who I guess were like,
they're like, any one of us, doesn't matter. Or all three at this, I mean, all three at the same
time would be the ideal, but yeah, but it shows you Belle's smarter than them.
Right. Or just, or has more refined taste.
Sure. And the song is fun. Like the song in the movie is funny. It's still funny.
Like it's kind of my favorite thing in the movie, even though the movie, I liked all of it.
Yes. Like, oh, this is really good. He's really funny.
It's always been very quotable to me. I don't remember what the, like,
I don't remember what the LeFou line is leading up to, I know.
Oh yeah. Yeah. It's a great voice. It's a, it's a, it's a wonderful bellow.
It's like in the wheelhouse. I like to stay in. It's one of the, he's one of the great bellowers.
And it's such a, like, it's funny that, I mean, I guess what it comes out at 91 and it's like,
I'm surprised it actually took them that long to put them in the, in the park because it's such a
fun character to do. And even still like, I'm surprised he's not in there more. I'm surprised
I haven't run into him in Disneyland because it seems like such a popular thing because all these
posts generally go viral, I feel, not all of them, but some of them. Well, and we're describing a
kind of old phenomenon. I feel like 2014, 15 seemingly was the time where these improvised
interactions in meet and greets had a pretty big viral footprint. And the view counts on some of
these are still immensely high and deservedly. So there seems to be, I mean, they're all really
funny, but there's one guy who really recurs and he's not exactly in that, like in that particular
voice range, but he, but the, like, he does just have this like blow hard. Whoa, what the fuck?
He's kind of like, he's almost like a situation kind of guy. Sure. Yeah. Just really what Gaston
is the original situation from Jersey shore. But boy, is he fun. Cause it's the same guy who
has the, um, I think there's a, I think there's a pushup contest situation where somebody
challenges them to do pushups. And I think there's the assumption, look, the muscles are fake,
the muscles in the suit are padded. So you might think maybe the guy's weaker under there,
but he'd boy, he did go for it with no preparation. This was faked or something,
but he ends up going, uh, one arm with it and the other guy crumbles pretty quickly.
Yeah. It almost feels like too perfect in a way. If it's completely impromptu, I don't know. I'm
not accusing anybody of anything. I'm just, it almost feels like planned in the perfect way that
it plays out where Gaston embarrasses this guy. It's really good. I saw a couple videos like that.
I think what it is is a lot of people can't do very many pushups. Well,
Gaston can probably do like a million pushups. Yeah. Oh, you're, so you're saying he,
maybe he's not like the strong man you might think he is. I think he needs an average shape
versus the average theme parkour. Well, I think he probably needs to be pretty fit when they're
casting, but I think they're like, how many pushups can you do? How much, what flex?
Could I, with the muscle suit, am I, I mean, maybe I've aged out of it, but could I do it with the
muscle suit? Could I play Gaston? Do you think I'm too, cause it's, I think height is a big thing too.
Height's a big part of it. But would it look, it might just look too strange. It'd be like,
why is Gaston so old and why his muscles don't even, they certainly aren't real.
I was going to say, why does Gaston seem so youthful? Like why is his Gaston so hip?
He might be 13. That's how youthful he is. Honestly, I feel like, can you even work when
they're, when you're that young? Whoa, this Gaston gave me a ride today and his shuffle went right
from Craig Finn to Haim. It was the reverse. Oh, excuse me. Haim to Craig Finn. Yeah. Well,
Haim, at least they're in their thirties. Craig Finn is in his fifties. I suppose so. Yeah.
So at least I'm like 10 years hip. I just mean in terms of cool music. Well, thank you for talking.
Also from the 2010s. Sure. Yeah. Wait, so you're okay. You're giving Mike credit for liking cool
music from the 2010s after a 10 minute stint about Don Knotts. Look, we all contain multitudes.
I contain multitudes. I love Haim. Love watching S.D. play the bass. Well, you should have pided me
down, Ed. So yeah, I was like, ah, I wonder, obviously these probably people are like 27,
28, but I do have the question of like how fit everybody is. And I don't, they don't probably
want, I doubt they want Gaston doing pushups constantly, nor do I think the performer Gaston
probably wants to constantly be doing pushup challenges. Yeah. Yeah. So no, if you're not
going to go viral, then what's the point? Right. Cause there was all the like, and I don't, there's,
I feel like I've seen this disputed, but there was that rumor for many years and there's pictures,
maybe there's one picture of that. You would say Andy's coming to Woody and Jesse and they would
fall over as in like the joke in Toy Story when they would, the toys would just flop down when
there would be a human. And then people were like, yeah, if this happened or if this was happening
regularly, they don't want like, Disney does not want this. It's messing up the suits. It's making
them dirty. It's dangerous. Yeah. So that, if it did happen, it was short-lived or there were certain
performers who tried it and it was like, no, this is becoming like, don't yell fire in a crowded
building. Exactly. Don't yell Andy. It's not worth the, yeah, there's free speech, but then there's
yelling Andy in a crowded Toy Story character gathering. Well, that's, you know, if you, if
the trick that people don't talk about is if you're at a crowded Toy Story gathering and you yell
fire, everyone will scatter. We'll just run in different directions, start freaking out.
That you can do. You can create a lot of pandemonium. They should have a thing in the new
Toy Story when a human tricks them all because they're so like, they never get tricked by humans.
I feel like, like sometimes they'll be like a little, like they'll make mess up a little bit,
but you would think once in a while, like potato head would just be walking and forget or like not
hear that the human walked in and you'd be like, oh, it would have happened once. They're not all
like, so like mentally sharp. Yeah, that's true. I bet you could, well, this is tough. I was going
to say, but you could catch some of them in a big net, but that probably get taken at security.
You could catch the Toy Story character in a big net. Yeah, you could catch the toy. Yeah. You get
them in a big net and they're like, sir, you can't bring your big net in here. It has to stay in that
locker outside the gate. You guys are hoping that Toy Story five is about somebody who cracked the
code. Yeah. I saw toys come to life and I'm going to prove it. Right. I'm going to out the world of
toys to everyone. Yes, that's what I would like it to be about. It's probably going to be about
the toys in like some situation where they're in like the human world and they have to like climb
a big like ladder and they can't cause they're small and that's what they're all about basically.
But this one is mostly going to be about a human character who's being driven mad because he saw
potato head walking across the floor for two seconds. I mean, what I, what I flashed to was
uh, Mr. Potato Head's caught and, and I, at first I thought, oh, is then, is he scared?
Is, you know, the jig is up now they know that we're alive, but I think the toys are smarter
than that and how do they maintain these rules? I think, uh, potato head needs to make sure whoever
saw him never leaves that room, potato heads gotta kill him. I, you know, uh, you know, he can put a
bunch of supplies in his back compartment. So I think you just, you just like, uh, thin little
wire and he can just like hop around, go jump up a guy behind the guy's neck and like, you didn't
see nothing and you'll never see nothing again. I was going to say the way, or one of his body
parts to one of them have like a point on it. Uh, well they all do a little bit, you know,
the mustache has the little like connector piece. So, uh, yeah, I think, I think, yeah, could potato
head quickly in an emergency fashion, his mustache into a shank? I, I'd say so. Well,
that's a good idea to survive. That's a good idea too. Yeah. Potato had not owned for subtlety,
but he can just wait for that person to be sleeping. They open their mouth. He just drops
an ear down there, clogs the airways. Yeah. Smart. Smart. Yeah. Yeah. Then waits for the body to go
to the corner, follows them to that. Like when they, once they like, oh, is this, it must have
been this ear. I put this aside as evidence. Then he can grab it, put it back. No need to ever
replace that air. The silent killer. Mr. Potato had. Yeah. Although he probably makes a lot of
noise with all that shit in his butt, like clonk clonk clonking around. If you have that much shit
in your butt, you're going to make a lot of noise. That's true. You're going to make a lot of clatter.
Or you put a handkerchief in there or something to like soften, you know, to push it all to the
side. Well, when you're, you're like moving to a new apartment or a house and you have a bunch of
glassware, you got to stuff it full of, you know, paper or newspaper. Yeah. So he's got to do that
in his butt. Cushion your fragils. Here's a good tag. You got to cushion your fragils. For Toy Story
five, Mr. Potato had, or any of the toys tries to call for help, but all the cell phones are
touchscreen nowadays. So his little plastic hand just keeps hitting the screen. Oh, that's pretty
good. Oh yeah. Cause they operated a phone in three, but now, now they need your fingerprints.
They need a face scan. That's a good bit. Yeah. My, my pitch reel for, for my pitch reel for Toy
Story five, uh, Toy Story versus small soldiers. Yeah. We bring the small soldiers in and they fight.
I think it's time. Yes. To bring these equal icons together. Yep. That's what I think. Uh, I think
that I would want to play Gaston. Everybody always says this quite like, what's the thing you would
want to do? Would you want to be on the Haunted Mansion? Would you want to work on Tower of Terror?
Cause you get to be a little creepy, a bit too weird. This Gaston does seem like it's the most
fun. Absolutely. This seems like, I mean, it'd be, it may be tiring cause you got to exert a lot of
energy, but this seems fun to do. Well, it seems like the quickest path in especially Disney theme
parks to hard funny. That's what I think you watch a lot of these videos and it is genuinely very
funny. There's a lot of like angles to work. There's, there's the ego and the, uh, out flexing
people, uh, even though the muscles are, are, are stupidly fake. Right. You get to do a little funny
fake chauvinism. I mean, in the really, the most viral of the videos, he, uh, Gaston gets into it
with a little girl who is really challenging to him and saying, the beast is going to beat you.
You're not going to win. The beast is going to win the race. Uh, and he gives it back. I mean,
the little girl, I think like clearly wins the interaction. It's pretty unbelievable,
but his comebacks are funny too. And that he's saying to a little girl, like go in the kitchen,
get in the kitchen, mom, keep her in the kitchen where she belongs. It is funny that they're like,
it feels like almost edgy for Disney theme parks to like, to do, uh, uh, fake chauvinism, you know,
like gentle roast battle, like gentle roast material. Yeah. Um, I, yeah, it's like a really
good spot for just like fast talking, fast thinking, uh, funny blowhard guys. And I guess if
you're asking, do you think you have what it takes to be one of those, what's the biggest roadblock
to you? It's okay. You got the, you got the stature and I think you put on the muscle suit and you're
okay. I think I'm okay. I mean, I think, I don't know that I'm necessarily people be like, oh look,
is that Gaston's dad or something? I don't know if that's like, it's there. You put on the wig.
Yeah, that's true. I mean, you might be a little older than the age range they're looking for at
this point, but well, if I get fillers in my face before I do it, or a little bit of Botox or
something, perhaps it would just help to create the illusion that I'm more of the original Gaston's
age. More fillers, Mike, you can't do anymore. You're going to get sick. Jason, stop talking
about that. That was a joke I made. I don't have fillers already. Wouldn't it be funny if I, I
don't know, injected hormone, if, if I put hormones in my face, stem cells and shot right into my,
you're always bringing up Sylvester Stallone and how funny it is that he looks the way he looks.
Isn't that weird boy? I would never do anything. I would never look up the specific brands of
everything he does. The type of HGH he's on. Yeah. I would never do that. You're just trying,
we know the Tulsa King, but isn't it time for a Tulsa Prince? I wasn't sure we were going to go,
I was like, is that going to become Burbank King, but you kept Tulsa and made it Prince.
Yeah, well, he's going to be the, the long lost son. Cause I'm younger than the Tulsa King. I
assume that's what he was going for. Jason is the Burbank Prince, first of all. Let's be honest.
This is the man here. He's been that way for, he's been the Burbank Prince for 15 years. Well,
this is what was in my head. Cause I was anticipating some of this, like, could any of us be
I think we all could be Gaston, honestly. Well, I mean, what, what occurred to me about who's in
the room, um, you know, within this room, there is, I would say, proportions similar to Gaston
and LeFou. Yeah, I knew that was coming. Yeah. But the, but the, the flip of it is that at least in
terms of our real personal dynamics, it's kind of a reverse because it's the tall one who's obsessed
with the short one. It is an inverse. That's true. That is you're a hundred percent correct about
that. I'm, I would be more than willing to play LeFou if Jason was Gaston. I'm willing to do it
right now if we want to do a little play acting. That'd be great. Like, Oh, should we go to the
Bob's big boy, Jason? What do you think? I was already there for breakfast. Oh, I know, but I'll
pay for your lunch. What do you think? Let's go to Coral Cafe, a different tiner in Burbank.
Oh, okay. Are you going to get the same meal you had for breakfast? Yes, I am. Okay. Of course,
Mr. Jason. Oh gosh. Jason's so great. Isn't he? Don't you think he's like the best?
These eggs are over hard. Send them back LeFou. I asked for over medium. Okay. Over hard. Is that
even a real, what does that even mean? I, I think I just always call it a fried egg, but I heard
someone ask if they, the waiter asked, do you want it over easy, over medium, over hard? Okay. Well,
Mr. Jason, Jay Staun, Jay Staun, are these over hard, Mr. Diner Man? No, I don't want them over
hard. Oh, you want them over easy. I want them, I want a firm yolk, but a little bit of yolk.
Jay Staun wants a firm yolk. That's one of the trademarks of his general days. But I want a
little bit of goo. Okay. He's got, he wants a little bit of goo on his eggs. Jay Staun
sometimes would have raw eggs, but he started throwing up too much from them. And now he has
very specific specifications that he wants his eggs. The guy who ordered the five dozen over a
hard eggs is sending them back. You cleared out big boy for the day. We don't have any more eggs.
We didn't have this problem with the buka de pepo last night. They knew exactly what
Jay Staun meant. Oh, wait a minute. Yeah. Well the way that would be like,
Jay Staun, isn't it, I thought it was Beppo, not Pep. No, it's Pepo. What do you mean?
It's Pepo, of course. Of course, I'm always saying it's buka de pepo. Anything you say, boss.
More giant dry, dry, dry meatballs, please. Is it hot? Oh, Jay Staun, is it hot dog day?
You dry cleaners yet? No, that's Friday, you fool. How many times do I have to tell you that?
Well, can we go to a different dry cleaner and I'll make you hot dogs and bring them and you can
eat them while we watch the dry cleaning take place. Make sure they take competitors coupons.
Oh, of course, Jay Staun. I'll do my research. We'll know. They'll just be like melting the
eatings. I swear they'll take the coupons. Dry cleaner to the stars. I know what they are. Of
course, you're one of the biggest stars here. Of course, Milton 80s dry cleaners to the star.
They are extremely famous. Of course, 7365. How many dry cleaners can brag about that?
Yes, we know you've said it more than five times on the podcast. That's for sure, Jay Staun.
You brought it up, boy. I know I did. You're right. Oh gosh, you're the greatest. You're right.
Talk about your loud shoes during your school plays again. No, we haven't heard that one before.
It gets more interesting every time, Jay Staun. They're at least two size too big.
Yeah, I love it. They're adult shoes. They're alive in your role.
No, every time the story grows more color. It's amazing, Jay Staun.
This is a great character. Suddenly we got Dooling LeFouz. The Burbank Prince, Jay Staun.
You're so commanding. You turn anyone around you into a LeFou.
Wow. Wow, wow. All right. I think that just goes to show you with a little bit more confidence,
a little bit more swagger, you could get us carrying around bags of to-go giant buka de bepo
meatballs. Another batch. Here you go, boys. What is this, 70 pounds? I'm going to have to
start pouring some of these on my head. It's cracking my vertebrae in my back,
but it's okay, Jay Staun. I'll carry it for you. No problem. I'll stand in the Voodoo Donuts line
for an hour. No problem. I'll buy you whatever you want. Oh, better. I've got windy tuna sandwiches
to eat. And then I'll go up and I'll check the firehouse subs for pieces of plastic before you
eat it. Don't worry. I'll pull the plastic out for you and save it and put it to the side so
you can take pictures of it for later. For content. Oh, I'll personally thank them for all the money
they donate as well on your behalf. Don't worry. First responders. You're right. That .0025%
that the firehouse subs donates does outweigh the plastic that they put in their sandwiches.
I don't think the pickle blew away because of, I don't think the pickle blew away in the wind.
It was your mighty breath, Jay Staun. Just exhaling makes a tidal wave of air. You laughed and it
pushed your pickle away. Go get more pickles to blow away. The reason city food is so windy up
here is when you exhale. Everyone's wigs are blowing off up here, Jay Staun, because of how
mighty your lungs are. Blown off CityWalk wigs is new. Everyone's wig is blowing off at CityWalk.
They got a wig catcher that they got to collect them at the end of the day like it's a roller
coaster where people will take their hats off. This is not so far from my life with Jason,
I think. Well, that's what I was thinking. That's your point. I do think that you,
at the drop of a hat, to cheer up your friend would get a whole bar to sing him a song.
Oh, I would love to. Yes, of course. Yes. Yes. And a made up song about him.
That's right. In thinking about this, I did have the lyrics in my pocket.
Oh, good, good. No one sleeps like Jay Staun. No one's cheap like Jay Staun.
No one's references are as oblique as Jay Staun.
Yeah. Can't you see he's the heart of the show?
That's true. Now, in all fairness, Mike did talk about Tulsa King a lot, a while ago.
What do you mean? I feel like you get to talk, didn't you?
I was saying maybe that was my in with the Yellowstone verse. Before it came out,
you were kind of like, you know what, I'm a little excited. I think Tulsa King might be the way to
it. Didn't it come out to kind of unify itself? No one likes it. There's a controversy that
Stallone was banishing ugly extras from the set, I believe, in the last couple of weeks.
I never watched a frame of it. Not like I knew what was happening. I just did not happen,
did not watch it. Yes, no, I certainly brought up Tulsa King first. Yes, that's correct.
But I have, have I mentioned, I think somewhere on a computer, I have an intro video for a never
shot, just like, I don't know, web series or a YouTube short we're going to do called Jason
Sheridan's Burbank. Really? Where I put in like Kenny Loggins, I'm Alright, and it was just like
pictures of Burbank. And it said, Jason Sheridan's Burbank. And they like can't, the title like flew
in, like it's a fun travel. What was that going to be? Like a fun travel show where Jason takes
you around to Burbank and all the sights and sounds. Never happened. But I have the intro
video for it somewhere. You're going to whet the viewers, the listeners' appetite for this. Well,
there's some of them are going to like pull off to the side of the road and just in anticipation
of waiting for me to find this and post it. I thought you meant if they were in Burbank,
they were going to pull off the side of the road and look around a little.
Well, if you're in Burbank, I would recommend that in general. Just take, pull off to the side of the
road and see Milton Eadies and get a hot dog if it's hot dog day. Where are you going on Jason
Sheridan's Burbank besides famous Milton Eadies and hot dogs? Oh, go to Chili John's. I think the
pitch was just honestly, it's going to be kind of real. It's just going to be like his favorite
places. Sure. Yeah, I think it was just like California Gold. There wasn't any grand comedy
idea behind it. Yeah, right. Yes. Hey, you know what? Let's save the little rifts and tears for
this show. Right. I think the listener, I think there are a lot of listeners who would like to
see a joke-free Jason Sheridan tour of Burbank show. I agree. You can point out, you know, how
getting in and out of the Empire Center can be a little difficult. Here's my trick.
You don't want to find yourself turning left over by the Krispy Kreme. You can, did you know,
you can pull out near the Staples toward the hotel and you can still go. That light is less busy.
Yeah, but not even light. Oh, hold on here. You can actually pull out more closer by the hotels
and avoid that light altogether. And there's still a way out onto the main street and a lot
less traffic. Yeah. How about that? They change the on-ramps and off-ramps of the freeway. So you
got to be careful. Well, that's, didn't they do that a while ago? Yeah, they did a while ago.
Well, it took years, but they did it a while ago. That would have been a thing you would have said
a couple of years ago on this hypothetical show. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Another good point, Jay Stone.
That's right. No, it still applies. People should know the on- and off-ramp history, Jay Stone.
Oh yeah. Did they get rid of your Mediterranean place over there, Jay Stone?
There is but three more took its place. Don't worry. Oh, okay. Good. I still need to get
pita bread while I shop at Target. Say, Jay Stone, was it hard working in post-production or was it
easy? It just kind of sucked. Tell us about what kind of marker you used on the tapes.
China markers, of course. Please, I don't want to beg you, but could I have another China marker,
Jay Stone? No. It makes me thought, all right, that's fine. Fair enough. How many feet? How
many feet? It was indulgent to ask. How many feet away were you from the hometown buffet,
Jason, when you worked there? A block or two. Okay. Not specific feet, not my question, but close.
A couple hundred, I don't know. I guess I don't know what a block is in feet.
I'm sorry. I'm stupid, unlike you, Jay Stone. My book learning was not very good.
I didn't afford college and I'm not a self-starter when it comes to learning.
Mike Fu? Mike Fu, what would be my name? I'm fine with that.
Carl Fu? Le Carl? Le Carl sounds too cool. Le Michael? Le Michael? It also sounds cool.
These are all too cool, I think. It's just I'm spouting cool stuff. Sorry.
Mike Fu. It's Mike Fu. That's just the guy who listens to Heim,
a cool guy who just naturally kind of comes up with cool sounding things. What can I say?
Mike Fu is the Jay Stone sycophant, the cool Heim fan who also talks about Donnots but contains
multitudes. That's Le Carl. Le Carl knows who Troye Sivan is.
Damn. Yeah.
Damn. Wow. Okay. Did we remotely do the premise of the episode? There was Gaston Le Fu talk,
technically. Do we properly tribute these? Look, we mentioned the things. There was one with a
little girl and that was good. There was another one where this one was from Disneyland where
Beauty and the Beast are walking and Gaston follows them for a long time. They walk all the
way to the small world exit where the nude guy was taken away, in fact. My favorite part of that is
that they pass by the monorail and Gaston says, what is that thing? Some kind of metallic snake
that your father built? Great. Justified. There's an inside edition clip where a woman was at
Disneyland or Disney World. She went on a trip because her boyfriend had broken up with her
and she yelled at Gaston walking around. Gaston, I'm single. My boyfriend dumped me and he says
something like, I'm looking for the most beautiful girl in the land. Again, a gentle ribbing,
a gentle roast. That's pretty harsh. It's all harsh. I guess you could also interpret that,
though. He's saying, you're beautiful. Don't worry. I'm looking for 10% more beauty.
He's got impossible standards. That's actually the only other point I was even going to make is
that there is a little thread in the needle on this of you're doing improv, you're interacting
with people, and this character seems to have the most freedom of all the characters. You've seen
Cruella DeVille. I've seen the performers do her and it's fun. Basically, everything's like puppies,
but with Gaston, you're talking to a true villain. He's supposed to be a chauvinist.
There's traps to fall into if you're doing the character as well. You've got to have a couple
filters on in your brain. You've got to clean some stuff up. Yeah, you can't be so, because even
saying go back to the kitchen is a little bit- Sure, for Disney, if you don't understand the bit.
There's nothing Bill and Ted show level happening with Gaston in these clips.
No. Yeah, yeah. Block her up, I say.
There's a terrible scourge headed for this country. It's called the second Biden administration.
It'll kill every man, woman, and child because of migrants coming in from across the border.
What did you pay for that Coca-Cola? $10? We're all going to starve to death at that rate. Don't
you see? It's possible it could devolve into that if you were in the right headspace.
There's only one man stronger than me. His name is Donald Trump.
I would never do push-ups in his presence. He could easily do a thousand in five minutes.
I stormed to the White House looking for the beast known as Mike Pence. What do you mean?
I was in prison for multiple years and I'm freshly out and now back to my tavern.
We must kill the election thief. We've got to hang him. Use your wires, use your bombs.
The man who brought the absentee ballots at Arizona at midnight. We must take him and murder him.
What do you mean a Georgia election official is suing Gaston?
Nothing I did was illegal. That was, by the way, very similar to Gail Gordon delivery right there.
You finally brought it back to Lucy Attributes, something we're always trying to do.
Let's go, boys, to the Capitol. I'll be right there with you.
That is funny, Gustav. He sent everybody to the castle and then didn't go. Of course,
it's great that he gets a big fight with, you know, he needs to culminate in a big fight with
the beast, but it would be great if like, all right, well, ah, some peace and quiet at the
tavern. You know, it's fun when it's full of people, but it's fun when I could just
raid the shoves myself. They'll kill the beast probably. I'll assume the job's done.
Time to do a deep cleaning. It's so satisfying. Now that's Jayston.
Yes. Get me a Swiffer. I enjoy. Swiffer wet and Swiffer dry. Both Swiffers.
Wow. Two gallons for one at CVS. No one scrubs like Gaston. No one does the Marie Kondo
philosophy thing like to get rid of things like Gaston. You know, there's a lot of legitimate
criticisms you can level at her methods. No one does laundry for three days straight like Gaston.
No one clears a schedule for laundry like Gaston. Are you crazy? I can't go out. I've got laundry
to do in two days time. I'm taking a day trip to San Diego. I've got to be prepared. I'm hunkered
down for 10 hours in my research fort. Then laundry. A big episode on myself to do for podcast
the ride. My job as a theme park journalist. Of course, Jayston. So yeah. Throw that ponytail
out I think is what people. It's time for a new look. Oh yeah. Please. I am due for a haircut.
No, you're not. Not anymore, you're not. No, throw it out. I want to see you locks, Jayston.
That is a different type of little boy Jayston could be. I was going to say turn of the century,
but I mean turn of the 19th century little boy with ponytail and little bow. Right, that's true.
You could do that. Sure. Well, it's more like little Lord Fauntleroy. Yeah. Right. Which is
another one of the many faces of Jayston Sheridan. A future Halloween, Jayston being the painting
the blue boy. I would really enjoy. Okay, yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah. So kudos to the performers
because I do feel like I would have a lot of fun doing this, but I feel like in like minute,
I don't know, seven of like a pretty like back and forth improv with some guy challenging me,
I would like call him a dickhead or something accidentally. Yeah. Like, oh, fuck you. I'm really
sorry. Say, drop trow. I bet you've got a tiny car. No one's filming this one, right? Hey, not
everything has to go to the internet, right? Hey, this is between all of you and me. Hey, we're all
just having fun. Why don't, why do I give you some tickets for $10 free $10 Cokes?
Yeah, they have to give Gaston a couple like tickets or like fast passes that he hands out
when he says something offensive. Okay, so raise your hand if I called you a fucking pussy.
Oh, that's a lot. Really? I'm sorry. I kind of black out during these sessions. All right. I
have to Gaston is a documentary supervisor to get more fast pass, complimentary fast passes.
I can write you all some really quick, but I don't know if they'll honor those.
Sorry, little girl. I'm sorry. I said your father's a coward and your mother's a whore.
I apologize. How would you like to meet Peter Pan? The first half of the day is the regular meet
and greet line for him. And then the second half is if you want an apology from him and the guy
out of character. Well, I'm really so sorry. When I entered the area and I said, why are we all just
sucking our own dicks around here? I really apologize for that. Have you seen a movie called
Jim and Andy? Well, that's a documentary that shows you how Jim Carrey really lost himself
playing a character. And what can I say? That's what I do for an hour to 75 minute shifts every
day. It's not me. I'm not even there. I become Gaston. So when I said, Hey, hey, sweetheart,
why don't you grind up on a real man? I shouldn't have said that. That was in character. I didn't
mean to insult your meek boyfriend. I'm so sorry. When I said you're the ugliest girl in town
to your seven year old daughter. Well, I didn't see I misspoke. Gaston did it. And here now you
can skip the line at the seven dwarves mind train because of it. When I, when I took your elderly
father, who's helping taking care of your kids on the trip, when I dragged him hair first over to the
drinking fountain and shoved more water in his mouth than he could handle. Again, not I, why do
I keep saying that when Gaston? And when I pretend, excuse me, when I pretend pretended that your
service dog was the beast and I attacked it, I didn't mean to do that. And I hope the dog will be
fine. But because of that, here's a free front of the line pass to the Dumbo ride. I, I'm sorry. I
gave your grandmother the undertaker's tombstone pile driver and then cross my eyes and stuck my
tongue out like the undertaker. Here is a light up bubble wand.
In retrospect, Gaston should not have cracked his daily five dozen eggs and made you eat them raw
one at a time in front of him on off the ground. Here is it. Here is a fast pass. Here's a front
of the line pass for the people mover. I know there's not usually a line, but sometimes there's
a little delay. You could get past like six people with that. Pretty good little boy. I am sorry that
you're yelling. You'll never defeat the beast. Got me so angry. I made you smoke a whole pack of
cigarettes. And frankly, I'm sorry to everyone who was in the line, who ended up having to wait an
extra hour while I did these methodical punishments while Gaston did methodical
punishments. Those were interesting to watch too. Weren't they? Were you not entertained?
Were you not entertained? It gets to you sometimes. And I think I will be forced to do just like
Pluto or Chippendale next week. Jobs where I can shut up. I'm going to be Pluto from now on.
So none of this will happen again. And Pluto is going to keep his tongue in appropriate places.
You will not ever lick anything inappropriate. Security, we have another Pluto beating happening.
We need to tackle the Pluto. This is a six, seven, nine, which is of course when Pluto wraps his
tongue around a small child's neck, ties it tightly and runs away with the kid dangling from his mouth.
Pluto will not stop doing pushups and screaming. I think we have another rogue Gaston punishment
on her hands. Pluto has also been yelling, I got that dog in me very loudly as he pushes
women's boyfriends away and snatches the girlfriend up and runs away with him.
Pluto is out of control. He has done once again, a tombstone pile driver.
Pluto has a tombstone pile driven a grandmother on Main Street. He has yanked the head off of the
dog from up, declared there's only one dog around these parts, thrown the head in the lagoon.
And now he's attacking every service animal in the park. He will not stop high-fiving Cruella
de Vil saying they had it coming, they had it coming. And then he says, I am ready to sacrifice
my skin for you. And he is cutting off the pieces of his uniform and allowing her to use them to
make puppy coats. And they're constructing the coat now in the middle of Main Street USA.
They've priced the coat at $700, which frankly, given it's shoddy construction, seems like too
much. Too much. The costumes have been around for too long. That is not fresh costume fabric.
It's dirty old costume fabric. So again, seize any cameras that are filming any of this,
burn them and make sure these don't end up on Inside Edition.
I wonder who the most famous Gaston, I wonder if anyone's gone on to stardom from the Gaston,
if it's a rocket to the moon as far like, is there anybody on TV? Is anyone on the new walker?
The guy, do you say the new walker? The guy who I think was in the most great viral Gaston clips,
his name, Rob Walker. Wow. I believe that's reported by GQ. Yeah. Yeah. So I want to shout
him out. I was looking because I would love to find out. Yeah. That he has some, he's had a big
career or at least he's well, whatever is happening because really funny. Or at least he's like
playing like Popeye now at islands of adventure. Yeah. Sure. Where you get a little more rope
where you can be looser there. Of course. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Not that Popeye's so bawdy, but.
But he could be. He could be. Yeah. Hey, there's a special room in me ship. I'm going to show you
the room in me ship that Aleph don't get to see. That voice though, it makes everything sound a
little more lecherous. Even a normal, even a non-lecherous statement sounds lecherous.
You think, you think the arms look weird. Wait till you see me, Dick.
Yeah. Hopefully it's also got a little pipe.
That's it. You survived. It's got to be a podcast. The right, the second gate,
a little corn cob pipe Popeye's. Dick smokes a little corn cob pipe. Is that what you're saying?
Yeah. Yeah. It was no innuendo. I was just talking about little corn cob pipe.
The Masked Magician's Dick has a little mask and Popeye's Dick has a little corn cob pipe.
Let's see if we can, see if we can keep this a runner. Let's try. What topic can't we give
a little Dick amenity to? Hey, you did it. Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
Sometimes we do episodes where we talk about the topic more. We will do that someday,
but I hope you like this pile of nonsense. And if you want even more piles of nonsense,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free. Um, well, uh, uh, well, I mean, first of all, rest in peace,
Orenthal James Simpson. And second of all, you want to send, send us off and send OJ off with a
little, uh, pipe. Doot, doot. Yay.