Club 3
Breaking the Magician's Code is today breaking the Club 3 curse.
I'm excited about it, Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan.
Yes, I'm here.
I'm very excited.
For this historic moment.
Yes, I'm also very excited.
Let me just, you know, keep recording, yeah, keep recording.
Oh my god.
No way.
What?
Whoa, what's happening?
I just, I wanted to prepare for this and also like the Academy of Magical Arts is like
right down the road and I'm scared of them and you know, so.
We have a hood going on, Jason's face, my god, what is this, with the famous Masked
Magician streaks?
This is wild.
What's happening?
Oh my god.
You know.
It's like he's here in the room with us.
Yes, or today it might be more perceived as a very low budget Black Panther costume.
You know, today I'm not Jason Sheridan on the Masked Podcaster.
As we're breaking the podcasters code, of course, a visual gag for an audio medium,
you know, everyone loves it.
Yeah, yeah, sometimes we record with a video.
Not today.
Yeah, yeah, not this one.
Yep, no.
So secretive was Jason's plan that he didn't even let his fellow podcasters in on it.
I appreciate the secrecy.
Wow.
Why do you have this?
Oh, I bought it and Jane made it like you did this for this.
Yeah.
A Masked Magician mask.
I made a Masked Magician mask because Scott, look, you can't buy a Masked Magician mask.
OK, so you got to buy a mask on Amazon.
And I bought paint markers and I was like, oh, no, I have to breathe this in if I'm going
to try this.
So then I bought.
Do you know what China markers are?
No, no.
It's clay.
It's like a clay pencil.
I have ones for you guys because they unfortunately only come in packs of 12.
Wow.
Clay pencils for us?
So if we want to make our own masks at home.
We have a head start.
You can make your own masks.
Wow.
Because I was like, oh, they'll smear a little.
When I worked in post-production, we would write work order numbers on the tape, like
the Digi-Beta boxes, because you can mark up like China in ceramic.
Revealing the post-production guys' secrets.
Yeah, revealing.
Yeah.
How do they do it?
How do they make those marks?
Well, there's a special kind of marker.
It's called China markers.
Wow.
Well, this is very exciting for us and no one else.
Well, until we take a picture.
Until we post a photo.
We take a picture.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
I can do the like hands on the microphone or the hands on the zoo.
Yes, please.
Are you going to give it that attitude?
Are you going to reveal any of the secrets to doing this podcast today?
Is that kind of part of your plan?
Ooh.
Because like, you know, the internet is sort of changing entertainment and it's
really like we don't want podcasters to sort of rely on the old tricks of podcasting.
So that's why.
Absolutely.
Everybody's so into the internet now that we're forgetting when we first fell in love
with podcasting.
Right.
Exactly.
So yeah, today we will, I'll say I will reveal some secrets about podcasting today.
Whoa.
Geez.
Well, this is, thank God this is behind the double paywall because we could end up with
all the other podcasters after us.
Yeah.
We're kicked out of the podcasters alliance.
I know.
And yeah, and if a fictional television show is to believe somebody might be after our
lives, if you know what I'm getting at, and I hope you do.
That's why we're recording this one in an undisclosed location.
Exactly.
It is not the place where we usually do it.
In fact, if you see pictures and it looks like places where we've previously posted
pictures of episodes in mid record, it's not.
We recreated our usual forever dog recording studio in an undisclosed location bunker.
Yeah.
An abandoned warehouse that is perfectly lit, kind of.
Yeah, I know.
It's funny how that works out that despite it being off the grid, they did manage to
light it perfectly for broadcast television.
Well, there's so many magician contraptions and stuff.
You might as well just load it up with lights.
They had to put a bag over all the lighting people's heads, all the assistants, everybody
who came to this place, they don't know where they went.
They might as well have been doing a drug deal.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I'm worried now.
I'm just stressed.
We might not even make it to the end of the episode.
That is how if you just suddenly hear a sniper's bullet and we go silent, and then they left
it recording for like an hour and then picked it up, posted it, which would be nice for
them to do.
That would be nice.
To still give us an episode to fulfill our obligation this month.
Maybe parts redacted.
Certain parts redacted.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
If you've heard even already just a two minute long beep, then that's what happened.
Jason, now I have the question of are you actually going to commit to this the whole
time?
I feel like you're going to get hot so quick.
Yeah, Scott, it's coming soon because I also can't wear glasses with this on Insane
Time.
So everything's just kind of a blur.
My laptop's in my bag and I'm like, well, that's I'm not going to be able to see the
screen.
So.
All right.
So we better get cooking with the info because it's either going to be foggy for you or inaccessible.
Hey, there it goes.
All right.
Hey, we'll put it back on for some pictures.
I was fully like, and I'll just put my glasses on over it, not thinking will cover my ears
and they will just slide off my head like they did in my apartment when I was testing
it out.
So the man, one of the mass podcasters secrets is his secret kryptonite is fog.
OK, fog, ear coverings, they get in the way.
OK, so we have arrived at breaking the magician's code and we have to acknowledge here at the
top that this was this is maybe the most fascinating thing that has happened in the
poll the entire time we've been doing the Club 3 poll.
This became the Susan Lucci of the poll, many, many runner ups, runners up.
It had to wait for six months, all told, in second place, lost to Macy's Thanksgiving
Parade Disasters, Jimmy Buffett's Christmas Island, towed ins, trounced by Griffin Newman,
does whatever he wants, despite Griffin himself voting for this topic.
And then it had to wait till the saga was done.
But finally, we've arrived here.
It held firm and, you know, quite a victory, almost, you know, sort of a magician-esque
build, reveal, a build of tension finally resulting in the prestige.
We have to make this episode.
I know.
That's a lot of pressure.
It really is, yes.
It has to be as good as the film The Prestige.
I think we're, well, with Jason's dramatic start, I think we're in good shape now, but
we've got to keep it up.
Second place in this particular poll, the American Girl Cafe, presumably the idea here
would be that the three of us would go to one, which we can do because there's one in
Century City.
I've poked my head in there before.
Then, you know, when you're in Burbank, Century City might as well be another state, but we
are willing to cross state lines to the other side of Los Angeles.
Going to 405, yeah.
Oh, boy.
Is this, this is not the Americana one?
Is that closed?
There has never been one at Americana.
There was one at The Grove that is no longer.
The Grove, sorry.
And it's, yeah, Century City Mall, I believe, is the final location in Los Angeles.
Okay.
So it is there.
We can do this.
I might hold this for a month because I have another idea and I'll pitch it at the end
of the episode.
My final reveal.
But for now, we arrive at Breaking the Magician's Code slash The Masked Magician.
I can't believe that I don't have to type those words into the poll the next time that
we do a poll.
Yeah.
I'm so used to it.
It might end up in there just due to force of habit.
But no, it is out and I can finally read, I had to go way back to look up the thing
that was written about it by the submitter of the topic, Michael Darling.
We know Michael.
We've participated in some fun articles with him.
Thank you for this, Michael, and thank you for your patience.
So here we are.
Let me read his quote.
These 90s Fox specials are classic PTR.
It's mostly forgotten bullshit that felt like a big deal at the time.
The mysterious masked magician was going to reveal magic's biggest secrets at great personal
risk to his reputation in the magic community and perhaps his life.
Of course, when his face was eventually revealed, it turned out to be some guy most folks had
never heard of.
It's magic and 90s nonsense, two of PTR's favorite things in one masked package.
Quite a pitch.
Thanks, Michael.
Sorry it takes so long.
And Michael, you know, you could not have been more right in terms of like highly anticipated
because any time one of these specials was coming, I got so excited.
I watched, I believe I watched all of these.
Yeah, I think I did too.
And it felt very much like the excitement of like, we're going to a theme park in a
few days.
Like, we're going to learn magic's biggest secrets.
And I also felt very anxious, like, he's breaking the magician's code.
I'm not supposed to know this stuff.
Yeah, it's really brazen that they would do this.
Like something that should be done, you know, hundreds of years of secrets just suddenly
spoiled in front of millions of people on primetime television.
The edginess of you're watching something coming from an undisclosed location.
Like is this, do they know, does Fox realize this is on?
Is this a pirate broadcast?
What happened here?
Yeah, I mean, it's in, we've said a million times in the genre of Fox doing bad, like
alien autopsy.
These are some shows that have a little edge to them.
And as kids, especially, you were like, well, Fox is the renegade network.
They show the Simpsons and they show real aliens that are dead.
They're willing to show a child saying, I, Carumba.
And then on top of it, yeah, they will just expose government secrets, break important
codes, and get a little bit sexy.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, Models, Inc.
Get out of town.
You kidding me?
The more modern theme park thing is the amount of punctuation in these, because it's alien
autopsy colon factor fiction, breaking the magician's code, colon maggots, magics, magics.
Well, this guy's a maggot breaking the code.
Magics biggest secrets finally revealed.
Did they use factor fiction though, the same with the Jonathan Frakes show?
I think it's just a phrase.
But I'm saying, did they use that twice?
Oh, I guess they kind of did.
Oh, possibly.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the title I'm seeing.
Can I quickly derail the episode real quick?
Of course.
I met Jonathan Frakes.
What?
Last week.
Whoa, Mike.
Wow.
By complete happenstance.
I won't say where, just because I'm like, I don't want to dox him.
You're heading into this thinking like, I hope that I can dovetail this into mentioning
those specialists so that I can mention that I met Jonathan Frakes.
I would have told you guys, but I was like, I got to save it for the show.
Yeah.
I met Jonathan Frakes.
Whoa, why?
Just by normal, undisclosed place, just that normal people go to.
Really?
Just me and him sitting on a bench.
At the American Girl Cafe.
It was not the American Girl Cafe.
At the toilet store?
Is that why you don't want to talk about it?
We were not at the toilet store.
Because it's a little private.
It was a little private.
Yeah.
But I was like, oh shit.
How do I do this?
Do I just play it cool?
Do I just go, excuse me, big fan or whatever, and let it go, or do I just give it up to
this guy?
And I gave it right up to him.
I go, excuse me, I'm a huge, huge fan of yours.
And I was like, book hard season three, you're acting, so I'm just like, I started rolling.
I was like, let's give it to Jonathan Frakes.
Sure.
There's other people I would have been a little bit playing it cool, but I was like, really
just, I just gave it all to him.
And I was like, there should be more of these, you guys were in such good shape, I didn't
say good shape.
But you guys, you were like in such top form, I go, I want to see more seasons of all of
you together.
It was so fun.
Sometimes these were, I'm just, I'm like, I lost control.
Did you give him a chance to say anything?
Yes.
And he said, he was so, he was, he knew exactly how to do it.
Like I've seen him in interviews before where he was like talking to Shatner and he's like,
well, how do you think like when somebody wants to approach you to say something nice,
how should they approach you, Bill?
And he's like, well, with money, maybe, like you can tell Bill hates it.
And Frakes is like, Frakes said like, I'm easy people, like say something nice to me.
Okay.
I assumed he would be receptive.
You knew a vibe, because you've like prepared yourself for the possibility of this moment.
This is something I have trained for my whole life, is to gush to Jonathan Frakes' face.
And I did it.
And I think I did a pretty, like 80% of what I wanted to gush.
Wow.
That's tough to suddenly summon, to like not be prepared.
This is not a, you know, this isn't like a story I forget if we've told where you guys
met Bruce Springsteen and you had hours in line.
Right.
And that was too quick.
I was not prepared for this.
So I was like 80%, like I felt good about it.
Can you give us any specifics he?
Well, he started asking me, like he was like asking me about, there's a room, like not
rumor, but like the guy who show ran Picard season three wants to do more Star Trek and
he's been pushing for it online.
And Frakes like, well, do you want to see the Star Trek legacy that they've been talking
about?
I go, well, of course I want to, like he started asking me questions.
He started talking about the Picard season one and two and then other stuff he's directing
within Star Trek.
Okay.
And so he was, he was very, he was a pro as far as like handling a lunatic.
What are you, what are you getting today, Mike, Kohler, American standard, like what's
your toilet choice?
We were both testing out toilets.
And you just happened, you ended up next to each other.
So you're stuck in one plea.
He has to talk to you.
Yeah, exactly.
So yeah, anyway, no, I just, I didn't get to the factor.
I didn't get to be on the belief or anything.
I just basically was Star Trek all the way.
Sure.
And I, uh, you got to prioritize.
I got, yeah, I, yes.
And then, yeah.
So anyway, it's just a quick, quick story there.
There's not too much more.
I don't want to say.
Geez.
Has it been hard to keep that inside?
Yes.
I've told every single person that knows who that is.
I haven't told anyone who doesn't know who that is.
So it's me and Daniel Roebuck to not tell you guys immediately, then you need the gratificate.
I got to tell everyone else.
Yes.
I told every, yes.
I texted Andrew Grissom.
I said, holy shit.
I just met Jonathan Franks.
Texted Lindsay.
You texted with, through handshaking.
I sent multiple voice memos to people too, like explaining the whole situation.
You described it all out loud.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
This is an interesting.
Did you just feel like that was going to be more efficient?
Yeah.
Then typing it out or just voice.
Cause it, cause it would also be easier than just doing the talk to text, which sometimes
screws up.
Oh, sure.
So anyway, I thought this Fox.
Who's Jonathan Flakes?
Oh, the cereal man, the inventor of flakes.
The idea of flakes.
He's still around.
Yeah.
Uh, congratulations.
Thank you.
Wow.
Big day.
Oh my God.
You're very excited.
Well, I hope you get a second round so that that one can be the major of that one can
be alien autopsy.
Wait, no, I'm sorry.
Alien autopsy is the Fox one, uh, it mentioned in Jason's list.
What was his show again?
Beyond belief factor fiction.
That was not Fox that aired.
No, that was Fox.
That was Fox.
Oh, okay.
Cause I think I consider that all in the same genre of these shows where like it's a little
bit out there, like a little bit dangerous.
Like these are true fucked up stories and then some of them are fake.
Yes.
Yeah.
How did they get away with it?
Well, some of it is entirely made up.
Maybe most of it was.
Let me bring up a, uh, I'll immediately take us into a, uh, a guy a little bit because
the background of this, I mean, we have perfectly painted the picture of the era that results
in this mass magician special series of specials that, uh, it probably is its biggest victory.
But like, yeah, late nineties Fox is getting edgy.
There's a big like specials budget.
Uh, I think they start calling it like alternative programming.
They, you know, even that has its own like air of mystery.
No, no, no.
Not specials.
That's not special enough.
Yeah.
Alternative programming.
And so this whole, there's, yeah, there's alien autopsy factor fiction.
World's wildest police chases, celebrity boxing, the very, very sad affair where Tanya Harding
beat the shit out of Paula Jones.
What is that pairing an athlete versus a woman who had bad things after, uh, anyway, this
all grew out of the reign of a guy who I can't believe I've never brought up on the show
before a guy named Mike Darnell.
I'm going to ask both of you and the listeners at home to please Google image Mike Darnell
and just give me an auditory reaction to what you find because he was really the czar of
all this and modern reality television in general.
American Idol is this guy.
Uh, I'm sure I'm forgetting.
I think like almost every major reality show, have you seen this gentleman before?
I have seen this guy.
Any, uh, anything you want to say to describe him and he was anything you want to call out
about his style.
He's got hair like Howard Stern hair.
Yes.
Absolutely.
Which a lot of scarves, leather jacket.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm trying to think.
What are some Steven Tyler, little Steven influence.
Very.
Yes.
Both that.
Yeah.
These are all in his vision board.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And it's like, I can't tell if that's a, I guess it's not a wig, but it could be a wig.
It looks so wiggy.
It's not the, it's kind of Jeff Lin also, and it's not like a natural hair color for
a man his age to have.
You can tell if he's the guy responsible for American Idol, then maybe he, his whole
style is in some ways a tribute to, uh, season one's Justin Guarini.
Oh, he does look like Justin Guarini.
He's a little bit Justin Guarini.
Yeah.
Um, he also, he's got this beard in some of these photos that makes no sense.
It looks drawn on.
Well, that happens sometimes with some of these gentlemen who draw a beard on.
That is so real.
Or just die.
The reason why it looks drawn on is because they drew it on.
Yeah.
I, I don't want to get into like celebrity plastic surgery and celebrities.
Don't lie.
You want to get into it.
I do.
I would love to.
Okay.
You're right.
I would love to get into it, but we can't do it for many reasons.
Um, but I'll say this.
There are some older male celebrities who I do think do some, like, there's like a technique
that some of them employ that is to like color in, uh, probably a gray beard.
Sure.
And perhaps just by doing sort of stubble and dyeing it versus the full beard that's big
and dyed, which would stand out more.
This is the choice they've made to try to reduce the like appearance of, of, uh, oh,
old, oldness.
No, nothing weird.
Cause then, then you just look like a living Homer Simpson.
You just look like you have an animated five o'clock shadow on your face at all times.
And that's much better than just then having some gray hair.
So much of, especially male plastics, I mean, I guess plastics in general, so much of it
is just to, when somebody's on TV or in a photo is just to make, uh, like have the person
who's watching be a little bit fooled about the age and see, and the longer you can fool
the brain into forgetting how old this person is, the better the situation is, the better
whatever you're doing to your face or head is.
Cause sometimes I go, Oh, that person looks really good.
And then I go, Oh, they're 70 years old.
That's, that's fantastic.
And sometimes you go, Oh, it's like they painted on a young person's face and hair.
Well, yeah.
What it starts to lead to is where like all of the, the eerie effects that you see in
current shark tank, where all of the age defying plastic surgery has started to come off the
rails in the last one to two years, all at the same time.
And it's like, wait, how can it be all of them?
Well, cause they probably all like, we're making the big shark tank money at the same
time and it only lasted for 10 years.
And now it's all synced up as the, as their faces start to make no sense.
And I'm not knocking it.
Cause in 10, 15 years, I'm going to have this drawn on a parent.
I'm going to have, I was wondering if you had looked into it because you want to do
it.
Yes.
I know all about it.
I know it all about it.
And I know what my options are.
So you're, so listener again, if you didn't already, please Google image Mike Darnell.
If you want to see a future vision of Mike Carlson, it makes sense because you, you have
previously said that you think that Steven Tyler, it looks good.
I do think he looks good for what his, he's never, he's always looked like kind of an
interesting odd guy and he looks pretty good in his seventies.
All things considered.
I think.
Okay.
Yeah.
Now I did.
I, you say that I had a late night comedy job that involved almost weekly writing jokes
about how Steven Tyler looks absolutely batshit insane, but you're entitled to your own opinion.
But he always has looked insane.
Yes, that is true.
It's a different situation.
He's keeping up the insanity.
Anyway, I just had to mention Mike Darnell and this guy genuinely for the insanity of
the look, he boy, did he transform, uh, reality television.
I think he, he took specials into a place that's not like, unfortunately for you, Mike,
that is no longer like with Ruth Buzzi.
I know.
Uh, but Paul and I, like he updated it.
He made it scary.
And I think that the big thing that these specials do, the mass magician specials is
they extract the scariness, the moodiness, the building of tension that essentially there's
like 20 minutes of stuff happening over the course of an hour.
And we stretch it out with just like music and music and dramatic pauses.
I feel like what these specials are trying to do is take the David Copperfield style
and do it without David Copperfield.
How do we build like an hour of mysterious magic without name recognition?
Well, we get some obscure guy, we make him a superstar with the mystery of the mask.
And I feel like it like brought magic back, you know, in a way, like in a way what the
guy ultimately declared he was trying to do isn't wrong because this, this kind of bridges
the gap between the early nineties Copperfield specials and the later, uh, Chris angel mind
free.
That's true.
Yeah.
It kind of like, it keeps magic momentum going during that lag.
Well, I read, I, I searching mass magician, I ended up on a couple of magicians web pages
and one guy, I broke the code.
One guy still seemed pretty pissed and little angry.
Another guy was like, yeah, it's whatever.
A lot of these solutions are the, can you say names of these magicians?
I don't have the names in front of me.
I don't want to put them on blast, but the casual guy was like, yeah, some of these solutions
are how it was done like a hundred years ago, but there's different techniques now.
Yes.
In the aftermath that like, okay, yes, he exposed one way to do it, but it's not like
you could just like use this as a, a cliff notes guide and just become a magician yourself.
And he was like, yeah, magic's always had a lot of competition, but like the year these
specials came out, the first Harry Potter book came out and that kind of, you know,
got people thinking about magic more.
And then the next year or two, like the David Blaine special started and that got people
a little more interested in magic.
That's a funny thing though.
And maybe that's true, but nothing I'd ever considered that Harry Potter, which is fantastical
made people want to do practical, like practical, like real world magic.
I guess, I guess this seems funny to me, like why, like there's, they're, they're real tricks
in the book.
Like they do.
They're real wizards.
So yeah, but it does wizard, wizardry inspire people to be magicians.
I don't know.
If you start fiddling around with it and then you discover, what if you're, you're the one
who actually discovers that magic is real, nobody ever, nobody ever tried enough.
No one tried Harry Potter tactics in the real world.
And I guess, look, wizards was magic and fantastical magic.
You mean the club?
The club, of course.
Wizards.
The City Wall Club.
Which I can't, you know, of course that kept magic in the air, the time before this special,
these specials happened.
So the initial run was four specials, which aired between November, 1997, October, 1998.
As you said, Jason, a formative time, I had nothing better in my life going on than these.
I feel like I would buzz about them for a week before and think about them for days
after real events.
And just, and that first one, you got to go back to like, they're doing what?
What are they going to do on TV?
They're going to destroy an industry forever.
This, I must see.
And boy, it came out of the gate, huge, 28 million people, I think, that first one.
That's unbelievable.
Wow.
24, 24.2, at the time, the highest rated special ever on Fox.
And they kind of diminished as they went, and then thus they had to do the unmasking
for the fourth one to kind of like dredge up the interest again.
You know, we've definitely talked before about, you know, the context, there's no need again
to go over like, hey, nobody actually watches anything now the way they watch these things.
But it still is astounding.
24 million viewers.
And it still wasn't the top viewed thing of the week.
That went to CBS TV movie Borrowed Hearts with Roma Downey, Eric McCormick and Hector
Elizondo.
Wow.
What is going, what is this world where, and again, a stat that's always staggering is
how I think the succession finale got three million viewers, 24 million for Mesmagician
and it still wasn't enough to dethrone Hector Elizondo.
Gosh.
What a time.
What a different time.
Yeah, really.
Which it feels like it's 300 years ago.
Yeah.
I mean, it's certainly been enough that there's been like several media shifts, you know,
obviously everything splintered and now we all know all the best stuff is AI and you know,
there's been that shift in the last month or so.
I want to, I want to look up more about alien autopsy because as soon as I was like wrapping
up last night, I was like, oh, this is kind of like alien autopsy, which I think was too
spooky for me.
Yeah.
I don't think I ever went into it yet.
The whole, the notion of like, I think I was scared to look up whatever they were going
to do about Bigfoot.
Like what if that, what if that is so scary?
Like the thing in signs, like when the, when the alien walks by in signs and all the kids
scream.
I was like, whatever.
I don't even want to begin to know what alien autopsy is.
Yeah.
But I want to know what the readings were for that.
I'm sure they were good.
Yeah.
This kind of bullshit, I think could be on the table in general, especially, you know,
again, we'll see how this goes, how people like it.
You know, I want to talk about aliens.
So.
Oh, great.
So this will be the, so this will be the end for the genuine Mike alien.
Okay.
Yeah.
Great.
Um, so, uh, this speaking of, of aliens, we, we are in a location that can't be revealed,
which is wonderfully lit, a big, a very dark blue warehouse.
And the first image you see is, uh, an actor in a black leather jacket and, uh, uh, with,
you know, an imposing vibe and kind of a gritty voice.
And I never thought about this guy before.
I didn't know who he was.
He is Mitch Pileggi, who is, uh, you know what, actually, I'll just read, let me go
back to, I cut something from Michael's quote, uh, the tone of the specials can be best described
as self-serious cheese featuring sometimes jokey narration from a sleepwalking Mitch
Pileggi, the X-Files own director Skinner.
Are you guys X-Files fan?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
So, you know, you know all about this guy.
Yeah.
Every Sunday, I, speaking of being freaked out, but like, I didn't make the connection
by the X-Files.
You mean?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It was an appropriate level of spooky.
You know, um, made you fear the future.
It made me fear the future for sure.
Uh, uh, Scully's.
Was it fear the future?
Was it fight the future?
Fight the future.
Okay.
Nevermind.
I was trying to fight it because I was scared of it.
There you go.
Yes.
Um, uh, Scully's skepticism kept us all grounded so we didn't get too scared.
Uh.
Dana Scully.
Yeah.
And she was, she was a hottie with a body, just like the assistants in this thing.
What?
Well, some of the narration, that was the thing I was going to bring up.
Some of this narration is not each particularly well.
But you're also letting your feelings be known about Agent Dana Scully.
A hottie with a body.
I don't, I, I don't think I, uh, am the first person to like comment on Gillian Anderson
or Dana Scully.
I also wanted my hair to look like David Duchovny at the time.
I know.
Yeah.
When you were in sideburns era.
We talked about it.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So I'm like in eighth grade or freshman, whatever it was.
And I was like, this is the coolest guy I've ever seen.
Cool hair.
This is before a Californ occasion.
That's right.
He was, if you imagine he was cool before that.
Imagine after.
Oh, of course.
Hank Moody.
Right?
That's the name of the character.
Yeah, Hank Moody.
I've never seen it.
But, and I don't, yeah.
I'm not that I don't like Duchovny anymore.
I just, that was peak Duchovny in that for so many seasons.
Kind of a briefly on a Jay Pharoah show on Showtime that I just mentioned to somebody
and they said, you know, that's in the California Keisha verse.
Really?
That's in the same world as, I never cared about what that show was.
Now I care, even though I don't know California Keisha.
I didn't know that.
I love that there would be, yes, there's universe building in Showtime.
Wow.
Uh huh.
I mean, I guess California Keisha was a hit.
Mm hmm.
I think.
Yeah.
And the whole, you know, the whole thing now is cinematic universes.
I don't know if you know.
So of course all our major franchises had to do it, especially California Keisha.
Okay.
Um, so, uh, Mitch Pileggi, what does he, as X-Files fans, what does his apparent appearance
as the host, uh, lend to you?
What is, what context is he bringing in or what vibe is he bringing in from X-Files?
Cause he's got, he's sort of like, you know, he's kind of like, what are you guys up to?
Like kind of a thing.
And he gets, I think he gets more, he's a little skeptical of my memory of him.
He's really skeptical.
Eventually, he kind of is a little more on board with some of this stuff.
But yeah, he kind of brings a little gravitas, gruffness, but he's a, it's a seriousness
to the proceedings.
Sure.
And I think that's like, you go, okay, this is real shit if we've got Pileggi here.
He's, you know, he's like almost.
True man.
This is, I mean, this is sort of pre rise of JK Simmons, who you could see like maybe
that's true.
No offense to Pileggi.
Like that's like the A list version or something you would say, oh, you wouldn't want him now
where he's got this voice and I'm here.
So that means everything you see here is real.
So you better be careful.
Okay.
So that's, that's
If you, if you're questioning any of it, it's like you, you're volunteering to fight him.
You don't want to do that.
I do not want to do that.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's, this is a good context for Mitch Pileggi.
He also, he hosted another special from the same company, Nash entertainment called conspiracy
theory.
Did we land on the moon?
So he was, he was playing in this ballpark at the time.
He was hot.
Yeah.
And this, this very much now looking at first, I was like, wait, who is this guy?
I know.
And I was like, oh, it's Skinner, but Pileggi works.
He was on sons of anarchy.
It was on that Dallas reboot from a few years ago.
Okay.
Current Walker reboot, I believe.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Did you even know that was, is it on TV?
I think so.
Texas ranger has a reboot.
It's just called Walker.
Is he?
No, he's not Walker though.
No, he's just.
No, don't be ridiculous.
Who's Walker?
I don't know.
Just a guy.
Somebody you've never heard of who has 400 times the money you'll ever have.
Is it been on for 10 years or has it been on for two weeks?
One or two?
I don't know.
These things happen.
I just saw like quantum leap reboot canceled and I'm like, there was one?
I knew that, I knew that, but I did not know there's a new Walker that had Mitch Pileggi
on it.
Check it out.
All right.
Is it on CBS?
Is CW still around?
I think it is.
It might be on that.
Okay.
If it's around.
I don't know.
I'm out of it.
This is not Fox in the 90s.
I knew everything that Network Fox was doing in the 90s.
Today, crap shoot.
Current CW is pivoting to alternative programming ironically.
Oh, okay.
As opposed to like sexy.
Oh, no more like Carter Dixie.
Sexy teen shows where the teens are played by 25 year olds, you know.
Less teens, more Pileggi is what CW's motto is.
And I, well, but then Pileggi just left Warner Brothers alternative programming in 2023,
it says.
What do you, Pileggi?
Pileggi?
Yeah.
He was at Warner Brothers for 10 years.
Wait, wait.
Who are you talking about?
Mitch Pileggi?
Oh, now Pileggi.
Sorry.
Who's the guy with the hair?
Darnell.
Sorry, everyone.
I confused Pileggi and Darnell.
I feel like a fool.
No, I just, I thought.
Get your leather jacket guys straight.
Darnell is a wacky leather jacket guy.
Darnell is not Pileggi.
Pileggi is a serious leather jacket guy.
Yeah, Pileggi didn't work at Warner's.
So he comes out, you know, like what we're about to do tonight is going to shock and
appallination and the tone is great.
I think I thought that the guy, you know, the interstitial announcer is kind of more
like Fox bomb ass tonight, but Pileggi really is.
He just, just, he'd like lures you in with this like about to fall asleep.
He's great.
He's so good at this.
He's really good at this.
They really picked the right guy, I think, for that.
Watching it now is very much like, oh, they gave him like half a day or half a night when
X-Files was on break to film this stuff and then he went into a booth to do the narration.
Yeah.
But it's great, sleepy gruff, but the real star of the show, the Masked Magician, and
you know, we'll do the unmasking of him later, but for now, I mean, this is what makes these
iconic if they are iconic to you or if you have, perhaps you've forgotten about them
as Michael said, but black suit, black turtleneck, gloves.
He's like, you know, so enigmatic.
What is his deal?
There's kind of a Darth Vader thing to him.
I feel like I, I think I always imagined that a guy underneath who was like terribly fucked
up and scarred or something, that's what I went to.
Did you guys have any notion of like what's behind the mask?
I thought he names checks them at the last one.
I thought it could be like Copperfield or Lance Burton.
I'm more like what Jason's saying.
I thought it was going to be a famous guy.
Yeah, I thought it was going to be a famous guy.
I feel like they themselves must have planted that rumor and tried to hype up the rumor.
So that it was some like power move.
What would motivate one of those people if we're reviewing that logic, which was not
ultimately true, but I really, is this a way to like crush the competition forever?
I'm letting it all loose.
Then I'll reveal it and like, and now this leaves me as the king, the only tricks I didn't
reveal are my own.
Right.
I guess, I guess, I mean, there's some, if Copperfield on that's probably at the top
of the mountain, so it probably doesn't really make sense for him to do it.
But maybe you're a Lance Burton and you're number two or three or four and boy, the reveal
of who you are would be like, oh my God, he just, he just burned off all these classic
tricks.
Like, where can he go now?
Where would he go from here?
I think what they did was actually a magic trick where they like planted some seeds or
like some innuendo and they just let people fill in the gaps.
Of course.
Yeah.
And especially kids.
They're like, well, I know two magicians.
It has to be one of them.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because it is pre, it's right before Blaine and it's before Angel kind of.
So yeah, who will?
He names a couple at the end and like, yeah, that's, that's all I got.
I don't, I don't believe this is Penn or Teller.
That doesn't seem right.
They have their own brand that they don't have to do this.
It could have been, it would have been funny if it was Teller, but he's too short to be
Penn.
Yes.
Penn is too tall.
Let's, let's talk about the mask itself as recreated by Jason.
Thank you.
The mystery, the streaks, the mysterious streaks and then kind of this, you know, yours is
cloth Jason, but the real one I feel like was kind of a, kind of a hard shell, maybe with
some cloth components.
Yeah.
And to me, does this make any sense to me?
It looks like a, it looks like a, like an almond, like a sinister, big sinister almond.
I know.
I don't, I don't see it necessarily, but I think I see what you're saying.
You know, it's around it or, you know, or if there was a watermelon from hell.
Uh huh.
Well, I'm trying to figure out if it's the same mask the whole time, because later on
there's like.
I think it changes.
It changes, right?
Because there's paint on the chin.
The bullet catch trick, they have to draw streaks on his chin because he's got to be
able to move his mouth.
And then of course in the last one, he starts talking, which had been verboten in the earlier
ones.
Like we can't hear him talk.
They kept saying it's not as regular assistance and you can't hear him talk.
Not as regular assistance.
Yeah.
That's a big way to throw you off the trail.
They did their homework.
There was no, they covered their tracks.
Hopefully they put this guy in a burlap sack and threw him into the studio.
Yes, of course.
Nobody could get a view on him.
But the, I do just love the, I mean, there's like kind of a Batman thing to it also.
It requires so much eye acting.
It really makes this get, which I will credit him for.
I think that his like hand work is, is good and cool.
That's obviously like all he has to work with, but boy, he'll just strike the big wide eyes.
Oh yeah.
It's like, it's all he's got really.
And it does just like create a character that with apologies to the guy is more compelling
than the guy.
Once you see him.
Right.
Yes.
Then Val, can I say his name?
Yeah, sure.
Val Valentino.
Val Valentino, who it turns out to be.
Yes.
And the mask is kind of scary.
And as a kid, I was a little scared of him.
Yeah.
There's a homemade, there's a homemade quality to it that also I think adds even to some
of the scariness.
Yes.
What you did, Jason, is not terribly different than, I feel like the streaks in the real
thing are kind of like patchy and uneven.
Right.
It is not, that, that aspect of it is not Darth Vader-esque.
It is not the highest tech, the highest design on him.
And when Jane was working on it, I was like, hey, feel free to smear it a little.
And I knew China, China markers pretty easy to smear.
So I was like, oh, this will be good because it won't make me, it's a wax.
It won't make me pass out.
I think he looks like almost aquatic or like alien and something like this, this picture
of him, especially.
Sure.
A little aquatic or something like a little blue, like tentacle.
Something like that.
So, so.
I see what you're saying.
Obviously his hand movements are distinctive, but too, I feel like as it goes on, he's
like crossing his arms.
He's like doing the David S. Pumpkins arm cross in, in some of them, especially number
four.
I did it to him again.
Not to jump ahead, but number four, they start to lose the heat a little.
I think maybe before that, because like the first one, you know, I think they may be only
intended for there to be one of these, but then it's such a massive hit.
They commissioned much more, but by then they've blown off a lot of the like basics, fundamentals.
You get like a rabbit out of a hat in the first, or you get like big, big basics.
And then the things that I think in the second one, it's like a big Houdini one.
It's like one of the, he's going to drown sort of things.
And they're like, cause Fox, you know, you need the later, the big scary thing where
there's going to be a death probably.
And then the third one, I think what they're pushing is like the secret to a car getting
crushed by a tank.
And then the, I guess the magicians in there and it's, it's just not a, it's not a primary.
It's I guess it seems interesting.
I'd like to see that car get crushed, but also you're showing it to me now.
And at this point, I assume that the answer is like a compartment or a trap door because
that's the answer to all of them.
So you can see by number three, how, all right, we don't, we don't really have our last act,
which is why for the fourth, they they're like, all right, we got to do it.
We just got to show the guy what else is going to get these ratings up again, because we're
down to only, only 12 million viewers.
This is eating shit.
Only 12 million people watch number three.
Number four, excuse me, is a lot of specialty made stuff.
Okay.
Yeah.
You mean it's far.
Like it's not just the rabbits out of the hat.
Like a room underground.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's elaborate.
It's elaborate trap door.
I like trap doors, but by the end, it's like too many trap doors, too many custom made
devices.
Yes.
And when that's the answer to something that you've never seen before to begin with, now
we've kind of lost some of the luster.
So that first one is really like, let's rip through all the biggest, none of which I can
remember now, as I try to think of examples, I did watch, I watched all of the originals
because this came back for another special in 2002 and then a series in 2008.
It wasn't Valentino by that point.
I don't even remember if it's Pileggi.
Just seemed like too much.
I was like, let me, let me, let me just focus on the nineties.
Yeah.
I looked that up because I don't think those are canon in my, my eyes.
Pileggi, I think maybe came back and did some voiceover for the later ones.
And I think Valentino has a producer credit.
But neither of them on camera.
Is that the deal?
It seems.
Yeah.
That's, that's what it seems like.
And had been unpromoted to my network TV from Fox primetime.
My network TV is like the decay of UPN.
Is it?
Well, or is it just what, I don't know.
What is it?
It's, I think it's, it's my blank in whatever city it's in.
Someone, a professor explained this to me once and we're all like, huh?
And it's like, yeah, it's, it's almost like lower than UPN.
It seems kind of complicated.
Is some people's Fox, my network TV with some, sometimes you see Fox on that.
I don't know.
Uh, this is a, this is a very dull, I know.
My network TV is not me TV.
No, me TV is different.
Is that what Svenguli is on?
Is it me TV?
I believe Svenguli is on me TV.
Stop hamfisting your things into this episode.
That's all I have to say about Svenguli.
We'll get to Svenguli.
This is our thing.
First episode later.
I let it meet Svenguli.
I won't talk about him more.
Uh, um, but the, a big thing we got going here as always is established at the beginning
is the threat that this guy doing this, that he has to do it under secrecy because he may
be blackballed from the magician's community.
Yes.
What this implies, this, that it's, it's been a handshake code for hundreds of years and
he is the first to blow up the handshake code.
Right.
Um, and you start imagining just like a conspiring group of, uh, uh, why am I flashing this?
Yeah, I think in the ladies man, there's a bunch of men who are like mad at the ladies
man because he fucks all the women better than they can.
That's what you feel.
You start picturing some group of magicians all going like, girl, we gotta get him.
And I can't tell.
It's, it's almost the most effective magic trick that the specials do is making you imagine
that where you're like, was that ever the case?
Was anybody actually mad at this or threatened by this or just some magicians were?
Well, the other thing I learned is that there are multiple like brotherhood of magicians,
Academy of magical arts, like brotherhood of mystical.
There's, there's a lot of trade groups.
It seems like, um, yes, the, uh, the Orlando magic I looked up, I assume that's like a
magic group in Orlando.
Yes.
I think I got that right.
Okay.
Yeah.
All kinds of organizations.
They're a team of magicians.
It's a funny thing.
The whole black balling.
We're going to get this guy out of the Alliance forever because I mean, all right, it definitely
does ruin the luster of some of these illusions to know how they're done.
But, you know, in a lot of cases, Jason, as you were saying, it does become, uh, you know,
like, like if I am, I watch these specials and like, wow, these taught me that anybody
can be a magician as long as you know the secrets.
Okay.
So all I have to do is have some carpenters build a special box with a compartment and
then a special place for an assistant to put her arm.
And you know, when I have the Batman 66 as spike mechanism builds, I just need to make
sure that the spikes are retractable and that they are custom built to my assistant's
back contours so that the spikes can retract and then rest along her back.
And the actual like this, you know, so much of this is like, so you want to see how I
did it?
It's easy.
Six hundred thousand dollars were spent building a special thing.
Yeah.
It's sort of, you know, it ruins it, but it's also like, yeah, but the effort, if anything,
this might have been the intent in a way.
It also like illuminates, you know, the craft involved and how, you know, some of these
things, very impressive amount of production.
I also feel, and I think this is similar to what you're saying.
I also feel in a similar way to a lot of like old professional wrestlers who were upset
when Vince McMahon finally said, oh, this is predetermined.
We're like, oh, well, yeah, of course.
Like I feel like there was part of it was like, if the public knows we didn't really
saw someone in half and put them back together, they're never going to go to a magic show
again.
You're like, oh, everyone knows that this is not real.
If you as an audience member, if the point of your experience is to go, ha, that wasn't
real.
Right.
I don't, you know, I, yeah, I think I think we're all aware of that.
I think in the late nineties, people didn't think that people were being sawed in half
and then put back together.
I don't think.
Yeah.
Only in these rooms, like, no, you could not just go to any surgery theater that you wanted
to and watch a man be operated.
You can't just watch a live heart transplant, but this we know this, you can pay money and
go see.
Speaking of professional wrestling, there is one of these that I think got relegated
to a UPN or a mind network TV of like professional wrestling secrets exposed.
Oh, yes.
Where they show you like, oh, the there's mics under the ring.
Sure.
Here's how this is maybe pre broken.
This is a real punch, but it's pulled.
I know you think that the way Hulk Hogan punches looks perfectly realistic and exactly how
a real fight would go.
But no, no, no.
Yeah, no, it's, it makes all the sense in the world that wrestlers punch and then also
stomp on the floor while they punch.
Yes.
You can take 50 punches to the head and you can still rally and come back.
And Jay Leno can get into the ring and dominate.
Hulk Hogan.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just a matter of how you do the hold.
Right.
Yeah, there was a wrestling special produced by the same group, Nash Entertainment.
That's where they went after this was a, well, now let's ruin wrestling.
With real, those are real wrestlers.
They're all different characters, most of them wearing masks.
Oh, they did.
Oh, it is a masked wrestler special.
There's a lot of masks because I think like, oh, they don't want to be caught on camera
for a thousand dollars, you know.
Wow.
You can go through the website of Nash Entertainment and see.
They didn't make all of those Darnell era Shocking Fox specials, but a lot and the list
is crazy.
Let me just call out a few world's scariest ghosts caught on tape.
When good pets go bad, secrets of psychics revealed.
Oh, they're going to ruin psychics for us.
Oh, no.
What do I have left?
There's a couple like alien ones, but the one that's the most interesting to me is all
these like long clunky names and then it gets to rods, all caps, rods.
They're not flying saucers or mysterious lights in the night sky.
They're a curious new kind of UFO, one that's been caught on tape all over the world.
We startling new evidence, aliens could be among us.
Experts call them rods and they can barely be seen with the naked eye.
You come across rods before in your alien travels?
Absolutely.
I have seen.
Is rods a big area?
Yeah, there's different types of different like common shapes and rods.
I have seen.
Okay.
of cylindrical or circular or spherical type things, but yeah, no rods are out there.
Keep your eye on the sky.
Look out for rods.
They're UAPs now.
What's UAPs?
I'm trying to remember now.
Unidentified Alien Phenomenon?
No, yeah, maybe that's what it means.
Look what it is.
UAP.
I buy it.
Mm-hmm.
UAP definition is, here we go, I'm looking it up, la, la, la, la, la.
UAP is Unidentified Aerial Phenomenon.
Aerial Phenomenon.
Not alien.
Okay.
If you had then looked it up and like, oh no, it's unbelievable ass pussy, why did I look
that up?
Ooh.
I gotta check into these codes.
I've never said that word on this show before and I never will.
I just want to say that.
A few of the word pussy on podcast override?
I've never said it.
I can't remember a time when I said it.
I gotta say, National Entertainment did not get the word out about Clipaholics, the Jason
Alexander hosted clip show.
Oh my God.
I need to do an episode on Clipaholics.
With no further information, Clipaholics must be.
I actually, fuck, you know, I was gonna maybe pitch you guys, because I went down this rabbit
hole of like, inane music videos that Jason Alexander is in.
I just sent Andrew Grissom a show that Jason Alexander was in that I've never heard of
before.
Who was that?
And I got a fine, I was like, what is this?
Is it the sitcom where he plays the host of Pardon the Interruption?
Oh my God, what?
Yeah, he plays the sports, right?
I don't know.
He's the star of, I don't even want to say the videos, I don't know how to frame this.
Jason, I don't know, miscellaneous Jason Alexander crap, is that the episode?
Jason Alexander's music video career.
Yeah, there are enough, there's enough to do it.
They're pretty funny.
Well, you know what, it's gotta be a construct that also lets you talk about him in Criminal
Minds, where he has long gray hair.
Oh, Criminal Minds.
Well, and my professors in school always taught music videos and commercials, because a lot
of directors kind of go back and forth in those fields.
One more creative filling, one more monetary fulfilling.
The Mick DLT, where he gets to use a little of his musical theater talent.
Oh, yes, so his big pre-sign filled, yes, yeah, okay, all right.
We'll figure out what to call it, but Jason Alexander, hey, if you could throw it on a
Club 3 poll, if you're out there and you want to grab Jason Alexander just for you
Club 3 VIPs, I don't blame you.
Grab him by the long luscious locks.
It is Criminal Minds.
The mysterious long gray hair of a criminal mind.
I'm gonna find this, I'm gonna find what it was.
I already don't remember what you were looking at.
It's a Jason Alexander show you never heard of.
It's not Clipaholics and it's not the show where he plays the part in The Interruption
Guy.
And it's not Bob Patterson.
No, I know Bob Patterson.
Give me some credit, I know his sitcom where he's a motivational speaker.
He knows Creeping Bob Patterson.
Do you know, though, that he separately had a different motivational speaker persona?
Yes.
There's Bob Patterson, but then there was Donny Clay.
They are not the same.
Was that the Funny or Die sketch?
He did that on Funny or Die, yes.
Of course I know that.
Uh-huh, with that creepy couple.
He made a sort of cancelable video, I forget what that was.
Do you wanna go through the allusions or some of the other, I guess, the other notable people
who are in this special?
Sure, yes.
Not his usual assistants, keep in mind.
Not his usual assistants, which is very funny.
I mean, I guess if you worked in magic, you do.
Might be a way to know.
I saw something online, though, that like, oh, some of his affectations or movements,
some people that are in the magic world, I kinda guess, like, I think that's Valentino.
Hard Copy looked into it, and a guy who worked at a magic shop looked at receipts, and he
saw where a lot, like tons of very expensive magic equipment was going, and it was to maybe
like, I'm gonna say Kentucky, and then he looked up what magicians are in Kentucky,
and I think already there'd been the rumors about this, Valentino, and then Hard Copy
confronted the guy, although it seems very fakey, like this whole thing, maybe Valentino
himself may have started the rumors just to get the old Valentino publicity up.
Sure.
So, anyway, so yes, but part of the, you gotta remember, before the reveal, it was crazy,
everyone was accusing each other.
You'd accuse your own father or mother of being the mass magician.
A paranoia was running high among everyone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, mass magicians could be everywhere, could they be in your home, in
your church, in your bed?
People constantly like, trying to like, they had a mask, or they'd hold it up and see could
this fit, like my dad or something.
Police lineups.
Yeah, exactly.
They'd make a bunch of people come in and put a mask on.
They could be in my home.
Right, yeah.
Okay, but you were saying, are there other notable people who appear in these?
Notable people, which I guess is a way to also talk about some of the narration written
for Mitch Pileggi, is alternately very horny and horny, like there's some very horny and
some very in poor taste.
That was the exact, that was completely what I took away from it, is how often it just
gets seized already in that zone and then we start going like, I mean, just a basic
is like, and you know, and that's when your eyes, he does the trick while your eye is
caught by one of his lovely assistants.
What a distraction.
There's a lot of innuendo about that.
There's a very odd one where he comments on someone's midriff.
Yes, I, yeah, I, speaking of Andrew Grissom, I sent him a copy of it because he loved these
specials too, he's saying, and I sent him a memo of, which is, it's something like,
this angle gives you a close up view of how our assistant fits into the compartment.
It also gives you a nice view of her midriff.
And that also, that it's horny, that's what's confusing about the horniness, is that it's
horny but for a midriff, which is kind of, it feels like a kind of a clunky, like a technical
term almost, a bare midriff, but saying like, oh, if I could get my hands on that midriff.
Look at that, I mean, I guess you could be like those abdominal muscles, like it could
be a little more clinical, but I really enjoy looking at the abdominal muscles.
And that sweet tummy.
That's because the assistants are, they're beautiful, obviously, but then they just,
they look like JLo backup dancers, you know, they're as attractive as anyone, any women
on TV at this time.
It is, it is strange, the like, oh my, my, my, my, my, about like, yeah, sure, yes, you're
not wrong, but it's also not the sexiest clothes or presentation I've ever seen, but to Mitch,
I guess.
Right.
Now I'd like to, I like the idea that Mitch went like rogue during the doing of the video.
Can I freestyle here?
I'm going to go off, something on screen gave me an idea, and you know what, it gave me
a little more than an idea too, if you know what I'm saying.
Here's the one I wrote down verbatim, because it's like so kind of like simultaneously,
like horny and clunky, now it is, John, here it is.
Of course, he couldn't pull off this escape without the help of his beautiful assistants,
also made in America, also very well built.
So that's coming off a car, where they drop a giant weight on a car and destroy it, which
the solution is so insane.
I kept rewatching it because it's like, okay, when the assistant closes the door, it activates
a secret latch, which dumps him onto the ground and dumps a motorized dummy onto the seat
so that you could still have a live feed of a dummy squirming of something, all right,
there's a body in there, move around.
They zoom in on the dummy, and meanwhile, he is getting out of his like Velcro restraints,
Velcro bag, crawls into especially made like gurney bottom, and you can just see him get
wheeled off, like it's so complicated, I kind of loved it.
Look, it's simple, we'll expose this, as long as you have a car that you're willing to crush,
a big heavy weight to crush it with, a secret compartment in the car that can help you slide
out, and a mechanized dummy to put in a bag to squirm, and a live video feed to prove
that there is a moving body in there.
That's all it takes, these magicians, they're fly-by-night, they're hucksters.
Now, there is a simpler solution in the terms of the prestige, he must be using a double,
because there is a trick, I think it's the teleportation trick, where it's like, how
does that assistant get from here to there?
They're twins, like, and the twins in this trick are the climb-a-zooski twins, climb-a-zooski,
that's a long word, yeah, this is a tough one, climb-a-zooski, they're the Coors Light
and Twins twins, a few years later.
I keep seeing the Coors Twins, what the hell, what were these ads?
These ads, oh man, these ads were huge at the start of the new millennium, they would
say like, something on TV, and Twins, and I, this is what and Twins is from?
This is, I believe, where and Twins originates, and they are the twins in this one illusion,
they would go on to be a part of WCW, they're on the dance team, the Nitro Girls, yeah,
they were Nitro Girls, and then they were gold and silver, as well as lolly and pop,
in a segment with Johnny the Bull and Big Vito LaGrasso, of course, yeah.
They went to, they were signed by WWF, went to Developmental, didn't really go much further.
I get them confused with the Miller Lite Catfight Girls, who were on many Miller Lite commercials
and then appeared on WWE.
Mike, Mike, get a paper towel, your sweat on your brow is dripping on the microphone,
you're going to electrocute yourself.
Every beer had a different set of girls that appeared on many commercials, I hear some
Ford voice.
Let's do an episode about beer girls.
We don't even have to put that one out, that's just for the boys.
Well that one, and then in that appearance of these very prominent twins, soon to be
extremely prominent twins, you get the line, most major magicians employ twins, and you
thought all they were good for was gum commercials.
Yeah I did think that all twins were good for.
Good for nothing twins, I've always said.
Then the gum commercials proved me wrong, all right, sure, those, but name me one other
example of twins who were good for anything.
Yeah.
Did we get the double mint hat?
No, I'm sorry.
Do you think there was a draft of any of the, or like a version of this copy where they
were like, God, this is so boring, this special, can you horny it up a little bit so we got
something to say in between?
Might have been Mike Darnell's notes.
Was it Darnell?
Look, we're covering the scariness angle of Fox, but we have no sexiness, so yeah, let's
horn it up.
Let's get it, and it's not just that there's ladies here, it's that Pileggi has to make
very good, interesting remarks.
Let's say you pull a rabbit out of a hat, boy I'd like to see one of his assistants
in nothing more than a hat.
That's actually too on the nose.
That's a little clever, yeah.
Now that's too much.
Fox standards and practices would say no, not that.
So the line is it has to be more, I mean the midriff thing is what I find funny.
It's like not, it's never over, it's not like I'd like to do something, it's just like yeah.
As long as he can break any, he can reveal all the tricks that he wants, as long as he
never makes her midriff disappear.
As long as he never makes any clothes appear over that midriff.
Oh man, I can see the place where she was connected to her mother to get nutrients in
the womb.
Clear view of the clavicle from this recording booth.
It's true, post having a kid you're like, hmm, belly buttons, I'm not sure my interest
in belly buttons is too high anymore.
There used to be a tube made of organic material that was connected to that midriff.
Boy the wonders of life, the greatest magic in all the universe.
Thank you God for all you do for us, the ultimate magician God.
I would love to have your secrets revealed God, please.
Maybe God will be unmasked when we reach eternal life.
I don't think it's gross, but God wants us to ingest this placental material for nutrients.
There's a cookbook or two out there.
I'd like to eat these women's placentas.
Too much, too much.
That's too, hang on, it's mine or Zoe's.
I self corrected that Mike Darnell would tell me that that was too much.
I was just observing that they're out there, okay.
Yeah, no Darnell would have noted me on that.
Mike, that was too much.
You want to tantalize, it's a magic trick, whatever, showing or saying anything.
Though they start pushing it a little more because here's another one that involves
spikes going right through one of the assistants and then he says, at last, some penetrating
television.
Okay, yeah, that is, I would have noted that, I would have said no.
One where he's sawing an assistant in half, I hope he's got it right this time, be ashamed
to mess up a body like that.
And implies he hasn't gotten it right in the past, or that's part of the illusion that
you're worried it's going to.
I see me, Mitch Pileggi, they show me all the raw footage.
They've they've they've gone through a couple of assistants.
It would be I start narrating and I go, oh, now look at that midriff.
Oh, no, the midriff's getting torn in half.
Wait, guys, cut this one.
Oh, thanks for flagging it, Mitch.
Was that the one word a bloody saw created havoc in the woman's body?
He killed another woman.
It's a bummer to me because I won't be able to enjoy looking at her body while I'm in
a VO booth.
Oh, that's the tragedy here.
Oh, man.
Jane was watching some of these and I forget when she finally tapped out.
I forget whether it was one of his lines or it was just the accumulation of just like,
oh, so you're saying, yeah, the misogynistic words.
But it was not.
She was still engaged by the magician revealing secrets.
Well, I mean, we are all engaged.
OK, I just want to make sure it should not be.
But they distract.
Well, they should have gone the other way.
Like, you know, we may never know the masked magician's true identity and he might never
pull that shirt up so we can see what he's got going on in terms of midriff.
That's the fix. Yes.
If he could just be equally horny for the masked magician, for Val, Valentino.
Who knows who's back there?
And if he has, I don't know, boobs on his forehead.
Oh, that's what I like to imagine.
Just a solid man with forehead boobs.
I wonder how tight his calves are.
I wonder if they're too.
Masked magician, why don't you whip it out?
You got nothing to lose.
We can't see your face.
If you get laughed at, nobody knows who you are.
If you're packing some if you're packing some heat, then you might want to take that
mask off sooner than later.
And it turns out we can't see his dick either because it's got a tiny little mask on it.
He came prepared.
Came prepared.
Most working magicians have at least several dick masks in their arsenal.
Step one, hire twins.
Step two, dick mask purchasing.
Did I miss any of these?
They're so fun. I'm glad you guys clocked this, too.
It is like, you know, because the rest of this is all they're all interesting.
They're all engaging. But like America, I kind of fell off after the first one.
As they go, the only things that are striking my interest are these horny lines.
Oh, shit, that might have been all.
Oh, wait, I don't know the context of this, but I think he at some point I wrote down
that he says, oh, oh, OK, it must be it must be another sliced in half.
We're like, yeah, right. Then it's revealed that she is OK.
And he says, and her stomach looks just fine.
God, God.
I think that was a maybe it wasn't because you could say that just
and her stomach looks just fine.
But he's like, I think is I think I know what you want here.
You want me to put a little Mitch on it.
Mitch it up.
Detective Skinner would never or whatever.
Director Skinner would never would never say that.
That's why I love playing the role of plain old Mitch Pileggi.
I can say and do things, think things that Skinner
uptight Skinner never would write.
I always keep telling the X-Files guy, when are you going to live with the producers?
When are you going to let me show off Skinner's midriff?
I work all day and night on this baby.
You don't let me show it off.
Hey, X-Files creator Chris Carter,
when we're writing the new episode, why don't we show some of these alien
autopsy photos and give them more of a womanly shape?
What do you think?
And then I can comment on them.
I can mention what I like about him.
He's pitching like, oh, yeah, this new show, Millennium.
I've got some ideas if you want to hear.
I'm going to do a voiceover the whole time on the show.
Any time I can see a belly button, I'm going to really let.
Can I just do the closed caption track?
You're going to you're going to need that, right?
For the blind.
Let me handle.
I am thinking like you, Mike, you were talking about meeting Jonathan Freaks.
Now, if I ever meet Mitch Pileggi,
I am only going to ask him about the mass magician.
And hey, what was recording narration like?
Were you in a booth?
Were you between, you know, were you at lunch from the X-Files
and they get you when you were on break?
You'll see him.
You'll see him visibly start sweating because of the sexual memories
he's going to have. Yeah.
He was horned up the whole time.
He was doing those memories are just for me.
Yeah. Well, per my request, we didn't do it in a voiceover booth.
We did it in a bed with satin sheets.
I laid down.
They mounted a television on the ceiling above me
and I demanded they all leave the room.
This is a safe space for just Mitch.
And you guys are giving a lot.
You're assigning a lot to Mitch.
I feel like he was just doing a job.
Oh, just following orders, Jason.
Is that what you're saying?
Oh, boy, here we go.
You know, he was just I know I think he was just cocky.
He was just reading what was written for.
But I think but, you know, I think actors have to do like
do a full dive, go all the way there.
Yeah. He reads that copy like, OK, so I have to inhabit
the horniest mind in America.
Well, so be it.
To be the Fox Network Fox. Transform.
I'm going to transform myself.
I mean, I love it's the best part about these, I got to say.
I it pulls a lot of focus.
Here I am, like not even watching the tricks after a while.
We're waiting for I'm clocking these lines for Pileggi.
Yeah. Uh huh. Yep.
He should really they should get him back,
but he should just do sort of narrating any other magics
like a Chris Angel magic special and just comments about Chris and stuff.
Like, oh, yeah, that hair.
Look at that hair like the brush that back behind his ear.
Hope it's real.
Hope it doesn't come off of his head when I touch the hair.
Boy, I'd like to take off that studded belt
and that other studded belt and the third studded belt.
That's a man you look at.
You go, hmm, wonder if he has ideas for Italian ice.
Oh, this Jonathan Davis music is really getting me in the mood.
Hmm. Yeah.
Anything any any magic.
What I think I just thought, wait, it's OK.
And that's how he makes a handkerchief disappear.
And boy, when I look at those assistants,
let's just say I'm going to need a handkerchief when I'm done.
You know what?
You're going to want to see that handkerchief disappear as fast as can be.
Do I think you've captured the voice perfectly, the special.
See, this is what happened.
I think I see I'm going to stay stuck like this from now on.
Four episodes from now when we're talking about the teacups, it'll say hello.
So Scott Gardner here here to talk about the maddest tea party there ever was.
Like, I'm not even saying anything sexual.
I just can't.
I'm not going to be able to shake it the longer I stay at it.
Right. Yeah. Hot, hot tea.
I had 12 and hot at 12 or 13.
You think I'd be like interested in this.
But I was so like, how's he going to get out of that coffin?
And like, you know, I was not.
I was not. I didn't clock any of this.
No, I was all I say.
Yeah. Well, shows you where all of our brains were.
But maybe our dads know.
Yeah, maybe.
But this is this this is for the dead.
You don't want to think about.
Look, you don't want to think about Pileggi as a sexual creature when you were 12.
You know, I was thinking about him giving Scully and Mulder so much grief.
Yeah. But now I am wondering if Pileggi was like pitching its publicists like,
look, Scully and Mulder get to be in sexy spreads and magazines.
When it's my turn, you know, Pileggi
never get to do a sexy spread.
I don't know that he did.
He was never in bed with between the two of them on like a Rolling Stone cover.
I feel like he maybe had like if he was in a photo spread,
he had like a button or two undone.
And that was as sexy as it got.
Let's find the sexiest photos of Mitch Pileggi.
The sexiest Pileggi.
Why was why can't there?
Why can't Pileggi go Playgirl?
Every he should have been in Playgirl.
They I mean, everybody in the especially in the 90s, they had their sexy
photo shoot if you want to have a popular TV show.
But yeah, Pileggi was, I mean, the third lead on the show.
Yeah. Basically, I found it pretty well.
This is this isn't like a photo shoot, but here he is shirtless from something.
Oh, wow. Yeah, there you go.
Yep. You didn't think I could make glasses sexy, did you?
Wow. Pileggi can do it all.
He really can.
Gosh. So that well, look, he is if he is if you got a sexy results
in your first two lines of your Google image. That's true.
I think you're you're in a good place.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
So, yeah, we've realized that Pileggi is like kind of the star of these specials,
really. How about this one from this is from Stargate, Atlantis?
Stargate, Atlantis, another show.
There's nothing sexy going on, but he's he's just in like a greenish, grayish
jumpsuit, but he's kind of like a spread eagle, man spreading.
But it's also a very it's a little I mean, it might just be the cut of the suit,
but it's a little bit a little bulgy.
You can see it if that's what you're talking about.
Yeah, you can see it.
He's he's he knows, too.
You can see the look on his face.
He knows what he's doing.
He knows if you're taking a photo of that, he knows.
He prepped himself before the take.
Can I just can I fluff real quick?
I'm always prepped to prep needed.
It's always 50 percent.
I'm Pileggi. That's how I that's how I work.
When I'm on set, it's always 50 percent.
Is there can there just be ever can there ever be a scene
where there's a lady scientist and I say, I'd like to see your
Stargate. Yeah, you keep pitching the Mitch.
You pitch every three seasons and I don't know.
It doesn't feel appropriate for it is your work and your Stargate.
Take me. OK. OK, Mitch.
And now we're not even the cameras aren't even rolling.
I don't know. Doesn't matter.
Just we're stuck in Max Masked Magician mode, Mitch.
Ever since we did that, we do that special.
Now you say everything weird every day, every day, every time since you did it.
Mulder Scully, we spend all this time focusing on the X files.
What about the X, X, X files?
Oh, man, she's got to be deprogrammed.
We have to take him to, like, a we never we never got him back.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, Nash Entertainment can find some of those psychics if they. Yeah.
Unless they exposed all of them too much.
Mr. Pileggi, I hate to say this, but the test results have come back.
You're permanently horny.
It's an uncurable condition.
Hey, I hope they never find one.
Good news.
I hope I test positive for the rest of my life.
Does he, by the way, does he introduce himself as just Valentino in the special?
Yes. Yes. When we get to the end.
Yeah, it is just Valentino.
I mean, we'll get let's OK.
I mean, we can head for the because the reveal is a big part of it
and something like darling implied.
But like on the way to it, besides the sexy, sexy voice of Mitch Pileggi,
is there anything we want to shout out?
Anything that was like genuinely interesting to find out
throughout these specials?
Really, it's just like just to make sure I say it.
The so much of this thing is just pace and ominous.
Yeah. Yeah. The feeling that we're getting away with something
because you could do there is a much drier sort of I don't want to say
Mythbusters because Mythbusters has a style and an energy.
But like they could have done the same special
on the history channel or whatever.
Yeah, you could just you could do this in a really dry way
and it would have no impact.
But how much of this is just that mood, just the air and waiting?
And it gets so it does get like, all right, now we watch one slowly
and then there's dancing and form and like, so how did we do it?
And then you watch it all again.
It is just it is it's not like 80 percent of this thing is style.
Yeah. And as yeah, especially when you're a kid and you
you don't notice how you're being manipulated by mood and style.
Yeah. Yeah. So effective.
And yeah, repeat like replaying things over and over.
You don't notice like, oh, they're patting this out a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's ones where they do kind of like drawing on the screen.
Like, look right there. A crew guy. Did you see it?
Yeah, I saw when you surf it.
Yes. I think it's extremely, extremely clear as the clip show editor
veteran. Right. This is a you got never worked for Nash.
No, I never worked for Nash.
And I never worked for that Jason Alexander clip show.
That's what you want. I was a dream.
Ways of the dream. Yeah.
David Faustino clip show, but not Jason Alexander.
So you're way up sitcom side. Yeah, you got to earn it.
Yeah. So, yeah, you you got to reuse this footage.
You know, you got to do it.
You got to show it from different angles.
You got to punch in. You got to do all all the tricks.
Yeah. Yeah. Milk it for all it's worth. Right.
But any but like things that were like that actually was I
I never knew how they did that.
Spoiler alert, I guess, for listeners, if you don't want these illusions
ruined forever, I turn off the podcast now.
I do like first of all, I'll say that there's a YouTube channel.
I'm sure we all found it.
I assume that has all these clips on it. Yes.
Like an official Masked Magician YouTube.
And they like they they have posted the same clips maybe once a year.
So you can find the exact same clips with the same titles
from different years posted.
So I don't know if that's something that helps them with the algorithm
to get views or whatever. Yeah.
But I found one of them that I like.
I like it when it's a really dumb, simple trick.
And like the explanation is simple.
Like there was one where they have four different,
I don't know, you'd call them bases and one there's a knife.
Did you see this?
There's like one of them is going to have a knife on it.
There's four bases.
And then you'll put styrofoam cups over all four of them.
And Masked Magician will slam his hand down on all three of the cups
and will not like impale his hand on the knife.
And the assistant, while he turns his back, the assistant moves the cups around
three card, what is it?
Three card monti table style.
And then he turns around, he comes back and it's very dramatic.
He crushes three of the cups and then, of course, takes the last one off.
And the knife is there.
And the way that is done is one of the bases just has a little string
attached to it.
And the assistant, like they make sure to put the knife
on the one that has the little string.
So when he goes over and sees the four cups, it's clear to him
that there's a string. Oh.
And that's where the knife is.
And like, it's just dumb.
It's an easy dumb trick that you probably won't notice
because the string is so thin.
Little string is the solution on a lot of the illusions. Yeah.
Contortionist assistant, that's like, yes.
Squeezing into like a secret area or a secret wall.
Although a tiger, the very first, like in the very first special,
there is one where they, quote unquote, make a tiger disappear, I think.
Or appear in a, they send up an assistant and then a tiger shows up.
The tiger is in like behind a fake wall.
So they have to feed the tiger a lot of raw meat before they trap it
in a fake wall.
And then it's still it's still airborne with because the assistant
ultimately just goes into a little compartment under it,
but has to share a really tight space with a tiger.
Yeah, that's kind of upset.
That one's kind of like, boy, that's still sort of death defying.
I think for this.
But yeah, a lot of the answer to so many of them is just compartments
and a really flexible assistant, which is a perfect fodder
for all it takes is flexibility. Right.
Here's a good narration bit that's not a corny, but is confusing.
That this is a real straight jacket, the kind you'd find in any good asylum.
And it's like, that's a little catty that if they're not corny,
they're very like a bit cheat.
Like, it's a diss of bad asylums.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Lacks asylum with no straight jackets.
Unprofessional asylum, huh?
Not again.
Let down by the funding, the government funding for the next time.
The next time you're taking a loved one to stay in an asylum forever.
First question should be straight jackets or no.
They say, no, you're out the door.
Yeah, it's all look, it's a he can sell anything with that voice, really.
Including shooting an arrow with a gun.
Yeah, that is another little string one.
And also the put upon crew guy
waiting for his cue, there's a number of shots of put upon
crew guys hiding behind something to fire a target or in one case,
make a very elaborate conveyor belt appear,
like so we can crawl out so it doesn't get burned alive.
Oh, right. OK.
This is this. OK.
I don't know if you guys found this, this crossover with the Masked Magician.
Cross. Do you know what I'm talking about? No.
You mean the dramatic series crossover?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
And I believe that's the same illusion that is used in that.
Where there is a rig that like pulls a rope through.
It's it doesn't matter, but like it doesn't matter.
He get the he will just just say where you're going that.
Well, the TV show that Masked Magician crossed over on is Diagnosis Murder.
Yeah. Classic.
My grandparents love diagnosis and the premise.
CBS, Dick Van Dyke, medical.
Not I was going to say drama, but maybe I'd never seen the medical mystery.
It is a drama, light drama.
But yes, it's not.
He's a doctor, but he's always solving.
Yes. And it's dark comedies.
And then there are light, light dramas, which is what this seems to be.
And it was on for like eight years.
Yeah. And I've tried watching it over the years and it's mostly unwatchable.
Seemingly. This is the first I'd ever seen it.
Oh, my God. It's so much hokier than I thought.
Oh, I've watched a lot.
Diagnosis Murder, Matlock, Walker and the spinoff of Walker.
Martial Law was the Sammo Hung light martial arts.
Oh, yeah.
Cheech Marin in it. Or was it Chong?
Which one was in it? I forget.
But yeah, Diagnosis like Murder, she wrote,
I think looks like a masterpiece compared to Diagnosis Murder.
This is so dopey.
This is so dopey, which is certainly fun to be had.
But the premise of this episode is that someone is trying to kill
the Masked Magician because he's revealing the secrets.
Yes. And now could they have done this with just anybody
playing the Masked Magician and being in that mask?
Absolutely. But instead, they did it with the participation
of Val Valentino, the eventually demasked Masked Magician.
And it kind of seems like, you know, because presumably this
must have happened after he had unmasked himself.
And it's part of his publicity tour, because he tried to get like a big bump out of this.
He went and did every talk show. He was on everything.
He was on Regis and Kelly and various talk shows and whatever.
And this seems like the biggest, like, put a lot of eggs in this basket.
Yes. To start his dramatic acting career.
Oh, my God. It is the dumbest shit.
It's so dumb. And there's he does unmask when he's in the hospital.
But then there also is a scene or more than one scene where he is in the mask
talking to Dick Van Dyke in the hospital, in the hospital bed.
And so the mask is just nodding around.
I don't even know if it's like I'll just show it to Jason.
He hasn't seen it. But this is this is like when he's later on.
Well, I'm going straight over to the studio and start rehearsing for tomorrow night's broadcast.
I don't think it's a very good idea.
The Mask Magician is performing despite fervent protest from his team of top surgeons.
You just told me I was fine.
Yes, but I think there's a very good chance that whoever sabotaged that trick
is going to try it again.
And next time you may not be so lucky.
Daring death for you, the viewer. Use it.
If I was going to be scared off, I never would have done this in the first place.
Besides, I'm getting a big raise.
Wearing the mask there.
I mean, that's the head just nodding around is so, so funny.
Fucking funny. Yeah, yeah.
I've got a clip, too, which is that so the I think important context
is that he, you know, some of the excuse we nodded to this at the beginning
once he explained what he did and why, why he revealed these.
It was it was kind of pinned on.
Well, the, you know, people aren't interested in magic anymore.
And, you know, other media has kind of taken it over.
And magicians are letting the old tricks grow stale.
They're leaning on the same old tricks.
And I want it to shake up the whole game to, like, inspire the best out of everybody.
So then it leads to this scene where he is unmasked and he has a real arrow in him.
Is that right?
He's got to pull out.
He let yeah, he got an arrow.
And then, like, they left it in until he got to the hospital.
And then Dick Van Dyke, 72 year old Dick Van Dyke has to pull it out.
Oh, my God. So then you get this little scene.
Only this time someone put an explosive charge at Dick Van Dyke's son.
They want to kill me for revealing these old tricks.
Well, another quarter of an inch down, they would have to.
You know, I can't blame them for being angry.
Why would you want to take the wonder out of magic?
I love magic, but it's a dying art.
Thanks to unimaginative magicians who keep rehashing the same old tricks.
There's no magic about getting what is this problem?
Like, what is this?
That's what I that reading magicians talking about.
It's like, we didn't really worry about a lot of these solutions are like
a 90 or 100 years old and people do stuff kind of differently,
which would make sense to be that old these solutions,
because there's some corny ass stuff in here.
There's some like stuff where it's just like, that's just like a trap door.
Like, I I'm reading this book called I'm the Flash,
which is about a guy who, like in high school, he, you know,
gets roped into being a corny.
And and and he learns all the like, well, here's how you hide the docks.
Is this like a sliding doors for you?
Do you think like, why didn't it happen to me?
Oh, yeah. I don't think I had to worry about that.
It's so nasty.
Like, it's like the fifties and sixties.
And it's just like, I yeah, they're running like in school.
They're running like the numbers gate or like they're running bedding in school.
They're running a casino for the senior class at someone's house
until it gets shut down.
But there's very much some of the tricks where it's just like,
and then he palm this or it's like, and then the other contraption
that just made it disappear.
Like I've this copy or whatever this line he says about, you know,
magic is dying or whatever.
I see it in a lot of places.
This seemed to be kind of the like the premise of this whole special
or his philosophy.
But also, and correct me if I'm wrong, was he not just a cast in this special?
Like, it's yeah, they just need somebody to do it.
It's going to happen with or without him. Right.
And then like all this like mythology was built and like his reasoning for doing it
versus just like he wasn't doing that well as a magician.
And he was like, yeah, OK, I'll do some work, some, but not a ton.
And this is a way to kind of get an angle and maybe get some publicity out of it.
Also, just him. Yeah, it's so funny.
He has this stock. All right.
Here's my justification.
And you hear him say it in the actual special.
And then a couple of months later, you're watching him do it
from a hospital bed with fake struggling.
It's these other magicians.
Ouch. They just want to out me for oof.
All of my revealing of secrets.
Ah, don't they realize that movies and TV
ouch are making magic less popular than ever?
Aye. Also, his his magicians may
his real name is not Valentino.
And it's not it's I forget it's like a regular name. OK, sure.
When I was like, oh, Valentino, he must like, I don't know.
I was like, he might have an accent.
He might have some sort of like sexiness or mystery.
Just hearing that name.
And then he's like, hi, I'm Valentino. Yes.
Yeah, that's the big disappointment, isn't it?
I was just hoping that he had some sort of like lover's voice.
I'm Valentino.
Not Pileggi necessarily, but something going on.
The longer you let him talk in this thing, it's just I'm Valentino,
the mass magician.
Ah, why do they hate me?
He's less. He's got a less sexy voice than any of us.
Val Valentino, born Leonard Montano.
There you go.
I don't know. You can work with Leonard, especially if you got Leo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm Leo Montano.
You could always in the end. Yeah, you could work. You're right.
That's not too bad. But yes, Leonard, though.
Hello, I'm Leonard Montano.
Like that's sort of. Yeah.
And I was disappointed because I forgot how he sounded.
But when I started reading again and I was like, oh, Valentino,
oh, he must have some sort of exotic sounding voice.
Oh, ouch, doctor.
Ah, the magicians don't like me.
There there's some.
I'm trying to make them up their game.
Don't they see? Oh, Barry Van Dyke has more sexuality in that clip.
That it's so if you like, you know,
I like to imagine watching this, you know,
I'm going to show you this medical show.
Dick Van Dyke is in it.
But interesting fact, one of the other doctors is also Dick Van Dyke's son.
See if you can spot which one 10 seconds in.
Well, now, doctor, I think you really got to take a look at this guy.
Oh, should I? I think I think I should.
He's losing blood. Look at him. Oh, wow. You're right.
It's it's not, you know, a hokey.
It's nice that they got to work.
It's nice to get to work with your son.
Just in the same way that Lucille Ball, nice to work with her kids.
A TV legend gets to bring their kid and force them into a show.
That's nice, you know, and they get to work with them.
So sure, that's just a nice thing, I think.
For that lot of time, TV sets, it takes a long time.
That's probably bonded a lot while waiting for the lights to get set.
That's right.
If only Jack Lemmon could have been on Thunder in Paradise with his son.
That would have been better.
They would have bonded.
Hey, brother, if we get season five, you know,
you're going to get Jack in here.
The Holster loves the apartment, brother.
Jack's shooting a machine gun on the boat.
I mean, what gets me cooking like Glegary Gleg Ross, brother?
Brother, I don't want to drive to Orlando.
Can we film this in my backyard?
Just do a lot of close ups of me.
Tampa, you're saying? Yeah.
Uh, the there is there was a Valentino quote of these, like,
and this I'm blowing up after these specials.
I've been doing giant shows in Brazil for 18 months.
Then I went to Japan to do more giant shows.
And whatever it was, I couldn't track him in the media.
I'm like, oh, I think he's worth like I love magic.
I have a lot of respect for magic, but I think he's working us right now.
I think he's lying. Oh, perhaps.
Just when he's like a lot going on, a lot of stuff going on.
Do you see all the stuff I got going? Yeah.
Yeah, it really it's it's kind of it must add to the deflation of the whole thing.
Obviously, that when the unmasking happens, it's not one of the one
of the two magicians that you've heard of. Right.
But then also that, again, he's not some like fucked up scarred guy.
That's what you want. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That or at least just like, you know, I want I want like a, you know,
you want to like a like a Lawrence Fishburne looking guy, you know, like,
so like somebody cool or something.
But that he is just kind of this like pasty guy.
It's me, Valentino.
It is it's kind of a letdown. Yeah.
The way it plays out in the actual special.
I mean, I remember this one.
I remember the first one strongly.
And I remember the here it comes, here it comes.
What's it going to be?
And then that he he does a big speech where he does some of this justification.
And they deepen the voice, even though he's going to get unmasked.
He hasn't talked in any of the episodes. Right.
But they still deepen the voice,
even though we are about to hear his real voice and see his real face.
But he's still we got to go through this whole like, I'm not doing this
because of the pressure that I'm receiving from fellow magicians.
I'm doing this because of my love of magic.
It's all right. This is dorky, even with the pitch down.
In recent years, movies and video games have overtaken magic as our main.
And then he does an even worse one down the road where he's like, oh, wait,
this was in a fucking Reddit AMA later. Like, why did I do it?
Well, because magic was being lost
amidst the age of the information superhighway, he says, in like 2013.
Wow. Using that phrase out of it as this guy.
But anyway, you know, hey, because of these specials,
remember to remember back when the first one aired,
back when it got better ratings and what's airing right now.
Everybody was gathered by the water cooler the next day.
They were talking about magic the way it used to be.
Back in, you know, 1904, the way everybody gathered at the water
cooler the morning after seeing the Boudini show.
People are still chasing that goddamn water cooler like he has a kid.
I was just like, what is what is going on in water?
It's like a thing.
See, you'll see the great American watering hole.
Certainly offices won't get destroyed forever by a disease
taking away most making people not want to share from the same water
cooler ever again. Yeah.
I even when I worked in office, I feel like most people's
feeling was like, I want to get in and get or it's like, oh, God,
I don't want to run into someone.
Yeah. How quickly can I let be a head down?
Must focus. I look I would look up at you and be friendly.
But you see, I have to make sure that the water cooler is working properly.
And sometimes with tea, you got to press the other tab down.
So I got to be staring to I cannot be friendly to you right now.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's it's all it's all that's all an illusion.
Also, like movies and video games where I I
I loved movies and video games as a 12 or 13 year old.
And I was truly confused sometimes
when they were like the dangers of this stuff.
And I'm like, what are you talking about?
Even the violence, even the violent ones?
Yeah, it was pretty still pretty indifferent to like I was never
scared because I knew it was pretend.
I don't know. I think I was more scared at the mass magician of school.
Yeah, mass magicians and school shootings that would come.
So I think I was too. Yeah.
I was scared of two things, possibility of school shooting
and possibility of mass magician getting kicked out of the magicians alliance.
Yeah, I didn't like so terrified for this.
So the tension in this last minute is sky high.
And then like at some point, he's like,
so now magic is center stage again.
Could you honestly say that you've been hurt by watching these specials?
No. Hey, hey, hey, Mitch Pileggi
jumping in here, the opposite.
What if I guess I was hurt a little bit.
Blue balls.
What if he took it off and it was Pileggi?
Oh, man, that changes the entire thing.
Yeah, it really does.
It was right in front of you the whole time.
He was the host and he was the magician.
Fuck. That would have been awesome.
That's that's the sort of sinister behavior
I would expect from the cigarette smoking man, but not director Skinner.
But that would have been that would have propelled Pileggi into a whole another career.
Yes. Yeah. Oh, he'd be selling out.
He would have gotten the Vegas residency that Dopey Valentino.
Yeah. Could only dream of. That's right.
And you know, we got some assistance from those wacky lone gunmen
or three gunmen.
What are they called?
Huh? The lone gunmen, the three guys, the three guys.
Yeah, they must have been working behind the scenes to make all those contraptions.
You think they're making his tricks?
The actors. Probably.
Yeah, the actors making Pileggis.
Sorry, buddy. You say assistance.
My mind goes to one place.
Well, that's what I thought, too, when you said his assistance.
A midriff. A midriff.
I do not need to see the lone gunmen's midriff.
The three. What were they called?
What was their official name?
They had a spinoff show for one season.
Yeah, I remember.
Wasn't that the name of the show?
Am I crazy? What's the go? Why am I thinking?
Why am I not remembering?
The Gunmen musical comedy Variety's Bower.
Well, yeah, that Mike would remember.
Eventually, he gets to the justification of like, because of this.
OK, so, you know, so really all builds to like, and that's all thanks to me.
Smoke, but the fakest smoke puff,
the fakest thing of all of the specials.
Valentino, I read the deflation of that moment.
It really like sorry to stay in the horny front,
but it is such a boner killer.
That moment really like you because you understand everything.
OK, A, you're not famous.
B, you're not mysterious.
See, you're not like just remarkable in any way.
Like I expect like Ricardo Montalban with that name.
And like if you if you if you go like, holy shit, look at this guy.
I want a guy with black hair and a gray streak.
I want the guy to still be like some bizarre.
Who's the guy, the host of Plan 9 from outer space?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Whatever, you know.
I want some some weirdo.
But Valentino, you just like you could just tell this guy's got nothing going on.
He just doesn't have it.
And then he keeps talking a little too long.
And he says, oh, magicians everywhere have been letting go of their old tired tricks,
creating bigger and better illusions.
You see, I inspire.
They're all I made everything better.
I changed the whole magic economy.
Everybody's doing better tricks because of me.
I raised the bar.
And the next time you see me, I'll be working on newer, better.
And then you're like, I know, I know, as a 13 year old, I will never see you again.
I am sure of this.
Yeah, we never did.
Val Valentino is not even a that's not even that doesn't exist
in the like Chris Gaines, like weird pop culture cobwebs.
Like, remember this?
I don't Val Valentino gone.
That has never stayed in my head.
He failed.
He failed completely to ever have any sort of like mental foothold
because you kind of you do look at him and you're like, I enjoyed all these specials.
But yeah, kind of fuck you, dude, on behalf of magicians.
And he did get sued.
Got sued. Yeah, they got the production.
And because there were some magicians going like, well,
I spent $50,000 making that contraption.
And now everyone knows how it works.
Yeah, justifiably.
Some of those, you know, I expose the Houdini ones, I guess.
But if you have this is in people's current act, it kind of sucks.
In terms of the fallout of the whole thing, the hard copy
did a victory lap.
They said we were the first to expose him.
And then they went on to call him.
So who is this hocus pocus turncoat?
And then the segment keeps going.
And then there's a title at some point that they call him the magic rat.
Wow. Really? Not good publicity.
They say all the publicity is good, but I don't know about this one.
He might have literally been blackballed.
Maybe he tried like there was like he was going to do a show
and the magicians are all like, fuck him.
Hey, better than blue.
Um, hey, they he tried to like ride the wave a little bit and like,
you know, put on a little show for hard copy and hard copy follows him
to as he goes and like, here he is getting a makeover
by Giuseppe Franco, hairstylist of the stars.
We were throwing a lot of names out in this one.
You guys ever heard of Giuseppe Franco?
I don't know Giuseppe Franco.
If you Google Giuseppe Franco, what you will find is a lot of photos
of a guy who looks like a real life Zoolander because he has jet black spiked
hair that doesn't work on a man of that age.
Oh, my God. He's got a salon in Beverly Hills.
Yep. He's still he does it.
He is still a hairstylist to the stars.
And it's a lot of photos of him in between Stallone and Schwarzenegger.
Can we go and get his hair done by him?
Maybe, maybe.
It might cost us a lot of all the club three monies go into one hairstyle.
God, I want to go and get Giuseppe Franco makeover.
You might need to.
You're going to have to prove your you're going to have to show off
all your stats, like, you know, give them your whole history,
you know, screen junkies.
So, you know, I kind of got some stardom off that.
And, you know, just pitch yourself.
OK, on the website for Giuseppe Franco Salon,
there's a picture of model Tatiana Franco,
which I assume is a daughter, but perhaps a wife, a young wife.
I don't know.
But OK, I'll make a I'll make a reservation here.
These are very intriguing.
Yeah, look at well, see if you can try to book one by the end of the cut.
Oh, he does children's cuts.
I assume it's not just famous children's cuts, but maybe.
Oh, it's one of those where they don't say how much it is on the website.
Oh, that's just franchising opportunities, though.
So we could open our own Giuseppe Franco Salon.
It is the cost of doing business that you have to get his hair.
You got to go jet black.
In which case, Mike, I know that's where you're heading.
I'm headed there anyway.
So, oh, there's multiple stylists.
But I want to see if you can request Giuseppe himself.
But isn't everybody?
I mean, yeah, you're probably right in line.
Probably your star meter has to be of a certain height to get Giuseppe.
Well, if anybody ever gets a big break, you book your big thing.
You sell a show that day when your meter is the highest.
You got to call Giuseppe Franco.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it should have been when Screen Juggies was at its height
and I was getting recognized at the airport every time.
That was the time.
Giuseppe, you're racing Dan Murrell over there.
Out of the way, Dan.
It's well, it's like it's my gig to get me, Mundy, Dan Murrell,
all in the different chairs at the salon, getting our hair cut at the same time.
Boys still waiting, still waiting outside.
Let me in, let me in.
I had an appointment time.
Yes, but I assume Giuseppe sounds like Geppetto.
Oh, yes, but the Screen Junkies are busy with the Screen Junkie boys.
Well, this is we'll explore Giuseppe Franco as well.
Anyway, anyway, I, you know,
winding down, but almost one of the only results I could find
was like Valentino trying to get into a Chris Angel party
and then Chris Angel saying, get that piece of shit out of here.
So and it seems to be like a planted story
that's supposed to show what a dick Chris Angel is.
But then several weeks later, in the same Vegas newspaper,
there was the flip side of it, which is like, yeah, this was a
this is a party like anybody could go to.
He just had to buy tickets.
And then he just he bought a ticket and then was like wearing a mass
magician shirt and trying to sign masks for people.
So angels like, get the fuck out of here.
Don't do that here.
So his respect among fellow magicians is very low.
There's a story that a pen of Penn and Teller has told in his book
where he went to a Vegas strip club and Valentino was there.
And he's like, hey, hey, Penn, it's me, the mass magician.
Tell these girls, I've been telling my girls here that I'm the mass magician.
He does this big like walkthrough like, let me name some names.
Jimi Hendrix, John Lennon, Jim Morrison.
What do they all have in common? I don't know what they all
we know their names because they didn't wear a fucking bag on their head.
I've never seen you before in your in your in my entire life.
Good evening.
And then he kept walking to get his victorious lap dance.
OK, all right.
So, you know, I think this guy I don't know about blackballing.
I don't know about band.
He certainly wasn't killed.
But Penn and Chris Angel don't like the guy suffered.
He suffered for it.
Yeah. And Chris Angel only likes the highest caliber.
That's right. As we know from his what's his podcast called again?
Oh, yeah, I remember talking.
Was it called Talking Junkies? Oh, well, great.
Now, now we're going to get blackballed from the podcaster.
Well, that's right. I didn't reveal any secrets yet.
You're showing the proper respect to his podcast with Rampage
from the 18 movie. Wow.
Hammer, his offensive standup comedian buddy.
Chris only chooses the highest caliber. Right.
And he doesn't want any part of Valentino.
So Valentine, it just didn't work.
He ended up like maybe worse than before, understandably.
But the specials are neat.
I think it helped Mike Darnell.
They used him up, you know, they took him for everything he was worth.
Wave your arms around. Wear this mask.
Yeah. And then they they left him for dead.
Mike. Yeah.
One of the more skeptic, like angry magicians was like
Fox was working for years to get these made.
And they finally found someone, an integrity free fraud.
Like, yeah, there's some people still mad about it online.
Understandably, because it did ruin some classics.
Here's a quote from an article from Kevin Spencer, a touring musician,
during Magician.
Certainly no one's out to break his legs or kill him.
That's just hype.
We're just disappointed that someone who made his living
performing the art of magic for over 25 years would be so quick
to betray their community and then still want to embrace them.
In Vegas is gentlemen's clubs.
He wants it both ways. Yeah, I feel bad for him.
I, you know, and I just I did see years and years later
in Philadelphia at the one concert hall there.
Penn and Teller did do a bullet catch trick,
but they each had like a six shooter.
They each had like a three fifty seven magnum.
So in their reactions to catching the bullet
were very like so intense.
I was like, oh, my God, they're like they thought it had happened.
I thought like, oh, it worked on me even after watching these specials.
I mean, in this special, he does it with a pen and teller live on stage,
which is an endorsement of their act.
Like it was so good.
But I have to imagine loading like a six shooter.
It's like easier to like, OK, that's a, you know, gunpowder
and the real bullet will put it in our mouths at this point.
Blah, blah, blah.
You say blah, blah, blah. I don't know what I don't.
Yeah, I'm not sure what you're talking about either.
To me.
So, you know, well, it's gunpowder, blah, blah, blah.
No, I'm saying like it's probably, you know, easier than doing like the musket
when he does the bullet catch.
Magician was doing a musket thing.
No, he does do a musket thing.
OK, with the arrow thing.
He like, no, there's another trick.
OK, where he catches the bullet and like someone fires something
so the target gets hit or it seems like a target gets hit
and then a glass shatters.
But he is like when he's using the rod on the musket,
it's magnetic, the end of the rod.
So he just palms the bullet and puts it in his mouth
when he's like walking by something.
So you're saying this just pen and tellers did a better version.
Yeah, I'm saying that that trick is still done.
And that's what it is.
Yeah, I guess it ruined like a kind of a stock version
of some of these.
But if you were innovative, it didn't matter.
Yeah, yeah, there.
Did you find some of his old stuff before?
Like he was on Merv Griffin and he's in a Herb Albert video.
He's in the like a smooth jazz music.
Yeah, I listened to that one, Magic Man.
I didn't know there was a video.
Yeah, yeah.
But then, you know, he called himself the star of it.
And I looked it up and there's just a room of magicians.
Yes, I also was like waiting for a little things.
He just he he paints it as that.
But then like, wait, there's like a bunch of there's a fire.
You know, yeah, yeah.
And then the thing I couldn't find is there's a graphic novel
or a comic book from 2007, I believe.
Masked Magician 2007 comic book.
And I was trying so hard to find like just a PDF of it or something,
but I couldn't. I'd have to buy it.
I think maybe I think there's maybe one on eBay.
The publisher site goes to an Internet archive.
Like someone posted like, oh, here's the publisher's page for it.
And it was so old.
They went to like just an archive.
So they were still trying.
They were trying to a movie at some point.
But who knows how far that ever got.
Character of the Masked Magician and and the YouTube is still active.
Somebody is posting clips to this YouTube.
They're the same clips they posted every year.
They just repost.
I found the like big saw one like three times,
maybe even with the same thumbnail.
I found the Masked Magician has a LinkedIn page.
Wow.
Oh, and there's a demo reel.
There is a demo reel to a rap song about the Masked Magician.
A rap song?
It's hard to tell if they commissioned it.
What? OK.
Is it good?
No. OK. All right.
Oh, damn. I thought I thought it was going to be really good.
I OK.
Also, if you're looking this this franchise up on YouTube,
you might run into a video that I made that I believe as far as I can tell,
I believe I may have made the only parody of these specials that has ever existed,
unless there's something deep in the mad TV archives that I'm unaware of.
But, you know, years later, I think 2013,
I made a video for Funny or Die that was a parody of these specials.
Which was very fun to get to, like, soaking the style of it.
Everybody I did it with, I think, like recreated it really nicely.
Just a really fun thing to to live in.
The premise of my sketch was that you're going to watch the Masked
Magician reveal how to make a handkerchief disappear.
And the secret is it actually is disappearing.
It is real. All magic is real.
But what you have to do is pray to the devil
and get him to show up in person with you and then give him a very awkward
hand job, and then he will actually make the handkerchief disappear or whatever it is.
The devil in this video played by future Lanuba boy Bugman.
I remember that his parents came to watch this particular shoot
in which he has like a big red waxy fake penis.
Sticking out of his pants.
We gave him a we gave him a real rod to use a term from earlier in the episode.
It was just very fun looking one way and watching this little
red penis scene happen and then look over and see his dad like, there's my boy.
But one reveal.
Who was the Masked Magician in that sketch?
Who was it who got the honor of giving Bugman the devil a hand job?
Well, here's the reveal.
The Masked Magician was played by none other than Nick Weigert.
So who was fucking great, by the way,
the getting to make videos in front of that time were like just the cast
in the office that you can grab or Bugman Weigert.
Oh, geez. So good.
Great with the eye acting, great with the the pantomiming and everything.
So anyway, if I'll repost this somewhere, but if you want to see a video,
if you can, if if you are a hardcore
Doughboys fan or podcast world listener,
if any, you would like to see a video where Weigert jerks off Bugman as the devil.
I'll make sure that you can see this somehow.
Very exciting. Yeah.
Um, do you have this song?
I have a demo reel here.
But does have the rap song in it.
Mr. M.
They want to kill him.
His assistant, is he going to hurt her later?
Showed up on diagnosis murder.
All right. Wow.
Wow. Mr. M. What a muse.
He inspired some of the best music I've ever heard.
I'm doing a sketch about him.
And it was, hey, pretty fun doing an episode about worth the wait, I hope.
I hope so. I really enjoyed it.
Thank you, Michael, for this assignment.
Thank you, Club 3 voters, for keeping it in that second place slot.
We're going to do another poll.
But I have I know it's been a long episode, and I'll just try to
I'll try to handle this quickly.
But now the Masked Magician has gotten its day.
We're kind of at a reset point with the Club 3 poll. Right.
And as we've recently discussed, Mike has recently celebrated
a special birthday, a special non-complex triggering birthday.
Right. Yes. Finally, 65.
Extremely youthful.
You ever seen a more youthful 65?
Doesn't look older than a day older than 75.
And my hair looks normal
and the correct color for my youthful age.
Get ready for Mike's new Mike Darnall-esque look
debuting for a 65 special.
So what I would like to propose for the next poll is this
that we finally do the revenge of all of the Mike
last place and second to last place.
Usually kitschy variety specials with lots of the kind of celebrities
that Mike likes. That's right.
That have popped up in these Club 3 polls
over the many months that we've been doing it.
And I've compiled some of the candidates.
If you want to yay or nay these, because I think I think I know what they are.
And if you're if everybody's down with this, I think this could be a good
next poll and a way to revisit some of your great suggestions
that haven't made it in the past.
Yeah. Well, obviously, I'm on board with this. Great.
It's exciting to me.
Can I can I pitch this title that we call this
Carlson's Clash of the Kitsch.
Oh, I like that.
Yeah. Great. Great.
I like that a lot.
OK, Carl. So the candidates for the next poll,
which you'll be seeing soon, listeners Carlson's Clash of the Kitsch.
I got to clear my throat because these some of these are mealy mouthed.
All right. The 1979 Legends of the Superheroes
comedy roast starring Adam West and Ed McMahon.
Four percent.
I would give the stats of course. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Approved. Just just give me a 100 percent.
I just saw a clip that just Instagram wanted me to watch Adam West
punching Solomon Grundy in this.
And I was like, oh, we got to we got to do it.
Who is Solomon? He's a DC universe bad guy.
OK. Oh, yeah.
He's not like a guy from McHale's Navy.
He's not in the Bilko show.
He's not an actor.
I believe a folklore figure, maybe to Solomon Grundy bored on a Monday.
I don't want to tip the scales for any of these,
but just to say, you know, this one also features
Ruth Buzzi, Gary Owens, Burt Ward, of course.
Pat Carroll, voice of Ursula.
Gilligan's Island versus 60s Batman on Family Feud in 1983, 14 percent.
Great. OK, in.
Oh, but and not all again, not to tip the scales on the Batman side.
Vincent Price. Yes. Very extra little treat.
Just confirm it. You said 1983.
Yeah, from later. OK.
This would be an episode about a 1983
family feud with stars of 60s television shows.
OK, Spider-Man Rock Reflections of a Superhero,
a 1975 rock opera released on vinyl.
I would love to do it.
The main theme sung by Ron Dante, who sang Sugar Sugar.
Oh, I didn't even know this is Ron Dante.
Ron Dante playing Peter Parker, I believe, as well on the album.
But yes, singing the main theme, which I believe calls.
I've played this on the show before.
Spider-Man is described as a sex machine in this song for some weird reason.
Wow. It's very strange.
OK. Grooves like a spider moves like a man,
I believe, is one of the lines in it as well.
It was like a spider moves like a man. Yeah.
Just wish that suit would tear off.
Let me see some of them in the roof.
They call him the wall crawler, sex machine.
I crawl the walls just looking at him.
Seven percent on that one, by the way.
Don Knotts at Weeki Wachee Springs promoting The Incredible Mr.
Limpit, one of my favorite phrases I've gotten to type in the polls.
Yeah, that's 11 percent on that one.
I am shocked that one was not received better.
Are you shocked, though?
No, I guess we haven't given enough attention to Weeki Wachee Springs.
There's a lot of those Florida tourism places, the pre-Disney.
It feels closer to what the technical premise of the podcast is.
It is, yet until this poll, I had never heard of Weeki Wachee Springs.
Weeki Wachee Springs.
It's north of Tampa.
Oh, yeah, kind of a like, yeah, whatever,
gladesy kind of tourist spot, pre-Disney world.
Yeah. And a lot of the basis of that is a special called Weekend
at Weeki Wachee, where Don Knotts goes.
You get to watch Don Knotts on vacation.
Am I dreaming?
A dream. And finally, and you feel free to knock the look.
This was pegged to like a certain time of year, but I don't think it has to be.
Right. The Paul Linde Halloween special.
Seventeen percent.
The highest of any of these. That did pretty well.
Yeah. Yeah.
What am I going to say? No to any of these?
I mean, of course not. It seems like the best shot.
You were watching some of these while we were recording.
You had your you were holding your phone sideways and like barely paying attention.
I think I just sent a clip of Paul and Kiss to Mundy a couple of weeks ago.
That just popped up. What do you say?
I don't think he did nothing.
Didn't respond to that. Usually he responds.
But will the audience respond to the top?
Because, yes, Kiss is in this.
Betty White is in this.
The Osmonds star studded.
And then this is really that was going to be the five.
We could go to six.
It's kind of a different category because we all all of these are kind of like
specials or records and all with a certain type of celebrity.
I will let you yay or nay.
OK. Tony and Tina's wedding.
Four percent nay, because we're going to do it, but not in this, I think.
It feels different.
We will have it.
There will be a different approach for Tony and Tina.
Yes, it will be main feed and trounced by Griffin doing whatever he wants.
Yeah. I remember you texting in the aftermath of that.
Griffin, when we let you do whatever you want, if you could do me a favor
and do Tony and Tina's wedding, I'd appreciate it.
Tony and Tina's wedding.
We may just have to do it in a live show.
Do it. Perform it.
Well, we're doing Tony and Tina's wedding.
Do we owe them a license or is this kind of an off brand?
Michael and Jason's wedding, we'll call it.
Sure. Oh, OK.
And we'll do a version of it.
Can't copyright those names.
Yeah. Wedding is a generic term.
I have. Well, you have one more thing.
No, no, that's it.
Those will be your five for Carlson's Clash of the Kitsch.
If the poll's not up already, it will be soon.
I wasn't going to declare a second gate calling a shot.
But now that you brought this up.
Yeah, I have to. Yeah.
Because this is another piece of pop culture trash that popped up.
And I just we need to do an episode about it.
I'm not saying we have to do it.
By the way, you could throw it into here.
Maybe that's not the way to do it.
But it seems like he really wants to.
I was going to say also up to you if you want to include
if you want to just put Jonathan Frakes into the poll,
if you want to put I feel like there was another one
that came up in this episode, but I forget already.
Oh, I don't know.
Frakes said a big catch all Frakes episode, perhaps.
That's maybe main feed later is.
No, Frakes doesn't go in this poll.
But there is I guess I like the idea that in main feed
one day shows up Frakes all caps exclamation point.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe we get him.
Let me say it does.
It does belong on this club three list.
But you but you know, maybe it wouldn't be fair to the rules.
But I don't think it would be fair to the rules.
We should give it the chance to lose in a future poll.
That's what I bring it back.
OK, yes, I agree.
It can go on a future club three poll and lose tremendously
because no one is interested in it.
But I believe you think everyone in this room will be interested in it.
I think Jason will cackle at it and you will go, oh, OK.
Well, why are we going to set us up to play our games?
I want to do an episode on Wayland Flowers and Madam.
Yeah, that was earnest.
That was earnest.
I fucking hate this shit.
I do. I like this is where we are.
We obviously have a lot of overlap.
If they're on something, I'm like, oh, these fucking.
There was a I had never seen this before.
There's some sort of sitcom where Madam is just treated as a character
where, like, the family is like the military and she's making like mad.
OK, first of all, well, he's a puppeteer or ventriloquist.
Remember, Conti contextualizes for people born after 1978.
And he had a famous. Amazing.
We know he has a puppet named Madam who looks like Lady Elaine from Mr.
Rogers is kind of like just a fine feather boa glad lady.
She's like, she's horny.
She's like, yeah, in the tradition of like, I guess, kind of a lane
stretch or other like actresses of the old days, Mae West, whatever.
And I saw a clip of this.
I don't know what it is.
I didn't even look into it other than just to go, oh, that's Madam.
And it's just like there's a it's a sitcom where Madam is just a character.
And I don't know if it was a sketch, but like there's this family in the military
and Madam is just like horny for this general guy.
And I was like, oh, we should probably.
We have to do a Madam episode.
We have we have to do.
We have to is really no other way.
And Madam for sure, Madam's nose and chin are penis and balls.
There's just no way around it.
Like you see, like, well, who has the filthy mind now?
No, I just watching a nice ventriloquism act and you're there seeing. Come on.
I mean, yes, that's not even a leap.
But this is one of those I like to get like I'm amazed it hasn't happened,
that I haven't like, you know, gone to get a drink and then rejoin the group
at a party and you're in the middle of going,
tell me that Madam's face isn't a dick and balls.
And then the person you're yelling at is like, what's Madam?
I thought you were going to say like you hadn't you.
You went to get a drink and then you come back and Mike has Madam.
I have a Madam puppet that I'm
because it's your birthday and multiple people gave you full recreation.
Madam puppets.
Your your goal should be to push this off until it's my birthday next year.
And that's the only way I can get this in, is to do it on my birthday
when I have like total control.
But how am I going to be able to push it off when the hordes of our listeners
start yelling, Madam, Madam, they're going to find out where I live.
They're going to be pounding on my windows.
Let me just to give the listeners a peek.
I'll reveal podcast greatest secrets.
I put my phone down.
I was doing some other stuff the other day.
I put my phone down for a while and I came back and Mike had started
a conversation in a group text about Lamp Chop and Sherry Lewis's daughter.
Mallory Lewis.
Yeah, not even Sherry, the daughter specifically.
Yeah, we all know.
Yes, we're talking about the category of hang around,
who is the hang around of their own parents, their own celebrity parents.
And and you said Mallory Lewis, of course.
I can't believe no one else is texting about Mallory Lewis.
50 text messages.
I thought something was wrong because, you know, the I-message
just displays something was very right.
All right. What I said, I again.
Sorry, we're making the listener Google a lot of stuff.
You Google Mike Darnell, now Google image Mallory Lewis.
And just take her in, first of all, and then you will understand
my comment that when I say I think that this woman had surgery
to look more like Lamb Chop, she had surgery to like narrow
her eyes to look like the cloth, the strips of the puppet.
Yes, it's a good theory to have to make her hair more like a mane,
the mane of a sheep.
Oh, this is like Mike's cosmetic surgery, making his chin
and nose look more like a dick and balls.
So it can be like you can look more like that, too.
Yeah, it can look more like madam.
Here's the clip I saw on Instagram.
And madam is now in a military outfit.
She just said, oh, my gosh, have I got to go through that,
which is what I'm saying right now.
And she's she's got her little puppet feet going through the tires
too far apart.
God, I just like the my the image of Mike holding his phone
as far away from a microphone as trying to get both of you guys to see.
But it certainly was not good audio for the for the listener.
Don't worry. When we get to the madam episode,
the audio will be pristine and perfect.
This is what you sure you don't want to just throw it in
and see if it like takes the cake.
Oh, you don't have to.
I just be curious as an all right, put a madam put put
Wayland Flowers and Madam in the bowl, five returning non-champion,
the opposite of champions and a future loser.
But maybe not this time.
This is Wayland Flowers and Madam Wayland Flowers.
Madam like takes like it's a blowout.
Yeah, maybe.
Oh, yeah, it might.
Then I'll be really upset.
This is a great Instagram account called Pop Trash Museum that I like a lot.
And this also I didn't realize this.
And we missed this in the discussion of different like actor records.
Richard Simmons has a couple songs, a couple.
I've heard one that I liked.
There was certified yacht on the Yacht or Not podcast.
Yes. And I was like, oh, these are pretty good.
I didn't even realize these existed until after we did the episode.
Richard Simmons, I'm not bad.
Yeah. So so that'll be on whatever part two.
Let's really think.
Are we going to throw it in as a wild card?
I will allow it.
You guys, you can make the final call if you want.
I got Jason, I think just really wants to do it.
I think he honestly wants to do it.
Well, is this accurate?
To do what?
Wayland Flowers and Madam.
I really don't know anything about Wayland Flowers and Madam.
So it would certainly be a new territory for me.
Oh, how exciting to learn.
I look, I'm just I'm a sponge.
I soak it all up.
I'm intellectually curious.
Yeah. I just no one on earth has ever said I'm intellectually curious.
And the source of it was learning more about Wayland Flowers and Madam.
Yeah, I feel like it might now.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
The Nut Club three numbers.
Spider-Man record is pretty appealing to me.
All that stuff is great.
Yeah, I do do a little search.
I think the Wayland Flowers may his life ended in a sad way.
So perhaps we just focus more on Madam, the character Madam.
But I don't know how much Googling people are going to do before doing this poll.
I don't know how often how much research is done before people vote in the Club
three poll. I don't know.
Yeah, you really need to.
You know, we don't send out a voter guide, but you can look up your own independent
voter guide and it's up to you to put in the research.
Yes. Yeah.
I mean, look, it could be good listeners could be like,
I was struggling to have some talk to my great grandmother about.
And we help.
We help them.
Well, all of these solve that problem.
All of these need to bridge the multi multi generational gap.
I've got a podcast that can help you.
I don't know that 40 year old family feud episode, though, that might be too modern.
That's the one I know.
This Richard Dawson and his new comedy.
Right, right, right, right.
All right. Well, on that note, let's we'll send these topics into the wild.
We'll see what happens.
You survived podcast, the right club three.
Thanks for subscribing.
Your bravery saved the pot.
Hey, wait, Pileggi style.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
And no pressure.
But, you know, we give you a lot of great content.
You ever want to send us like a midriff pick?
We won't complain.
Thanks, Mitch.