Forever!
Dog!
Warning! The following podcast may contain
Vanilla Ice singing
Dismissive Brownie remarks
Nameless and faceless judges
And famous pig name theft
All that plus Eva Anderson and Amy Nicholson return to talk about the LA County Fair
On today's podcast, The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast that always gets the blue ribbon for ignoring theme parks to talk about long-dead character actors.
I'm Scott Gardner, Jason Chardon. You laugh loudest, I go to you first.
I did laugh loudest. Hey, once again, rest in peace, Dabney Coleman, you know, we gotta give it up.
If you don't, yeah, if you missed it, that was a second gate thing, if you missed the live reaction to the death of Dabney Coleman, which occurred only many hours earlier, and directly in the middle of a sentence I was saying from Jason.
About your loving family.
Jason was like, whoa, whoa, we have to address something right now.
Hang on, hang on.
Dabney Coleman has died.
No, the castle's not on fire, don't worry about it.
There's Mike Coleman.
I mean, Mike, look what you got me doing now.
I'm here and I respectfully, I wait.
If Larry Storch dies, I wait till a sentence is complete before I announce it.
That's what I bring to the show.
I'm like this rude man sitting next to me here, Jason.
People had to know many days from when we found out about it.
No, same day, I had just three minutes before, gotten an LA Times alert, and Mike's like, that happened 12 hours ago, and I was like, I can't control.
The episode came out many days later, is what I'm saying.
You were breaking the news to no one, unless there were people who missed the entire thing.
I assume all of our listeners have Dabney Coleman death alerts ready to go.
They want to know.
Well, if they listen to this show, they also are interested in the alive status of over 90-year-old actors, so they should have an alert.
Yeah, and we do have a lot of those in play.
What's that podcast you listen to?
It's about theme parks and actors over the age of 90.
Cutting off a young audience at the pass.
Hey, today we are talking about the LA County Fair.
This is exciting.
This is fun.
And I was thinking how the fair is all about, you know, like the crazy indulgent foods and like the here's the combo of burger with Krispy Kreme doughnuts.
And that's in a way what we've got going on guest wise today is, you know, like the burger with Krispy Kreme doughnuts, both elements great on their own.
Perfect guests on their own together.
Oh, my God.
What a treat.
Right.
All right.
Perfect.
Everyone loved it.
Great. Great.
What I'm saying is we got two great guests, great separately on the show.
Best pals together.
And I'm so so glad you guys came here together to talk about this and your history with this one renowned film critic and the host of Unspooled.
The other, you know, from all the best episodes of this show, it's Amy Nicholson and Eva Anderson.
Hey, we're here.
Yay.
We're best friends.
You know what this makes?
I'm a donut in your Krispy Kreme donut.
And these guys are the three burger patties in between us.
Oh, because it's triple.
You're right.
It's triple.
Wow.
Oh, I love.
What an honor.
Jason's the middle patty.
OK.
No further questions.
So excited about this and to talk about both of your rich history with this event.
And I don't look I don't want to tangent for too long.
I want to get to the fair.
But Eva, this is your beat and I feel like it needs to be discussed.
I'm starting to think Copperfield's never going to get to make the moon disappear.
Oh, you know, I heard he was still.
So somebody wrote on your subreddit that he is still advertising the moon disappearing from his show at the MGM.
Yes.
While it's while it's going.
Mm hmm.
Still going for now.
Let's be clear.
We were all you know, if you haven't heard some things have been going on with them.
Yes.
Double things have been going.
So very atrocious.
Double digit allegations.
Uh huh.
You might say his good name is disappearing.
I might say.
But the question is, like, a, when will that show stop?
Because we've been discussing on a text thread how he's going to they like he will be dragged out kicking and screaming.
So the technique and do we're like, all right, what's the distance from the stage to the door?
While the while the police are dragging me, can I get out all the rest of my lines rapid fire?
So that technically counts as one performance.
And that still goes in the record book.
What happens to blue if he doesn't have a show to do?
What happens to Moosha Kay?
What happens to the monkeys that paint your face?
What happens to the puppets and the ventriloquist dummies?
The rooms and rooms of puppets and we just realized while we were discussing this, Mike, that Madam is in the museum.
I think David Copperfield owns a Madam puppet, maybe the Madam.
We're not sure.
He also owns like a lot of lamb chops.
You said you've gotten pile of lamb chops.
You sent a video and then you said he has more lamb chops than this.
Yes.
He has a room that's mostly lamb chops, including some giant lamb chops that were in that.
I think we're in Macy's Day parade.
Whoa.
No part of me wants to see a big lamb chop.
A life-size lamb chop.
So yeah, I don't think, I still believe he will make the moon disappear, but now every day it feels like more of a threat.
Oh yes, we talk about that.
Then he will like, all right, we're going to go through with these allegations.
We're going to go through whatever legal process.
All right, fine.
Do you want the moon back or not?
Yeah.
I hope you liked your tides.
And then he starts to like, and then I'll make Idaho go too.
Idaho will disappear as well.
Do you want to keep asking questions about what I can make disappear?
If I can make the moon, and you've seen over many specials, what else I can make disappear?
Where does it stop?
What about you?
Can I make you disappear?
Yeah, this is making me very scared about the health and safety of the women who are testifying against him.
That they'll all make it to court without disappearing.
It's certainly, it's positive.
We don't know supernaturally what he can do.
Can he make the entire courtroom disappear?
Can he make the city that the court is in disappear?
Your Honor, the witness has been sawed in half.
But also, this is just in the background.
So, you know, if he, say, does leave MGM, that leaves Chris Angel as the reigning cool guy magician.
He wins.
In Vegas, he does win.
Copperfield's nightmare.
And yet, a hero, a new, what do they say?
A new hope?
A new fighter has entered the arena.
Because David Blaine is now doing shows periodically in Vegas.
Yes.
What can you tell us about this?
So this is a new, he's doing it, and there's, what is the deal with the residency?
There's like three shows, three shows last month.
He's doing three shows at the end of August, the best time to be in Vegas.
And then he's doing three shows in December around New Year's.
Okay.
So it's very limited.
Yes.
Exclusive.
Exclusive, very highly exclusive.
It's the win.
But I do have a friend that went and texted me immediately that I need to get there.
I need to go.
Oh boy.
So he said that David Blaine's disaffected, emotionless performance makes it incredible.
Wow.
So we have a new, we have a new, really listless magician named David in Vegas.
Void filled immediately.
Who wants to be cool?
Who's in the posy posy?
The hero has risen.
Exactly.
When we need it in the most.
I'm not missing Copperfield at all now that I hear that.
Yeah, I know.
That's fine.
That really helps.
He just needs blue.
Well, he should just buy blue or just, or use magic to make blue where he is.
Oh yeah.
Just point in the general direction of what part of town you think blue is in.
Blue should just retire to the island.
Blue.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
He's earned it.
Blue is in charge of the monkeys.
A lot of performances.
This is yours now.
Blue beer.
Underwater statue's mine.
He inherits everything, I bet.
Yeah.
David left everything to blue.
The only one who showed me true love.
None of my wives, none of my parents.
I found a quote from a, like an interview.
There's this dirty puppet ventriloquist, Otto and George act, called Otto and George, which
is where the Madame Puppet video is from.
But did you see the, where he, it's an interview where Copperfield's like, you know who told
me about Otto and George?
Kevin Spacey.
And it was like, oh man, this was like 2009.
It's all tying together.
Like, were you guys on a plane when you had that conversation?
Us and Diddy, you know.
The boys.
Wow.
Oh my God.
So somebody needs to save that Madame Puppet also.
But I don't know.
I'm not going to be the one to do it.
Seven or eight lamb chops.
And a bunch of very big lamb chops.
A scoop of all the lamb chops you could find.
Which might only be half of them.
But just if you can get in there, grab as many lamb chops as you can and get out.
All right.
Well, I just wanted to make sure we, you know, we discussed where things were at because
we were wondering if by the next time you were with us, if it would have happened.
Yeah.
Since October, we've been having this conversation.
And I think we'll check in every time, I think.
No matter how worse and worse it gets.
But to a more pleasant, Todd, let's talk about the fair.
And I'm so glad you both brought this to us.
Because, like, I feel like we've talked about the fair and you participating in the fair
and in the contest for a long time.
But what is the whole history here?
Who does it start with?
And how do you guys end up doing it together?
This definitely started with Eva.
Yeah.
It was like 2007.
I was dating a guy.
We went to the fair together.
And it was a very fun day.
My first time there.
But I witnessed, we went to the beer and wine pavilion and tasted some beer.
I ended up in a conversation with this old married couple from the Inland Empire
whose names were Ron and Nancy, who were competitive mead makers.
And they got into the drama of the mead tournaments.
And I was like, that's interesting.
And then I went to see the baked goods.
I overheard someone being snarky about some of the cakes in there,
like saying something mean, an old person saying something mean about something.
And I was like, this is incredible.
So the next year I entered, I made chocolate cookies.
I'd broken up with that boyfriend, but I was like, I'm all in on the fair.
I'm taking the fair.
So I made these cookies with candied bacon on them.
And I needed a date to the fair.
And I was just starting to hang out with you, Amy.
So it was one of our first like, I feel like solo hangs was that we went
and ran around the fair together and I totally lost.
I entered the cookies and I did not make it in the cabinet.
I like belly flopped spectacularly.
And that radicalized me, to be honest.
Because I thought chocolate with candied bacon was a cut above.
I thought chocolate with candied bacon was really like pushing the limits
of what bacon could do.
I was really proud of you.
Oh, thank you.
And so in your failure, I then became hooked, addicted, angry,
emotionally caught up in the drama of the baking cabinet.
And I've been really, I've spent many years by your side rooting for you.
The year that you added a lot of pretzels to your cookies
and they got upset about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I feel like we go a lot together as a team
and have like for the last decade basically on and off.
Geez, this is beautiful.
And like rooting for each other, supporting each other.
Oh, yeah.
And getting like more and more fond of this place
and like the odds and ends and like stray corners of it.
Because I would imagine, because this is like a, you know,
there's 2,000 things to do at this particular fair
and like entire swaths of it you could miss very easily, I'm sure.
Oh, yeah.
No, and then on and off, we've gone on and off for the last 10 years.
I entered stuff.
Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose.
Sometimes you make it in the cabinet.
Some days you get a blue ribbon.
You know, every year it's a different story.
It's you making your own LA County fair story.
Wow, wow.
And I have liked going, you know, when I do go without you,
like I will visit the pastry cabinet on years where you have done well or not.
And I will send you pictures of me flipping off the winners
if it has not been your year.
Yes, you always do that.
Yeah.
It makes me so happy.
Because I love being passionately angry about something like this.
I always wanted, I was like, the best way to experience this seems to be
to have an emotional stake.
You just have to find what that stake is.
And then it becomes this whole giant 2,000 thing,
thing becomes about you, about me.
And it's my special thing.
And this is the dream is to get in the cabinet.
I don't think I knew the cabinet aspect of it.
Yeah.
But I went to the fair yesterday as encouraged by you guys.
And I took my son and I had a great time.
And I'll factor in into the discussion.
But I don't think I knew that there's the initial competition,
but then you get to stay your cookies, cakes, whatever it is,
stay in that cabinet for the run of the fair.
For more than a month.
Wow, wow.
Just rotting?
Oh, yeah.
There's some really moldy, disgusting stuff in the cabinet.
The ones that are like buttercream and fruit, they're just not holding up.
Yeah.
Falling apart.
If it's hot at the fair, then it's a particularly,
the way it's trapped in that under the grandstands area,
and then a case within that, that's three levels of heat.
Three levels.
And they have a whole category called sugar art,
where people are making delicate, filigreed sugar that just does not last ever.
It immediately dissolves into a pile of goo.
Oh, yeah.
There was, I cannot figure out what was going on,
but there was one slice of cake that was so mangled this time around
that I think a rat got into the cabinet.
That was the only way I could explain what had happened to it,
because it was like only parts that were just missing.
Oh, you've got to see the rats.
You've got to see the fair.
You've got to get deep fried, or you've got to meet the fair rats.
Eva was actually really trying to get people involved in this rat conspiracy,
because we were standing next to an older couple,
and you were telling them that you believed there was a rat in the cabinet,
and you were being really insistent about it.
I mean, the best thing to do in the culinary baking area
is to engage with whoever is standing nearby.
So sometimes you're like, hey, I won a prize,
and an old lady gives you a mean girl look to her husband
like a bitch from seventh grade.
Or sometimes they drag you over, and they're like,
look at these disgusting caramels.
And you don't know this person, and you don't care,
but they're just like, you're not supposed to wrap them.
He always wraps his caramels.
There's just weird stuff always happening in that.
But you have to talk to strangers to engage with it.
We also love the culinary arts pavilion,
because it has the greatest competition of the fair, tablescaping.
I don't know if you admire the tablescaping.
I found tablescaping.
As soon as I saw this area, I was like, have we talked about this before?
And I'm also taking in this has to be an Eva thing.
And the tablescaping and semi-relatedly doors, yeah.
Doorscaping.
Yes.
Competitive, in that case, competitive decoration of doors.
And I was really blown back by the phrase atop a QR code,
vote for your favorite door.
It's not a phrase I expected to see that day.
Also the fact that all these doorscaping and tablescaping,
you can read the judges' comments, and they can be very, very nasty.
But my favorite was on one of the doors this time.
I think someone had stretched fabric to cover the entire door,
and one of the comments was like,
the door is no longer functioning as a door.
They got points off for making it no longer a door.
I'm finding doorscaping fascinating, because it's new, right?
This is only the second year that they've had doorscaping.
Yeah, doorscaping is brand new.
And when you think about it, I grew up in the Texas suburbs.
There were definitely women who got into wreaths, you know,
door frames.
But now when you watch an art develop,
which is what we're doing with doorscaping,
brand new second year,
you're watching people push the frontier of what a door is.
Because I feel like last year it was a lot of holiday doors.
You know, kind of basic, like, oh, it's Christmas.
Oh, hi. Oh, it's Memorial Day.
This year somebody had an indoor door
where it was like a door representing being inside a teenage girl's bedroom.
And then it's just that little flip where you're like,
oh, this is a world opening up.
It's literally a door into a new area of competition.
You can imagine any door now.
In year two, they flipped the entire thing,
the entire system of doors on its head.
And honestly, a really spectacular Twilight Zone door,
where they made it into the door from the opening to the Twilight Zone
with all the stuff around.
A big stand-up Rod Serling and everything on it is black and white,
including like the big eyeball.
Yeah. Is that, but is that maybe like, it's like IP?
Is that frowned upon?
Or like, could you make like a Marvel Comics door?
Oh, yeah.
They're fine with that.
There's Harry Potter tables every year.
Yeah. And like we're very into competition.
And we have, I would say lamented how IP has invaded the competition space.
Like poodle grooming competitions are another thing we're really into.
They're not at the fair. They may be someday.
Yeah. That would be so good to do creative dog styling at the fair.
But we've watched like IP enter the poodle grooming space,
which has been kind of a bummer.
It used to just be like, I'm a dog that looks like a carousel horse.
And now it's like, I am all the characters in Moana.
And it's tacky here.
Oh, yeah, sure. I went one year for that.
And yeah, that one, the winner was like, it's Spiderman.
And who's Venom?
That was the coolest dog.
But then how it was like the mouth of Venom wasn't the mouth of the dog.
It was like the teeth were on his chest.
Well, was it the symbiote coming off of Spiderman, the alien entity?
Jason, you know what I'm talking about?
I think it was a little more traditional.
The Venom symbiote tries to get off Spiderman.
He has his own mouth sort of jutting off of a head.
So perhaps that's what it was.
His neck was his mouth, his wide mouth, his teeth.
But we will get in fights with judges.
Oh, yeah, we really hate the judges at the poodle grooming competition.
Yeah, we'll scream at them and then we'll get mad about the wrong table winning.
Because there's a lot of, you know, sucking up to your audience
that I think happens in these kind of competitions.
Yeah, condescension.
Yeah, a lot of like salute the troops tablescaping.
That happened this year.
Yes, door and tablescaping.
I noticed that.
And there was one, and forgive me, I don't want to be stealing valor.
But I think the one that I was, I swear when I was looking at the photo later,
I saw like a little swirl on the forehead of the soldier pictured.
It was like a little like, I mean, tablescape, this might be a bigger explanation required,
but it's like, all right, you set a table for some kind of theme
and the competition is not, it's the plates that you choose
and the forks and knives that you choose,
but then also like the menu of what's being served and the backdrop
and then other decorations.
So in this case, it's like welcome home.
We are proud of you over red, white and blue.
And then photos of the returning soldier hugging his children.
But I swear I saw a little swirly on his forehead
that indicates the watermark of a stock photo website where it was not.
I really think so.
And if I'm wrong, I'm wrong, but I know what I saw in the photo.
I think I'm looking at like it's a cloud something or other.
I've seen this swirl before.
And if that's the case, then I don't know if it won or anything,
but like I'd rather go give it to the fun Halloween door
than be guilted into it by a troop who is not the...
Properly licensed.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
A troop whose image was not paid for to be part of this competition.
Don't you sit with your son, though, and look at when you eat dinner,
you look at framed photos of you and your son.
Yeah, always. Yes, of course.
That are on the table where you're eating the macaroni and cheese.
If he's in it, fine, but mainly me looking sharp, handsome, doing my duty.
You know, it's a bonus if he's in it, but yeah, me is the main thing.
And it's on the table.
Yeah, yeah, yes, while we eat.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you need to look at your food to make sure that you're properly getting your food,
but you know, when you're not reaching for your peas, eyes on me.
Jason has dinner with that photo of him in a sailor suit on the kitchen table.
I tell him at ease and then we can start on the appetizers.
The other aspect of that door also, you know, I'm not...
I don't really come from a military tradition.
I'm not in a military family. Maybe this is how it is.
I'm left to assume that if you're a soldier,
then you want to eat dinner next to a framed photo of a bald eagle.
Really close up, staring right down the barrel of the lens, angrily.
A mad bald eagle.
A terrifyingly powerful bird.
I believe the table that won this year is like a really spectacular, nice midsummer table.
Didn't it win?
I had some objections with the nice midsummer table,
where like the whole center of the table was just a huge floral display,
you know, kind of like you just took a wedge out of Florence Pugh's costume and put it there.
To me, I felt like there wasn't any room to eat.
You know, I was like expecting them to take some points off,
but they did put ribbons around the table legs, which I thought was beautiful.
And I like the Edward Gorey table, which was the like masterpiece mystery table.
That had all the characters from the opening of mystery from PBS.
I had to really like divide.
Luckily, my son was eating churros during all this,
but I'm like, as soon as these churros are up,
he's not going to have the patience for the table scaping contest.
So I was taking in what I could, but I knew I had a ticking clock,
which was, you know, cinnamon and powdered sugar.
One giant churro.
I did really enjoy getting to see this.
I feel like, you know, I mean, we're looking at like theming,
and if the show is about theming, you know,
this is just some good just like winnowed down theming.
Let's take a table and just with a table.
How can we transport you into another world?
And my favorite thing was that this table competition invented the idea of summer ween,
a summer Halloween.
I mean, maybe that exists outside of this, but I've never heard of summer ween before.
And I now want to host my own summer ween party because it was like,
I mean, the detail I love the most was like, here's the grill with cobwebs all over it.
And then there's burger patties and then melted cheese on top.
But they made jack-o-lantern.
They made a jack-o-lantern smile in the cheese.
Oh, OK.
See, that's great.
I want to make haunted hamburgers at my summer ween party.
I thought that one was wonderful and it didn't score very well.
And I was really upset about it.
I thought it was because it had a very kind of sexy looking Frankenstein head
taking up a lot of the table.
It did, and he was really sexy.
He seemed weirdly aroused.
The way the head seemed aroused?
Yeah, he was a paper mache head that just had the wrong expression for a Frankenstein.
He was like, ooh, is that one?
He was like, hey, ladies.
OK, it was more like...
He was like Austin Butler Frankenstein.
He did look like Austin Butler.
Yeah, he looked too much like Austin Butler.
Austin Butler does seem like he's always aroused.
Yeah, he does.
The Jacob O'Lordy Frankenstein.
Somebody who's just got too much to sauce around.
Right, right, right.
Subjects to these actors.
Every second they're unframed, they're rock hard.
That's how they get the performance.
They just have to shoot around.
Who else is going to play Elvis?
But then there was a table that tried to add a specific erotic element.
It added storytelling.
For me, I think the first time I'd seen storytelling at a tablescaping competition.
The text chain?
The text chain.
There was one, it was a couple who were sitting down at an Italian restaurant.
That was the idea you were getting.
And the front of the tablescaping had a brick wall.
And on the brick wall, you could see the text of the couple arranging the meetup.
You know, like, oh, we're going to go, we're going to get some spaghetti.
Oh, it's going to be great.
But when you walked behind the table, which is a space that I don't think they've ever used.
I've never seen theming behind the table before.
When you walk behind the table on the backside of the brick wall,
the guy was cheating on his girlfriend by texting somebody else
and saying he can't wait to meet up with her after dinner.
Did you just have a sense there was more story back there?
Or did anything point the way to it?
How did you know?
I just, I'm a curious person.
I'm going to get every angle of the table.
Wow.
That's so great.
Wow. All of these, geez.
These art forms that presumably our listeners have just heard about for the first time.
Tablescaping and doorscaping.
Boundaries are being pushed instantly in this fledgling new art.
I learned about tablescaping, I think, a few years ago from Eva's posts.
Oh, yeah.
From Instagram stories.
I kind of was able to suss out what it was.
I'm like, there has got to be a whole subculture and competitiveness.
Oh, yeah.
A whole world of this.
Doorscaping, decorating doors does make me think of,
besides Christmas and Halloween,
I do think of people who are really excited
and doing a big Disney family vacation.
If you stay at the Disney hotels,
you will often see a decorated door.
Same on cruise ships.
People go all out decorating doors.
Decorate their own hotel door?
At least it's like dorm rooms, right?
When I was in college, they let us paint them,
and I painted giant carrots all over mine for some reason.
Oh, you're so random.
Oh, light bulbs.
It's like the Simpsons' curtains.
That's what it seems like.
Don't they have carrots on their curtains?
I think that's right.
When you're talking about any of these contests,
how in the shit are you as far as knowing who the judges are?
Not at all, very surface level.
We have no idea who they are.
I don't recognize names year to year from people that enter.
We should.
It'd be good to really get specific about our competition.
Yeah, because we know the dog groomers.
We have favorites and most hated dog groomers.
Yeah, we love Angela Kumke.
She's the best.
Yeah, we love Angela.
We're Angela stans.
So you're in the shit when it comes to dog contest stuff.
Yeah.
Okay, because there have been times when I'll talk to you about something,
and you'll be like, I can't.
You have a limit usually for like,
I already have five things I'm in the shit on,
and I have to cut it off there.
Is this about wrestling?
Wrestling happened, but it also happened when we were at breakfast club.
I think of a similar thing where I asked if you were going to get involved,
and you're like, I can't.
I can't go deeper.
Yeah, exactly.
You would put the wall up there.
Yeah, getting more into breakfast club.
Right.
Which is the whole thing.
Which is the Los Angeles club.
You go to in Burbank where Bob Gurz is there.
Yeah, Los Feliz.
Los Feliz, yeah.
We became members last year.
They make you put your hand in a fried egg.
You get blindfolded.
They put your hand in a fried egg.
You have to recite like a rhyming poem about yourself.
If you go, you will hold hands with the oldest man you've ever met
and sing things or chant things.
It's like a goose lodge or an elk's lodge kind of thing that anyone can go to.
We want Jason to be involved.
We want you to just be in it already.
You should be the president.
Oh, okay.
You don't want to watch the steps of him engaging with it.
You just want it to have happened.
I want to be the president tomorrow.
It's turning 100 next year, so I feel like it's a good time to get in.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, and you have to get up pretty early, but it's breakfast.
You get sausage.
You get bacon.
You get some sort of croissant bread pudding usually.
Well, now you're speaking my language.
I love variations of bread pudding.
You could probably work something out where you put a cot in the building
and just sleep there the night before.
Sleep there the night before.
Is there any way to ...
It happens every week, is that correct?
It's every Wednesday.
Every Wednesday.
At seven in the morning.
Between seven and nine.
Yeah, but is there a 10 o'clock Wednesday, third Wednesday of the month?
No.
This is one of the things that you'll try to institute.
Are we not all tired of these early hours?
Everyone says, no, we're old.
We love it.
This is perfect.
Oh, man.
Everyone except Eva and Amy are old.
Actually, with that and the fair, do you feel like you are some of the only people
taking the torch generationally on some of these areas?
Not so much with the fair, but I'm always surprised that we never run into anybody we know there.
Because it's really close, and it's so fun, and I have never, ever run into any acquaintance there ever.
I find that just bizarre.
I love my friends, but it makes me a little mad at them.
What are you doing with your life that's better than this?
I saw pictures over the weekend.
Some people I went to college with were there.
Oh, really?
I think one of them had a ribbon in cross stitching.
What?
I got to look it up.
Do you have another friend that's entering?
And then last year, the other thing we're not even talking about is the entertainment possibilities.
Last year, Amy and I went and we saw vanilla ice at the fair on top of everything else.
Oh, this was where vanilla ice happened.
I remember you talking about vanilla ice.
He stands on a box.
That's the one thing in my head about it.
And he sings, no woman, no cry.
But he also wrapped himself in the American flag, because I think he knew his audience.
He also was just joined on stage with everybody on the planet.
He had all Ninja Turtles come out.
They came out really dramatically to do the ninja rap with him.
He just brings good Ninja Turtle suits with him.
Yeah, they came out one at a time and got behind mics to dance.
But there was also a giant polar bear and a clown.
A guy in a reflective silver suit.
Yeah, like a disco ball guy.
He also, eight months later, was performing at Mar-a-Lago on New Year's Eve.
Hopefully doing the exact same set.
I was wondering, did the turtle costumes make it to the Mar-a-Lago show?
I don't know.
I would love to be able to talk to somebody that was there, but they probably...
Doesn't he do unpleasant versions of all of his songs, too?
Like their worst versions?
He does a Rob Van Winkle heavy metal version of some of them.
He does the hard to swallow era.
He does a hard to swallow set.
He thinks that was when he was the most sexy and cool.
So he definitely dresses hard to swallow.
Come on.
When he was the most sexy and cool is when he had White Guy Dreads, obviously.
When he had a chronic era way after all that music was popular.
Did he arouse Frankenstein of White Guy Dreads?
He should have.
But you can see all sorts of tribute bands.
You can see Vanilla Ice.
When we saw Vanilla Ice, it was with Tone Locke and Young MC.
All for One, do you remember?
They were great.
They started with the music from Thus Spake Zarustra.
Am I saying that right?
Dun, dun, dun, dun.
Like real dramatic.
Oh man, Tone Locke was great.
I loved the 90s tour.
And then also because Coolio was on it for a long time, Vanilla Ice did sing Gangsta's Paradise himself.
Which nobody wanted that from him.
But it did sort of descend into chaos because at one point Tone Locke had started it.
He started inviting the sexy women of the audience on stage with him during Wild Thing.
And then a lot of them just got on and never left.
And were there pretty much throughout the entire rest of the show.
It wasn't the end?
No.
You got a second act of like seven acts.
When Vanilla Ice finally came out, I think the last 20 minutes of that show was Vanilla Ice on stage with all the Ninja Turtles, the polar bear, the clown, the DJ was dressed like Bruce Lee.
And then all of his kids and then everybody else's kids and then all of these women.
And it was like 50 people and they were just, he was out of songs by this point.
And he was just chanting Ice, Ice, Ice.
Because he was still.
That was not, it wasn't the end of Ice, Ice Baby.
He's just doing it.
All right, now it's just, let's just go back to basics.
No woman, no cry.
He couldn't hit any of the good notes in that.
And then he just was yelling Ice as the place slowly, quietly cleared out.
Having seen, this is the seventh act, you're probably, yeah, you're worn out.
If you aren't closing with the hit, don't just shout your name at me.
He was also going like, things were better in the 90s, weren't they?
People didn't have phones.
Let's give it up for the cops.
He was like trying out all these like weird kind of cheer lines.
Cops had their own show back then, remember?
They made that go away.
Everything I ever loved has been taken away from me.
Whose fault is that?
Not mine.
I did everything right.
He had sex with Madonna.
Shook night dinkled me out of a window.
It's PC culture that caused me to stop having sex with Madonna.
She'd be down, I know she'd be down.
Oh man.
I also went, so my previous experience, I had gone, I went in 2017.
And I did some, it was somewhat to see the fair because I'd never done it.
And I had a decent enough time, but it was also kind of the prelude to a concert,
which was a very like, yeah, we got nothing to do.
Why not try this?
Which was Boys to Men and Babyface.
Oh, that's a good one.
Yeah, we were excited about it, but like had no particular affinity for either
and just thought maybe this will be fun.
Then Babyface is opening act.
This is one of the ten best concerts I've ever been to.
Oh really?
I never had any feelings about Babyface.
I'm like producer and he's always on the Grammys.
That's why his 90s hits were kind of boring, like his adult contemporary kind of.
Will I Like This?
It was so fucking good.
It was the most energetic, just juiced up set where like,
okay, I don't know any of these songs from Boomerang or whatever,
but they're the best.
They are all awesome.
And he did this medley of all the songs that he wrote for other artists
that took a half hour.
It was so long.
And by the end, you're like, this was all you?
I didn't know any of them, which I'm trying to remember.
All the Bobby Brown hits, Every Little Step,
Tevin Campbell, Can We Talk, Rock Steady by The Whispers,
Then I'll Make Love to You and End of the Road,
Bye Boys to Men, who are coming on after this.
He does them already.
He scoops them?
He scoops them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so good, like absolutely as good as they're going to do it.
By the end of that medley, he's up in the audience.
He just needs one person, not four.
He's like, I'll show you guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Why should I wait in here?
I think they're down to three.
I think somebody left.
So you have three boys to men?
I think it's been that way for a while.
I don't think they replaced the fourth.
Is he replaceable?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Why bother?
But by the end of it, he's up in the grandstands,
which it is like where you watch horse races also.
So he's climbing stairs.
He's going way the hell up there.
His shirt comes off.
I really, at the end of this, I'm like, Babyface is God.
And I've listened to him ever since.
He had this old group called The Deal that's fucking great.
And I didn't know any of those songs.
But anyway, it wore us out so much.
We were so spent.
And in a good way and the best way,
it felt like Babyface had fucked us.
Like we had personally been fucked by Babyface.
And we felt great about it.
And it was like, all right, do you want to watch boys to me?
Yeah, maybe.
And we got one song in.
And we're like, they don't have a Babyface ad.
Babyface gave us three concerts in one.
And we just filed out of there.
We're fine.
That's great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I had that coming into this that truly one of the best,
the most surprising great concert I've been to came from this.
But it just had not been begged to the fair for whatever reason,
I guess COVID being one of them.
But now I got to do it with a kiddo, which was great,
which thank you both for inspiring that.
That was wonderful.
Let me say this, though, just early on, because if you're like in terms,
we definitely had a good time more than we didn't.
But I did get in there, parked kind of hot on a weekend afternoon,
get into like the main midway, like the fun zone.
Would I be crazy to walk in and think, oh, my God, this is very stressful
and very crazy.
Am I crazy?
Like, if I say that, are you like, oh, Scott, you scrooge?
No, weekends are really crowded.
Yeah.
And all the cool guys have big stuffed animals on their back,
and it's really hard to walk.
Yeah.
And people are eating like 24 inches of pork on a stick,
which is basically a weapon.
There could be a very long line for a beer.
Yeah, yeah, imposing lines for everything.
And I'm probably the least crowd amenable of the three of us, at least.
Mike, your crowd tolerance is, it's not even tolerance.
I think you prefer being in a crowd.
I'm uncomfortable here.
Only.
Not enough people.
Yeah, no, I'm OK with crowds.
I'm tall, too, though.
That's probably part of it.
I can see for miles, you know?
Also, yeah, Jason and I both, we like lines fine.
I don't know about crowds, but there's more of a comfortability, I would say.
Sure, sure.
If there's an option to go on a weekday, I would recommend a weekday fare trip.
Because it usually runs Thursday through Sunday.
I think so, yeah.
And by the way, as you're hearing this, if you're in LA or not in LA,
you can still go to the fair, I believe, but it would have to be a weekend, right?
The dates this year were May 3rd through May 27th.
So you still have a little bit of time.
It's still worth going.
We went on a Sunday, we went on Mother's Day.
It was great.
It was absolutely wonderful.
There are people winning prizes for their moms.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Can I just confirm, are you both Blue Ribbon winners?
Oh, yes, let's get into that.
Yeah, because I wanted to get the terminology.
I didn't want to insult you.
I wanted to get the terminology right because I feel like I've seen pictures of your cookies.
The terminology.
You want a Blue Ribbon for your bunts, right?
I want a Blue Ribbon for one for the lemon bundt cake and one for some chocolate chip cookies, 2019.
Great.
Do you change it up based on, do you ever feel like you see an opening?
Did you go in a previous year and see some real shitty bundt cake and think maybe I can take it there?
Yeah, I was all buns all the time and then I got Blue Ribbon, I got third place, which is red, and then I got pink ribbon, which is fifth place.
And then I was like, well, I need second place.
And that's a really hard thing to aim for.
And then I started just not getting in the cabinet every year.
And these ugly buns did.
And I was like, I'm out.
I'm making something else.
So I started making other stuff then.
Wow.
You did get your second place for sugar cookie last year.
Yeah, so now I've completed everything.
I've got all the ribbons.
You got every place?
I don't know where they are.
But I did get all the places and then fifth, which is insulting, which is they just don't give me anything.
Don't say I got pink ribbon.
That's not real.
What is the ranking of the colors of ribbons?
Blue is the best.
Is that right?
I think actually it's blue, red, white.
Isn't that it?
Yeah.
It's blue, red, white.
I mean, they say that they judge everything based on what they call the Danish system, which is the Danish system of judging is they say that they're not judging you against your competition.
They say that they're judging you against the best execution of the effort that you are trying.
Okay.
You know, so they're judging you against your own limits, I guess, which when I read that, I was like, oh, that's basically how I'm a movie critic.
You know, it's how I review a movie is to well, you know, I'm judging Garfield against Garfield and not Garfield against El Topo.
But boy, that would be an article to read.
But also, I don't really believe them because at the end of the day, they are doing the American thing where, like, if you really believe in Danish system of judging, everybody gets a blue ribbon.
If they do a good job.
Yeah.
And here there is a winner and a loser.
Yes.
And there's also best in class.
So in order to talk about this any further, I think we need to change topics a little bit.
Sure.
Yes.
Talk about.
So two, two or three years ago, the first it was two years ago, first post pandemic fair.
I went I did not ribbon that year.
Well, you did not make it in the cabinet.
It was another bundt cake, which I shouldn't have done.
I knew my limits.
But I do want to say really briefly, they don't tell you how you did.
You have to go to the fair and look for yourself.
And that's when you find out.
Oh, really?
Or somebody else to go and take a picture and send it to you.
Yeah.
They don't contact you.
No.
And then after the fair is over, you get a check in the mail for around twenty five dollars if you got a little money.
That's nice.
But OK, so I was one year it was a year, Amy, that you left your tickets at home and you had to go back home.
That was such a bad.
And so I was waiting for like a couple hours for you and Adam to show up to be physical tickets.
Well, because I like to go and get my tickets at Superior Grocers because they're cheaper.
And you can get this like ride pass where instead of buying individual tickets, you can just be like, I get 12 rides for 40 bucks flat.
And I prefer thinking that way.
It's easier for me than counting out tickets.
And Amy's a rides girl.
She loves to do all the rides.
OK.
Yeah.
And I'm sorry to say I have to report that I went on no rides because I have a four year old who's startled by any ride at this point.
Could he go in the haunted house or anything like that?
The little like we didn't try.
He's in a very not trying phase at the moment.
OK, so I'm it was like it was like five hours of like solo ride a fair time for me while you had your whole adventure.
Because we basically got to the fair.
She got all the way to Pomona and then had to go back to Koreatown and then come back to Pomona.
And then she couldn't find parking.
So I was just wandering our areas of the fair.
I had never been before.
And at this point, I've been going for like 10 years on and off.
And I round a corner and I spot a costume character, a walk around character I'd never seen before.
Yeah.
I was like, who is this?
And he's he's just waving.
He's in a little weird corner, kind of by the animal, the animal competitions.
And he's in a little suit and he's a pig.
And I asked his handler, like, what is who is this?
And he was like, this is Thummer.
Thummer.
And that's how that's how we met.
That's how we met Thummer.
Now, I want to say Thummer, I think, has been looming for a while.
I feel like you may have even pitched some kind of episode that isn't even about the fair that is about Thummer.
Yeah.
So this is, I guess, is also the secret surprise Thummer episode.
And I would encourage the listeners to Google Thummer, L.A. County.
And to be clear, there's no B in there.
It's not Thumber.
No, it's it's Thummer.
And you will see a very dapper pig who I guess sometimes you'll see him in current mascot mode.
But probably like the the classic version of Thummer seems to be like original kind of 40s era.
Hobo.
Sure.
Yeah.
Which like what else about what's like what are the primary facets of Thummer?
Thummer is yellow, weirdly, not pink.
He carries a suitcase which could contain, I don't know, money, bribes, brushes.
Yeah, it's suspicious.
What are door to door salesmen?
Oh, yeah.
Combs, harmonicas.
What would you sell if you were an industrious guy in 51?
He's dressed like Robert Mitcham from Night of the Hunter, basically.
Like a weird traveling or like.
Yeah.
Orange vest.
Kind of a case.
He's like he's on the go.
Say, fella, I got a I got a tail for you.
And so he was originally made as the mascot for the original fair.
And he was just kind of ripped off of a pig iron mascot because the guy had already drawn this pig for a pig iron company.
And they're like, here, just take this as the mascot.
And he was hitchhiking because they didn't want too many people to come and fill up the parking lot.
So they were encouraging people to hitchhike to the fair.
This was about this was they wanted hitchhiking to happen.
Yeah, they were like, yes, share a car.
Wow.
And it's also it's hard to convey the hitchhiking when you don't have a thumb, which ironically.
And maybe we need to get into that, too.
What does the name isn't about thumb?
Or is it?
It is. It is.
And is it about hitchhiking?
Is he thumbing a ride?
So that's why he's thumber.
Well, it wasn't what his name was originally, though, guys.
As you saw, his original name was Porky.
For years, he was Porky Pig.
And he looks almost like Porky, the hitchhiking pig, a pig that was modeled almost exactly the same as Porky Pig.
They do have the same shoes.
They both were kind of like cloven hoof slippers.
Fancy. They're both fancy pigs, professional pigs.
And they this is in the 40s.
Right. So he's Porky's around.
They can't deny.
We know Porky.
We know Porky more than ever.
He was a decade in.
They were like, we're going to call this Porky looking pig Porky Pig, which is sort of like net today.
What's your snowman, Olaf?
Like, it's a recent.
Yeah.
So Warner Brothers lets him go for a couple of years.
And then they're just like, no, stop it.
You can't just steal Porky Pig.
But they had made so much merchandise with him on it with the name Porky.
Oh, I saw that they they were promoting the fair with napkins that were distributed to restaurants and bars across the city.
And they'd already printed up and sent out a million napkins, even knowing that the copyright was shaky.
So what are we going to do not to have the napkins?
The napkins are gone. That ship has sailed.
But, yeah, they just had like, oh, here, I'm pulling up this article really quick.
So, yeah, they they were like, real quick, we've got to change this name.
We're in trouble with the Brothers Warner.
So they they did a quick like, name the pig contest.
So people voted and were like, Thummer, Thummer.
This is why we live in a democracy.
You get the best results.
Has there ever been a name this thing contest where the where the good name was chosen?
Bode McVogueface.
That's your idea of the best version?
Yeah. Bode McVogueface and the I voted sticker are the only two times like the good thing one, I think.
Oh, the grotesque I voted sticker.
What's the story of the I voted sticker?
Just a kid is just like they were like, make it our local vote stickers for I voted.
And just one kid just drew like that screaming head that says I voted.
That's like dripping color. Jason's finding it.
Yeah, it's like a little monster head.
Okay.
Okay. So the year though, they were like, we have to change this.
But yeah, this is from the quote from this article from the Daily Bulletin.
Some one hundred thousand decals with the character were distributed.
And so we're five hundred thousand attractive for color cocktail napkins.
So that's probably how the napkin ended up like at Warner Brothers.
What the hell is this?
Like that's probably because they were trying to get the word out.
They advertise so well.
They're at the smokehouse.
Yeah, they're at the smokehouse.
So, Scott, here's the I voted.
Oh, wow.
They're calling it a spider crab.
A kid drew that.
I like it.
Everyone voted on it and then it became the I voted sticker for like this for some city.
That's great. I love it.
But some.
So they changed it really quick to Thummer.
But still, for the next year, some 90,000 Thummer buttons were distributed to children.
But like Porky, but still a million napkins with Porky were still in circulation.
Come see Porky.
Porky the pig who you can only see by buying tickets to the fair.
And Jack Warner himself is staring at this.
I can give you this napkin.
I need this napkin.
I need to spill a little booze on it first so it covers up the name.
So Thummer's around.
Then in 1981, a young pig was donated to the fair CEO, Ralph Hines, who spontaneously named the pig Thummer.
He said he represents the spirit of the fair.
Soon it became clear that the pig was a she, not a he, and was pregnant.
In response, the fair's mascot was made a female and named Mrs. Thummer.
Mrs. Thummer.
Yeah, so they just, they made her a pregnant female pig.
This is a real problem.
This is definitely not an invented problem.
The real pig is female.
What else, what other choice do we have?
We are a livestock fair where everybody coming will learn how to sex a pig pretty quickly.
We have a huge pig display.
I'm sure they're paying a lot of attention.
So then they, three years later, were like, what were we thinking?
And they just went back to original Thummer.
But then they were like, we should change, he looks too old-timey.
So they made him a farmer.
They gave him overalls.
So he looked like Whittles.
Yeah, not very firm.
And everyone hated that too.
So they had to turn him back into a weird traveling con man.
They did a competition of which did you like better, city Thummer or country Thummer.
And city won by a lot.
Which is weird because it's a fair and he's a pig, but vastly people preferred fancy Thummer.
I guess it makes sense.
But now he's got this kind of dumb, it's almost like bad latter day vanilla ice look.
He's got this bucket hat.
That's what they're pushing lately.
We've gotten away from maybe just no one's paying attention anymore.
And we're allowing base Thummer to just have this kind of dumb red bucket.
Who dresses like this?
Smash Mouth guy?
Rest in peace, Smash Mouth guy.
Who's like a current red bucket hat wearer?
Well, he looks like one of the CG chipmunks.
When they're like cool.
Yeah, he has too much detail now.
He's got freckles and too much shading.
I don't know how I feel about this kind of detailed Thummer.
He's like a pet boy.
He's meant to kind of stay 40s forever.
But Eva, I feel like when you saw Thummer for the first time that one year at the festival,
it was kind of like that moment in Spider-Man where he sees venom.
And you're just like, that's evil me.
This is like the creature that I will hate.
You just have hated this animal.
I hate Thummer.
I wasn't clear on this.
I didn't know the opinion.
I find him to be loathsome.
I mean, the comparison to Night of the Hunter.
That's not a guy you want to be.
Yeah, and the fact that he's just like a series of rip.
He's a ripoff was was a ripoff name.
He's just like a just a bunch of stolen.
You know what he reminds me of is like that it's that theme park that was in Shanghai
that looked just like Disneyland and they had a Minnie Mouse that was named Girl Cat.
That's what that's how I feel about Thummer.
Thummer is just a like a shitty like brush salesman mascot
who was named Porky until someone was like, stop it.
He's like, OK, whatever.
Sorry, I can't I can't even drive myself to this fucking place.
I got to get a ride.
Can you guys give me a ride?
I don't exactly have a car right now.
Could you?
I only come out and walk around an hour a day and then I just go back to wherever.
Well, that's what I didn't see if I were overall.
Make America great again.
I need new clothes. My clothes broke.
My suit isn't nice anymore.
It's got holes.
All this background on Thummer kind of adds a different level to this post
on the L.A. County Instagram a few weeks ago.
A single rider looking for a fair buddy.
The cardboard sign he's holding.
But then the caption reads, riding solo slide into the DMs.
Oh, he's a DM slide.
No, no, no.
The John Cusack pose.
The most romantic pose there is.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
This is I've caught this that on the Instagram presence gets a little bit like
they're like someone is looking up the modern phrases and giving them to Thummer
because one was like just kind of a basic photo of him.
And then it says that does that felt cute might delete later.
No, that was a few years ago that phrase.
I'm impressed they made it that far.
Honestly, they like county fairs making vaguely modern.
Another one is similarly holding up a sign and the sign says main character energy.
Oh, trend chasing.
And also, once you see Thummer, you can never unsee him.
He's everywhere. He's painted on the ground.
He's he's on the walls.
He you can take pictures with him.
He has his own corner now in the barnyard area.
Yeah, Thummer's house, which I believe you went to.
Yeah, I went I went to Thummer's.
There were areas set up for not just Thummer, but also his his friends.
Lily, the sheep.
And what I now know is Daisy the cow.
But I swear I copy and pasted this from another article that maybe multiple times
called her daily the cow.
And I was trying to wrap my head around that.
I was even glad I figured out it was Daisy when I saw Daisy in person
because I was ready to start doing like now I daily the cow.
Right.
Is there a walk around Daisy?
Not a one.
There was like kind of a standing plywood one in the area where actual cows are.
I took a picture with Daisy.
Daisy is like trying to kind of like look feminine and cool.
But then so like using the bell around the neck as jewelry.
Yes, I still wear the I'm a cow.
I wear the bell.
But I'm trying to be make it like kind of my thing, make it a little trendy.
That's nice.
Yeah, there's this kind of up your alley is in the Minnie Mouse woods like a nice set of pearls.
They're trying to do a kind of a Mickey's house thing.
But they just it's like it's just a really shitty sign that says Thummer's house.
It's just like a porch.
It's really nothing.
And when I pass by it, literally nothing.
Now, I don't know.
I maybe I should have looked up the times that Thummer would be there.
But I was sure anticipating some kind of specific Thummer interaction.
And there wasn't even a comeback later for Thummer.
There was no Lily.
There was no daily the cow.
None of them were there.
So I got nothing out of that and not even a good.
Yeah.
This photo.
That's just a that's a bad banner.
You got nothing.
And that's how they label the area where Thummer is.
I've only seen him once in 15 years, I guess.
So he's not really.
So there was no way I would show up and all those times.
You can look for him, but he doesn't.
He's not working.
He can't get a ride.
He's lazy.
He's a taker.
I'm still in Azusa.
Could somebody grab me?
I overslept.
Oh, no.
I know.
I keep doing this.
I swear it is not.
I've had I've had a lot going on.
I'm going to have to bring my briefcase to work so I can change.
I can shave.
Do we get I'm do we get comped on the food?
I mean, I work there.
So, like, could I just grab like what's the surprise?
What's the per diem for the fair?
I here's the thing.
I was sort of I like, oh, yeah, Thummer.
I knew you had an opinion about Thummer.
Everything you've said makes me like Thummer a lot more.
Oh, really?
Because I long for the day when a mascot of a place was a big scumbag.
We've talked about it a lot of times.
The Chuck E.
Cheese, the original Chuck E.
Cheese was like, hey, you dimwit.
Like, he was really like an angsty asshole character who was a scumbag, who was up to no good.
He was scamming people.
And this was a trend, I think, for a long time.
And then, of course, now corporate America's come in and smoothed all the edges off and maybe Thummer is a throwback to this old type of character I like.
I think maybe he is.
I don't think no one's got eyes on Thummer.
No one has eyes.
No one cares.
They don't even know if it's a man or a woman.
People don't care that Thummer might be like making children uncomfortable.
Yes.
With his weird comments or with weird posting where he's trying to.
Like if Chuck E.
Cheese was still his old shitty character from the 70s, he would be like, hey, slide into my DMs.
Come in.
That would be happening.
So Thummer is trying to keep this going.
Keep this going.
Thummer is weaponizing therapy talk.
You're gasolineing me.
So I should probably say, though, I entered baking for the first time this year.
Yes.
I have never entered baking.
I don't know how to bake.
I've been learning how to bake in the last two years as a project to learn how to measure things.
Oh.
Yeah, because I like to cook, but I don't like to bake because it involves following somebody else's recipe and believing that what they say is right and that my way isn't necessarily better.
And that's really hard for me to trust in other people's wisdom.
And you don't get to bring enough to the table, maybe.
Yeah.
I've never been a good baker because I would just like, I'd be like, you don't really need four sticks of butter.
I would just think that they're wrong.
I come into things with a level of distrust.
So to unwire my brain and become a better person, I have to try to learn baking for this reason.
So I entered cookies for the first time this year.
I should also say that Amy got me to take a sugar cookie decorating contest.
I mean, a class like a year and a half ago.
And it was really complicated and I was like, well, I'll never use this skill.
And Amy made it just she did it all the time.
She's been doing sugar shape decorating really fancy sugar cookies for a year and a half now constantly.
And she's gotten so good at it that she could like open a shop if she wanted.
She was a professional film critic with a lot of other stuff going on.
It has become my passion.
But because of that, when I entered the cookie fair for the first time this year, when I entered the county fair with you, I was like, I don't think my ego can take losing.
Yeah, I'm not as resilient as Eva is.
So I decided I was going to just suck up, do the absolute best I could, work my ass off on these cookies, spend 14 hours on these cookies.
She spent 14 hours on them.
And I made thumbers because I was like, I know my audience.
I'm going to go all in and do thumber cookies.
I'm going to do a little briefcase.
I entered under like the cookie themes are kind of all over the place.
So I entered under best representation of festival theme, which was a terrible theme this year.
But it was strangely specific.
Stars, stripes and fun.
Terrible.
Fuck off.
Yeah.
That's not like if you do like red, white and fun and then like the third is that there's no third of stars and stripes.
Stars, stripes and fun.
Yeah, it's nothing.
So I made the most pandering ass cookies I could.
I was very proud of them.
They're thumbers.
He's not wearing his little suit, but he's not wearing overalls.
I put him in a series of different striped and starred mixing kind of like an old time bathing suit.
Old timey bathing suit.
It is a bathing suit that Dirtbag would wear in his time.
So Dirtbag bathing suit.
And then I made him little suitcases and I made you a special thumber that I didn't submit to the fair that kind of expressed my rage at thumber.
Where his briefcase says what I think is inside, which is dirty little secrets.
So I made brownies and Amy and I the morning of like you have to drop off your stuff the day before the fair opens or the week before the fair opens in person.
So you drive to Pomona.
There's a window and we did the drive together.
You get to go into the empty fairground.
We happened to walk in and drop the stuff off at the exact time that they did the rope drop for tablescaping.
Which is intense because they get to pick their own table, which we didn't know.
Like table placement.
Oh, so everybody like runs to where they want it.
Because they want the corner so you can get like real views of all your table.
Right.
We talked to the lady who got the corner table like, did you get a sign table?
She's like, no, I picked this one.
Are they all the same table?
Yes.
Okay.
I think so.
Unless there's like one wobbly one that everybody's trying to avoid.
They're definitely the same door.
But it was so we walked in and I handed over my brownies and the guy was like, oh, there's a lot of brownies this year.
Good luck.
Like total like you're going to lose all the way there to get brownie attitude.
And then he took Amy's cookies, opened them up, looked at them.
It's like face lit up and he's like, always smart to do summer.
And I was like, God damn it.
Which is also at the same time a compliment that you don't get, Eva, but then also but still the always is like, well, you're not the first to do them.
But he also was like, you could tell like Amy had had brought it brought it home.
She had hit a grand slam from the look on the guy's face who was checking in.
I gave him those pandering ass thumbers.
Like one briefcase said he had cotton candy.
Another briefcase said that he had caramel apples.
He had a ride ticket.
He had pig race prizes.
Oh, I was like batting my eyes.
You didn't make one say counterfeit cash.
They were so beautiful though.
They were the most beautiful cookies she's ever made.
It was a lot of help because I was having problems with like blush placement and stuff.
Like how do I do his eyes?
So Eva served as a thumber expert.
Yeah, he looks great.
Yeah, isn't he amazing?
To get Thummer on model.
Well, I guess we could post a picture.
But like when you're doing the any of these cookies, not just Thummer, are you drawing by hand a little designer?
Are you sort of doing it like so you just kind of on a piece of paper will draw like what the cookie is going to look like?
Yeah, like I take the cookie cutter and then I trace on a piece of paper a couple of times.
I sort of work out the proportions of where the eyes should be.
The people who are really into the sugar cookie game and like I'm in some Facebook groups and they're just intense.
Yeah, like they all use projectors.
That's kind of like basic cookie one on one, which I'm not ready to go there.
Trace it with a projector.
Wow.
Like if I posted my cookies in the sugar cookie group, they would be like, nice try, sweetheart.
Keep practicing.
Like they're really, really.
Then I'll kill them.
But I should say I came in first.
She got best of class, which is a level above.
She gets a special rosette, which is like very few people in the cabinet.
There's like a handful of best of class.
And it's like one step below, like best of entire baked goods division.
So Amy, Amy, absolutely.
You saw these, right?
Well, I saw them in person.
I found them.
And I knew there was something.
Either you sent a photo or you posted it.
I knew like once I figure out the cabinet system, like, OK, I think I know.
But where are they?
And then my eyes went straight as soon as I oh, Thummer, got it.
OK.
And then, yeah, they look great.
And they aren't rotting.
And the rats haven't gotten to them, at least as of yesterday.
Listeners, if you go this weekend, I can't, fingers crossed, no rats.
Although also it might be interesting to see what the rats do to Thummer.
It's not what your work deserves, but it's what Thummer deserves.
Did you see what second place was?
Some girl just tried to enter some stars.
It's like, good job, girl.
That's right.
You did some stars.
Really?
Red, white, and blue.
You're just going to enter stars?
You're not really clock the multiple ribbons first and over that.
That's great.
Wow.
Congratulations.
So that's going to get mailed to your house and you have to frame it.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm one and done.
I'm never entering again.
Oh, I was going to ask.
Geez.
Take it and then go home.
She took it.
Can I suggest an idea that it would be time intensive, but would be funny.
You do another series of Thummer cookies, but you put like one of his briefcases has
loose pills or something, or yeah, like counterfeit money like Scott said.
A real F you to the cookie contest now.
Sort of like you won and now you're asserting dominance in a different way.
I mean, I do feel like I was planning a future.
I was going to rest on my laurels of now.
Every time I go to the county fair, I can just mock all the cookies.
I can now become the main old lady.
But the idea of using this cabinet placement as a plant, like we can do it for like an
escape room kind of thing, some sort of like living game.
If I could put subliminal things in my cookies.
Right.
Then they would be here.
We could gamify this.
If I could do like a QR code.
A QR code that takes you to a website about like how Thummer is a.
A pedophile.
Antifa.
I've seen Thummer on the college campuses.
He's playing those ideas.
Why would Thummer need this length of rubber hose and a syringe if he wasn't a heroin
user?
Like if we find out what the theme is and it seems like something we can do next year
to manipulate.
Yeah.
Like the year before it was spring into fun, which whatever.
But I think we could make a jigsaw kind of trap.
We could also do a summer door and we could really get weird because I feel like we could
have gotten a door very easily.
The table scaping like fills up really fast, but we were thinking about doing door scaping
right up until we changed our minds.
And the learning curve on door scaping I think is a lot because like with your mythical menu
that you make up, they judge you on, you know, if you say you have a soup, but you don't
have a soup spoon, you just absolutely lose.
Like you're tanked at that point.
There's so many ways to lose.
There was this fine table that was representing the coronation dinner of Nicholas and Alexandra.
It was a beautiful one.
A feast fit for the last czar.
And then there's the actual menu.
It transports you to Russia and like and then it just said like there is extra silverware
that is not reflected on the menu.
Actually, it said of the menu.
They didn't even get the grammar right in their snippiness.
Who are the judges, by the way?
I don't know.
I'd love to watch the judges.
What about a table theme of Thummer's last meal?
He's on death row and you're making the menu for whatever he's having for his last meal.
Pork and bacon, please.
I want to eat myself.
I hate myself because I hate myself.
Or if it was like a horrifying door where on the other side it is Thummer.
And like you can see him coming at you or like trying to get a paw.
He's got his like little hook coming around the door.
Or he's at your door trying to sell you garbage.
Here's Johnny with Thummer.
He's like been chopping through the door and he's like.
Here's Thummer.
Yeah.
And you could have like the Lily.
Is she Lily?
Yeah.
The one on the side.
Daily.
Calling her Daily.
Yeah, I'm going with Daily.
She's got the Shelley Duvall like face.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
But then you'd have to update it.
So he's not going to say here's Johnny because Johnny Carson's been off the air for so long.
So he says like here's Jimmy.
He means Jimmy Fallon.
He says here's Porky.
And we have to flip because since he's like absolutely.
He's re-embracing his real, that's my real name.
The suits made me change it.
And since he doesn't work, we have to say I'll play and no work because he's just a lazy
bastard.
Yeah, right, right, right.
Oh yeah.
She has no motivation.
We do have to recreate the ballroom photo with him in the middle.
Yeah, see I'll enter the fair again if I can do it to troll the fair in some way.
Yeah.
Do you think there's.
There he is at the 1924 fair.
He's always been here.
What about a Thummer like stealing Porky Pig's clothes or something somehow?
Can you, can we visualize that?
Oh yeah, an embarrassed ashamed Porky Pig.
Like Porky Pig locked in a closet.
He went to the YMCA to take a swim and while Thummer waited.
Hey, I live here.
I'm kind of between more stable accommodations right now.
Has anyone been kicked out of the fair permanently?
Do you think they have that ability?
Well I think something must have happened because on the on the tablescaping rules they
do say fair reserves the right to reject any table sitting that is objectionable or unsuitable
which makes me think somebody did try to push it further than everybody.
I mean this is the question is how are you going to know if you don't try?
Yeah.
We don't try to get permanently ejected from our favorite place.
Why we've been there enough it's time to get thrown out forever.
At this point we've eaten everything.
Yeah, we've tried everything.
I got a shrimp bowl that had.
Fruity Pebbles.
Fruity Pebbles on it this time.
Is that in half a pineapple?
It was in half a pineapple.
Disgusting.
Yeah.
I was going to say.
It was okay.
It was gross.
I was trying to find the grossest thing I could find.
Yeah.
What is like the stunt food?
That's a big like the deep fried Oreos are kind of par for the course now.
Yeah.
But now there is like.
Fried Kool-Aid.
Yeah.
Every year they seem like they're getting into new trends like this year it was very
spam heavy like spam fries, spam sliders, spam pot stickers.
Pickle has been huge for a while.
Explain the one you heard about.
Yeah.
Well a couple years ago there was one that I like had to find it took me all day to find
it but it was a it was a giant dill pickle and I've been hollowed out and stuffed with
nacho cheese and then also hot Cheetos and inside the nacho cheese.
So it's like a hot Cheeto pickle nacho burrito and that was not a winner and I think they've
been like retooling it since then so now you get it more in the form of pickled nachos
because it's hard to eat.
You know.
Yeah.
They've been really pushing hot Cheeto pot stickers which I think is a failure we tried
it last year.
Yeah we had those last year but the pickle split.
The pickle split I was looking for and I couldn't find it.
They said it had it.
But it is what is it a banana split with a pickle basically?
Yeah it's a banana split but there's a giant pickle instead of the banana and they use
pineapple dill whip in between the pickle and then they cover it with like spicy like
tahini candy.
Like tahini.
Yeah.
There's a lot of chamois stuff everywhere there.
And strings of sour spaghetti candy.
The whole.
This didn't seem.
Yeah.
I saw this on like the Eater Roundup of food.
This is a slice of pizza but it's pickles and hot Cheetos and I guess ranch.
That looks good.
That does look good.
Yeah.
That looks good.
I don't think I'm I think the hot Cheeto area doesn't have any appeal to me.
I don't know.
Am I missing out?
Have you guys tried hot Cheeto stuff?
I think it's tricky because like you know in 2020 when there was a pandemic I tried to
make my own county fair just for me and my boyfriend in the backyard because we missed
it so much and we had to do the triple cheeseburger Krispy Kreme because that's our favorite.
And we also tried to do like elotes covered in hot Cheeto which was really difficult.
We couldn't get them to stick and it made me really appreciate whatever science they're
doing to get hot Cheetos to stick to things.
It's probably science or mayonnaise.
It's like leeches or mayonnaise.
And then I showed up.
We also made a balloon pop and that was so hard to make your own balloon pop.
That takes forever.
Oh yeah that seems I don't know where to begin.
Wait wait what do you mean by balloon pop?
Like I blew up a bunch of balloons and stapled them to cardboard and it took me like six
hours.
Okay.
And then you were throwing darts at it?
Yeah I bought a bunch of darts.
Oh that means carnival game.
I didn't know this was a snack.
Okay okay.
Oh yeah.
And I'm missing the balloon pop.
You play you eat.
Yeah.
The triple cheeseburger, the Krispy Kreme triple cheeseburger is mentioned at the top
of the show.
I had been thinking about it.
Didn't end up going for it.
But like you were describing it a little bit the other night.
I think my boyfriend and I were both attacking you trying to get you to eat it.
Yeah I know he did the hard sell and he described it almost as if he had been, that you guys
share food typically but it like made him go feral or something.
Like no not in this case.
I am hoarding this.
Yeah like the first year that we tried the triple cheeseburger Krispy Kreme burger.
Like I thought it sounded gross.
He bought it.
We usually do trade off bites and when he took his first bite and I said can I have
some actually?
I'm curious.
He said no.
Which has never happened before.
But he said no like a raging wolf.
Like he kind of curled his body around the burger.
It was like you cannot have any of this burger.
Caesar's first word in Planet of the Apes.
It is the most primal bite of food you've ever had in your life.
Like I cannot explain it.
Like I've had good things.
I've eaten good food before.
I'm a human.
But this it hits something in your brain stem where you're like I'm a caveman.
I'm supposed to eat charred meat.
I want sugar too.
And you're just boom straight there and it's all you can think about is eating this burger
as soon as you have your first bite.
It kind of scared me.
I didn't know that you had that reaction.
We had that giant pretzel this time that was actually the best pretzel I've ever had in
my life.
That was really good.
It was really good.
It was like this big.
So we all three of us shared it.
I've learned that I can't eat gluten but I ate a bunch of that pretzel and I was sick
all week but it was great.
It was gorgeous.
That description kind of scared me and the one that you just did too.
We're like what is this going to unlock?
What if I don't come back?
Does this have like a werewolf effect?
I want it to scare you.
Like my life has been divided into before and after.
Oh god.
Well it had kind of a hold on me through the day and eventually my son too because I was
thinking about it and I was doing the parent math the whole time of like when are we going
to do dinner?
Are we going to keep him on schedule for dinner and do we do it here?
Is this plenty he'll eat here because he only eats chicken fingers and burgers and stuff
but he was kind of getting a little tired and wanted to get out of there and I was proposing
options to him and I said like oh you know what they have is like a donut burger.
Like the bun is a donut and again I was saying he's not really trying a lot right now so
his initial reaction like no thanks is very polite at this stage and I was like you know
I'm going to back off that too because he doesn't eat cheese on burgers and he might
think it's weird and gross when it comes out so I kind of backed off it and then we do
a long walk from where we're kind of close to the cheeseburgers all the way to the entrance
of the fair and at the end of it he does the saddest um dad I do want the donut burger
and he clearly had just been like going over and over it in his head for 15 minutes and
like I just lost my opportunity I made the wrong choice and he doesn't go back on stuff
like that he usually decides and that is it but he clearly he just like wrestled with
it so again something primal about this and then I thought do I go back but it was so
far back and I didn't know if he would actually like what if he doesn't like it and then we
do all this effort for he probably will so what if he likes it too much what if like
what if it breaks him the way it broke me and there will never be anything as good as that
triple cheeseburg with the two donuts and then he's going to be in his imagination of
it is maybe better than it could ever be what would it do to a child you were at least
an adult imagine if yes he's still forming where's nobody more raw than a four-year-old
boy resets the floor he's drinking the dune water of life as a little boy he becomes the
twilight zone kid who can control stuff with his mind sends you to the cornfield that was
the true juncture point of am I a good dad or not and I made the wrong choice I know
then I was like well I got to do something we got to do something fair and I can just
a little exhausted not want to go all the way back I didn't like reinvent the wheel
but I have not had fried Oreos before certainly he is not before so I did that
You had fried Oreos for dinner?
No it ends up no no no
You're a good dad that's a good dad thing
Okay
Fully as the dinner I don't know if I'm good dad but going for it at all but yeah we did
we did give him a taste and like yeah this is not like as Jason was saying these have
been around a while now this is almost like the standard of the crazy fair combo and I'm
having it like and you guys know I'm far from the treat boy of the podcast this was just
like there's nothing weird about it at all this is just like good primary there is no
like bizarre or bizarre but it works it just works
Those are great
They're just so so good they make all the sense in the world so just fully satisfying
experience there side track then the rest of it is like I got to get out of here and
get dinner on time and he wants burgers so what do we do and I end up like I'm then feverishly
looking for burgers in San Dimas like not far from there and I find oh wait this is
interesting NASCAR refuel tenders and burgers and there's three locations in San Dimas
is this like a thing in the Inland Empire I got to figure and this is something for
the show too a NASCAR chain and then I start my gears start turning like almost like 30
seconds before I get into the parking lot and I was just ahead of it because I pull
up and I go to the address and I find an IHOP this is a ghost kitchen folks there are no
physical what a fool am I I should I would know if there were lots of NASCAR refuel
stands everywhere this is a sub brand of but anyway now I have that to bring to the table
that if you do want to ghost kitchen order NASCAR themed food you can get talladega
tenders
Wow
Are they at least in a fun NASCAR box or anything
It's like checker pattern but yeah that's kind of all you get and the theming is not
much more from there and then I start looking it up and like where are the other ones and
I find wait there's one at CityWalk no that's different that's NASCAR refuel wings so we
got two different
Is that at Buca de Pepo
It is in fact at Buca de Pepo
Yes
Yeah yeah
Jason how do you feel yeah and I'll let you put it in your words but how do you feel that
there's another ghost kitchen at Buca de
De Pepo
Yeah got it nailed it
Fine
Yes as always you nailed it I don't know why we even made that a thing
I guess I'm just flummox like how many more ghost kitchens can they run at once
In that one location you know because I also I'm looking at burgers in that area and I'm
like tons of Mr. Beast burgers too
Oh yeah
I think San Dimas is ghost kitchen city
There's this old timey I think I've talked to you guys about Billingsley's which is by
my house which was Barbara Billingsley's primary restaurant which is where I was at
the bar when I saw Tim Kaine had been announced as the vice president for Hillary Clinton
Does Barbara Billingsley leave it to Beaver
Yes
Anyway it closed during pandemic it turned into a ghost kitchen for a thing called burger
bitch so it's this beautiful old restaurant that then had a sign up front that just said
burger bitch
It feels so insulting that they kept her initials
I know
And then burger bitch collapsed and now there's just a rotting burger bitch sign on top of
the Billingsley sign and it's falling apart too and the whole thing is like boarded over
That reminds me of the chain that was a scam burger rim
Oh yes burger rim yeah
It was everywhere for like a really short time not well reviewed and someone found out
Like they all quickly closed I think because they got sued or it turned out to be a big
Ponzi scheme
It was like an Israeli Ponzi scheme or something crazy like that yeah burger rim
There was one by UCB I feel like
I think so
Yeah I never ate there
Did you somebody send this to me I don't know if it was from our Facebook group or some
other Facebook group that the Ford Motor Company has a series of restaurants
I've learned about the Ford restaurant
Ford we put it in the this was in the club three whole once it was one of the worst
It was one of the worst performers worse than yours Mike
A Ford restaurant where are they?
Is this like the Ford filling station that used to be by the Staples Center?
No that's Harrison Ford Sons restaurant
Wait oh really?
Yeah Benjamin Ford
We gotta start talking celebrity too Eva
He was on Hell's Kitchen when the season I worked on
That had a really good marshmallow ice cream
Really yeah
He's a good chef
I totally forgot it was even in that poll but it's a lot of Florida but it's just like
a chain restaurant that's owned by Ford
That's Ford where you learn about Henry
I guess
I mean that's fun
Yeah I'm not mad at it
Yeah
Ford's Garage
I feel like I would trust a chain restaurant about Levi's I wear a lot of Levi's I like
Levi's I feel like a Levi's restaurant would probably serve pretty decent food
Yeah
Sure
So like probably the containers and boxes and silverware are all denim
Yeah
Maybe not literally denim although I mean sure
You could yeah
During pandemic I took my stepdaughter to The Grove because they had opened a restaurant
inside Brandy Melville at The Grove that just sold folded over pizza sandwiches and iced
coffee and she just really wanted to go and I was like I can make this happen for you
So we drove to The Grove she got a little Brandy Melville food
Brandy Melville is a sexy teen girl clothing
Right
It's like the gap for teenage girls
Oh I always thought Brandy Melville was like a real housewife I didn't know that
No it's a it's like it's like cheap really cheap clothes for teenage girls and I think
it's kind of like minimal sizing where you're supposed to just sort of only wear one
I think I might be one of those
There's only one size
There's only one size yeah
Isn't it that name is close to a real housewife though
I'm looking at Brandy Glanville
There you go
Yeah you're really close
Oh that's why I've been getting confused
For some reason they had opened a restaurant in the peak like I think it was Christmas
2020 they had opened a restaurant inside the store
Wow
And we went and got our little sandwiches and then ate them outside and she's like okay
thanks
Is it kind of neither good nor bad
Is it like the clothes are stretchy or you just can only be a size
It's the second thing
They're encouraging a specific type shape of girl
So it's like when they used to be five seven nine when we were kids and you could only
be five seven or nine
Or else you don't get clothes
Or else you don't get clothes or else you go naked
Yeah or else you have to go to Torrid
At least they tried to jazz it up with a cool word
See it's not so bad you get a cool word with it
Torrid
Yeah it's crazy
Wait what's your ranking of the how do you rate the Brandy Melville restaurant
It was better than it should have been
Oh okay
But it shouldn't have existed at all
So it's in like existing not totally offensive
More clothing companies should take a stab at restaurants
Yeah
Well I'm a fan of Nordstrom's Bar Verde
Oh I know
Oh Bar Verde get out it's of course it's great
Yeah yeah
Isn't Bar Verde like for angry like traditional husbands to drink at while their wives
Bar Verde
Buy fancy hats
Bar Verde is for everyone
Spending my paycheck on who knows what
She'll get some disgruntled people
Brasiers and jumpsuits
One more pour please
Three fingers of Jack Daniels
Leave the bottle
My heart earned money
That's that's that's Thummer
I thought we were going to Ford's garage for lunch
I'm stuck on the top floor of goddamn Nordstrom's for the third Saturday in a row
Mrs. Thummer gets pregnant immediately upon her existence
I'm going to tell the fair they should discontinue her
I was flying solo everything was going great
Then they made me be here for two three years like Robert Durst
Hiding out in Louisiana
Wearing a dress so nobody notices my crimes
Is that what Robert Durst did really?
Yeah he hid out
As a lady
And then he killed another person as the lady and got in trouble for that
That's the guy he chopped off
I didn't watch Jinx 2 is this the this is what you learned?
That's not even what that's about
He went on trial for that one and he got off because he was like I didn't kill him
But I did chop him up because I got scared when he died accidentally
And they're like checks out
A lot of people would do that
The other day when you reminded me of the guy from Dogpatch USA
And I thought about him in a while
I looked it up there's no footprints of the guy
Was this really like backwoods theme park in Arkansas and the guy was a scam artist
Little Abner
Seemingly just fully disappeared
He like stole all the town's money and left
And I was now I'm like I think that I think that's I think he did all this Durst stuff
Oh yeah
He was like in disguise somewhere
And got into his next scam
It's like end of Dark Knight Rises
Where you'll be at like a cafe
He gives you a nod
You'll see what's his name hair or something hair
Michael Hair maybe
David
David Hair thank you
Yeah there's no there isn't there are no Google results since the episode that we did
He convinced the landowner that he was going to redo the Little Abner park as like an American American dream park
And then he just didn't do anything and he ran the place to the ground
He just did a YouTube channel that was half songs and half apologies and explanations of why none of the stuff was happening
And all of a sudden he was chased out of town by the cops
See I think this was Thummer's original plan
I think that Thummer wanted to start the fair and then take all the money and run away
And then Mr. Thummer got pregnant he got stuck
Oh yeah
Yeah
No one's got eyes on this place
Pomona who gives a shit
I can't believe they're still doing this crap
I was going to burn this fairground to the ground
And be done with it forever
I well look you know it was it was a very good time
You know it ended up resulting in a very fine half habit half Jersey Mike's meal for the two of us out in
Out in San Dimas that was nice
And then before that at the fair proper here's what I have to thank you two for
Is that I hatched the plan to go let's go and then realized oh my god two big train things
Which are year-round apparently and always there and maybe accessible even when the fair is not going on
There's a train museum where you can climb up onto big giant working trains
Which they turn on turn on the motors kids can you know pull the whistle
These are the most poorly guarded like there's climbing up onto real trains
Under like very steep ladders with railings that don't block little children from falling off the side
25 feet so I'm really watching him there
But he had the time of his life getting to go onto some real trains
And then also a model train that's been there for a hundred years
That is the side that is half a football field
I love model trains so much
I don't know why I have this like very intense reaction to them
It's just when they we create things like little drive-in movie theaters and stuff
That's all the little dioramas
Like making the little city stuff
I like dioramas
Playmobil
Have you been in any of these stores in Burbank, the model train stores?
Yes
I've beaten, I could never do it
Can't have another thing
Guys I don't know if I've ever told this story on the podcast
But when I was in college I met Gary Coleman and I was wearing a train conductor hat
Because I was being random like Amy was random in college
I remember you had that hat, I used to have a hat like that too
And Gary Coleman said your hat's the universal sign for I like trains
And I was like yeah and he's like do you want to come check out my model train set?
And he like gave me his phone number and he wrote on the note HO scale American trains
And so I like got back to my dorm and I like called and left a message for Gary Coleman
And then
You called? You did it? Oh my god
Yeah I called him
I left a message saying yeah I'll come check out your train set
And then I talked to someone else but they're like what are you doing don't do that
You can't, don't do that
He's like he beats people up and stuff he's gotten in trouble and I was like oh right
So then but I got back home and there was like a bunch of messages in a row from Gary Coleman on my machine
Like escalating rapidly even in the messages
And then I stopped whatever dumb game I was playing and I just ended it there
Eva did you learn anything from this experience?
Obviously not
Because I'm the person I am
You've got to have a stronger creep meter at this point
This creeps around every bend of all the stuff that you're into
But sometimes I look at you and I'm just so relieved you're alive
Oh you too babe
You only dated Gary for like a year and a half it wasn't a big thing
You're always in control you always had your eyes on the door
I kept the note though in my like cabinet of cursor items
Cabinet of curiosity
Your museum of the weird
He did have a model train set though
He was an enthusiast
Wasn't he wearing like when he was on the Simpsons didn't he have like a train conductor hat?
There's some appearance he had like where he cameo'd somewhere where he had like a train conductor
Like him in trains was like a thing post his TV show
It's possible I could have just seen the train set and left but that's like one
It's a multiverse of possibilities
One of the great mysteries of my relationship is my boyfriend hated my train conductor hat
Like really actively hated it in a way that he doesn't hate almost anything I own but he hated my train conductor hat
And I went missing and three years later I found it in the neighbor's yard buried under a bush
Just incidentally looking for his hat
In the middle of the night he buried your hat
He denied it but like I was I don't know his cat went missing I was hunting around for the cat
I was behind the neighbor's gigantic bush and my hat was there
And I took it back and I was like can you explain this and I said no
No and I choose not to and you have no proof
Why would he do it so close to home though that's such a mistake
He should take that into the national forest
Yeah
Yeah like a shallow grave for it
He tried to convince me the cat took it back there
If I was looking for his cat there maybe it was his cat's hiding place
So we both had a train conductor hat?
Yeah of course
These stories are really taking a turn for the Hummer dark side
Thummer?
Thummer
Oh I was going to say is that a phrase Hummer dark side?
No
Did you have a train conductor's hat?
Yeah I think so
Of course you did
But I also
I didn't have a train conductor's hat
Maybe when I was five I did
I was thinking of the name because this place closed a couple years ago called Roadside America
Oh yeah
In Pennsylvania and it was just a giant miniature train
Like trains going every which way towns mountains like
It was a big roadside tourist attraction but yeah the pandemic kind of did the man
San Diego in their Balboa Park has a model train museum
We went to that
All of our travels are train motivated
Which is why I have to thank you for that
Because like you can climb on trains and look at model trains
He lost his shit he was so excited
And all of my dad calculations at this point are like
How much time does it kill?
How much does it cost?
And how much is it trains?
So this satisfied all of that very nicely
Like probably the biggest one he's ever seen
Probably the biggest one I've ever seen
I mean I also like I'm unemployed right now and I saw the thing
I was telling you Scott that said be a volunteer at the model train
And I was like am I gonna do this?
Even if you did it this could be our way to troll the fair next year
If I'm there every weekend just like painting and dusting little guys
If you made miniatures of us and you put them in tiny cars
And we're flipping off Thummer?
Yes
If we put like a tiny Thummer on the side of the road trying to hitchhike
We murdered him and he's in the trunk
Or Thummer tied to the tracks like Dudley Doode right?
Smiley whiplash
I was gonna say like a double indemnity sort of thing
Or if you were a cultured person a double indemnity
We're in fake crutches and we're on the back of the train
We're gonna throw Thummer off
Fucking Mrs. Thummer
Yeah
If you're flipping him off in the process and they call you out on it
You could always just say no we're giving thumbs
Yeah we're hitching a ride
That's on theme and Amy's a prize winner for being on theme
Oh my god his thumbs are flipping us off
He's not thumbing a ride
Wait you're right
He's been thumbing all the time
And thumb being in the name is a way to throw you off the trail
He's either like flipping you off or he's gonna drag that hoof across his throat
That thing's razor sharp if you get close to it
One false move and you're gone
The loathsome Thummer
Just have a little some characters and someone's having an affair with Thummer's wife and he doesn't know
Yeah we do like shadows like in the window of a motel and Thummer's outside with a gun in his mouth
Or Mrs. Thummer's pushing a stroller but it's like two pigs and a cow
Oh yeah that's good too
She says it's recessed DNA
I still have to pay for it it doesn't make sense
Once in every sixth generation you end up with a cow
She says
Thummer also has a pile of lamb chops
Back in the recesses of his neighborhood
One of the rooms in my house has a bunch of lamb chops
One of them's really big
Shut up I'll make the fucking moon disappear
All these cows and sheep coming after me
They'll never take down Thummer
Until his SWAT team's at the door of my neighborhood
Top of the world
They don't know it's just a plywood flat with nothing behind it
I got nothing
I've been alive
For 65 years and I got nothing
I found an interview with Thummer
In which they ask
Last question how did you get your name
A long time ago a local TV station put on a name the pig contest
Thummer was the entry I liked the most so that's where it came from
So he got to pick
He existed before the name
I mean we know he was porky but that's a weird way to answer it
I watch television
He probably stole it from another contest
Thummer won a different name the pig contest and he took it
I like Jim and Pam
So many great characters and you know what it has heart
And that's why the office still works to this day
Lecturing you about the American office
I like TV
I need to tell you something
The real Thummer died in Korea and I took his dog tag
Living his life but I don't feel much
That's why I drink don't you see
I do have to volunteer to go to Pomona and work at the Tremies
I think so
What else am I worth
Isn't it disheartening to find out that train work is volunteer based seemingly
Because you're probably thinking maybe I can make a little scratch becoming a train person
It's probably competitive and there's clicky like everything else at the fair
Everyone you're against has been doing it for 70 years
You will never get seniority
No I won't
I'll die I'll be dead first
Leave anything you'd like to plug
Upcoming very sad train volunteering career
A freshly dusted train set that I want you to all come and see
I've only had time to dust one they take forever
We've got a new tunnel you can take a look at
It's bigger than the other tunnels
The lights work again
Ronald is angry with me again
I don't know what I did but I think I remind him of his niece or something
I guess let's make our way to the door
Any closing I mean there's boy like you know tales of horror with Thummer
Tales of victory with Amy
Going all the way from not baking in two years to winning two ribbons at once
Incredible
Clearly yes
And inspiration from me
This seems like a microcosm of the friendship and of the support and the inspiration that's there
And that you both are glad the other isn't dead
So it's really nice to see
Despite taking the other person to places where they'll probably die and then we both end up surviving
Yeah
Cuba
Chernobyl
Parting thoughts on the fair though
Anything you're looking forward to next year or something that you haven't done fair wise that's on the list
I mean if you're just not at the fair what are you doing?
It's mostly just the threat to all the people listening go to the fair
If there's a fair in your county go to that fair
I was going to say any thoughts on the Orange County Fair
I love the Orange County Fair
The Orange County Fair has the most tribute bands
Like every weekend they have a different tribute band
So if you look even on their website it's like fake Abba, fake Pink Floyd, fake Fleetwood Mac
Like you could just really live a whole fake dream
They had fake Alice Cooper but then he disappeared
Like he was on this calendar and then they took him off
So I don't know what happened with fake Alice Cooper
I recently stayed at the Lawrence Welk Resort in Escondido, California
Where I was delighted to find
They have a little, it's like a little shopping center and a little theater
Where they have entirely tributes also
We got a fake Huey Lewis on our hand
I'm kind of amazed that there's enough tributes out there that you can be a full time Huey Lewis
Oh yeah there's like a fake no doubt
They're really serious about it
You would think in Orange County like a fake no doubt
They're chased out of town like they're not being authentic
But I don't know maybe they want it because no doubt it's not gone besides your schedule
I will say that the competition in sugar cookies in Orange County is a lot more intense
Like when I looked at their cabinet last year I'm not up to snuff there
Oh really?
You are, stop comparing yourself to other sugar cookies
Their floral work is like intense
But that said, I made a new batch of cookies this weekend
And I only had two left, I know there's three of you guys here being the burger guys
But you can like break them in half if you want
As much as I want
They're very small
We made Hoda Rao's cookies because we went to go see El Topo
El Topo cookies
But they're the same recipe of the Thumbra Cookies
They're chocolate
Yeah the chocolate cookies are bangers
The vanilla is very good too
She makes them for this book club, the smut book club we're in
She makes themed cookies to the book every month
I bought like a six inch dick shaped cooker cookie that I haven't had a chance to make yet for any smut club ones
Because we've had different themes
Jason shoved the cookie in his mouth already
They're delicious
They're genuinely good cookies on top of being beautiful
Wow, wow, geez wonderful
Amy, you can keep adding things, I don't know how you keep adding things
I'm done, I'm quitting
I'm a retired baker now
You just bought a dehydrator though so you could make the frosting
That is true, I bought a dehydrator to keep my icing puffy
Like a month ago
The icing is very aesthetically pleasing on this
It's got a nice poof
Take a bylar before he grabs yours
And I saved my Thumbra, I didn't eat it
I'm keeping it forever
I will say for people going the ride to ride, there's two rides that are just the best
Alien Abduction is one of the ones where you're just in the dark and spiraling around really fast
And it's like crazy and your feet lift off the ground
But the other one, Joker, is at the county fair and that one's amazing
It's like there's 12 people on kind of a long tall spoke
And you swing back and forth and then finally just start swinging all the way upside down and around and around and around
And you get completely head scrambled
Like you're taller than palm trees and upside down and it is probably the best ride there
Also beer and wine pavilion where you can taste the award winning beers and wines
And behind it is a nature walk where we learned about bees and they had a lot of other original characters teaching you about camping
And you could take home a tiny palm tree if you wanted
No, a tiny pine tree
They had little trees that you could take home and plant
Yeah, the nature walk area is really underrated, I just got into that in the last year
Oh jeez, wow, wow
You missed it, you haven't even seen the train area that's there
Oh, I don't know, the train museum
There's full corners of it
It's so cool
Do they still have kind of a weird dinosaur zone called Jurassic Planet?
I didn't see that
I remember that though
Because every year they kind of do a different theme sometimes at the back
Like one year is all light up paper insects
They have some year round Halloween stuff
Like a Halloween maze area
Which is fun
This year they added a roller rink
Oh yeah, which I saw
Which is included with admission
And skates, you don't have to rent skates separately
Yeah, my boyfriend did it
Because he loves to roller skate
We watched him skate around
Amy ate a four foot long stick of pork
Two foot long
Half is like, yeah
I've really mainlined that thing
More than half your height
I usually get the two pound pork chop
But I thought it would go a little different this year
Yeah, it was
Two pounds of a different meat
Same meat, but different formation
Fair enough, excuse me
Does eating a ton of pork get out some aggression against Thummer?
I think it is why I do it
I want him to know that he's not the boss of me
But Thummer gave you the gold this year
We can give Thummer a year
I feel dirty
To pander to that level and have it win
Makes me a little disgusted with myself
I'm not disgusted
Oh, it's me
You're kidding, you did me
That's so sweet
Here's the prize
No, I think
Accept your full congratulations
And
Not just for your victory
But for a great episode of the show
Thank you, Eva and Amy, you survived Podcast The Ride
Wow, wow
What a fun time
So happy to have you both
Let's exit through the gift shop
Amy?
Not much, I'm still doing Unspooled with Paul Scheer
We just are Mad Max
The original
1979 one, we just did that one this week
Which was honestly when I went back and watched it
And you see just the through line
Of all of the little visual pole vaulting
And tough old women
How he just has been building on that
I remembered Mad Max
People being like, the original one's boring
And it doesn't get cool till two, but they are actually completely wrong
I've like now turned around
I very much love Mad Max one, I think it's scarier
To watch the civilization
Slide into disrepair
That's cool
I don't have anything to plug, but I did discover this website
Yesterday morning
For this company called
Brave Books
Which is owned by Kirk Cameron
And it's children's books
Written by like
Important cultural figures
Like Kirk Cameron?
Well, this one I'm just plugging is called The Night The Snow Monster Attacks
Written by General Michael Flynn
What?
Oh man
Michael Flynn
You can get a signed copy of it for $50
$49.99
Michael Flynn, is he the most famous author they have?
No, I mean it's a lot
Kimberly
Guilfoyle posted a picture of herself holding
A children's book called The Princess and Her Pup
And I was like, this is the dumbest thing I've ever seen
And I looked into it
They're all written by like
Your morning check in with
Guilfoyle accounts
Dinesh D'Souza has one
Of course
Wow, the cookie's very good, I'm eating it
Oh, I'm so glad
It's marshmallow flavored icing
Oh, okay, I actually didn't even identify it
You might also
Once I learned a recipe I tripled the salt, that's my own little flavor
Oh, nice
Is another potential plug
Like, you know, if we're kind of
You know, if we're given the finger
To thummer a little bit
Would you be mad if people
Went to the fair this weekend
Punched through the cabinet and took your cookies
And ate them
No, in fact I hope they send me pictures of them flipping off my thummer
Do you want to eat a six week old cookie?
And as for us, for three bonus episodes
Every month, check out Podcast The Ride The Second Gate
Or get one more bonus episode on our VIP
Tier Club 3
You will find all of that at Patreon.com slash Podcast The Ride
I think now we're going to do a Memorial Day break
I said we're going to do one
We did this instead so people could
We could tell people to go find
Thummer and give the finger
To your thummers
So now we'll take a break, but I hope this gives everyone
The lead time to
Flip off thummers
Yeah, you're flipping off the character of thummer, not Amy's cookies
Not Amy's, it's what Amy wants us to do
Well, you can also go and take a detour
And just flip off the brownie winners
Because I had Eva's brownies on the way up and they should have placed
I was pretty mad, they didn't
They were malted milk flavor, they're incredible
They're very kind of you, but like I said
A lot of brownies this year
Shouldn't have done it
It's political, I'm sure
Someday I'll be the mean old lady
We should figure out how to be judges
Yeah, we will have to probably kill someone
That's the only way, yeah
It's a supreme court appointment basically
I need a lot of enemies
I need you to parry down
The list
I mean an easy way potentially is
To plant some poison brownies
Yeah, they eat them that night
They eat one of your
Things that night
We suddenly need two new judges
Something terrible has happened
We're ready, we'll do it
Do you think anybody has ever spiked their cookies
Out of revenge?
I mean, that's kind of fun
With like, what, ketamine?
What?
Probably ketamine
Probably
It would be so easy to put liquid LSD
In oral icing
It would even make it pay
You just lick the cookie, it's like a big stamp
I'm not saying if this ever happens we have anything to do with it
And I'm sure you can retroactively
Delete all this
And also, like, you know
There's hundreds of competitors in that cabinet
How are they to know that you are the one?
That's a great idea
How do they know it was somebody else's?
There's so many names out there
Yeah, you planted the idea on the podcast
And somebody else took and ran with it
A lot of brownies this year
There's a fungus that naturally occurs
In some grains that actually can cause
Solicitation, so it could just be naturally
It could be natural
That's great, you had a natural answer
Go for what happened
No, it was a fungus
We're covered, great
Dog
This has been a ForeverDog production
Executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit
ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts, Spotify
Or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest ForeverDog
News by following us on
Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
And liking our page on Facebook