You gotta hold it closer.
Happy birthday, Islands of Adventure, 25 years.
You brought a noisemaker.
Oh, one of those.
You did a good job hiding that in your hand.
Oh wait, you're not done.
I know.
I was practicing palming it.
I brought one for you.
Wow.
Like a magician.
Like you kept it slight of hand.
That's right.
Yeah.
Here, I brought ones for you guys.
Oh, great.
Whip it.
Yeah.
Holy.
Because you can only buy, you cannot buy a single noisemaker.
You have to buy a bag of like 20 or so.
You can't buy a single bag.
He did not want to give us these.
He wanted one for himself.
Oh, this is an accident.
The end.
This is an accidental gift.
Did you try to barter with them and say, come on, can you open up a bag?
It's like when you, like there's a six pack of something and like technically the store
could probably sell you just one can of something.
Mm-hmm.
No, I just got it on Amazon.
It makes sense.
Oh, okay.
You didn't email Amazon and say, hey, could you split this bag open and give one of these
to me?
Or eBay.
I bid four cents for one noisemaker.
All right.
Yeah, the shipping costs more than the items.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
To a ridiculous amount.
I was hoping you.
$10.99.
I was hoping you were haggling at a party city.
Oh.
That was my hope.
Yeah.
Like, look, the bag's partially open anyway.
Right.
There's a hole in the bag.
It's basically damaged.
You're going to have to just exit out.
You may as well just give it to me.
Right.
I mean, it's, I put the air into it.
I'm the one doing the labor.
Right.
I don't know what moment is this piece before my lips have touched it.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, mine's kind of a lower pitch.
What is that?
Yours was much more of a uncomfortable fart.
Yeah, weird.
That was weird.
Oh, you should get your money back with this one.
Yeah.
This one sounds weird.
I should've said, Mike, I thought you were going to blow on the noisemaker and I'd put
your butt up against the microphone.
And whistle.
Whistle on my asshole.
Got him.
Do we say our names?
Do we say what the...
My name is Mike Carlson.
Mike Carlson, Scott Gardner.
Yeah.
Our names don't matter.
Just in case.
On a week like this, who are we?
We are just ballast and trash in comparison
to the great park who we celebrate today, 25 years.
Yeah, we cannot hold, like, we're not in the same league
as, like, walk around John Hammond or walk around Merlin
or Woody Woodpecker and Explore Gear.
Yes, these are the names we celebrate today.
The names of the, like, atmosphere characters
in Lost Continent who absolutely no one knows
unless Jason looked them up in the last 24 hours.
Well, I rewatched the open, like, the souvenir video
that you could watch.
One more time this week than usual.
One more time.
I had forgotten.
It's only about, like, under 28 minutes long,
and I feel like it's one of those things,
but it's like souvenir VHS at a theme park, $40.
Right.
You know?
And you paid for it at the time, do you remember?
I did not.
I did not buy that or the soundtrack.
But did your parents complain to you about the price?
Probably.
Here, this is, okay, actually, while we have the noisemakers,
I don't wanna, like, keep making this a thing
in case they're annoying for the audience,
but can you just, like, what I wanna do
is, like, use one for bleeps.
So can you, like, describe your dad finding out the price
and he does it in a profane way
and I'm gonna bleep you with this.
So you're pretending you're your dad.
Yeah, yeah, you look at the price, $40 for this.
Yeah.
These am-f-ing rip-off artists.
But I bleep you.
So here, okay, here we go.
$40 for that?
I'm not paying for a god damn thing.
That's pretty good.
For one tape?
If these mother-f-ing think that $40 is a fair price
for 28 minutes of content,
they're out of their f-ing sucking minds.
I, you know, my mother was more the one
who worried about that sort of thing
and she hates profanity.
Oh, okay.
So it wouldn't have been.
She would have live done a noisemaker
in order to not be doing this work.
Yeah, yeah.
She hears the show and hears the profanity sometimes, yes?
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I am told that sometimes.
Okay, yeah.
This is the biggest reason why I don't encourage
my parents to listen more.
Right.
I'm certainly aware of that.
I know that that is, they're hard out at that,
which in fact, something, they recently gave some praise
to a feature film, which we all were praising.
We were praising it in text and have been for,
you know, we work in comedy,
so we admire other comedy out there.
So we've all been, everybody's been abuzz
about the movie Unfrosted,
Jerry Seinfeld's stirring tribute to the serial Cold Wars
and, I'm sorry, the Breakfast Treat Cold Wars,
but my parents, one of their bits of praise for this film
was, you know, and there were all those comedians in it
who were usually so nasty,
but here they were keeping it clean.
Nasty is a particularly good word.
Well, nasty, I don't know.
I get, maybe just due to, you know, association.
I hear nasty and I think female.
I don't know what that says about me.
Oh, right, right.
But it doesn't, I feel like that,
there's the implied adjective there
is it's directed at Amy Schumer.
Who else are they talking about, right?
So they've probably seen her on a roast
and gone, oh, no, why bring that foul language
into a roast like that?
But here, she's just like a 60s businesswoman
who's trying to get her kind of breakfast square
off the ground before the other ones can.
Well, I think Melissa McCarthy is.
That you're right, oh, her too.
Oh, because she does.
Her movies are full of farts and poops.
Nasty farting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh-huh, yes.
Is there like something, maybe,
where like Jim Gaffigan makes like a joke about,
I don't know, something very light,
but maybe, oh, he's kind of nasty.
And this could just be something different,
something we're not.
A light entendre, an entendre and a half.
He does, in his act.
Right, and this nasty man, Jim Gaffigan,
has been cleaned up by unfrosted.
I don't know, I'm just throwing it out there,
I don't know.
One of the cleanest stand-ups going.
Yeah, yeah, but we're also talking
about my parents' standard here.
Right, she could say, I like rock and roll,
like a specific type of rock and roll,
like this Black Sabbath, maybe.
Yeah, does Gaffigan have a Black Sabbath joke?
I don't know, I don't know, I haven't seen all of it.
He likes Black Sabbath.
Isn't that what he does?
He talks in kind of like a.
He does that, yeah.
What is he saying, why is he talking about.
It's a lot of funny voice delivery, yeah.
Right, right, okay, so all right, so anyway,
if you want to watch a clean film
that doesn't need noisemaker censoring,
watch the, we're out of.
Unfrosted, but that's not what we're here to talk about.
No, we're not, Jason, can I real quick,
because we're here to celebrate the 25th birthday
of Islands of Adventure, you're gonna love it.
Which I believe is yesterday, as people are hearing this,
May 28th, 1999, hence the episode.
So let me throw this out here on the episode,
and you tell me you could do this as much as you want,
or as little as you want, could we frame this
as if Islands of Adventure is your son,
and this is his 25th birthday.
Or daughter.
Or daughter. Or daughter.
Sure, that's true, you're right.
Or nasty daughter.
You're right.
Islands of Adventure is your nasty daughter.
I don't like that at all, I don't like that at all.
But Jason is allowed to choose.
Sure. So, you know,
as we look back on some things today,
I want you to really feel pride.
I am, yeah, I'm very proud.
They can finally rent a car without paying extra fees.
Oh yeah, yeah.
They're probably, they're not off the health insurance
necessarily yet, but next year they'll get kicked off.
Their parents' health insurance.
Their parent being Universal Studios,
the original. Right.
It was not a, I don't wanna say luxury,
not an option, I feel like, when we were,
like I feel like when I was finishing college,
like the, or whatever sent my parents a letter,
like you have one month more after he gets out of school.
And then you have to buy a plan.
Like you were. I think I may have made it.
Kicked out after school.
This might have been an ethno problem.
Yeah.
Perhaps, yeah.
So, yeah, so today, so as we go through.
As we celebrate, Islands of Adventure's still having
health insurance and being a great son.
I want you to think of this, yeah, as your son.
And then sometimes people will find something
that you didn't like as much and you'll say,
well, that was a real trying time in growing up.
Bad phase. Sure.
Bad phase you were going through there, son.
Wow, that's interesting.
So, yeah, let's think of this as if you had a child
25 years ago.
Let's not think about how old you were
or the logistics of it.
Oh, yeah.
Some sort of an immaculate birth.
Could have done it.
Babies making babies.
Certainly could have done it.
Yeah.
Jason had relations with, I guess,
Universal Studios, Orlando.
Yeah, he, he, he fucked the gate.
The globe, yeah.
The globe's a good way to do it, yeah, yeah.
What's the, where does life come from?
Which landmark?
And a beautiful baby was born 25 years ago.
Yeah, yeah.
And now, look, he's all grown up.
Wow, boy, crazy.
Does that sort of, is that relatively in league
with how you're feeling on this special occasion?
Sure, yeah.
Well, I was reminded rewatching that souvenir video
that it is the theme park of the 21st century,
which I think they say about five times
in a 27-minute video.
Can you also, this video,
because I've watched some of these things.
Yeah.
Is this a video that's like,
is it the Disney-style thing
that's like a family going around
and you see what they do?
Is it the thing where the characters talk to you?
Is it like, where there's a really,
I know there's one where there's an extreme close-up,
which you should not do on someone with a prosthetic beard.
And there's, all right, let's go as tight as possible.
We want to really see that netting in the beard.
And there's a guy who's like,
hello, I am Merlin.
And is it that one?
Yeah, Merlin has a long prosthetic beard.
Yeah.
Walk around John Hammond.
You can kind of tell it's glued on.
Yes, yeah, that's a very fakie beard.
Yeah, so if you want to see a video
of the closest close-ups on the worst beards
you've ever seen,
this is how they needed to herald their arrival.
It's the highest-checked theme park,
of the 21st century.
Beards could use some work,
but that's some of the charm, don't you think?
Yeah, so that, we could say,
that was maybe a rough start, son.
Trying to get old before his time.
Exactly.
Putting on a fake beard
instead of growing a real one.
Exactly.
But that's the one you're talking about, Jason.
Yeah, yeah.
And kind of the denizens of each land
sort of welcome you to Shilin.
Yeah, you do get,
I feel like you don't get much,
I guess you get Popeye in Toon Lagoon,
kind of get a Hodgepodge in Soos Landing.
That's tougher.
It's cartoon characters,
who's going to be your host,
as opposed to the original,
the port of entry guy on the-
The storyteller on the big adult tricycle.
Of course.
I don't know what you call a full-size three-wheeled bike,
but he's just kind of riding around everyone.
Mantrake, it's a mantrake.
And he's very boisterous.
What are you most looking forward to?
And then he gets them at the end of the video.
What was your favorite adventure?
What did you most enjoy today?
Like, oh, I did the whole,
oh, very good.
I did Spider-Man.
It is like most original theme park IP.
There's a lot of clamoring for more original theme park IP
and not things from movies.
Characters you can only meet here,
or in these specific places.
And it's funny how usually what that ends up being
is somebody going, hello, I'm the X-Maker,
or the X-Finder, or the X-Doer.
It's always what they always, they do-
There's a default.
If Imagineers or Universal Ears or whatever you call them,
like ARK just cut loose.
What they always end up at is a boisterous guy with a beard.
They always end up with Santa Claus.
Yeah, yeah.
It's always just Santa Claus.
And we like it.
Yeah, it often works.
I love all of these guys.
I don't want to call them fake Santas.
They're not fake Santas, but they're like Santa siblings
or Santa, I don't know, adjacent relatives.
I don't know.
I'm the wish grower.
You take your wish and whisper it into this pot,
and then you go about your day,
and I'll sprinkle water and positive wishes onto your wish.
And by the time you come out for the day,
you can look at a fully grown wish
and purchase it for $60.
My name is Mr. Enchantment, of course.
I'm gonna write this way to a whole world of enchantment.
You see in the video,
a lot of the citizens of Port of Entry,
which have changed a lot over the years.
There were pirates.
There's been a mayor on and off.
There was a quick shot in the video
of a poem reader with a real brook.
She's got a real Brooklyn axe.
Oh, I'm looking at your lines.
You're gonna get wet today.
It was very easy.
It's like, yeah, you're at Island's Adventure.
The water wires are really intense.
I like this voice coming out of you,
because you're landing in a real Edith Bunker.
Rooster, oh, I was going more for Archie.
Rooster, we gotta get this Annie girl.
She's gonna be rich.
We gotta get Daddy Warbucks' money.
That's one of the people after,
not the Carol Burnett orphanage owner.
Is that what you're doing, or who is the?
Which Little Orphan Annie character are you doing?
I was doing Rooster's girlfriend.
Oh, okay.
I'm not familiar with the musical or the movie.
Mm-hmm.
So that's why.
She's like a mall.
She's like a real, like, gun mall.
A gun mall.
Yeah, she's a real gun mall.
She's a real gun mall.
You know what a gun mall is.
People are having trouble understanding
what Rooster's girlfriend is in Annie.
All right, a gun mall.
She's a real gun mall.
Jason talked about gun malls on the show a few times.
No, I know, I remember the gun mall chunk, yes.
Good, thank God.
All right, anyway, back to my lovely child.
Yeah.
So we were talking about what to do for the episode,
and I was pitching the most niche,
most niche, like, smallest rides imaginable,
some of which have, like, haunted me.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
I will set, like, pterodon flyers back in Jurassic Park.
This is a children's ride.
This is for children.
It flies above Camp Jurassic.
It flies above the land.
Yes.
But it has, it doesn't just have a minimum height requirement,
it also has a maximum height requirement.
Oh, so you gotta be, really,
like, certain, like, Knott's Berry Farm rides
for kids are this way.
Yeah.
But those are not, those are rides that go
around and around in one area.
This is, like, this takes you on a little journey.
This gets you way away from mom and dad.
And so I think if you're supervising a child,
if you're riding with a child, you can ride.
But the maximum height is 56 inches,
so just under five feet, so.
Wait, so you're allowed to be, you can be a parent,
but does that apply to you?
Do you have to be under five feet as a parent?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Because the other trick for this ride,
which I narrowly missed out on
when we were down there last fall,
is that during Orlando and former events,
it's opened up, anyone can ride it.
Right.
Though during those rides and events.
This is typically not, this is typically not running.
That's, yeah.
Well, no, it's running, it's just.
It's running, it's just running for parent-child.
Oh, okay, yeah.
It's used exactly by the rules, too,
but you have to be, to be an adult to go on it,
you generally have to have a child with you.
Yeah, maximum height, 56 inches,
or accompanied by a rider meeting height requirements, so.
This is one of the most confusing things.
It is. In my mind.
Because I've never quite understood how you get on this.
I think you just have a kid,
but are you saying I cannot go on this?
Or I could with my child?
Well, I'm saying you could
if you were accompanying a child.
Even though I'm over five foot.
Because the minimum height is 36 inches,
maximum height is 56 inches, so.
But you have to be a child as well.
So you have to, you could be a five foot child,
and a parent could go on with,
but the parent doesn't have to.
No, you can't be a five foot child.
If you're a child over 56 inches,
then you don't get the ride.
You're shit out of luck,
unless you're accompanying a smaller child.
If you're 4'11", and an adult, can you go on alone?
It appears so.
Yeah, it is purely height.
It is purely height,
and things typically fall along adult-child lines,
given the heights, but not always.
But I can go on with a child.
Yes.
What?
So you're saying, why not,
why wouldn't I, you be able to do it normally?
Right, it's just a cut down on the adults, then,
to go on it?
Well, yeah, here's the thing,
because this runs like,
it dispatches a lot of ride vehicles.
The ride vehicles only hold two people at a time.
So it's maybe a weight thing, all told?
So it's a cut down on adults.
I tried to ride it in June 1999.
I was so excited to be soaring above Jurassic Park.
However, the wait time was two hours.
It was longer than Spider-Man.
It was longer than Hulk.
Touring Plans calls it,
it says it can only do 170 people per hour,
and they also call it
Islands of Adventure's biggest blunder.
Wow.
Bad phase, son.
Yeah, bad.
Bad phase.
Yelk, they can't, you know, you've had some victories,
you've had some Spider-Mans,
but you've also had some Pteranodon flyers.
And it's still around too, so it's a bad habit
that Jason's son just can't kick.
You gotta quit Pteranodon flyers at that point.
You gotta quit Pteranodon flyers, Jason's son.
The height requirements are confusing,
but that's okay, you're still getting,
you know, by the time you're 30,
maybe you'll figure it out.
I always share it in.
Well, here's another seemingly blunder.
A big portion of Toon Lagoon
is occupied by a massive amphitheater.
Okay.
And this is a shot I wanna call for the future.
You're not doing it here?
No, I'm not doing it here.
Too much to do.
When I explain it,
you will understand why I'm not doing here.
Pandemonium Circus was a show that opened with a park.
And it is all your favorite.
Jason's right about this.
Yeah, it's all your favorite.
Jay Ward, Fleischer Studios,
and King Features Syndicate characters
doing circus acts.
Okay.
Doing like.
Scott, try not to be bowled over in your chair.
Try not to fly over in your chair.
You see me teetering.
I'm trying to get back to the microphone.
Guys, could somebody pull me back, please?
I've got a show to do.
Like, someone does tightrope walking.
Like, does Beetle Bailey do tightrope walking?
I think it's Beetle Bailey does tightrope walking.
Are you really? Is that true?
I saw a video and I wasn't sure if they were joking.
But in the last couple years,
a full video of this show was uploaded.
It hadn't been online for a long time.
Pandemonium Circus.
So like, if Dagwood is throwing knives
at Betty Boop, you know.
It's also in here.
Do we know that these, have you just never like,
I'm sure you've watched the video.
I would hope.
But, or maybe not, I don't know.
Are you just, you have not done the dot.
You aren't sure what's going on in that circus.
I'm not sure.
I saw it in 1999.
We were kind of befuddled by it.
Cause it's half like face characters
and half fur characters.
Beetle Bailey is in the show.
I'm looking at a picture of the cast.
Bluto's in it.
Rocky from Rocky and Bullwinkle.
Popeye.
Woody Woodpecker is in it.
Boris and Natasha.
Sniley Whiplash.
A lot of J Ward.
But yeah, Beetle is there
and he's wearing like a fun little suit or something.
So the whole gang, everybody's there.
Yeah.
Broom Hilda.
Bimbo.
When you know Bimbo, that's,
I've definitely heard of that before seeing it right now.
Bimbo is from the Betty Boop universe.
I have heard of Bimbo.
Maybe.
The little white dog.
I hope so.
Cause otherwise, what are we doing
with this Bimbo character?
Yeah.
So yeah, no, Jason's 100% correct.
Just not enough time to get to that.
Okay.
Can we, can I go back real quick?
You said that you were haunted by pterodon flyers.
Cause I wanna ride it.
Okay, that's what you meant by that.
And it's been 25 years.
So.
And I haven't figured it out.
Okay, so that's good.
I wanted to go back to that
cause I didn't know what you meant by that.
You just meant you wanna ride it.
It's like the one thing I haven't ridden.
How does it?
And it's your one reason to have a child.
Oh yeah, right.
Oh.
Like there's an idea.
A lot of McCann territory,
but pro, I could go down there.
Pterodon flyers.
There's gotta be a way,
I guess you could go on with one of our children.
I suppose we could do that.
If we're all there together with children.
We're all there with children.
Uncle Jason could go on with one of our children.
I wanna go with dad.
No, no, no.
This is out of your hands.
This is, we are dealing with something
that has been around longer than you.
This man.
This has nothing to do with you, son.
This man has been haunted.
Haunted.
We need to end the haunting here.
This is about setting a spirit free.
You know, or if our kids aren't there,
if one of the nice listeners brings their child,
they could force their child to go on
with their favorite podcast host
who has been haunted by this.
Yeah.
If you're looking for a way to give back to the show.
Right.
Lend us your children.
Exactly.
So yeah, if you brought your children,
if we're down there all at the same time,
maybe there's a whole line of a bunch of different children
that wanna ride with Jason and make his dreams come true.
Yeah, cause I wanna re-ride.
I wanna get back in line.
Okay, we need more than one kid.
All right, so don't come to us with your single kid.
That's worthless to us.
Right.
Two kids minimum.
And none of these kids,
none of these growth spurt kids over five feet.
Yeah, no.
They have to be under five.
And then we can finally,
this is your unfinished business.
Finally, Jason can rest.
Yeah.
And go on what Touring Plans calls
the worst ride at Island of Adventure.
I don't know, is that possible?
Is that junky little coaster over at, like,
Oh, look at this.
Look at this shade he's throwing.
I guess there's a unicorn animatronic now.
Yeah, I don't, okay.
Is it the same coaster as in Harry Potter's year?
Yeah, yeah, it's the same.
Because that's all right.
You know what?
On a day where everything else
is really crowded at Universal Hollywood,
I'll do that and I'll have a nice time.
It's over so quick and it's not worth the big wait.
But yeah, you get an animatronic at the beginning.
But also the one here has the benefit
of it's up on top of the hill.
So you're getting nice views,
which will be kind of irrelevant
when the Fast and Furious coaster opens,
because that'll be a real coaster with better views.
Real views, yeah.
But so I could see,
that Islands of Adventure one is pretty inessential
because you don't have the view component.
That was back in the, like, pre-dates,
I believe pre-dates Hogsmeade.
Oh yes, it was there before.
Yeah, it was called something else.
I don't remember.
It was back in Merlinwood.
That section of Lost Continent.
The souvenir video also has great views
of the massive Enchanted Oak Tavern,
which has the big, ugly tree,
the big, scary tree on top of it.
This was a Lost Continent restaurant
that was demolished for Harry Potter?
Yes.
Okay, uh-huh.
Was it good?
Do you miss it?
Does that haunt you?
I think we only ever walked through it.
Okay.
Can't make a judgment.
There's no way you think Pterodon Flyers is a word.
There's just no way.
You would give it, your guess would be
that that effect goes there.
I can't judge, I haven't been on it.
Oh yeah, oh that's why it's haunting you
so that you can't actually rule.
You know what's funny is I feel like I went on it.
I feel like I, was I small enough?
Oh, maybe.
Because I went in the first year of this park.
Yeah, me too.
But I was in high school.
Would I have been too?
I feel like you would have been too tall for that.
I really, I feel, I kind of have the memory
of going on it though.
Am I crazy?
Am I completing things?
Yeah, I was about to start high school
but then I assure you, I was not too tall for it.
That five, five one, getting to that last inch or two
of five one took a while.
I hear you, yeah.
I'm looking at a, this is from looper.com,
ranking rides best to worst.
Are these fighting words for you
or are you gonna defend your son?
They put, at worst ride and out of adventure
Storm Force Accel-a-tron.
Is it Accel-a-tron or Accelerator?
Accelerator?
Well then this article can't be trusted.
Wait, no, no, no, I'm looking at the sign of the ride.
It's called Accel-a-tron.
It is called Accel-a-tron.
Yes.
Well that's how I knew.
Jason said the other way and then immediately flipped.
Well, if it's on the sign,
yeah, I don't know.
I haven't done that in a long time.
What is it?
Is it like, it's teacups?
It's teacups.
And you hear Storm and Magneto just screaming at each other.
I tried to do it.
I told this story in Orlando.
I was about to go on it and the line was kind of long
and then there was a like a teen working there.
He's like, and we have defeated Magneto.
And I was like, I think I got the best actual part
of this ride so far.
So like I'm good, I don't need to do it.
Did I maybe, I'm looking at Pterodon Flyers.
I feel like I did it.
Maybe.
Maybe it was my sister.
Maybe she was small enough to do it
and I was the one accompanying and that's why.
Oh, maybe.
That might be it.
I think so.
We will get, look, we know people, okay?
We will get you on this goddamn ride.
I, oh, God.
Oh yeah, thank you.
Ride.
We can make this happen.
I don't know how, but we will make it happen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Next time we're down there.
I wanna go to one of those Informer events.
Okay, that seems like-
Unlimited food.
Just unlimited.
Hang on, one of those Informer events.
You just dove in with that.
I don't know about the Informer event.
He said there's a, yeah, there's a meetup
where they rent the park out.
Okay.
Orlando Informer rents the park out
and you get-
That is a newspaper.
I don't know, I'm so in the dark.
I gotta, you gotta help me out.
Sorry, sorry.
It's like a-
These are big, they're very popular.
You pay like-
It doesn't mean, I still need content.
You still, I'm sorry, I'm making you provide context
of any kind. It's a theme park.
Specific thing?
Am I, or am I wrong?
Or is it a regular newspaper?
I think it is like Orlando tourism in general,
but it's a lot of theme park coverage.
Right, right.
So they rent out Universal
and you can get in like in the late afternoon
and after EPM or so,
it's only people who paid for that ticket.
The riff-raff is gone.
Wow.
And the people who paid-
The riff-raff is gone.
And then there's some sort of unlimited food
that Jason has brought into this.
All you can eat like at the counter services,
they set up a phase and stuff.
You can cross parks backstage.
Okay.
And it's anything goes. I like that.
Adults can do taradon flyers.
And adults, most importantly, adults can do-
You can ride a shirtless too.
Taradon flyers.
Whoa.
Because it's adults only.
You can go fucking nuts at Islands,
excuse me, you can go fucking nuts at Islands of Adventure.
Yes.
God, I'm just imagining the kinds of things
you can do at these informer events now.
Can you like f**k and f**k?
Because that's illegal in Florida.
When you're a Toon Lagoon,
you can do all the f**k-ing and f**k-ing you want,
specifically at Toon Lagoon.
Love the boys, but the noisemaker joke got old.
They committed to the bit a bit too hard.
Jason's warming up for some part of it.
That was a very quiet one.
I was trying to do a sad one.
I don't think you have that control.
Yeah, there's not.
That was kind of a pitch bend, can you?
No, I see what, I fell right into his trap.
Yeah.
I mean, that was sad.
That was absolutely sad.
That was pretty dramatic.
It wasn't slide whistle sad, it was a new type of sad.
Look, I was just saying, Jason,
I'm sure there's somebody at Universal
who could figure this out for you,
but I think Jason wants to pay the money
because he wants to get all you can eat mozzarella sticks
at the Fantastic Four Cafe.
Oh, that sounds nice.
Yeah, I want my tummy really rumbly
getting on the pterodon flyers.
Yeah, yeah, well you get them.
You want to be up there, finally soaring,
achieving your long-eld, your 25-year-long dream,
and then to puke up mozzarella sticks on the people below.
I ate too much green eggs and ham
at Circus McGurkis Cafe Stupendous.
If you pay for the Orlando Informer ticket, though,
you can take a Target bag,
fill it with mozzarella sticks from the Fantastic Four Cafe,
and then eat it while you're on pterodon flyers.
Or take them back to your hotel if it has a kitchenette.
Or not, eat them cold.
Sure, yeah. Sure.
But that's what you get for those,
that ticket price. That's a recipe
for one of those great, like Jason's saying,
something made me sick, I don't know what it was,
and then we're doing the autopsy of it,
and like, wait, you were having mozzarella sticks
that were six days old? No, it wasn't that.
No, those holes. It was five days old.
It was the wind, the wind did it to me.
The wind threw off my microbiome.
Eat some of that red light treatment,
just like Steve Harvey gets.
That'll get rid of, that'll fix your microbiomes.
We will get you on pterodon flyers in the next two years.
I pledge this to you. Let's do it.
When I pledge it, I mean somebody else
is going to figure it out, but I pledge it to you
that you will be on pterodon flyers.
Who out there listening has the override
to this awful height restriction?
Does somebody work with this restriction
that tears our society apart?
I bet there's a 13-year-old like me listening to this show.
I bet there's a little...
You mean a literal one from a multiverse
or literally a person like you?
No, not a multiverse, like someone molded in my image,
like a little 13-year-old theme park weirdo.
That has been listening to us?
Yes. That we molded?
Yes. That's your actual son?
And if someone...
No, just hypothetically, I think.
But if so, I hope you're using your own money for this
and not stealing mom and dad's credit card.
We appreciate the business here on this Patreon episode,
but let's make sure that's on the up and up.
But I'm sure it is because if they're in molded
in Jason's image, I'm sure they're a very good boy.
They have a lemonade stand or a paper route.
They're making their money the old-fashioned way.
It's funny how that one, most of the money comes in
digitally, but then we just get sent an envelope of nickels.
And it's sent to Podcast The Ride,
but the P is backwards.
And then we send out a cassette tape to them.
Hey, hey, kid, kid, listen to me.
I know you're hearing this.
Okay, now's the time.
You gotta be a little rebellious.
Oh my God. Just take, just take the credit card.
Take one they don't use that much.
Oh my God. Just take the credit card.
Take the Sears card.
They're not around anymore. The Sears card.
The Sears card.
The Sears ain't gonna send a bill.
Take the card from the store that doesn't exist.
Well, it exists in Burbank.
Yes, I know. We've been through this.
We'll go through this clearly an infinite more episode.
Well, we'll have to go through the store
before we do that.
What else? Other island stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
If we're going, if we're going,
so we're going through like, what are the,
it's the, it's the, the obscure,
the obscurities that don't get the.
They don't get the proper.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some of which won't get full episodes,
although it sounds like a lot of them still will.
I mean, it could be.
I initially, like my instinct was like,
well, if it's just gonna be happy birthday
or islands of adventure is a theme,
I'm gonna make it an Island Skipper Tour backdoor episode.
I'm gonna make it the backdoor violent.
Okay, all right.
For Island Skipper Tour, which was of course.
And if you're gonna do that,
I'm gonna make you explain what Island Skipper Tour is.
Island Skipper Tour at the very beginning
of Islands of Adventure has only lasted about two years
and then for a third year, I think it came back seasonally.
These were the sole attraction at Port of Entry.
And technically the first ride you would hit
after you got to the end of Port of Entry.
These were kooky looking boats
that would take you from Port of Entry to Jurassic Park
or from Jurassic Park back to Port of Entry.
I bet you're gonna flip the script on that one.
Or also the same thing from before.
Well, there were plans for a third dock at Toon Lagoon.
It was never built.
Third dock?
That's right.
It was never built because the park, why bother?
And also these were very expensive
to upkeep and buy gasoline for.
So you could, instead of walking around
in like a circle basically,
you could just go right to a boat
and take a boat across the waterway
in Islands of Adventure, which is named what?
The Inland Sea.
The Inland Sea?
Yeah.
It is, I never heard that.
The Inland Sea.
Yeah.
Catchy.
I was gonna say, it's just like kind of a utilitarian
type of name for it.
Yeah.
I was just calling it.
The Dream Finder will take you to the,
no, not the Dream Finder.
The Enchantment Finder will take you to the Inland Sea.
It's the Inland Sea over there, sea inside.
The Inland Sea, just kind of gave it.
That's actually the name it was when we got here.
That was the natural swamp name.
Right, there was a swamp.
Well, when the big comet hit Marvel,
the big comet created all the islands,
the big impact, and you could see the impact area
at Marvel's superior island,
and then it created all these islands sprung up.
Is that the mythology?
This is canon, right?
This is canon.
That's what, wait, that's the story
of Islands of Adventure, a comet hit
and created a bunch of magical islands?
An asteroid, comet, some sort of large impact.
Did you know this, Mike?
No.
I've never heard this backstory.
Do you know there's these big crystal structures
at Marvel's superior island with all these big story line
artwork painted on it?
I'm sorry, there are barely any Google results
for Inland Sea.
There's enough to show that it's accurate,
but you are talking about something
that is such a thin slice that it's barely documented.
This shows how deep you go.
I don't even, I don't even call it,
I always just call it the lagoon,
which is standard, I think, theme parlance.
Where did you learn about the comet
that created Islands of Adventure?
I think this is like early on,
there was a lot more myth-making and stuff.
I mean, so the body of water, ostensibly,
is the impact of the comet?
Well, I guess, well, you can see the impact on the ground.
You can see like the effects at Marvel's superior island.
But then isn't that the impact point,
not the Inland Sea? That's the impact point,
and then it all just sprung up.
But did the blast create the Inland Sea?
I think so, I would guess so.
At least certainly a part of it,
if it all of a sudden created these islands.
But it was a magical comet of some kind, too,
because it grew dinosaurs.
By the way, I'm seeing a website saying meteor,
but again, it's, you know, we're picking it,
you know, we're, this is Christmas grass.
It was a magic, big piece of rock.
Okay, but yeah, I'm seeing this affirmed somewhere.
The crash site, okay, hit in Marvel's superhero island,
and the, well, they keep switching,
they call it an asteroid, too.
The asteroid is said to still be under there,
and it has magnetic powers,
and both good and evil are attracted to that site.
So that is why good and evil are always
jockeying for power, especially in-
Well, that's why you get a Spider-Man ride
and a Doctor Doom ride, you know?
So all of that is powered by the underground media.
It created, it was a blast, it created six fun islands,
and then stayed underground,
where its powers make a fear-fall machine possible.
Right.
And they flared up at some point,
and it attracted King Kong and Harry Potter, too.
Don't worry about it.
That's its own, I don't know.
Then magic happened, also.
Right, wow, so okay.
So that is, I know that there's a lot of, like,
mythology around just, like,
the new epic universe in Celestial Park.
I've seen, like, little pieces of storytelling
that they've already, like, hinted at or just said.
Yeah.
So it feels like they were already on this here,
because I don't, I'm trying to think,
is there anything in, I guess, Disney, Orlando,
is there anything that has any of the parks
that have, like, an origin like this,
other than the water parks?
It's like, Blizzard Beach has kind of an origin
of why there's a blizzard happening on this beach
and Typhoon Lagoon, but I don't know,
like, Animal Kingdom doesn't have, like,
a magical- How did this happen?
Right, a wizard blessed a zoo and something happened.
Well, it just comes along with being
the theme park of the 21st century.
Yeah, it has a- I guess you're right.
Well, Disney MGM Studios had the backstory
of the world's greatest man wanted to chase
a villainous other studio out of his state,
out of a state where they had planted a flag already,
and he brought all of the best talent together,
Bette Midler and Rick Moranis
and creepy, upright walking muppets,
and he, you know, he forged a place in fire
to show an evil studio what for.
Well, that's the most inspiring story.
Yeah, I'm wiping tears as I said.
Right, so did you know that story, Jason,
when you were a kid?
Did you know the meteor story?
I think so, well, you know, the first time I went,
there was like a souvenir pack at Marvel Super Hero Island,
and I think it had a lapel pin
and a poster, I believe, and a comic book.
Oh, was there a narrative about this?
There is a comic book with three stories in it
that explained the backstory of all three
rocks at Marvel Super Hero Island,
and they had Marvel talent, like Chris Bockelo
drew the Spider-Man, Sal Bechema drew the Hulk,
Mike Waringo drew the Doctor Doom,
so these are like A-listers they put on this.
So this is another calling of show,
this is another episode of this comic,
we gotta get our hands on this comic.
It's somewhere in Pennsylvania,
it's somewhere back at my mom's house.
Oh, you literally have it.
Yeah, I have it, and I'm sure I find it on eBay.
Is it in a glass case?
I hope it's not just rotting away.
What if it's under a leaky pipe or something?
It's perfectly protected.
What's going on in the house?
It's got a bag and board, and it's in a short box, you know.
Okay, all right.
Well, we're gonna get your copy of it and do an episode.
Just read it, and not even with funny voices,
with realistic voices.
No jokes.
Yeah, that will be the first joke-free episode.
Some things are sacred.
On purpose.
If there's been a clunker here and there in our catalog,
I can't say, I'm just saying that we tried on those.
I'm not even saying specifically which one.
This will be the first joke attempt-less episode.
Right, exactly.
So Island Skipper Tours, getting back to it.
These were, this was so exciting to me.
I never rode the Animal Kingdom boats
that would take you around, you know.
This is a common theme park thing, I guess,
is like having boats briefly
and then stopping, bothering with that.
Right.
Yes, because boats take a lot of upkeep
and a lot of fuel.
And you know, I should never have bought mine.
Yeah, you're haunted by that thing.
Sitting in your driveway.
Rusting away, yeah.
I can't even put my kid on it to run around.
Spiders will get him.
Do you wanna know the names of the boats?
Of course.
Do we, Jason, please, who do you think we are?
They're a little confusing, so Tropical Trader,
that one just looked like a sailboat.
Sure.
Sure, basic boat.
That one's fun.
Great, basic gas boat.
Samplane.
This is like repurposed, like, junker.
It looks like it got plane parts on it.
Samplane.
Well, I do not, vehicles deserve to have names.
Yes, one does.
It looks a little like something Jimmy Buffett
would have driven.
It's got a little bit of atmosphere, dancer vibe.
Right.
And then the last one was called Boatney,
and it's like a funky school bus.
It's like a funky painted school bus on skiffs.
Like the Muppets rode in.
Yeah.
Or the Partridge Family.
Or Electric Mayhem.
Mm-hmm.
Huh, Boatney.
Well, they all rode in it at some point, Mike.
No, but it was Electric Mayhem's bus.
But do they not, all the Muppets end up on the bus?
I knew what you meant.
I guess I didn't have to add that I knew specifically
whose bus it was owned by.
I mean, you're correct.
All right, if I looked at the registration,
it would say Electric Mayhem.
I'm not arguing on that.
Right.
Okay, so you get, these were not just like
the Epcot Friendship Boats, where they're just regular,
they all had their own theme and personality.
Yeah.
And you don't know which one's gonna show up,
so you get kind of a different little experience.
And the videos, the best video about this channel,
Storybook Amusements put it up.
There's some VHS footage of someone on the ride.
There's another one or two videos.
All of them seem to mention that the boats
were air conditioned, which is a plus, you know.
No wonder you've dreamed about these boats.
I mean, that is nice.
It's very muggy.
I don't disagree with that.
One of the strangest things I read about the boats,
on the first boat of the day,
face character John Hammond and face character Ian Malcolm.
Really?
They had a walk around Ian Malcolm?
They had walk around Ian Malcolm.
Supposedly, they would ride the first boat of the day
over to Jurassic Park.
Wow. Wow.
The two good pals who got along so famously.
Arm in arm.
Let's go see what you've created, Mr. Hammond.
I love it.
You know what?
I'm sorry I was so testy at that one brunch.
After this spectacular tour,
I love what you've done here and I'll never leave.
I'll take a boat with you every day.
Does it reset every morning though?
They haven't even gone through the events
of Jurassic Park yet.
So every morning, John Hammond and Ian Malcolm
are sort of born anew and their relationship starts over.
You know, it's kind of like half of that land
is everything is fine and then the River Cruise is hell.
Isn't though, does not the video in River Cruise
slash Jurassic Park the Ride,
does it not refer to like we had some unpleasant trees
because the park's open too.
So I think actually timeline wise, it is.
All this stuff happens, the Jeep got pushed
and the kids were in the tree and all that happened.
Then they got their act together and they open.
I guess you're right.
You're in a time that's post-Jurassic Park, pre-Lost World.
And so Malcolm being there is kind of wrong
but he did go back for Lost World.
It's like they added another thing of him.
Maybe he's there to be mad and try to stop it.
Right. I don't know.
Maybe. Or there was a brief period of time
where he flipped and then by Lost World,
he was anti-park again.
Right. Interesting.
Yeah. I don't know.
The big question is, did he lie on the front of the boat
with his shirt open and let all the ladies ogle him?
Please, of course.
I mean, that wasn't the meme thing yet though
at the time when it opened.
No, I think it took a generation growing up
and all admitting to each other that,
I don't think anybody cared about that,
unless, although I don't know,
there probably were a lot of people out there
secretly stopping that VHS right at that part,
watching it through shaky lines.
I think it unlocked a lot of people's sexuality, certainly.
But no one acknowledged it until, I feel like, a decade ago.
I didn't see it online a lot.
But it was a collective awakening.
Yeah.
The power of the internet.
They were all talking about the water drops on Laura.
They're insane.
He's the most sensual man of all time, in general.
That is right.
That is what he does, his hands and little,
that is like the-
That's what he does in real life.
That's why that scene was so effective.
If you've ever been around it.
That's why it was his ultimate character
that broke it all open.
Or they just like the comedy, like,
that's him yelling, must go faster,
must go fast when they're being chased.
Well, there's a lot to love about it in the movie.
There's a lot to love about Dr. Ian Malcolm.
There's a lot of funny,
there's a lot of sensuality.
We're here to talk about the sensual side of Jurassic Park.
Wouldn't you say Jeff Goldman's very sensual?
That's the word that comes to mind.
I would say so.
Yeah, certainly, yeah.
And then you got Alan over there, giving him side eye.
What's this happening with my wife?
Were they married?
No, they weren't.
No.
They were like, just figuring it out.
I think they were figuring it out.
And he doesn't want kids, so that's a conflict.
Right.
Ian Malcolm and Julia Moore were estranged.
Yes.
They had an adopted gymnast daughter.
Right.
Who like kicks a velociraptor in the head
with her cool, cool gymnast maid.
Best decision they ever made,
signing that girl up for gymnastics class.
Right, save their lives.
Little did they know how that would come into play
on a certain dinosaur island years later.
Seeing that in theaters, I was like,
why do they keep talking about her being a gymnast?
And then she like kicks a velociraptor in the head.
And I was like, hell yes.
This is awesome.
I remember thinking it was a little goofy at the time.
And now I wish most movies had something as fun as that.
I agree, yeah.
I felt that way at the time.
I have a quick clip here of.
The Skipper Tour.
The, well, it's a souvenir video,
and you're seeing a familiar face
on the Jurassic Park boat dock.
Okay.
That's in Jurassic Park land.
Now we can.
Hey, there's Mr. Hammond, the man who created it all.
Welcome to Jurassic Park.
So John, in that instance,
you did get a good view of the Jurassic Park boat dock.
John Hammond's already at Jurassic Park,
and he's welcoming you.
And this is that John Hammond
that looks exactly like you slash your dad.
Yes.
This has come up before, hasn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
David, my dad looks more like David Attenborough,
but this John Hammond does look more like me.
You mean Richard Attenborough.
Richard Attenborough, excuse me.
David's.
Animal guy.
Oh, your dad, okay.
Or nature documentary.
So you're saying your dad looks like the real deal
in the movie, and this looks like you
if you put a beard on it. And you look like Theme Park.
If you put a beard on it. John Hammond.
Yeah.
It really is.
I look like spirit gum John Hammond.
Right.
I mean, is that something that adds to your fondness
for this place, or at least this video,
that there's something about you,
you're looking at that, like what is it I like
about this guy?
Something about this guy.
Again, it all comes back to family, I think.
See, if I could have just, if I could borrow
walk around John Hammond, he could accompany me
on Pterodon flyers.
Oh, God.
Can we, okay, we're helping the auntie
for the Orlando Informer event.
We have to have somebody dressed as John Hammond
accompany Jason on Pterodon flyers.
Oh, Universal Bounding, John Hammond.
Yeah, yeah.
Why isn't Universal Bounding at the end?
That's a good idea.
Here's more John Hammond.
Oh, please.
Very strange clip.
The knowledge we've gained in Jurassic Park
will transform every aspect of human life.
Nothing will ever be the same again.
So come back soon.
And kids, remember to mind your studies.
Thanks, Mr. Hammond, we will.
Remember to mind your study.
Why does he have like a Scotty on Star Trek accent?
Yeah, and he also, I don't remember John Hammond
being very focused on kids keeping up on their studies.
And then the narrator going, thanks, Mr. Hammond, we will.
He means, wait, he means his gymnastics.
He knows that's the best.
Oh, maybe.
That's his best way to make sure the people
who test out his facilities don't die.
There's a gymnastics kid at the ready.
That makes sense.
It is crazy.
You put that video next to your face
and I'm just darting back and forth.
It's the closest doppelganger.
It is odd.
It's just like the facial, the type of, the eyes.
I don't know what it is.
It is odd, I cannot dispute it,
but it is not terribly flattering.
I think part of it's also.
I wasn't thinking that either way.
I was thinking about it in the sort of like
the gentle demeanor in a way as well.
Whoa, that's nice.
Yeah.
You also, you know this guy could do
a killer Scottish accent.
We know anything about Jason.
You want to give us some minor studies?
His minor studies.
Scottish is the hardest accent to do,
and now Jason can do it.
I know, it's really hard.
I can't do it at all.
And even when there was like, you know,
everybody could kind of do Daryl Hammond
doing Sean Connery.
I couldn't do that.
Yeah, I can't.
Yeah.
Anyway, I mean, look, if Jason wants to give it a shot,
he can give it a shot.
He's got to give it a shot.
It's going to come out as Shrek.
Oh, please.
If you're lucky.
That's the best case scenario.
Mind your studies.
It's better than I thought.
I was doing it.
Yeah, wow.
Not bad.
Hey, geez.
Yeah.
Pretty good.
He did it, he delivered.
So, do you remember when you were a kid taking this tour?
Do you remember, did you do it the first thing,
or did you, like, as soon as you got out of port of entry,
did you say, mother, father, we must go on these boats?
No, because I went right to Marvel's Superhero Island.
Right, as you should have.
I went right to that theme park land,
and pretty much very quickly wandered
into a comic book store.
Okay.
Because there is a store.
Not a ride?
You just went to a comic book store?
I take that back.
I did Dr. Doom's Fearfall.
I think at 13, I was not brave enough to do the Hulk.
And Spider-Man had, like, a two, three hour wait.
So that was, like, we came back at the end of it.
We knew, like, okay, we'll do it later.
Lines go down.
We'll do boats later.
I think we did boats, trying to remember.
I feel like it was in the afternoon,
and either, because I was there in 99 and 2000.
But it was something you were looking forward to going in,
or was something that you realized was there later?
Do you remember that?
I think it was one of those, like,
we were looking around, taking it all in,
and we saw them crossing the lagoon,
and it's like, oh, gotta do that.
Gotta get on a boat.
And we embraced, and we said,
look where our family is today.
Look where our journeys have taken us.
The wonders of man.
Also, the first time I was there,
it was so goddamn hot.
Like, it was, I know it's Orlando.
I know it's June is the summer, but.
Can I remind you guys when, a month ago,
we were talking about how the LA cold
is so oppressive at night,
that you have to bring a sweater
to even make it out after your phantasmag,
but the Florida weather, which is notoriously perfect.
That was the story in an episode one month ago.
Now here you are saying, so hot, so muggy.
No, it was bad, like, it was a heat wave.
There we have it.
This was a unique situation,
I think is what he's saying. This was unique.
The rare day of bad Florida weather.
Extra 15 degrees hotter, extra humidity,
because everyone has a limit.
Even Jason and I love humidity, you know,
you gotta limit, and I don't know,
we could probably track down exactly
what the humidity was that day,
if we found the dates.
Oh, historical weather records?
If you could find out what day you were tripped.
Famously, the most humid day.
Right, it's possible it broke some sort of record.
The humid apocalypse.
Right.
Yeah, thousands of people got muggy to death.
It's possible.
Their eyes fogged up, and they just walked
right off of cliffs and into the sea.
We were there, when we were there in 2019,
it was kind of a brisk day when we went to Universal,
and I, at 5 p.m., as the sun was going down,
did Dudley Do-Right, it got drenched.
So I had to.
This is one of the great tales.
Jason, we know, the socks, of course, of course.
This is scripture.
Going into a store asking for just the largest bag
they had, so I go in the bathroom,
throw a t-shirt in the wet bag,
and just put a hoodie on.
I think you're saying,
you give me the largest bag you have,
and then you walk out wearing that.
Yeah.
It would be warm.
Theme park hack.
If you don't want to pay for a poncho
or a change of clothes, just ask for the biggest bag.
Like you, it's a bag usually reserved
for like a big sword prop or something
in Marvel Super Hero Island.
It's very long, the bag, and then you could wear that bag.
We have these for Namor's Trident.
Yeah, there you go, thank you.
That's the specific I was missing.
You know, he's the one swimming through the toilet water
above the restroom sign.
Yeah, that toilet prevents Disney
from making a Namor ride in Orlando.
That's right.
It's true.
A what ride?
Namor, the Submariner.
Namor?
Yeah.
He's like Marvel's Aquaman.
Okay.
He's got little trunks on, and he's shirtless,
but he's like, he rules over an underwater kingdom,
and he's a dick, and no one likes him.
But he is plastered outside the bathrooms
at Islands of Adventure, which now that prevents Disney
from ever making an Orlando-based Namor ride.
Wow.
Yeah.
Finding Namor.
Nope.
Not gonna, he was in Black Panther 2, right?
I believe.
Yes, I haven't seen it all.
I haven't seen Guardians 3, I haven't seen Black Panther 2,
I haven't seen Ant-Man 3.
I'm so behind.
Yeah.
From what I've been hearing,
you're missing all the best ones.
Well, that's what I've heard too, but.
Did you finish X-Men yet?
No!
Oh, we have so much to talk about.
I don't see anything, I don't watch anything.
I know we have a lot to talk about.
I'm going to.
Guys, it's really, and it's not even for the show,
I'm not going to sit around for an X-Men 97 episode,
but you guys as friends need to have this moment.
I agree, I believe we do need to have it.
This is, you're spitting in Jason's face
not finishing this show.
I know.
And it's not because you're not watching anything,
because I feel like you're,
I think you'll still do like.
Well.
All right, so just a quick two and a half hour
Club Random with Alice Cooper.
But you can do other things while you listen to the wisdom
from Alice Cooper on a Club Random.
Yeah.
No, the visuals are so much a part of it.
You need to take in the colors so murky in his club
that they don't exist in nature.
Right.
New colors are being invented by the merging of magenta
and dark green and smoke gray.
It's experimental television.
You need to examine the very confusing chairs
that seem to have very sturdy armrests,
but they're really like low.
They are kind of low.
Well, that's what Richard Dreyfus famously
sunk into his chair on his Club Random episode.
All the way down.
And he was like lying down on the chair by the end of it.
One of the strangest things I've ever seen.
But yes, no, I can't watch,
I can't passively watch X-Men
and I can passively watch Club Random.
Yeah, yeah.
So.
Well, come over, you should go,
I'm gonna set you up on a date.
You go to Jason's place.
You guys sit and watch together.
On your old TV that I have.
That is funny, I forgot.
Jason has my like, what year is it?
It's 14 year old.
2010.
It's a 14 year old TV.
Wow.
Still pretty good, right?
Yeah, it's still really good.
I mean, it might as well.
It is 8, 1080 HD.
You know, it is a giant.
Is it 1080?
No, it's not.
Top of the line.
Highest resolution there is.
There's no way, isn't it 720?
I don't think so.
Really, I got a 1080 14 years ago?
Movies look great on it.
I'm gonna have to look that up.
Maybe that's right.
Movies look a little too clear on some new TV.
I don't, there's not time.
Well, you gotta, there's settings for that.
Movies are too clear.
Let's get back.
Islands.
Notable, the first Universal park
to have an original soundtrack.
You know, Universal Florida is mostly movie.
Hooray for Hollywood.
And hooray for Hollywood and Back to the Future and E.T.
But this as an original soundtrack,
many years you could buy it on CD.
Universal recently uploaded it to YouTube.
It was on Spotify for a short time.
It is not anymore.
It's unclear why.
Can you save it on Apple music?
I can try.
But yeah, I love this app.
I was playing the call to adventure, the main theme.
The only, so years ago I ripped,
I downloaded a bunch of,
I downloaded the full soundtrack
and I changed the track order in a playlist
because the track order on the CD
has you going counterclockwise around the park.
Where you would start, this is so,
this is nasty to me.
Where you would start with Cat in the Hat
and end at Marvel, that's insane to me.
You start at Marvel and you end at Cat in the Hat.
This one, I'm curious if listeners feel the same way.
Well does not, does though today
the rush to get to Harry Potter
or Velocicoaster change the equation?
Is that not the priority for a lot of guests today?
Yeah, I mean, for normal people, yes.
But for me.
But you're so, you're an advocate
of starting with your dessert.
Yeah, I am.
Essentially.
My version makes it, your day gets progressively worse
as you go around.
Are you saying, would you quantify
Soos Landing as the worst of the islands?
Well, I was never a real little kid
and I never had real little kids.
So I was-
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You used to be a real little kid.
You mean when you were at Islands of Adventure?
When I was at Islands of Adventure, I was like 13.
So I appreciated Dr. Soos.
I love Dr. Soos, but like-
But he has a trash ass land
when it comes to Islands of Adventure.
At 13, I wanted to be at the bankrupt era Marvel island.
I didn't wanna be-
But in an adult way of reassessments,
do you think Soos Landing is the worst
land at Islands of Adventure?
I, oh, in adult, well, hmm.
Okay, how about I put it to you like this.
Okay.
I have a missile shooting device
and it could blow up one of the islands
and I'm gonna blow up either Toon Lagoon or Soos Landing.
Oh, Soos Landing in a heartbeat.
All right, well, that's it.
It answers the question to the core.
Because Toon Lagoon has these one of these,
like two of the best water rides in the country,
in the world. Soos Landing is the worst land
in Islands of Adventure.
And by default, and I'm sure it's different
if you have kids, but even then,
is that the strongest little kid land there is
even on that property, I don't know.
New DreamWorks thing opening might end up taking it.
The DreamWorks stuff looks really fun.
Yeah. Yeah, I agree.
I gotta get them credit.
And they've also been, I was saying to Jane,
like I saw some vloggers and they were going through,
like, you know, stores had a lot more
DreamWorks characters merged, like unique merchant stuff.
And I'm like, this makes me more interested in the land.
Just seeing the commitment that we're going all in.
We're doing merchandise, we're doing food,
we're doing meet and greets and play area.
I'm like, well, now I'm interested.
Now you've got my attention.
Now I'm interested. Now I'm interested.
I was worried they wouldn't commit.
I wanna wear this. And sell some shit.
The troll headband, but it just seemed a lot less generic.
And when parks, I feel like, commit to that,
it just shows they're like, yeah,
we're kind of going all out.
Yeah, sure.
Shrek's farting outhouse slide.
Fantastic. Great.
Why could I be mad about that?
No, it's great.
I can't find the islands on Apple Music.
I see it on YouTube, the island soundtrack, excuse me.
So I don't know, I don't know what happened.
So like 10 years ago, I used probably a weird
like Russian YouTube converter, downloaded the MP3s.
It had to be, certainly you couldn't do
one of the very common American ones.
You had to go Russian.
You recommended one a few years ago
that I use a lot nowadays.
But back then, I just couldn't find,
like, it was just a million pop-ups,
but I was like, I want these MP3s.
And you took initiative and you changed it.
I changed the metadata.
Wow.
So it goes in the order I want it to go into.
Wow, wow.
And how did that work in terms of it being a musical piece
with emotion and builds?
I think it worked well.
Okay, okay.
How often do you listen?
Is it a soundtrack that you listen to now to relax?
Is it something?
I'll put it on the background every now and then.
Okay.
And is it, like, as far as theme park music,
do you have any sort of ranking
is this your favorite thing to listen to
or would you rather listen to a Tomorrowland loop
or is there anything you prefer?
Is it just in the mix?
Well, speaking of, it's in the mix.
I like the, I have one that's like the Hollywood Studios loop,
the main drag loop, and that's a lot of old standards.
Oh, okay.
That's a rate for Hollywood.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
As long as you're getting a rate for Hollywood somewhere.
Yeah, absolutely, yeah.
But yeah, this was the first Universal park
with an original soundtrack.
You could buy it, now you can kind of stream it
a few places.
It's on YouTube, yeah.
It's on YouTube.
Official uploads are on YouTube,
so the quality is pretty good.
What's the banger?
What's the best one?
I think the main, the call to adventure
and is the last song when you're exiting,
the adventure continues.
The adventure continues.
That's at least.
Oh, that name before Star Tours became that.
Yeah, wow.
Wow.
So that's something, that's a thing that,
we always knew your son had good music.
It's always been the case.
Yes.
We always bonded over the music.
In the end, it was about the music.
Yeah.
So that's, yeah, that's always been consistent.
Is that port of adventure, port of entry,
what the hell it's called?
Port of entry, port of entry.
Port of adventure, whatever, what is it called?
The one with the pirates and the palm reader.
Port of adventure.
Port of, you made it too interesting.
Port of entry.
Port of adventure is, adventure is better.
Wow, that's, yeah, port of entry.
And at the end of the day, it's the port of exit.
The port of, yeah, port of entry and the inland sea.
Some of these are a little flat, aren't they?
Yeah, in hindsight.
They get like dressed up in your mind
because it's like interesting looking
and there's music and stuff.
But if you really analyze just the name,
they are kind of, whatever.
The international hub of walking.
Take your steps, yeah, please.
Steps, Stepsville, I don't know.
This is, Stepsville is better.
What am I saying?
Stepsville.
Yeah, so, I don't know.
I was watching ordinary adventures
at a video from Universal Beijing, which looks insane.
Like, they just went so big with that park.
And they, you know, they pointed out like,
oh, you only see so many brand new theme parks
open in your lifetime.
You know, Shanghai, Beijing.
But in the 90s, the one, two punch of Animal Kingdom
and Islands of Adventure was so exciting.
And who knew it would take another 26 years
to get a new theme park in Orlando?
Yeah, yeah, totally.
Yeah, yeah, they both stopped, didn't they?
Except for, I mean, one stopped seemingly forever.
And, but Universal at least is back
with something pretty spectacular.
And what do you think in terms of,
do you think it'll, you think it'll be better?
Is it possible for it to be better to you?
Can it, can it dethrone Islands of Adventure
for you personally? Epic.
Epic Universe. Yeah.
I don't know if it can dethrone
just because I have so many fond memories
and such of fondness for Islands of Adventure.
But there is a lot of cool stuff
seemingly coming to Epic Universe.
Just that center of the park, this celestial park.
I'm like, I might be most interested in that
just to see like what- We're gonna have to drag him
through one of these pipes.
He doesn't wanna go through a pipe.
He's going celestial.
Oh, there's a pipe at the entrance,
but the Kronos is above it, so.
Well, the Kronos is good. What's the but?
Does the Kronos make trouble?
No, the Kronos is cool.
Oh, oh, okay. I'm into the Kronos.
So you're getting a pipe no matter what.
If you're in there, you already got a pipe.
I just like the landscape architecture
of like all the greenery and all the water and stuff.
Okay, Jason, I have my missile launcher again.
And now the missiles are trained
on Toon Lagoon and Jurassic Park.
Well, I thought this was gonna be your bullet.
It's Islands of Adventure Epic Universe.
I thought this was smaller stakes than I would imagine,
so we have more questions.
I thought it was gonna be Epic Universe Lands.
Okay, fine. I'm gonna change my question.
Toon Lagoon is in the crosshairs on one.
And then let's say Monster Land in New Epic Universe
is in the other.
No, that's too hard. That's too hard.
You gotta make a decision. Choose, choose.
You gotta make a decision.
It's going to your head.
The missile's going into you.
Sorry, Monster Land, I don't know what you are yet.
I don't know what you are yet.
Okay, all right.
Now quickly answer me. Is there any scenario?
Dracula doesn't have a cape.
That's a good reason, yeah.
Okay, now the missiles are different.
The missiles transform things.
They terraform. They don't necessarily just blow up.
Oh.
There's, okay, so the terraforming missile
is trained at Hollywood Studios Entranceway.
It'll be changed into, let's just call it,
it's gotta be something sort of boring,
so it's gotta be like, hmm.
It'll be, let's just call it Office Land.
And it doesn't have to be based on the American office
or anything, the TV show,
but just it's like sort of office buildings.
You take away the old Hollywood theme.
It's still the stuff in Hollywood Studios.
You're turning it into Scranton?
Wait, I'm confused.
Why is there Office Land?
I'm just trying to give Jason a choice,
where Hollywood Studios,
he loses his beloved old Hollywood theme.
It turns into a much more drab sort of Main Street
that's maybe much more modern.
It all looks like Apple Store aesthetic.
Let's say that instead of Office.
So everything is sort of like,
it looks like an Apple Store and it looks new,
and they've completely gotten rid of
any of the old Hollywood stuff.
There's no hooray for Hollywood.
They're playing modern pop music,
and they renamed the whole park
to Disney's Cool Adventure.
Okay.
So that's one of your choices,
or you blow up Toon Lagoon.
Well, you know, I don't want to,
I want to give you credit for that very strained idea.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
It seemed to be giving you.
You noticed the strain.
It seemed like it was hurting you,
trying to come up with generic specifics.
My brain was smoking.
I think in that case,
I would terraform Toon Lagoon.
Really?
I think maybe.
You found one.
Wow.
So you would preserve Hollywood Studios as is.
I don't know what I would do.
Just to keep the 40s entrance?
I don't think I would blow up Toon Lagoon.
I would turn it into an Apple Store
over to having Toon Lagoon going, right?
I think I would too.
Wow, look at that.
Wow, that's funny.
That's a shocking move.
What that just shows is that we don't care about the 40s
the way Jason cares about the 40s.
I guess that's true.
The Hollywood that never was and always will be.
That is what that says, I guess.
Because Apple, you're like,
well, Apple Store's overdone as far as an aesthetic,
but that's just the entrance away.
You're not getting rid of Popeye.
I like the Americana.
I might like the Americana more
than being on a little 40s street.
Americana's now, baby.
That's modern.
Wow.
Oh, you need that grow then.
You don't want Hooray for Hollywood.
You want.
Like a Josh Groban song.
Honestly, I think I do prefer Josh,
and I don't like Josh Groban at all.
Well, that's Michael Buble,
but I would take,
I do like either one better than Hooray for Hollywood.
When it gets to the lines about silly,
ballyhooey, screwy,
I think I do not like that song.
I'm not a big fan of the song Hooray for Hollywood either.
Wow, it comes out.
We don't, oh.
This is supposed to be celebrating your son,
and I apologize,
but I'm not a big Hooray for Hollywood.
I didn't like it when I was a tour guide.
That was one part I didn't like
is that you'd end up back there.
Sometimes you'd have to do 10 minutes on a microphone,
just like, hey, everybody keep heading down the escalator.
Don't stop on the escalator.
Keep moving.
Remember, you remember how escalators function, right?
Okay, don't,
remember these are,
don't let your shoes get torn up at the bottom here.
It was like a kind of boring thing.
It was not as fun as the rest of the tour,
and every bit of that was covered by bam, bam, bam.
I don't like Hooray for Hollywood, Jason.
I'm sorry.
No business like show business
is a little bit better in my mind.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's a lot better.
I mean, I still love Hooray for Hollywood.
That's funny that that's like a duh for Jason.
Yeah, Mike, of course.
No business like show business.
That's the meanest he's ever been to me.
Like what's better, eating food
or shitting it out is diarrhea, dude.
Everything about it is appealing.
I, look, I like old music,
but those two, I'm not a big, huge fan of either of them.
Okay.
Are you reaching for your gun?
Just my recording gun.
I just, it's not loaded.
Wow, I can't believe you would get,
you would get rid of Toon Lagoon over that.
That actually kind of blows my mind
because I thought I was presenting some real hard choice,
but in hindsight, and when Scott pointed it out.
Well, if you ask me again tomorrow,
I'd probably give a different answer.
Oh, really?
I feel like I'd go back and forth.
I thought that was going to be,
if you ask me again, you're fucking dead.
I'm sorry.
I will choke you out.
Dead, I didn't forget.
We should add something more positive for Jason.
Yes, please, what else you got, Jason?
We have just shit on his two favorite songs.
Not counting, I guess number three would be
from the soundtrack.
Long Way to Tipperary.
And then like one song by Postal Service.
Yes, such great heights.
Long Way to Tipperary.
Such great heights, yeah.
Long Way for Hollywood, no business like show business.
Jimmy Crack Corn and Muse.
This is your birthday celebration for your son.
Yeah, for my son.
What do you want to get out before we wrap up?
I think I got out.
You did?
Oh, okay.
I think I hit everything I wanted to hit.
I will say, oh, it hasn't,
as we're recording it hasn't launched yet,
but there was a podcast coming out on the 28th
called Recalling the Adventure,
where they talked to a lot of the show directors
and creative people who worked on islands.
And I'm very excited to listen to that.
Great.
Well, can I ask though, going forward,
as your son turns 25 and he gets older,
where do you want the Islands of Adventure
to be at in 10 years?
Where do you want your son to be at at 35?
What do you want it to look like?
We've heard the rumors.
To look like 1999 forever.
So your son still lives in the house
and you are not encouraging him to move out?
Well, he moved in the ADU.
He moved in the guest house.
Oh, you converted the garage.
Yeah, converted the garage.
Right, okay.
So that's the most you want to change,
is garage conversion level, because otherwise.
Yeah.
So even, and even Suzanne,
I certainly miss the storage,
but you know, you love your kids,
so you make sacrifices.
Would I rather have my old files or my son?
Well.
Well, okay.
So you don't want a single thing to change.
In fact, you want Lost Continent restored.
Yeah, I'd like some attractions in Lost Continent.
I mean, I like the vibe of Lost Continent a lot.
But the rumor, of course, is Zelda.
I think you can-
Is that of course?
I didn't know that.
Where's Zelda gone?
Lost Continent.
Oh, oh no.
So Jason wants it out.
That's what I'm asking.
I think you can merge Hyrule and Lost Continent pretty easily.
Merge Hyrule and Lost Continent?
Hyrule is the land that Zelda takes place in.
I think you don't need that.
Well, I've outed myself as knowing not one thing
about Zelda or Zelda coming to this park.
That's the rumor.
I mean, the rumor.
What Orlando Informer is.
Pokemon gonna replace Simpsons, that's the rumor.
Okay, yeah.
In Orlando, or excuse me, Main Universal.
So you're comfortable with Zelda taking it over?
I think so.
I think they will find a way to keep
Mythos and the Sassy Fountain.
You think Mythos will last?
Yeah, I think it's pretty popular.
But they're gonna change it to, if it's Zelda land,
you gotta have a Zelda theme.
I think they'll tweak it a little.
But also the exterior of Poseidon's Fury.
I feel like you don't have to tweak that a lot
if that's where you're gonna put a big ride.
I mean, maybe, or it's a show.
There's been rumors of show.
Show, maybe, yeah.
So you are comfortable with this.
Seuss Landing, would you burn it to the ground?
I don't think so.
I like Seuss Landing.
I like that they tried to really commit
to the Seuss aesthetic.
I think it's hard because the very flat color palette
of Dr. Seuss in the Florida sun fades very quickly.
Well, that's a problem with all the cartoon lands
is that the colors tend to fade.
So maybe it's a problem.
Maybe you gotta get it out of there.
Maybe you gotta replace it with another.
And I think it's funny that the sun has been
such a big factor in this episode,
but Florida was regarded as perfect in the Phantasmic episode.
Just think it was an interesting kind of shift of the rules
that has been fully 180 on.
This isn't just aesthetic purposes
is that the sun is a problem here.
Sure, it drains all color from Dr. Seuss,
but keep in mind, sometimes it gets a little nippy at night.
One bad day is what Jason was discussing
when he said it was a hot day.
The only bad day.
It was bad.
We were in tank tops and it was bad.
They were sleeveless.
That's how bad the day was.
That's a not a regular Sheridan thing, or is it?
When we were kids, I feel like tank tops
and occasionally a muscle shirt.
Oh, okay.
Just cause we were vacationing.
The whole fam in muscle shirts in Florida.
No, just me and my brother.
Now, follow up question.
Do any of the Sheridans have muscles?
How are you filling out those muscle shirts?
I don't think we're the most muscle-focused clan, no.
They are definitely not muscle-focused, that is for sure.
So yeah, look, Happy Birthday Island Adventure.
I wonder what this place looks like in 10 years.
I wonder if they cling to Marvel
just so Disney can't get it, or if something does change.
Who knows?
But it could look a lot different in 10 years,
and I wonder, and I'm afraid for you,
cause if that Marvel land goes away,
I feel like you will not be able to step foot in this park
because it'll be too dramatic now.
I mean, yeah.
Like, that's the draw.
I think all the focus and money is going
to be the epic universe, though.
But that's true.
So hopefully Marvel stays around for a while.
And that's really why, ultimately,
the excitement about epic universe
is because it'll hopefully keep Islands of Adventure hidden.
Exactly as it is.
Never really touched up.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's just my special little boy, my special little guy.
Yes.
Do you want to wish a happy birthday
to your special little guy, specifically?
Special little guy, I've seen you grow and change
and also not change.
And I'm so proud of you.
And the fact that you were, apparently,
the last few years, the second most attended theme park
in the world after the Magic Kingdom.
So proud.
Was there an end to that sentence?
Happy birthday, son, and then how about a little kiss?
All right.
You survived Podcast The Ride of the Second Gate.
Thanks for subscribing.
If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
And we're still going to do the pandemonium circus,
the beetle bailey tightrope.
Beetle bailey on the tightrope is its own thing.
That'll be sectioned off.
Yeah, right.
Bimbo spinning around in a big tire,
and then the rest of it will be.
So three episodes, ultimately, about pandemonium circus.
At least.
Okay, and then I'll, I'm sorry, that won't be here.
That'll be main feed, but something will be here.