5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Greetings fellow outdoorsmen!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
Getting nice and rustic here.
Talk about, you know, angling.
There'll be a lot of angling talk from me, Scott Garner, and Mike Carlson.
I'm here. One of my friends in the backyard wrestling days in high school,
his gimmick name was the angler.
He would come out and cast.
Just with his hand?
No, with his hand, yeah, mime type of a thing.
I was going to say, look, wrestling gets dangerous,
but you bring a fishing line and a hook up on the stage,
that's not what it is in wrestling.
Well, there's a stage.
But the ring, you could say, into the ring is generally what you mean, probably.
Okay, well now I've learned that, and now it's been officially confirmed what angling is.
I would have guessed it was about fishing, but I wasn't sure.
Jason, share it, and we aren't leaving you out.
Yeah, I was going to say, with some hardcore matches,
I feel like you could cast a fishing hook and line into someone.
Yeah, I've seen in GCW, I've seen a spike go through somebody's cheek.
Pretty gross.
So you could do like a fish hook or something, or yeah, I'm sure.
I think they have. If you look it up, I'm sure.
I'm not going to look it up, but I'm sure.
Is angling just when you're...
Here's the answer. I don't know the answer to that.
Casting is throwing it out, and then I think angling is...
I don't know if it's associated more with fly fishing or traditional fishing.
I have no further information other than we knew it had something to do with fishing,
and somebody thought it was funny. I don't even want to take credit.
I don't remember if I came up with the angling.
Angling is just it, and again, I had to look it up to know for sure.
Again, my guess would have been angling is like it's it in general.
I think you could just call fishing...
Oh, wait, no, it's fishing with a rod and a line, as opposed to with your bare hands.
Or a net, or what a grizzly bear does.
Swatting, or a spear.
Going in with your mouth. Yeah, that wouldn't be...
Grizzly bears are not anglers.
Or what Jason used to do is fish for pond eels.
Fish for pond eels.
If you recall, this is one of the famous Jason stories I learned when we first became friends,
that I was like, I don't know what you're talking about.
That sounds like the little rascals did that.
You're telling the listeners that the history of Jason bringing up something as if, of course,
and you saying, what the hell are you talking about, goes back to before the podcast.
This is no podcast pose that you or I are putting on.
This is Herald Team era, I think.
This is like 2010, 2011.
Jason presented this to the friends on the Herald Team as if,
you know when you go and fish for pond eels?
And we went, no, no one knows what you're talking about.
But how did you remind me how you angled for pond eels?
So in the little neighborhood down the shore when my family had a little beach trailer,
there was a small lake that was connected to the marshes outside of Ocean City.
And the lake kind of gave way to a little creek, crick, as we say.
Of course.
Back east.
And then there was a little pond behind the bath houses where the washers and dryers were and stuff.
So you'd ignore the loud sex sounds from the bath houses, the absolutely rapturous sex.
Sex banging on the walls of the bath houses.
No, this is like a bath house next to us.
It's not that kind of bath house.
A swimming pool.
Like this is like, it's like where you use the restroom.
That could be anything you want it to be.
It's up to the imagination what kind of bath house it is.
So, yeah, so we got fishing rods at some point.
And people would just go out there or go like next to the pool and just like fish.
And you would catch guppies or these little yellow fish that everyone just called sunnies.
The one time we went to...
Sunnies?
Sunnies.
We haven't heard of sunnies.
So, but then the one time we went to it, I think like we caught one guppy or something.
It's just catch and release.
And then we just started catching eels.
So I just always called them pond eels.
How long were they?
Wow, they were long.
Yeah, they were a little long.
Like 10 inches?
Yeah.
So, I mean, you're just trying not to catch every now and then there'd be a snapper turtle back there.
So you didn't want to catch one of those.
And he wasn't on a hook.
You had a hook at the end of the line or no?
Yeah, I had a hook at the end of the line.
Oh, you did.
So you were injuring these.
And we were...
You were injuring them.
Well, but we were also giving them hot dogs.
And then sharp cheddar cheese we found to be the thing they most liked.
So you were way out of that park and left out.
Sharp cheddar.
You used hot dogs to fish for pond eels?
I know one thing at a time.
But here's the thing.
If you cut up hot dogs, they fall apart really quickly.
Like the fish, the fish just grab them and swim away.
Sharp cheddar cheese.
Or the young boys named Jason just grab them and run away.
Well, I think we tried that as an alternate.
The sharp cheddar cheese were like, oh, this is really sturdy on the end of the hook.
And then the creatures in the pond just went wild for the sharp cheddar cheese.
They loved the sharp cheddar.
We kept catching things.
So did the sunnies like the sharp cheddar?
Did you feed sharp cheddar to the sunnies?
I think it was kind of like 50-50 eels and sunnies.
But we just kept...
Every time we would catch, we would just keep getting eels very quickly.
And then you try mild cheddar and nothing.
They need a little more bite to it.
It's got to be sharp, extra sharp, and who knows?
I don't know.
You got more eels than you could deal with.
I specifically remember sharp cheddar cheese
because we would just always have cheese and crackers around, you know.
And was your preference sharp or was that the family's preference?
I think my family's preference, usually Triscuits and sharp cheddar.
Are they mad at you that you're taking their sharp cheddar,
their fine sharp cheddar they paid for out of their own pockets,
and you're giving it to eels?
I was doing this with my dad and brother.
This is not a pilfering story.
Okay, I'm still picturing a little rascals gang
that is in defiance of the parents.
I didn't realize that parents were part of this.
No, I was terrified.
And I was terrified when we caught anything.
I was like, oh, we got to get it.
We got to send it back.
We don't want to kill it.
We got to get it off the hook.
Good humanity to the...
So never an eel fry.
And then at the end of the day,
your reward with inherent sharp cheddar lining.
Like, ooh, I can taste the cheddar in these eels.
That's their marinated cheddar.
I was initially terrified because cartoons had taught me
eels are usually electrified,
and that I think it had to be explained to me
that those aren't very common, period,
let alone in this part of the world.
Don't.
Mom, dad, if I catch one of these eels,
am I not going to flash on and off, regular and then negative,
and you'll be able to see my skeleton on the inside
from the outside?
I'm picturing you frying up an eel
and then putting it on a hot dog bun.
Well, that is naturally like...
Fits the shape.
Hot dog bun or Kaiser roll, you know.
Eel-wrapped hot dog, yeah.
Ooh.
I also just...
Because this is only in the last so many years I realized
that if you're fishing with a hook, generally you are...
Like, there's a good chance you're killing the fish,
even if you throw it back.
Because the wound that the fish or sea life will have
after a, you know, metal thing goes through their cheek.
The Jason's eel pals are not with us anymore.
So, chances are you were killing all those.
Oh.
You killed all those sunnies.
Oh, thanks, Mike.
I'm just wanting to let you know,
in case you are going back to get sunnies,
don't use the hook if you want to just throw them back.
Sometimes crabs would end up in those waterways, too,
every now and then you'd see a little blue claw crab.
Did you ever catch one?
I never caught a crab, no.
That seems harder.
Yeah.
They can run away.
They scurry.
They scurry, really.
Yeah.
You got to surround...
You got to, like, build a fort of sharp cheddar
around them, distract them,
and they got to eat their way out.
Do you have any sharp cheddar in the house?
I use string cheese.
That's pretty firm.
But not sharp.
But I don't have sharp cheddar, no.
Okay.
I don't exactly think string cheese qualifies as sharp cheddar.
I don't believe so.
No.
It is in theory mozzarella, but I didn't know mozzarella
could be shelf staple for so long.
Oh, yeah.
You mean it lasts longer, then?
Well, I'm just saying I can't...
Are you eating unrefrigerated mozzarella?
No.
I've got the string cheese in the fridge,
but I feel like that keeps for a while.
Hmm.
Maybe.
Individually wrapped, you know?
Kind of.
I just want to know if your preference is
regular mild cheddar or sharp.
If you have to go with the cheddar.
I usually like it pretty sharp.
Okay.
You know what?
I do have a brick of sharp cheddar from Pennsylvania.
This one dairy farm run by Mennonites.
They make this amazing different types of cheddar cheese.
How long have you had that?
It's sealed in wax.
I think I've had it for a year.
I haven't opened it yet.
Well, that keeps a long time, then.
Yeah.
I looked this up once.
Wax.
You have a year-old block of sharp cheddar cheese
in your fridge.
You haven't cracked it?
You didn't do that in the first week?
It lasts for like three years if it's perfectly sealed in wax.
Wow.
So you could seal a lot of food in wax, I suppose,
and it could maintain its freshness?
Maybe.
Well, Jason loves sharp cheddar.
He's a regular eel.
Yeah, I'm a real eel.
He's a real eel.
The new nickname.
We finally have a new one.
Jason, the real eel.
The real eel.
There are only 100 nicknames.
Watch out.
The real eel.
Get a steal of a deal with the real eel.
OK.
Sorry.
Let's get to the title.
No, no, no.
That was worth an exploration.
Here's what's happening here.
So I have had this queue of stuff that I've been wanting
to talk about for a while.
Just other things have gotten in the way,
and especially the city walk saga and the prep for that.
That just sort of was an override of a lot of fun stuff
I've been doing with my family and fun little trips
that I've been taking.
And I've had this mental queue of like, OK,
some of these have got to start turning into episodes.
Like I did Legoland finally.
I posted a picture of that.
That's got to happen at some point.
Really fun trip with Disneyland that probably could splinter
and do a couple things.
Mike, you did it.
You just this week, very successful second trip
to Disneyland for your daughter.
Second trip to Disneyland with the daughter, and yes.
Much better than the first one.
That's great news.
That seems like you had a little magical one.
Yeah, and I had one that's got stories and stuff to talk about.
This isn't the one, but Erin, birthday present,
I got her tickets to Kenny G. We saw Kenny G together.
This is absolutely a podcast worthy.
There's at least like a five minute tangent on what happened
at this Kenny G concert, but this isn't the time.
Let me just whet the appetite.
This was without a doubt the most interesting concert
I've been to in a very long time.
Yes, there's much to it.
Now is not the time.
I'll just put it up.
When we see one that feels a little bit light,
although you never know because you end up
at 10 minutes of cheddar angling.
Any episode can be a packed full episode if you want to be.
I'm so sorry.
I don't mean to bring the mood down.
I just got a news alert.
Dabney Coleman passed away.
There was no reason for you to say that.
Why?
What possibly?
You know, so a lot of fun with my family.
I must tell everybody we must break.
I'm hearing this for the first time.
I didn't know he was still with us.
That's so funny that you said that.
I saw it at 10 a.m. today that Dabney Coleman died.
Wait a minute.
So it didn't just happen?
No, I just got the Los Angeles Times Apple News
notification one minute ago.
And I think he's been dead for at least 12 hours.
Like, I think.
And this will come out in, what, four or five days.
This must be said.
Sorry to interrupt.
Oh, my whole thing is to name the old character actors
from Gilead's Island.
But I can't pay tribute to the wonderful Dabney.
I know the best way to do it.
This will be the most somber tribute.
This will be so beautiful.
People will get so misty when I say Dabney Coleman died.
It was so funny, though, because you interrupted.
It wasn't even like, well.
Didn't even get to the end of a sentence.
Shut the fuck up.
A man is pressing away.
The Muggle Martin's boss is dead.
I knew it would be kind of funny if that's how I went about it.
Well, it was, by the way.
We're having fun with it.
Thank you so much.
Anyway, back to the topic at hand.
How are we going to go on?
He was 92 years old.
Jason, was that two seconds from brain to mouth,
or were you sitting on that for three minutes?
I need to get in.
I need to get in there.
It was kind of a minute.
I mean, this news alert was two minutes ago,
so it wasn't cooking for that long.
OK.
The detail that you got the alert now,
but this has been news for many hours.
Yeah, yeah.
I saw it very clearly.
Not even worth mentioning on the way in the door to record.
Not even like, oh, Dabney Coleman died.
Because it actually was news to me.
I didn't know about this.
If you need to take, the listener won't notice,
but Jason may need to take a couple hours.
Yeah, if you need to take a personal hour.
Sure.
Stay here.
Don't leave.
But we can't pay you unless you're physically here.
But feel free to not talk.
The other reason it credited him as the boss from 9 to 5
and Yellowstone guest star.
OK.
Well, if I had ever seen it, I would have known.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm going to get to it, though.
Yeah.
You didn't know.
You could have been enjoying one of the final Dabney
performances.
He was great.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
We loved Dabney Coleman.
I mean, I wish I had more time to prepare, but yes, of course.
Hearing this for the first time.
Very good Colombo villain and one of the greats.
Yeah.
Anyways.
Anyway, back to your lovely adventures with family.
What I was basically, I've had a little queue of things
I've wanted to get out.
Things got in the way, still getting in the way,
such as the death of Dabney Coleman.
And I was like, what do I get to?
Because some of them are more rides proper.
But when I was thinking about it, what is the one I most
want to get out of recent travels with the kiddo?
Absolutely Bass Pro Shops.
Wow.
There was no question that this is the one I was
the most dying to talk about.
So for people not in Southern California,
you were probably well aware of this chain.
You were probably like, Scott, how is this new to you?
This has been a thriving thing for a long time,
and it's a mega, mega success.
But I'm in Southern California.
If I didn't show my cards already, I'm no angler.
I guess I knew some of the stuff.
I knew that these stores are massive.
And I think I've passed by, until very, very recently,
the closest one to us was Rancho Cucamonga.
And that's pretty far away from us.
That's not a place I'm at very often.
And even then just passing by, I think I've clocked one
of these outside of Vegas, but never gone in one.
And then somehow I get algorithmed a video of local news
that one of these is opening in Irvine in Orange County,
not too far from Disneyland.
I don't know why this showed up in the YouTube
and why I clicked on opening of Bass Pro Shops,
but I'm like three seconds in the video.
Like, what?
That's what's happening in there?
I got to go.
I have to go.
I had no idea the scope of these places, the level of theming.
I want to declare that I think, just pure theming-wise,
they're different types of businesses.
But I think that Bass Pro Shops is the heir to the Fry's
electronics store, unnecessary store theming throne.
And I don't know.
So this is where I'm coming at it from.
And then I got to take a trip down to Irvine.
I went out of my way on the way to go see the grandparents
in Newport Beach.
I'm like, I'm going to do a little sidetrack.
I'm going to take a trip, just do Bass Pro Shops.
And obviously, I'm coming in with a lot of enthusiasm
about that.
That's what I'm bringing in here.
When I bring in Bass Pro Shops to you guys,
did you look around some videos?
It doesn't seem like you've been in one, unless you have,
that I don't know about.
No, I haven't.
Does it read in video photo form?
Does my enthusiasm make sense from what you've seen?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there is some elaborate stuff
that I am blown away by just on video.
It's crazy.
The themed entertainment, aesthetics, and certainly
scale, I mean, these places are massive.
There's different varieties of them,
which they helpfully put on the giant sign,
whether it's an outdoor world.
Outdoor world or outboost.
OK, OK.
Probably what I'm mostly talking about here are outdoor world.
And what I went to was an outdoor world.
But I forget the delineations exactly.
I figured, keep the umbrella loose.
What with Bass Pro Shops at all.
Well, at some point, too, I only learned about this chain
in the last few years, Cabela's, which they bought at some point.
OK, yeah.
And is another massive kind of.
They seem to be either merging the brands or keeping them.
It's one of these.
Well, it's like Fry's and was the other brand, Incredible
Universe, or a pizza time theater, showbiz pizza situation.
Yeah.
And you never know.
Is this a friendly merger?
Is this best for everyone?
Or is this a hostile takeover?
Right.
No way to know.
All I know is that this brand is ginormous at this point.
There are so many of these.
And again, if I lived anywhere else in the country,
I think I'd know this better.
But it finally made it our way to Irvine.
It was a little bit of a long car ride with the kid.
You're like, well, that's got to really be a payoff once you get there.
And I am really happy to say this went over so huge.
Oh, that's good.
Four-year-old boys, what I have now.
And from the get-go.
So basically, what I saw on the news was just this live footage
and it's in this atrium, which is sky high.
It is like not even that miniature of a version of the Grand
Californian lobby.
Right.
It's crazy.
And it's so ornate, clearly.
And lamps are incredible.
And animal silhouettes on everything.
And everything's custom-made and just full of antlers and so many animals
all around, like hundreds and hundreds of them.
And then a big tank and waterfall all the way in the back.
Yeah, the big tank and stuff.
It's wild.
It's crazy.
So I knew all this going in.
And I was watching opening day footage.
So I'm like, OK, this is jam-packed.
And how recently was this?
Like eight days ago.
And I'm going on a Saturday morning.
This could be a little nuts.
I was kind of prepping for, is this going to be a little bit of a clusterfuck?
And I get down there.
And it's not.
It never felt like chaos or disorganized.
But I pulled up to very familiar theme park feelings.
Because there's light-up road signs directing where to go.
There's big paths of cones.
There's people pointing with orange flashers, whatever.
It is more coordinated than I have seen Universal Studios on some days.
Absolutely.
I believe that.
Yes.
Clear paths.
And OK.
And I got to go over here.
And I parked far.
They sent me really far away, off several stores over, over to the also massive golf store
wherever I was.
I don't know what neck of the woods this is.
Have you been in Irvine a little bit?
A little bit.
Lindsay went to college there.
I don't know if she fondly recalls her Irvine days.
She does.
But I don't know that she has anything about this neck of the woods.
I don't know if it's the Spectrum.
Wait, no, no, no.
The Spectrum is near the Spectrum.
The Spectrum is a crazy mall with a Ferris wheel and stuff.
It's around there.
It might even be off Spectrum Way or something.
But the amount of hubbub as I come in, it's like, geez, OK.
Now we got a long walk ahead of us.
And boy, I hope I can muster up my four-year-old's enthusiasm.
And thank God the approach has, first of all, so many boats.
Big line of boats outside.
So that's exciting.
And then I'm getting excited by fake rocks.
We have fake rocks before we go in the store.
Lamps, incredible.
Doorknobs, amazing.
Just like, you know, it is really theme park-y.
Right.
Style of wood.
And like, honestly, truly up to par with like Disney's lodges
with Wilderness Lodge and whatever the one in France is called,
which I get to go in.
Oh, yeah.
And then in Grand Californian.
And then we're walking up to the door.
And just the sign, he's like, Dad, there's a big fish.
There's a huge fish.
Yes, I know, son.
Isn't it wonderful?
And then he's making a fish face.
So let's do a selfie.
Let's do a selfie with fish faces.
Hooray, Dad, I'm so happy.
Like, we haven't even gotten in the door.
Wow.
This is working.
It's so great.
Wow.
And then we get in the door, experience everything
that I saw on the news broadcast.
And like, oh my god, if I just like turn my head,
I think I'm looking at like possibly 300 animal facsimiles.
There's giant shacks that look like the out,
the exteriors of like the best margaritavilles,
like the most well-themed margaritavilles.
And fonts are in a similar neck of the woods.
Yes, they are.
Which I've started to have some, you know,
I had some issues with the food during the Sauget that we did.
I remain fond of the vibe of everybody
on the design front of these places.
And they totally got it at Best Pro Shops.
And I'm like pretty blown back by what I'm looking at
and realizing like, oh, we got a bunch of fun in store.
This place has everything.
Now, because it was a long car ride to the bathroom,
turn, bathroom's both broken out.
What?
Yes.
And after all this just like paper sign and guy outside,
no bathrooms.
Oh, so there are other bathrooms?
No.
There are only two bathrooms.
There are like 300 models of fish,
but there is only one set of bathrooms and they are not working.
And I ask, what do I do?
And they're like, gas station or Del Taco.
And I go outside and those are both so far away.
And again, in the most crowded parking lot
where there's traffic being directed
and cars are coming in and out.
I'm like, oh, this is a walk.
Oh, my God, which ended up being fine.
I'm not complete.
It was just so funny that like the reveal, ah,
it was honestly like a theme park level entrance
only to see a badly printed out bathroom's broken sign.
And there are only two bathrooms?
There are only two bathrooms in the whole place?
Yeah, yeah, right in the front.
Yes.
And with that amount of size,
how is there not at least one more?
Again, I'm looking like three separate shacks.
This is a back lot's worth of little buildings.
Yeah, I know.
And there is not even one stall
anywhere in the back of these.
It is very funny you say that
because I watched some of the video of a couple
who were going to the pyramid in Memphis
with the giant Bass Pro shop.
Which is the giant Bass Pro shops, yes.
With a hotel inside in multiple restaurants,
including something called Wall Burger's Wild.
Yes, yes.
They immediately were greeted by
a water main break bathroom's closed sign.
What?
And they're like,
we don't know what this means
for our hotel room bathroom.
Oh, right.
If it's the entire facility,
yes, it's a hotel inside this big pyramid structure.
Yeah.
Whoa.
That's exactly what happened
because if it's both men's and women's restrooms,
that means the entire thing is gone.
That's just a line down.
How is it happening?
What's going on?
Are there eels and sunnies getting into the pipes?
At the giant pyramid,
which is famously terrible for live events.
It was a sports venue.
They tried to have concerts there.
Acoustics in a pyramid are dog shit.
So that got wrapped up.
Bound trapped, yes.
But they were, you know,
theme park can do this,
and they were just same way delighted to discover,
like, we thought this would be a gag.
We thought this would be, like, a lark.
Yeah.
And they're like,
this is, like, nicer than parts of the wilderness lodge.
Wow.
And they thought that about the hotel.
About the hotel.
And very funny, an indoor balcony,
which I think we've talked about before.
I love an indoor balcony.
Looks down on a massive, vast pro shop.
You get a view of the store.
You're in the store.
And America's largest freestanding elevator,
which I believe goes up 28 stories to the restaurant,
and look out at the top of the pyramid.
It's so bonkers.
I don't, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
I mean, I knew some of this,
and the pyramid was in my head a little bit.
But I've, like, never, sometimes you just,
you see these things fleeting.
You don't do the dive.
But it being in my, not quite my backyard,
but several black backyards away from me.
Like, I'm going to do it finally.
And I, really, what it is is, like,
this is 2024, something like this is happening,
where, like, does, I mean, on some level,
it's got to help their bottom line,
because it creates this fun hub,
this theme parky environment,
where it's fun for families to go hang out for a little while.
That helps them on some level.
But also, I feel like we're in such an era
of any extra frill, we don't need that, get rid of it.
And, you know, and in the wake of the very, like,
depressing end of the fries chain,
it is kind of amazing that there's this, like,
one of the most successful cross-America brands
does so much crazy theming
and fucking waterfalls and bears and fake rocks.
And keeps, yeah, keeps it up.
I mean, like, because it's been around.
Yeah. I don't, yeah, I don't know
when they started opening exactly.
But it's certainly, the pyramid came in 2015,
which is, like, the real sign
that it's, like, a behemoth of a brand.
So let me just, like, shout out some other stuff.
Okay, we're imitating the bass on the way in.
There are, you immediately, like, as soon as you walk in,
like, really homey fireplace with giant comfortable chairs.
And then, like, many, many deer and buck heads
mounted to the wall.
I don't know if we're dealing with taxidermy or real here,
if it's all fake, but...
Well, you mean taxidermy would be real?
Yeah, yeah. I just don't know if they're real
or if they're very good simulations.
But either way, it's such a forest in there.
And then you've also got a ton of recreations
of what are the biggest, like, you know, species ever created.
Like, if you're caught, it's like, you know,
the biggest swordfish or whatever.
Right.
With 16 feet.
And here is a 16-foot swordfish.
And then here's a big shark hanging up,
which feels like the Jaws photo op at Universal.
And my son gets to touch a shark tooth, and that's all fun.
He's just so lit up.
So once we make our way back from the Del Taco bathroom
from very far away, we get back in.
Absolutely, yes, absolutely.
Especially because there's, like, toys, stuff to play with.
He's putting on a cowboy hat. He's laughing.
He sees a row of little guns, little toy guns.
And he asks, what's a gun?
And I'm like, oh, there's a big question in the life of a child.
Ah, I'm not prepared to tell you the whole deal here.
And in fact, yeah, you know, put that down.
Don't worry about that right now. Let's not think about that.
Did you have any questions about just the sort of mounted animal heads?
No.
OK.
I have wondered that we haven't gotten into death yet.
He can deal with the notion that an insect is dead.
And he's never asked, what is dead?
He's never said, will I be dead?
So I think about that, though, of like, oh, boy, we're like really...
We got places to go here.
I'm glad that a bee being dead is OK to him.
But when we start asking further than that line of questioning,
there's a lot to deal with.
Have we talked about this on the show? Did we all ask our parents about this?
I have a very vivid memory of asking.
I don't remember mine. What happened with you?
I just said, wait a minute.
I just remember going to bed one night and going, Mom, am I going to die?
And she just like sat there.
I mean, that's probably dramatizing the more she sat there for a second.
And it was just like, yes, but not for a long, long time.
Not a long time.
And I go, oh, OK. OK.
And then I kind of like, it disturbed me,
but that was enough to at least put it in the back of my mind and not the front.
OK. OK.
As long as you keep those Kleenex bedsheets away from your Ghostbusters
and don't start a fire, you'll stay alive as long as you want to.
As long as you have no posters above your bed
that will suffocate you in the middle of the night.
No, you will not.
You will. Long may you reign, sir, my child.
Jason, do you have any memory of this?
I'm wondering if I learned in a roundabout way
that lined up with the real Ghostbusters cartoon.
Yours does involve Ghostbusters? What are the odds of that?
That's weird.
Well, I think I would have been.
I remember liking it in preschool and kindergarten.
So I think the concept of you die and become a ghost.
That show taught you?
The real Ghostbusters taught you.
What is a ghost?
Yeah.
It started, it was kind of roundabout.
You started with mommy, what was Slimer's profession when he was alive?
What kind of man was Slimer?
Did he file joint taxes or was he an individual?
Did he date?
I think I was more obsessed at the time with why is there,
mom, why is there a real Ghostbusters and then the original Ghostbusters?
That was more of a pressing issue for you as a child.
I liked it, but I was confused by it.
This is even heavier than what happens after you die.
I didn't know probably until a few years ago about the Sid and Marty Croft
live-action Ghostbusters that inspired the original Ghostbusters cartoon.
Yes, the wall, because they had already a Filmation-owned,
we can't talk about Ghostbusters right now.
So I think, of course I was worried about dying.
You were worried about it, I just wondered if you remembered a moment.
I don't remember a moment, I was not concerned about my own death.
The children's media convinced me that if my parents out on a date alone,
there is a very good chance they will die and you will be an orphan.
I don't want to bring things down, but Larry Storch died in July 2022.
I just got the alert two years later.
To be fair to Jason, if Larry Storch had died,
I would have interrupted any sort of speech either of you were making
to talk about Larry Storch dying.
It's more recent than I thought, he almost made it to 100.
We might have been recording that day,
we might have been making our jokes and not even realizing that we had lost an F-troop.
I think I announced Larry Storch's death on this show, I thought.
Didn't I? Or at the very least I had mentioned that he was still alive on this show.
I said, I know Larry Storch is still alive, he's in his 90s.
Wait, I'm remembering that one a couple of years ago.
I remember it was weird that you insisted on starting it with
it's so hard to say goodbye to yesterday.
Larry!
That was on the Dippin' Dots episode.
It really, we never recovered.
I never thought we had as much fun with Dippin' Dots as we could have.
It tainted the whole thing.
Okay, what have I missed about...
Shocked I haven't forced us to do a Dippin' Dots episode.
That's a good idea.
Alright, well that's soon.
No Minnie Melts talk.
Get the fuck out of here, Minnie Melts.
You set the rules, man.
Out of bounds.
Anyway, so many things.
This big main display, oh my god, big fish tank that's so high
that can fit so many children at a time to all look at fish together.
There's so many real fish, there's so many fake animals,
there's elk and there's bears and big towering rocks.
And then we start exploring details.
And while I come in focused on like, wow, a big moose and a big fox
and I swear hundreds of these things, it's so crazy.
And that all maybe kind of takes my eyes off of details.
Such as, well one thing I'm looking at like, toys.
What's going on toy-wise?
And I notice that there are a number of trucks, or my son does,
he goes right for those.
And there's like big racks where all of the kind of truck are available
and it's like kids' names, Thomas.
And then there's like a bunch of trucks that say Thomas.
And then the only one that's fully sold out
are the kind of truck that say I love Jesus.
In eight days they are out of I love Jesus trucks.
That sort of answered my question overall about the store, I think, right there.
Yeah.
Because that is what I was assuming.
I'm not even trying to put the store down necessarily.
I'm just saying I would assume more of a certain type of folk
are going to these places.
I mean, yes.
I think so.
And yeah, some things have to be acknowledged.
I mean, that starts to give you the vibe.
And then as I go further back into the store, I notice another thing,
which is another shitty, just like for all the immaculate theming,
suddenly really shitty sign on green printed paper, ammo line starts here.
Yeah, there we go.
And the ammo line is so long.
There are so many people waiting to get ammo.
Some of these have shooting ranges.
Do this one have a shooting range?
I don't believe so.
Some of you saw that, right?
I think that if they were building from the,
because I think they tend to put them on the bottom level.
So I think, and this might have been like a modded out space
that existed from something.
I don't know, this might have been a Costco and a Best Buy,
and it took over full of them.
It was so big.
But I think if they're building one from the ground up,
they're digging a basement and they're putting either a shooting range
or an archery range down there.
And a shooting gallery like the UV, like at Disneyland.
Oh, they had a video game one.
Yeah, a video game one.
I think that was at the pyramid though.
Yeah, no, I think a few of them have that.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
So again, we got a store.
You know, I'm torn here.
Is it a place that's selling a lot of ammunition?
Yes.
However, they also have-
With the fake rocks!
Yes, yes, amazing rocks.
And you know, all these bad places, all these terrible stores,
and most of them don't have fake rocks.
Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville,
none of the restaurants have a shooting range in it.
That's true.
No.
They don't have certain things.
But it's interesting, because on one hand, you're like,
it's sort of celebrating the outdoors.
That's really what we're getting at here.
And I think the three of us aren't maybe avid outdoorsmen, I would say.
No.
Maybe some of the listeners are.
You might say that our son asked if we would go camping ever,
and Aaron straight up said no.
I shudder at that thought.
Yeah.
I do not want to camp.
And granted, I went camping with a group in a very comfortable way in 2008,
and that is the last that I've done.
So it's not my...
I can't pretend it's my field.
Not interested, says me.
Jason, would you ever go camping again?
I have camped a ton.
Yeah, I was in the Cub Scouts and the Boy Scouts.
So I've camped in hot weather, fall weather, winter.
So were you the most outdoorsy of the three of us?
I think I am.
By a technicality.
I know how to put up a tent and such.
I know you need to put a tarp down to put the tent on top of,
otherwise groundwater will make you very cold.
We'll get into the tent.
Okay.
That's the real thing he knows.
He knows how to fish for eels, too.
He would catch us so many delicious eels
if we hadn't eaten in days.
I know how to hang a bear bag.
Do you know about a bear bag?
Oh, you've talked about bear bags on this show many times.
Here is one when we went to...
Real quick, you hang your food up in a tree
so a bear can't get...
Or you put your garbage or your food in a bag,
and yeah, you hang it up with rope
so that bears can't climb up and get it.
This is the one I remember coming up a lot.
You don't remember anything about a bear bag?
Oh, yeah.
Bear bags, sometimes there's bear...
I think they would call them bear boxes,
which were like strong plywood boxes, padlocks.
It's not bear back.
Don't get confused.
Well, no.
He's talking about that, too, though, but not on Mike.
The other big thing we would do,
I was thinking about this, that it's a trick.
When we went to Boy Scouts summer camp,
you got breakfast, lunch, and dinner
at the dining hall, mess hall.
But if you wanted to pack snacks or candy and stuff,
they're like, well, don't pack chocolate, it'll melt.
But hard candy and gummy candy is okay.
And then what they told everyone to do
is get a Country Time lemonade, those plastic...
Yeah, canisters?
Canisters, you put hard candy in that
and powdered sugar so it doesn't stick together,
and those seal really airtight.
And the bear won't smell it.
And the bear won't smell it. That's very important.
But you take the Country Time lemonade out of the canister?
Yeah, you take it out.
Okay, it's an empty canister.
Yes, but I'm wondering nowadays,
are they still making those canisters,
and are that many people drinking
powdered Country Time lemonade anymore?
Well, the real question is, are you?
I'm not right now, but I was drinking glass of water
the other day, and I was like,
I only have water and seltzer, really, in the house.
I don't feel like coffee.
But I was like, I should get some crystal light packets.
You were trying to drink more soda in the new year.
I do, I have a lot of beverages, right?
I stocked up on soda and seltzers.
Do you have a 10-year aged Country Time canister?
Sort of like a...
Oh, yeah, perfectly waxed.
You can drink it 10 years later.
So, these stores are interesting,
because, yeah, they are like, on one hand,
you go, oh, this is just outdoorsy stuff.
This is sort of just general stuff, nice and woozy.
No, they're conservation funds.
Conservation funds.
On the other hand, it's a right-wing haven.
Yeah.
It's a religious right-wing haven.
Yes, why does it end up in Orange County?
Well, yeah, that's, no, no, no, uh-huh.
Yeah, and you don't feel it that much.
I think in other ones, I do think that, like,
as I read articles of people kind of being charmed by all of it
and then finding some blue lives or some MAGA or something
and like, okay, well, sure.
When you look up Bass Pro Shops, the first on Yelp,
the first picture you see is a person with a gun in their hand.
That is just a close-up of a hand and a gun.
Just a picture of a hand and a gun.
Which location are we?
This one is, sorry, one sec.
Is there a caption of that?
Is that like, is it in this?
This is in Rancho.
Okay.
You mean like, oh, when we click on the actual photo?
Yeah, let me find it.
It says, testing my Glock 34.
Ha!
Three likes on it.
And then there's a picture of like two smiling children
sitting in a big rocking chair in front of a Christmas tree.
Isn't that, that's the dichotomy.
Doesn't that say it all?
Of the place, yeah, yeah.
It's an interesting just the position.
That's what you want to make it, isn't it?
I hate to bring it down,
because obviously I love the pictures here.
Well, look, I've been down since Dabney Coleman's.
You can't bring me any further down.
I know you're shining down on me from heaven.
I've been down at thinking all the sunnies that Jason injured.
Yeah, well, it's okay.
Dabney's with the sunnies now.
Just, if someone could make that art of a puffy cloud
and Dabney Coleman surrounded by eels and guppies and sunnies.
A very joyous, under-the-sea type scenario of like,
they're whisking him up to his mustache hairs
or twirling in the bubbles.
All eels go to heaven.
All Dabney's go to heaven.
Anyways, I mean, what this becomes,
I don't have too many more stories,
because really just, it all unveils like,
crazy atrium, okay, gun quarter, uh-oh.
But then like, you know, now we're just like playing in tents.
We're playing in the tents that we'll never buy
because we aren't going to go camping.
But like, there's one that has like a little like,
porch that's still enclosed, right?
Like, here's the main tent.
But then there's a one that's just,
that has just like some sheer coverage.
And we're just like sitting in these little chairs
and just having some good little patio time.
And then he goes and stacks up firewood
and the little firewood display and then knocks it down.
And then he's climbing up on boats and climbing up on ATVs
and testing them out and vroom, vroom.
And it is, it's just the most like, idyllic fun.
Just like, you know, I mean, you know,
you're starting to like branch out in terms of what you do
with your daughter a little more.
And it's just like, you know, sometimes you take a swing.
It's not a place we've been.
I really hope it's a hit.
When it's a hit and then they're talking about it later
and like, all right, we got a winner on our hands.
Hell yes.
It just, it feels so great.
Fill the slot.
You just want to fill the slot
with something that makes him smile
and eats up a lot of time.
And yeah, this did it.
I loved it.
Yes.
That's what we're going through for sure right now.
And especially like we just did Disneyland.
Not only, yes, do you get the thrill from like,
oh, thank God she likes this.
And then the stuff she really likes is very exciting.
And then at the end of the day, and I said,
also like, thank you.
I thanked her.
I think you gave us what we wanted today.
Like your smiles and laughter are why we took you.
Yeah.
Like she delivered is what I kept saying.
I go, you delivered today.
Oh, hey.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, it's, you know, hey.
That's the selfish way to look at it.
It's all mirrors, right?
You've got to bounce those smiles and that energy
back and forth and you know, because it's infectious
and they start happy and you get happier
and they get happier and that's what you want.
I really like, and I don't, I can't like compare
and contrast Bass Pro Shops and Disneyland.
We've had like just glorious, joyous times
at Disneyland with him.
But like he likes it I think as much
as he liked Bass Pro Shops.
Yeah, sure.
And we don't have an annual pass right now.
And I'm like, yeah, that's because like we can have
that much fun at like with him just running back
and forth between two trash cans.
Well, yeah.
I don't know, we're like pointing out the sign
that where an animal is pooping
and making me make poop sounds or fart sounds.
And like that's, it's just like all a big tie.
Disneyland, great, but it's tied with 30 other things.
Yeah.
That are closer and more convenient.
I'm really glad your Disney time is good.
Sure.
And I will keep having wonderful Disney times.
Well, the year, yeah, he's maybe a little,
a couple of years away from realizing like, oh,
the quality of one experience is different
than the quality of another.
These will start separating.
Yeah.
And I enjoyed especially the like two to three year old run
where like it's all the same and it's all new.
Yeah.
If it lights them up, then it's great.
And especially if it lights them up for zero dollars
instead of 150.
Yeah, that's a nice bonus too.
My daughter loved Mater's junkyard jamboree,
but would she have also loved it if we just put her
in like a red wagon and like just like,
just like zipped her around the driveway.
Pretty much the same, really.
Yeah, yeah.
But we took her to Disneyland for us
to see her get happy in the place we like.
And it's elevated.
It's for sure elevated.
Of course, it's elevated.
And she likes the music and she like dances in line
and stuff, so like all that stuff is great.
Well, you know what you have in Disneyland is like,
OK, here's a place with like 20 of those opportunities
all next to each other as opposed to, you know,
there's a cutoff right after Best Pro Shops, you know.
He's not going to have that much fun at the golf store.
Right.
The Del Taco was only so entertaining.
So that's the look.
I'm not putting down.
It's just funny that at this age, like it's all,
it's all kind of a tie.
It's a lot of fun.
Yeah, the flattening.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But the flattening is so high up.
It's a high, because they're having a lot of fun.
But anyway, it just became this like,
I was reminded of something I think about
from one of my favorite movies, The Brady Bunch Movie,
where Gary Cole, Mike says,
all right, kids, put on your Sunday best.
We're going to Sears.
And then you do, it's a sunshine day,
as the family has the most fun in Sears,
just testing out cameras, and we'll go out,
dance on the escalator.
Like, we had one of those Brady Bunch Sears days.
We had it at Best Pro Shops.
It was pretty killer.
And yeah, I don't know.
And if, you know, if we're feeling iffy at all
about some of the things that they supply and sell,
I did spend $0.
We bought nothing.
Smart.
No, yes.
And I'm OK with that.
In a little establishment, if we come in,
and we tear it up and we play with their toys or whatever,
like, I'll buy something.
But they're fine.
Best Pro Shops will be fine.
Well, you say that, but your whole family
has been wearing a lot of wood print,
like UV-protected long-sleeve shirts recently.
Are you accusing me of stealing?
Oh, yeah, Scott.
Scott, I realize you recently started
wearing Wrangler retro jeans that they sell
at the Rancho Cucamonga location.
You're cool.
I could have gotten those from anywhere.
Oh, that's true.
I suppose.
What do you say?
Are you saying that I went inside the tent,
wrapped my little son in several pairs of jeans,
and then I out the door?
Wrangler retro jeans.
We call it Jean Day.
He loves them.
So anyways, that's my personal experience.
And now I'm like, what else is going on with this brand?
And I'm looking into the other ones.
So it starts in Springfield, Missouri.
OK, it starts in 71, but this is not the mega store
that we know today.
It's related to another.
It's the guy's dad had a kind of a Brown Derby liquor store.
That store was the Brown Derby liquor store.
It's a chain of Missouri liquor stores,
and he started selling to tackle out
of the back of this liquor store.
Wow.
There you go.
OK, OK.
And OK, so it starts in this very homespun way.
Grows and grows.
Springfield, Missouri remains the, well,
I guess not the biggest because of the pyramid,
but like a un-incredible, well, I think
they call it the granddaddy.
Where's that in my notes?
It's the granddaddy of all outdoor stores.
There it is.
Is that one maybe 500,000 square feet?
I'm mixing up some of my notes.
I mean, they all have incredible water features.
That one has a separate aquarium,
and so they're called the Wonders of Wildlife National
Museum and Aquarium.
That one has a shooting range under the store.
It has a time capsule, very optimistically
to be opened in 2102.
There is something called Hemingway's Blue Water
Cafe, which exists to attribute the travels of Ernest Hemingway.
And on the website, it says, from your first step
into Hemingway's Blue Water Cafe,
you feel like you are in Ernest Hemingway's library.
And then from the Underwood typewriter
to the antiques book, and I'm like, oh, OK, cool.
And then I'm looking at photos, and I'm like,
I don't think Hemingway's library had
a bar with a fish tank in it.
Unless I'm really mistaken about how Hemingway lived.
Let's ask the guy who reads books.
That's the book where the bookie will over here.
The Hemingway Mansion, I believe in Cuba, I think
is filled with wild cats.
Weirdly?
Yeah.
You can tour it, and there's like.
What is it?
It's a place he lived?
Yeah, I think it was where he lived.
It's Cuba or Florida.
But it's much like the Disneyland cats.
There's just cats that live on the property,
and they feed them, and they're always there.
I'm seeing Havana.
Havana, yeah.
He was cat guy.
I'm seeing Key West.
So he would have had a cat tank, not a fish tank.
Yeah.
Learn his Hemingway home and museum.
Walk the path of the legend.
And it does say the cats on here.
And is it Key West or is it Cuba?
Both, well, I think both.
Oh, OK.
Yes.
Well, now we know that.
Now we know facts about a writer.
Wow.
And I don't want to bring things down,
but he died in 1961.
And I know you're shining down on me.
A song that would come on at middle school dances
and it would make me tear.
I'm like, why are they playing this song?
It's about someone who died.
That is really strange.
OK, the one I'm going to mention is not as uncharacteristic,
but as I'm saying nice memories of my son recently,
the current thing, again, just fun out in the world.
He's just in a regular Target.
And all of a sudden he's like, Mommy, what is this song?
And just really fixates on it.
And the song is All My Life by Casey and Jojo.
Here's, Scott, this is so fucking weird.
What?
I've had a bunch of weird things with this.
What's yours?
Because Jason just said that about like tearing up.
And I will never forget hearing Casey and Jojo's song
in like eighth grade on like a boat at like a dance,
whatever dance.
Like as soon as Jason said that, I went, oh, Casey and Jojo.
You were already thinking it.
I was already thinking it.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa.
Yes.
For whatever reason, like it felt just so like it was intrusive
in a way.
It got in my brain and felt like emotional or weird.
It just gives me.
Everybody's just been harboring a lot of feelings.
Because as we tell this story to people, everyone is like,
I learned how to play that on the piano.
It's been really like soothing to me.
And like I was just talking about that song.
Boy, I feel like it's making a comeback or something.
Yeah.
I didn't know how much was tied into this song.
It isn't a song.
I don't know.
Not that I'm not listening to it lately because of this,
like it's too raw, the emotions or anything.
But it is weird because it is one of those songs that just like hit
at the right time when I was like nervous about girls and like dancing.
And it felt like this is the most emotional song.
The epitome of slow dance for our era.
Yeah.
Right.
I was a very, I had some wires crossed.
I guess I was just too much of a morose child.
Because thinking back to being emotional when that song came on,
I'm like, oh,
all my peers were like slow dancing or making out with each other.
And I was just like, I wonder who this song is about.
Who passed?
Like, you know,
I should be mourning right now, not dancing.
I should be.
My Pepsi has gone flat.
I'm not enjoying it.
Did Casey and Jojo have another hit?
I don't think so.
I've been thinking, well,
they were part of Jodeci, which I did,
but I'm not sure that the separate Casey and Jojo.
Here's the two then sub-stories about that,
is that he has been,
so like just around the house,
he was here in the other room all the time.
Oh,
just singing it to himself.
It's so funny.
Of all the funny,
and it's on a little playlist of his favorite songs,
which are otherwise Thomas the Tank Engine theme songs, Beach Boys,
Bird, and now Casey and Jojo.
It's so inexplicable.
And he, at preschool, asked,
like, can you play my favorite song?
What's that?
All my life.
And they're like, what do you mean?
And he says, by PP and Jojo.
Oh, really good.
Really good.
That's been some of the best kid stuff.
So good.
I love it all.
Anyway, I'll suggest, and now I'm like, who is,
this is about a friend and collaborator.
One Sweet Day is about Mariah's close friend and collaborator,
David Cole,
who died of spinal meningitis brought on by AIDS.
That's a very sad one.
So now you know.
Mariah Carey and Boys to Men is One Sweet Day.
Yes.
And then Casey and Jojo is All My Life.
Not PP and Jojo.
So I don't have the heart to tell my son that.
Anyways.
All right.
Well, I'm getting all these nice things out.
Okay.
What else about Springfield, Missouri?
Obviously sells guns also.
Let's get bad again.
And they have a section called Fine Guns that caused six figures.
You could go in, you could spend 200 grand on a gun,
one gun in the Springfield, Missouri store.
This one has exhibits that are so big,
they had to cut a hole in the roof to install them.
They have things that, I'm not sure what those are,
but like animal displays or rock work or something.
Like, all right, got to cut the roof off.
Weird things in all of them.
Oklahoma City is a bowling alley.
I think the pyramid does too.
Vegas has an aquarium or tank, as a lot of them do,
but that one does mermaid shows.
And I think one where Santa goes down during Christmas.
Silverton Casino, I think that is located adjacent to his Vegas.
Oh, okay.
I saw some video that said Silverton on it.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to go next.
I like these now.
I'm going to go.
A number of them, Jason, get ready for this.
A number of them, fudge stores.
That is a common thing.
And a lot of these, apparently, people like the Pespro fudge.
The one, yeah, Big Cypress Lodge, I was on the website,
and it says D-licious fudge in general store.
And that's like one of the main, other than the archery range,
aquarium, and pistol range.
They spell it out D-licious?
D-e-e-licious fudge in general store.
They do operate a number of resorts, restaurants,
tied to this sort of outdoor aesthetic.
Did you see that picture, too?
That's just nuts.
Looking down on the pyramid, yes, from above a little bit.
Oh, that's a view from the hotel.
Yeah, and there's man-made crick.
There's a crick there.
There's a crick.
There's a crick that runs through the store.
Not a crick of fudge, but that's something they should get in there
at some point.
So a fudge-full crick.
That's a dream, right?
You're Willy Wonka's outdoors.
Jason's going to need a minute.
Well, let's, okay, I think we could switch over to the pyramid.
And I don't even want to call this, this is one of those,
it's similar to when we're talking about Rainforest Cafe,
and I'm like, I don't know if I'm emotionally ready to talk about
the Galveston Ride, the River Ride, yet.
I'm like, there's still a part of me that thinks I might try to go,
because I am knocking out things of this nature,
and a little tease of something to come.
But, so the pyramid, I mean, there's a whole history of stuff
beyond the Pro Shop.
And Jason, it seems like you looked into a lot of this, too.
I know this came up when we talked to Jesse Farrar
about Opryland a long time ago,
and I don't think I really knew it until he was bringing it up,
and it sounds so crazy.
For a long time, Memphis had a plan to build something called
the Great American Pyramid,
which is maybe going to be three of them,
and they were going to, like, let's just start,
let's go straight to three, why not?
It was somebody's dream that didn't happen
as a way to set Memphis apart,
give them something crazy for the skyline,
and it didn't come to pass,
but then the guy's son started it later,
and so, like, pyramid, it started with pyramids.
Second thought, what is in it?
And it slowly becomes, all right, well, I guess an event space
of some kind that makes sense,
but then there are all these other plans of, like,
they are building it.
Let's just start building it,
and then we'll decide what's inside.
So, all right, well, pyramids go up really high.
What's going to be at the top?
Well, let's just make sure there is a lot of room
so that if we wanted to have a hard rock cafe,
we could do that, which would tie in nicely
to what we're going to do on the island next door,
which is a rock and roll theme park called...
Oh, no, where is it?
Music Island? Is it just Music Island?
Yes, Music Island.
They were going to build Music Island.
That today remains with the name that it's always had
since they were building this, which is Mud Island.
They didn't get the theme park,
but Mud Island does seem to have some big letters
that say Memphis on it, and that's it, I think.
If I'm missing something on Mud Island, I apologize.
Good place to buy your mud.
Yeah, you can't overlook a great source of mud.
So anyway, they have all these crazy plans
of what they're going to do,
but they'll just start with being like an arena,
and it's where the University of Memphis Tigers play.
In 91, they start there, and then the Memphis Grizzlies
move in there after they moved in from Vancouver.
Both of those teams left in 2004.
Some of what you said, Jason, it's kind of a, it's,
look, the place, the pyramid is like, it's black inside.
It's muddy, it's depressing.
All the sound goes up to the top.
I think that it put the Grizzlies at an advantage,
because other teams would come in and be like,
this is, this is depressing to be in here.
And wait, what's the term? It was like, do they call it like,
oh, why don't I have it at the ready?
They call it like the, you know, something,
something about a tomb.
I'm not thinking of it.
The sarcophagus, I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
Nonetheless, I mean, they did a lot of stuff in there,
but NBA, basketball, not profitable,
so that's a big one down.
They did do gigantic fight,
Lennox Lewis versus Mike Tyson, in 2002,
which means that this pyramid, due to attendees of that event,
this pyramid, at least for one night,
in the same night in that building,
Samuel L. Jackson, Denzel Washington, Tom Cruise,
Britney Spears, Clint Eastwood, Ben Affleck, Hugh Hefner,
Dwayne The Rock Johnson, Vince McMahon, The Undertaker,
Wesley Snipes, Michael Jordan, Magic Johnson,
Alec Baldwin, and Donald Trump,
all in the greatest assembly of all the great, great people,
and one has there ever been.
That's a real Sergeant Pepper cover, isn't it?
Yeah.
You know, there were some designated survivors,
you know, just in case, Nathan Lane,
Matthew Proderick, and of course, Dabney Coleman.
Oh, okay.
Ironically, thank God.
Two producers and the star of 9 to 5.
Yeah, some of our greats had to remain.
Oh, if Baldwin and Trump only knew
what was coming for both of them,
the dance that they would do for so many years,
and how America would be so entertained.
Anyways, but then it's like, what do we do here?
They filmed some of the movie Black Snake Moan in there.
Really? Oh, I missed that.
I don't know.
Really?
Yeah.
Which part of it?
I think they just built, it was a soundstage.
Any of it could have been in there.
I don't know, a scene in a room.
Might have been filmed in the pyramid.
Yeah.
I learned the site of the WWE pay-per-view,
the Valentine's Day massacre.
St. Valentine's Day massacre.
Steel cage match between Steve Austin and Vince McMahon.
Someone they should have left in a tomb under the pyramid.
Vince took a really ugly bump there.
He fell off the top of the cage, and he landed,
so this is his belly facing up or whatever.
He fell off the top of the cage,
and he lands on the corner of the announce table like this.
One of the ugliest looking bumps.
And it's such a shame it didn't fall twice.
He would go on fall many more times.
If only it had taken place at the top of the pyramid.
Yeah, I know.
It's true.
Whoa.
And it's the debut of the big show Paul White,
who was originally being called the Big Nasty.
Whoa.
His original name was the Big Nasty.
Sounds like an Austin Powers villain or something.
Yes.
Then they changed him to the Big Show.
Similar to the fun of me,
I already had the trademark for the Big Nasty,
so we had to change it.
They didn't want to pay me.
You were 14.
Yeah, I was 14.
An industrious copyright getter as well as an outdoorsman.
It didn't work.
It didn't work at all.
It didn't make me cool.
Kids just beat the shit out of me.
I own the copyright to the phrase Big Nasty.
You're the little nasty piece of garbage.
They would shout.
We'll make you nastier.
You're the real eel now.
Now, yes.
That's all in the past, and now you're the real eel.
Oh, will that make me cool in the high school 21 years?
It's a time machine.
You've got to go to a reunion and find that out.
No, I already skipped that.
That's correct.
Good move.
Anyway, it never turns into anything.
Do we visit it?
Do we make it a church?
Do we make a Smithsonian, a middle of the country Smithsonian
to fill a pyramid?
None of it.
And by the way, the 10th biggest pyramid in the world,
bigger than Luxor, bumped Luxor from the top 10.
So this thing is massive.
And then suddenly Bass Pro Shops ends up in it.
There's some lore, which assuredly is fake,
and which went better in terms of fake lore, fishing stories.
That's what it's made for.
But supposedly, the owners of Bass Pro Shops
were fishing in the shadow of the pyramid,
and there was a bet, like, if you catch a 30-pound catfish,
you've got to build a store in there.
And then they did it.
Johnny Morris is taking that bet.
That's what happened.
His friend did, almost in the shop, a 34-pound catfish.
And sure enough, they bought it, and they moved in there in 2015.
And they built this.
I mean, I just feel like I got to go here.
There's nothing else.
Well, look, I want to go to the Sun Sphere.
I want to go to the site of the 1982 World's Fair in Knoxville.
And I know these things are close to each other.
But maybe I just got to figure out some kind of Tennessee loop.
Yeah.
I'll also include .look.
Just Tennessee.
That's just going to have to be a block.
I'm going to have to go to the Memphis pyramid.
Because this seems, yeah, that photo you were showing,
you look at it from above, it's unreal.
You put some fish eye on there.
This is one of the strangest environments that's ever existed.
Yeah.
No, there has to be all Tennessee thing.
I would like to do a Tennessee thing.
If I've only driven through Tennessee, I've never really hung.
Yeah, I went to Bonnaroo.
That's right.
No, I did go-karts there.
And I saw the Beach Boys there.
So there's some on-brand things.
Right, right.
But still not.
And I didn't get to experience all the things.
Oh, and that's where I stayed and what I determined
was a holiday in Holodome.
So I got some of the, I got some good Tennessee stuff.
But yeah, there's always room for more.
Yeah, yeah.
And there's room for so much in this place.
Wait, there's live alligators live in that pyramid.
There's alligators in the pyramid.
Theming-wise, you've got a cave and a swamp.
It's all real swampy.
Tallest freestanding elevator in the world, like you said,
which takes you up to a bar that was never built out at the height of,
never when they were hosting NBA basketball.
They never developed the top as a bar.
And now it took Bass Pro Shops to do it.
And now it's got an incredible view of the Mississippi River,
which is, I don't know, incredible.
It's a muddy view.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
But it's a view of Mud Island.
The narration in that elevator, they say that freestanding elevator
is taller than the Statue of Liberty.
Wow, really?
Jesus, that's nuts.
The scale, how do you build that?
That being said, Statue of Liberty is shorter than I thought it was.
Yeah.
There's a lot of calibration to do here.
But nonetheless, that's crazy.
There's also a whole crazy thing about this place that Alex Jones
started yelling about that there's a crystal skull up at the top of it.
Oh, really?
The Illuminati planted a crystal skull.
Yes, the same thing from the Indiana Jones title.
And that inspired the Danic Red Vodka.
And there's a crystal skull up at the top of it.
You take away some of the plants, and then you'll find that.
And Alex Jones, of course, as he often is, was completely right,
100% right.
Oh, right.
There is a, and it actually was, a crystal skull was put up there
by the founder of Hard Rock Cafe, Isaac something or other,
Isaac Tigret, Tigret, who, because they were thinking about putting one up
there, and then they didn't, but somehow he still fit in a crystal skull.
So this has to, this has to, you know, if this, then what?
What else is Alex Jones?
So it's an aspirational crystal skull.
I think, yeah, to like just put some good rock and roll mojo.
Just lurking above the bar where you can now get like mozzarella sticks
on top of a Bayes Pro Shop.
Yeah, yeah.
Wishing you a good, wishing you that you don't fall off the glass bottom bar.
Is it like an old crystal skull, or is it a new crystal skull?
Like is it a, he had it like commissioned or something,
or is it like something from olden days?
I really don't know.
And I'm also now going, did Isaac Tigret move to House of Blues
and then work with Dan Aykroyd?
And yes, the answer is yes.
Is that, okay, did they become friends because of crystal skulls?
Yeah, good question.
Did he, was he already friends of them?
So he was like, like, traveling to Memphis, huh?
You're going to want to have a bag of crystal skulls with you at all times.
I got in a close call with a plane crash one time,
and ever since, I've always got the power of crystal in my pocket.
Do you want to check that bag, they say.
I say, absolutely not.
That stays on my person.
I got to say, if I was in a plane crash,
the last thing I would want floating around the cabin
would be a giant crystal skull coming right for me.
No, but you're wrong.
Oh, okay.
Crystal skull will protect you.
What you want to do is buy another seat.
Put them in the seat belt.
Lock them up.
Make sure they can't go flying around.
Put an oxygen mask on one.
That's good luck, too.
A crystal skull.
I'll put a crystal shield of armor around you.
Just check in for my flight.
Here's my passport.
And then I have a ticket for my skull.
Put the skull on your head.
My acroid turned into a little McGruff there.
I've listened to a lot of acroid lately.
I don't know why.
There's just been a string of acroid interviews
I've been listening to recently.
Are you saying that as if I'm supposed to be surprised
that you are listening to lots of Danica?
No, no, no.
I just wish that the people would let him go farther.
I don't care about Ghostbusters.
I don't want to hear about Blues Brothers.
I don't want to hear about any of it.
I want to hear him get to the really alienating weird stuff
about ghosts and aliens.
All right.
So you're saying that there's a guy on a podcast,
and he starts to kind of want to talk about ghosts
and aliens and stuff.
And then the other people doing the podcast
are sort of giving clues that they don't really
want to hear about that stuff.
And then maybe we should stay on the topics,
like Bass Pro- I mean, Blues Brothers.
Right, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
That's interesting.
Yes, sure.
Or if it's like if, for instance,
if he wanted to talk about Wayland Flowers and Madam,
they should let him go.
Let him talk.
Let him go.
If hypothetically, one of the things that Matt Crud
wanted to, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm just saying, I want even more alien content
and ghost content.
You relate to somebody who's being passive
aggressively censored.
Yes, I do.
I do feel that.
You're a truth teller.
A fellow truth teller.
Yeah, like me and Danny.
And Mikey Carlson been hanging out trading skulls.
Yours went to McGruff now, too.
Yeah, that was extremely.
I put it in your head now that it's McGruff.
I'm also losing my voice a little slightly,
which might be, I think, so high as my best Pro Shops
enthusiasm.
So I'll try to wind it down and take a little break there.
But got to get a little time to, OK, well,
just really quick.
What's really confusing is you're
looking at a, if you don't know any of this history,
and you're just like, we're also like,
it's not exactly in downtown Memphis, but close.
It's part of the skyline.
It's very close.
And so if you don't know what's going on in the city,
you're looking at one of the biggest pyramids on Earth.
You go, what is it, though?
And then you drive up, and you see Bass Pro Shops.
Huh?
And then under that, separate sign on the outside,
the Ducks Unlimited Water Fowling Heritage
Center.
This only gets us further into the weeds,
which apparently is just a very nice museum about ducks.
I don't think there's anything to fear.
The word heritage makes me worry that something weird
is going on.
But I don't think so.
It's just a further, like, OK, maybe
I've heard of Bass Pro Shops, but you're
throwing a lot of words at me.
You asked Ducks Unlimited as a brand I should be familiar with.
Ducks Unlimited is one of the conservation charities
they work with.
Oh.
OK.
Well, and that's what I've read, too, is that, like, sure,
yeah, does this all, like, you know, yeah, it's hunting.
You know, will animals die because of this place?
Of course.
But there's also conservation involved in the, you know,
where there's hunting, there's conservation,
said something I read.
Somebody please point to me in a lot of ways why that's wrong.
I'm just trying to make heads or tails out of this.
We're not outdoor guys.
For Jason, kind of.
The logic, I think, with, like, in Pennsylvania and Jersey,
when they would give out hunting licenses, some seasons
I think they would give out more, cut the prices,
if there was too much of a certain species,
if it was overrunning the area and upsetting the ecosystem.
Oh, OK.
So there's, like, there's some sense of balance.
Well, and also, like, there's, like,
hunters probably create the need to, like,
preserve big areas of land as nature,
which is a good thing.
Yeah.
And that leads me to one odd thing that I didn't know
was in the Best Pro Shops story, which is they bought,
sorry, I'm looking for the...
The shotgun pellets that Dick Janey blasted in the
The shotgun pellets that Dick Janey blasted into that guy.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Preserved in the Bush Janey Heritage Museum,
which is the very, very tip-top of the pyramid.
Yeah.
Never forget the best presidency.
Next to the crystal skull.
They should put that in the pavilion in Epcot.
The skull.
They're doing this.
Well, they're doing this George W. Bush painting.
Oh, the paintings, yeah.
Let's get the shotgun blast when Janey hit that guy
when he was hunting.
Was it punk shot?
Was it salt pellet?
Maybe it all melted.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe it's not there, but still, they should have
something to honor the moment.
Yeah.
Sure.
In the American pavilion.
Yeah, one of the great moments of American history.
It should really be portrayed in the...
They should cut one of those American adventure scenes
and then just put in a big scene where Dick Janey's
just going on and on, waving a gun around
next to a friend animatronic who just nods, looks around.
And then, I don't know, imagine your technology.
Maybe it's a projection mapping thing, but all of a sudden,
blam, shot in the face.
Well, you know what it should be.
Actually, you know what it should be.
They just take, at the end of the Disneyland Pirates,
the two pirates hanging on the cannon with the guns,
just take their heads off, put Janey head on one of them,
and put the other guy, the senator or whatever,
on the other, like, and then...
The other guy who I believe apologized to Dick Janey.
He said he got in the way, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, maybe it was his fault.
I don't know.
It's like when Superman apologized to Lex Luthor.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Really, good boy.
To be fair, I'm sure the other guy was a bad guy, too.
There's no way.
Well, if he's on a hunting trip with Dick Janey,
he's absolutely a bad guy.
Harry Whittington, longtime Texas GOP supporter.
Yeah, I think I found my answer.
Well, which allow me to say that Johnny Morris,
the CEO of this chain, who is now worth $9.6 billion,
big Trump donor.
What?
Yeah, I'm sorry to say.
Look, I'm trying to say these things.
I don't know.
It's tough.
Again, fake rocks.
What do you want me to do?
I'm excited.
Kid had fun.
He doesn't know.
He's not following the donations of Johnny Morris.
Yeah, and plus, if you go in there,
and you shed a few liberal tears in there,
that's sticking it to them.
Yeah, and the coffee mugs that say that.
My mere presence is defiance.
If Casey and JoJo was playing in a Bass Pro Shop,
you would shed some of your liberal tears on the floor,
and it would contaminate that space.
That's getting back at them.
I think I have a fun note to end on.
I have several things, but feel free to end.
Oh, please.
No, I thought you were reaching for the end.
I mean, I sort of am, but yeah.
I got shopping results looking up Bass Pro Shops,
and I didn't know that Fishing Rods, Fishing Poles had unique names.
You sound like you're setting up a talk show.
Johnny Carson.
These fishing poles have some very unique names.
In the segment we call Weird Fishing Poles.
Bass Pro Shops, Johnny Morris, we've established the founder.
Johnny Morris Signature Series, Made in USA, spinning rod.
Okay, pretty normal.
Then we get Bass Pro Shops Crappy Max Quick Tip, spinning combo.
Crappy Max?
That's C-R-A-P-P-I-E.
Crappy Max, M-A-X-X.
So I don't know what a Crappy Max is, but I think my favorite name I came across,
Bass Pro Shops Crank and Stick, crank bait casting rod.
Crank and?
An or N, like an N in place of an N.
C-R-A-N-K-I-N apostrophe crank and stick.
Crank and stick.
That's a little bit of a...
Pretty nasty.
Innuendo, is it not?
That's a big nasty.
Is it a place that stands up for values and yet sells a crank and stick in a place where
children can go?
Yeah, what about that?
Sickos.
Yeah, we should make a TikTok about it.
Jason, you do it.
Crappy Max, crank and stick.
First of all, they're swearing in front of our kids.
Secondly, they're teaching them what cranking with a stick is.
I had to explain to my son what a gun is or run away like a coward from explaining what
it is.
And then I almost had to...
If I'd taken one wrong turn and I had to tell him about a crank and stick.
Daddy, what's a crank and stick?
I'm not prepared for that.
God, I hate this place.
So much work.
Not until you're a teenager and we never discuss it.
Okay, just quick other things.
Actually, just before I leave the pyramid, Wall Burger's Wild, you mentioned.
There was a full other restaurant called Uncle Buck's something or other, and it became
a Wall Burger's, but a sub-Wall Burger's brand called Wall Burger's Wild.
What does Wall Burger's Wild mean?
I went to find out and I started looking at a menu and I saw almost nothing different.
I got confused.
And yeah, it's in kind of a tin check sort of vibe, art direction, fantastic.
But it's still like the green logo, which is just very urban, kind of doesn't tell you
anything.
So what's Wall Burger's Wild?
According to the initial press release, it's that they're going to have Gator Bites and
Venison Chili and a Bison Burger.
And that makes it a separate restaurant, Wall Burger's Wild.
So you can eat Gator at a...
When it's designated wild, it means that they have Gator and Venison.
Well, let me now correct you and say it meant that they had that because according to someone
who wrote an article recently, they still have the Venison and the Bison and they do
not have Gator Bites anymore.
No Gator Bites.
And they were Gator.
That wasn't just a cute little thing to call French fries.
They were Gator and that's the thing you can...
I remember having that on a Disney World trip one time, but I think it didn't make sense
to keep...
They were starting to eye the Gators who live in the store and maybe realizing there's a
conflict of interest there.
Do you think Mark Wahlberg himself had to test the Gator Bites before they were approved
for Wall Burger's Wild?
If I'm to believe what I learned from his reality show, Wall Street, in which he was
like ushered at all times, he's on a motorcycle filming a movie, then he's ushered to a tent
where he's trying a burger and then going like, it's a little dry.
I think we got to work on that.
We got to prey on that.
Let's hollow up and figure out how we can get a little more juice in that burger.
All right, but that's fine.
You keep at it, bro.
And then he's like calling the boring gym he works for.
So I don't know.
I actually kind of do think that Wahlberg at least performatively had to try the Gator
Bites.
Yeah, yeah.
No, but taking Gator Bites off the menu, if he had been there, it wouldn't have gone
down like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why didn't you lube me in on this?
Donnie.
Why are we calling a Wall Burger's Wild if we don't...
Two things doesn't make it wild.
It doesn't make any sense.
And then they punch each other and then hug it out.
Yeah.
I made you bleed because I love you.
Donnie dances it out, though, not punching.
Donnie, did you download the Catholic app?
You got to download the prey app.
Are you preyed up?
Are you staying preyed up?
I looked at your phone.
You don't have Hallow on there.
That hurts me.
If I can't trust my brother to have Hallow?
All right, anyway, confusing thing.
But where I was starting to go with it all is in talking about,
well, at least there's land conservation as a part of it.
And here is one of the big things that Bass Pro Shops is doing
that they have in Arkansas bought 400 acres of land,
which they are turning into a private nature reserve.
That's kind of boring, what I'm telling you, right?
Ultimately, they're building an eight.
Because I'm like, oh, they're buying a bunch of land.
What's that for?
And then Parker said, no, it's just going to be a nice looking place.
What they have purchased is the land on which existed,
a place called Dogpatch USA.
Whoa.
They bought it.
They own that now.
Wow.
Yes.
From that guy?
Or was it too removed?
I forget.
I'd have to go back and remember the history.
In my head, and I know this is wrong, in my head,
it was all given as a settlement to that guy who almost got decapitated,
a teen who almost got decapitated by a taut wire on an ATV.
And he owned it like when Cartman owned the water park or whatever.
Yeah.
And they gave him like 5,000 bucks.
Yeah, sure.
I don't want this shitty place.
But no, I don't know who they bought it from.
I know that, I did some math, 400 acres is Magic Kingdom plus Epcot.
That's how much land that is.
And they bought it for $1.2 million.
$1.2 million in Los Angeles is like, well, you get the one bathroom for that.
You might get a second bedroom maybe for the $1.2 million.
They bought 400 acres of all of Dogpatch USA.
And they also probably have the phone number of someone who can comb through
all those acres and find all the tripwires and garret ropes
and all this stuff that would kill you.
And bear traps.
And bear bags.
Bear bags, bear traps.
Bear bags full of explosives.
Electric eels.
They know the wilderness survival experts who can de-weaponize.
Yeah, of course.
Yes.
Land mines filled with paint for particularly violent,
totally off-the-grid paintball games that could actually blow your arm off,
beat or no.
Right.
They were packed enough.
Have you heard from your friend that owned Dogpatch,
that was getting Dogpatch off the ground?
What's the guy's name again?
My friend?
I'm forgetting that I had a friend.
Sorry, he's not your friend.
He's not your friend.
But what's the guy's name that owned the place and was losing his mind?
Oh, that guy.
Oh, my God.
It's been so long, I don't remember, who did the little variety shows.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, man, I loved him.
What is his name?
I know, I can't think of his name.
Oh, right.
The Puppet Man?
Well, yeah, he did the Puppets.
The Down and Dogpatch.
The Down and Dogpatch was a song I liked.
Yes.
I thought that was pretty good.
Yeah.
But he had like sort of, he had like...
From Heritage USA.
Wait, we said it earlier.
That's why I had a weird feeling about the word heritage.
Right.
These are ancient episodes of this place.
I know, and I can't think of the name of people anymore.
What's his name?
God, what a psycho.
I love that guy.
He would pop up here and there.
Hubble.
No, David Hare.
David Hare, because...
He named the character Hubble Hare.
Right, Hubble Hare was a rabbit character.
Well, wasn't he...
I haven't looked into him in a while.
Wasn't he like on the run?
He was like...
Yes, right, right.
Last I heard, he was on the lamb.
Yes.
But that was a long time ago.
And there were these long YouTube videos of him like rambling about like problems with
things, and like he was really like, oh, just like really strung out and stressed.
He might have just like changed identity, moved to Ecuador.
Just like a god on a boat didn't ask where it was going.
Yes.
It's very possible.
How do I search for him?
David Hare, con man.
David Hare.
Last I remind you, I believe he was also very litigious.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Very litigious man.
Well, we did a main feed years ago.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, that was behind the page.
Yeah, I'm sure we said way worse things there.
Anyway, incredible just way that that all ties together.
It's great.
And you know what?
I trust them more to.
And I think what they're going to do is just like make it a nice looking.
They're calling it Marble Falls Nature Park.
And it is just a place with like caverns.
And I think they're going to do I think they're going to do a great job.
Johnny Morris, who I am simultaneously praising and noting that he is a big donor to the Trump
campaign.
I can't speak to that.
But I know all I want is that among all of the nice rocks, real rocks there, you put
some fake ones and maybe all maybe we'll all be back down in dog patch.
I'm upset by this plan.
I thought he should reopen dog patch.
Yeah, I think we need more little Abner stuff.
You need more little Abner.
You need to meet the shmoo.
He has enough money.
He could generically engineer a shmoo.
He should genetically engineer the actual shmoo into reality.
Jason's correct.
He could do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, they can 3D print species.
That's right.
So I'm mad.
I'm upset that dog patch is dead forever.
Yeah.
So we can go shmoo hunting.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I hope, you know, I really would like to make it to Tennessee and maybe that can
be in my future family travels.
But just on the way out the door, I know it's a long one, but I did want to tease this because
there are these there's other little things that I want to talk about the fun stuff I've
got to do with the family.
But there's going to be a big one.
So on the topic of family travels that will spin into future episodes, this is a little
thing that was brought up in an episode a couple of months ago.
And I just just to cut to the chase, I'm thrilled to announce that after some amazing intervention
from my pal Joe Carnegie, the Gerdner's are going to Casa Benita.
Wow, it's happening.
We've got a date and it's soon.
And we are due.
I complained about it in an episode because I realized it's like a yearlong waitlist.
Right.
And my friend Joe realized that he he's like, oh, yes, of course.
And I'm on the waitlist.
What?
Oh, God, I wish I knew.
And suddenly he's like, you know what?
I don't think I'm going to be able to go.
I can't just drop everything.
Whoa.
And I never canceled my flight.
So I like I just like, I don't know, I just got a feeling.
I think.
And so suddenly I didn't fully pull out or lose hope.
And I get to take his flight.
You mean even?
No, not not taking his flight.
No.
OK.
That's what I had booked a flight and then gone.
All right now to get my Casa Benita reservations.
Oh, God.
Wow.
It is an incredible process.
You know, you know, and our our friend Landon was was trying to work some angles for me,
which kept hope going for me.
It was a whole crazy thing.
Wow.
But anyway, that's we're now we're on the way.
That's exciting.
Soon.
So I will soon be able to come back to the PTR audience and report on Casa Benita.
Whoa.
Legendary Denver restaurant.
Jason is sneezing up a storm.
Violent sneezes.
So excited.
And yeah.
So that episode to come and we can only hope that no character actors die earlier in the
day.
We might overtake.
Of that being recorded.
Gene Ackman better stay alive.
Oh, God.
I guess he's more of a leading man.
The epitome of PTR curse there.
Why?
Because he's in his mid 90s.
Yeah.
It is because he's we say like he's fine.
He's fine.
Anyway, so very excited about that.
And as for this, you survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon to your club three or you
can get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
I'll also I'll just try to like be on the hunt for David Hare, too, unless he's untrackable,
unless he has unless he adopted a new name and a new backstory, found the most shady
Arkansas relocation program.
Maybe he got he got Ria say he's living as an animal.
He's that's possible.
He's in a bear suit.
They're going to find him when they're clearing the area.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Oh, is that a bear?
Watch out, everybody.
Wait, hang on.
I think I see a zipper.
He's like that a man who's been posing as a bear for five years to avoid the feds.
Wasn't there someone in Japan doing that is like living like a dog or something like
for like permit.
I don't know if it's permanent, but like for a while living as a dog in a dog suit.
So maybe he's doing the same thing or maybe he's he's assumed the identity of Hubble
hair.
Yes.
Now he's just a big rabbit.
And it's not even it's not even a disguise to him.
He has become him.
This is my I am become Hubble hair.
This is my skin, he says, when somebody like pulls at it.
Oh, he says, oh, please don't pull my skin.
Right.
Well, good luck finding him.
World record breaking rabbit.
The biggest rabbit there ever was worthy of best pressure.