FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast may contain
Jason-sized booby traps
grown men begging people
half their age to see
robots they like
and moose hot wife fantasies
Jordan Morris returns
to loudly clack with us
about mostly defunct robot
restaurant chain Bullwinkles
on Podcast The Ride
Intro Music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
where today's topic is about
to trigger a live Vince
McMahon meme
I'll get you guys in
I'm Scott Gardner, this is Mike Carlson, there's Jason Sheridan
in case you all want to do this with me
you know what I mean
and our guest Jordan too
let's jump around
I'll do a better intro
and if I'm thinking of the same meme it is a four panel meme
anyway so having a fourth guy
that makes sense
I will do the captions on the side
and if you remember
yes it's the four panels
and you'll see what I'm doing here
so today's topic
kids pizza restaurant
with arcade
and go karts
an animatronic
band
themed after
mostly forgotten characters from
the 1960s
red eyes
galaxy brain
that was the thought
process as this topic
was presented to us
by now
here returning to the show
with a proper intro
a friend of the show who hasn't been on in far too long
from Jordan Jesse Goh
and from the new writer of the new graphic novel
youth group available for pre-order now
Jordan Morris
hello
thanks for having me back
thank you, thank you for
suggesting it, bringing this topic up
bowl winkles restaurant
slash play place
arcade it's one of the
show room
theatrical experience
fountain shows
dancing water show what don't they have
in some cases go karts I don't know
we will figure out
the full breadth of what they had
and this is a topic that has been
on the podcast
the right to do list I'd say for a very long time
I remember making some list of like
we're starting the second gate this could be a good one
it came up in a club three poll
at some point but with Jordan it has
to be main feed and you know what
it needed to be main feed
this has main feed written all over
yes it's a really
strong
area and a really good
brand I mean it's one of those
where actually last night
Jordan we were hanging out at the same birthday party
after you left somebody
asked what are you doing on podcast the ride soon
I said Jordan is coming on to talk about
bullwinkles and one person at the table
had no idea what I was talking about and the other
two were like whoa
wow they were they did live
they did live Vince Mcmahon's
I think it really depends on what part of the country
you're in but if you were near one of these
and went to one of these I think
it's a big deal yeah yeah
so a lot of Southern California locations
Pacific Northwest and
Canada that was those were all that was
bullwinkles country okay okay yes
and like maybe some stray
ones in like
wait I have a list of kind of the odd
where they were
yeah you know Myrtle
Beach Pensacola Florida
Grand Rapids Michigan
but other than that mainly
California and then
Jeddah Saudi Arabia
I didn't expect
don't know not even one like
not Europe not Asia
but Saudi Arabia
really weird
the strangest spottiest brand
and just as we're getting basics
out this is based
on the Rocky
and Bullwinkle world of characters
the J Ward world
of characters the show
that aired in various names
but basically Rocky and Bullwinkle
from 1959 to 1964
but this chain was mainly
an 80s
phenomenon
that went away yeah there's a commercial
for it I think this dates it pretty well
there's a commercial for it where
Bullwinkle is making fax machine
jokes did you guys see this
well I have a commercial loaded up
but it's not this one I should have loaded up this one
it's like you know he's saying
it's something like the
narrator who he would always banter with in
the cartoons was saying like you know
Bullwinkle just give me the fax
and then Bullwinkle says something about a fax
machine he's like okay what about this new
technology so
I think this this this chain was
at its height around the time that
fax machine jokes were hot
and I think it's
that commercial or it might be another one
with a tagline as
really good food
and that's it
really good food and not even
like plus games
plus like no it just says that
and then it shows some of the ugliest
pictures of like bar
food you've ever seen
the original draft was good food
and then someone's like can we plus this up
yeah yeah like Cameron
writing the dollar sign
by aliens
James Cameron came in
wrote really we've hired James Cameron
to consult on this pizza
I mean they have bumper boats you can't tell me
James Cameron doesn't love bumper boats
that's a good question yeah he oh he must
have at some time James
James we have to eat dinner
before you get I see why
boots does he have you're saying
I had two bites mom I had two bites
do you think he has a
bumper boat thing on his like estate
wherever he lives I bet he has
bumpers on his submarine oh yeah
so he can bump other millionaires in their submarines
while they're exploring various
trenches making documentaries that's just a
fun thing though it's just a fun little
love tap it is of course yeah
bumper it's not aggressive
they're just a brazen
just a little bit of a brazen
one thing I do want to say
I don't think we've said it yet
still around
kind of ish sort of
not fully not but you know what
more than I thought
a little more than I thought
let's let me let me throw it
to Jordan because also you can you can
speak from experience at the level of
still around sure but
personal experience
with bullwinkles why did you
bring this to the table with us yeah
I loved Bullwinkle as a kid
loved the cartoons loved those old
J Ward shorts I think they
were you know rerunning in Saturday
morning TV when we were kids and
loved them loved that they were a little self-aware
he talks to the narrator he talks to the
camera I love this made me feel smart
clever
meta yeah exactly and more
than yeah yeah he was the
Deadpool of his day
just as twisted as the
Merc with the Mouth
what are those yeah
so yeah
and we would go to Bullwinkles it was like a
special treat I believe we went to the
oh boy we went to the Anaheim Bullwinkles
I believe and it was special for a lot
of reasons I loved the animatronics
show obviously gorgeous animatronics some of my
favorite characters I think it was the first place
I had waffle fries
and it was the first place I played Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles Turtles in Time well
one of the greatest arcade games ever made
two milestones for a childhood
sure yeah yeah and then
anything else out about Turtles in Time
while Turtles in Time has the
floor because I'm not super
familiar with it actually I know that first
arcade game so much more
yes you know what actually in the arcades I
ended up playing the first one more there wasn't a good
Turtles in Time cabinet near me
growing up that's my memory
Turtles in Time was like a rare white
elk like you see it
every now and then like in an
arcade you didn't go to a full moon
the mist would roll in
next morning it'd be gone
staying at a hotel
I feel like you know
family hotels I wonder
if it's still the same but
family hotels I was always
like alright there is an arcade
what's in here what's the scrap
bag going to be and every now and then
it would be Turtles in Time
it was hard to find in our area I don't
know why you know what Mike you couldn't
have had it all you know
Sean Berg you had everything
you had every experimental restaurant
you had Caesar land
it would be unfair if you had
your way and I think it made you a
stronger kid and a stronger adult
today well thank you thank you for saying
that I do believe that
I will say
screaming at Mike like you had a happy
childhood
concepts
you got to have
the McDLT before any of us
sold a hot dog at the McDonald's
it would feel
I still remember what McPizza
tastes like you had it for six
months longer they I will
say what I do own is though from
the game Turtles in Time is figures of
Pirate Bebop and Rocksteady
because they go back in time and they're pirates
you have those
I have some
Turtles in Time figures and I have the
whole collection now like on PS5
the whole Turtle collection
of all the games and the arcade games
so I've played it I've honestly played it more
recently than I have when I was younger
but it's a cool game superior to the
original I think because they traveled through time
for sure and that made it better
yes yeah yeah I agree
self explanatory
how do you top that okay well that's
all that's all major stuff
and that's I feel like I've been to
that one post
ghost bullwinkle
ization yeah because
this that's a kind of an interesting thing about
the brand is that they are
the remnants of them
are around a lot it's not like
they all closed and
just became you know
orphanages
or smelting facilities
Mr. Beast's ghost kitchens
so many of like you
especially in Southern California
and kind of south of Los Angeles
if you see a
mini golf course a batting cage
these kinds of things it may well
have been a bullwinkles in the 80s
and 90s yeah I think what
happened is that most of them became boomers
or at least the one
in upland California became
boomers yeah okay
the chain where everything is
themed like a CBS procedural I don't know
where everybody
can buy a house for 30,000 bucks
gotta be something there
that's good
it's a place where you can go to be the incredibly
cocky about every decision you've ever made
right yes it's a place to go to be radicalized
by YouTube
maybe that's the one
have a few houses
yeah but I guess what's happening in upland
California now very exciting
they are transitioning from a boomers
back to a bullwinkle so I went
to the upland one and they are slowly
adding in the bullwinkle theming
wow because I guess the community
demanded it wow geez
yeah that's what I feel like I think I watched
like a little local news report about
that I read an article and about
how it's always
still bullwinkles to them right they
can put this boomers brand this
listeners might have a boomers near
you it's kind of a nothing
compared to if you
grew up with those characters you
see bullwinkles on a restaurant
you have your associations
with these characters and if not him then that
whole world and Peabody and Sherman
and Dudley Do-Right and all of them there's so
many things that you're you're flashing to
and then there's this oddly
generic bland boomers
branding
it's the Westfield of
mini-golf courses I don't
know what it Connets I don't
like Jason I think you were saying
before we started it's just it's
mysterious what does it mean
there's never any justification
who is Boomer you know
yes going through the website
like god damn it the theme
seems to be families enjoying themselves
like what
is there nothing weird in this sauce
that's not enough
what is it we're all part of
we're all experiencing Boomer should be a seal
with the roller blades I don't know
something yes that's all it would take
it could look like shit it could be the worst
clipart graphic design
ever but give us a character
we're simple men yeah we just want a dumb
half-assed even character
an ostrich with a surfboard under
his wing I don't know
put any animal in a navy outfit
and we're on board
it doesn't matter what it is
yeah eyepatch peg leg
yeah yeah oh that's pirate
that's mythology and that's a backstory
he had to get them from somewhere
he had accidents somehow
possum scrubbing the deck
with a toothbrush you're a monk
that'd be great
being punished by Captain Boomer
what did he do did he mouth off
did he try to take
control of the ship this is
great it's like with very little
organics a mutiny now he's
peeling potatoes yeah get that
in there I don't care oh children
like go karts still
fuck off
yes but what world are they
existing in what is the mythology
yeah
it's it's it's bland it's nothing
I never liked any graphic design I've ever
seen from the boomers camp the facilities
themselves sure
I'll take any family
fun center these have been a really nice part
of having
having a child and remembering that like
oh these are four children and not you
to go to and bitch about lack
of characters yes yeah yeah yeah oh that's
right I'm watching sincere smiles
as I take a kid around an arcade
great beer tap selection
losers
I did go to the upland one that is
you know in betwixt the boomers
betwixt the boomers and the bullwinkles
with a friend who brought his kids and they
had a blast they really had fun
so yeah so yeah
the power of these places you know
they they stick around for a reason kids love
them yeah yeah the um and it's cool
the community specifically held on to
bullwinkles and that it would have meant something to them
this now your trip to the upland location
is no small feat because that's like
an hour from where you live
correct something like yeah I'm a little
you know I'm in Altadena so I'm freeway close
so yeah maybe
maybe 40 minutes so not a huge
pain in the butt but decently
long did you feel
did it feel like a little
insane or a little risky are you
like what am I doing am I going
to go there and find something
rinky dink or not for
me was it I don't know was
there any worry in the transit
to bullwinkles fall a little far away Scott
tons tons of worry
I'm glad I just said my friend who came with me
Jesse Thorne who I co-host my podcast
friends you go with he came and he brought his
brought his wife and kids everybody had a great time
the kids actually knew the
bullwinkle characters and were bummed
that there wasn't more bullwinkles
characters yes because it seems like
hope for the future generations oh yeah yeah that's
well that's something I've wondered is like
because I don't I guess I
could see that this started no
oh hang on it doesn't make sense I was going to say
I could see why this started going away
because the characters were
not really passed to future generations but they
made that movie they
started going extinct in 2002
but that movie where with weirdly
Robert De Niro
as a character he wasn't even one of the main
characters Jason Alexander is fearless
leader fearless leader right
coded villain ah
yeah oh that's so that's why he did there's
depth here there's like you know
can I play a likable villain
a challenge like any De Niro
role would have there was a big
resurgence of all that stuff especially in the 90s
because it was everywhere and it was
cool I feel like to like it even too
but I feel like the movie
is like the nail in the coffin for
its resurgence maybe that's like
the pinnacle of like hey we're
it's going to be here forever they flew
too close to the sun yes I was so
excited I think we went to see that
movie opening weekend and I was
so disappointed by it because
in the 90s
Rockin' Bo Winkle aired on both Nickelodeon
and Nick at Night
that hadn't really happened
it happened maybe once before
but like I just
thought that was so cool
and I loved those characters and then
they show up at Islands of Adventure
well that's what I was going to say is like they were so
popular that they were like
will you Dudley Do-Right is going
to be the basis for one of the big major
rides here yes there's a new
theme park in 1999
and we're putting a lot
into Dudley Do-Right he's going to have his splash
mountain here yeah it's pretty wild
just before we get too far away
from the Rockin' Bo Winkle movie
the writer of that film Kenneth Lonergan
who wrote Manchester by the Sea and
Gangs of New York you can
count on me wow oh my
god really he's like the sole
credited screenwriter on that that's
insane you said his name and I'm
like I know that name yeah
I'm also like
okay your eye went to that
I'm on the Wikipedia looking at the cast
which is Robert De Niro
Rene Russo
Randy Quaid who's
wild now but was an Oscar
nominee that you know Billy
Crystal Jonathan Winters John
Goodman Jeanine Garofalo
Padgett Brewster Carl Reiner
Whoopi Goldberg James
Rebhorn great character actor
James Rebhorn Kenan and
Kel are in it wow
I didn't know that Piper Parabit
it's an insane kit
this is a Robert De Niro
Billy Crystal John
Goodman vehicle from the writer
of Manchester by the Sea that
I don't think I've ever heard anyone
like yeah I've never heard a good
opinion about it I mean I love the characters
and I still haven't seen the movie
I'm more curious now having
been boning up on Rockin' Bo Winkle
Has anyone seen this movie?
I haven't. The 1992
Boris and Natasha movie
starring Dave Thomas. This always
confused me. I would see this VHS
case and like huh
what are you talking about but it's not a cartoon
no it's not a cartoon. Boy
I haven't thought about that probably since
I was seven years old in the video store. 1992
Boris and Natasha
movie it's not
Who's Natasha? Natasha is
hold on Sally Kellerman
Oh my god
from MASH? Yes
Hot Lips from MASH
is Natasha
Andrea Martin. Wait John Travolta
is in this film? Andrea Martin yeah
I've not seen it
Written by Mr. Julia
Louis Dreyfus Brad Hall
Wow John Candy's in it
Wow so they're tapping
into the SCTV like
the most quality group of people and
yet this did not come to well
Oh my god maybe this was just not meant
to
it was not meant to be translated
to any even half live action
maybe. This feels like a movie
that's a trick for podcast
like I'm gonna like get a copy from the
library or find it streaming on
Amazon and a big net
will be put up
like it's a trap. Is somebody
trying to eliminate podcasters?
No just trying to like
I don't know eliminate or
So the scheme is they planted a fake movie
from 1992 about Boris
and Natasha which they know you like
so they know okay any day now
he's coming into the library cause Jason's not paying
for that movie he's renting that for free
I'm not doing that $3 right here
I'm with you Jason
I've
sworn up and down
how great the Burbank library's
movie collection is but also
I'm looking it up. Buena Vista branch?
Of course Buena Vista branch
Great branch great branch
I got Cobra there the other day
Oh cool!
Blue ray? No regular DVD
It's literally a blue ray selection but how are they expected
to have a lot? I understand
They do have a lot of blue rays but
I pulled up the Just Watch
page which is my
choice of
finding where stuff is streaming
and it's really only available to rent on
Amazon. Oh okay
interesting. I don't
By the way I don't think this is at the
library. I mean this will
really be the test of the Burbank library
right if it has it. I just don't think this
doesn't seem like one that needs to be preserved
for future generations. They don't have any VHS
left at the library do they? I bet they did
have it on VHS that's a very good
point. Well I think they also
get a lot from the studios
from like Universal
Warner Brothers I think donates a lot
I see. Okay well
I don't know if that's worth further
investigation. Jason
will maybe do it. I'm already on it
I think it like it speaks to like how
beloved the characters were
that all of these people
said yes to these things and we haven't even mentioned
the Brendan Fraser
in Georgia the Jungle movies. These guys
are part of this averse as well
Two forays
and those are like beloved movies
Voice of Rocky June forays
yes but this is I'm saying
two forays by
Brendan that's crazy
that's really strange. Nobody thought
were they like no I think
it helps I think he proved that he
fits in the tone. I say
do give him a second one but they were
wrong right because Dudley Do-Right is not
particularly well regarded. I think people like
Georgia the Jungle they don't really like Dudley Do-Right
am I wrong? That feels right I don't feel like
anyone ever talks about Dudley Do-Right. I mean
I'm a Do-Right head so
you're asking
the wrong guy I love him
Is that true? Okay so you do
yeah you are into those characters
and they were present at the
restaurant. Yeah absolutely you got a
Snidely Whiplash when you come in he's behind
bars it's an animatronic he's like
in the lobby before
the main show that's really nuts
that's so cool. You know I was even
stoked to see Tennessee Tuxedo and Chumlee
in the restaurant as a kid. Don Adams
Don Adams very exciting
I was on a path of
discovery I saw a website that was talking
about Tennessee I already don't
remember. I can't believe you've been doing the show
for this long and this is the first time Tennessee Tuxedo
and Chumlee are coming up. You're here for
PTR history
no I don't yeah despite the Don Adams
no because they were in the
animatronic band in maybe just one
of the locations and then I'm like
what's going Chumlee and
because I've never heard of Chumlee I'm like
what? Chumlee is a walrus with
human hands?
What does that mean? And he does he does the dumb
guy voice from cartoons
oh I know Chumlee
now that you do that thank you
boosts from Archie the
yeah the ones like a
bean pole and the ones where you go big
you know the ones got a hat
but they were only they were not
regularly in the band
because if we haven't said
this it's an animatronic band
a la Chuck E Cheese
but it's all of these characters
not necessarily
contained it's the whole J
Wardiverse all
playing instruments all in like
it's kind of a folksy
I would say that the vibe
is this like Pacific Northwest
Cedar
Lodge where like
totem poles would be in play
and it's a very totem pole
vibe on the stage where
all the locations
had at least
bare minimum Rocky and Bullwinkle
animatronics and
one of them's playing a jug and the
other one's playing a like a
boxy wood guitar
it's a bare jamboree vibe
it's not completely the same
vibe but it's close it's close some family
yeah kind of a kind of a
hee haw structure to the show
you know a little one
liner and now a song
kind of vaudevillie
yeah yeah so you at least got that
like if nothing else Rocky and Bullwinkle
on banjo Rocky on like a fiddle
then maybe
the band is expanding depending on
the ambition of the restaurant you might have
underdog not really said till now
on saxophone
Boris and Natasha
factor in I love this
that Boris and Natasha are
the like masthead
on the top it's great sort of
like a little totem pole
so they are represented in more
of a carved in wood fashion
but they do come to life
and interject and are sort of the
Statler and Waldorf
or maybe or more the
the moose
and buffalo on the wall
Buff Max and
Melvin
Melvin yeah there you go
so you know they're
taking cues from the way Disney
is doing things but not exactly
one to one it's not a
full rip off but then I think only
in Santa Clara the first location
do you have Tennessee Tuxedo
Chumlee Hoppity Hooper
who is a frog who plays the harmonica
and maybe more locations
had Tudor Turtle on the drums
not fully sure about
full Tudor
the one had Dudley
oh and big thing I'm
forgetting yes Dudley Do-Right
is like the side
stage like Big Al
and they play Big Al
similar beats to Big Al
where he's like the one
encountering problems
where his cue is wrong
or they close the curtain
on him on purpose
they play into the Dudley
bumbling
but of course underdog as
his famous saxophone
yes of course
we all remember when underdog would wail on the
sax
I found this picture of him
I don't know
in this picture he looks like he's
smoking a damn bong
in this picture
cause it just looks
kind of strange
you should be excited
this should be like hell yeah
look dream blunt rotation
me and underdog
and no one else
underdog
Chumlee
Chumlee and Tennessee
Tuxedo can come too
and of course his alter ego shoeshine
boy right
that's right yeah
that was underdog Clark Kent
yeah I watched the first underdog
short because
one thing about
Bullwinkles the audio of this
is strangely well preserved
on YouTube yeah I know
there are you can kind of listen
to the sketches over stills of the
restaurant yes
and yeah there's only some video
of the animatronics but yeah all this audio seems
to have been uploaded
and I'd forgotten underdog's voice
cause I feel like
in the bullwinkles audio he sounds
very droopy dog
but Wally Cox
the voice of underdog did not do
droopy dog different
it was Dawes Butler
right no no that was
Huckleberry Hound sorry
Dawes Butler was Huckleberry Hound
sorry I'll cut this out so
this is the good stuff
but yeah it does seem like
most of the voice actors are doing their
voices for the restaurant
it is Rocky and Bullwinkle which I think
they yeah they insisted on
Jordan when you were a kid did you
where did this fall in sort of the hierarchy
of robot restaurants was this maybe your
number one or were you a Chucky guy
I mean Chucky was fine we had a close
Chucky you know I'm not anti
Chucky but this was
a special trip this was a good report card
this was like
cousins are in town and we want to show
those cousins a good time
yeah I love this
we probably only went a handful of times
but when I
maybe it was on the way to Vegas
driving by Upland
and seeing from the freeway the like coming
soon bullwinkles just a
flood of nostalgia
I'm like oh my god bullwinkles
and yeah it was really like magical
I had to pull over and go to sleep
calm down just calm down
just sleep it off sleep it off
the nostalgia wave and yeah and then like
watching so there's a lot of like corporate
videos that are on YouTube for this place
like you can watch their like
kind of pitch video and like you know
taking around the basics of the yes
each bullwinkles location and yeah and I
you know and I don't want to like live in the past
I know nostalgia can be toxic
but like watching the videos of this
place in the like late eighties I'm like
look what they took from us
this was beautiful
the wait staff were all dressed like Mounties
I mean it's gorgeous
and it's well it's in that like
cause I just my fuzzy baby
brain first five years of my life
I just remember so much pleasant
calming brown
like and I never I never went to a
bullwinkles but anywhere that I
liked anywhere that made me feel really
comfortable in the first years of my life had some
calm brown or perhaps
bricks or those like you know kind of the
orange or red bricks that malls
used to have or they kind of blandify
all the malls and then like
wood carved signs with
complementary colors to brown
and kind of like a in a reddish
orange a fiery orange
and this place I just I'm watching
this I think the same corporate video as you
and like god I would have
locked onto this place like everything I was
after in the late eighties
this this had it all aesthetically
it is such a bummer
it is so is anything close to that
like pleasing wise now is it just
from your baby brain or do you think there is
something to that it feels like there is
but maybe it's just a trick
yeah I don't know if there was anything inherent
to the two eighties
brown yeah but I
it's certainly something I'm fixated on
it's you know it's the family
ties aesthetic scheme
that's really what I musically
and visually and font wise
I chase it I want them as much of that
around as possible sure
but I don't know if it actually is
superior calm at most a lot of people
might see that kind of thing and think like
stodgy out of date grandma
but cigarette staining
yeah well that's good yeah you're
right that's what happened I'm sure there was smoking
a lot in every bowling goal
probably reeked of cigarettes
they didn't even bring it up in the video
because bringing it up makes it a thing it wasn't
a thing you know it's an establishment
you smoke and yeah there was a
you know so there's the showroom for the
kids but there's also like what is it called
it is called Dudley's Den
for the parents to retreat to and it's a little
more calm
what if we kissed at Dudley's
Den as the
meme goes I mean the Dudley's Den is kind
of beautiful I bet you know I bet a lot of
this was a lot of key parties got negotiated
in Dudley's Den take your nail
to Dudley's Den
this was because this was
the old Chuck E Cheese as well they had
the parents rooms right and so that's
what Dolly Dimples would play
or say hippopotamus right or the
beach bowser or the beach bowser so they did have
rooms for the parents I think
those are gone I mean they're the
rooms exist but yeah
they put more games in them
thumbs down or whatever but it doesn't feel like
catering there should be nothing in here where mom and
dad gonna go to connect
I have recently started showing my daughter
Chuck E Cheese videos including the new ones
Chuck E and me and my friends and stuff and she does
a little of the dance and she does munch and stuff
and it's very adorable
then I will put on she's gonna get into bowling
for soup Mike and it's okay
it's okay if that starts you on the popcorn
if you don't think that's what Mike's fishing for
if that starts you on the train that's fine
another guy who does Chuck E
Cheese now the bowling for soup
Jared Reddick or something
don't ask us Mike
I follow him
I follow him on Instagram
but then I do put on some of the old stuff
see how she responds to it
and it is just for
parents that is what's interesting about it
is the new stuff is like oh you get a little funny
little joke once in a while but the old stuff is
just written for parents Chuck E is smoking
a cigar he's unnerving
he insults Jasper he calls him like a
dimwit or something there are jokes
it's just like a bunch of stuff
we're gonna do a show oh
sounds good
it actually isn't
written like Bullwinkles is
Bullwinkles has the cleverness
but I guess I just mean
there's no gentleness to be like
what do kids like it's just
adult characters like behaving
badly in front of children
and then there's other
rooms more for parents
that show that I'm talking about is
for everyone for the kids there's a screening
room where they just would show the ice
store
stag films
dad could go and jack off
with his buddies
the kids could go in the ball pit
and cry
and cry yes yeah yeah
of course yeah that's always part of it
they're showing nudist documentaries at Chuck E Cheese
naked some of the robots are naked back there
take a gander
I like when you look
I wanna show off cause like we do our
Chuck E voice sometimes and he is an insane
caricature but when I'm watching
I'm like it's not that far off
he's crazy this cigar
smoking mouse or rat is crazy
he's a crazy drunk
yeah he's real he's incredibly
so it's funny though to just
be like oh yeah they cater like everything's
too catered to children now
the problem today the problem is
put it back in the bowler and the
tucks and tails he wears they do it
together we got it video with the pup
the new puppets which is one of the famous Chuck E songs
yeah George you have any idea with that
that was rushed by they do it together we got it
so anyway
I'm using context
listen I can use context clues
I listen to the show I know
it's like their big hit it's the big Chuck E hit
I'm prepared to argue about goo goo dolls if it comes to it
together we got it is their black balloon
but they do
put the little puppet Chuck E
in like a little vest and bolt
like they do give you a little
of the old outfit but it's not the full
cigar or whatever
well here let's you know
we need to discuss your specific visit
more Jordan but really quick I mean I figured
this would be the episode to talk about it
it is relevant
that my little boy
just turned four and
we locked into
I think the best place to possibly
do a birthday party which is
the one Chuck E cheese that kept the robot
which is in Northridge California
it happens to be my childhood one
which is really strange that became
the only one that kept the robots
and could we have done it at any
at much closer Chuck E Cheese
more convenience to more
Pasadena Chuck E Cheese
yes so there are so many
but no we chose
robots over convenience
and no
regrets about that but here's how this
played out is that
we get there and first of all
rope dropping a Chuck E Cheese
is really something where we're arriving
slightly before 10am when it opens
to which is the start of our party
and in doing so we are watching the
employees be dropped off by their
parents the employees who
are half our age
checking in for work and then
yes the 17 year old
maybe who's like the party host
who like okay so we've got this
and we can do lemonade for the kids and here's
the wristbands and is there anything else you guys
need and my
wife's like no no no we're great
everything's wonderful actually there is
something there is something why is the why is
the curtain closed
we chose this one because it is the one with
the robot so if you were just
at some point if you could open the curtains
and it took so and she's like
oh yeah sure yeah
but I don't think it's a request she's
getting a lot and I
don't think it was going to naturally
happen without me asking for it
so it did happen
me and
my same aged friends
all lit up about
it and no one else
the parents my parents didn't like it
the children did not like it
the music was so quiet
the clacking was twice as loud
as the music and then the
curtain closed after one song
and it was clear that that was all they were prepared
to do then I asked
to do could we do one more
because there were some late comers
can we see them one more time even less
interest from the children this time then
Michael shows up
we were late that baby's sleep schedule was
effed up after she came back from San Diego
with Lindsay and so we were
late so Scott
says okay for the show you have to
ask for it and he is polite enough
to ask the 17 year old
for the third time
the third time in two hours
she's a party host that's what
I know and by the way
the great
most friendly the most accommodating
with all of the things that mattered
this was the smoothest I by the way
recommend to parents Chuck E. Cheese birthday
is great the pizza got better
it is a very well
run operation the only
sticking point was that I think we're
the only psycho parents who've asked to see
these robots in the recent past so
yeah you get there late enough that we're like
we're still there but we're clearing out and even
the birthday boys losing patience and I'm like
are you eating pizza at 10am?
I did
yeah I didn't think I would
but then like I don't know it's in front of me
and their pizza did get better so yeah
I'm having 10.45 pizza
why not? Being so late also it's
a stressful thing because I'm like Lindsay you have to
remember this is the one with the robot like I'm explaining
like
does she have to eat breakfast in the chair
can't she eat it on the road
like there are things I'm trying
to get like
toss a gogurt in the car seat and let's get up there
millennial in the bedroom
oh North
they've announced that Northridge is the only place
they're actually giving the robots so like there's a whole thing going on
there and I was like oh well it's really
too late to go but I would really like to see
these robots
in none of this factors
my family or my son
that is there's none of that in your
let's hurry
this is about munch let's be clear
this is about munch well the reason it's not even coming into
it's because like because we were just like they're
going to leave yes
we want to go to this but they won't be there
if we are this late so I'm like
yes but you understand the robots are there
the robots are what we
need to even if we're even if
we show up and everyone is gone the robots
will be there we can still watch the robots
alone of course
so your daughter can shift
around and try to
leave while you watch the robots of course
Lindsay perhaps the same
probably she didn't
say that to be nice to me but probably
what Scott yeah she actually
the party host did go back
and fired up it's just it's run
on a Windows XP machine
with a floppy disk drive
so that's how long it took
to get started yeah that's a 20 minute
startup and then she closed it so it had to
happen again yeah so Scott asks
the 17 year old and she said oh yeah
we'll do it we'll do it she goes back there did you ask twice
or once I think I did once
and then I said we gotta go
if you want it you gotta ask
and I actually don't know how things played out
for you and that's why I'm bringing it up on the show
so what happened is yes again we were
so late everybody left and we were at
Chuck E. Cheese in Northridge which is
not the quickest place to go to no
no no so I was like well we're here we
let's enjoy it so
I asked her again I said oh excuse
me is there any way
we could see the robots she goes
oh yeah yeah oh I forgot I'll check on her
she says something like that and I go okay
so we're like lingering and then like
our my daughter wants
to go do other things she doesn't want to sit by these
tables she wants to go investigate where all the other kids
are and I'm just like what I'm like
but we're gonna miss the show if
it starts it's gonna start any minute
so we're lingering too long I see
her one more time
and I ask again and she says sort
of the similar like a similar thing
and at that point I go
this is not happening
we are not seeing the show
so we're like walking around like
through the games and and and my daughter's
climbing on things and doing stuff or whatever
I'm just keep my eye on it I'm like
the show ain't happening it's not happening
just listen for clacking just have your
ears open for the clacking of
eyes opening and closing
is like yeah
she's like you want to ask again
I go I'm not asking the 17 year old
again I'm too old
to be asking again
that's okay this is our punishment
for being late
so you left the Chuck E. Cheese disappointed
the child
at a ball not only did I leave
the Chuck E. Cheese disappointed but I am
85% sure that this Chuck E. Cheese
gave my daughter her first
awful cold of her life
no no no
oh no no no
she's fine now
it was bound to happen because we don't do
oh you said she's been sick oh no
Mike no look I would I would only
say it on Mike because it's funny for the
audience I would not have put it on
it's not your fault no you're not I know you're not
it's not your fault we don't do too much
she's got to go indoors someday
right we stay out a lot we don't do
a ton with her she's had a little mini cold
but this was a fucking cold
well we have now looped back
around to a kind of cold you can only
get from a ball pit right so funny
that the Chuck E. Cheese is likely
the culprit
in less than an hour well we oh my
well I'm sorry no no apology
I'm sorry for being so late we have
yeah you should have been there in the hour when there wasn't
cold going around all of the 11
o'clock hour children were fine
yeah of course yes one of those
nooners showed up and
coughed all over your daughter
we have now looped around to why
at least my parents did
not like places like this
it was actually funny being the cause
of my parents going back
for the first time in 35
years and they were like
ugh they were like shuddering
at it were you guys no okay
you were saying about Bullwinkles Jordan
that this was a family like
no we like it this is a yeah
I wonder if I was to ask my mom how she felt
about our trips to Bullwinkles if she would be
like oh yeah I fucking hated that place
but yeah to me it's a fun
family memory and I think I don't
remember any like Bullwinkles meltdowns
or anything like that yeah I think we had
a good time well here's I think
what might be
this might be the theory
because I think we've already discussed some things that might be more
quality about Bullwinkles
than Chuck E Cheese
but when I brought it up
last night the consensus
was actually
good food and actually good animatronics
there was a sense of like it's a little
it was actually a little more Disney
level do you agree with that yeah I mean I think
I think that the you know you get to see
the menus in those corporate videos
and you know not just pizza but
deep dish and thin crust
salad bar that
themed after W.D. Wright's girlfriend
was her name Nell
Nell gets the salad bar
Nell's salad bar and they
also say that the salad bar has
Mousselaneous dressing
which is a good pun but it sounds
disgusting like you know
what's in the dressing though right it's not
I get it
it's not just different liquids that were in this facility
to begin with it's like
Thousand Island French and like
Catalina right
whatever gross 90s dressing
I do not remember what is in it
creamy Italian the 90s
were a big decade
there will be a nearly empty
bottle of oil and red wine
vinegar that's kind
of gross
that same video goes
right into a breakdown of the pizzas
which I have queued up right now
this is well wait it might announce
itself let's see I don't know if they
mention the heroic sandwiches
it must be do rights
I don't know let me
I think the underdog has the sandwich
oh you're right yes yeah hard to read but yeah you're right
underdogs heroic sandwiches and then
this little pizza explanation
just to keep an ear out
Bo Winkle's traditional thin crust
pizzas are called Dudley Do Wright's
pizza the house specials
are appropriately named mother load pizza
garden cash pizza
and our unique pizza of the sea
we need to talk for a minute about
and I'll make it bigger for you guys to look at
strange phrases
to begin with mother load
okay you know tons of toppings
I get that garden
cash I got nothing
on this I don't know what
C A C H E we should say
computer cash yeah right
what does that mean I think
cash is like it's like a
it's like a stash yeah a stash
of like vegetables I think
vegetables I think that's what they're saying
so like mother it just implies a lot that's what they're
saying I think so yeah garden cash
I just I only think of that in computer
terms and then put next to garden
electronics and garden
jam together a strange
phrase is cash cash A I mean
I think about like when they talk about oh I found a weapons
cash yeah maybe that's an RPG
term or something and I think it just means
to be like a that's like going
golden eye right or something yeah
it's like health and ammo and
armor and vegetables and vegetables
and veggies well garden cash
could be in one of those E.T. botanicus
video games where you have to like put fertilizer
in soil is that in the corporate
video yeah what is the
title of that yeah I'll recommend it
to listeners Bullwinkles family
food and fun restaurant tour
Santa Clara California
yeah um which well here I'll
say my Santa Clara thoughts but just to go
straight into the next one which is
pizza of the sea
this is the most nauseating
looking pizza I up until
I trust everybody that this pizza was pretty
good in general but
looking at this pizza with little
canned shrimp all over
it the pinkest shrimps you've ever
seen oh no no no
tiniest no
nubbins oh nubbins
even like
maybe somewhere today
could pull off little shrimps I just
don't trust this
is 1980s
canned shrimp pizza I'm concerned
you and I shared a fishy pizza
a few days ago Scott oh sure
but anchovy
and they had capers as
well what if they had little
shrimps on that pizza though is it
I'd be fine there
yeah that was a good place yeah
but little I'm just what you're saying that the
you can't imagine little shrimps
being good in the 80s I feel like I've watched
Mike eat a pizza with little
shrimps but again today
as long as if it's anywhere
but City Walk fine have at it Mike
but what's the place on Sunset
that has that is that what I've had no I had a
tuna pizza at that place we were
at an Italian restaurant in Manhattan
and I remember you just
getting like a tuna pizza
and it's forever stuck in my mind
was it an Italian salad how did the tuna
how did the tuna present it
one day in Manhattan
I guess we were a couple times
only once or twice
that's why it sticks out in my mind
what was that establishment in
Manhattan I don't remember
Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville
anyway I'm
disturbed I just don't
but people said the food was good
I do but that has
to be where the I'm I'm only
doing cheese there I'm not I'm not doing pizza
the sea I'm out on pizza the sea
yeah I think I remember the fried chicken and specifically
the waffle fries to me were a big a big
memory that was a big revelation to me
never seen that form factor of fry
before yeah yeah
and I think yeah maybe the fried chicken looks
kind of good in those videos and
it does yeah yeah I don't
know I'm very brown you know it's a very
it's a better way the
more the more legitimate way that
they used to do I feel like fried chicken was generally
done with more care
in the 70s and 80s right could be
wrong I feel like the affection people
have is probably does indicate maybe
the food was a tier above a
Chuck E Cheese I think so
I don't think it's pure because even
if it sure nostalgia could be blinding
you to it but it but it's people who remember
that the Chuck E Cheese food was
shitty right and this was
better I have to quickly share
a not so good
association about that very same one
the Anaheim one which was shared
to me last night
by our pal Ryan Perez
okay yeah we grew up in
the same Ryan and I have a lot we're you know
the same age and grew up in the
you know Orange County we have a lot of like
shared memories I don't think we knew each other as kids
but like oh yeah we went to the same movie theaters
a lot of the same like malls and stuff so yeah
I wouldn't be surprised if Ryan had been to
the same one yeah yeah I was kind of surprised
if he had fond Bullwinkle's memories too except for
I think well I think he had been to the Anaheim one
they had a fun time
then they
he was ten years old they
went to a softball
game for his older
sister and she got a
terrible injury during the game
and they had to go straight to an
Anaheim hospital and in the
window there was a perfect view
of the Bullwinkles
and he is ten years old and not
only is he pining for well I'd rather
be there than here he's like
you know he doesn't understand the stakes
he doesn't know hospitals and what's
happening at this point he's like get a cast on the arm
and let's get over to Bullwinkles yeah
well that's what I thought it was more of that vibe but instead
it was that his concern for his sister
was so heavy he's like we're
in a hospital that means she's gonna die
I'm gonna lose my sister
today and he's which did not happen
spoiler but he's in this
room sadly looking at the window
and like once my half family was happy
we had Bullwinkles and now
we are here at Death's Door
we will not all leave together
as a family this is a very
haunting memory
innocence of childhood and now he's
on the threshold
as he passed into double digit age
leaving
childish things behind yeah isn't
that a beautiful sad little memory
and I do picture like
in the way he painted it there's
nothing in that window view except
for that Bullwinkles there's not one
other street light or
gas station children frolicking with their
alive siblings
fun cause she didn't die
I love you sister
I love that you're alive mainly
yes ah
anyway
yeah such a poignant little picture
that Anaheim zone seemed
exceedingly close to
the fries where I got to have that video
played for a couple days before
it was closed so I'm looking at that
and what you got to experience as a kid like oh man
I wish that had been my go to
childhood place I'm also looking at the Santa
Clara location because Santa Clara
is the same neck of the woods as
San Jose
Campbell where I have this
I've had now two deliriously
fun trips the one initially
inspired by wanting to go to a car wash
that looks like an old river boat
and then I went back and had an equally fun
time with my family at the world's
largest Chuck E Cheese which is
up there and I'm like this area
had the theme park great America when it
was good
they had the world's largest Chuck E Cheese
this one and then at the same
maybe the primary
the world's first Bullwinkles the one from
the video which looks pristine and awesome
and then at the same intersection
there was one of those places
this one was called
pizza and pipes have we ever
talked on the show about
yeah I've never yes I
know a lot of people who have very fond memories
of pizza and pipes the pipe organ
themed pizza restaurant
before animatronics I can't believe you
don't know about this I would have assumed you have a
depth of knowledge about it
I thought you meant pipes
like tunnels this is the one
that got absorbed by discovery zone
leaps and bounds
leaps and bounds yeah that's
the pipe I was picturing another treasured
Schomburg thing yeah we had leaps and bounds
and discovery zone
and a Mickey
cafe or whatever
but anyways
no
pipes and pizza
was like this is the
precursor before they figured out animatronics
your pizza entertainment was
watching a guy play the mighty
Wurlitzer organ a giant
Wurlitzer
that would have scored silent
films and these are still around
a little bit I'm so intrigued by this
concept and that they do still
exist where's the nearest one
I don't know I think there's one like
in the like three
counties surrounding us but I
don't know for sure okay I think this
is a tradition people have tried to keep up
and the word the big organ feels
so stodgy put next
to pizza which feels like what
you know right should be
you know pizza and liver sorry
pipes and liver or pipes
and crab
pipes and pancetta I found
an SF gate article
about it is was the full name
at some point Capin's
the Capin's galley pizza
and pipes it might be a different one
yeah there might be because I think there are a number
of these I don't think it is one chain
this many pizzerias could afford
the mighty Wurlitzer
organ from baseball
games don't play it dumb Jason
now you were the phantom of the opera that haunted
the area
underneath the pizza and pipes
hey man play cool
sorry sorry to blow up your spot
swinging in the rafters
sometimes stray pizza would fall into one of
the pipes wow Bloomberg.com
remember the dining fad of
pizza and pipes
I feel like am I are these the
last moments of my life is
this just like a funny gag
that I am a man my brain
the funniest gag is telling you there was a place
called pizza and pipes right before you die
you're on an operating
you got hit by a car on the way over
you're on the operating table
pizza and Wurlitzer that's pretty funny
that's so weird and then you go
to the library to learn more about it and somebody
catches you with a big net
God catches him with a big net
well a net is a
what's that? God catches you with a big net
what is death but God's net
I was going to say
God catches us all eventually
you can't escape the net
I was going to say a net a non-lethal
weapon
I guess if God is wielding it
to take you to the great beyond
he shanks you a couple times while you're in there
stabbed you with a box cutter
oh man what a dirty death
God
so he does it
there feels like there's all these different
historians for the different places
like Chuck E. Cheese stuff is pretty well
documented you can get sound files
of all the characters and this is pretty well
documented I wish there was one person
that literally was like I will tell you all
the different places in America
you can go right now
and there's an organ show
there's a robot still working
I want this comprehensive list
of everything that's still there
a map or a GeoCity site that's
sure it does not have to look fancy
I guess there is one
Bullwinkles that still has
some of the animatronics it's in Seattle
there's a haunted
looking man that does a tour of it on YouTube
and you know it's in
the pizza room and it's just Rocky
and Bullwinkle and then a Boris and Natasha
above them
and you know they're
old the clacking is deafening
you cannot hear what they're saying because it's
all clacking when they blink
also and he had to make a point of
can you turn this on for me
watch this video absolutely
there is like you can see a
frustrated stone teenager
having to cater to this YouTuber
one of those weirdos is here
turn a big crank for a while
or something it feels hard
feels like there's a reason they don't want to do it
the restaurant was closed that
day too the family
fun center and the snack bar he says
in the video the restaurant was closed
but they're going to open the show
so they had to open up an entire area
not to get back into it
if you're going to tell me that this is where
the residency is happening for
as much as make believe ban
I just couldn't believe why close
the curtain as we all know
the Chuck E. Cheese tradition is
you leave them all just creepily
blinking and shifting back and forth
no matter what all day every day
frozen in rigor mortis
you know?
if one loses an eyeball that's it
there's no replacements for that
Five Nights at Freddy's was a big hit
which is why it happened
a terrible movie
you would think these places would be having
a resurgence because of that
you would think that they would be returning
robots right? I don't know
I think it's the only thing that saved the one
and they still seem ashamed
by it
I was actually expecting a little more of something like
oh it's like showcasing the fact
that they have the robots but it is like
don't ask us about what's behind the curtain
I mean I personally I'm
just glad they took out the robots before they made
them woke right?
I don't think I could handle
a woke rockian
that Chuck E. Cheese in the picture frame
with the cigar was not woke
he was not
that's when comedy was existing
that Chuck E. Cheese could drop a hard R
nobody
it's me just kidding
I'm just telling
the truth here
the radical left won't let us do our show
I'm saying a hard
A through Z
I'm saying all the words
I'm using old time
racial slurs no one's used since the 20s
you have to look it up in a dictionary
just real quick I found
a post
Jordan is sitting next to me
and I think I can see it a little
the Valley
relics museum
is a great it has a lot of old San
Fernando Valley like
neon signs and stuff
that's preserved and statues
big boys you know
so they post a picture
oh wow a number of years ago
and I think this is a sign
it says pipe and pizza in recita
and it's just captioned
sweet woman candy
and it's just this
woman seated she must have been the
organ player at a pipe and pizza
it looks like a really cheap album cover
but she's like zazzy
look at her
sparkly red dress
for a Kristen Wiig movie
take that to Kristen Wiig's production
company
I've got four words for you
sweet woman candy
would my hair be very
teased?
the most Kristen
it's got a Palm Beach look
or Palm Royale look like
kids play
1970s pizza and pipes here
Bay Area pizza chain
wow this is wild
I assume we had talked about it
we maybe did I have to forget some things
we talked about so it's possible I forgot
70s and 80s
craze
in this Bloomberg story
predating the robot technology
they say craze too
as if it was like the nation couldn't stop
enjoying pizza and pipes
it seems like everyone is driving to places where pipes are
I think if you were like a Wurlitzer player
you like cursed the robot
oh so this is what people want
I mean you know they're not
they're not playing live you realize that
look at their hands their hands don't even touch the instruments
oh you like all these rock and roll songs
nobody wants to hear camp town races anymore
classic no one wants to hear Buffalo Gal
well that's
Jason says this every episode
I'd say this yeah
that's when music was real before
Sinatra ruined it
the Oregon man got fired from the Cincinnati Reds
he got fired from pipes and pizza
where it's supposed to go there's only so many
minor leg teens that can afford an Oregon
yeah the world going
woke to Jason equals less pipe organs
around every turn
less cigarettes indoors and less pipe organs
those were the days
when you could say the hard R
anytime you wanted to listen to
Little Brown Jug
the star spangled
banner
we'd all stand and salute and then go back to our
pizza bites I've said this before
I've said it about I think Pirates of the Caribbean
I've said it about Womp Hoppers
I would pay $100 to $200 to smoke a
cigarette on like Pirates while it's
going or in Womp Hoppers
does everybody have a dream place they would just smoke a cigarette
if they could go back in time
it's on my mind
but of course it's just because it's
right in front of me but what's the Dudley Room
again that Dudley's
Den yeah
I can't not say that
put in front of me I don't smoke and I don't
like it but I would smoke on those two places
but I would smoke in Dudley's Den as well
I have about four cigarettes a year and I love
all four of them
that's where I was for a little bit
but go back in time and where
would you like to smoke those for
with current California regulations
I would say my hotel or my
apartment building balcony yeah
okay that's fun but is there
any robots
the
the robots
at the Seattle location that you can see
in this YouTube tour yeah
I don't know where the Natasha came
from but
someone said
let's have something for dad
I see I see
assuming that dad loves giant tits
because this
Natasha that they have is out of
control she's a bosomy lady
yes like it just might be a repainted
Elvira like
and Bullwinkle's package too
Bullwinkle you can tell he's got like a half chub
in there
as long as his nose yes
the exact same shape but in his pants
right just as thick
hey Bullwinkle I didn't know you had three legs
oh Bullwinkle's stupid and
hung
that's why I never wear shorts Rock
no need for me to learn anything
that's not my value
to the world I haven't eaten pussy in my life
I don't have to
gee Rocky should still learn
it's the only way some women can come
which I had a better
Rocky pretty good
that's pretty good
we'll pitch it up in post that's what you do
in context with Bullwinkle too
yeah people you understand
you have the character down
thank you yeah
of the audio files we've talked about
I think my favorite
which is I saw
it named
just after what the song
the chorus is a song
underdog sings called country is
dumb
did anyone watch it you were telling me about
this already yeah
he sings a song called country
is like mad
they play too much country music
country music yeah like as a band
because there's no chance
for him to play his saxophone
that's pretty clever
so that's kind of clever yeah
but yeah watching the old
underdog cartoons I was like man yeah
he really does sound like
droopy dog and like the
switch from shoeshine boy to
underdog I thought
oh but he sounds like superman
no it is slightly
pitched down
but yeah country is dumb
underdog is
mad at country music because there's not
enough saxophone
it's a very good little routine
for him that's good
yeah I don't know
I mean I didn't dive too much into the show scene
I just know that like the
animatronics do seem
of higher quality
seems like those ones are
clacking around and I'm not saying that just because
of that Natasha revelation I think
overall even forgetting
that no these
bullwinkles are so charming
I don't know just like
and they seem like I don't know
range of motion they look just like the cartoons
it is not the scare
factor that the Chuck E. Cheese ones
admittedly have even still like
Chuck E. Cheese now is very I don't want to
it's not like an apple store aesthetic or anything
but it is very much a cleaner
very bright like
establishment but I do feel like
it's always there's always been a weird
vibe in a Chuck E. Cheese
like they've never matched any sort of like
Disney feeling going into this place
which is what they kind of want
yes it's like always was like dim
and weird and it smelled like
diapers and pizza and like
it still kind of smells like diapers
and pizza they have like
you know when you start
Pirates of the Caribbean there's the like
cricket noises
I think those are getting piped through bullwinkles
when the band's not on you have to like
chirping crickets
even from the pictures and
just a little of the audio yeah you just get
the sense that like whether
dad or mom can articulate it they
feel like this is like a
higher end establishment
it's just it's such a massive
build I don't know if they all
were I don't know if Anaheim was but like
this Santa Clara one they show
because the Northridge Chuck E. Cheese that
I brought you to that is just
like a you know that's I feel
like someday it's just going to be a Verizon store
that is not like the biggest low ceilings
very true do you know why they picked that
one to house the robots the last
robots I don't I don't actually
it was it was among the first maybe
they made the calculation that like
LA hipsters are going to be the most
likely to want to go
to but I don't I don't actually but isn't
it basically that they just have been decommissioning
these things for years and years and
that was one of the only places left and they just decided
maybe more than you'd think
but they I think they had they were about
to start getting rid and there might be stray ones
where they haven't I think there are all the
ones okay but in my mind and maybe this is wrong
they just looked at a list of ten places
that still had the full band and when
they'll say Northridge gets to keep them
arbitrarily maybe I could be I'm sure
there's some reasoning but close their eyes pointed
at a map yeah doesn't feel like where do our
neighbors not mind clacking yeah
I'm fascinated
Chuck E. Cheese is still in business
it must be some real estate scam or something
like it must be like well they own the
buildings or something but they are
like it is working for
no it does you know it does and they figured out
what they want now and like my child
has a good time despite not knowing
any mythology and not having
layers upon layers of
bizarre
maybe not natural affinity
for half thought out mythology
he just he likes to play
basketball in there imagine
that yeah family fun centers
I think are still
money makers yeah it just
feels like a place that should have gone out like
the pandemic should have taken it down right
it feels like just something should have taken this down
but it didn't well there could be
I feel like JCPenney's is
having I saw them having money
trouble or
other do I think JCPenney's is
in trouble no no what I'm saying is there might be
another wave of bankruptcies
I feel like oh I don't think
Chuck is on the chopping block if that's what you're saying
if Biden gets re-elected yes
folks Penny's is gone
where are men going to buy
slacks
slacks and quarter zips well the Sears is already
back at the mall and the Burbank so
is it is Sears
back we've talked about it before we'll do a
quick there's a Sears
that all of a sudden is reopened in Burbank
wild yes what a great
thing to happen in Burbank ask anybody in there
about it they don't know they don't know why it
opened again I don't know why I work here
article where they called Sears and said why did you open
the store again and they said we don't really want to talk about
it wow maybe a soft launch
for an all new Sears
the basic answer might just be
like we kind of like paid for rent or
we own the part of the bill I don't know and
it's just not it's like we'll make a
few dollars opening it huh
it has its own free will now it opened
itself back up it's possible the Sears
opened itself back up but over here yeah
over in Burbank yes the
Sears just opened one day again after being
closed that's wild yeah
so anything can anything can
come back stay on your toes well including
Bullwinkles which the let's make sure to
carve out some time to talk about your specific
visit because this is not like
you know we're not seeing animatronics again
let's make no mistake there but there
is like what is the extent of the
Bullwinkle feeling at this upland
location so basically nothing
some signage
some like employees only
signage where you'll see a character
they have a mini two mini golf
courses an outdoor and an indoor the indoor
is weirdly fairy tale themed
uh and
and charmingly janky I should say if you
like a kind of a mini golf
course clearly painted by the teens that work
there oh great yeah and like a big
crescent moon hanging in there maybe I saw
you know you might be right yeah
okay so yeah really
yeah fun and then a little
arcade with a lot of
like big versions
of cell phone games you got a
fruit ninja you got a
Angry Birds restaurant
not open yet but they have a
little on a tiny tv
by where you get the like you
know play cards you can
see a
like 3d
kind of model
of what it's going to look like
I would say the 3d is lawnmower man
quality
PS1 cutscene
uh and it looks like
they're gonna add so the arcade is gonna be
badenov's oh cool
Boris Badenov
last name of the character and
it looks like you know there's gonna be some maybe
a guy in a bullwinkle suit walking around
and this is wishful
thinking I don't know that this is gonna happen
probably not but one of the rooms does
look like you can kind
of see there's a tarp over it but you can see
the walls and it looks lodge
themed I have to hope that
maybe they're trying to bring back a lodge
and maybe it would have
animatronics in it I don't know
this is you know
that's something okay at the very least
you know if it's I mean like
Berry Tales came back at nots
but you do at least sometimes at least
appreciate whoever's doing
a new version of something or trying to sneak
in like an Epcot reference into
a line like that is something
you're giving me a little morsel thank you
for that at the very least if they're just
trying to pay homage to the old room
at Bullwinkle's I appreciate that
but hopefully what you're saying
I would like it if they did
what some other
locations did a promotion
an after dark promotion
21 and up
it's Bullwinkle's head and it says after dark
and this just happened
that was but days ago
and it's like
psychedelic poster
drop acid at Bullwinkle's
is that what they're
implying do some drugs
maybe the animatronics cuss
you turn Dudley's dead into a chill out room
these are strong just take half
see how you feel
alright just make sure to test
the drugs you're taking
know your dealer right Bullwinkle
there's Narcan
in Dudley's
the teens have Narcan if someone OD's
on fentanyl
the teens at our place
were kind of great I should say this is kind
of just a fun you know themed
entertainment moment
Jesse's kids loved it
and when they were looking to you know
cash in their tickets one of the
kids only had 30 tickets and I think
30 tickets all you get is candy
kid doesn't like candy
she wanted the samurai swords
which were 3000 tickets
fucking stoned
teenager just gave her the samurai
swords
I think you can
bargain with those kids
okay okay if they're
in a good mood
if they're paranoid and upset
then maybe not
they'll like spray
you with mace or something
okay so
vibes are good good teens
good teen jobs
so yeah I hope that whatever the redesign
they're doing that you know hopefully
that's a lot more theming some of the
old Bullwinkle stuff but yeah the vibes in there were
great everybody was having a really fun time and I
think it'll be even more fun when it
you know is back to its back to private
events 21 and up there you go
millennial crowd going looking
for second
spouses
wanting to add to their
polycule
Gen Z and Gen Alpha get it
during the day but it's
time for us
it's time to look for our second spouse
it's polycule night at
Bullwinkle
starter marriages
Natasha if you're looking to fluid bond
with another primary
come to Bullwinkle
find someone else to come in
Chumlee is taken
Chumlee is
exclusive with
Tennessee tuxedo they are monogamous
they're kind of square
he has human hands you gotta lock him
down
human hands and a dumb guy voice
on the adults night though you have to plant
a security guard in front of that Natasha
because
trying to rip her off the wall
a sad dad who can't find
his second spouse yeah who hasn't had
Bollie in a couple of years
she said this was an Ilter Tarkin
worse than Natasha
when's Natasha losing that top
I've been
tipping her I wanted to buy her a nice
meal I was told the food was really
good I thought she'd like that
I bought her Klondike fried
chicken
I paid her $500
for a private dance
she just stood there
I got a cache of vegetables over here
she implied they would be touching
I hope they can restore the feeling that's all
I hope yeah yeah yes no this is
clearly this is the vibe
of this establishment
turn to Bullwinkles feel something
feel something Bullwinkles
well I break from the numbness
I feel like we
said it all I mean toss in anything
on the way out the door but otherwise
there was some crossover from
Chuck E Cheese actually sorry my phone went
gone but they used a voice talent
that did oh yeah
that is the real voices and also you know what's
cool is that Snidely Whiplash and
I think maybe other characters were Cory
Burton who is has
universally taken over as Snidely
Whiplash like in the new shorts
or any new iterations of
it in Dudley Dewright's Ripsaw
Falls the voice of the Disney
parking lot tram is like
in this and many other media like
taking over the old Hans
Conreid characters I believe
Helen Henny's voice is also
she did voices here you know
I just want to say it felt good for an episode where we've
talked about Cumming several times it felt good
to get back onto our solid
ground of saying the name Hans Conreid
and Helen Henny
now we're back
some nice names
so somebody who was like wagging
their finger at the show up in tone all goes well
now I like it now I like what they're
saying again and the voice actor of
of Cumley is oh shit no
they're writing their letters again
they're taking pens and paper
to express their disapproval
I thought this was a clean show
they say they're good boys
I have a name as well the guy
who started this David L. Brown
at some point he got the license
and he toured
a stage show called Bullwinkle's
Call of the Wild show
which included an
original character Bullwinkle's
girlfriend Moonbeam
I have not been able
to find anything on the original
character Bullwinkle's
girlfriend Moonbeam so
if there are any Moonbeam heads out there
you haven't even found a photo of Moonbeam
you've been searching
I've been searching
you went to the library to look
I got the microfiche
I got my keys out of the ball
at Bullwinkle's
you accidentally called it garden cash but then you
oh wait no microfiche
maybe my
guess knowing that and knowing the time period
I wonder if she was supposed to be like a hippie
I think she was probably a little hippie hippie
it just seems like Jason
you're going to find Moonbeam one of these days
one of these days
searching for Moonbeam
this is your six part investigative
podcast
what did she look like?
how did it work?
knowing what Bullwinkle's packing
how could any human woman
have possibly withstood
even a brief lovemaking session
with Bullwinkle
Bullwinkle's dumb and packing
they get a fuck marry kill situation
that's a fuck, that's not a marry or kill
get a marry Bullwinkle
that's why it's girlfriend not wife
give me the other two options though
because there's certainly other characters you would have to marry Bullwinkle over
I'm just saying
I think you'd marry Dudley Drew Rockie
oh
you guys started out
well I didn't know how many were in the
I don't want to kill
I don't want to kill any of the dumb
cartoon characters
I don't want to marry Rockie
Rockie's so small
it would feel weird and wrong
I would marry Mr. Peabody
he's a responsible guy
it's a little condescending
well sure
you're all marrying the dog
I guess you could marry Natasha
you've got a perfectly stacked super spy
right there
who you can spend the rest of your life with
I'm marrying the dog who travels through time
sorry
oh shit, oh you get a time machine out of the deal
god damn it you were right
I could smoke a cigarette at Wampop
I wish I'd married the dog
Dudley's taken, this is so hard
who are we going to marry
they're exclusive, they'll open up eventually I'm sure
they have to
was it for sure a human woman
I took a stab there
you could be right
but she could be a moose
but she could be any other animal too
a lot of great animals out there
badger, possum, field mouse
that's what listener
call to action
find a picture of moonbeam for us
and if you can't
make her up and put her kissing Jason in a photo
what moonbeam do you see
and then draw
I'm going to get Mr. Peabody's wedding
and then draw me trying to
take it from Bullwinkle during our long weekend
in Reno
can I add
to Jason's that Bullwinkle is standing
by and his nose has gone
limp because he's so
saddened that his girlfriend has
been taken
Bullwinkle's in the cuck chair
so yeah
preferably the real moonbeam
I'd love to see what moonbeam
looks like for real
Jane's going to kill moonbeam
she's going to be so mad when she hears this
who's this in your phone?
moonbeam?
you didn't protest enough when they
proposed you kissing
I don't know a cartoon skunk
or
in the dog house now
it wasn't about her
it was about wanting to cuck Bullwinkle
don't you see honey?
he likes it it's the only way he can get hard
no he brings his
snoot back to life
tell me I could never make you come
Jason is this show
though was it like a sesame street on ice
like what was the actual show
I think it was like costume characters I saw this
too he got this license first and then
then he had it and thought well why
not also do a Chuck E Cheese
well I have it but yeah it was dubbed characters
and the dubbed characters were wrong and in fact
the voice of Bullwinkle was the guy
who's usually the voice of Chuck E Cheese
in that sleazy era
so part of the
for them to approve the property
to do a Chuck E Cheese out of it
they said okay but it's got to be the real voices
which is why they got June Foray and Bill
Scott once again
back to this podcast
let me be clear this is a podcast
where we say names of deceased
people and not where we say filthy
words
like the C word or the
other C word
I did not
despite the
audio files being well preserved I didn't
find a lot on eBay or Depop
in terms of selling I think a lot of bars
would use the generic
name Bullwinkles too
yes I saw a lot of bars on like Yelp and stuff
a lot of matchbooks and stuff it could be matchbooks
from these restaurants
Bullwinkles also like in the early
90's again coming back around
had a promotional
tie in at Taco Bell
so there's some
Bullwinkle paper products and toys
I think from that era
okay how much
expensive?
I don't think too expensive
I don't think those are holy grails for toy
collectors I could be wrong the Taco Bell
Bullwinkle stuff I just got a picture of
Bullwinkle with a bullhorn telling
gotta leave folks
just ask for your crunch
card
gotta leave folks
it's pretty good
on the scale of Jason
voices that was pretty great
the first one or the second one
like this
that's not bad
wait here alright try it with confidence
crunch your way to
food ad
I don't know I got felt on my spot
Don Pardo
crunch your way
Bullwinkle and Rocky
we can't avoid it I try to do Mr.
Conductor
Sir Topham Hatt from the Thomas cartoons
is a voice for my son and it always ends up
in like Thomas
Gordon are you causing confusion
and delay on the railway
we just can't you know when you want to
you gotta go Pardo
musical guest bowling for soup
can you give us a Bullwinkle
and say Jordan Morris
you survived podcast the ride
Jordan Morris
well that stayed fully Pardo
but I hope it was nice anyway
to me it was Bullwinkle
to me I was being
my hero
you visualized a big full
pants bulge
as he said that
well Jordan
let's exit through the gift
let's exit through the gift shop
says I Bullwinkle
is there anything you'd like to
I'm about to get
blown up by a big circular bomb
hey I wrote a new
graphic novel that is coming out
July 16th it is called
Youth Group the artist by the great
John McGurdy
who's a great comics artist you might know
from Specter and Specters and Marvel comics
it is a YA
horror comedy about teenage
exorcists
they're all in a goofy bible study group
and they have to go out and fight demons
in Orange County
it's pretty
autobiographical for something that has a lot of
like demon fighting in it
a lot of my childhood is in there
I think if you were a bible study
kid you'll find a lot of good
hopefully familiar cringe in there
oh that sounds up my alley
yeah yeah
it was a blast to make
I think it really turned out gorgeous
if it sounds cool to you we'd love a pre-order
of course you can pick it up on January
sorry July 16th
January 6th
I'll be handing out copies at the capitol
demons like who might be
reelected
close his desk
June 6th
July 16th but also we love a pre-order
it really helps books it's huge
so if you think it's a cool concept
go to bit.ly
slash youth group book
bit.ly slash youth group book
and you can see the gorgeous cover you can see
some of Bowen's beautiful pages
and get all those pre-order links
so yeah it's a little gift you can give to yourself
in the future a book pre-order
yeah you can do that anywhere you get a book
Barnes and Noble better yet your local indie bookstore
or you can request it
at the library
call the Burbank
library Buena Vista branch
tell them you're going to want to check out
youth group when it drops on the 16th
yeah yeah and get the adventures
of Boris and Natasha
the Dave Thomas
yeah not in
the system for Burbank or LA
library
I think you're onto something I think it might have been
I'm sure it was on VHS
it probably got sold during one of those friends of the library
sales for a book in
oh that's the big ticket item
we can't sell it in the library
book stores it's considered
a carcinogen
toxic materials were used to create
the VHS groups yes
Jordan thank you book sounds great
everybody check it out
I'm going to be gross and build on your plugs
because I have a specific thing to plug
there is a show that starts
airing tonight Friday
May 3rd as you're hearing this the show is
called John Mulaney presents everybody's in LA
this is a series this is six
nights worth of a live
variety special
series of live variety specials
put together by and hosted by the great
John Mulaney and I had the awesome
opportunity to direct a couple of
the pre taped sketches for the
show those will not be on
tonight as you're hearing this but next week which is why
I'm telling you because these are live this is a
live Netflix event except
not my parts that's what the show to
bridge the so they can take a rest while they're
doing the live parts you see
I'm glad they needed those because I got to
come help so Tuesday
and Wednesday next week
May 7th and 8th I believe that's when my
sketches are airing if you see
a sketch I can't say what they are but if you see a
sketch with the our good pal and
aforementioned in this
episode Ryan Perez that one is mine
there is this show
is like crazy ambitious
and funny and writers got cut loose
to do exactly what they want to do
and it seemed everybody involved is
awesome PTR pals
Dave Ferguson and Stoney Sharp did a bunch of stuff
and I got to
so check that out next week
if you have Netflix
big if
big if you haven't sworn
it off in anger for some reason
but yeah hey I did some
fun stuff for it so thanks for letting me do
some some extra plugging
so and for piggyback look
I'm sorry I made you like share a plug
spot no no this is great I'm head
let's all plug
this is what the end of podcasts are for
plug in yeah we should
pad it out and I don't know anything
you can plug anything you want it doesn't have
to be new
web series from
over a decade ago I might be in another
sort of that web series the wrestling web series
thing I think I'm in another I filmed a scene
for it I don't know if it was cut though great
great so and Johnny loves Taya
and AEW is YouTube
I'm playing the dogs agent
and I've been pushing to try
to get on live TV because
of it in the ring oh oh
I see I don't think it's going to happen
in your picture your character from the web series
would appear yes I am
Canon
Johnny TV and Taya Valkyrie
I am their dogs agent
great in Hollywood and I am I'm trying
to pitch now that I would of course come out
to the ring with like the dog and like be on
the phone like making a deal
mid entrance or something is the
is the ultimate goal to get hit with a folding chair
is that like to you the most exciting
skewers in your head
or a pizza cutter just on the
forehead I could take the pizza cutter the forehead yes
I would take a bump is that's what you're asking yeah
I would like to take a bump yeah I don't want the dog
to get hurt but well obviously
make sure the dog won't get hurt yeah
but I would like to take a bump yeah and Jason
Sharon is planning a personal appearance at
the Burbank library Buena Vista
branch you can find him in the microfiche department
learning more about pizza
I'll add the clear green
accounting advisor
nice yeah yeah
I will be smoking in there and they're
not going to like it
but I'll slip them a 10
I'll slip them a 10
well everything's free around a library
a 10 is like a thousand
irregular people
volunteer
volunteer you have a single slide
from like a Bullwinkles live show
and you're like trying to zoom in and you're like
I think in the background that's moonbeam
is that moonbeam
is that moonbeam or just a person a woman
from the 70s
and that is that moment that ends
the first episode of your investigative podcast
yeah there's nine more and that's when you
and they are interminable
so we did not have enough
story for this they didn't need that
could have been done in one easily
nine hours and I heart said
they would break my fucking legs
if I didn't get this done
you don't want to piss off I heart
I heart's coming at you
you know and look patreon.com slash podcast
I have to say the whole thing it can be quick
sometimes they can be quick there all right
thanks Jordan that was fun
what a blast thank you
forever
this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner, Brett
Bohm, Joe Silio
and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows
on apple podcasts, spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts
keep up with the latest forever
dog news by following us on
twitter and instagram
forever dog team and liking
our page on facebook