FOREVER
DOG
Warning
In each of us, two natures
are at war. One normal,
the other mad.
Consumed by obsession with hyper
specific minutiae that's
only ever addressed by this one podcast
inscrutable to significant
others. Today
unleash your madness
with discussion of clackety sphinxes
fraudulent purchases
in Nantucket and the defunct
New York theme restaurant
Jekyll and Hyde Club
with Jekyll and Hyde graduate
James the third on podcast
The Ride
Welcome to podcast The Ride
where we know the Greenwich Village
folk scene paled in comparison
to the Greenwich Village broken
robot scene. I'm Scott
Gardner, joined by my Carlson. Hi.
Hi, yes, here. It's
so much more like
needing a documentary, really,
when you talk about the broken robot scene
in Greenwich Village. Yeah, absolutely.
Needing, you know,
let's, we can fictionalize
it. There's the documentary version.
Let's like, let's, you know, let's follow
I think like 10 part documentaries
about every performer, every
animatronic, the clackety
old sphinx. That's definitely
you know, you could show that
through the years, the evolution through the
decade. Yes, Jimmy Buffett's best friend
Frank Marshall is doing a lot of
rock and roll type documentaries lately, and I
think he might be the guy to do. That was fast.
Within first two minutes.
Just in case this is your first episode and you didn't know who Frank Marshall
was. In case, yeah, you need to be acquainted with
Frank Marshall. He's a movie producer, Indiana Jones, blah, blah, blah.
But most importantly, he was Jimmy Buffett's
best friend. And he makes a lot of rock and roll docs.
Jason Sheridan is a perfect reason to
stop talking about that. Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi, yeah. I was just
thinking, I was thinking about the
Village folk scene.
I wish there had been an episode
in the early seasons of Mad Men
where, cause Don Draper
ends up at like a coffee shop
performance venue at some point.
But he was just
surrounded by malfunctioning robots.
That would have been a great
juxtaposition.
We don't know what he got up to
after the series ended. He might have been one of
the people who funded the animatronic
movement. He might have given
Nolan Bushnull his money
to start the checky cheese chain.
You've been a hero to me.
Well, we're going to start
digging in here because what we are
doing today is a
deep dive into
a theme restaurant. Technically a theme
restaurant chain. There were
a number of them, though seemingly
briefly. I feel like most of the run
there was one.
It is called Jekyll and Hyde Club.
This was a haunted
explorers club.
If that tells you anything. If that
phrase means anything to you. It was
a weird horror themed restaurant
with a ton of animatronics, a ton of
performers, and just like a generally
creepy, spooky sort of vibe,
correct? Yeah, it's like Rainforest
Cafe if instead of a rainforest it was
a haunted house. And if
the storm went off like way
more often. It was kind of always
the storm. The storm was pummeling you with
the storminess of whatever the type
of storm it was. Many, many
storms within the bigger storm.
We talked about this place a little bit on stage
in New York, having come literally
from there to do the live show we did a couple years
ago. But that was not the exhaustive
conversation. I think this can
be that. We need more conversation
about this restaurant.
That's what the listeners demand.
But especially because I'm so
excited that we could do a deep dive here
with somebody who was
on the inside. Who worked there.
And that's why this has come about.
A former employee,
a former performer
and I made a point
of not asking too many questions so
we could find out together.
Also a
writer on the out very soon, Fairly Odd
Parents and New Wish from
Astronomy Club. He's got a kickstarter
for a comic book he's writing called Junior.
It's James the Third. Hello.
Yes.
Excited to do it. The way you were just a
deep dive. I was like, oh my god, am I
the whistleblower of the
Oh gosh, it depends.
Only you can tell us. Only you
are on the other side of those walls.
James, so
excited to have you here.
And we were emailing back
and forth about stuff to talk about a little bit.
And you had some
theme parks you were fond of that you grew up with
and some memories. But it was kind of a
like, do I have stories about this
place or do I not?
Are we trying to find the one?
My memory is, I don't
have it. It's gone now. It's fully
gone. Everything is like thin,
vague, like
blurry photographs is sort of my
entire memory of my
childhood. Okay. So this is
going to be like a psychological horror
movie where we are helping you
uncover. But
landing on this
was simply because I spent so many
days of my life there that
there has to be some
chunks of things that I can talk about.
You have to imagine. Well that was, you know, so we're
like, we got some theme parks and I was like, well you know when we
do other stuff, we do this and that, we talk about
theme restaurants sometimes. And then
you did like a full backup. Like, wait,
did you say theme restaurant?
Do you happen to know what Jekyll
and Hyde Club is? Oh, do
we? We absolutely do.
And yet never fully, fully did it.
So let's
dive in. What was the,
what are the details of your
employment at this place? When and what did you
do? So I was there
shortly after college
for me. So it would have been something like
2009,
2010, somewhere around there.
And so at the time
there were a couple locations.
One was
at
57th Street and Seventh Avenue.
That was the main location.
That's where I was. Okay. And then there was
That is a, like, they expanded
to that maybe like later in the 90s.
That is like a four story, like
kind of the most nuts one. Although I don't know
the others fully to compare it to.
Yes. And then the other one
which I think was the first one
was in, was, yeah,
was on 14th Street
or something like that.
The pub, the Jock and Hyde pub.
Oh, I didn't know that designation. Okay.
Yeah. And there's
one actor there. There's several actors
at the club. There's one actor at the
pub.
And you know,
that was something that like you looked forward
to having that opportunity of like
I just gotta chill at the pub for a little bit.
There's like a handful of
customers maybe. You know, like
it's like a, it's a lighter day there.
I mean, less
like less animatronics and stuff there too.
Okay. Which it's, and it's funny you say that
because that's the one that we got to go to. Right.
Kind of on its last legs.
And it's funny that that is the less
animatronics because it did
look, I mean, we were there to do
that, do the stuff. Yeah.
But we were also like chatting with
friends. Our mutual friend Griffin was with us.
And like it, boy is it
a place where like you start to get on to some
point and then like, hold, stop!
Arrrr! Like just
every, boy is it the loudest.
Right. And so when I say less animatronics,
I think I mean more mean
were they interactive? Could you talk to those
robots or were they just robots talking
at you? Mostly talking at us.
Yeah, yeah. And so what I meant
there's less responsibility for the actor to
to
puppet up a puppet and talk
to people. Okay.
Which is something that we're doing a lot at the club.
This is a full dimension of the place then
that I do not really, not only are you maybe
like out in a, laying a mad doctor
uniform, but you're also
behind a wall. Yes.
Being a, I don't know, a werewolf?
I feel like I saw those.
Yeah, there was a lot of different
people. There's a gargoyle,
there's a werewolf,
there's a head, there's like a two
headed doctor, there's
just a head in
a corner, I'm trying to remember
who else, but there was a bunch, every floor
had at least one, and the
main room had one that performed
to all the floors, like the gargoyle performed
to all the floors. Okay.
And stuff like that. Okay, okay.
So then you, so you're hired
as a
performer who can take
on any number
of these things? Yes. Okay.
So the thing that, the perk was
you got your equity card for
doing the job. Wow.
And so there was a lot of,
you know, there's a lot of, as an
hacker at the time, you're sort of going like, do I
want to get my equity card right now, and do I want
to get it for this? You know, cause you're not
sure what the prestige
of that is going to be. Sure.
Once you become a union actor, your price
point goes up in a way.
So it's like, you can't do the
non-union jobs, you can't do this,
that, or whatever. Oh, so you're like, am I ready
to get pulled out of things that are potential
work? Right. And that could be
good work for me, as somebody
developing as an actor.
Sure, yes. To be some guy in an eye
patch or whatever it is.
While serving pizza.
I was like excited about, like,
I was excited about doing voices, I was excited
about improv, like I was like, I was,
I, and, oh, and I should also
say, I went as a kid,
we did, I'm from Ohio, and we did
a couple trips to New York in fourth and
fifth grade, and I went as a kid and, like,
had a, it was,
I loved this place.
So then when I learned, like, I could work
here? I could,
I could, I could get in, you know, and so, yeah,
and so you're, you're essentially hired to, like,
play characters and to, like,
and to do the voices of the guys.
Gotcha, gotcha. That is the sense that I
get, is that if you were in New York,
as, yeah, like, you're
10 or 11 or 12 or something,
and you could do a birthday party
here is something that this place was
pretty ace, the seat, like,
that's, that's definitely the sense I got.
You know, I don't think we're there, I think,
I think we knew we were not there in the peak
of the existence of
the place. No.
We were the only table there
full of people, perhaps? I believe so.
I mean, it was an odd, it was like, it was a
Sunday at 3 o'clock, it was
perfectly not a meal time, so
I will give them that. But I'll also say
especially at the pie, and
and depending on when you went,
they might not have had any,
there was a Times Square location that popped up at one
point, and I don't know if 57th Street
was still going, but like, the
pub, even when I was there,
and at a time that we were sort of
there was bustling, you know,
it was always, like, quiet there. Gotcha.
The late night shifts were always, it was like
no one was there. If you actually, if you went
back to, like,
you went back to Ohio,
I, hey, I went to New York, I
did this thing. How did you describe it?
I want to make sure
we capture the, like, what this
was at its peak.
Like, what is the shorthand
that made you excited then, and that made
you excited to work there later? Yeah, I mean
what made me excited then was
like
I fully remember there's a
there's like an animatronic
of an explorer
who, like, it's like
something's coming to
to get me!
And, like, I remembered that
I remembered that moment.
I remember that moment being fun for me
as a kid. Growing up, I just
once I was, like, there and actually working, I just
called it, like, I called it, like,
Chuck E. Cheese with Explorer.
It's Chuck E. Cheese, but there's
but it's mad scientists. It's Chuck E. Cheese
but explorers. Sure, sure.
Which is so insane that that's, like
cause it's not an idea, that's not an idea that, like
this is not, like, a natural
idea to make happen, you know what I mean?
Like, it's not, like, of course
million dollar idea, but it's
also really neat.
It is just, like, you know, it's kind of
a cousin, like, there's shades of
I mean, it predates Trader Sam's
the enchanted
Tiki bar at Disneyland, or
the Adventures Club was before that
down in Disney World. It's like
a cousin of those things, but doing this in
New York definitely
and that it was working for it.
It does feel tourist trappy.
Obviously it doesn't feel like authentic
New Yorkers are gonna go here every day.
It wasn't. It was
always, it was tourists, it was
it was, drunk people
any level, you know,
from all walks of life, drunk people
would come also. So it was like kids
and, you know,
someone who was, like, drunk at 4
p.m. or whatever.
Sure, sure. I kind of didn't
know it was real. I think I first became
aware of the concept
when
The Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt started
airing and Titus
Burgess works at
a Jekyll and Hyde stand-in
kind of restaurant. Yes.
There's a specific line he says in that
that, like, I felt like we were
being read for filth where he goes
he goes, I'm
auditioning for the doctor role and I get to
have a monologue. That was exactly what it was.
It was like the premier role
you got to play was the doctor and the
doctor had the three minute
show every
it would happen every hour or
every 30 minutes or something
and, like, and once
you got to be, and we, like,
admired to the people that were, like, good at the
doctor and, like, the people that could, like, do
that well, you know.
Because you're carrying it
in a big, but aren't you in any
because any role that you have
has improv
You're on the whole time.
Yeah, every role you had to be on
the whole time, and we were, like, scrutinized
if it, like, seemed like we weren't.
Like, if it ever seemed like
you were, like, laxed or whatever.
You know. But the
doctor specifically would
have to, it would
it was like you were commanding
I had a friend
who did it, Stephen
LaFerriere is his name. He
said if I were, if I, and this
sort of answers a question that you had, he was, like,
if I were to tell my younger self, he'd
be, like, you know, I
I do eight shows
a week at a fancy
midtown Manhattan
location, you know, like, for
for several crowds of people,
you know. People from all over the world.
That's how he would describe it to his
to his younger self. Because, like, that is
there were
times where it really felt like
the quiet of
the four floors was like
was like, wow,
like, everyone's listening to the doctor.
You know. Oh, you're commanding
the entire restaurant. Yeah, you're
even if they don't have eyes on you. Wow, wow.
And was it a speech, like a completely written
speech that you'd have to do verbatim?
And you could
you could improvise around it.
But
there was, like, a speech that you had to
that you had to do. Do you remember any of it? I'm not telling you
you have to do it. So I don't remember any
of it. I remember a lot of Stevens
actually, because I watched a lot
of his. I don't remember what I what
I said, but I remember that my doctor
character. Yeah, you can tell me
if this sounds like anyone you're familiar with.
But he kind of talked like this.
Oh, okay.
Okay. Got it.
What does that sound so familiar?
Like a little bit like
and is
this a doctor? I don't know, an affinity for
jello pudding pops.
Every now and again, he would have the jello.
And
and you would and you were essentially
bringing a Frankenstein's monster
to life. So there was a lot of like life, give
it life. And
and I remember Steven doing
a line of Shakespeare. He would he would
go,
blow winds come rack. At least I'll die
with harness on my back. Shakespeare, I thank you.
Give it life.
This freaking this guy's a rock star.
Like
it truly felt like, wow,
you know, you know, young kid, fresh out of
college looking at him like, wow,
I can't believe it. You go to
the, you know, like you're starting out
at an improv theater or whatever. And like who are
the stars there at the
time? Remain stars to you
forever. So yeah,
like the, you know, the big dog doctor.
Of course.
Even if you graduate. Okay, so congrats on
graduating to doctor.
Those are in order.
Thank you. I wait a minute.
So so that's like, okay, the centerpiece
of the evening. Like there's there's all these
little shows going on, but where everybody were
the doctor that gets everybody's attention
and it's to bring a
this isn't
it's not Dr. Jekyll.
No. And so Dr. Jekyll
is there.
I think Dr. Jekyll is
who like grabbed
that explorer that I remember.
But but no one's
ever no one's playing Dr. Jekyll.
Okay. This is a big question.
Yes. Like that's the
namesake. But it all seems like
like people
he knew or associates
or people who like tell his legend.
It's an explorers
club, you know, who
and you could like you could know Dr. Jekyll
if you if your character chose to
my first character
I never knew Dr. Jekyll.
That was never something that my first character was an explorer.
He had snakes
around his neck.
His name was Colonel Plunder.
And then
you there were explorers you could play.
There were scientists
you could play. And then there were butler butler
house staff that you could play.
So I was a butler, an explorer
and a doctor. Okay. Okay.
Gotcha.
And in that way, does Colonel Plunder
come to you
or is that an existing character?
Yeah. And so
he was an existing
character. I didn't have like
an example of somebody playing
it. And he just sort of had like a
is Colonel Plunder
was his deal.
And yeah. And you and you just
had he was like he
liked adventure and was suave
and stuff like that. Okay. Sure.
I feel a little good. I was just
going to say so like Colonel Plunder
was an existing character. Yes.
Plunder was not a name I came up with.
I remember that being given to me. But you would have
maybe like guidelines or no?
Yeah. I mean the essential things were
like
you could essentially do whatever you
wanted.
I knew that he was like adventurous.
Right. You know.
Club members
so like doctors and
explorers had to carry around a drink.
And
and then that was it. You could just you just had
to go around and you had to
go up and talk to everyone at all of the
tables. And I don't remember
any of his like
log line except for that he was
his name was Plunder. Okay.
So yeah. You really could go nuts
with whatever a backstory
you wanted. Be like my wife
passed away today. Like you could really
bump people out if you wanted. You could
make them happy. Like who knows.
Yes. And some people were really good
at that also. Like I didn't
have a my guy was just
always just like trying to have
Plunder was always trying to have
fun. My butler was always like
he was kind of sniveling and
and you know like kind of you didn't
really like him. And
but like yeah
you could you could you
your story could be influenced by the
people you're talking to or the day you're having
or whatever. How would
you get evaluated
for your performance by like the owner.
Okay. Yeah. So
the there was a head
of entertainment who
was the person who like you auditioned
for and who would would
rate you. And
it
mostly had to do with like
how well your because the because the
animatronics had had prerecorded
voices. Right. So like how well are you
are you matching those and like they
shouldn't sound different once
a person you know but there's also like
there's a variety of different
people all day playing all of the different
characters they're going to sound like how they're going to sound.
And then I think I think
it really was just like guest satisfaction
like right. If
if they're what they're there they're
watching you know they're the whoever
if it's not the entertainment head of entertainment
it's whoever is like the shift captain
for that day. And they're watching the monitors
there's cameras everywhere.
So that you can like talk to
you can like actually talk to the people
you know that's what the cameras are for. But like also
it's like well you haven't seen you at
this table. You haven't done this
you haven't done that. I see.
I was just picturing like is there ever like an
undercover boss situation where somebody goes in there
and they're like Colonel Plunder do you like
exploring. And then you're
like no I don't. I don't like it.
There were
because the
the actual owner
and like people that knew the owner
were people that would also come all the time.
And you didn't know
you just didn't know.
I don't even I can't tell you what the owner's
name was or what he even looked like.
But they would be there all the
like at any point that could be some
of the people that are there. So if you were like having
a slow day and you just didn't feel like going over
to the corner but you're like I was on that floor
you're screwed
if you didn't go and talk to specifically
them you know.
How often
are you encountering
people like
how often are people into it
doing it with you and how often have people
been dragged there or you're trying
to like poke holes in you
and the story. It happened too
many times that people didn't want to.
I would say I would say
seventy five percent of the time people
are like jazzed.
People are like just
like I'm now
remembering to
the point of like getting a voice right. I
now remembering being the gargoyle
and talking to the entire crowd
and like some woman on like the
third floor being like is that Colonel Plunder?
Screaming at me
and I'm trying to like
yeah like I was I didn't mask it enough
to like
so like most of the times
people were like that. But
whenever people were there and like
hating their lives it was like why did you come?
Like don't come here.
We're in New York City.
It's infinite. You could go
be in a corner. You could be in a
like unpopulated.
You could sit at the corner of a sad bar
two feet away. Infinite places where
people will be rude to you as far as
wait staff is concerned. They will leave you alone
essentially. You don't have to do
improv with them. You could go across the street
to Outback Steakhouse or down
the street to lay Mrs. Rob
and just you know
just occupy yourself otherwise.
Absolutely.
I will feel that forever
about anything. Like
don't make
I have to talk to you.
If I don't talk
to you I'm going to get they're going to say that
you were such and such as best friend and I'm going to
get fired or whatever. But you didn't have
to be here. You could have gotten
you know
jalapeno poppers from any number of other
popper establishments.
Did you ever get hit with somebody who
was like too excited in the sense you were
like I'm Colonel Plunder or whatever and they're like
hello there. You're like whoa
no no no no too much. Yeah
plenty of people would come in and want to play
characters too.
We
we we also had
like people that like wanted to do it
but like didn't like you know like
didn't book or whatever and they would they would like
come in and be like
you know. Really? Yeah.
Hangers hangers hang around
and kind of like yeah stuff like
that happened. I don't remember any. I wish I had
like a specific story of a time like somebody
was like playing to the third floor for an hour
before we realized he brought
his own car. He brought his own like cleaver in the
head from a Halloween
store. There was a guy there was a guy when I worked
retail at the container's door when
I was like 21 or something. There's a guy
in the parking lot that bought an old cop car
and would come in and kind of show it around
and like he wanted you to get the
idea that he was a cop. Yeah. But he wasn't a cop.
So it's like
there were like Jekyll and Hyde people going
in there like doing voices and they kind of wanted people
to think maybe they were part of
it. Yeah I mean I don't I I
just recall people being like
excited about it on that level
but but never like
but never to that degree of like you
shouldn't be you have to go. Like get out.
Not full like stolen valor.
Where they were taking like orders or something.
Yeah.
And to that point
it had to you had
to be separate. The
waitstaff could have fun
but we were the characters
and they were you know and like that
was always a weird strange like
they're having I do recall in terms
of the like scrutinizing like they're having
more fun with the waitstaff than they're having
with you guys.
You have to blah blah blah. That's something you're not
keeping up with. They're they're just like talking
to a friendly person who is regular.
Did you ever get
approached by
did a customer ever go like
this fettuccine Alfredo is
cold. Can you send it back?
Would you just have the flag down the waiter?
And and and that was
always weird and strange
because we're
supposed to be we're supposed
to be not employees. Yeah.
And like you'd have to like act
like whatever do you mean?
I'm enjoying my drink.
Talk to whatever you know.
You don't want to but then you want their satisfaction
to be right. Like they're at the point where
they're like if you don't do this for me
I'm going to whatever raise hell
they can do. But they're like I haven't been
paying attention to any of this
as far as I know you are
the server. I didn't look anyone in
the eye in any part of this. So
it would be funnier if they were yelling
all this at the gargoyle though. Yeah.
Right. Yeah.
Can I just put it in your mouth and you'll take it somewhere?
Yeah. Can you ingest this and
do your pipes go back to the kitchen
somehow? This burger is supposed to
have bacon on it and it doesn't.
Yeah. This
is very funny to hear like how
intense this was because
the TripAdvisor
reviews from like
2021 and
2022 are all about
COVID protocols and
coupon errors. Yeah.
And like that is such
that's such a bummer that that is
how like it eventually fold
it is like they didn't honor a
coupon right.
I mean I feel like that was
I can I can I can understand
why people were probably
upset about COVID protocols given how it
was when I was there.
I mean I don't I it was a we
had the vibe that it felt like corners
were trying to be cut as much as
possible. But but I can't
speak I can't speak that wasn't there then but like
I can I can understand you know
and I can imagine like
people were mad about like Groupon's not being
honored the whole
time like the entirety of them.
Part of the if you're if you're involved
in getting Groupon's like
chances are you're kind of excited
to maybe go write some reviews about
them not being that's part of the Groupon
experience. Yeah. Disatisfaction
with the Groupon experience. I also
remember the vibe of stuff like that being like
being like you would go to a
higher up if someone did come to you about
a problem you'd be like they're worried about this and
they'd be like I don't know what that is
would be that would be would be the top
person I can talk to his reaction to that
thing.
There's no way to handle it or
or or deal with it at that point
when they're just like what even is that
you know and then walking away. Yeah.
Especially if you're dressed as a knight
in that scenario.
Okay.
The characters
and all this this
was one of the things that was like
really fogging my
brain as I was getting ready for this
because okay
it's called Jekyll and Hyde Club
and it's kind of you know if all right if you read the
description of the place it is like Dr.
Jekyll assembled many unusual friends
souvenirs and artifacts in his quest to
rid himself of Mr. Hyde.
So that's what okay these are all
it's all things he did to try to go
cold turkey on being Mr. Hyde.
Now I'm even more confused
actually but we brought them all together.
So it's like a place for his his wares and
what he's collecting. So okay so we're not going to meet
Jekyll while doing
this. We are going to meet a doctor and there
will be like like bringing a thing to life
but the like
is that between their own website
and reviews of the
place it went on
and on and on the amount of characters
and mythology usually
in ways where I could
not tell which one is an animatronic
and which one would have been
you or one of your friends.
Nowhere is there
delineation to where I was
reading you know I'm reading about like Tobias
Bloodworth okay and then
it took me like a couple days to
realize Tobias Bloodworth is a is a
werewolf head. That's not a guy
walking around because nothing in that
name tells me Tobias Bloodworth could
be a guy. Don't know.
We I believe met Tobias
Bloodworth. I went through
our videos. We were there so we were there in April
2022.
The place I believe closed one month
later. We were right there
and the whole vibe Mike was it was it not
very like you
couldn't tell if the it was
like wow it's themed to being a
place that is very like full of
decay. Oh it's falling apart.
Oh what a maculately
created old
restaurant that's been lived in
for centuries. Such accurate
cobwebs and dust
and that stench whatever could be
and it's empty to give you that
eerie feeling of who's around the corner
wow what have they done this magical
place. The floorboard
is loose. So well I'm
glad to know that because I was
there a good 10-15
years prior that they maintained
their
like the blurred
lines between is this thing messed
up or is it.
And I say that having never
been to the Times Square location which
from the outside looked like it was like
nice in there. Do you know what I mean
like that they like it was
you know newly it was newly built so it had
to be like things were like fresh and
working well and
every every animatronic like
moved with a glide
instead of like a you know creak.
Yeah yeah yeah yes like it's
dying as it's turning on
yes jittering.
But anyway I brought up to say that
Tobias Bloodworth or whatever
the wolf the werewolf I was looking at
that I'm filming doing a line of dialogue
red eyes glowing
and just mouth not opening
or closing in anyway
just firmly on there. And then let me
like I'm just going to say some names
tell me if you have any associations with these names
even if it's just. I recalled Bloodworth but
could not remember that it was a werewolf head I'll say
that. Okay okay sure. That'll give you my
frame of reference. Oh do you remember the name the
last name of the doctor unless this
is a different doctor character is that somewhere
in there. There were various doctor characters
so okay so
because we weren't all the same
doctor and even sometimes
this was always a thing like if someone predominantly
played a doctor character
when you when you arrived
you were like told like you're this
role you're that role you're the you're the you're the other
you know but like there couldn't be two
doctors at the same time
you know and that would always be confusing
and so and so sometimes that would happen
just for someone being like
this costume's clean or whatever like
the other one.
But so they were all different
you know. If you get you had to be like technically
be a dentist or something.
I know I'm in a lab coat but
what I saw a lot
was a doctor named
Dr. Hackenoff. Okay.
Saw that a lot. A maid
named Tippi Toppingsworth. Yes.
You remember Tippi Toppingsworth.
What was the name
of the actor
who played I think
Sarah I can't remember her
last name but I remember a Tippi I remember a Tippi
like being present like
and she
she had a you
every time she like entered or exited
a room.
It was always fun when Tippi showed up.
That's a character I get a sense of the character
crowd pleaser. Uh huh. Uh huh.
Dr. Sawyer Bones.
I like that.
What you could tell me was the full name
of the lead character on the show Bones.
As far as I know. Sure.
Dr. Sawyer Bones. David Boreanus was Dr. Sawyer
Bones. It might have been.
I'll never know or not know.
Aloysius
Gould the wacky chief
mortician. Yes.
You got Jervis.
Were you Jervis maybe?
Maybe that was a butler. Yeah Jervis might have been
the name of my of my butler
character.
Sort of
butler.
That's good. That's where he was.
So that feels like a
Jervis to me. I wonder if you're gonna like keep talking
I'll be like no that was the I feel like
I remember Plunder the most because
that was my first guy.
And then you know over time you're doing
like 12 hour
you know 16 hour
it's like I don't remember. Did you do that many?
I don't think 16 hours was how long
but I would do you would do double 12 hour
14 hour
doubles. Did you lose your mind
being in that space?
Absolutely. I mean it's probably why I can't
remember any of it but like yeah you would
and you would and I think
in the event of a double you would be
the same character all day. You
wouldn't like you wouldn't like switch I don't
know yeah because that could be potentially confusing
for anyone that was.
Who was there all who was also there for 12 hours
as a customer. Why are they still here?
Would you get stuck like Austin
Butler playing Elvis?
Would you come home and be like
hello there? Yeah yeah I mean
that would that would happen to a to
a degree like after afterwards
I just
remember like
remember like leaving and sort of still
talking to people like in my t-shirt as
like you know like
you know
but never like
I'm so method. Not too long.
But a little like maybe
you stop somewhere in Times Square like stop
at the Gap or something and you're like
just a quick interaction with the employee
and you still have a little bit of a voice going.
Why'd you say the word prithee?
Why'd you say pray tell?
While ordering tacos.
I'll just rip through
Gertrude K. Boom
Dr. Brain
Major Michael Magoo
Philip Andrew Edward Carrington
the fourth. Now we're into somewhere there's no
like pun
or anything. I don't know what this is. I don't know
what kind of monster you are. Priscilla
Plank. Ariel Boatsman.
That's just almost a plain name.
That's what I'm saying. And then you're
throwing out plunder. You're throwing out ones I've never
seen. And then it still keeps going.
Sydney Feamer and Marty Patella
and Sydney Feamer
Okay. Okay.
I also never know if any of these were in the pub as opposed
to the club. There's some confusion
there. Yeah. I mean there were some
I think
I don't think there was anything that was
pub exclusive
because club
where I spent most of my time was the offshoot
of that. So I think that they like
had the handful of things that were there
I think. And then
and then expanded on that. Sure. Sure.
I
Mike any other memories of our time
at pub since that's the biggest
overlap. I mean
it was it was memorable
and yet when we were talking about it
on stage two hours later
I just I just I felt like I've been
like I feel like I've been hit
by like a bunch of soft bats or something
like nothing that hurt me
but it was confusing. It just
left me in like I felt like
I've been soft pummeled you know
to where I recall nothing too
specific. I could not make some big
judgment about the place. Yeah
I didn't have anything like so
profound to say about it nor do I have
anything to say about it in that way now
but it felt like yeah like you went into that
Halloween section of the Home Depot
and it was really squeaky
like all the all the robots were extra
squeaky and then the one perform human
performer was
really good I felt. Yes.
But it was one of those things where
the pressure now because you're like the only
table in there is that you need to be
the audience for this guy. Yeah. And I get
very anxious when it comes to that.
I get very anxious when there's like a person doing like
close up magic right on top of me
because I really want to perform
for these people. I want to be like yes
or yes so funny or whatever but then I
start to get like oh my god I'm going to have to like put
it on but it's maybe it's going to sound fake if I'm not impressed
or I don't think what he's saying is funny.
So I felt the pressure of that where it was like
if he kind of just did a quick glancing
blow of a joke at us
great but I felt like oh he's here he's
still here he's still here. Yeah.
And I'll say the quick
glancing
blurting out a joke is
how I preferred to be
because I'm I'm that way
in both scenarios. I'm like I'm
feeling uncomfortable being directly
in front like having to perform directly
in someone's face and I'm also feeling
uncomfortable if I'm the if I'm the audience
member as well. But
you had to stay. Yeah. You could
not you couldn't if you did if
you did that they someone would
know and and and that was the other
thing about but that was the other thing about the pub
that was nice was you that you didn't
have that as much oversight as you did
at the club. So if
you wanted to kind of be a little bit more casual
you could but it would somehow
get back like somehow they knew like someone
would find Dr. Jekyll would find out.
Yeah. Yeah. And we
were also we had been up to like 6 a.m.
the night before. Yes.
He slept about three hours.
Jason didn't make it. Jason wasn't quite there.
I didn't make it. I guess I
went to the CVS clinic that morning too. All right. It's been two years.
I'll say now I drank too much
rye whiskey at an SNL after
party and I woke up with
like a froggy voice. You sure did.
So then I yeah
and that's why the last
time I really drank whiskey.
Oh wow. Oh geez.
A lesson learned. We had a boil
I had a Boilermaker when we were celebrating
the city the end of the City Walk
Saga. Okay. And that was
the first time in years.
It was a whiskey on retirement. Yeah.
So but we had a show
to do that night
and you guys were like we're going to
Jekyll and Hyde. I was like I need
to stay at the hotel. I'm alternating
cold water and hot tea
to heal my voice
and I'm sure they have
both of those things.
How many doctors are there
at any given night. They could have fixed it in no
problem. Oh yes. Perhaps leeches
for you.
I had also fallen.
Jaynes the
intensity of management kind
of makes sense because when we were planning
this trip to New York I
looked at the website
and I was like oh my god it's like
50 or 60 bucks
a head and you got to buy dinner
and there's a show and like. This is
where Jaynes you made the
decision back at Holland.
That had nothing to do with the whiskey.
There was timed
entries. There was timed
stuff and I was like guys I don't know if we'll be able
to do that and then Griffin's like no
it's just a bar you just walk in and
it's empty. And it's like oh okay.
Especially at that time.
But of course I want to follow the rules
so I maybe at the time might have still been like
okay but you know our timed entry
it says 320 not 310
is that okay? And then walking in and like oh no one
is here. There is no human being in this.
There are more robots. It's a shame
that they implemented
stuff like that when
no one was there
because we would have
there's like a thing that happened I don't know
about at the pub but at the club there's
like a show that happens to
even bring you in.
So we would have to like sometimes
in the winter be like you have to wait
while the show happens for
whoever's walking you know in.
It's some little like it's an equivalent
sorry of the like
you know like the haunted mansion
like you're in an elevator
or the stretching room before you go into the
ride. They like hold you in a place
to like kind of set the scene. Exactly.
Exactly like that. That like ends with
like I think there's like
we're all gonna die!
Enjoy your meal. You know like
is what the Bible that was. But I think it
takes like a couple minutes. And
and yeah we would always I feel like
it was it probably is better to be
like yeah you set a time and you come
at this time and then everyone comes in you know.
Did you have to hold people out
in the cold while people got through?
There are
a number of views of like
we had to stand outside despite it
being 30 degrees.
We were not allowed to use the bathrooms
if we were.
Can we just pop in? No, no, no.
The bookcase swings.
You had to go
through that experience. You had to hear
I believe it was a
a butler up front or a
butler or maid or whatever house
worker would
do whatever their spiel was. And you had
to have that experience in order to go in.
There was no other way to get in.
Yeah literally there's no side entrance.
There's an exit.
So there's an exit
right next to it. So sometimes you would
come out like you'd be done with your shift and someone would try
to get in and you'd have to like
you'd have to make sure they didn't get in.
Still at work for like 30
seconds.
Technically you could go through
the kitchen but you don't want to do that.
You don't want to let customers in that way.
Wow.
So much funny procedure.
Can I ask how long
did you work there for?
I was there for about a year and a half.
Which is not enough time.
That's enough time to like you did it.
Maybe you didn't get too sick of it.
Or did you? How do you feel?
From the beginning of the experience to the end.
I think it's that thing where
I like really
was excited about the job.
And it had a variety of different
things that would like reinvent
it. Like oh now you're playing this character.
Now you're playing that character. Now you get to go to the
pub. I think the owner also like had like
he also had like
a couple
amusement parks. I remember like doing a day
somewhere like somewhere else you know.
Oh in his little sister.
Yeah in Long Island.
Yeah okay. Yes. That must
be it. I forget the name of it.
Bayville Adventure Park. Yes.
I think that's exactly it. And you could go
as
I went as an explorer
because I guess teamed into
like tied into
adventure. But like so there were things
that like would
reinvent it. But I was ultimately
like it was
it was like a job. There was a point where it became
a job and not like as fun as
it was. Yeah. Yeah. Which a funny
thing for that to become
rote is turning out like you
listlessly doing
welcome fellow travelers.
No I was just like
today's special is jalapeno
poppers.
It really is. That's also funny that it's like
it's an assembly of the
creepiest kooks and the most
you know odd ducks from all
over. And you're in like vaguely the
late 1800s.
Maybe seemingly you know it's hard
to like you don't end up in the area of like
what is that strange device.
Right. But bacon
on top of macaroni and
cheese.
Now I have seen everything.
The
food is very for it being
like you know that you're going to
like old foggy London town
and then the food is like spinach
and cheese dip nacho chili supreme
margarita chicken
quesadilla.
I saw the New York
Times did a review of this
place where they called the pasta
there they called the pasta sauce
red tinged
water. Sure. Sure.
And granted then the guy
even he wasn't even being that harsh
he's like I was there with my nephew
and niece. And what do you want
at that age for red tinged water.
I serve this at home to my
four year old. That's exactly what he wants.
You got they're vaguely
themed with the
you got a mummy burger you got a baddie burger.
That was something I couldn't remember was if the
if the food was was themed
or not. A little. But then baddie
burger is like cheddar cheese
lettuce tomato onion and
a pickle.
What does the baddie come in. Well the
mummy burger should be wrapped in something.
Right. Which it certainly wasn't.
Sauteed mushrooms
swiss cheese that almost with the
holes it almost looks like the
you could wrap it. The netting around
the cut up bandages all over your hand.
I guess you could wrap it in bacon.
Oh.
So it would be a ton of bacon but still it would be wrapped
in you. It kind of looks like decaying
skin. You could put it in like one of those paper
little wrappers like in and out comes.
So that might work. Yeah.
Yeah. That would have been cool.
I don't think we did it. They did anything like that.
I think it was all like it's this by name
solely. You know
but like yeah. That's such a
that's like problem number one for any
themed restaurant is that the food
sucks or
is unimaginative and then it
starts out that way generally
and then just quickly goes very very
far downhill. Yeah. Yeah.
You know there's at least at some point there was
a conversation with this with some
like you know
like edible
to like concocted a
strange array of like you know
that like budgetarily they started by talking
to a guy who invented 70 things
that look like you're like and it's like you're pulling
the top off and it's brains but the brains is
really a steak and it's just painted and then at
some point it becomes it's
look it's gotta be potato skins. There's no other way
we're gonna make money. There's a place where there's a
truck that will come here and bring us potato skins
and we heat them up and that is the end of this operation.
It's the same thing we've talked about forever
is that it's like dad is gonna get
confused. He looks at the menu
we can't have dad be
confused. We were at Disneyland
yesterday I suggested my dad eat shawarma
what is shawarma
that turned into a whole other thing. Like it's the food
that you it's the same food you have
everywhere else rearranged
slightly. It's chicken and it's out
chicken and bread basically.
I remember the food. I remember
the idea of the food
was that it was pretty bad
but you got a shift meal depending on how long
what time you arrived or how long
your shift was and I just remember like
needing it. I was also like
you know very poor at the time even though
I have this job and blah blah blah
but like being like there is
a you know
a vat of
a casserole
I'm gonna eat this whatever and it is like
it's watery it's a
soup it's a casserole but it's a soup you know
but I'm like I'm eating this I need it.
It's here it's the yeah yeah yeah yes
I had the I got
the blandest pizza of my entire
life but it was before
like before shows
not to get too processed I'm just like
I'm usually not hungry but I'm like but I
have to eat so I don't faint
so I essentially want a paste
I want paste on top of
mush and that is kind of
what I got out of this and it was honestly
absurd I'll always be
fond of any food that helped me not faint
somewhere so
I give it up to the pizza. Do you have any
mush that will be good for my blood sugar
levels? Blood sugar mush
is really what I'm looking for
oh fries just get the fries got it
thank you. But fries sometimes taste
like something well these no no no don't
worry about that. There
are like if you get bad steak
fries right those are the sort of the thicker
fries yeah if you get bad
steak fries those are still good usually as long
as like as long as they're not like rotten
yeah no the sort of
soggier the
the sort of like lack
of being done the better
with the steak fries. Yeah yeah yeah
that's true. Did I have I'm going back
just existing yeah yeah do you you know what
I have I have one video that might be worth
playing yeah this is this is a
Sphinx head this is my main memory of it
because this was the Sphinx
okay I'm glad I brought up the Sphinx then okay
this is a big part of it this I mean it's
my main memory before I
started diving in this week
and here is
the audio
it's just like the lower jaw
is going and this is right above our heads
could not be closer to us and I think the audio
will paint a real picture of it
it's like it's a telegraph machine
yeah
yeah so I forgot that
looking at that that that image
because that's at the that's the pub
Sphinx yeah the pub Sphinx
is has color
to the face
right to the to the design
blue and then the eyes blue
oh you had a much better view that
looks great from where you are the Sphinx at
but it sounds exactly the same
the course of the future
yeah we had to like
ooh we're the Sphinx
I can't remember what the voice reference was but like
this is where he lived
the drive time DJ guy
the party man
the cool horizon
he was a fun one
but I think we were told
him and Fang who
this is not going to sound like Peter
Laurie but this was how the
Sphinx the Fang was supposed to sound
Fang was the gargoyle
yeah and those are the two that were like
fun to do but it was always
like you had one that you liked
to play so it was like you can't
you gotta switch it up you can't
just be the Sphinx although you can't just do
okay okay which is good to make you a more
well-rounded performer to find your
in on characters who
aren't exactly yours that's that's good
training yeah but the thing
I was saying I just remember that the Sphinx
in Minntown was he's just
like brown
he's just like you know like stone
and yeah
and so that's I guess one of the potential
differences but same deal just his
just his goatee
moved you know you're puppeting
it if you're doing it yeah and so it was just
like it was like an arcade game
was how you would puppet them there's like a joystick
and like a couple buttons
and yeah anyway and
I had I had like songs
that I would like to sort of like every now and
again like if I didn't if I didn't
want to play a character at the moment I would like
put a song on
as as
like like the
there's a there's a doctor with a two-headed
doctor on the third floor and
and I would do Monster Mash for like
whoever was sitting in that corner with a
doctor got the biggest show but everyone
would I would like turn on other puppets you know
what I mean like so everyone's a part
of the little multiple get your hands
a couple
it was fun
I remember another
strong memory I know actually I forgot
until looking at videos I'm so glad I remember now
that the there is a
like they do have a version of the like
he's alive kind of like a Frankenstein
that was the power show yeah okay
okay I think this was entirely
oh maybe the performer was in it but it's like
a it like a kind of a metal
bed descends from the ceiling and
then the thing sits up and there's a lot
there's narration pre-recorded narration
about how like he's out of control
get him with the tranquilizer
but he's doing nothing
there essentially so you just gotta
take their word for it but then
that video ends then I go to the next
like oh what's happening in the next and it seems
as though the creature coming
to life then gave way to a full restaurant
performance of I got
the power
and watching us all
kind of like confusedly listlessly
danced to I got the power
over with some
some house white wine at
4pm at an empty restaurant
it's a vibe it was something
I'm glad I got to
you know did I get a real New York
experience could I have done something cooler
with a more cultured thing yes
but you know
you gotta go with what's up your alley
so alright
let me just call out details before we
wind it down here
let's see I don't know there were skeletons
who play the piano and their heads
spin around any other just big
images that you're like well that's a thing
you can't bring it up with I mean the sphinx clearly one
of them yeah the
I'm remembering the skeletons now and they had
like they had like set songs
that they would that they would sing
two headed
doctor I'm trying to go through the floors
what were the main
puppets that you would
do let me ask was
there a magician
I saw people mention a wandering
magician yeah yeah
I there were
club members so like the club members
were like adventurers and there were also magicians
I don't recall anyone actually doing
magic if that makes sense
so like it would be like your character was a magician
that could
could do magic
seemingly do magic
but I don't recall there being any any actors at the time
that I was there I could actually do it
there there was one review that said
the lovely
they had been there once before and they
said the lovely magician is
gone and replaced by
an annoying old man who comes around
to the tables
so just
imagine just all these characters
that it's like alright your father time
go bother them
like
but it's like depending on the time
that you come there's all these set
things that happen but there will be different characters
the lovely magician might be back another
time right you know that was a thing for
people needed to remember they could
maybe just came at the wrong time
your best bet is to just go
if you're gonna go once go three times
that week yeah different times of the day
oh yeah and turnover was always
was really high like I was there for
for you know a year and change
and that's long for
like people that are just like trying to get their equity
card in bounds
that happened a lot you know
generally solid run for you
that sounded also like that person was maybe like
was smitten with the magician
the lovely magician
would guests ever
which episode was it
we were talking about how there would be fans of specific
people playing Disney Princesses it was the Amanda
Lund episode in Tokyo Disney
specifically would people come in that were
super fans of yours
I didn't have anybody
that like was a soccer
of me in that
in that way
I do remember like
I'm thinking back to that woman that was like
is that Colonel Blunt you know I do
remember there being times where people would be like
you're my favorite of the day
you know like oh I'm so glad
you're here you know I don't like that
that other you know but
there weren't any like
I fortunately
didn't have anybody that was like following
me home or like waiting outside
when you get off the shift
and could you stay in character when you're out
let's get a drink but you
have to have a vague British
accent
don't tell me you are not slightly
British or this is over
the Girls Next Door
went to this
they made Hef go here
I went and watched the episode
I've been missing out also on Girls Next
Door clearly a fine broadcast
I used to watch it but I don't remember that
episode
season one they were there early on
Hef had to like kind of clap along
while like the lady did
some like blood curdling
somebody mistook him for one of the skeletons on the wall
how'd you come loose
nail him back up
wow really realistic
though
when the girl's touching pure ash comes out of his mouth
who's puppeting this guy
so there's that you know hey it's a hot spot
Hef is there things are working out great
but I think the Times Square
location stretched him
kind of thin because that goes
I think the other one that you worked at
on 7th I think
merges with Times Square but then Times Square
goes down because that's a high pressure place
to do something meanwhile they were
trying to expand they did
Chicago and they did
Dallas they did
it was at one of the mills
Grapevine mills
okay thank you yes
and neither of those
made it very long Chicago is now
in Italy that's what that is
and then Dallas
can't be mad at that
it makes sense
I love a good Italy
that is a four story business
establishment where the model
makes sense
so that they start going
down the other ones I believe the mills one
is a became
an indoor skate park and now it's a
Legoland thing so people just
across the country did not have it
in their heart to accept these 1800s
theatrics
and then it's so then it's down to one
it's down to the pub
but it was not looking so great when
we were there and I think even then they had already
declared bankruptcy
oh and the
whole enterprise was not doing well
in 2013 already
because it was announced that they owed two million dollars
to their landlord
yeah I was going to say I thought that we were done
that I was surprised when
when Times Square happened
I was like how like on what
yeah you're in there
and part
of the appeal was that we weren't
you could have an experience like this
and you're not like having to fight through
everybody to get to like Madame Tussauds or whatever
like it's like being
not in Times Square was what was like
good about it to a degree
a little off the beaten path, yeah yeah
it's around a corner
you're not fighting crowds, sure sure sure
but were you also in there going like
even in success are you like
this seems weird
how does this place exist?
I'll also say like I
to it being off the beaten path
I worked at New Year's Eve there
once and it's like one of my
most memorable New Year's
because it was like afterwards you could
just leave like I was there
and you could go through to like
12.30 maybe 1 a.m.
but you could just leave there's no traffic
there was no people there was no nothing
because of how far away it was
wow
and everybody that was there was like
like everyone wanted to be there
you know like
better than I've never understood
being there in the Times Square when the ball drops
that seems like an absolutely
that is the
last place I want to be
has anybody ever done it for some
like no I've never done it
you have to stay there too right like for like 8 hours
you can't yeah you're there and you can't
go to the bathroom you can't do anything you're stuck
you have to like pee in your pants
but that's what I was saying
take a diaper and then you do
you have to pee in a diaper
you are baby new year
everyone in Times Square is baby new year that night
and they pee and poop
and it's cold it'll harden up it'll be like
just like you're wearing like a second layer
you're wearing an ice diaper
it'll freeze the diaper to your balls
your pee will freeze to your balls
sucks
the like odd structure of it
this is where I'm like yeah like when did
this ever seem like it was doing well because there's bankruptcy
and then they owed 2 million dollars
and the
company that owned the plot of land
was called
a very normal name Africa Israel
USA
ultimately they owe all their money to Africa Israel USA
an odd
sounding group that apparently
also was one of the main funders of Hard Rock
Park oh wow
Hard Rock theme park in South Carolina
so this is a spend money to make money endeavor
yeah maybe
this somehow I guess this aligned
with whatever they needed to do to burn cash
and the company that owned
the company that owns Jekyll and Hyde is Eerie World
Entertainment yeah
Eerie World Entertainment which also owns a lot of
other things there's something called like the slaughtered
lamb or something
do I have the animal rights there was supposedly
a restaurant like the theme is that it
is owned by a family of werewolves
because the
slaughtered lamb had a wolf
head logo I had never been
but I remember thinking
so to your question
yes I thought it was weird but I also
thought at least going into
it I thought it was so cool
I thought it was like
I remember seeing all the logos next
to each other and I had from
from the fourth grade kept
one of the like pamphlets
that like explained what Jekyll
and Hyde was and I had that
I remember I think I took it with me
when I moved to New York as like a
you're now here you know type deal
yeah and
I just remember thinking it was cool
and then you know the longer I was there
and the more it was just the more it just sort of felt
like oh I don't know if we're how
are we keeping afloat and like what's
all of this and that and whatever feeling like
oh man it's not as fun as like
yeah isn't that that's been our
arc doing this podcast we've taken all
of these things that we felt the same way
about when we were nine we've poked
holes in their business plans and
more become more than understanding
of why they all went away
yeah there's so many familiar
patterns too yeah
I feel like we've really
you know we've talked about theme parks for a few years
and that's been fine or whatever but really what we've been
doing is figuring out how to perfectly run
a weird chain restaurant
and open and open franchises
and know how slow to expand
and know what markets like I know we've been
giving ourselves an education about
when we finally decide to go all in
on a very fun stupid
idea this whole thing has just been like a
thesis level grad school for ourselves
to ultimately get it more right
than anyone ever has we've learned
the most right way
to do it is money
laundering
is sort of
watching like okay you have
the cash but you need to wash
it quote unquote
so it's not the same cash and make sure
it's people who are good at it who've done
it for who aren't new to the money laundering
you need to be in there with pros
you need to have like seven other businesses
just like this professional
money launderers and also we need
a bunch of people fresh out of 401
at the Upright City
hey
bright eyed bushy tailed
improv kids
hey speaking of expanded too fast
oh boy
oh no
wow
they needed to learn
like we're learning it's what this is all about
anyway honestly
then covid hits
and that's not good for anybody but it's
especially not good you know this place
just ends up on it's last legs like
because of covid and covid protocols
well not exactly because ultimately
the thing becomes we get to
this headline owner of
Jekyll and Hyde theme restaurant faces
up to 30 years in prison
for using covid relief money to buy
nantucket home
come on bro
did you know any of this
no I didn't and can you remind what's his name
his name is Donald Finley
Donald Finley is the guy
Mr. Eerie World Entertainment
who is one of these figures who like
like the weird rainforest cafe guy
who built the rainforest cafe in his house
before it opened who has this odd
okay so his thing is
horror and like pulpy
novels and we're gonna I don't know
it's cool he like he found a
everything up until this
seems fine but then he gets
like 3 million dollars
from the government and immediately
buys a house we should have done this further
podcast and bought houses
we blew it
all of us should have James I hope that you
took out I hope you took a million dollars
off for some business I'll tell you
my accountant kept
at the time kept
asking me to do it
he kept saying take out
a PPP loan the money is there
the money is there take it out and
and for like
my S corp which is my business
that you know sure yeah but I was just
like what are you talking about
what am I gonna say
I'm not gonna do this
he's like you worked at Jekyll and I'd improvise
just figured something if
IRS calls you just weave him a tail
I am not surprised
that that is what happened
though I'm not like I
and I can't even remember what the lore
was about him at the time but I think
we all kind of generally felt
like I don't know about this guy
is he more Mr. Hyde
than Dr. Jekyll
I remember there was a day of the week
where he would show up
to get the
it seemed like I don't know if this is what he was doing
but to get the money do you know what I mean
like he left with
briefcases
weekly it happened
weekly
went up to the werewolf's mouth
tapped it and a bill came out every time
you know what I mean it was like I would
you would see him come and then you would see
him leave with something and it was
always like two sort of suitcases
at his side with dollar signs
yeah it was like yeah cartoon
yeah yeah and in one case
he had a bit like poke out of his jacket
pocket was a bit like a clearly
labeled deed Nantucket
mom yeah he always
talked about how it was important everyone
was spooky but then he would go on and on
about how beautiful parts
of Nantucket were
it's the
anti-transylvania believe me
we should have oh we would all be
living in Nantucket if we took these peepee
meals yeah oh my god
we'd be living next door to them too
welcome to podcast rather podcast about theme parks that
suddenly for no particular reason is coming to you
from three separate Nantucket
mansions next to each other we've just been very lucky
the patreon's been very fruitful what can
I say
anyway that was like a year
ago that got announced and then just a month
ago it came down two years
went from 30 to 2
so things worked out for old
maybe he hired one of your old improv
buddies to be his lawyer
were there any lawyer characters in the show
there weren't any lawyer characters
but I wouldn't be
surprised if some of us
are lawyers now
mr scott free or
mr loophole
gotta be somebody
mr
scratch my back
that's all run together
it's a polish name
judge look the other way
anyway in the
sentencing the judge
tied his profession into it
not so much Jekyll and Hyde he was like
that'll be too obscure of a reference
but he says today's sentencing
means that no one was amused
by this bayville adventure park
owner's criminal acts and he will
now face time in prison
I mean they should have said amusement park
maybe just to like super
but he doesn't write for a
little polished
sentencings are not exactly what he does
it always blows my
mind even though I've seen it a million times and it shouldn't blow
my mind but like I forgot to pay my
target bill for my credit
card one month I got the most aggressive
phone call of like well here's
how much you owe and here can we do that now
let's pay it I see you have a thing on
file now can we just put it through now and I'm like
the most aggressive thing ever and then it's like two
million dollars are owed from
a restaurant in time square
enough time the more we talk
about these restaurants and figure out
their failure we just become
by the time you know when we're in what
he's like 60 or so
a great time to go to jail by the way
but like that's what we're
building towards you know
we got like yeah in 20 years
will be the pros
yeah just why like why
does the government though
seem to care more
about corporations and
businesses than people
you know what I'm saying
I mean they are our betters
oh Jason
figured it out
they were like he's gonna pay
corporations
corporations like a gigantic
huge person
bigger than the globe itself
I don't have office space
well that's true I don't know
I don't own anything I don't think
am I do I
own myself even
yeah I don't know
yeah it's hard to say I don't yeah
that's what's going away
not just home ownership but just ownership
ownership of the idea of owning
you own nothing
I bought my car but I still
owe so much you know what I mean
I still like I don't own it yet
still you know
will I ever like will I
ever actually pay this off
you have your foot in the door
to own a thing at some point
well so I don't know a weird
tale of
ancient horrors that
ends in current
modern horror you're not surprised
seemingly but you'd like still
fond memories glad this was like a formative
interesting time truly going
back to those days if this
has been very nice for me in a way
like I'm surprised at how fondly I
remember that stuff because I
I do remember towards the end being like
I can't wait to get out of here you know kind of thing
but also I need to work what else am I
gonna
so yeah I'm surprised at how much of it was like
yeah I loved that I really
wanted to do that job
yeah a really specific
dream came true and if you were ever
called on in a pinch to
push a bunch of buttons and operate a
series of puppets I can do
you know they have to be dated
to that I can't do whatever they're
doing now it's probably it's probably
some crazy to advance
as long as they haven't updated the system
decades they look some of those stuff
at Disney parks now look
like the Pixar movie
just alive have you seen those
the stuff that they're doing like the new
Tiant the Tianti animatronics look
it just looks like she's moving in
the movie yeah
like Roger Abbott style the cartoon
just is in the world yeah but in the world
right yeah yeah absolutely
it is pretty wild so I don't know how they
I don't know what kind of controls
that have to do alive yeah but give me
like a give me like a shrew
with fangs that's operated by me
pounding just one one red
button and then I turn the head with
a with a joystick I'm good I got that
sometimes I say happy birthday
and then I'm set
well what a fun world
to visit and I'm glad we got a bunch
of time to talk about this crazy place especially
with your experience James the third you survived
podcast the ride
wonderful to have you thanks for having
me absolutely and
let's exit through the gift shop anything
you'd like to plug yes
please watch
Fairly Odd Parents new wish
that's you know especially if you got
kids or have fond memories of that show
that's on Nickelodeon Paramount
Plus I actually don't know
it's on it's gonna
be on TV or something and
and my comic
book Kickstarter it's called Junior
you can follow me at rule of three ink
or just search for Junior or
daddy issues on Kickstarter and you'll find it
great great I'm also I'm just gonna toss
into good burger oh
yeah oh yeah what do you what is your
what do you call your role so I so
what I it was
this I wrote on good on good
burger too but I punch up writer on
good burger too and then
and I also am a voice over
I do voice over for the
burgers there's several of us but I'm
but one of those voices is me
wait does it open
with like a dream sequence it opens with a dream
yes yes yeah so
I'm I'm in that
and then I'm also singing in the
bring good burger back
montage when there's like a like
celebrities
I don't know if the burgers are
in that but I am singing as a
burger which is kind of look that's a basic
puppety that's very much
I mean I didn't get to puppet
those but yeah
I don't because I had said
out of and I've just said to a number of people
anyone who will listen
I thought good burger too was so
great and it's like it's so glad
I
I hope you're super proud of it and I
like and and it's
a genre I think that's really fraught
the like bringing characters
back after
the way way later sequel
is a really rough area
and I was just I was
so pleasantly surprised by it
as I was I didn't really grow
up with the first one I only like threw it on with a
bottle of wine like five years ago
was like oh damn good burgers good
will I feel the same way about too
and I absolutely did my whatever I was so
delighted I'm so glad you feel
that way because I know it's a I've
I've not read all of the reviews
but I've seen how many people
enjoyed it and also how many people
like didn't feel like it captured the same
thing I would say that my role
as a writer and why they asked
me I worked on the all that reboot
and my role in that room was predominantly
having an encyclopedic knowledge of the show
oh wow
well we did it like this and you didn't do it like this and blah blah or whatever
and so I
I feel like that's why they asked me
to come in on on
Good Burger 2 Kenan and Kel
like it was like a glove
getting back into those characters
like yeah so I mean
yeah like we of course we know we see
Kenan so often that it's a given that
Kenan is going to be right Kel was so
fucking just like
so on it hadn't missed a beat
and especially the and I don't know
forgive me if I'm giving if this is not your
compliment when Ed
gives a speech the inspirational
speech that is only one line
and then the rest of it is just
silence with the shots that would
be there if there was a
full speech to get that I
that is honestly my funny
my favorite like comedy set piece
in anything in a while
Kevin and Heath the
writers of the movie were there for
the you know original and
they will tell you that like
they there's so much stuff
on the cut room floor from that first movie
that like they just they're
just jokes and bits and jokes and like
they're just they're machines in that way
and and
the script that I read
before I was even brought on I was like you could just do
this like you could it was so
but that moment is one of those moments
like from the like from the original
where they were just like
ready for it it's just like that
could have been and I think and it's a scene
I think we would have all if that had been in the first
one we would have been like oh yeah good burger's great it has that
part in it yeah that's okay
well that's crazy scenes info but
yeah everything you did on it fantastic
James very funny man
check out the kickstarter and
yeah so glad you could do this yeah thanks for having
me okay as for us next week
we are off the main feed for memorial
day but for bonus
episodes that just keep coming
three of them every month check out podcast
the ride the second gate or get one more
bonus episode on our VIP tier
club three you will find all of that at
patreon.com slash podcast
the ride so now for memorial
day we transform into our
alter egos three
guys taking a nap
oh scary
oh
far for the course for Jason
forever
dog this has been
a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott
Gardner Brett Boehm
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts
please visit forever dog
podcasts.com and
subscribe to our shows on apple
podcasts spotify or
wherever you get your podcasts keep
up with the latest forever dog news by
following us on twitter and instagram
at forever dog
team and liking our page
on facebook