5, 4, 3, 2, 1
May the first be with you!
It's an early...
May the fourth...
While it should be more like...
Oh yeah, much better, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Star Wars.
Airhorn. Hey, it's an early
Star Wars
day episode because it's
more trouble than it's
worth to change the release date to
actual May the fourth. So here we are
now. We're getting it done. Hey, we're unwrapping
our life day presents
early this year. I'm Scott
Garen, you're Mike Carlson. Hi. I'm here, yes.
A life day has come
early. Enjoy it.
You know, I'm trying to remember, there's of course
the Star Wars game
where the characters dance.
I've shown you these videos before, I think.
Oh yeah, I already don't remember the name of it.
I forget what is the name of the game, but it's like
instead of... It's from Xbox
Kinect, right? You would hold the
orb connector. And you would
dance along. It's like the games just dance,
yes. Jason Sheridan providing that
information. Ah, yeah. I was also
sitting here as we were about to get started.
Well, we could always say May the first
be with me. And so, very
happy to hear it. Happy season
of the Force to you both. Yeah, I mean
season of the Force at Disneyland.
I was thinking that's the thing. No matter
when we put it out, the point, you know,
as long as it happens within
the season of the Force and as long as
the season of the spirit is with us.
Well, it's Pixar and happy Pixar
Fest season of the Force.
Oh yes, depending on which you celebrate.
If your
tradition is Pixar Fest, then we
honor that. If you're a season of the Force
and if you're everything or none
of the above. We celebrate all of it.
Well, what would you say you guys are?
Jason, you're like a devout Pixar
Fest follower. I mean,
yeah. You know,
I love... You're an orthodox Pixar
Fest follower. Yeah. And you're a
reform season of the Force.
More of a reform season of the Force. We're a little
looser with what we believe as far
as Star Wars is concerned, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
We don't accept... Look, I've seen all
nine movies. We don't accept all of it
had to have happened that way, you know?
We're a little looser. It's about the
message. It's about the message of Star Wars
versus actually enjoying maybe all nine
episodes of the movie series.
That's all. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's not, you know,
you know, the way these things work with
the, you know,
different authors might have muddied
up the text over the years.
Yeah, that's why I'm reformed. But ultimately you
go back to what the original
mission and thought was. The sacred
texts. What it's all about. Which is, of
course, tiny little beings in your
bloodstream who give you magic
powers. Right. That's what it is.
Ultimately. Ultimately.
Well, you gotta wish... You know
what? I mean, we've talked about those wills.
We've talked about that
George Lucas's versions of
Episode 789 would have been about
the tiny creatures, the wills who
make up... They are the...
They're the force? Or they are what...
Even though I've read
a lot about the wills and have spoken at
length about the wills, I can't remember...
You've given several speeches at
Oxford and... Yeah, yeah.
Cambridge. Yeah. I can't remember.
Are the wills part of midichlorians? Are they
smaller? Are the wills what make
midichlorians and the midichlorians are what make the force?
Or are those one and the same? I don't know,
but I love the wills. Whatever it is, I love them.
It doesn't matter. The point is that you love them.
I was gonna say
the real failing
in those not happening is
not getting Star
Tours levels
where you go and meet the wills.
Where you get microscopic.
Although, if that's what
all the movies were gonna be about, you would have been
microscopic the whole time, I guess.
It would have been like Toy Story.
Star Wars. Even tinier.
More like
Bugs Life, but maybe smaller still.
I don't know.
But you could have a big
bunch of wills, like
the minions in the minions ride.
They all kind of band together
and make shapes.
Form a shared climb onto each other. Yeah.
Well, that's what's happening, I think.
Every second
in Luke's body
is constant
like team will chains.
That's really what we
these would be movies set entirely
in the bloodstream of the characters
that we know.
We'll finally know what was going on
in their veins
and in their arteries.
And maybe in their private parts, too.
I'm for sure in their private parts.
I think we would have spent a lot of time seeing what the wills
are up to in Luke's dick.
Something magical.
Cranking it.
Cranking that lightsaber.
The low lightsaber.
Or maybe not so low.
Well, this isn't Doughboys.
We shouldn't speculate on Luke Skywalker's
dick size.
We need to stay away from their territory.
You know, look,
we're here on May the fourth
week, once again
participating in what is
definitely the most beloved
yearly tradition that Podcast
the Ride does.
We hear about it all the time.
We're lauded for it all the time.
It definitely lands that we do this.
People definitely do
notice and remember that
we do Star Wars episodes
every year. Frankly, you don't need
to send the letters anymore, the physical
letters. We get the point.
You're welcome. You're very
welcome. And the
pandemonium that must be happening now that
we're doing it again.
And like we said, we were talking about
knowing what's going on.
When it comes to 2020 Star
Wars events, we definitely
know. Yeah, hell
yes. I definitely understand
what's happening. Although something
today, I might
be back on board. I might have to catch
up. I don't know if there's enough hours
in the day to do that because there's
so much stuff now. There's a lot
of stuff. So what do you
refer though? I'm referring
to the new scene
with the space
whales, the Purrgill. Oh, yes.
Well, that's the main course.
That's what we're hearing. So yeah, let's not jump
too ahead on Purrgill talk.
We'll tease it, tease it, but
it's pretty exciting. I didn't know all the
details. Ah, okay.
Now I'm back on board.
This is a fun addition. If you don't know what
we're talking about for
this year's season of The Force,
of course we know it. You know
in your heart that this is happening and that
this was done. But for the first
time in a little bit, although they've been
pretty regular about these, there has been a new
addition of scenes to
the beloved Star
Tours franchise.
The adventures keep
continuing for this
beloved simulator ride.
They've added scenes based on
episode 789 and maybe other
things that I am not remembering.
But this is kind of the block that
celebrates the
Disney Plus series
in a bigger way that
represents Mandalorian
and Andor
and Ahsoka.
Let's get this right from
the get-go because I don't watch
the show or know. Just say Ahsoka.
Jason said her name crazy
a couple days ago and I can't remember
how I think so. Ahsoka. Ahsoka.
I forget what you said. I don't know.
Ahsoka Tano? Tano?
Tano? But no, you got,
we were on a different planet. I don't
know. Well, it's okay. All I
know is I would love to get my
own vehicle so that
I could yell the now
20 year old movies. I know these
actors from like, it's
Zorzario Dawson from 25th
Hour. You want your own vehicle
to yell it? It's the guy from E2 Mama
Tambien. They jerk
off into the pool.
We stay, we're staying odd here. E2
Mama!
Mama! That had a lot
of zest to it. Yeah. Well, he's
excited. Were you saying
you want your own vehicle, like your own Star Tours
vehicle to pilot solo?
Well, I don't want to annoy people
yelling out their other roles.
We did that motorcycle
movie, I think. It's
probably not the voice
but could be of Pedro Pascal
who I know from many
fan cams where he is looking
delish, am I right?
Can't see him here, but
this is all the stuff we would yell at if we had our own
Star Tours vehicle to ourselves, our own
Starspeeder. You're looking
delish. I assume
under there. I think so. If you're part
of this. And again, I would put my money on
not. Yeah.
So yeah, these new scenes
have been added. I'm saying
the word scene, but in
the preparation for this, and I don't think we
know what we're calling this episode yet,
but in my head,
I've been saying levels.
I've been saying levels for a while.
I was going to ask you guys, is that silly
to call these Star Tours
scenes levels?
But then, dinner the other night,
Mike, you said the exact same thing.
You called them levels. I like
levels. Let's go with levels.
Yeah, I think level. I mean, I
bet it's not technically called levels.
Don't think so. Don't internally, but
it feels like levels to me.
It's an active term
when we're in video game territory.
And it especially feels like levels to me
because they change.
They can be altered as far as your
lineup and what you get.
So I think that's partly why.
Well, hang on.
The spy notion in general
is that if that is a change,
it's custom to every
single Star Tours voyage.
Yes, so levels. I mean, Millennium Falcon
for sure you call those levels
because you are actively playing a game.
I think. Yes.
Those don't change.
No, never change. Never change.
OK, when Galaxy's Edge
opened, there was some talk of
do they retire
Star Tours, which I'm like,
I still feel the vomit
gurgling in my throat when I even
think about this notion.
But you get it. Well, isn't it weird to have
some straight Star Wars over
here? No, no, it's not. Why would you
get rid of this? Right.
Anything that's like this, like
that in Hong Kong, the
Star Tours simulators became this Iron
Man thing that looks awful.
Thank God they did not start putting that
into
replacement of Star Tours.
But if there was any question
back in 2019 or in the lead
up, what is the use of Star
Tours now that there's a Galaxy's Edge?
Well, look at this. The proof
is right in what we're talking about today.
They're still changing these things out.
And Millennium Falcon, we've been
dealing with Coaxium. We're at the
fifth anniversary of Coaxium.
Coaxium turned five. Wow.
Happy five. Going to
Kindergarten or out of Kindergarten already?
Maybe, it depends.
Coaxium's making friends.
Developing interests.
It's a whole internal life of Coaxium now.
I just saw, when they
were teasing the ride, when
they were previewing it, they
showed some footage of like, here's
sample footage. And
it's all like stuff, it's like
AT-ATs, like you knock over AT-ATs
and they're, I think they're restoring
troopers.
And that is,
it looked cool. Like it looks
cooler than Coaxium.
We probably talked about this before. The idea that
the Falcon could knock over
like dominoes a
ton of AT-ATs. Which is
very fun. It's very funny.
Yes. And
ultimately nothing that
silly happens, I don't think.
There's kind of a silly like thud on the ground.
The thud is the most memorable part of it.
Yeah. Yeah. I think.
I'm also thrown by the, because I
was like, this is gonna come up at some point.
And I did, I was watching a video
discussing, is it AT-ATs or
AT-ATs? Oh yeah, yeah. And I think
that before, because listeners have
been fucking jumping on us
left and right about pronunciations.
There's been a lot of that lately.
Let's cut that off.
Maybe this is my comeuppance for
bringing up any time Jason says
anything slightly weird. As you did five
minutes ago. Oh yeah.
Look, I don't know.
I can't be as natural as
Scott talking about the delish fan
cams, which sounded very
good, authentic.
Yeah, you have to have watched as many
fan cams as they have. You said it right before we were recording.
And I'm like, oh, here it goes again about the delish
fan cams. You guys see anyone?
This one's like, this one's not as delish.
I mean it is delish. Less delish.
Guys, there's a new Glen Powell.
There's a new Glen Powell
fan cam.
Look,
here and there, but that'll always be the minor
to the major that is Pedro.
No, but I think
what I was finding is that
AT-ATs or AT-ATs is acceptable.
So let's not...
I'll say this. I know
that you can do both, but
calling them AT-ATs has always annoyed
me. But a lot of Star Trek
Jesus, I did this the other day too. Star Wars
people do that.
So I can't be that mad, because it seems
like it's pretty, like
either way. Yeah, yeah.
I'm looking at the percentages of who...
how many says, at AT-ATs,
AT-ATs, and I don't know.
This is interesting data. It's definitely interesting
data that I'm looking at. Thank you.
Wait, that's the right one? You said it right.
Hey!
I've made progress. I knew we were headed
somewhere and then you did it right. Thank you
so much. That makes me happy.
Oh, wow. Okay, okay. I guess I
absorbed this lesson then. Yeah, you learned.
Oh, good. Well, I'm happy to have given you a nice
little... Yeah, that must have been
a little... I think data has been
peppoed in your mind.
Yeah, except I... Yeah,
except corrected. Right, but you really want
to needle me with the wrong one.
So you're saying the wrong one. So you've
peppoed data right now.
That's what happened. What I want is the
other. Exactly. I think
when you're talking about actual
data, you can say data
or data.
I said this. People were like, no. No,
you can't. No. No, actually
it's only data, actually.
This is like a particular...
Have you noticed this? This is like a particular...
I feel like... Bug up the audience's
butt lately. I would not bring this up otherwise
that you bring it up, but I've seen you get
hit a lot lately. I think, yes. That's what I've
seen. Uh-huh. Yeah. I believe
there was confusion about entomology
versus... Oh, oh,
yeah. Yeah, well, I already don't
remember. I don't even want to try.
Come on. For God's sake.
We say... How many thousands of
words do we... How many millions of words
do we say a year? Millions, yeah. Some of
them are wrong. Again, as I say this, I realize
this is my karmic come up
for all the years of Jason. I did say...
Oh, well, well, well.
I know why it's happening now. I think
also you mispronounced
YouTube rock and roll guys last name
Rick Beato. I think you called him Beato or
something. You know, how
in the goddamn world am I supposed
to know that? Someone please tell
me why... He says his name. Why
on earth... You think I watch the
beginnings? I go straight to
this is a Mark Maron situation. I skip
10 minutes in when the interview is
already in progress. I literally have
never heard him say his name. Rick...
And also this is the most obscure
thing. He's very popular.
Yes. Yeah, but how
many of our listeners, how much
overlap is there with Beato?
And he's a music guy.
Rick Beato. Makes sense to me.
Hey, Beato on the beat.
Maybe people are watching these 90 minute
Butch Vig interviews with
Rick Beato. I do. I
watch things like this, but I skip
past the part where he tells me to subscribe
and I don't need to know any
of that. He does videos where he counts down
like the 50 best 90s rock and
roll songs and he just kind of plays like five
seconds of them and he kind of nods his head like this
and he goes great song and then he goes like
great riff and then goes to the next one.
Content. Great. Yeah.
That's not in
debate.
Great content.
What's in debate is my right to call him
the wrong name or to call anyone the wrong
name. Okay, well going forward we'll see.
Focus on the amount of words that
we get right. Praise
God for the right pronunciations.
Not insult him for the wrong.
Oh, they will.
Clearly they will. Love that
you pronounce the whales or the space
whale. Pergil.
Well, what do we think?
I've been
thinking about this. I'm all on
edge about it now. I think
it maybe is Pergil. I think it's Pergil.
Yeah. Yeah. In my head
it was like Perjil, but I
checked to make sure. Yeah.
I watched the episode, but I don't remember
what they called them. I did
watch this episode of Ahsoka. And even if we were
saying it wrong, guess what? This is
made up. This is pretend.
Somebody made this word up.
Well, you know what? Everybody has their
own data though. You know what I mean?
Like the data thing that needles me.
It's going off a different data set. Some people
are Pergil. They're upset
if we're saying it a little bit wrong.
So I understand.
It's also the type, like no offense
to who's listening here, but the type of audience
we have.
There's definitely people that are going to be upset
about having the wrong word
or pronunciation.
Yes, in the nerdiest avenues. That's what I mean.
Because obviously it gets my
dander up when data.
So there's got to be a lot of listeners like me out there
who are like, Mike, it's Donder.
I think we all know it's Donder.
Cut to genuine comments. I thought it
was Donder.
Anyway, let's get into it. I do think that Star Tours
is better than the Millennium Falcone.
You could
say it like Harrison says in the movies,
Falcon.
He says Millennium Falcon in the movies,
and I always say Falcon, but he says Falcon.
He says it in like it's well, it's because he's
so cocksure.
I think it's cool that he says
I think if I said Falcon,
it would be a problem forever.
Again, I recognize the hypocrisy.
Jason, I feel like
I owe you an apology, but of course the next time you say
something like Mama, I'm still going to say
it. I'm going to jump all over you.
I had to look
up
the actor who was Andor
just now, because
I, you know,
You were at a brain
fart, perhaps?
Well, I was like, wait, the
two actors from Ito Mama
Tambien, Diego Luna, and
Jason just sticks with it
and doesn't adjust. I love it.
Gail Garcia-Vernal.
They are forever tied in my
that movie made
such an impression on me.
That you'll confuse the two actors sometimes.
I will confuse the two actors careers.
And they are both in the very underrated
Will Ferrell Spanish language
vehicle Casa de Mi Padre.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I haven't seen it.
That's fun. Check that out.
His pronunciations of things
I don't know. He studied very hard.
We don't got coaches
on this thing. No, we don't have coaches.
Anyway, I love
both of the wonderful
actors. Sure.
Terrific stuff. I have not watched Andor
yet, but it's the Michael
Clayton guy doing a prison break
TV show. So, like,
I got to get around to that. Like many things,
I've watched half of it.
Watched half the episodes. You know,
here's the, yeah, here's where
we're in trouble here because, like,
okay, everybody
let's not make a big, just really quickly say how much
I'm going to go through the rundown of the three shows
that are represented in this.
Everybody just say how much you've seen.
Mandalorian, almost made it
to the end of season one. I've done two
full seasons. There's three seasons
of Mandalorian, I believe. I've done two
full seasons of Mandalorian. I did a whole book of
Boba Fett. Forgot that one, yeah.
I did
half of Andor. Not that it's bad, it's good.
It's a much, it's a real
show. And then
I've done spots, like little spots
of Ahsoka, including the whale episode.
Nothing on the last two for me, Jason.
We already said no Andor.
I haven't watched Andor, I haven't watched Ahsoka,
watched three quarters of the first season of
Andor. That's exactly where I,
were you in the same boat as me where episode
one, you were like,
oh my god, it's everything
that the movies haven't been
satisfied, we're back, this
is pulpy, this is, like,
it's reinventing, and then like
four episodes later, you're like, oh no, maybe I'm
good, I might be fine. Maybe I'm good to go.
I'm more just like lost
track, I just kept forgetting about it.
I was just watching other things. I'm
all caught up on X-Men 97.
I'm halfway, I'm like three episodes in.
Not halfway, I'm like three.
I'm shocked by it. I love it, I love that.
Those three episodes are great.
And you know, I was thinking about it a lot,
like watching these new scenes
and like this new
levels, these new Star Tours
levels, cause I'm like,
I think, I think
they were expecting,
I would say X-Men 97 is near
a universal claim, but it's very
popular, it's very well reviewed.
I think they just thought, like,
oh, every time we put out a Star
Wars, we will get this organic
response.
We will get this, like, praise.
Well, I think there's been
a hubris, you might call it,
and a number of these
giant franchises, when it's like, all of a sudden.
Do they not know the parable
of Darth Plagueis the Wise?
You would, first of all, they don't know that,
I think. A lot of the people in charge do not
know that. But yes, that's very important.
So no, I think you're correct.
Oftentimes, you can see where everything,
all of a sudden there's a break from, like, just,
oh, I thought everyone just liked the, like,
if it was called Star Wars, I thought everyone was going to love it.
Like, what happened?
I don't know. Marvel, DC,
it happened with everything. Yeah.
And I think that everybody was shocked, like,
oh my god, the gravy train's not going to run forever?
What the fuck?
Yeah. And then, of course, they all
learned their lesson and realized,
well, perhaps, instead of trying to
prop up an ailing franchise,
we should try to find the next
new Star Wars. No, no, no, no, no.
Shut up. Original voices. Shut up.
Original ideas. Shut up. No.
No, no, no. Never that.
No, no, no, never that. Never that. Even though.
You're not wrong, but I'm also
like, I have not seen any of the
Deadpool movies and I keep seeing the
new trailers for Deadpool and Wolverine
and I'm like, I might have to get
caught up on Deadpool. Like,
I kind of like these trailers. I'm in on
Deadpool, Wolverine. Jack, I'm in on
Jackman. He's back. I like
Jackman that much. You know,
he's in the yellow outfit. If he's in the right outfit,
I'm on board. You could
win me back with the right outfit
for a character. That is
how shallow I am. The outfit looks good.
I think it looks good at first. You put down the outfit.
I put down the outfit. There were screenshots
leaked of him. I didn't like the screenshots.
We got mic points happening.
He said, I don't think the yellow outfit
looks good. I said, I think it does look good.
I think Jackman in the yellow looks good.
I think it looks better. I appreciate that you're
admitting this. Filmed. Yeah, I think it looks
better in the trailers. Okay, this is good.
Than the screenshots. I do think
it looks better. Hey, Jane
mentioned, speaking of Jackman,
Jackman did Gaston
in Beauty and the Beast on
Broadway. Oh, he did? Oh, wow, I actually
didn't know that. Yeah, yeah. He was speaking of yellow
outfits, or partially. There's some yellow in there.
Yeah, red and yellow.
Scott thinks there's yellow
in Gaston. Found a
problem. He thinks he's
Gaston with Lumiere.
Lumiere is a golden
yellow. That's not
Gaston, it's Lumiere.
Let's make sure we
talk about these things.
Thank God they do this, though.
We complain about this all the time.
Toy Story, they did one update.
They never did an update on Toy Story
4. The screen rides,
it just doesn't happen.
They pump us full of
promises and leave us on the side
of the road without water
or shelter. With Star Tours, they're pretty
good about it. I would say really good
in the scheme of things. Maybe
the best at updating
rides and giving you a fun little thing.
Not only that, but the
star power rises.
I don't think that
they aren't in it
because they're celebrities, they're in it because they're
the stars of the franchise. But that was
never too much of a runner
of any previous
Star Tours, other than like
Anthony Daniels being part of all of it from the
beginning. But now
it's like this Star Wars
franchise rite of passage that at
some point the major actors and characters
end up appearing in the Star
Spear at some point.
They have such a library now.
They did Billy D. Williams,
which is great.
They should have gotten Harrison
for a second
to do it. But if they didn't get him
for Indiana Jones,
how are they going to get him? That was a whole controversy.
When he was doing episode 9, they should have
tricked him or something. Hey, look over
here and then read, here's the teleprompter
and it doesn't matter. As long as you
got him.
You sure you want that?
Of course I want that.
Yeah, what am I saying?
The more pissed off.
Yeah, Star Tours.
You got to get out of here.
There's purgels coming
at you.
What is it called? Watch out for the
purgels.
We're hauling raptors or
whatever. And then they can't, they have to
cut out and sing. I didn't agree
to this and then cut out. Yeah, yeah. Just leave it in
because it needs to be a certain amount for the ride
to work.
I think they should leave any of that in.
We're like reading, what is that?
Or you could just say line. Line.
And he does it
and the only way, like
the only time they could get with him to do it
he was on his way to a
Halloween party with Calista. With the bottle
of wine, yeah. He's dressed like
the mask.
You think it'll be distracting that Oncelos
dressed like the mask?
That's fine.
Look, it's her.
They got him dressed as Oncelo
because Calista wanted to do a
couple's costume.
And we tell people, she's Oncelo
too. We tell people we're a Han duo.
That is somewhat one of their costumes.
Yeah. I enjoyed that.
He likes the costumes. We know. We cracked it on that
episode, I think.
He has the nun with the funny
glasses, like the
gag store glasses.
Everyone remembers.
Yes, so
I didn't know the degree
of new stuff
that was done, even before when I proposed
doing this.
And in digging in
if we're being a little
loose with the tangents, maybe
it's because
really it's the
missions. Really it's the hologram
transitions in the middle. Because I started
doing it, I did like a watch through,
realized that the beginning scenes are essentially
the same. The one that collected all of
them still had the
Wookie centric
first scene, which I love. I love
the Wookie kind of shaking
his fist, like, hey, come back
here. There's minor adjustments
to those first scenes.
I mean the take off, looking for the spy
kind of scene. By the way,
you know what I meant to say?
As we cover
the newest of the new Star Tours
stuff, something that we have not done on the show
is Star Tours Adventures Continue.
I know. Did part one
with Kyle forever ago.
Part two we have not done. It seems like something
we should try to do in the
calendar year. I agree with that.
Here we can piece
three of these levels now. No, not three.
Three transmissions. Three transmissions and
one level. Are off the
table. Thus making it so that
that one will be only three and a half
hours. And one wreath side vertical
screened. And one vertical.
And we've knocked out a vertical. Because Ahsoka
shows up. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Call those Snapchats.
I call those Snapchats on the side.
Again, it sounds so natural.
Yeah, yeah. The current
stuff. Are you the young one now?
We're all trading hats.
Well, I don't know. After
sweatshirts or a young person's term,
I think I'm forever the young one. I think that's
right. Yeah. I remain
baffled. I still
don't know. I came back from
the recording in a fog. I heard
that. I don't know. They were saying that sweatshirts
are a young person's term. And that
you're not supposed to say blue jeans after
college. I don't know. Maybe
Mike was fucking with me, but Jason seems
sincere. I honestly,
maybe there's gaslighting involved. I don't
know. I don't even, honest to God,
I listen back to it. I don't
remember that chunk much. I don't know how
we got to any of it. I'll never forget it.
Yeah. I don't really remember it.
I know kind of where we started,
but I don't know. I don't know. I think
I blacked out. I don't know. Jason was
serious, though. That's how it
seemed. And let's get it through all of our heads.
None of us are the young person on this
show. No, no. There's no such thing.
Nope. Unless we have a guest
under 30. We should try
to find one of those someday.
I disagree. Hey, we had that
guy who was, you know, from
oh, yeah, from
there we go.
See, he was a nice young man.
A nice young man. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what? And now that I think about it
on the Zoom, he looked pretty, he looked
pretty sharp in a sweatshirt. But I didn't want
to say that because that's not my term to say.
Yeah, don't say it. It sounds weird
when you say it.
Everybody got the creeps when I said it.
Old man Scott saying sweatshirt, a
clear young person's term. We're getting up there.
We've got to get some quarter zips.
Some what? Quarter zip sweaters?
Oh, quarter zips.
I've never heard them called
quarter zips before. That's what they're called on
store websites. Wow.
Quarter zips. Store websites.
Do you know quarter zips?
Mike, you're
trying to get me to say no so that
the new flood of comments
Jason knows quarter zips.
I know quarter zips.
I know how these fucking comments work.
Quarter zip, the quarter zip page
at Macy's shows right up.
No, I don't think you're making something up.
I just didn't know what it, I just never heard
that. I never heard it called that before
and now that's one of my new favorite things
to say. Maybe Jason is the young person.
Quarter zips.
Oh, you're going to be a quarter zip boy.
Quarter zip man.
He has a lot of quarter zips.
Oh, if it's a your father thing then it's not a young
person. Okay.
Quarter zips are not for young people.
Quarter zips. I don't.
That's why the defiance of young people,
that's why they wear sweatshirts, to spit
in the face of the quarter zips of their fathers.
That seems practical.
If you're a little hot you just unzip it a little
but it still keeps you warm.
I don't really understand the quarter zip
to be honest with you. I don't understand the design
other than like, oh, a little stuffy in here.
It just feels like, I don't know,
it feels frustrating. You should be able to unzip the whole thing.
After the first level
you get a transmission from
Asoka Tano. Yeah, I know her.
She's from the show Asoka.
She's cool. I like her. Jason wants to yell names
of old movies she was in.
Here's
some of the issues. Ultimately,
you know, what are these?
Like, hey, you're traveling with a friend
of mine, the spy.
Head to the rendezvous point.
Good luck.
I'm looking at these ultimately like, what I wrote
down was, they sure did film these.
There are not a lot
of exciting things or sentences
given to you
as a viewer of
a writer, I should say.
We didn't know when we started.
Grogu does a funny
little thing that he does on the show.
Eating the frog, which is still funny.
Yes, Mandalorian.
I'm not going to say the name
of the, I know he's not called
that. I know the character's name.
I know what his name is, but
now I'm scared to say it.
His name, first name is Din.
I know that.
I'm not going to say his last name.
They don't come for you, they're going to come for me.
I know, I know I'm not saying it.
His name is Din.
He kind of
just gives you a very dry
explanation
or instruction.
I don't think so.
I don't know if we have confirmation on that.
I don't think so, though.
The video I watched, obviously I was confused
by the video I watched, but the video I watched,
I couldn't, it was sort of in the back row
and I couldn't fully get it.
It wasn't as glaring as
No Bradley Cooper on Guardians Coaster,
but yeah, probably not him.
Yeah, yeah.
But you've got a frog
or something
floating in front of
Grogu, and then he
laps it with his tongue.
He eats it.
And Mandalorian says
what? I have it.
Spit that out,
he says. There we go.
I could do V.O. for it. Spit that out.
It's not fully Harrison, but
he's like kind of gross. Spit that out.
Wow, this is a new debuting
impression. Mike's Din.
It's my Din. Wow.
Hey, be careful out there,
star doors. You don't want to get hurt.
Pitch perfect. Spit that out.
Definitely, if you just started
that without, not in context.
You know. Yeah, if you cold open an episode.
Welcome to Podcasts, alright.
Whoa, Din, just a beer in the room?
Hey, it's Din. Hey, it's me, Din.
Be careful. I can't take off the helmet.
They made a character where I can't
take off the helmet, but the actor has
just gotten more and more famous.
He's never on set.
Except for the one,
two episodes of, I don't know, maybe there's more
now where I take off the helmet.
He takes off the helmet on the Bill Burr
episode in like the first or second season.
I think second season. But is it the back of his
head? You can see his face.
Yeah, yeah, it's him. Oh, okay.
It's Pedro, yeah. And then he shows his face
to Grogu, spoiler alert,
before Grogu goes off with Luke
Skywalker to be trained.
Because I don't mean taking the helmet
off practice, I mean like it's a religious
thing for the Mandalorian. You're not supposed
to do it. They keep their battle helmets on.
So that's a massive thing.
But he took it off
an episode prior, so it's baffling
to me why they didn't save that
for the moment when Grogu leaves him.
Truly, I don't know.
So maybe somebody can explain it to me. But I was like,
wait, what? The moment where he
takes it off for Grogu is the moment he should have taken it off
the first time. It's important once, it's extra
important twice. Yeah, and then he goes off with Deep Fake
Luke.
I'm really happy Deep Fake Luke
is not anywhere to be found in these.
Can I say, I don't
want to open a can of worms.
And now I know, okay,
there's this thing that's said all the time.
It was said to me last night
by a fellow podcaster whose
name I think you could guess.
They gotta redo Rise of Resistance
and they gotta put in the characters and our
friends and the people. If they did that,
are we looking at Deep Fake
Luke? We all think we want Luke.
Actually, I don't know if I think that.
There's that notion of like, they're gonna redo
this someday and put the old
characters in it. But do we really
want that creepy
ass video? I have watched Deep Fake
Luke at the end of that
episode. Is it a season finale
he shows up, Deep Fake Luke?
It's a season finale and then he's on a full Book of Boba
Fett as Deep Fake Luke. Oh, okay.
I like the season finale.
It's real wonky in there, I would say.
There's a lot more Deep Fake Luke in the
middle of the day. They should maybe be.
They should be a little more sparing, I'd say.
What's funny is the guy they had
playing Deep Fake Luke looks
just like Young Mark Hamill also.
Yeah, I'm always
in favor of practical effects
and it's crazy what they can do with
makeup. Well, the robots can be fine.
You can make the robot look like Young Luke,
no problem. He doesn't have to look like Deep Fake Luke.
That would be really weird
if they made him look a little fucked up.
Yeah, robots they could do, but if we're
doing any video screening content,
I think now we're in Deep Fake
Luke territory. Is that gonna
fix the ride? Put the hood
over his head if he's giving you some instruction.
You don't have to see him necessarily
or it's just in a lot of darkness.
This ride sucks. I want my
friends in it. Yeah, you could put a hood over him.
As long as I see 10% of their face.
That's only on the pre-show. The robots
can look like any age. You can have
Young Harrison, you can have anything.
What are you saying?
What do you mean by robots?
I'm saying if
they put more animatronics on Rise of the Resistance,
this is never happening. No, no, I thought
you were talking about like robots
in film, TV shows or something.
And I'm like, did I miss robots? No, no, no.
We mean on Rise of the Resistance because
it's not my friends.
That has to get done someday.
Which will not happen, you're right.
No, the bigger issue with Rise of the Resistance
is making it so you get fucked up
when you're riding it. That's my number one.
That'd be number one on the fix.
New ride vehicles where you get fucked like
jostle your body. Hardcore.
Maybe take the seat belts off
it too. And you see your version of what might
be called Rise of the Resistance hardcore.
There's a big red stamp
on it. Right. Yeah.
My version of that is much different.
I said my version of
Rise of the Resistance hardcore
is much different. Yeah.
Yours is more
snuff filmy. You're hanging with like
Jabba's dancers.
Oh yeah.
The big lip, the big mouth.
Oh, well that's nice noodles.
Sice noodles, excuse me.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Jason and Sice Noodles.
I like this parents. I like this for you.
My whole past. Sice
Noodles.
Or Max Rebo.
Max Rebo's cool. He did not die
in Book of Boba Fett. He got out. He was not
playing the night that the bar was bombed. Don't worry.
Well, for anyone who knows what that meant,
I hope that cleared things up. Max Rebo was in Book of
Boba Fett, but playing at a different
bar and then that place gets blown up.
But they like made a point somewhere
maybe online to be like Max was
not in the room. I love that Max is
gigging. Yeah, of course.
He's got to. Yeah, yeah.
One club is not going to. Jason and Sice
Noodles. Yeah, those big, I like the
who's the lips? Who are the big lips?
I really like that parents. She's got a
trunk and lips.
She's got a long trunk, long skinny trunk.
Give me a trunk and then the
lips are on the end of it, right?
Yeah, yeah. So that's Jason.
That's what your Rise of the Resistance.
You've been mad about just no Sice
Noodles sitting next to you in the car
while you ride. No opportunity to
smooch Sice Noodles.
I don't know what Star Wars language
she speaks, so I don't know how to translate
come up and see me sometime, big boy.
I'm sure she's saying that, though.
I have to assume.
Come up and see me sometime is becoming a
clear occurrence. Yeah, you say that a lot.
You're like, OK, Mae West can't use
it anymore. She's long gone.
It's my catchphrase now.
That is funny.
Yeah, calling in the Star Wars
episode.
I'm saying this is my catchphrase now.
Why not?
You can't copyright a term like that.
I don't know. Maybe you can. I was wondering
like, do people like everything is being like
bought up by company? Could somebody
try to buy Mae West's come up
and see me sometime?
When do we get the deep fake Mae West?
We're all asking for it.
Oh, I think that will happen.
Oh, Mae West could meet Ricky Stinnicky.
You know? Wow.
OK, that's interesting.
Look, it's an old
thing and a current thing.
No, you're right.
How do we take
Stinnicky to the next level
with a time traveling Mae West
done post demise?
Maybe Ricky
and size noodles
and Jason Sherwood.
It's a trio thing.
It's a throuple.
Three tickets for challengers.
I noted this, that you seem
a little interested in challengers.
I was warned about you
long ago that you were interested
in being a third.
What is it about this
film?
What is doing it?
I don't know.
Man, rise to the resistance.
It doesn't have my friends in it.
Why don't they redo it with Mae West
and Ricky Stinnicky?
It's an easy change out.
Just take Finn and put Ricky Stinnicky's head on him.
The best friend they never
had who became real and became
their real best friend, I assume.
I bailed pretty fast on that.
Ricky
Stinnicky, I saw a couple of people
talking about this and even I had heard
it talked about a specter
that haunted Hollywood
comedy.
This script was bouncing
around.
I remember hearing about it years ago.
It's like, oh, this new
Ricky Stinnicky is going to be
a fig.
There's a ton of those.
I'm not sure if I'm going to say it.
It got made 28 years later.
Okay.
You know what?
Thank God we found some other stuff to talk about.
If I'm being honest, that Andor
one is pretty.
He did the
intro for
The Void.
I almost think that one was better.
This one is dry
and nothing.
I was getting excited about, I think that the new,
like the episodes seven, eight, nine actors
had fun with it, I think.
Like Finn and Poe in their little side screen
Snapchat appearances, I think they gave it their all.
I think Billy Dee, oddly, for somebody who you might think
could be kind of, what is this, what am I doing?
I think he was fantastic.
These are not the most spirited hologram cameos
I've ever seen in Star Tours.
Yeah, I agree.
I mean, you're like, the star power is good.
I think the Mandalorian one is really good
and maybe the first funny one of these
mid-rides transmissions.
And I would be excited if I got it.
I think as these, because apparently the plan is
these are gonna run through June,
through season of The Force,
and then they will get put into the randomizer
and they will be possible options forever.
And I think in general, when I get on that ride,
what do I want?
Next time I go on it, I think the ones I want the most
are Lando or Mandalore.
Lando or Mando.
Yeah, I think that's, yeah, I think so.
Not to say, there could be better ones.
I like Yoda, but I've seen Yoda plenty of times.
I like Leia, but I've seen Leia many times.
My ideal, yeah, that's what I'd be gunning for, maybe.
Yeah, just a little bit anew,
but also I didn't see Lando too many times.
So I'd welcome him.
I agree.
Where do you want the last scene to end up?
Where do you wanna be dropped off?
That's a good question.
Well, I need to, admittedly,
I only did this by watching videos.
I didn't see, I have not seen Pergill's in person,
so I'd kind of like to.
I was thinking how, I think there's more good first,
scenes than last scenes.
I think some last scenes become just sort of like
muddy action, a little bit hard to follow.
Yes, I agree.
But I actually think Crait is pretty good.
I think getting to explore what all those
red stalagmites, stalagmites,
when you go like into the ground in Crait,
I think it's good.
And I like the Jar Jar.
Naboo is the answer.
Yeah, Naboo is really fun.
Naboo is the best.
Is the definitive answer, you're saying.
I believe so.
You were getting tense when I was talking about Crait there.
Like Scott's fucking up, he's over there,
spinning his wheels.
What is this guy doing?
Very visually straight.
He's ruining it.
End of the podcast.
He's acting like an amateur here,
doesn't know what the actual answer is.
I knew with Crait, I knew that I was in dicey territory
by everybody take a deep breath,
complimenting something related to The Last Jedi.
I know that that's, but I knew we could all
get through it together as adults,
as people in this world trying to help each other.
Right, yes.
But no, I think I like Naboo.
And then you get the little fun thing usually at the end
with the break through the glass.
Yes, that's one of the best pieces.
The glass is really good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But some of this can be in.
But let's go through you guys.
Your preference, Naboo, Jason, next start to his visit,
what are you hoping to see?
I think Naboo, I think Crait is very visually striking,
but I definitely saw,
how many times did I see episode one in theaters
when I was like 13?
Is it over five?
I think three times, at least, I think.
Okay, so you mean that's why you like Naboo?
No, well, I was 13, I obviously have more affection
for the movie I saw when I was 13
than the one that I saw when I was like,
you know, when was I?
What do you mean?
Ages can't be coloring opinions on any of this.
No.
Jason, this is an insane thing that you've said
about everyone's Star Wars opinions.
Uh-huh.
The idea that the age that you were
when you saw them might possibly have.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You liked the one you saw in high school.
I remember being at Sears once,
they had a big display before we saw the movie,
and I bought a shirt with the characters,
and my mom bought the soundtrack to play in the car.
It was so exciting.
It was so exciting hearing the episode one soundtrack
before seeing the movie, and you're like,
what is happening?
What is Duel of the Fates about?
Oh, boy, yes.
Maybe one of the best Star Wars music stings.
Sure, of course.
Let's make sure that we talk Pergil.
I mean, this is very exciting.
Mainly, these new sequences are about the transmissions
and getting the actor cameos in there.
That's what they can easily slot in and out, especially.
But I think if you're going on Star Tours
for the next couple months, what you are guaranteed to see
is this Pergil sequence.
What are Pergil?
Pergil are space whales.
Space whales.
You suddenly land in a very cloudy atmosphere
full of space whales.
It's pretty striking.
It's pretty cool.
I was not previously familiar with this.
I think they've been part of Star Wars mythology
since Rebels, possibly.
Yeah, they should have been Rebels, from what I saw.
And then they started showing up in live action
with Mandalorian and Ahsoka.
Yeah, Ahsoka's the big tie.
They're in it a lot.
I think they're a little bit in the primary sequence.
And then she's also in the, she pops up
in this third act sequence as well.
They also, you have to note, they
are whales in space who can jump into hyperspace.
And I'm like, back on board.
So that got you jacked up.
Yeah, this got me in.
You got fired up.
Silly inventive idea.
No, this does seem cool.
It seems like a cool sequence in the ride.
Now, I have to bring up, and when I say have to,
don't really have to do this, especially
this late in the episode.
There's a character that I've loved
that I brought up before from the Archie Ninja Turtle
comics called Cuddly the Cowlick,
which is a giant cow's head that was
an interdimensional traveler.
You're saying there was a way to not bring up
Cuddly the Cowlick?
I believe, yes.
I think there was, but I didn't.
I don't see that.
I took the wrong, I took the other road.
I did bring it up.
Wait, stop.
You're going the wrong way.
So I feel like these.
Stop immediately.
No, no, shut up, officer.
I was like, well, these whales are cool.
I like them, but there's a cow's head,
disembodied giant cow's head that
traveled through the universe like this before, I feel.
So I was a little bit like, a bit of a rip-off here, huh?
Wait, what?
Why is one the other?
There's one that's a cow's head.
Because the whales travel through,
like they go through hyperspace.
They travel through hyperspace.
But one's a cow's head.
I know, but they're animals in space
that don't have to breathe.
I'm just saying.
How can a space whale be a rip-off of a cow head?
Because they would do the same things.
They were both sort of floating in space, and they're animal.
We see them as if they're from our.
But aren't they both rip-offs, the theory
that the Earth is floating on the back of a giant turtle
shell?
That the Earth is on the back of a giant turtle?
Well, now you've introduced another episode.
It's some mythology.
I forget where that came from.
Ultimately, yes.
Well, I guess that's right.
I guess Jason's ruined this whole argument here.
I guess he's right about that.
I don't know.
I'm surprised that that's where you're going with it.
Only because of the existence in Rebels
can I not be upset about space whales being portrayed who
are not from Avatar Way of Water.
Right.
Do I like these purgles?
I guess I do.
Yeah.
It's interesting motion.
I like that they kind of undulate in this jellyfish way.
Yeah.
I think that they're neat.
However, space whales, you're going
to give me space whales post-Tulcune, post-Piacon.
So we're all upset with these.
Yeah, maybe we are.
Maybe we're, this whole thing is stuff that we don't like.
I don't know.
I do like them.
I'm just saying, after I have been
moved by the journey of a space whale with a lot of depth,
how are you going to give me just a bunch of cattle
going by?
Right.
But while the Tulcune can't travel in space,
that we know of, yeah.
No.
And you know what?
And that's where, though I've used the term space whale,
it is not technically correct.
They are in space in that Pandora is in space,
but also Earth is in space, which would then
lead to that whales are also space whales.
We're space people.
You're space Mike.
I'm space Scott.
That's true.
If that's the definition.
So really, we should have never been calling Tulcune space
whales, and I apologize.
I'll get ahead of that one.
These completely, and I think within,
it doesn't see 3PO call them space whales.
I believe so.
So it is finally an appropriate term.
So I'll give it to them for that.
But I'm just saying, look, I'm still
going to use the broader term.
Whales, I mean, whales not on Earth
is what I'm getting at, ultimately.
So non-Earth whale power rankings, number one, Tulcune.
Number two, Star Trek IV.
Sorry, Per Gill, you are at a distant third.
Yes.
Very, very true.
Sorry, Jason, we're really, Jason was hyped up for now.
We're like, trashing these whales.
I mean, I didn't say they were the number one space
creature, because it also made me think about the dolphins
in Each Acre's Guide to the Galaxy.
The dolphins flee Earth.
So long, and thanks for all the fish, you know?
You know what I'll say, the episode
that I watched of Ahsoka with the space whales,
it's a very, the scene where you really get to enjoy the whales.
It's a very peaceful, beautiful scene.
And I think they felt like they had to have some shooting
at other spaceship antics in this scene.
So I almost think maybe we would enjoy the whales more if,
I mean, I guess if they just, we just chilled out in this level.
You know, I like the idea of, because they made,
finally one of the transitions was a little,
the transmissions was a little funny.
So why not?
How shocking would it be to follow that up with a tranquil
sequence where there's no conflicts
and you just swim with space whales?
I think they got scared that people would be like,
well, that was a letdown.
But I don't think it was, I don't think
it would be if they did it right.
It could be like, wow, I don't want
to ruin this for Mike, but there is a scene in X-Men 97
with a very prominent music cue.
Oh, I think I've seen this, but yeah.
And characters dancing in the air.
That is very peaceful.
And then total chaos.
Is it the Goo Goo Dolls Black Balloon?
It is not Black Balloon, I'm so sorry.
It's actually a few years older than that.
I was gonna say, well, it can't, oh, is it really?
It's from the 2000s.
Cause it's X-Men 97.
No, it's from 92.
Oh, okay.
So it makes sense it would take place.
Maybe it would be in a 97.
Got it.
Okay.
So yeah, so that scene is very,
that scene in the show is very calm.
So you're saying they didn't capture maybe.
So perhaps, yes, if they were like,
they took a little bit of a risk
and they felt like, you know, dad,
the average dad, not the dad's here.
Dad's here would hoot and holler
at a tranquil scene on Star Tours.
We would get so excited, like, oh my God,
there was no action on the scene?
Wow.
Yeah.
Holy crap.
This is what I needed.
A nice, peaceful trip to the skies of Citos.
Yes.
Wait, is this, hang on, is this a,
is this a Beato situation?
It might be.
Is it Seattle?
It might be Seattle.
Guy walked right into it.
I feel like 3PO is, you know, actively impressed
and peaceful in his delivery of seeing the giant whales.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, it's true.
I mean, they give you the little beat of like,
oh, the whales, like it's a beautiful thing or whatever.
But I'm just saying they still had to end,
like, oh, we're following and shooting
and there's still some antics.
Which I mean, yeah, both of our dad lives,
you know, stressful for different reasons.
I know, just like getting to go space whale watching.
Yeah, why do they have to,
why do they have to be weapons involved?
Why do they have to have weapons?
Can't dads just have a nice little trip?
Yes, dads should be able to have a nice little trip.
I will get you guys tickets to whale watching
if you want to go and do it.
Nah, boring.
Earth whale.
Ah, snooze.
Plus you got to get up so early for that.
I want a break from getting up early.
That's what I want.
I want to wake up.
I want to sleep in, you know, 7.30 a.m.
and then choose my own time to go to Disneyland
and watch fake whales.
Yes.
That's true.
Yeah, so it is interesting.
I like that they put the,
the whales make sense of all the different stuff
I've seen on the new Disney Star Wars,
but yeah, like you're missing the essence of the whales.
Okay, yeah.
Well, I agree.
You know, I think if Star Tours
is getting experimental with tone,
I really think it would,
genuinely it would stand out a lot if like.
Yeah.
Now, we're, this is a history going back to what, 87?
The, like, there's a tone that Star Tours has.
What, if there was like a real break
and suddenly there was a,
like, what a surprise it would be for C-3PO.
I don't think he would know what to do.
Yeah.
I think C-3PO, like yourself, Mike, thrives on conflict.
Can C-3PO, and stress, I'm saying,
I can't even imagine C-3PO just being like,
ah, wonderful.
I'm relaxed for the first time in centuries.
I've said this on the show before
that one of my favorite parts of the new Star Tours
is when they give you that heavy beat
and he goes, it looks like we've just joined
the Rebel Alliance.
Like, you get to sit there for like a second or something.
That's kind of like, calm C-3PO.
So I guess, yeah, that's close, yeah, close.
Just hear him kind of, ah, ooh, oh.
Oh, I drifted asleep there, I'm so calm.
And that one over there, and that one over there.
You know what, fuck the resistance, I'm not going back.
I'm part of all of these conflicts
and I seem to not make any difference whatsoever.
In fact, I only get in the way.
Deadline announces C-3PO has joined the cast
of White Lotus, season three.
He gets a little relaxing, but then he quickly finds out
there is conflict under the surface.
Nothing is what it seems at the White Lotus.
She was a prostitute.
What do you mean he's dead now?
If you could somehow, like, C-3PO is like,
R2, land this thing right now at the White Lotus.
And then you land at the White Lotus
and then you somehow can get him out
and then you just watch him on the video screen,
and then go over and get in a beach chair or something.
Yeah, yeah, well, and be tranquil for a minute
and like, ah, welcome, champagne, wonderful.
I've lost my bag of pills and I wonder if you can help me.
It is a lot like the Naboo ending,
like you land in the water, but you're at the White Lotus.
It's a little bit, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, love this.
And then, yeah, where he falls in love
with another droid on vacation,
but then gets insanely jealous of who else
that droid might be fucking.
Oh, yeah.
So is it just in his head?
Are you fucking Steve Zahn?
Tell me.
Steve Zahn is back as a new character.
He's actually playing himself.
Oh, thank you, okay.
Thanks for clarifying that.
Sure.
Visions of Steve Zahn each and every night.
I can't have sex with you anymore, normally.
I cannot compete with Steve Zahn.
I love Steve Zahn.
Is there any, is there any, okay.
I'm trying to think if there's any Star Wars name
that sounds like Zahn that you could, like,
piece together Anthony Daniels saying Steve Zahn.
I guess Grand Admiral Thrawn is close to Zahn.
Sure.
So you got the on there.
Yeah.
If you could just get a Z.
Well, if you don't think they've already AI scanned
Anthony Daniels' voice to use for centuries after he's gone.
For sure.
You've got a new thing coming.
Grand, Thrawn, you know, the Purgill,
I think, helped fight Thrawn.
Yes, Thrawn related to the Purgills, I believe.
Yes.
It's like, we're about, what, 16 years out from, like,
wow, Deadpool.
You've made it to Endor.
I think there's, yeah, so there's an emergency valve
that they just, like, they all look at it every day
as if the money isn't good at Disney and they go,
it's today the day.
All, all characters.
Wow, Deadpool, Mickey Mouse, May West, you're all here.
R2, we've landed on Abbott Elementary.
If the current billboards are any indication,
this is where it's all going.
Every day, everyone walks by there.
Kevin Feige looks at it.
Kathleen Kennedy looks at the valve.
It's today the day.
Look, R2, a help wanted sign
in this Chicago sandwich restaurant.
Perhaps this will be less stressful
than our typical endeavors.
So the billboards, so then the Disney plus Hulu billboards.
Yeah, yeah, oh, this is a pretty, yeah.
I think they're actually pretty cute.
It's gonna be looked at as like,
this was the nice time when it was mere billboards
and not full franchises.
Yeah, they're like, wait, what if,
the Griffins do meet Lilo at the stage?
Yeah, well, yeah, for the first, well, yeah,
Peter will have a, remember the time,
and then C-3 Bill will be in it, and then he'll stay.
He'll transition from the remember-when-a-verts
to and become a regular character.
I mean, I would love to see Lilo Pern make,
like some, Lilo urges Stitch, like, you know,
coughing out a, like, fuck you to make.
Can you give us just a quick,
Well, I walked right in, I've walked right into this.
Yet again, I've walked right into it.
What a mess I'm in.
If Stitch suddenly started using
Quagmire's famous catchphrase,
what might that sound like?
Oh, smart, yeah.
J-J-J-J-J.
Very good.
Well, there's nowhere to go from there.
I think that's the end of our mission.
Yeah.
Well, we did some talking about the new levels
of Star Tours, but what we can now do is,
we've cleared those out.
So at that pace, yes, a Star Tours
Adventures Continue episode will be,
well, it might just, maybe we have to do it,
could we, look, now we've done some experimenting
with formats with our time travel,
reshaping the past episode.
Is there any way that we can do episodes
that are interactive adventures,
where you don't know which Star Tours level
we're going to talk about?
Good question.
That sounds like a job for Mike and only Mike,
and Jason and I to not think about ever again.
Maybe I could figure that out too.
I threw the idea to have me figure out the mechanics,
but that should be fine.
Okay.
There is a way, there is a way to do it, I think.
There is a way to do it.
Because I saw-
But are we crazy enough?
Are we crazy enough to do it?
But there is a way to do it.
Okay, wow.
All right, well, let's commit to it.
Fully interactive Star Tours episodes
where you don't know where you're going to go.
But isn't that all episodes?
You don't know when we'll be talking about May West
and Smoot and Snootles. That's true.
It's really, every one of these is a, you know.
What's going to happen?
Yeah, yeah.
You have, just like C-3PO,
you barely have any control over the vessel.
Yep.
But that's how it is here.
And you survived podcast The Ride of the Second Gate.
Thank you for subscribing.
If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
And where we're due to voting,
we'll be doing an episode about when Gilligan's Island
and 60s Batman met on Family Feud.
And I think you will be, well, no, you won't be shocked.
Actually, you will not be shocked at all
how much more enthusiasm there is
about old actors on a game show
than like the average feeling
about all of the new Disney Plus Star Tours shows.
Survey says.
Survey says, it's a hit.