Club 3
The Gilligan family and the Batman family on your marks
You're the winning contestants on Carlson's Club 3
Clash of the Kitch
That's it, right? That's the right song
I know I just watched this
Or is that Price is Right?
Yeah, I think so
Shit!
It is Price
Family Feud is the jazzier
Yeah, yeah
Even as I hum that, I feel am I doing the Elvis walkout music
It's very similar
It is similar
Yeah, yeah, kind of big fanfare
Can't believe I blew that
Look, we did our home
We all watched it
I watched it
We will prove it with our YouTube search history
We did despite any fuzziness we have about the music
So Mike, here we are
This is the result of a poll in which many of your last place to second to last place candidates from Club 3 polls passed
All went up against each other
And what I think is quite remarkable is that in a competition of last place finishers
You managed to insert a new last place to be the last place to not rule them all
It was entirely just to recap for any
Listen, if you don't know what we're talking about
Yeah, we're kind of revisiting old topics all suggested by Mike
All of which kind of have like 60s, 70s kitsch about them at the center of them
All suggested by listeners who are like after your heart
Right
They're chasing you and a number of these would be a lot of fun
At the last minute in the last Club 3 episode we inserted into the poll a new idea never tested in a poll
Which was Waylon Flowers and Madame
Madame, yes
Who still require context despite us having talked about it
Because I do believe nobody knows what this is or doesn't care, I don't know
It's like very 60s, 70s variety show mainstay ventriloquist act
Yes
We put that in, let's try that
Within the episode I'm starting to think
Oh my god, this might take it
Because it's the energy of the new
And also it's needling me
And maybe that all will dovetail into
It's an easy win for Waylon Flowers and Madame
Instead, last place, straight to last place
There was never a moment in the poll where it wasn't last place
People looked into this and said no
I mean one photo is all you need to know
If you're not into the photo
There's no way to get you back on board
And I feel like that was kind of my arc
Where I initially was like you know what
I really don't know that much about Waylon Flowers and Madame
This could be very interesting
That's often how I pick a Club 3
I'm like oh that could be very interesting
A chance to learn, yes
And then I saw one photo and I'm like
I'm gonna watch something, I'm gonna put a movie on
Yes, anything else
What are you showing us Mike?
I'm showing a photo of Madame, the puppet
The old lady puppet
And she's bathing a man
I think it's the third episode of her sitcom Madame's Place
Which I think has over 70 episodes
And I don't know if this, to me
This makes me want to talk about it more
But I think to the general population
And even to the freaks on Club 3
And I say that in a good way
This is too much for them
It's still, you managed to find something
That was too far even for who we've gathered here
And again, I really
I think it managed to make it over an incredible hump
That like, I played into it too
You predicted that I would recoil at whatever you were gonna say
Then you said that and I did
And I was like
This is gonna get picked to troll me
And even that was not enticing enough
People still, it was, yeah
And what you're showing, it's a good litmus test
You see an old lady puppet giving a sponge bath to a man
A human man
Do we know who the human man is?
I think it's Eddie
I'm not sure which character that is
Again, because we didn't get to do the research
We didn't get to learn like Jason wanted
Because we were not given that assignment
How about this though?
When I say this to you
Will it make you want to see it more?
Madame's Place specifically
Corey Feldman plays Buzzy St. James
Like Buzzy as a kid
This is like presumably
This is like on the way to Goonies
Yes
I don't
You know, I'll be honest
I've been to a Corey Feldman concert
I have engaged with the Corey Feldman phenomenon
I don't know how much further I want to engage
Okay
Even with that, even having attended a show
I might have hit peak Corey personally
As much as the name is pretty good
You had to let one of the angels down
You're like, I'm sorry
I met someone
Her name's Erin
She's really great
Yeah, I'm so sorry
Yeah, I met someone, Erin
She's my wife
That's how I met her
No, no, I was saying it was like
This is a history
It was will they, won't they
And you were with you and Erin
And you and one of Corey Feldman's angels
I had to choose
Ultimately
Love won
I chose to stay on earth instead of go to heaven
Anyway, I don't
I mean, now where does this leave you
Does this make you more determined
Does it make it more likely to be a birthday shot
Where are you left with Madam given the last place finish
In some ways it's the least successful choice ever
I feel like by some metrics
That it lost to all losers
Right, all losers beat it
So it's the least popular choice of all time
Which makes it very attractive
I might be a little more curious now
Because I feel like
Ages and ages ago
If you put blanks place
Like that was an easy set
Oh, it's called so and so's
Yeah, it was just like Jason
And it wasn't successful
It only ran for like a hundred and nine episodes
Everyone only made ten million dollars
Yeah
Off of it
But it was a failure
Off the thing that no one remembers
On this earth
No, Jason, you were right before
When you declared you weren't interested in
We got to get you back to where you were
When you saw the photograph
That was right
You overshot it
Here's what's going to happen
One day
I'm going to bring two bags here
One with the recording equipment
And the second
Containing a madam puppet
That's what's going to happen
No, I'm resigned
And you know what
You said it the last time this came up
You said
What you need to do, Scott
Is just delay this as long as you possibly can
But that correctly calibrated me
Where I'm like
I know I can't push it off forever
It is going to happen
She is coming
It's just a matter of when
One day
Now, madam would say
She would really like that
It's like a double entendre
I don't have the voice down yet
But I'm not saying it in a double entendre way
You could do any voice
And convince me it's the voice
I'm not sure
I think anytime these characters
Have appeared on screen
I have shut off what I am watching
So quickly that I don't even get to hear the voice
I'm not sure I've ever heard madam speak
Okay
And I'd like to keep it that way
Well, one day it will change
But I don't know what day that is
But you're saying
If you had to do an impression
It's like
It's kind of like that
Yeah
Well, shocking
Innovative
All right
Well, we await the arrival of the bag
But for now
I do think that the poll landed
In the most pleasant place
Given the possibility of unpleasantness
Throughout this
I think anything besides madam
I would have been cool with
Hopefully you definitely would have been cool with, Mike
The runner up Paul Linde Halloween special
I'm shocked this didn't win
Yeah, you made some calls about
You thought it was going to be this or
Ah, now it's not coming to me
Superheroes
Legends or whatever of superheroes
Yeah
Or Spiderman
The musical thing
Yeah, that could have been it too
Didn't make it
I think maybe Paul Linde Halloween
Just didn't feel right
Because it's not Halloween
Yeah
But given that we tend to
Carry over the runner ups
Into another poll
I think it makes all the sense in the world
To put this into the Halloween poll
Where it had lost previously
Right
But we'll put it in the Crypt 3 poll
Sure, yeah
Which will be in September
In preparation for October
Makes sense
You earned it, Paul Linde
Good job
You hung in there
But this one
Oh, wait
And next month
Where there is no theme
And no particular direction
Club 3 subscribers
Throw ideas into the comments as always
I think we have good ideas from previous polls
That I'll throw in
But new stuff would be good too
And that will all go up against
American Girl Cafe
Which remains
Yes
In the running
A previous runner up
Right
But for now
Let's read the suggestion
Which I had to go way back into the archives
And figure out
When this was even from
This is from Matt Kamegis
Who I feel like suggested
Another one recently
Listeners, it's on you
To track how many of these
You have won
Because I think
That a number of people have won too
And I'd like to celebrate
Whoever gets to three
I don't want to
That's a good achievement
So Matt, if it's you
Let us know
If you get three on Club 3
Please tell us
But the suggestion
In 1983
The cast of Gilligan's Island
Went up against the cast of 66 Batman
On the family feud
Bob Denver is AWOL
Big spoiler
What a bummer at the top
But that is made up by the fact
That Vincent Price is on the Batman team
And of course
Alan Hale is there
You can find several versions of this on YouTube
This was in a
It was in a poll way back
And it came in
Second to last
Against Warner Brothers Studio Store
Which took it all the way
And we did an episode about
But thank you Matt
Eventually it came to pass
And here we are
And thank you for
About as pleasant of a viewing assignment
As we could be
Because we've gotten some bad ones
We've gotten some
Like long watches
That were very dispiriting
And here we're just watching an old
Pleasant episode of a game show
With people we love
Wonderful
Thank you
Thank you very much
Family Feud fans here
I feel like it's probably
I guess my favorite game show
And not just because Steve Harvey
Now hosts Family Feud
Yeah
No those
When you're seeing a Steve Harvey clip
From Family Feud going viral
When you're seeing
I was thinking about this
How he really
Jason we were on a text thread recently
Where Jack Benny came up
And I feel like he is
Is he the current Jack Benny?
In a lot of ways
Is he the guy who can get
The most laughs out of
Not saying any words
Or even making too much of an expression
Yes
We're just so loaded for Bear
That when Steve Harvey walks away
From the desk towards us
Looking worn down and upset
He can milk that for like a full minute
Before he even says anything specific
About the suggestion that he
It's pretty amazing
It is amazing
He does that better than anybody
Maybe even better
Jack Benny would do that
But he has the same kind of move
He would do
He would just put his hand
The hand
But then he looked to the side
Like he was exasperated
Steve will do it in different ways
I feel like
He's got a couple different
Variant ways he can do
The I can't believe you just said that
I'm offended by that
Yeah
It's a matter of how much
Does he walk around
Right
Yeah does he throw a hand up
On the head
Does he like bend down
Yeah
Have worn down
Head in hands
Yeah
He is the best family feud
Host of all time
Have I said that on the show before?
I think he got it
Yeah
I'm with you
Not that it's
I mean I like Louis Anderson
I like Richard Carn
I don't
But Steve Harvey
I want to say
That I like John O'Hurley
But I think I like him
From other things
And frankly forgot
That he was the host
Until looking at a Wikipedia earlier
And that
I've seen a few of those
And though that's fun
But Harvey
He's the best
He's the longest running now
He's 14 years
Oh and he realized that
It's been that long
Which I think
Richard Dawson
Who was hosting
In this era
And kind of the like
You know main classic one
That you think of
I think nine years for him
And then some comeback
A little bit after
Later day
After the thing happened
But
Oh right right
Which thing
Oh the thing
Yeah but
Steve Harvey
Longest running
I think yeah
I think it's his
Yeah
I don't know
I can't see anyone ever
Beating him either
Yeah
Now that's all great
Love the deadpan
Really good host
I'm not going to go
All the way with you Mike
And think that
I should be following
His health regiments
Okay alright
You don't want to get hit
With a red light
Fine
He was the red light
I got confused
There were a lot of
Celebrities in black
Ice bath and red light
He has some sort of
Machine that bathes him
In red light
Steve Harvey's
Red light special
Yes yes
So there's that
But yeah Steve
I do watch
I feel like I watch
Show more now
Than I maybe even did
As a kid
Because like Dawson
Is not really our era
It's like a little bit
Before
I watched it a lot
On the game show network
Yeah
Although watching this
Made me realize like
I don't
I didn't remember
The mechanics of
Family Feud
Everyone knows
Survey says
And then you like
Oh also
You get together
And stuff
And then
I really didn't remember
The final
Where it's like
Turn around
And here's your results
And someone else is
Out of the room
And they have to do it
Yeah and you need
A combined 200
So you want to do
As well as the camera
That was exciting
It was exciting to watch
But I forgot about
The steal of like
I feel like you're
Not a real Feud fan
Huh?
I feel like you're
Not a real Feud fan
You are bringing up
The basics of it
Yeah I didn't remember
Any of that
What was your game show
Then?
Jeopardy
Oh Mr. Smart Guy
Over here
I'm a big trivia there
He loves to learn
I love to learn
I am dog shit at
Wheel of Fortune
Solving the puzzle
I was going to say
I'm going to say
Oh solving the puzzle
Solving the puzzle
I was going to say
Have you practiced
Spinning the wheel
Are you bad at that too?
No I bet I would be
I'm a little guy
That wheel is massive
Fair enough
It is a big wheel
These are big pieces
Yeah
I tried
I did
There were so many
Levels for Teen Jeopardy
I just did the test
At my school
Oh wow
Like once
And did not
Did not get passed
You weren't smart enough
Yeah I was not smart enough
Did anybody
At the school?
I think one or two people
Went on to region
But no one got on the show
Okay okay
And then you probably
You got to like camera
You got to like
Okay you're smart
But are you
Awful to
Look at
Are you comfortable
Yeah yeah
On camera
Can you do the buzzer right
Like
Buzzer is what
Everyone says is tough
Yeah that seems
To be the thing
You got to nail that
And timing is more important
It was fascinating
Watching people do the
Buzzer
On this
Cause they had their hands
Flat
Like as close as
They could get
Can we get you on
Celebrity Jeopardy
Or something
Like podcast Celebrity Jeopardy
Oh I'd love that
Cause then they'd make
The questions dumber
Celebrity
No offense
But Celebrity Jeopardy
They usually
Dumb it down
I think if they did
Podcast Celebrity Jeopardy
It'd be nice for them
To like
Take a break from
All those ratings
Just to like get
Take off the pressure
Of the people
Are watching the show
Yeah
It'll be like
Oh this is
All right
We can just
Fuck off here
Because absolutely
No one is watching
The podcast Celebrity
Well but then Jason gets
To live a dream
So that'll be nice
Yeah
Works works for everybody
Takes the pressure down
I was a dummy little kid
Who just like
I like Price is Right
I like Family Feud
Like
That's what I like
I would like some of these
There was this like
Kind of like
One with attitude
Then where there was like
Cut a little deeper
Pop culture wise
That I want to say
Lifetime
With Wink Martindale
Who's like
Throwback game show host
Yeah
But now I don't remember
Was it possibly
Det was Det the name
Of the show
I remember Det
Because I would like
Things like that
Or win Ben Stein's money
Right
Where there's kind of
This odd premise
To where the money
Is coming from
I like kind of like
Deconstructionist 90s
Game shows
Yeah
I really liked
The syndicated reruns
Of Let's Make a Deal
Yes that too I liked
Yeah
I'm fond of both now
That my wife has appeared on
Both times
Right
I'm so proud of her
It's still what she will
She will find a way
To turn conversations to this
If possible in social settings
Right
She should
As she should
I've never seen it fail
I've never seen people
Not go really
Yeah
She did good on both
She got me a wallet
I got a nice new wallet
Out of
Okay
Out of Let's Make a Deal
You know
And which has made me
Very fond of Drew Carey
Yeah
At this point
As if there was
All right
There was that
He was apparently so nice
And commercial breaks
And all that
And then all the strike stuff
Paying for all the Bob's Big Boy
And now that he's
Explained to us
That going
And seeing Fish
At Sphere
Was like
Having a pussy
Yeah
It was an incredible
Now I'm like
Series of tweets
I thought he was just like
Kind of a guy on TV
But there's a lot of guys
On TV forever
This is Ryan Seacrest
Or whatever
Ryan Seacrest has never
Tweeted anything
As insane
As Drew Carey
Yeah
The tweets
Sphere giving him a pussy
Or the tweets
Yeah
It's like a new
You know what
Because I always found
That Kevin Smith one
So unpleasant
Right
This is like
It's weird
This is good
But what a blast
Did you like the follow up
That Fish sent him a blender
I didn't hear that
No
Water blender
Because he said like
Oh I would put my dick
In a blender
Wow
It's also like
He's the host of
The Price is Right Still
So it's like
Bob Barker never
Went to a show
And tweeted
That he felt like
He had a pussy
Yes for something
That is meant for
Like you know
Not entirely
But like
You know
They try to make that
A show that
Old people
Right
Can watch
And it just goes
Down pleasant
It's one of the
Crazier things
That like
A middle America mom
Type celebrity
Has ever done or said
This is Bob Barker
Elvis Presley's residency
In the International Hotel
In Las Vegas
Was so good
I would like
Someone to harvest
My prostate
And throw it in
A trash compactor
And he said that on the news
Or something
Because at the time
There was no Twitter
Yeah yeah
He issued a statement
Now we go live to
Bob Barker for a statement
Back to the desk
The Chernobyl incident
Continues to get worse
It was so to
Experience something
Like this again
I would gladly
Spay or neuter myself
Right
Okay but this feud
So we go back to 1983
For this
And this pairing of
Batman and Gilligan's Island
Comes as a result of a week
Of classic TV family pairings
Yeah
Now they obviously have to
Break from the family thing
A little bit
Of the family thing
And either one of these
Is a family proper
Right
The howls are related
But other than that
You know
Now this
I looked up the full context
Of this
These all are
By the way this is
All these episodes aired
This very week
41 years ago
Wow
That's what we're dealing with
April
Or wait aired in
May 83 I think
May 83
Okay
So this particular week
This was number two
Of TV's all time favorites week
In addition to Batman and
Gilligan's Island
You had Lost in Space
Yeah
In the Running
Led by June Lockhart
And Hawaiian Eye
Which is a show
I have no
Familiarity with
What so ever
Connie Stevens
Troy Donahue
Poncey Ponce
Wow
It had Poncey Ponce
Whoa
A name I've never seen
In my life
No
I've heard the phrase
Hawaiian Eye
And never investigated
Any further
But I did
It was just that you thought
It was a disease
You were worried you'd get
I probably just confused it
With Hawaii Five-O
I don't know if I want to
Go to Hawaii
You can end up coming back
With Hawaiian Eye
I did
I watched the finale
Of this week
Oh
With Lost in Space
Versus
Oh oh
Spoiler alert
Gilligan's Island
Oh you ruined it
I ruined it
You made it to the
Gilligan's Island
Cleaned the clock
Of the Batman family
Very
I feel like
Everyone's playing like
Very strategically in the
Like in terms of
There's a good amount of
Passing
What do you mean?
Like they pass it
Do you want to play
Or do you want to pass
Oh I see
And they're
Once or twice
Dawson was like
Really?
Like
It doesn't mean
They're playing correctly
Sure
But it does happen
But it is
Very strange not to have
Bob Denver
When the Batman family
Which is a term in
Comic book parlance
That you use the phrase
The Bat Family
And that's
That's Batman Robin
Batgirl
That's like the people
On that side
Nightwing
Asriel
All the others
There's many others
Oracle
Like all the extended
Cast
Alford obviously
But yeah
They have the three
The core three
Here
Batman
And the other family
Food
Yeah and that's
That's the
Batman family
As the core three
And you've got
Most of the
Primary
Gilligan's Island
Well yeah
Let's talk about
Who we got here
Yeah
Gilligan's Island
Is a little more
Besides not having
Gilligan himself
I think
You know hey
The skipper being
The leader is
Probably a more
And he's got the hat
Way to go
Right
Of course
He dresses somewhat
The part
And he does like
Disney bounding
He does skipper bounding
It like suggests it
Without being fully
The costume
Which I think he did
Most of his life
I think so
He did it at the restaurant
Which is
Yeah which
And this must be
Some of the reason
This came up
And was suggested
By Matt is that
We did cover
Alan Hale's lobster barrel
Right
His restaurant
On La Cienega
When we covered
A bunch of celebrity
Owned restaurants
Yes
And it seems like
In that setting
He would just
Walk around
Fully skipperfied
Yes
And it's
And Richard Dawson
Mentions it
Yes
Which is so exciting
Yeah
You know what
If we hadn't done
Celebruary
This might have passed
Yeah
And I would have not
Known what he's
Talking about
But when they're
Making small talk
Right
It is such a
Friendly familiar
It's what it's
Something like
I think when he's
Asking about
What the cause is
And what they're
Playing for
And he says
And then like
Sounds good
Very good
Wow
Which that
It's so familiar
That you're like
Dawson must have gone
Yeah
I think so
Boy all the
Who wasn't there
Caesar Romero
Would probably pop over
After
I forget what his thing
Was called
Yeah I forget
Whatever
Celebrity restaurant row
Casa de Joker
Yeah
God
I don't think he
Dressed as Joker
Every night
But I could be wrong
It's more of an effort
Yeah that's true
Yeah yeah
And then
All the makeup
Probably not
But yeah this was
This was
This got a pop
I got a big pop
Out of me for this
Because I go
Because I've never
Really seen it referenced
With the old stars
I've never
I've never seen
Johnny Carson say it
On an old clip
I've never seen
I don't know
I've never seen it
Referenced until now
I've only seen
Yeah like little cutouts
From newspapers
Right
When trying to find
Any material
To do an episode about
But it is real
All the biggest
Oldest stars in Hollywood
Drunkest stars
Yes they were all there
The oldest
Drunkest stars
The most red faced
Hollywood denizens
Always there every night
Yeah
So Alan Ayl Jr.
Skipper leads it
Then you got the Howells
Jim Backus
Backus
Backus maybe
Voice of Mr. Magoo
Yeah
Right we got Magoo
In the house
Which is
And some of the fun
Of this entire episode
That we had
We had
Which the whole
Entire
Episode is hearing voices
That you know
From other
Contexts
Yeah
Kind of shout
Answers excitedly
But in a voice
That you know
Right
Not to jump around
Too much
But there's
I think one of the
Categories
Is something about
Ways that
You relax
What are ways
That you relax
And you get to hear
Mr Howell
Slash Mr.
Magoo
Say make love
He might be the
I missed, I forgot or never knew that he was Magoo.
I missed that as I was looking at pictures
of all of them and stuff.
But his timing is really good.
Him and Vincent Price are in the race for MVP of this.
What crazy people to see in the wild.
They all feel like wax figures.
It's kind of strange to see them doing something
as themselves.
I mean, I'm sure all these people,
I'm just not as familiar.
I haven't seen many hours of match game or whatever.
But I also don't know if those people
did that sort of thing often.
Some of these are special.
I don't think Adam Wiss was doing it.
He was not like a mainstay of game shows or anything.
No, but back as in Vincent Price,
a lot of them, it just evolves
into friendly conversation with Dawson.
It doesn't even hit banter level.
Cause I'm like, oh, are they all bomb?
And I'm like, oh no, they're not really thinking
about this as performing.
But Vincent Price and Bacchus,
and Alan Hale especially too,
are like, oh, I'm on camera.
This is a chance, I, you know.
They go for it.
Perform a little.
They were their pops.
All right, you got Natalie Schaefer, lovey.
Lovey.
You got Russell Johnson, the professor,
and Don Wells, Marianne.
They are, aren't those the characters who were paired
in the original insulting opening as and the rest?
Oh, well, Skilly and the skipper too.
Don Wells was Marianne?
Yeah.
Professor Anne, Marianne.
Yes, but wasn't there an original version
where it was and the rest?
Oh, I don't know that.
I believe so.
I think they were like, even though there's only two left,
they would get through movie star and the rest.
And at some point there was,
I don't believe I'm making that up.
Yeah, they were just like, there's no time.
Like the composer, like, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
There's no way to fit in professor and Marianne.
And the producers are like,
well, what if it's just like professor and Marianne?
Too much, too much, too many syllables.
Get out of here.
Let the music guy do the music guy's thing.
I can't fit it in.
And then after season one, like, are you sure?
Are you sure there's not a way?
These people are gonna quit.
All right, you're right, I tried it.
I've never seen a full episode of Gilligan's Island,
I don't think.
Maybe one, maybe one.
It feels crazy to me that you would know.
And it does, doesn't it?
Wow, wow.
I don't think I've ever seen a full one.
At least I don't remember a full one.
I've seen clips, I've seen the like Harlem Globetrotters
clips from that.
Oh boy.
And that stuff's great. Throwing sharks in the basket.
Throwing sharks, sorry.
Throwing basketballs in the shark's mouth.
Yeah, I love the idea of Gilligan's Island, obviously.
Yeah, well, but it's, yeah, there's probably,
you know what, there's a lot of these shows
that I probably have not watched all of and I'm just,
that went a little bit more.
I remember watching that on a little bad black and white TV
that got hot as hell when I'm at home sick,
when it's on at just 10 a.m. on a channel
that doesn't even have a name.
But yeah, part of me is like,
you've never seen Gilligan's Island?
It's one of the classic,
and then you stop and think about it and go like,
was this good?
I mean, I think at the time it was probably,
if you're like a snooty TV critic,
you're like, it's the same thing every day.
And how do they not figure out how to get out of the island
and they keep repeating ways that they could get off
and it never happens.
But Gilligan feels like the,
whereas Batman, I think, holds up and is clever
and has these levels in writing, you know,
Gilligan feels more in the category of like,
is it remembered pop culture because it's good
or remembered because it was on?
I would say more of that.
Probably, yeah.
I think in terms of kitschy shows,
I dream of Genie, probably stronger show
than Gilligan's Island.
And one of my favorites, Green Acres.
You're a Green Acre, that makes sense.
I was a big Green Acres kid.
Sure, sure.
I didn't watch,
I would say I'm more familiar with Gilligan.
Okay.
And overall, if you're taking all this into account,
Brady Bunch all the way.
Yeah.
That is one I've watched a lot of Brady Bunch.
I think I've seen all of the Brady Bunch at some point.
That's like the one that reads the most.
That's the most like, to me, compelling,
everybody's fun to watch, but also bad.
And they're like, the good and the bad
are fighting constantly and just aesthetically
so pleasant and musically great.
Mm-hmm.
So yeah, would you say Green Acres number one
of all of these kinds of shows?
If we're including Batman, I mean, I guess Batmans
Yeah, I think Batman.
Yeah.
Probably Batman, but yeah, it depends.
There's the tiers.
Like the Dick Van Dyke show is a better show
than all these shows, probably.
Yeah.
Yeah, Dick Van Dyke, Be Witch.
But it's almost in another.
Yeah, it's a different category, I suppose.
The fact that everybody's got such pedigree
and Carl Reiner and these people who are true
great minds and writers.
Yeah, it's maybe not what we're dealing with with the,
no offense to Sherwood Shore,
it's a hooligan and Brady. Perhaps,
not on the same level, perhaps.
He was just, he's the TGIF guy of his era.
That's a good way to put it, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, they carved the way for,
they paved the way for all those kinds of shows.
Russell Johnson, by the way, the professor,
I didn't know he was like,
he was in the, he was in World War II,
he was shot down in the Philippines,
he broke both his ankles, his co-pilot died,
but he survived, he got a purple heart.
Wow, and now he's here playing the Feud.
Wow.
And everybody just thinking of him as like,
oh, hey, all right, yeah, the professor.
And boy, he never, how did they have the professor?
And he made the stuff out of coconuts,
but he couldn't get him off the island.
You know, this guy was like a true hero,
like narrowly escaped death when his friend did not.
Like, what an amazing man.
Most people are just like,
hey, you were on the show with the island.
You're like a joke, right?
You're like a living joke, right?
Isn't that right, professor?
I remember, I feel like an old Conan O'Brien
has referenced Russell Johnson a few times
as a joke of like, who he could get as like,
early on in the early days of the show, maybe?
Yeah.
Or like, Ralph Malf or Donnie Most.
Oh, sure, yes, yeah, yeah, that's who would say yes
in early late night days.
Right, right.
But I think Russell Johnson popped up as one of his.
That's also like who he would want to.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You'd have to imagine.
But okay, on the, let's go to the Batman side,
which is pretty stacked.
You got Batman and Robin themselves,
Adam West, Burt Ward.
Pretty stacked.
I wonder how they went about,
was that the first Catwoman they asked?
Or was that?
That's a very good question
because she's only in the movie.
Leave me alone, is the only in the movie,
she did not have most appearances.
And they refer to, like Adam West says,
and she would, she'd try to get me on the show,
but she was not on the show.
Not on the show.
And yet, I think due to the movie,
which is the height of the franchise, I think.
Right, that's the best.
Could be the best Catwoman.
I really like her as Miss Kitka, the alternate identity.
And the two of them are like in the back of a limo
and like, you know.
Oh, the romance.
Cooing to each other.
Yeah.
These insane poetic romantic lines.
But what is action?
Or what is an idea, if not a course for action?
Which is like what preludes him kissing her on the ear.
Yes, it's ridiculous.
Seeing Bruce Wayne romantic and talking and that insane,
it's so good.
He is doing like reserved, like Bruce Commissioner.
Like he's doing the Bruce, I don't know,
he seems so dignified.
And I gotta say, I like his vest.
I like his vest, but I really like Burt Ward's outfit.
The green shirt, the striped tie, the blue blade.
I'm like, oh, I would wear that.
I would wear that now.
I didn't clock this.
I don't remember either.
It makes sense, though, that you would take
fashion tips from Burt Ward.
Burt Ward looked pretty good, I thought.
I'm not denying it.
I just don't remember it either, really.
I think he looked fine in my memory,
but I don't remember the actual outfit.
I feel like, and Vincent Price looking good.
I feel like the Batman family bringing it,
the fellas bringing it with style.
Sure, sure.
Hey, but don't leave the ladies out of it.
Lee Merriweather, as Adam points out, of Miss America.
I didn't realize that.
Miss America, 55.
Yvonne Craig, beautiful and very charismatic.
Sure, yeah.
Batgirl, which I'm not unbelievably familiar
with Batgirl, because it's kind of later.
They added her later, yeah.
We're getting into some Cousin Oliver territory.
They were trying to spin it off,
and it was a gustful spin-off grip.
Motorcycle, yeah.
Good motorcycle, I like the motorcycle.
Very cool motorcycle, yeah.
But I don't remember any moments
with Batgirl, particularly.
I don't know that I have one that sticks out
that's like, oh, that was an amazing one.
Bit of a cursed character, in a way,
because there's no, you know, hasn't shown up in new ones.
No place for Batgirl, really, in the Nolan verse.
Yeah.
Alicia Silverstone is in, Batman and Robin.
Trying her best.
Suit me up, Uncle Alfred.
Alfred's niece, that's right.
So that is, when they have to repeat the suit-up sequence
with the push-ins to the body parts.
Oh, yeah.
It is really unfortunate.
I feel like, do we have to do this
for what you've presented as a young girl character?
No nipples on that bat suit would be very inappropriate.
Yeah, yeah, they should.
That was tasteful.
It's one area where they were tasteful.
Thank you, Joel.
That was tasteful, finally.
Yes.
But yeah, she kind of like, you know,
is the beginning of the end.
It's not because of her.
There's plenty wrong with Batman and Robin.
Sure.
It's funny that she shows up, and then the three,
it's, at the end, it's the three of them
running through the bat signal.
They're like, now it's them forever.
Get ready for, you're gonna see them soon,
Batman triumphant or whatever.
And nope, we didn't get to see him fight Howard Stern.
Something I have never believed is actually was true.
Oh, was Goldblum or Howard Stern
were the two rumors for that?
Both as Scarecrow was the thought.
I mean, I feel like they both would have been great.
It's possible.
I mean, Goldblum for sure.
Goldblum, yes.
I don't know that Howard is that good of an actor.
He made it through private parts,
he's good in private parts as himself.
Could he have been...
I don't know. Sorry to imagine it.
Yeah, in the wake of the scenery chew
of Jim Carrey and Tommy Lee Jones.
I mean, maybe with the right outfit.
And I mean, with Schumacher.
Perhaps it would have been fine.
Schumacher around him directing.
But yeah, I don't know that he would have.
He would have gotten the best performance out of it,
as he always did.
He pulls. As he got everyone's
favorite performances of their whole careers.
That's true, yeah.
Every, it might not have popped.
Carrey and Joe, I think they are both pretty funny.
Yeah, and I think we're, yes, of course.
It's the greatest thing, yeah.
And Tommy Lee Jones seems like he's just trying
to outdo Jim Carrey, because he hated him so much.
I mean, according to Jim Carrey, he hated him,
which I don't think that's an exaggeration.
But it is, if you watch now, you're like,
why are these guys both playing the same thing?
Amped up.
Both of them are playing the same energy.
Taking it to 12.
They've gone past 11.
Because Two-Face, in general, in my mind,
as a character, is just more of a low-key guy.
I guess Eckhart played him more like that in Dark Knight.
But he's obviously explosive.
But Tommy Lee Jones is not letting the foot
off the gas in that movie.
No.
And I have a feeling it's because he's like,
I am not letting this fucking punk outshine me.
I can do this crap, too.
I can yell and be big.
I can be for babies.
Right, yes.
He's so reserved in the Batman animated series.
Unless he's losing his coin, then he freaks out.
And Schumacher hated working with Tommy Lee Jones.
He said he did not like working with Tommy Lee Jones
or Val Kilmer.
But Jim Carrey, he loved working with.
Of course.
So there you go.
And then reunited for one of the greatest films
ever made, number 23.
Of course.
Yeah.
OK, so that's our take.
Oh, wait, and then Vincent Price becomes kind of a motley crew
hero, where it's heroes, all three of the heroes,
and then a Catwoman who was only Catwoman once,
although a great Catwoman.
And then you think of the big four,
and Egghead is not necessarily in the big four.
But what a delight, too.
Yeah.
Had any of them passed away by this point?
I think so.
Maybe they're building options are limited.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Maybe Caesar, no, Caesar Mero probably a little bit later.
But no, Gorshin was alive, and Burgess
was alive well into the 90s, at least the 90s.
So yeah, I don't know.
It's a good question.
Somebody just wanted Vincent Price on there, I guess.
As do we.
Yeah.
It's great.
It's great to remember the existence of Egghead.
And that also, I can't, Egghead's theme was eggs.
And he had a bald head, like an egg shell.
Right.
And did his henchmen also, were they like egg men?
Kind of, yeah, I think.
Yeah.
And if he was going to make a pun,
what is the nature of a pun?
Eggcellent?
What is it, just eggcellent?
In the same way that I feel like there is so much perfect
with Catwoman.
Yeah.
I think every single appearance of her, they hit that perfect.
Right.
But eggcellent is a harder one.
I don't know how much juice you can get out of.
He's sleeping in a big half egg here on one of the episodes?
Oh, OK, yes.
OK, you're showing me an egg bed.
And then there is bacon on the walls.
And this answers a question for me,
is if bacon is in play in the theme of Egghead.
Absolutely, yeah.
He can talk about, if he robs a bank,
he can talk about bringing home the bacon.
Right.
That would be acceptable.
Yes, I think so.
All right, good to know.
Burgess Meredith, I looked at, likely not here
because he's working a lot.
The Rocky movies.
He's such a legitimate actor.
When does foul play, he's in foul play as well.
That's around this time.
Yeah, foul play.
The Chevy Chase, Goldie Hawn.
Yeah.
Clash of the Titans was only two years before.
Guy worked.
I'm looking at, I'm like, OK, let's see some quotes.
We don't stop at eggcellent.
OK, eggcellent, I might even go so far as to say exquisite.
Then later, I for one am exhausted.
This isn't a pun, but I like it.
I for one am exhausted.
It's been a trying day, and I must rest my fantastic brain
for tonight.
So that's part of, that's egghead too, is that he's smart.
Because I guess egghead is important.
I just didn't know that was part of him as well.
He's smart.
Yeah, egghead, yes, yeah, he is smart.
He could have made that, I have to rest my giant,
I feel like he could have been like,
I've got to rest and harden my yolk.
OK, that's a good plus up, yeah.
That sounds like it, yeah, yeah.
He's also got a henchman or a sidekick named Miss Bacon.
There you go, we're filling it all in together.
Great egg-spectations.
You may have the import egg-sport concession
for such and such.
How egg-sasperated.
I got to give these writers more credit.
They figured out a lot.
They figured out a lot of these.
There are a lot there, yeah.
And they couldn't even go to dictionary.com.
They had to have a physical copy and filter
through those EX words.
Find them all, make sure that it was ones
that kids could understand.
You can't have too massive of a six syllable term there,
or you lose the kiddos.
Great job.
There's also an episode of Batman
with a guest starring spot for Al and Hale Jr.
I don't know if you saw this.
Oh, I was wondering about that.
And egghead is egghead, he's on it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
And the joke in the scene is that Chief O'Hara is there.
I think he's like a bartender, or Al and Hale's
like a bartender.
And Chief O'Hara keeps going, hey, Gilligan.
So the joke is that he's calling him Gilligan.
It's not his character's name.
But then egghead shows up in the scene.
So they kind of have a little tiny thing.
Really?
That's the chemistry that comes from this entire thing.
They didn't work on set together,
then they're hanging out at the lobster barrel.
Of course.
Yeah.
It's practically heat.
It's Pacino and De Niro together.
Practically heat, I agree.
Basically the same thing.
So that's the groups, that's the families.
By the way, I just did some calculations.
When did these shows go off the air in comparison
to this in 1883?
These shows went off the air 15 and 17 years prior,
which that would be the equivalent of today,
a family feud that is a classic TV
reunion of the casts of According to Jim
and That's So Raven.
That is how long ago.
That's the exact length of time.
I was going to say like, oh, it's the OC family
versus the Gossip Girl family.
Of course, now we've already gotten to Gossip Girl reboot.
Gossip Girl versus Gossip Girl would be great.
Let's focus on each other.
That's good.
I feel like they do do these kind of,
because there was a pretty viral thing with Jackass.
I don't remember what it was in Steve Harvey era.
I think they do a lot of casts.
Oh, Jackass did family feud.
Yes, that's right.
Yeah, I don't remember what the thing was.
I don't know what made Steve make the face.
Oh, I think they were getting a little nasty.
Those guys, what?
We save it for your unrated movies.
Well, we just took a break.
I just want to say that here, because Jason,
on the way to the restroom, made some just observation
about Richard Dawson.
I said, Jason, what are you doing this?
Don't say it on the mic.
Well, I didn't want to forget.
Oh, OK.
That's why I was saying it.
I was just worried you weren't going to do it.
So I just want to make sure the audience knows
that I freaked out, because I was like,
Jason burned off a funny comment.
The question was interesting.
Yeah, yeah, you broke your phone.
You threw it at me.
Yes, I did throw it at you.
Shut up.
Right.
Do not speak unless microphones are for weird things.
It's very cold.
We don't talk before or after these episodes.
Well, we haven't talked much about Dawson.
You're right.
Let's bring it around to Dawson, graduate of Hogan's Heroes,
known maybe even more as the host of this show,
and known for, within this show, smooching.
Yeah, kissing on the mouth.
Kissing the ladies on the mouth.
On the mouth, which I'm like, in 2024, I'm like,
you should kiss the fellas on the mouth.
You should kiss everybody.
You should just equalize it.
He's very intimate with the men, too, when he grabs Adam.
He's always pulling them in to watch those final scores
in the last round.
So he's showing them a lot.
They're arm in arm.
Some touching.
There's touching.
But you want it to go further.
But everyone seemed prepared for it.
Everyone seemed like they had.
OK, so he comes around.
If you haven't ever seen this before, there's a long intro.
And I feel like the intro's a little shorter these days.
Yeah, because you kind of meet everybody.
They introduce all the hosts.
And then he goes down the line and talks to them all.
So there's two introductory rounds.
And maybe it's because they're celebrities.
They're taking a little longer.
Yeah, if they were just common riff raff, junk people.
Of course.
But he goes person by person.
And if it's a lady that you have,
I don't know if a producer yelled at them,
like, you have to kiss this man.
But he kind of put his hands on their arms.
And then he'll like, I don't know
that he requires a mouth kiss.
But he'll kiss them in some ways.
I think every woman on this episode
kissed him on the mouth.
And by the way, in some cases at least, because it's not,
sometimes it's just like, all right,
it's a quick little moment.
Maybe they try to play it off like it's nice.
But Lee Merriwether, they lock in.
And she actually comes in with like, this one's for my mother.
This one's for my sister.
And this one's for me.
She goes like cheek, cheek, and then mouth.
Yeah, she goes for it.
And that is a flirtatious moment.
Solid bit.
I swear on most of their eyes, I sense
that they were all like, OK, here we go.
We've gotten through that.
I know I have to do it.
Which culturally, I think, was, I bet,
in this era, which is my parents' era,
where you kiss your friend's wives on the mouth.
This was still, I've seen this happen
with my parents' generation.
Wow, really?
Yes, yes.
Jason, you've seen that with your parents?
I've seen, like, a quick, like, a cheek kiss.
I know the cheek, yes.
I've never seen mouth-o.
And I think that was allowed on family feuds sometimes.
They would throw the cheek at Dawson.
They really don't want it, yeah.
Just give him something.
But he's sitcom royalty, so I guess
you have to kiss him on the mouth if you're
all in the sitcom families.
It's very off-putting.
It's so weird.
I knew it would come up in this.
And you could say, like, yeah, well,
under 2024 standards, it's a little bit.
I think in 1983 standards, this was weird.
People thought it was weird.
Absolutely.
People definitely thought it was weird.
People absolutely thought it was weird at the time.
I think it was complained about, and then maybe they
tried to stop doing it, but then other viewers, oh, wait.
I think they actually ran a poll.
And most people were like, no, I like the kissing.
That's part of it.
But it grew from a small minority.
This is strange.
And he is not European, I feel like, in Europe,
different standards, so maybe a little more common.
Is he British, though?
Oh, is he British?
Is that the excuse?
Maybe he is.
I think the accent really disappeared, but I believe.
Yeah, he is.
You're right.
The other thing I mentioned during the break
when Mike knocked over all the Mike stands in Fury,
Dawson in a full tuxedo for sitcom week.
Yeah.
Was he not typically in a full tuxedo?
I think he usually dressed up.
Well, that's what I thought.
He was always in a nice, but he might have been a tuxedo.
Here's what I'll say about Richard Dawson.
As a kid, I did like seeing the old episodes
with Richard Dawson hosting.
I was not a Big Hogan's Heroes kid or anything.
I saw it.
I will say that in my mind, I want
to like Richard Dawson more than any time I see him now.
Yeah, because the energy is.
He's just like, I don't know if he's drunk
or doesn't care or both.
He's like under his breath meanders.
And sometimes you really end up in a territory,
sometimes where he's so like, because this
is the round where you get the score and blah, blah, blah.
Like he gets slurry at the end of this one.
Yeah, he might be drunk.
I mean, that would be believable.
But I also like even some scene clips of him on Hogan's Heroes,
I hate to say this about an old character actor,
but I don't see it.
I don't know that I see it.
You've got so many to choose from as it is.
You're already exploding with love for so many of these men.
In the front of my mind, I want to say Richard Dawson, that's
one of those crazy 70s, 60s celebrities.
It's fun to go back and watch him.
And I'm like, maybe it's not.
Maybe it's not so fun for Richard.
I know what you mean.
No, I'm much more put off by the kissing.
And I'm not just trying to.
OK, Dawson, often in a three piece suit,
I think this is sometimes in the tux for special episodes,
it looks like, but sometimes just in a suit.
But wait, do we get to what your question was,
involving the tux?
Well, I think the tux is for celebrity.
No, but what you had asked during the break was,
is the kissing better or worse?
Oh, is it better or worse?
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
Is the kissing better or worse in a tuxedo?
Like he's, with a tux, you start thinking,
well, this is James Bond.
How can you resist a kiss from the debonair?
It's tricky because it's TV and it is still a performance,
but everyone's there themselves.
Obviously, you're not offended necessarily
by a kiss on a sitcom because it's written into the script.
But here, it's reality, but you are playing the role
of someone who has to tolerate a kiss
from a drunk Richard Dawson.
And that's really where, tux or no tux,
when those lips get close to you
and you feel the booze.
The anxiety, I'm sure you would feel.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's why I think even like Lee Merriwether,
who went in hard, was just like,
all right, I'm biting a bolt,
like biting down on the leather strap.
I'm gonna control the situation.
Yes, that's what I sensed.
Most of them wanted to control the situation.
They're like, I'm not letting this motherfucker
put his tongue in my mouth or anything on the air.
Like, if I have to do this,
because he's gonna be weird
or the producer's gonna yell at me,
I'm in charge, I'll give him the smooch,
not the other way around.
Yeah.
Control the narrative.
Exactly.
I'm looking at the hosts and announcers section
of the Wikipedia, and I read this about the kissing.
Dawson showed himself to have insistent affection.
Oh, I do not like that phrase.
Showed himself to have insistent affections
for all of the female members of each family
that competed on the show, regardless of age.
Kissing them, an act that attracted some controversy
then among viewers.
And then right after that, citation needed.
I like that, that somebody's perusing this Wikipedia
and then like, I don't understand,
people didn't like the kissing?
What, where, where?
Show me, citation needed.
Show your proof.
Hey, come on, oh really?
People didn't like it, huh?
Well then why didn't they ever put pen to paper
and say in the media that they didn't like it?
This is fake, this whole thing is fake.
Everyone loved the kissing.
I'm taking to Wikipedia, I'm gonna write this wrong
on behalf of dead Richard Dawson.
This is like Jordan Peterson would take this up
or something, or like, Elon Musk would be like,
we have to defend the honor of Richard Dawson's estate.
Jordan Peterson just openly weeping.
Right, Richard Dawson was a.
Some people are trying to take away his kissing.
He was a wonderful.
The young men don't have any guidance.
Somebody, yeah, somebody really cares
to preserve the magic of the kissing.
Yeah, I will not let this be said.
Apparently the defense of the kissing was that like,
well you know what, you know what made it good
is that it was equal opportunity.
He kissed everyone.
And there was even the defense that like.
Oh, he kissed like grandma.
And not only that, but like racially,
he will, at a time where on television
you don't really see that.
But I'm still like.
I mean, it's still weird.
No, no, no.
That's a nice thought, I suppose.
That took some real spin room,
like let's put our heads together.
How are we gonna make this kissing?
Okay, it's progressive kissing, don't you see?
If you're kissing everyone,
you should kiss dad and grandpa too.
And that is real, that's, you're right.
He could have gotten away.
Like truly, if it was equal opportunity,
you kiss everybody in that family.
He truly would have gotten away with it
if he could have just kissed dad and grandpa as well.
Yeah. Yeah.
They deserve it too.
Give it the cheeks, the cheeks.
They work hard.
Some of these grandpas probably in the war,
like Russell Johnson. Yes.
Kiss Russell Johnson.
He has a purple heart.
Kiss him on the mouth.
Yeah, for sure.
He needs some more.
Kiss your heroes. Open mouth, open mouth.
He deserves some. Open mouth.
The whole audience should have enchanting that.
The other weird little affect, if the Richard does it,
because we're watching some like blurry old copies
of this on YouTube.
And there's these kind of like trees next to the podiums.
I'm like, what's these trees?
And I, because of the blurriness,
I was baffled when they reached for the trees
and pull out like Tootsie Pops.
This was part of it. Oh, yeah.
There was a, like truly it looks like a potted plant to me.
And like, wait a minute,
all the branches of this are Tootsie Pops?
And that was a thing on this show,
was that he always had a big array of Tootsie Pops
to so many things, a lot of things on this show.
Yeah.
Vincent Price had a marker.
There's a bit about his marker,
and then they start scribbling on the Tootsie Pops.
That was confusing.
Was that like a, he was doing like a,
was that a gag?
He thought he was on match game or something else?
No idea.
My notes just say what is going on.
I know, I also was like, what is this?
No idea, yeah.
This is, and really, much like this episode
where we were probably taking more time to talk
to like set the table than to actually talk about the game.
There's so much, I feel like they're not playing
for like 15 minutes, which is fine.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We want to hang out with these guys.
The game is as good as any game, but it's not like there's-
It's not about that.
No, no, no.
To me, if we start getting into the gameplay,
any moments that jumped out as like,
well, it was cool to hear these sitcom people
say these things.
No, because it never gets too like naughty or anything
because that's always an aspect of the show.
But did anything jump out?
Here's a moment in the gameplay that I like.
When Mr. Magoo says, when he talks about Ronald Reagan,
and he goes, what does he say after a word?
He goes like, great man or something.
God bless him. God bless him.
That's what he says.
Yeah, the category is name a celebrity
who is also a political activist.
Yeah.
Jane Fonda, top answer on the board
with 78 out of possible hundreds.
So clearly, the like absolutely like dominates,
but maybe it feels like she was almost one
of the only ones at the time.
Yeah.
People here in 2024, people are still mad at her.
Yeah, it does be.
Sure.
Our current right winger would still say Hanoi Jane.
We're talking about things from-
50 years ago.
Yeah.
My God.
Their vote counts the same as ours.
That's great.
Paul Newman's also in there
and then Ronald Reagan's number three.
Ronald Reagan, God bless him.
Great moment.
And then right after-
I was shocked by this actually.
Even though I know this.
I didn't know it.
Ed Asner.
Yeah.
I did not know the strong political meanings of Ed Asner.
He got 10 points, so people knew this.
A real lefty.
A democratic socialist and a fierce opponent of Ronald Reagan.
Right.
So how must Bacchus have felt?
He must have known Asner was possibly coming.
So he's got to like get ahead of,
I got to plant my Reagan flag
before that devil Asner is mentioned.
He must.
Well, you know what?
He, when he had the spinoff, The Lou Grant Show,
which was a like serious spinoff of Mary Tyler Moore,
where he played like, he ran a newspaper, I believe.
You can do a Lou Grant's Place
where Madame has given him a back massage.
Oh my God, did Madame ever appear on Lou Grant?
Even as in a serious role.
Yeah, it was a serious episode about,
they were trying to do an article about redlining.
Yeah.
And Madame was like pro redlining, I don't know.
But I think Ed Asner claims
that his political beliefs canceled,
just got the show canceled.
That's what he says or said.
Wow.
Well, thank God we've come such a long way
in terms of actors being able to say
whatever they think about current events.
That's true.
Don't ignore all articles about the Scream franchise.
Yeah, the Scream franchise.
Some, a member of the Scream franchise
acknowledged Palestinians' humanity and she's out.
Scream family, come on down.
Why are there only three people on this team
in the Scream theme?
One of you was an extra in the movie.
I was still in the movie though.
It's just three people with masks.
They can't all be the mask guy.
Other categories, I mean, things have just jumped out
like Aries Sejimbekis, Make Love.
I think one of them is like,
Oh, Things to Buy Before Boarding a Plane.
It's one of those where just anything Vincent Price says
is gonna be music to his ears
because he just says something to read.
It's great, it's nothing, anything would be good.
So good.
He also, in Most Relaxing Thing You Do,
he says, for me, the most relaxing thing is gardening.
Perfect, what a nice garden.
That was a buzzer, that was an X.
And I was like at home going like,
you're right, Vincent Price, the people are wrong.
Like, yeah, working with Lance is very relaxing.
Not in the top though, what can you say?
Who are they interviewing?
Who in general, how do they do these polls?
And are they made up?
Is somebody going out there, somebody knocking on doors?
Hello, I'm from Family Feud.
I feel like someone said this,
this is not sourced at all,
so I don't take this as an actual answer,
but I feel like they would poll people
in a mall in the Midwest.
Ah, sure.
I don't know if they'd contract a company to do it
or something, but you just,
somebody's job was to ask people at a mall.
That being said, easily could fake all this.
Yeah, yeah, if they just need to get it done.
It does seem like, because today this seems like a show
where they're probably filming seven in a day.
Let's crank these out, no one looks Steve in the eye.
If we throw him, we'll lose one of these episodes.
Even back then it seemed like they were filming a lot
in a day. I'm sure, yeah.
This entire thing might've been,
they might've done this full celebrity week,
because they all just, you know,
you could say that Gilligan won the whole thing,
but I feel like they all got a chance to win and lose.
I think all the shows won at some point
and all the shows lost at some point.
Yeah, and everyone's charity got some money.
Regardless.
Lost in Space family, by the way, no Dr. Smith.
Well, that's a, that's all I'm saying.
Which is a tragedy.
Passed away?
No.
No, he's in Bug's Life, he's a voice in Bug's Life.
Oh, right, right, right, right, that's right.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Maybe he was working.
Yes.
They do have somebody who they just credit him
as the robot, because I watched,
I ended up watching the other Batman one,
Batman versus Lost in Space.
And there's nothing too notable there,
except that in that one, Richard Dawson says to Yvonne Craig,
you have the best legs in the business
and don't let anyone tell you otherwise.
He also looks at her legs under the desk
in the other episode too, he like peers,
yeah, he does a real leery creep thing, yeah.
Yikes.
That one, there's a kind of a creepier category.
Not creepy, it's funny, it's like a funny
little scandalous category.
Innuendo was always, it was a good reminder
watching these, like, oh yeah,
it didn't start with Steve Harvey.
Yeah.
Steve Harvey just is very funny.
He perfected it.
Yeah, he perfected it, but there were always some innuendo.
Too bad you don't get the kiss from Steve,
because imagine the relaxation
of getting brushed by that mustache.
Imagine a little brush from Steve.
Oh, yeah.
And how thick that is, that hasn't moved in years.
So there's gotta be a lady who's tried to kiss him
on the show before.
Yeah, probably.
There's gotta be a clip or two of that.
Yeah, and he like, he propels backwards.
Yeah.
Eyes pop all the way out of the head.
Right.
The other one that, I mean, Lost in Space
has the category, places for where a hubby goes
to make it with his number two.
That's like where you go to cheat on your wife.
Which Adam West gets X'd with the response, parking lot.
He gets the X and then says, I'm on a cheap date.
How, real quick side note, Batman versus Lost in Space
sounds like the coolest 60s show you could've done.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That would've been awesome.
They really should've done some competitions more.
The dirtiest category on the Batman,
Batman, Gilgamesh Island episode,
there's like, name a magazine with like, sex tips?
Is that what it is?
Is that in one of these?
Oh, I don't know.
I didn't see that one.
Well, the answers are like,
Cosmo, Playboy, Hustler, Playgirl.
Oh, I didn't see that.
Was that in the other one?
Was that Lost in Space?
Maybe that's on the other one.
Yeah, I don't remember that.
Cause we would've been scandalized.
We would've come in with a lot of like,
Playgirl, did my virgin ears hear Playgirl magazine?
Which, I mean, yeah, once you get Cosmo knocked out,
it's just dirty magazines afterwards.
Adam West should've done Playgirl.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
In the 90s.
If Lookwell had gone forward.
Oh, God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, they would've demanded it.
Pure West.
Big, like, bat, you know, like a boomerang,
like a batarang, like just covering the girl.
Yeah, that's right.
Yep, he would've done it, would've been packin'.
So, what else?
You know what, I think, as much as I thought
it'd be the most fun to see the Batman gang,
I like seeing the Gilligan gang work together,
because that's what they did on the show.
They put their heads together and worked through a fix.
So I like seeing Alan Hale seize the group
and like, come on gang, let's, let's huddle.
That felt the most like the show is back.
He just, he's dressed like Skipper
and he's acting like Skipper.
And he seems like, just like, oh, the nicest older guy.
Okay, that's so great, he seems so supportive.
Like we hear those stories about Alan Hale's lobster barrel
where he was like hangin' around,
it was the nicest guy to everybody.
It seems maybe, I mean, he could be performing here,
but it seems like maybe that is,
he just became the nice guy Skipper.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the proof, the ultimate proof would've been
if Bob Denver was there, got X'd a bunch of times.
Right.
What do you've gotten hit with the hat?
I think that's why Bob Denver wasn't there.
Cause he knew, he knew that the hits were real.
Right.
And what we saw on the show were second takes
after first takes where the hat hitting was so furious.
Right.
Where Alan Hale started putting rocks in his pocket,
putting them in the hat so that the hats
could have more impact.
Yeah.
And actually bludgeon Gilligan.
And he knew it, yeah.
So he was.
He saved his monsterism.
As long as you weren't Gilligan, he was nice,
but watch out if you're Bob Denver.
Well, maybe if, yeah, the other thing,
maybe Bob Denver just didn't wanna wear the bucket hat.
Cause if he was gonna be there,
they would've made him wear the bucket hat, I feel like.
Possibly.
It's possible.
I mean, I guess if Alan is dressed like Skipper,
there's more pressure on you to do that now.
Yeah.
And they might've, then they just keep going further
and they, instead of X's, they plant coconuts
up above their heads so that those drop on you
when you get a wrong answer.
The slippery slope is dressing like the Skipper
cause then that side has to be, yeah.
It's an arms race.
Batman, other than just Vincent Price being himself,
they were not playing the characters.
Not so much, but you get little flickers of it
like when Burt Ward, he gets an answer wrong at some point
and he says, DRAP!
You get a little Robin.
That's true, that's true.
And one thing that I might notch up the other episode,
Batman versus Lost in Space,
is that Batman and Robin do the end round together
where you gotta pick two of the five to come out.
And the two of them kinda like hustle out
towards the podium or towards center stage or whatever
and I'm like, this is like the opening.
That's true, yeah.
The two of them doing their little run.
That was more of a Batman and Robin are back moment
than the other, this main episode.
In the Gilligan Lost in Space finale,
all of the Gilligan family gets giant trophies.
Cool!
Oh, good!
Giant cup trophies.
That's great.
And Bacchus just seems very confused
why he's being handed this large cup.
It's...
Well, what other moments are we missing?
I mean, that's a lot of the fun stuff.
You know what, I learned two fun facts about Burt Ward,
just to get him out before we wrap this up,
which is one that he got paid sag scale to play Robin
and because he was so cheap,
but getting a stunt man for Robin was more expensive,
they would often have him do his own stunts
just to not bring in another guy.
So here, Robin, you think he got it made,
he's a TV icon, and instead it's like,
hey, let the guy who's making pennies
make him jump off the building onto the boat.
They both had to do stunts, him and Adam, I think.
They both kind of got hurt, I think, decent.
And it's funny too, because you see it
and you think, oh, somebody got hurt doing a stunt.
It must be the most amazing, crazy looking thing
and it's just like the sloppiest,
poorly choreographed fight scene.
And it's like, oh yeah, I guess you could easily
dislocate a shoulder just taking a wild swing
at Egghead's goon.
You're right, it does not have to be like Tom Cruise
jumping between the buildings and the motorcycle.
Yeah, you can hurt yourself horribly
and it looks like shit.
Exactly, yeah.
So it happened all the time, I think, on that show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They were often very uncoordinated
and I love at the end of Batman 66, the movie,
when all the villains and heroes
and all their henchmen who are pirates
are all just in a big tank next to a submarine,
all just bashing each other with wet hats.
It is the least coordination of an action sequence
I've ever seen, but it's so great.
It's just such pure chaos.
They're all wet.
The direction given was action.
The end.
That's how this episode should have ended.
They all should have been hitting each other
with wet hats and laughing.
But they are older now.
They are older.
They are older, which, that plays into,
I thought maybe a decent way to end this
could be playing a little bit of Feud ourselves.
Oh, yeah.
Mike, come on down.
Jason, come on down.
Okay.
Mike, it's good to see you.
You have the most beautiful, oh, your shorts.
I can, mwah, mwah, mwah.
Can I kiss those legs?
Thank you for kissing my little legs.
Oh, and not to leave out Jason.
Oh, my, my, my.
Let me take those glasses off so they don't fog up.
This is one from me, one from me, one from me,
and one more from me.
Wow.
I hope there's a lot more of you where that came from.
Okay, so. There is, there is.
Thank God.
All right, after the show.
You're not going anywhere.
Stay in the green room.
Okay.
Okay, so top nine answers on the board.
Name of people on the stage
for this Batman versus Gilligan on Family Feud.
Name the performer who died the soonest
after this 1983 taping.
Jason.
Jim Baucus.
You got it.
Number one, number one answer.
For bonus points, you want to guess how long after?
Two months?
Not quite, a little bit, a little bit longer.
Six years.
Six years, okay.
Well, here, do you want to stay on a streak,
but Mike could steal?
Okay.
Can you go for number two?
Well, he can do it or he can pass it.
Oh, that's true.
Oh, yeah, yeah, if you want to keep.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Go ahead.
Okay, all right, number two.
Oh, number two, I'm confused.
Number two of actors who died the soonest after Jim Baucus.
Is it Vincent Price?
It is not Vincent Price.
Yeah, yeah, all right, do you want to go for Mike?
I mean, I guess, secondly, he could,
well, no, yeah, he's got three strikes,
but we're not playing the official game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, we gotta keep it short.
Is it Alan Hale?
It's not Alan Hale.
Damn it.
Natalie Schafer.
Oh, wow.
Because the answer's seven years late, I think,
unless they're like, I don't know,
that's just a guess.
We're doing some kind of, I believe so,
but yeah, much more Gilligan cast members lost before,
Vincent Price was the first in like 92, I believe,
which lines up with him having been able to do
that voiceover for Phantom Manor.
Yeah, in my head, I was doing the math
of when would Phantom Manor be?
Yeah, yeah, so there you go, excellent, excellent work,
Jim Baucus, soonest deceased.
Wow.
I'm gonna check that, wait, oh yeah,
Alan Hale made it to 1990,
so I believe it is Natalie Schafer.
Got it.
Well, any further observations,
questions before we wind it down?
Yeah, I just, it's interesting that
these crossovers happened on Family Feud
and many years later,
because as I said, Lost in Space,
if it was in the heyday of both shows,
even though they didn't quite overlap, or maybe they did,
actually seeing crossovers would have been very exciting.
But we got that Alan Hale cameo,
so there was a little bit of the funny,
fun business, I'll call it.
Wait a minute, I have checked the results,
I have double checked the results.
Mike, you in fact were correct.
Alan Hale was number two,
that means the points go to you.
Holy shit.
And the points, of course, in this game are smooches.
Come back this way.
Okay, on my legs, please.
Ah, yes, oh, they're good.
Kneecaps, please.
Much more room than on a human face.
Yeah, of course.
The legs, I could do this for hours and hours.
Thank you so much, this is so nice.
I appreciate this.
I'm glad we're finally acknowledging each other's
no, no, don't say it. Sexual beings.
For some reason, I'm more comfortable pretending
to kiss both of you than that particular phrase.
I don't know what it is about it.
Too any, acknowledging each other.
Jason's saying it specifically, too.
Well, is it better or worse that I'm wearing a full tuxedo
as I do every recording?
Oh, Dan, you know what you're at.
I wonder why I was more charmed by that phrase
than previously.
Well, I think that winds it down.
I think you survived podcast The Ride.
Hey, what a fun one.
Thank you for this assignment, Matt.
Best of luck as you try to make it to number three
to get three green check marks instead of Xs.
Maybe somebody has already.
I wanna know.
I don't know.
It's not like, it's a little person to have a suggestion
that's good enough that we take it
and then that the audience has to choose it.
We do a survey just like Family Feud.
So good work.
And I throw that assignment out to everybody else, too.
Let's see what goes up against American Girl Cafe
next month.
Your Bravery Saved the Podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
And I don't know, does he say,
does Richard Dawson say anything at the end?
He just like mumbles and slurs, I guess.
Yeah, falls over.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, so from all of us here at Family Feud,
make sure to gaborata.
Make sure to use a.
Oh no.
Scott actually did that, too.
Oh, Scott spilled his seven and seven.
That was not just theater of the mind.
He fell over out of the chair to make that sound.
I just wanna let everyone know that
because maybe people would think he threw a book.
Now he's grunting and he's rolling around the floor.
All right, just appreciate what he did.