FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast may contain
fairy fights
incredible ignorance about
ancient bricks
and a bendy-ass Eiffel Tower
Soon you will be airborne
on a potentially bombshell-laden
episode about Soren around the
world on Podcast
The Ride
Welcome to Podcast The Ride where
hosts and audience alike
will soon have the definitive
answer to a decades-old
theme park mystery
Is Michael Eisner the golfer
I'm Scott Gardner. This information is in my brain currently. It will soon be released
I'm like nervous as I say this honestly, I've been
Coming to the table with this and and to be able to share it with you Mike Carlson and you Jason Sheridan guys
Yeah, Mike Carlson here. This was so interesting because I you proposed this
Let me ask a question real quick
You proposed doing this episode and I said I wonder if he knows the answer and you did know the answer when you proposed
Well, it was on a short list. We were talking about what we do post saga getting back to theme park attractions
It was said do we want to do the second half of Soarin?
We owe the second half of Soarin and I was like, yeah, maybe yeah
I guess so and then I went and thought and I was like, yeah
I don't know if I want to do it unless I have the answer to this question
Yes, so I went and I explored I did some what you might call theme park journalism
Yeah, and I have the answer and I'm not even gonna back down from I'm not gonna say I think it's a good lead
Yeah, I've got it for sure. I did like a double intro. I feel like Jason you can get to say anything
How do you feel with this knowing that earth-shattering information? He's coming your way. I answer for Jason. He's scared
He's worried that sort of the glass house. He's built all of his theme park sort of imagination on top of I don't know
Why he's building it on top of a glass house, but that's what he did
It's all gonna come crumbling and crashing down that's what he's worried afraid you nailed it
You hit the ball grand slam, you know
Sort of put you in this position
It's funny cuz I I had a pin note for a few months cuz I had stuff
To talk about from first Soarin. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I do too. Yeah, this is look work
We're this is this is the second part of our Soarin series. We're gonna focus on the world
Versions
But there's still things from a Soarin over, California
the original iteration of this the Disney hang gliding flying simulator attraction and
Among the many things that were talked about the first time was the debate about whether or not in the golf scene the Palm Springs scene
If then Disney CEO Michael Eisner made a cameo as the golf as a golfer who hits a ball
Towards the camera that it that is what we're dealing with here
There is going to be a conclusion to this and I think that that conclusion will come at the end of the episode
Yes, yes indeed to go out with a grand finale
Much like the fireworks at the end of all of the iterations of this attraction gotta save the fireworks for the end
The fireworks of discussing whether a then old and now even older man
Appears as a little guy here you squint at this one part of a ride
Yeah, but yeah, yeah, we're gonna know we will we will find out and I hope you guys aren't filled with fear now
I am still proceed and do the regular show. I'll be honest. I was projecting earlier. Yeah, I'm afraid
I've built all my dreams on top of a glass house. You put it on you put it on Jason
You were so afraid you put your fears on top as I often do with your glass menagerie
Menagerie inside it's all just gonna be a pile of broken glass
It will be a pile of broken glass that I will step in and roll on
It'll get in my skin and I will bleed after this episode. That's what I'm worried about
You know what though?
I listened to the first episode back and the one thing we need to make sure we put a pin in is doing an episode of
Michael Eisner's novel or autobiography
Camp. Yes. Yeah. Well, there's multiple books to go into
Yes, some of what came as the supposed proof of whether or not
Michael Eisner made a cameo in this ride. Yeah was that he went on Larry King
Promoting his book camp, which is about his days
As a boy as little Eisner which I believe is available in the Libby app from the LA library
But it's a bridged it is a bridge what you said on the other episode
Still haunted that's why I haven't like come on to listening. You're really gonna use the word haunts
How haunted are you his glass house is haunted? I cuz I I mostly I've been doing more audio books in the last few years
But I mostly like the unabridged first, of course
You need to get the raw details with the raw detail young Michael
But he does read his own audio book. So like
I'm Michael Eisner the man who's about to take your virginity
Is a raw yes
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's not a bridge a bridge is probably sanity totally unabridged
Yes, that's that's rated is the more common term
But yeah unabridged books, you know might leave in some of the some of the naughty stuff
A bridge is just about him in the canoe and stuff. Mm-hmm
Passages about his canoeing fucking in the canoe, but in the unabridged, okay
Yes, there's no fucking in the canoe all clean canoe rides clean safe. Nice canoe rides when it's abridged. Okay, right
No, I noted that too. All right
Well, it's good that we go back and we revisit these things because yeah fall through the cracks
Imagine how haunted to use Jason's term the listeners would be if we did not do a full thorough
examination of Michael Eisner's book camp
There really there is so much stuff to do
I mean, I'm always happy when when he is part of these episodes and part of these discussions
He's gonna be part of this one in a big way
But let's save that for the end because there's other stuff to get through
So as I said, it's our second episode about the sword and franchise. It started in California adventure
It's now in parks all over the world and that is kind of our focus today is the world version
There's a number of different names for that soaring around the world soaring fantastic flight
It's roughly the same ride film but different
Aspects to the the pre shows and even though even the ride films themselves in yeah
But you know, this is kind of the rough division that they wanted to start peppering in this, you know
The only hit for California adventure really yes when it opens in 2001 and a hit big enough that they want to start putting it
In international parks, but is it weird to be in international parks and you're going over Camarillo
Landing at Disneyland, that's a big thing about the various soaring around the world
It it writes that last scene to like you're going over the place
You are every one of them gets a custom ending usually of the theme park
You're in but sometimes not not in the yeah in the case of Shanghai
but that said in sort of the
Non-strict confines of the Soren over, California episode back in September
We made it such that you know, we just we cut it off after two hours, you know
Hey, we can save that stuff for next time
Well, we're at next time before we move to the world
Is there stuff that we want to talk about from the original iteration of Soren?
Well, we didn't this is tough because we didn't get to the ending
We didn't even talk really about Tinkerbell. I don't know if we should just save that for the end of this
Because it's sort of similar. Mm-hmm, but I don't know some of my thoughts
Hey, if you're if you're if you're anchoring to talk tink then let's talk I am hankering. Yes
I think we didn't even discuss how do we feel about Tinkerbell showing up because this is a ride that does not have
Cartoon characters in it. It is human beings
Obviously, there's a little CGI in the first version in the Soren over, California
Which is the hang glider and I assume some other places I forget maybe the maybe the balloon well the golf ball
Yes, this controversial scene that they did not shoot a golf ball at a helicopter camera
No, that was soaring toward a golf ball. Yeah. Yeah
And that's that's one question. I don't know whether that proves
It is Michael Eisner or not. Do we think Michael Eisner was a good enough?
A crack shot. Yeah. Yeah. Yes to be that perfect to hit a moving target in the air
This isn't even something that regular golfers deal with no is to like they're they're thinking about the hole
But for a golfer to have to hit a moving target. This is more like skeet shooting. That would be awesome
I would really want to play golf if you had to hit
Moving aerial targets. Yeah, there's like a more like duck hunt
Yeah
Yeah, a hole in the front of like a
Helicopter and they would just swoop down and you try to get the hole for the ball in that hole
Yeah, that'd be awesome. It sounds insanely hard. Yeah, you're at now. You're you don't really have a putting option
This is almost this is like golf is yeah hole in one or nothing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, which is the stakes are high
Mm-hmm. Well, look, I know the creator of slam ball. So maybe he would be interested in my new idea here
So it was an effortless drop knowing the creator of slam ball
I do these not commonly said thing on the shit something you've said a lot
Yes, and I still don't really know the ins and outs of it. I gotta know if that's true
No, it's but I've said this a couple times on the show. No one has asked any further questions
I was I was thinking how this has never been explored. It is something that I kind of want to keep moving
Bring it up now though. I don't do you know the full story already Jason?
I know a little bit and I remember slam ball is trampoline basketball. Yeah, no spike TV
Well, that's that's maybe one reason I've kept moving is that I don't actually know what slam ball is
Oh now I know it's I was like that's not the one with wheelchairs. Is it? No, that's a different thing
That it's just called wheelchair basketball
Isn't there there's like a documentary about it
Oh
No, I do not know the creator of murder ball. Okay. Well, I would have stopped you if it was the creator of murder ball
Set up outside of Universal Hollywood many years ago. Oh, yeah, I saw it. Yeah
Yeah, I saw that was actually next next like an accident actually though. I would didn't get there like VIP passes or something to it
But I'll score the VIP slam ball
I brought this up on the show before. Yeah, mine was also accident. Like I just walked by and saw the sets
So you guys ever stop and think about how lucky you are just an accidental pass by slam ball
Mm-hmm, and that's just a day in your lives in Hollywood
And I was there the day that Gavin Newsom stood by a minion and said that the pandemic was over
Didn't you miss it though? I didn't see it. I was down over a lot. Hey
Humble, you know, you aren't lucky all the time. That's true. I was what year was that? Oh
2012 right, is that right? No, it was 2021. I think 2021
Summer and Optimus was there too. Optimus was there. Yes. I assume that Lucy was standing next to Gavin
We would pecker probably she took her Vitamita, Vegemin mask off. Mm-hmm. They did the whole
Routine with the conveyor belt with Gavin Lucy and Gavin doing the chocolates. Oh, yeah putting them in the hat and stuff
Yeah, it was fun. Everything was that was even harder than being the governor. Just kidding actually, California
These times have been extremely trying even more than a fast moving chocolate machine
But that ends today because covet ends today let's french laundry is open for everyone now
Next let's say like next time I find a reason to crowbar and then I know the creator of slam ball
Let's explore it, but not now. I want to talk about tinkerbell. No save it for the camp episode
Um, how do we feel about tinkerbell in it? I don't know
You know, it's it's at the end if it was in the middle
Yeah, it would take me out of it
But we're already at disneyland. We're we're dealing with magic
The fireworks are also seem very fakie in all of them. Yes, not in a way that bothers me
but you know, it's I think we have reached magical realism by the end of soren and I have no objection to
Tinkerbell other than her being from my least favorite cinematic world. Sure
Um, I I don't i'm not mad when she shows up
I like I believe you I like tinkerbell. I'm not mad. I don't get mad every time I see her, but I don't know
That it would have been my choice. I don't think my I think I would have been in the room arguing against this
I understand ending up in disneyland, but
I don't know why we need a cartoon character in this
ride
I don't well, I don't maybe a child needs to be part of this conversation
Child a child in here. What about a man with a mind like a child? That's what i'm that's where i'm coming from here
Uh, uh, I just feel like there was a way to do it without tinkerbell
Because it doesn't it's you know what here here
If they had done like more of like a wonderful world of disney intro or something if patrick was not there
And like it made more thematic sense. They're like, oh tinkerbell's there
She's putting a little bow on the end of this thing. I just like she's giant. I guess in this screen, too
I don't like the scale of it
Again, I don't not like this. She's fine. I'm not upset by it, but it's not my choice
And I always feel like it not that it takes me out of it
But I feel like it's not really like a mismatch or something to me a little bit of a mismatch
I don't know. It just doesn't feel like the ride to have a cartoon character on
Am I crazy here in in around the world? Does she only show up in the american versions?
Oh, that's a good question. I haven't watched fantastic flight in a while. I watched all the endings and now I forget
Oh, well just let's thinker bell appears of no above like disney sea. No, I don't think so. Yeah, so I'm just magic
It's a magic kingdom thing. It's a castle park thing. Yeah
I don't know. I feel like
I should be coming in with like the hot opposite take you could say you like it me
This is something I have no feelings either way. Oh, okay, it's just something that's never
Bumped me interesting. I don't understand your pitch about you have to remove patrick
In order to make this work if it was like if there was some sort of like framing where it's like
Oh, this is a wonderful world of disney and now we're doing a travel log or something
That's sort of the premise of the ride because tinkerbell would be on that show and it's like she's putting a little bow at
The end of this ride where you're you're going through the actual tv show or something
Versus to be through the tv show. This is a pitch off the top of my head
I'm just saying a way to maybe make it make some thematic sense to me
You think she just kind of seems like an afterthought just showing up at the end a little bit of an afterthought
But also the way I read the ride when she does the little you know
The little magic thing at the end the magic swipe at the end. She blesses you she blesses you that almost feels like you're
Saying oh by the way, what we just did was magic
But everything up until that point is practical everything up to that point is sort of acting like this is a real thing
You're going on. Here's a pilot. We've got this contraption
Everything is practical except for the clouds at the very beginning the golf ball that comes toward you the hang glider
Practical in the sense that they're
Like pretending that it's real. It's the real world. It's more the real world than it is
Like we have some we found a little uh, uh canister of pixie dust
And we're sprinkling it on these little seats and you put your your seat belt on and your dirty yellow strap
You tug on it and then we sprinkle you with pixie dust and you fly
the way it's sort of being like
Portrayed is that this is more of a practical
Fun trip through the world. Obviously you're teleporting to some degree
So there's magic involved obviously we don't know what this flying contraption is
I think more in fantastic flight they go more into what the details of it are
But it just feels like oh this was actually just some magic thing tinker bell did at the end. It almost is like
It comes in out of nowhere to me
And it makes it feel like well that kind of like you think it's a reveal that she made all the flying happen
Yeah
Why would she be there?
And why does she do it again and we transport back because you're a disneyland because tinker bell lives at disneyland
She comes up and says hi. Yeah, but it is the park for adults
It is a park for you're right about that, but that's not where you are in that scene
You're above disneyland and you're above a castle a concert forever decorated for christmas
Mm-hmm
The most lights that way I think that's nice. Hello
She does a little her wand thing and then we all of a sudden transport back
Uh-huh. She's flying we're back down. That's her taking away your flying powers. That's her
That's her shutting the machines off. Sure. She begins that that's it's practical
She begins the power down procedure for the hang gliders
so
If there was a little hidden thing where she was like pixie dusting
The machines before we started then I would be comfortable with it if there was like a little easter egg
Where like she sort of sprinkled you wanted to wrap around you want less photos of like
Howard hughes in his how about this patrick is sort of doing the introduction
He has all the same lines that we love and then he goes he's like there's something in his pocket or something
He's like quiet down there quiet like there's a little like a
Tinkerbell he's shoving the pixie into his pocket because the pixie flight attendant is keeping a pixie
Well, maybe she can't breathe. She's in the what that happens to her
I think of peter pan a couple times right where she's in a pocket. I wouldn't know
Jason help me out here. How many times is tinkerbell in a pocket?
Well, I do under the camera up top my head. She gets caught in the pocket
Am I crazy? She gets caught in stuff sometimes. No, I think that's right
But yeah, so i'm just saying if there was a little bit like they were alluding to her first or the early part
Then it would make more sense or I guess if she just waved at us
And that was it and then then our machine
Powered down this but then you would be here saying
But in the why i've tinkerbell in there if she doesn't do the pixie dust
That's what tinkerbell is about. I think you'd be finding some problems. It's not no matter. We'll never know. We'll never know
I i'm never again. I'm not mad. I believe you i'm not don't raise your voice
To tell us that you're i'm not mad. I'm not mad. I I I think my
Objection my version of this is in this
Soarin around the world over the horizon whatever you want to call it
Sure is a little more like the soarin over the uncanny valley
Where it's like wait those animals are doing tricks. Yes, like that polar bear's dropping at the right point
Uh, it's far worse because then they're trying to sell it as realistic
Yeah, as opposed to just cartoon laid on top of uh, but you know just to close it out
I hear you. I think it's interesting. I also think
Who fucking cares? What do you mean? It's tick tickable shows up for one second. How could this possibly bother you?
I look i've i've expressed my feelings about it. I think it sort of invalidates everything we've gotten up until that point in the ride
and I think they could make some tweaks and it would make a little bit more sense why she's there and then she
De-blesses you and sends you back into the real world
Unblesses you that's the way I feel. I don't feel she's blessing us. She is like the sun
And you are icarus and you have you your hubris has gotten out of
She's sending you back down to earth, but at least she's humbling your fault. Yeah humbling you it's really a mental change
Yeah, she's we want to soar forever and she's like no way get out of here. That's my territory
I'm sure the moment where patrick in the pre-show captures her in a jar
As tinkerbell is constantly being put in jars
I'm sure that was cut for like bullshit budget reasons
That's possible. Yes, and that would help if they put it back in if they have some money left
From these new haunted mansion renovations they could do that and fix a big problem a big
Uh, it's gotta be from there
They have to come in under so they can put in a scene with patrick in a jar
I also what is up? Why are we by the way so familiar with patrick?
We're all saying so patrick and patrick if they're listening to sorry
We mean patrick warburton the who's in the pre-show they listen to soren 2 they listen to soren 1
Yeah, I know. I think people know that it's just an odd choice. We've unilaterally made patrick, you know patrick
Yeah
So anyway, that's again not mad. I'm just saying there could be little fixes
And uh, like taking away the little bit of child whimsy
In an otherwise kind of adult ride you want to rip the cartoon fun
Right out of this instance. Yes, and if I was in imagineering at this point, I would have
Handcuffed myself to the desk until they took her out
But would have been your chair throwing i'm not mad moments in the office next time I see her
I won't be mad at her. Okay. Yeah, and the you know, just hey
I'm gonna i'm gonna clear these chairs before we get out of here today just to make sure one doesn't go flying
Okay, if you're if you're still this not mad at the end of the episode
I'll handcuff myself to the chair if something gets said in this episode that I don't like
And you'll have to take it back. That's fine. All right
We'll just we'll shut the lights out on you lock up the building
You have to live with the knowledge that i'm in here while you're sleeping in your beds
I mean we are gonna have to set the security codes. So try not to move around too much
Well, but when the police come i'll explain what they did what they did to me officers
What these gentlemen did why what they said first they didn't remotely understand why i'm properly
Not upset about a ferry at the end of a disney ride. Yeah, right then
um, here's here's what I want to
Say before we close out
California, yeah
My biggest block of information that I have to expel from my brain is about a kind of dry scene though a cool scene
Which is the scene with the aircraft carrier?
Uh, I believe you're in you're in long bay. No, no, no san diego. Why do I say i'm san diego?
You're in san diego in that scene and uh, you are flying over
You know, you're you're coming close to landing on the uss john c stennis
And I thought I gotta figure out if there's anything else here about this man or about this ship
And there is both so here is some story time for all of you about john c stennis first the man
Uh john c stennis was a mississippi senator from 1947 to 1989
If you can imagine
In those years the kinds of opinions that a mississippi senator might have had perhaps a segregationist perhaps
Opposed all of the uh important 1960s civil rights legislation
Uh, not a good man. Um a democrat
Uh, and yet still man, so this I don't know this proves to me that a democrat can be not a good guy
Well, they kind of the party's kind of swapped
I think he was also joking
The republicans were awesome in the 1960s. Oh, they rocked they rocked
Um, but anyway, I say that he's a democrat because it factors into
The story i'm going to tell here, which is his main
uh kind of
I don't know notability in history
Maybe uh, I mean one one part of history was all of these bad things that he did and the bad votes that he made
Yeah, but uh, the other thing about john c stennis is his uh participation
In the watergate scandal
Uh, so we're let's cut too late in the watergate scandal nixon is
Against the ropes a special prosecutor has been appointed and he wants nixon to hand over
His many hours of weirdly recorded tapes in the oval office, please give this to the special prosecutor's office
Nixon does not want to do this
Uh, because they likely incriminate him and also on the tapes
He uses a lot of foul language and racial slurs sure so he nixon's like, okay
Nobody's the american people are not going to hear these tapes
Uh, here's what but I want to help out. I am a helpful man me richard nixon
I will make you a compromise
We will do the stennis compromise
Um, this is probably if you're into the whole watergate story
You surely know this but I didn't know this step of it and this was the stennis compromise
Uh, you know, all right john c stennis. He's a democrat as you know, he's not he's not I should be a little bit nixon
He's not in my pocket. He's impartial, right?
Uh, so here's what we'll do
He will listen to the tapes and he'll give you the gist of what's on the tapes
We'll put him in a room with the tapes and then he will describe what he heard on the tapes
And then no one needs to hear the tapes and special prosecutor archivald cox said that seems weird
Uh, why would that be?
Why would he be a good person to do that? Because democrat he is democrat. He that is and then
Uh the special prosecutor keeps thinking and says wait a minute
Do you want him to give the gist of what's on the tapes because he's extremely old
almost deaf
and
Extremely medicated because earlier in the year he was mugged and shot. Oh my god
So here we have him nixon's idea of how to be fair is to get the most
Enfeebled man in washington a guy who's like his senses are not working in multiple ways
And he's just gonna listen to a tape and see what he retains or hears at all if anything
This is like a cohen brothers movie or something like it's really
This was cut from bernie after reading for being too on the nose
That's really funny. It speaks to the calm frame of mind of nixon at this time. What do we do?
Okay, we're gonna find a deaf guy who's a deaf guy and make sure okay
Why don't you have somebody mug and shoot him? Okay, wait cut that from the record
We're not gonna say that i'm the one who commissioned the shooting anyway, okay, um, so uh, yeah
The plan's crazy and paranoid the special prosecutor archibald cox rejected it nixon said okay
You're fired and that was the saturday night massacre
Oh, yeah, which was the big thing that showed the corruption of the office at this point
The kind of thing that trump did all the time and will possibly in the future
Or maybe not eat. I don't know. You won't even have to do it all the time
Very good point but at the time
This was a scandalous thing for a president to do and it involved this
Very stupid idea involving the man who the ship is named after wow
And now every time you go on this ride think about that
When you see that ship, yeah
You could hear nixon's voice in your head when you see this scene like oh what else how can we add to this?
We could spin him around real fast
Making me a lot of spicy food. How about that?
Freedom the freedom the spiciest hot wings we could find there was another great real quick off the off nixon
Nixon's of course his brother had the restaurant on harbor
Oh, that's right. Yes in the inner county near disneyland. There was a there was a nixon diner
Yeah, yes
And i'll shout out uh the bob gurr show that he's been doing on youtube where 20 baxter just did an interview and told a very
amusing
Walt and nixon's brother story
Really which got like he asked his brother to get nixon to come to the opening of the monorail
I believe or something
I I won't go in the full thing because I don't remember it obviously but uh, it's got a bunch of
New newer tony stuff in the sense that I haven't heard him say the same story. Oh 10 times
Like I have another it's not but does but does he do the hits does he tell the breck eisner?
No, breck eisner. No george lucas big snake story here. We're cooking. Okay. I was impressed
I was like, oh I haven't heard like a couple of these. Wow. Yeah. Wow new tony drops new tony drops. Yeah
Okay, so yeah bob it's on youtube. I don't know who's making it but bob gurr has a talk show
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know why I have not been uh watching this. I'll i'll check it out. Um,
Anyway, the uh, that's the man, uh john c stennis to get back to the ship
Uh, the name was approved by reagan on his way out of office like late in the second term
There's a lot of people now who want it to change due to his being a sure terrible segregationist and a racist man
However, there's some history of the ship that has nothing to do with any of this and that is the ship's participation in pearl harbor
Not the attack on pearl harbor, but the world premiere of pearl harbor held by the walt disney company
So this is weird. They must have filmed the scene for soren above the ship, uh late in in 2000
In preparation for california venture and then
may of 2001
pearl harbors
Landing in theaters everywhere. We got to celebrate. We got to go to pearl harbor of the ultimate pearl harbor party
Uh, so hey, why don't we get that ship that worked out so well for us? Well, it is in san diego. That's fine
Why don't let's uh have them take it all the way to pearl harbor, which they did it took five days
Yeah at the military's expense wow, really they paid yeah, well, but they would
Probably because the military probably gave them money for making pearl harbor. I'm guessing
Yeah, it's probably breaking. Yeah, it's one of those things where like as long as it's favorable
The military will pay for certain parts of movies. Oh, did that happen sometimes?
I don't know that that's actually what happened with pearl harbor
But there's like uh, there's articles about it where like if a certain as long as you like say the right things in a movie
It's almost kind of like you're doing an ad, huh? I don't know if that's the pearl harbor
at the very least get like
military liaisons and tanks right they'll give you they'll loan you tanks and jets and stuff and maybe a base or two. I don't know
Well, maybe armageddon or something could have been one of the other, you know
Sure. Yeah, it's possible. Isn't there like there's like a big battle at the end of bed knobs and broomsticks, right?
Maybe the military helped with that. It's very possible a bunch of like inanimate objects
Maybe the military advised it's very possible. Yeah, remember, um
So the patty jenkins was gonna make rogue one the star wars. I'll never forget that
Do you remember the teaser where she got out of a jet? Like it was like it wasn't rogue one
It was a separate show or well, no film probably was it called rogue squadron? It's called it's rogue squadron
Something that does did not ever exist or like the x-wings the video there was a lot of rogue one
Rogue squadron video game rogue squadron was of course the group of x-wings. Yes. And of course jason
Do you think I don't remember patty jenkins with the roller blades?
On the military base with the jet talking about why she's making rogue squadron only for it to be cancelled within a few weeks
Or something maybe not a few weeks. But uh, yes, of course, and then there's a rumor
It was back a couple weeks ago, but then somebody said no, it's not back. Oh, it's back and it's a trilogy
No, wait, it exists less than ever
It's very similar to like there's some you know, I like the first captain marvel movie, but there's some very like
blatant air force propaganda
It's like why what is that? Why why do we need to see them getting out of jets with cool jet stuff? Yeah
Top gun obviously has a good relationship. Yeah, that's all
I mean, it's you know
I with top gun two i'm trying to think
Well now they know I saw it I saw it and I like yeah, they did the movie remember if you saw it
Right in baby time. This is like a month after baby. I watched top gun two
Yeah, this is movie in this theater on a in at home at home. All right. Well, that's a more forgettable
Yeah, yeah. Oh, I saw it at city walk. Yeah, the thunder of the jet. I wish I was having a baby
But they did they did the smart bring her
They did the smart movie thing where it's like we're the good guys and we need to
We need to fly a mission against the baddies
Like the smartest thing ever. Yeah, not saying who the baddies are. Very generic. Uh-huh. Uh-huh
So yeah, so they could have been aliens for we don't even we don't even see human heads under those helmets
We don't know who the hell's in here
Did walt ever get the military to move a giant ship somewhere for some sort of promotional reason? I wonder
Like back in walt's day. It was on the to-do list probably they were satisfying 20 000 leagues or something
Do they have any subs?
Oh, I remember what I wanted to ask. Is this an active aircraft carrier? Is it decommissioned? I believe it's active
Okay, at least it was at the time. Yeah
But you know, it was not active on the night of the premiere in 2001 where it hosted such
Hollywood luminaries as ben afleck alec baldwin tom sizemore dan ackroyd
Courtney love lots of actual veterans and of course byron allen
Hell yeah, he's not in the movie, right? I've never seen pearl harbor actually
I don't think there's a byron allen. I don't know but maybe you know, I could play a general or yeah
No, I know that would have actually have been like I would have put that to the top of the queue if he's is
He acted in something. Um
Don't know that's a good question. Uh, uh, maybe in the early days. Yeah
Um, I know I did well something to dive into. Yep
Uh people are salivating for more byron allen. We will content. Yeah, my biggest question because it is funny that like
All right, hollywood head out to hawaii because we're having the pearl harbor party of a lifetime
And it did make it gave me a question on the way out the door, which is did the movie surfers go to the pearl harbor premiere?
Do you remember the disney channel movie surfers? Oh, no, I don't actually
Um, they're out of you know, it was like I don't know if any of them got famous or anything
But they were like, you know like they they'd send a bunch of uh, uh, cool confident teens to go cover movie premieres
Oh like red carpet like yeah
And I wonder if the movie I wonder if like the movie surfers ever did a you know
and we're and was it like a typical like
What's up guys psyched to be here with the great tom sizemore and we can't wait for pearl harbor
Did you know pearl harbor was based on real events?
Or did they acknowledge it and like hello everybody and welcome to a particularly somber movie surfers
Um, we're surfing a little slower today in honor of everyone who lost their lives on that fateful day
Did they ever do a touching tribute?
movie surfers on imdb lists from 97 to
Do really it's a franchise is still it says jungle cruise
Like oh did movie surfers help promote the jungle cruise movie possibly
Wow, I haven't checked in in a while and I don't know what's on the disney
I don't know if the disney channel is just a test pattern today or I guess iqvc things are on it
I don't know. It's a home shopping thing
Um, yeah, it says episode guide on imdb 97 up like 97 episodes. Sorry of movie surfers
And this is what you're talking about. I can't imagine it's something different
but I it's got to be weirder today because at the time the surfing kind of referred to the
internet aspect of things that these are some like
tech confident to me
Who can go to?
Traditional movie premieres and post their findings on the internet where the fellow teens are you see what this says disney online podcast
Is there a movie online podcast?
Wow, and well like most uh film reviewing enterprises in america has
Movie surfers turned incredibly toxic and see the right wing. He probably
Would we if disney online podcast still exists I would leave forever dog in a second
I don't care. I will join disney online podcasts as long as they make the right offer
You know, well, I assure you they won't
Well, we gotta look at that famously cheap company the disney corporation
I'm sure each movie surfer was paid their their fair shake movie surfers is hard to search images only
Because you had to go through all the images and go like okay movie surfers
It's not johnny tsunami and it's not rip girl and it's not teen beach
And it's not teen beach, too. It's not a movie about surfers
Yeah, so they made a lot of a lot of beach movies movies really came back
So that's a famous ship. Yeah, it sure is. So yeah, don't just you know
Don't when you pass by that on the ride
Don't think that that was just involved in some like
Boring kind of like all right. This is going to be parked off the coast of guam or whatever
Right, you know thomas sizemore party bear
Dan ackroyd and presumably donna dixon had a blast that night probably that is also that
Feels like a very rich territory of like
Huh? I never really thought like who is this building named after like looking into like oh no
Yeah, I think um, well mccarran
The va the vegas airport is now harry reed airport and he was an okay guy because he really wanted to get those alien records out
But um the person was named before him mccarran. I think was a a bit of a nut job
Well, I think it's fair to say that if you if you are in a big expensive seeming building
With the name of a man on it. It's a bad man
Just a rule of thumb. I mean maybe not always good chance
Freeways if you're on if you're on a highway named after somebody, I don't know. That's uh, that's that's that's dicier
so maybe sometimes that's somebody who was
Killed on that stretch of road or said, you know that that one's iffier but the building
Definitely probably and and they're like that person
Uh murdered people and those bodies are buried in the basement of that building
Except for the john bon jovi rest stop in new jersey. Oh, yeah with all the
About the new jersey great residents charity work
He has his wine. We everybody likes hampton water. Everybody loves john bon jovi. Do you think everybody likes hampton water?
I assume they do. I've not tried. What was that based on? Let's back that let's source that
Well, let's not let's not source it
Well, what we should do is after that that chunk of info unless i'm missing anything
Uh, we should move on to the world. Yes, we're deep into it now. There was a lot
I feel like world gets hate
Most I think the cool opinion is to like california better. Yeah
and I
Slightly disagree. I think I like world but I think i'm just coming out hot here really interesting
I do think I like world better. Don't be mad at me. I know i'm throwing a lot of
Hardcore opinions around incendiary opinions today
But I think I like world better and I just want to put that on the table
Up front the only thing i've been mad at and I haven't had the wine
But my guess is that hampton water sucks. So i'm mad about that
Okay, but I just I should try it and know for sure that would just be we should do a hampton water episode
Um, well, all right, I should I should have let that I you know what you should have left that back at the rest stop
The wrestling chant, uh, you fucked up
I was clear and then I went backwards. No, no, no, I wasn't even thinking about an episode
I was going to say get some hampton water
For the uh, feek soren episode, but I didn't consider a whole exploration of the world of hampton water
Again, I think you know, I think we were I think we were fine where we were
I was saying it as something I was mad about incendiary opinion wise this one
I don't know. You know what I was going to come in with and it's less hot of a take
I think I would still vote california over world, but I think that
being
Mad at world. I don't quite relate to yeah, I don't think that I don't think that it's bad
I think we will talk about things that we don't like as much and maybe mike will disagree with those things
But I yeah would I vote for california over worlds definitely
But i'm not upset if I get to one of these and it's world. Yeah
Um, yeah, I don't know jason. What do you think? Um, I think I lean towards scott's opinion
I I I like california better. I think
I don't know if that's just the inclination of like
Well, it's it's much more
I don't know. It's shot on film and it went to those locations now. I did see the
Sizzle reel on the disney youtube channel of the helicopters
Flying over the world locations. They did it wall. They drove. They drove the helicopter the big wall
This is this is the most dismissive tone i've ever heard. They did it. They did incredible shot
He sounds like he's putting it out
They took a camera to the great wall of china
Wall of china, but this was hand-drawn animation. It was so
This is a beautiful shot. It's incredible. It's beautiful shots
There are some like there's some more cgi. There's some episode one level wipes
There's some episode one level
Transitions the wipes are my biggest issue
Yeah, I would say and just as as a reminder of what we're talking about the the first version sorenover california
You go to all these different locations
And I remember before I went on it thinking how do you transition from one to the other and it's just hard cuts
There really aren't transitions here. They decided to do these kind of digital
Stitch work moments where they find something like what's the one?
where
Um, why am I blank? What is it? That's something turns into balloons, correct?
Uh, what is what is it? That's around that then because oh it's the top of the taj mahal
Right, yes
The rounded shape of the top of the taj mahal becomes balloons in monument valley, right?
I look at those and think stupid the transitions are the silliest part to me
I think it's shocking how well the hard cuts work
In the original I forget if I said this in part one, but it reminds me of
How in many christopher nolan films if you see it in imax format?
It shifts back and forth giant sequences are shot imax which has a different size of frame
Than the rest of it and I remember the first probably dark knight
I was like, how's that going to work and it's just hard cuts and works fantastic. There's no it's so simple
They don't he doesn't need to do some weird morph between scenes. It's kind of crazy. You might you might not even notice it
It's so subtle and I think that's what I think something about the size of the room
Enables that where it's just so I don't know you're playing in such with such broad strokes that you can just do cuts that
That sweeping and sudden but yeah, uh, I don't know should have just been hard cuts
That is my probably my biggest qualm. I think but i'll say something
Uh, very positive. I think one of my favorite theme parks since like pumped into the ride
Is that sort of fruity?
Florally when you you fly over a fiji
That scent and it's I I believe in
It's in flight a passage, too
Um, which was refreshing. It's very refreshing cool
That magic candle company that sells different scents based on rides even as a note on the like
flying over fiji scent like this is very similar to the
Banshee flight scent like so i'm like, okay
Uh, it's a it's a really great scent. That is something that I would put in the
world's
Side of this debate. I think that while you know, we did us we did the fake smell final four
and I think that the
Citrus smell from california made it very far not the final but to the final two
Um, so I think that is the height of the good smell the orange smell
Yeah, uh is is the best of all of these smells
However, I think overall if you're averaging all of the smells and the innovation of the smells
I think the world smell game is better than california
Is that possible even though the best smell is in california? That's a good question because I really like
Fiji. Yes, I really like taj mahal. Yeah, I really like not really like I
I'm fine. I adore africa. I adore africa grass. Yeah, uh, I know I like it. I don't know
Um, I agree with I you know, I think you're right. I think you're right that the winner is in the fur in california
But uh overall what's the other one in california is like pine in the
There or is it is there a malibu? I've already forgotten. Did you say is there milk?
Malibu is there milk? Yeah, is there a milk smell?
Is it the part where they get a baby formula?
Out of the rye when there's a nasty ass milk you drive by that you drive you drive by in the sky
By those cows and you smell milk remember that scene
um
Yes, the scents very good real quick scott back to your point of the transitions. I
I get why they were like, ah the they bother
Me a little bit in the first one. I could see that bothering somebody but what they did the way they did it
It's like there's a kite is a transition to another scene and the kite is so like cgi and fast
Yes, and takes you out of it because I think the hard cuts they were probably thinking like well
I don't want it to be so jarring that it takes people out of wherever they're immersed in whatever scene it is
but I feel like it maybe had the opposite effect because they did such like
Whimsical style cuts. Yeah with like a little like flourish with like a kite cuts you right to the next thing and it doesn't
It's it's more jarring and it takes me out of it more that one is jarring a simple fade
I think would have achieved what they
the best one to me is is uh from I believe
Fiji to
Iguazu the waterfalls. Yeah, that's the closest to a fit. That's just like matching the perspective
Right speed of the water. Yeah, and that one works pretty good to me
It almost like feels like an effect of the mist or something. Yeah, where as opposed to
Kite kite kite hurry up. Get up there. Wipe the scene. Hurry go right and like the desperately quick
Yes, they all feel too quick too. Just like the plane that like flies at you and transition coming in
It's too quick
It feels unnatural
Like it takes your brain out of it too because your brain goes. Oh, that's not real. That's not real the golf ball
I think tricks people still maybe if it's your first time
You go, oh
It's not until like the last five frames. Do you realize that that is fake like it's kind of done
Yeah, it's it's small enough
You know, it's like a small enough little detail that they get away with it as opposed to yes
Like a a sky captain in the world of tomorrow playing flying into your face
Right out of nowhere. It wasn't visible in the frame. It's not like it even crept up fast. It's just like
I'm here. I gotta what to do. Here we go. Yeah, so so
Yeah, I
They would have been better if they just did like a transit like a star wipe. It would have been better
Now we're talking. Yeah. Yes. Yeah
Um, that's I mean it might have been more appropriate for california
To tribute not so much the film industry as the the public access video in yes
You know what the porn industry it'd be a subtle way to nod to the pornography made in the san fernando valley
To do star wipes and page peels. Yeah page peels. They should page peel every scene to the next
To the next place
I'd like to ask somebody re-edit soren and put in all all of the great wonderful wipes out there blinds the ones that are like
Yeah, like venetian blinds suddenly. I know split the screen into 14 parts the old like final cut express
Like things I use in college. Yeah, any of those perfect
Yeah, when you see those when you're getting ready to edit something well they have them here
Am I supposed to not use them?
Why would I I wouldn't be taking advantage of the program that I have possibly borrowed but possibly
Burned from the one copy that's going around this entire school
Yeah
That all all 100 people editing on are on the backs of this one set of cds and then like is it harder or easier to steal?
Editing software now. I'm not sure
Uh, i'm i'm a i'm a sucker in a dope and I pay the subscription for the adobe
Products and i'm positive. There is a way to because that's you know
It used to be that you'd buy a cd and now you have the program forever
They figured out that the money is in you never fully have it you pay them forever to have these products
It's a monthly subscription in which you get nothing new
That's like streaming services
Well, at least you get new shows. I guess that's you know, this is just you get to continue to have adobe audition
Uh, this is a dry point
But it's a it's a silly thing
I am positive that there is a way that I could hack my way to not paying this company anymore
Uh, but i'm just too good of a boy to go figure it out. I meant um
I meant in colleges. Is it easier with like, um we transfer and dropbox?
and google drive to just
Send someone the driver. It's you just have to have the code to like unlock a piece of software, right?
So I don't know how I do remember getting like a cd that was burned of some software and then people being like try one of
These 15 codes
And see if one of them works. Yeah, and i'm like, I don't know how you got these codes
But I will try them and then one would work. This is too much editing talk. Sorry. Sorry
But it is a lot of I mean
Editing plays such a big part in both easy tracks. Oh, yeah. Yes. There we go
Yeah
We did all just point at jason a lot
I've never been more frightened when someone was agreeing with me. No, no, that was us going. Yes
Good good good
You did transition us back into that was a transition as smooth as those in soren around the world
A seamless morph as if done by a quick moving plane
Editing does play such a big part in both of these things both of these sets of footage
But it this I feel like
around the world
Is a good reminder of like oh, yeah editing is so subjective
But you know something is wrong like like instinctively people whether they know editing or not they
Either they know when to go like
Or when they're like, oh, I don't really care about that
Well, you know what?
I mean, yeah speaking as an editor it is true that like I mean, I think what I like to avoid
Is something that's so fast that it takes you out of it
Yeah
That like I don't like either it's got to be slow and graceful enough that you kind of like transition into it and accept it
Or there's just nothing there and I think that is the problem with some of these that play
I think if the plane took two seconds and not yeah point zero zero two
Uh, yeah, it's just uh, it's too fast. It's very jarring. Um, let's talk about uh stuff
In it though. Yeah, uh, and that's that's really what I mean something you'd have to give it up for this ride
Is that you do see?
um incredible sites that they
broadened the horizon of
What they can where they can take these cameras where they can take us
Using this technology not that camera rio wasn't great
We could have stayed in camera rio forever and looked at citrus groves forever and it would have been fine
We didn't even get to the outlet malls of camera rio
Uh, well, well that look that's a saga you're talking about. So we'll deal with that. Uh for many many days
2037 um, but yes you get to go
You know like just to sites that you will you may never get to see in your life and certainly not from
This particular perspective. So I think you got to give it up for this global version for uh, you know
Doing that for being like a genuine sightseeing adventure. Yeah, and the scope. Yeah, it definitely feels like oh
It's the bigger sequel. It feels the scope is bigger now and we're getting to do
It's just like the other one
But now we're really exploring the world like it does I feel like they
They made good on the they made good on the premise literally
It's soaring around the world, but it just it feels like the sequel in a way
Like it feels like they've upped the ante
Definitely. Yeah. Yeah. Um, so these start popping up in
And epcot had started showing the california version
Which at the time it felt a little bit strange, but of course now whenever they bring back california, everybody's like fuck
Yeah, I think it's just you just got to keep that but you just got to like slot them in and out
Yeah, it's easy enough. You know, yeah, then it keeps excitement up for both of them
You get a break so that you can come back with open arms. Yes
Although like maybe I kind of feel like it should just be california forever in california. Oh, really?
You know what? Yeah. Oh, okay, because it's special
They know it's now it's location specific and you got to go to
You got to travel the world to go to the world ones. That might be where i'm landing. Okay
Yeah, I disagree but I would like it back and forth
I don't know what a good distribution of months would be because like that's a whole we always have that are in custody
Yeah, because like obviously the whole debate over haunted mansion
How many months should the overlay be and we all have opinions?
I think we all want a little less ideally sure of the overlay
But yeah, I half and half would be good for me even though I prefer world I think
Yeah, I would I would accept half and half. Yeah every other month or six months six months
I think I think we're asking a lot of them to do the every other month. Yeah, I think so
I mean it is interesting to see the switch over only took like
A day or two. Yeah, they didn't shut this down for a long time
No, I don't think it takes that long. No, I I think
Um, all right fine six three months three months three months three like switch over every three months
Well, I kind of like the way they do it a california adventure of when the food and wine festival starts in the new year
Oh, and then they bring back california sure. Yeah, that's good
It's like they were they were also doing that. It's like uh food and wine
We're bringing back that we're gonna have a very small room where you can watch seasons of the vine or narrated by germy irons
Germy you did call him germy. Oh, excuse me. Jeremy
Is it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, okay. It was just the way you you know what I know, you know, his name is germy. I I
Was blanking on his name until the last second. Oh, okay
And I was like, I don't think it was narrated by max von seidel, but I know it's one of the older actors
And then I remember germy irons. You were I thought you were saying you were wondering if it was uh, pepo irons
It's pepo irons
No, I thought max von seidel is going to narrated as death as his character from the seventh seal
He's got to be I mean he's passed away, but he's got to be 40 years older than germy irons, right?
He was an old guy
That's true got about I mean germy irons probably seven years old. I don't know. We don't talk about this. Yeah
We really do. We do not over talking about next on site. Uh, uh, let's talk about these things
Okay, so I think you know what? I think it's a uh, a really excellent first
Moment, I think the the original one set the bar
That the the first thing you see really has to make you gasp because it's golden gate bridge and the first one
And here you're looking at the matterhorn
Yeah, real matterhorn at the border of italy and switzerland in the swiss alps
I also think it's kind of neat this activates the like
Uh genuine disney dork side of me that I think it's neat that this is one of several
Little nods to disney attractions within the world
Right experience. Yeah, I completely agree and this is the type of reference to disney and the company that I like on soren
This is not showing his cartoon is tinkerbell flying
but this is a little
this thematically makes sense and then you can turn to
A partner of some kind and go by the way, did you know this is a little reference to the matterhorn over in
We're looking at matt. I like this tone. We're looking at matt. That's real matterhorn as opposed to the fake matterhorn in park
That's a clever. It's clever. It's clever. You're hitting you're hitting you gotta get right in
Hey, hey dig into their legs. Could you shut up? We waited an hour for them
I'm like you're hugging you're holding a pencil
Stop just stop stabbing my knee with that pencil on my yellow strap. You're tugging on my yellow strap
It's gonna pull the seatbelt out. Are you trying to undo it?
I can't just until you acknowledge this is cool
This is a good reference. I will tighten this and tighten this for the rest of the ride until you tell me this is cool
Has anyone tugged on the yellow strap so hard that they pulled the whole seatbelt out?
Like the strongest world's strongest man
Like it's maybe somebody
Google it. Oh my god. Yes, mike. It happened the entire row
All of the rest of whom were children under five years old
He was taking around as part of a make-a-wish foundation arrangement
Wow, they all felt and they were all on the top row too. Oh my god
Well, I was talking about before takeoff
So that's crazy to hear that I was just imagining a row of american gladiators all on soren
And they tugged on the yellow strap and they ripped the seatbelt right out
They were all chanting matterhorn right matterhorn and so excited that they were yanking and yanking and the whole thing fell apart
So yeah, if you're a pro wrestler or an american gladiator, do not tug on that yellow strap too hard
Know your own strength turbo
Um, I yes, I love the matterhorn reveal and it's a little
We can talk about how the way like depending on where you are how the
Some of these images are a little curved and a little
Well, this is some of the and I know why is it now it happens at the golden gate bridge
It's part of the first one too
But I and I don't know why it is more of a problem in the world version it just is
I don't know what's going on. I know I don't know exactly either
But if you're sitting in the right spot
Yes, it's so fun. It's so cool. I love this reveal not to jump around too much
Sure, I am convinced. I mean the the in this particular ride film where it is
The biggest problem is clearly the eiffel tower. Of course. Yeah, I think you have to be
Front row center you have to be dead in the middle maybe top
Maybe all three. Yeah, maybe all three's okay. Maybe all the centers are fine, but there are certain
angles
from which it seems like the
Eiffel tower is going into some kind of warp tunnel like it is being sucked into a black hole
It is it is it is you might say
Unrecognizable as the eiffel tower a building that we all know goes straight up
Because sometimes you see it at a perfect c
It's kind of crazy. It is is that do you think the high definition element of around the world?
Do you think it's too clear and it's heightening the curve? Does that make sense though? I don't know
I really don't I wish I could say one way or the other obviously if you're on the right or left like the
Like the hard right or left like that's when it's like it warps more
Is the screen curve it's because the screen is curved a little bit
Where the screen didn't change? You know, you're right. That's the I I don't know all
Maybe it's just maybe it would have happened more
In the first ride film, but they you just don't look at as many tall pointy things
Maybe that's it. You're kind of more it's kind of more like landscapes, right? Yeah, and
You know, it's pretty spectacular getting to go right up to that light on top of the eiffel tower
It is a great moment
But if you're in yeah, if you're down in the corner if you're in the basement of this ride
It is definitely a little weird. It's not weird enough to make me hate the ride. It is not however
Um, but it's enough to make you curse eiffel in his foolish tower
Come up his cookies cotton has come up and see yet again
Jason is now of course we haven't revealed the show he hates eiffel
His famous tower why was why must history know his name and not mine? Carnegie would never
Diddle daddle was such foolish
Uh, jason, you should have your own tower
Oh, I'd love to have a tower. Where would you have your tower?
Oh, I don't know
Delaware county, pennsylvania outside of philadelphia. Okay, sounds good. And it's all my favorite spots tower of uh,
hotcakes
Oh and get some hotcakes in there, you know
Just a tower of all the stuff you like kind of a big dagwood sandwich of all of your interests
Tom jones diner that we used to go to after plays that smelled like cigarettes even after smoking doors was banned
So that's in it. There's a diner in the tower in it sex hamburgers, uh bruster's ice cream
All the great local landmarks bruster is franchised in in la now
In la very weird seeing a local, uh ice cream company. Yeah
I do think I like they call the screen 180 degree dome screen
So I think you're right that is like when you in that when it's like a dome screen
It's if you have a long tall object. I just think it's like it's not gonna look right
It's hard when you're coming at it from yeah, you're right. Yeah, it's being it's if it's being projected
Curved well, I mean this this now begs a question and maybe I don't know if you can speak to this or not
But do you think that this kind of thing has been fixed?
You know screen curvature wise at vegas's famous sphere same question
Well, you know what? It's a good it's a good point. I have not seen the postcards show the the darin aronofsky show
Um, I bet it hasn't I bet it's unable to be fixed
But isn't but aren't there those moments like when you're in the tower of code that falls on you
Yeah, uh in the u2 show, although that is that is now passed, but that's a part of the show
Uh, but yeah, but isn't that but that's like you're that's something on a curved screen. That's that reads as
Uh straight lines like I feel like they're able to account for the curvature in a smart way
Yeah, I guess that's true for that specific thing
We're talking about which is when like a the whole sphere feels like it's a trash compactor of numbers coming down on you
But I think it just looks I don't know. I it's a good question
I don't think I think we'd have to play soren in sphere
To know for sure which by the way is something they should do
Let's do that. I postcards is kind of like that the darin aronofsky a lot of people have said is that yeah
It's like a it's like a big sitting soren, right?
So they should have had they should have had all the seats just be soren seats
In this in sphere. Yeah, they did. Yeah, it is it is kind of crazy. They didn't make a move
Yeah, yeah, it was probably on the drawing board, but 40 exit. This is I really shouldn't go on this tangent
It's a lot of time, but I think I can do it quick. Um, I have to bring up when
Uh, there was a lot of text threads going on during the grammys
During the grammys there was a performance by u2 of their new song atomic city
And it was kind of like a greatest hits a little bit of like all of the tricks of throughout their show
Uh that like that, you know like all the many different projections that they would do throughout the the full run of the u2
Sphere show and you expressed on a text chain mike that you were dissatisfied with the performance
Yeah, because you felt that it misrepresented what was on the screen during atomic city, right?
And I said what was on the screen during atomic city and you said I don't know I went to the bathroom
From
Well, all I know is that it wasn't the stuff they were showing because it was in other songs
We don't miss some of it might have been
Well
No, I don't think it was I just thought it was strange that you were defending
Atomic city's honor and here you were taking a piss all over it while you were actually there
Well, look, I guess you're right. They could have done a greatest hits of all the effects during atomic city
But I bet I would bet a million dollars no way and that they used all the effects to make it look like
The number trash compactor was happening during atomic city. Let me ask just I mean you pay so much to go to these things
Um, do they have the projections on the toilet so you don't miss them
In the 180 dome toilet screens, they should be projecting them down into the bowl. That's right
You know which works better if you're peeing then if you're into bono's mouth, basically
Well, you like have a live feed from his now. You're just being ridiculous
Being ridiculous, but uh to an effective end because I think that sounds really cool
I would love to pee into bono's mouth pee into
Pee on like tre Anastasia, whatever his last name is
Anastasia guitar not a musician of that caliber. Yeah, he's now bono. That's another
Thing
I fucked up. I can't think of tre's last name guys. I'm so sorry, but he's fished fished it for
uh for
Sphere shows that did the visuals looked awesome, too. Yes. Yeah, I I do
I I don't necessarily want to go to the shows, but uh, the visuals looked really awesome
The big robot stuff and yeah, oh, yeah that robot looked really cool
They really I feel like did uh did the homework and mainly they did not do any affronts to the
Memory of atomic city. No, not that I saw
But if like educate me, I don't know what happened at every show. Yeah
Okay, we don't have to talk about everything in in all of these but let me just shout out some some scenes
Greenland you're in a yeah world of ice bergs and ice patches your glaciers fjord
Uh east fjord greenland. I don't know if i'm saying that right
Uh, um, here is where we start getting a little nutty with our polar bears
Yeah, our transition whale we get a little a whale splash
That is one of the wipes and yeah, it's you know what?
I don't think you need it and now i'm going to be where you were with. Yeah tinkerbell
I think it's a little goofy. I agree with what jason said earlier. We're in canny. Yes, maybe maybe full cartoon
whales
uh, you know
Pyrocon was in it. Obviously i'd be very happy but besides that
Yeah, I don't think the animals themselves look bad
It's just like but you can tell again doing tricks. You're talking about editing. Yeah, it's just something's different
Something's wrong and I guess most guests probably wouldn't
Articulate that afterward and it's all that was nice or whatever. But your brain is like
That's not one of the chances
Yeah, you know what it all reminds me and I'm not that the cgi is
this bad but it activated the same it's the worst of it activates the same part of me as the
monkeys in crystal skull
As well as the little is it like a a squirrel what pops up?
That's really like a gopher a gopher like caddyshack gopher
at the start of crystal skull
And whatever face he makes is actually broader than the i'm all right dance
Yeah, it's actually sillier than caddyshack. There is like a squirrel cgi
Yeah, or yeah go for cgi the start of crystal skull indiana jones and they these i'm just saying these animals would all be pals
I think I think that I think that the elephant throw in the grass would get along great with the indiana jones monkeys
They're just all cut from the same cloth
Yeah, I it's it's just not my favorite and I think we're going to see a swing away from
This sort of the need to like goofify it with cgi I think cgi is more effective when it's
Realistic or you swing all the way and it's like very fantastical and right again uncanny valley
I think it's it's caught between I I don't know if you guys saw this like
It was just a short like how they did it but the david fincher
Uh netflix movie the killer
There is like he's riding a motorcycle
Cycled through the city and I had no idea this was composite like it was
Some of it was cgi there. There are very
Unique close-ups. I feel like and some of the riding through the city
Is cg and I I had no idea that's I think what it's and i'm sure there's a lot of there must be a lot of
Effective invisible cgi in this ride that we just aren't noticing
Um notably I always think about it in the disneyland parts where you're like what's past disneyland? I guess nothing
What's up north of disneyland? Just a lot of black. I suppose. Let's not worry about whatever
Office buildings and hotels we don't own up there. Yeah. Yes, so there's stuff like there
Yeah, there's little like cleanliness things that they're doing
I'm sure at all of these but that are that are more effective than like the the more showy
Cgi like the plane in sydney, australia in the next part. That's I think the dumbest
I thought it was the animals, but I think that plane the plane is bad. There's a plane. I think it's
Very dumb and takes away from uh sydney and that it's cool to be in that
Part of the cg. Yeah, it kind of makes me think like it's like oh we need to put something dynamic in there and it's like
Do you think whatever you?
Edit in there is going to be more entertaining than uh the outback
or the uh
Mount kilimanjaro like yeah, the most majestic natural beauty you've ever seen it's like it's a little insecure
Yeah, yeah, you know, maybe it's we might be looking at like notes here
We might be looking at kind of like studio executive
Like I don't know. I think you gotta hit them. I thought hey, it's 2016, baby
The kids they some unfocused ran, but they play they play video games instead of seeing movies
We gotta make this like a video game. What does that mean? I don't know. That's for you to figure out
now, you know, it's like how magic is
losing some of its
Credibility as entertainment with movies and video games stealing kids attention
You're kind of quoting the masked magician specials. Oh am I uh, which was the club three thing
Check out club three check out the masked magician episode
um, uh
Now talking about natural beauty and a cool thing to see from a particular perspective. Uh, we see this bavarian castle
Let me take a stab at pronunciation. Noishuan stein
Noishuan stein castle in bavaria. Noishuan stein. Ah the eagle's nest hitler's lair
Yep, you got it. It's not
Yeah, so here is so history you're looking at the the castle where
Soaring over hitler it's all famous hitler places you look closely you can see his rotting corpse
Nobody ever went near it. Nobody touched it
Uh shockingly well, but it's just a skeleton with a mustache on it cga. They cga skeleton in though
They didn't put the real skeleton in there
And it looks fake. Yeah. Well, I think it's really silly that it winks at you. Yeah
Yeah, tinkerbell the tinkerbell carrying the skeleton
At the end
I see I know mike i'm gonna go on record. I think it's nice that tinkerbell is disposing of hitler's skeleton
All right, you know, you're right. I like that hopefully going to drop it somewhere terry in a big pit of fire
Somewhere where it'll never come back. I agree. Yeah. Yeah, I agree with that
In a big pile of shit take it to a sanitation
waste disposal place
Uh, so the real history here is
This is one of those disney nod things because here we are looking at the castle that most closely inspired
Sleeping beauty castle cool. Tell your partner next to you
Grab their thigh jab their legs bruise them
If they leave the ride not blue and black on the leg then you have failed as a trivia provider, sir
We're not going to let you use the single rider's line again if you keep accosting other guests
I gotta do it to somebody with trivia with trivia
This is a point in the ride and I I brought this up
On this last soren episode and I think I completely forgot about it
Because it's something I meant to bring up on other like big ride episodes is that there's a point in rides where
Even if you're tired, you've been on the ride a lot
The magic comes back you can feel that jolt and I would call it maybe like a magic point or something
Where like even on the sleepiest day where you're not so into going on soren
It's nine o'clock and you've been on soren a couple times this year. You're lucky. Whatever
There's a point when you go. Mm. This is good. I'm back
And I feel like it's the castle part of soren over the world really where i'm just like, yeah cool
This feels cool. I feel immersed. It's cool to go around that castle. It looks like such an interesting part of the world
Yeah, I don't ever see it because I don't travel
But this is cool. Yeah, wait, no, no europe for either of you guys. Yeah
I would like to go. Mm-hmm. And uh, well what you did, uh, you did japan. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's good
That's a good one. That's something. Uh, um, yes, there was a theme park in full
Well, I I mean, yeah, look i've i've also yeah, i've been to theme parks on all of my
of all any of my international travels, uh, uh, but um, yeah, you're looking at this you're also like
You know you're looking at this castle and you're like well this is and this makes me now
I have not you know, i've i've been to germany but this you know, this area what i'm looking at here
I'm like see why haven't I been here? This is great. This and this is like some real history
You know and I gotta get I gotta get out of my theme park mind
Yeah, and go see some real history like this castle
Which I can only assume is thousands of years old and is steeped in and then you look it up 1869
This is
Right around civil war this thing is built
It's really crazy
And this the the guy whose castle it is
I looked into king ludwig the second of bavaria who was married to jaja gabor
So that's prince von you're not far off. I was gonna say it's like that
It is like one of those weird
Yes, like the you know when yeah when you're going to tour the liberace house or whatever and like and who are they?
They're a consulate to something. What is that? It's kind of like that because this was like a born into royalty
King who like I think didn't want to be doing it and was and got bored and shifty
And what can I do to make this interesting now?
the good end of this is that he was the main benefactor of richard vogner and like underwrote
Many of his works and a lot of other great like musical and theater works
So he like, you know get used his position to fund that kind of thing and also to fund like
Many fancy houses for himself despite already having the one right this what we're looking at in this
Ride is not a castle. He needed to have he was set on castles
But just like had a lot of money to burn
But then he's like he's kind of like a michael jackson of his era because then he went broke
Like building more fancy stuff. Yeah, so he had no money to finance things like this that he did not
Need and he just like basically this guy he started to be known as the mad king
And wow he like that's the first stuff a professional wrestler known as the mad king
No, oh, yeah, but that's a nod perhaps perhaps a nod. I don't know. He's not quite doesn't sound like this guy
Um, he's really so yeah, I mean it's gay first. I'm like, why is this guy? What's wrong with him?
He's like, you know what? He's using his position of power to
to empower
Uh great artists and architects much like the soon to be talked about again michael eisner
You know what? He's he's in this position to like leave his mark on the globe
Artistically by helping these other people as a benefactor. What's uh, and then you started reading more
I mean, he really only hurt himself
I feel like he started sleeping during the day and riding horses all night
He commissioned hundreds of plays that were for himself alone to watch
He would just sit in a room
Many many people on stage and then hooray
All right. Well, it's now it's uh, six a.m. Time for bed. Wow
He stopped talking. He communicated only in notes
Uh, you couldn't look him in the eye
Again, we're still i'm still feeling good about this. This is like prince
That's like the only he only he just asked other people to make the music and he didn't do it himself
Right, right. That's the memo steve harvey sent that out. That's a normal thing to do. Don't look me in the eye
You're busy. You've also outed yourself as a as a steve harvey supporter
And yeah, like i'd be a believer in everything that he does. Yeah, so he was just he was a steve harvey of his time
Um, but then ultimately it was the rampant spending and going into dead on castles and operas that he didn't need
Uh, which was the fuel to declare him legally insane
He was captured and deposed and taken to some kind of compound
Which had lots of bodies of water to prevent you from escaping if you had been declared insane
Like the marvel universe the raft or whatever like this super villain prison in the middle of the ocean
The i'm just talking about like a creek but
The rock I guess
And ultimately he's just like a this is just like an out of shape guy
He's probably not gonna make it out of the creek. So it's no it's not as cool
Yeah, yeah, it's not like trapping people in the middle of space. I see
Negative zone, but yeah, he no they didn't need that because I think immediately they took him there and then like two days later
He tried to escape and he drowned and it's unclear whether that was
Suicide or he just fully drowned or if it was a murder because there were maybe signs of
struggle, but then they said no that was him fighting the other guy and then he was he killed the guy and then
And then killed himself because of what and I think this is still in dispute whether uh, king ludwig
Died by suicide or was killed while trying to leave the combat. So the abstin of his day
The debate
Again, I didn't read the full history. Yeah, baby, you know
It's always safe to assume that there were a lot of bad things of that nature happening
But that didn't seem like the primary facet of this guy and I say good job
Paying for lots of plays that no one else got to see
Why is that right? This guy should not have been taken to this compound
Uh, he should not have been anywhere near this creek
Um, so anyway, yeah, that's all like pretty recent history at this castle
This was the summer home of a crazy man
Wow, yeah
Not that far just like only a couple decades before walt disney himself was born the magic and that's my magic point
That's the point where the magic of the ride will it's undeniable to me again
Yeah, because you feel the spirit of king king ludwig ludwig
Yes, madness gets you excited. It's got the bavarian monarchists in the show. They're gonna be pretty pissed at you
There's a few of them he's casting doubt on the ludwig story
Let's drown him at once and make it look like suicide. Do you know good bavarian voice probably? Yeah, it seems like right. Uh, I don't know
I don't know what i'm talking about
Um, I wonder like is the castle like is it tourist available?
Like can you because it's giant so you can do a tour of it. I believe so interesting
Yeah, I don't know that for sure
I just I assume you're assuming think about you know what you're looking at that shot on the ride and you're like
This is going to involve a lot of climbing or at least a shuttle that's going to really sputter on the way up there
Here on the ride. I just get to enjoy this and then i'm on to the next place
Well, that's what the whole joy of going to theme parks that transport you to places in the real world
That's the whole thrill of it. That's right knock stuff off. You go back out then you go out all that
and the headache
But wouldn't it be nice if there was like a like a little mini mall outside of the king ludwig castle like a like a city walk
And then the way that you discovered that there was like an abbey or was there an abbey road city?
Oh, yeah, I forgot what it was called. Yeah, it was like liver walk or something. Yeah
Liverpool city walk
beetles themed everything
Um, I don't know. Well, you know like I mean there's truth
I mean vatican city is surrounded by the shittiest shopping district you've ever seen in your life. So very possibly
Um, yeah, no there there could very well be ludwig walk. They just disney just scrubbed that out. It's vatican city like
It's buying indulgences, right?
It's buying like groceries and stuff. I mean, I think that's part of it
So a hard rock cafe is there like I think it's I think I think it's all yeah
I think yeah, I mean not too far is I definitely saw the one in rome but vatican city specific
I mean, I wouldn't be surprised if you're looking at like
uh poorly photoshoped
T-shirts of the pope hanging out with tupac
I feel like it was that level next to a chipotle
Because I mean you gotta eat my infinite blessings to you deadpool
It's gotta be deadpool has to be within
200 feet of the vatican
It's on like a shirt or like it's pretty trashy pretty clearly. Yeah, it's gotta be I think so
I'm gonna look up pope and deadpool just while in case there's any
Let's see
Uh, well, there's pictures of there's somebody who like mashed them up who was a who was a pope deadpool
Well, of course, I like that costume. All right. So there's yes. Hey in keeping with the spirit of the man himself
Um the man deadpool and so in deadpool's name
Jimmy changa, jimmy wade wilson
Uh, I think you gotta
Kill him in jaro after this. Yeah, tanzania elephants. I like that. As I said, I like the smell here
I like the smell the grass. This is grass that I like and uh, it's good grass and then
Uh, but digital anime, I don't know. They aren't all so bad
They're running elephants is good. They're close to you and they're better than
Lion king slash mufasa coming to theaters end of year. That's true. But what isn't better?
True. I mean of all all art on earth. What isn't better than the new lion king questions?
I'll get look I haven't seen mufasa yet. Maybe mufasa takes it to another level. I don't know. Yeah
Well, very yeah, barry jenkins says it's about empathy. So there you go
So if you want, all right, if you want a movie about empathy mufasa is the place for you. I do want that
the great wall of china
Yeah, the best
Yeah, in my mind. Yeah, this is the best scene. Beautiful and also makes me
Hunger for a little more thrill even and like the way they they because they did a very dangerous seeming dive
By the wall. Yeah, get you to really kind of feel like you're like gonna kick a guy in the head
I think it's a cgi guy probably but
Uh, uh, you know what then it's one that I don't really notice if there's digital people in there
I don't know that's invisible. I don't know that to be a fact
I was just guessing though, but but um the way that it kind of soars you over that wall
I think is real cool
And I do go oh man wouldn't be fun if they like the whole thing was a little more of a thrill which
There's a big what patent?
That was just filed for a more aggressive soren by disney
Oh, that's the same. I caught this in passing. What it what can it do now that it basically can just fuck you up
And also soar you okay soars you and fucks you up a little bit more
Wow, so I think you can shake you around like a bad parent of a newborn. Yes, that is very much
That's the way in the patent. It's the office as it listed
um
Imagine that you're a parent with no regard for your own. Yeah. Yeah, like
That's what this ride will do to you
And it's also you're an audio cue that says i'm mad at you and i'm not gonna tell you why
And then you launch like you can I think it here it goes up
It's like you start from this and then you can like you all I don't know how to even describe this
It's like you're in the same row, but then you can go up along the side essentially
Of this mechanism and I think it can like kind of drop you and put you up
And then do more things with the seats. So I think it has like range of motion on some level
There's some like extra level of yeah, and I think maybe
Perhaps it can tip the seats itself or something. I'm not sure
But fucked up soarin. Yeah. No, it looks like you can do that
You can like tip there's a mechanism to like change the direction your actual like seats are going
Versus the way it is now where it's just you're all connected to the same contraption that moves you up or pushes you down a little bit
There's just a very small range of movement. It seems to be we wish they had this now so you could kick tinker bell in the head
Get out of here you pissed. Yeah. Well, maybe that's what they're building the new version of it
They'll do what we're all thinking
But I I think this is the most effective use of the old technology making you feel like oh cool
I'm really flying over this thing. Yeah. Well, there's such like there's such levels
They really like guide you along the yeah dips of that particularly
hilly section of the wall
Um, yeah
No, very cool until the kite comes in and until the kite comes in. I agree. Yes
which then you
You it's a bad cgi kite that transports you to a wonder of the ancient world
You go to the great pyramids and it's like I don't need a hard transition. It's the great pyramids
Yeah, you know, yeah. Yeah. No, let's let's not let's not goof it up
Um, yeah, I don't have much to say about that section. It's great. It's great
I don't that's not on my short list of places to go
I don't know if i'll make it there and if I do I certainly won't be able to like
Look at individual bricks on the very top of they really get you right in there
Yeah, you feel like you could kick a brick you could it feels like you kick a brick off the top of the pyramids
Nail some idiot down at the bottom. It's it's yeah, it's really
It's one of those where if you're on the right side or the left side
It feels like the pyramid is warped a little bit. Sure
But it does. I don't know. I don't know. There's something very
What is a word like where you just imagine?
You know exactly what all the bricks feel like because it feels like you get so close tactile
I guess tactile is the right one. So it's just like you see like the dust you see the dust
Yeah, it's it's really cool. And yes, you imagine i'm holding one of these bricks
I know what it would be like to hold one of these bricks in my hand
And I don't think they're gonna let you do that if you go they don't let you know
That's let's get that info out there security is there by the pyramids because it doesn't appear to be a ton
Well, they let me take a brick
Yeah, are you judging the lack of security on this ride footage?
Do you think they deleted the security from is there a big like perimeter on the pyramids?
I think access is limited to the pyramid. How do they limit it?
Don't go in there. It's the pyramids
Armed guards, you think so?
I mean, I guess they would have to because it's probably not at this point the most sturdy structure there
But do you think there's like a big perimeter with guards and barbed wire worried about this the stability of the pyramid?
All right, I didn't mean to insult this stability
I'm just saying they're they're old buildings
I I mean, I look there's a political unrest would have more
There's a bigger chance the luxor falls over in the next 10 years than any of that
I'm just saying though that like it's this building material that could be within the week that could happen any moment
depending on they're putting up a new like frito ad or a
Dorito ad on it and all the glass breaks from the weight of the sign
And they got to close the whole place down forever
Do you think president lcc of egypt has been approached of like hey, would you do this?
Would you do this on the great pyramid of giza big to read it turn into a big
Dorito
Big branded opportunity for the nation. I don't know. I don't think they've approached him and I think that's the problem
You know would calm your political unrest
uh gaming arena
Sure, I would love to game inside the actual pyramids. Yeah, that would fucking rock. Yeah
Yeah, be so sick most of these places on this ride. You cannot bet inside of
That's yeah, that's a problem in terms of security. The pyramids are heavily guarded 24 seven. That makes sense
Yeah, yeah, did you think there was a there weren't security guards?
I would guess it's just interesting because i'm gonna I just had the thought where i'm like, I wonder what it looks like
I wonder what it looks like around there because it would be such a
Protected site, but yeah, is it like is it like getting into a city walk?
Orlando where there's a security barrier. You got to go through it
You got to prove that you're not like you don't have a bag that says
A brick bag that you're going to steal a bunch of bricks in
Like an empty bag that could carry the weight of it
I don't know. Yeah, especially made like something you carry wine bottles in one that like has the compartments
This is clearly for bricks. I think those bricks are pretty large
I'm sure they are you got to have a big bag for one of them
Like a sedan size bag are they said are all the bricks sedan size
I don't know about all of them, but I think there's some pretty you got one of those
Well, i'm not gonna i'm not look i'm not gonna try to take the ones at the bottom
Yeah, no, what are you fool foolish? You got to go one from the top
Yeah, obviously you have to climb all the way to the top before the hopefully on that day
Not so many armed guards, right?
And you get one of those mattress bags to put a mattress in when you're moving and you just get the king size
You put them in one of those now that I look at yeah
Per jason's point. Yes, look at the size of a person next to what we're referring to as bricks
Sedan size was right on the money
All right, all right a real big bag two of those king-size man
You might need to put one put the bag in another bag that thing's not gonna
Furl up too neatly small bricks in a pyramid. There's I do have this question
Yes, I feel like you might have some smalls at the top. I think it takes all kinds
I think you got a number of are there any small? This is the most
The one who actually thinks like are just cringing right now at this conversation
If you know anything about
Bavarian monarch and serbanic scott
Egyptologists are mad at mike. Well, I say bring it on they do not respect our bricks
They think that our bricks are small and not mighty
They can easily topple the president lcc's cabinet is furious at me for invoking his name during such tomfoolery
Yeah, then why'd you say it again? Yeah, we're gonna have to bleep all of those
I would you know, I would look maybe there'll be like a world i'll world travel one day and i'll go to the pyramids
Because i've always thought the pyramids were awesome. Like that's always yeah. I mean, it's obviously it's not
That's not an unusual thing to think
But still perhaps i'll go one day and try to steal a brick
Well, this is one of the you're very confident about certain abilities of yours in the checking arena
But you think you think you're getting out of there with a brick?
I guess maybe i'm not maybe i'm getting cocky. I guess I guess i'm probably not getting out of there with a brick
It seems like this
Yeah, okay. Oh wait, yeah now i'm
most of the blocks wage
I'm like let's let's be clear. I didn't think I was taking one from the bottom. I knew those were bigger
I didn't know they were all made up. I feel the same way though
And it's this is a hard thing to google quickly because the questions make me sound stupid
But I do wonder are some of the pyramid bricks also small it goes to a point. It's gotta be smaller
That's what I was saying imagine the effort to get the big the biggest ones up to the top
How small are the ones on the top?
Yeah, what's the smallest pyramid because it would have to at least be I don't know like
24 inches on the one on the top of my crate or it would be like four feet
How big does it have to be? Well now that I know that some of them are 25 tons all bets are off
They might not be anywhere near as small as you're describing. You need a whole brick. Can you just take a chip?
Can I just take it? Well, yeah, of course you could chip a piece off one of the bricks sure
Because they have to be falling off here and there but there's pyramids in mexico
Yes, that's true there start chipping. I'm sure they'll love that. I could just try to steal a piece of the luxor
To get my abilities uh heightened to get them just take a carrot top a banner
Yeah, well, I want a piece of the building take a body piece of the building
Oh, you want a piece of the brick that built the luxor?
Hmm, but you would you settle for here? Let's let's uh, let's compromise. Let's stennis compromise in the middle
Uh, just go cut off a piece of carrot tops hair
I mean that'd be cool to have right you might you know
He because he in a way built the building with his show and his comedy in his residency
And how cool would it be to have some of the famous carrot top of carrot top?
Yes, that's one of the modern seven wonders of the world
I would like that but I don't know that i'm ready for that type of heist
Did you mike did you stay there when we were in vegas did you stay I did stay there one night
Yes, so did you get to take the inclinator? We told this whole story. Yeah scary almost scariest
Things in my life going up that I just need a reminder. I just need a reminder because i'm like man
I almost died and jason didn't even care
Scary it was so fast and rattly and it lasted forever
And then the door didn't open right away and I was just like oh shit
Like i've never been and i've been in like those old elevators in an old building which where you got to pull the
Yeah, like like where you're just like this makes me very uncomfortable
That was like a walk in the park compared to this this felt like a runaway train a rickety runaway train
Yeah, right
You still do after that. Well, I would like to ride a fully functioning one
I don't know. I don't know if we can promise you that we can't guarantee that at the luxor
It seems like that is the last thing they can guarantee. Well when we go and we do the
universal horror permanent horror nights maze we'll all stay at the luxor and you'll do
You'll go up and then you will not we will not do such a thing
Well, i'm not saying not go i'm not i'm not getting in so i'm not getting no inclinator
In the last 10 years there's a there's a
Brand new hotel rooms that you can request I think and you think the inclinator is fresh
I think that is a normal elevator as it is a
That still doesn't make me want to stay at that shady weird hotel it is so weird
Yeah, new to a non-broken inclinator, huh? That fixes everything. Yeah, okay
Um, I okay that's that's giza. Wow boy have I never felt so stupid in front of the audience
I was with you. I thought some of the I thought some of them were small bricks
If you know if you can make us feel less stupid and tell us yes, there are some small bricks
Please do so because I feel humiliated now and mike really should so Taj Mahal
beautiful another
Beautiful majestic place. It's really nice. This is a nice. I know this feels I will complain and say it feels a little too
Digitally clean. Absolutely unless that truly is the natural beauty of the Taj Mahal
But I don't think so
Sydney feels a little like eerily too digital cleaned up and I think it really feels too. Is this all digital?
I don't want to say that. I just think it might not be but it feels like it could be
I think it's I think it's the base is real and then it's a lot of scrubbing. Yeah a lot of scrubby dub
Yeah, yeah, because that one feels definitely I still like the scene, but that's the one that most feels like cgi to me
Yeah, yeah, I really like that smell and I don't even I forgot the specifics with jasmine. Is that okay?
I think that's right. Great
This is what i'm saying. I think it's an unexpected smell and you kind of have to place it
Not that orange isn't unexpected. I just look
There's no reason to pit them against each other. The smell game on these attractions is wonderful
Yeah, they really did it jasmine is more subtle than the citrus scent. Yeah, which is pretty intense
Uh-huh on a bad way, but it's very forward and you know what let's talk
Music really quickly because it's the same base of music
Based on the jerry goldsmith score. He I believe had passed away by the time
The new score was being done
But it is certainly based on it's like different iterations of the theme
That he originally did and I like the different little movements of it. I like the
The more indian influenced music in this part
I really like the fiji the like the south seas
Uh, yeah, like they feel it's like it almost feels like entirely new music but still
Sort of tonally and it's not the hardest shift right but that's such a big part of something like that combo of
smell and music shift
I think I feel the most transported
In the fiji section of any of these that's maybe the second magic point
Yeah, you're like I can't help but be really immersed and we've done water scenes also because we talked in the last one about
How completely calm I feel in that dusk?
Scene the very the shimmering pink dusk sequence at the end of california. Yeah, so the water game
That you know, they got to step it up if they're gonna do a water sequence
In another soren and I think they they completely brought it. I don't know if it's better
But it's wonderful. It's it's a different type of water scene. And yeah water and greenery
You know, that's what I think that's just calming to most people like
Even the concept art or early pictures i've seen of the dream work stuff universal orlando. I'm like
Oh my god, there's so much greenery back there. That's so smart. That really looks like
It elevates the experience whether it's just play areas or not, you know
Yeah, I am. Oh god. I was just saying I am seeing enough people on claiming that it's all see that tajmal is all cgi
Really? Really? I don't know. There's not an official source here, but everyone seems to believe that
Well, look if there is a theme and we'll get back to this theme
Uh, you know, I I don't think we can automatically trust everything that we read about soren
On the internet. There's also some confusion some some element some elements of the pyramid
They some people feel those are the two most cgie
Really?
But don't you see at the end of the pyramids because I feel like you kind of see off into the city proper
I don't know how close it is to the pyramids. Yeah, that doesn't feel
Certainly that feels to me more like we're getting some reality here
But the tajmahal does feel like it could be completely cgi. Yeah, it's a little yeah a little little too much of a sheen
Um, I wait I skipped ahead monument valley or look where we go through
The one of the west and oh, yeah mitten buttes. They look like big mittens, I guess
In monument valley, arizona
This is another kind of disney nod because monument valley
And those rocks are the basis of the magic kingdom version of big thunder mountain
Yeah, so I like that they are nodding to the real world. It's like we're going backwards
We made fake versions of these things and now we go take you back to the real cars too
Monument valley. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'd have to think that um, there's a bird that wishes by and it's stupid but uh, uh, lao islands in fiji. Great
Uh that transitions you to igwazu falls. This is at the border of brazil and argentina
This is a place that I have been. Wow. Yeah early into
Aaron and I dating we took a
Really magical trip to I mean it was all great
Uh, uh all argentina, but in the dead center of it. We went to igwazu
Uh, this is one of the coolest things i've ever seen in my life and I I it makes me so happy to see it
On the ride and to get a little return and see it from a vantage point that you never could the vantage point that you get
Is unforgettable and it's just this long long series of catwalks
Uh, and we had like a real like, you know boat and atv adventure getting back
The whole thing was just such a big adventure and I remember that that night
We had just like a long long romantic dinner
Wine fueled talking about god knows what and at the end of it
All I know is that by the end of it we were both feeling this is the person I want to marry
Say it out loud then but we I mean there were hints of that before but we really knew it at igwazu
And you like someone over california better after this is in the second version of the ride
Yeah, well, I don't know. Uh, uh, oh my god
This makes me want to tip this over. Yeah, I suppose. Wow. Um, yeah, I don't know. I look uh, uh, you know
Incredible indelible memories from your own life and travel sure but that those
The balloon transition is so silly
Uh, I that's great. I didn't even realize that story
Yeah, god if you get that shit that is a that's a world travel this is high high recommended
This is one of the this scene is so cool
And this also and the way the way the movement of the vehicle sort of pulls you back in that moment
I don't even I can't even describe it just the way
In which oh like it simulate like suddenly you stop because you know
There's no this there hasn't really been a stop until exactly and they stop you right here and it really
Emphasizes what like the scope of what you're seeing and how cool it is and yeah music really hits there
Yeah, that is the and you know what it's kind of that is the most that they just show
natural beauty in the world
and uh
And you know what and you know, because there's beauty throughout this but some of them are man-made landmarks and this is really
Just like hey, this is god's god's creation speak for yes what god has done
Uh, yeah, this is awesome. I this
I've already said favorites. Maybe this is the best scene in all the sorens in a way. Wow. I don't know
I just it's so cool. I think
I mean I like I I can't apply my own feelings about this place to it because I mean
I think fiji's wonderful and I think the dusk. No, I know those are great, too
But there's something so yeah, everything we just said the movement
What about the scene in california where you're going over the 110 freeway and the footage is sped up by a thousand percent?
And if you look at the cars for too long you get a little bit dizzy
And it reminds you that the arena is now the crypto dot com
And how about bizarre that will always be unless they that changes unless that's ripped out in five months
That speed up I think was more novel in 2001 than 2024
Like we're too well because now they would plan on that and they'd shoot it in a way that accounted for that instead of
Right. Yeah, it's it's it's I don't know. It's sort of awkward and it's yeah processing it kind of I do like this better than that
Yes. Yeah. Yeah, no offense to the the 110 freeway
That's just all it's also like it's a stressful place to be the one living in los angeles. You try to avoid that freeway
Make you you try to make all of your decisions in your life to avoid that particular stretch of freeway
Yes, like you've fucked up if you're there
Hi, yeah go at downtown la is so much interesting like cool
history and architecture and
All of this awesome stuff. It is such a pain in the ass to get down there
truly if you want to cut
If you want like this some of the biggest driving tests of your life to cut across six lanes of traffic
on a freeway
To get to an exit once you get dumped off like the 101
The go to the 110 that's that's where you're going to find some challenges city all really breaks down
Yeah, it's the nerve center and the nerves are decaying
Yeah, i've done it enough now where I know the little there's a little tricks
But I don't have to get into it now or too deep into this episode
Yeah, can you instead describe the best way to get out of the burbank empire center?
I think that'd be much more of interest though. Haven't we done that already? I think I think the listeners go back towards the hotels
Yeah, okay. Oh great. Well, it's easy then it's quick and then there's lights. Yeah. Okay. Okay great
Yeah, we just I wanted to give some tip. Thank you. Yeah
bendy eiffel tower we talked about yeah, um, and here's where we start getting different between the
locations, yeah
because
disney
Cal disneyland california has the horrible wretched
Tinkerbell appearance the absolutely vile
appearance
Uh of the she devil herself
Um epcot you get
Okay. Wait a minute. Was it when it was the california ride film?
Did you just go to disneyland at the end of it and that was a little like
so then you get to go across the country and that's fun, but then
Seeing like the like the epcot of your dreams the purple pink
Perfect epcot now now preserved before they did all that stuff in communicor you get to like
When you're on this ride you get to go to epcot
circa
2006 I forget when they did it
Uh, but it's you know, I don't know. It's a beauty. It's a wonderful spaceship earth. That's all i'm saying
I yes, I
If I could choose I would always go to the epcot one
Just seeing epcot. Yeah at night
It's interesting the disney seat doesn't have a ton of nighttime lighting
I think because it's it's meant to
It looks tasteful, but it's not like super lit up like epcot is
Did you get that sense when you were there?
Like you mean just in general the lights at night the lights at night seemed to make sense for all the areas
But from above it wasn't that bright. Maybe you're going over the big body of water
So there's not that's true. Yeah, I mean, yeah, there was a lot of light. I don't know
My memory of it is that everything was perfect. So
Yes, yeah
No, the memory is that it's the greatest place i've ever been more than igwazu. Maybe
I mean aaron might agree with that. I I will just there is truly there is a feeling I get
Just hearing the word disney sea. It's just it's unreal which to that to that end we can go back to other ride films
But in disney sea
You know, this is one of the main things motivating doing a version that is not entirely set in california that they wanted to open it there
Uh soaring fantastic flight in asia. They stopped doing the n
Apostrophe, yeah, presumably is not something there is an equivalent of in any of those languages quite a translation
So soaring it is there
um, and if you can imagine
Uh disney sea did a version that's in the coolest looking building you've ever seen with the coolest architecture and set design you've ever seen
And incredible columns and every corner of the room you look at is really cool
And it makes you profoundly jealous that there is not really anything that good in the california parks at least and and and
You say like a full new story tied to a new character
I didn't say I didn't to see the society of explorers and adventurers. We get a new and now okay now here is where we do
Depart from our beloved patrick flight attendant. Yeah, who by the way since the last episode returned to the role did a little video
Uh at the california adventure soaring. It's nice to see him again. Nice to hear him saying all the stuff again and talking about the strap
um, so that was cool, however
They just I mean
I like soaring i'll always like soaring. It doesn't matter but soaring is a little bit of an industrial ride
You know, uh, you're kind of in a factory
You're sort of looking at walls
And there is a man who could be in a pre-flight a real pre-flight video telling you real pre-flight information here
We are transported to a wondrous world
or a
inventor
Uh, uh, like a woman from the past passionate about flight a dreamer
Weaves tales of fantastical flying machines and doodads and she's got a magical bird with her
And there's magic tricks in the pre-show. God damn it. I want this one. It's so good. I
She's got a paint. Yeah
She comes to life in a painting and there are all these like shadows on the wall in the pre-show that imagine in
I mean it reads in a video anyway, but can you imagine in person how?
Great that I bet that effect is like, oh my god, that's a screen
I'm sure you don't know until that second
Well in the bird is shadow and then it flies into the painting and it's an actual
Falcon and then goes back in goes back to shadow. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's incredible. It's so great
It's it's a real with little magic tricks
And that the pre-show is unbelievable and then kind of tops the other iterations pre-shows were in the territory of their tower of terror
Yes, yeah, we have it's so good
Why can't I not just say all this and say and that's neat
Why am I saying it with the tone of like god damn it? Ah, they got jealousy. Yes, my anger is but maybe
Unmaskable, it's just there. I want to be able to go on this version more often. Maybe one day
Camellia falco will be in that sea
Television show if it ever gets made. Yeah, and she'll be able to turn to the camera and go, uh, is that even a thing?
She'll be able to get the bird. That's like a consolation prize
Yeah, she'll be able like the bird will land on her hand and she'll go. Oh that just happened
That's with access to all of our flying machines and time travel possibilities
We must go and harvest the best quips from all areas of time
And all of the best quips come from the year
2014 and beyond
Let's scour the commercials of 2014 the advertisements
to find
My first it's like let's scour the advertisements of 2019 to see what the movies and films of 2013 were doing
My whirly gigs and birds don't just fly now they fly always
It's they fly now. Yeah, they fly of course
Uh, I it's so cool
I almost want to do I I don't want to do episodes on any of this stuff because I want to go but also
Yeah, I don't know you want to go on it first
Well, shanghai has a different story, too
You got a tribe that graces you with the power of flight. Well, we gotta do so you meet another magical woman
You meet a shapeshifter
It's a whole other like and she turns into a bunch of stuff
And she she turns into an eagle and a frog and a hummingbird
Because they have to make it that's the first soren in a castle park
They had to make it fantastical enough to fit in a place. That's all
World of wonder they couldn't just do a hanger and it seems like they did a really great job
You would give up patrick for this
For camellia. Yes, the other one seems neat. Um
You have to have it both coasts I have to yes, well look I think my ideal version would be that it's patrick and uh
Uh california in california forever
But you know, well it wouldn't make any sense and it already doesn't make a lot of sense in the land
Let's be honest. I don't think that suddenly like, you know, uh, you know, uh, yeah right next to that like
Unpleasant restaurant to be in that you gotta then then you go meet camellia falco
Um, so I don't know. I don't know they can stay what they are. I just just build this one, too
That's what I want two sorens
They gotta build that disneyland forward area. Just give me another soren. Give me the camellia falco one. It'll be fine
Got it. It's worth worth doubling up. Nice
Um, so that's what what have we missed there? Um you oh wait now tokyo
Wait a minute
In which oh, oh they replace paris with uh, just a view of tokyo at night
They don't do paris and there and the falcon appears several times at the beginning in the end. So you have magical character like
Characters running throughout yours. That's what you're saying. You want it at the beginning and end
There you go, but isn't it like even if you knew tinkerbell was coming then then she showed up at the end
You just say oh tinkerbell again. Shanghai also would be confused
Shanghai doesn't fly over the park. It flies over the
City scape at night. Yes of shanghai and you go right past the shanghai world financial center
The world's tallest building with a hole
It is there you go. I was I did have to rewind once or twice and go like does that building with giant hole on top
Got a big hole in it, but it's not a problem
It was it was meant to have one. I love the giant buildings with the hole in top or in the middle
It's a very cool building. It's cool
um, well, I think this loops us back around to the original point and uh,
Let me just kind of reset the stage a little bit of how we
We came to this point. So we did an episode about soaring over california back in september
and you know when you think of
Funny trivia about this ride one of the things you definitely think of is this thing of michael eisner
Being the golfer who hits the golf ball that flies at you in the palm spring sequence
Of that ride and I went into the episode not with any intention to like it had never occurred to me
To like that there could be anything up with that fact
I just I was like I want more I want more eisner as always
and I want like
Photos of him doing it. I want him sizing up golf clubs. I want video of him getting ready
I want the movie surfers talking to him on the set of so we're here on the set of soren
With disney's big cheese michael eisner
Um, so you're playing the golfer today. Tell me about that
Um, you know, I just I wanted more to bring to the table
But what I started finding was kind of distressing to me and i've gotten kind of a preview of this recently with this other
Issue that had come up that's still kind of unsolved of does space mountain have fans that simulate the speed of the ride
And I so i'd gotten a little practice with that and you know, we've been doing this show for a long time now
We get our sources from you know, you know, we we source information from like particular
Sources that we that we trust, you know people like jim hill theme park historian jim hill
That's a that's a place where we turn a lot
But with as with the fans with this issue, I was just not finding
Yeah
any sources that I try I was finding a lot of things that i'd put in the category of
That it's a really poorly designed website with lots of ads that look like the way ads
Started looking 12 years ago. Uh, and there are and it's and they'll be called like, uh, you know
dis bloggy mommies
It's and you're getting four of those ads at once
Yeah, yeah, yes, you know, I have to clear out all of the ads from all directions of the browser
Yeah, yeah
Yes
No
The things about to explode so that I can even clear them away to see the name dis bloggy mommies
It's buggy mommies dot mouse. That's the kind of thing that i'm looking at and i'm like
I don't know
I'm just not seeing enough of the kinds of sources that I think are credible and there might be i'm just not seeing them there
And I want to know definitively
And I and I want to encourage these places to not be in the
To be like jim hill and not like dis bloggy mommies. Let's make sure we know these things
Let's back them up with with photographic evidence
um, so
I decided to turn to a source that we all trust and that is jim hill people might have seen this
Uh online not long after
Our episode came out. I said, uh, let's get down to business jim hill. Do you
Believe or can you back up that michael eisner is the golfer on sorum?
And he presented a couple of thoughts that were sort of in my avenue of not necessarily
Uh believing it. Here's here's the thing that he said. Well, first of all, uh,
Somebody said at bf se sq said I hope my heart doesn't get broken
I've always believed this
And uh, that brings me to to a point because I asked the audience
What do we think soren golfer is eisner not eisner?
60 of our audience said they believe this is wow michael eisner
Where do you guys put it at that? I don't know. Where have you landed in your your personal belief system in this area?
I I
I don't think it's him. I think you did a good job
You've landed it. Yeah, I did not get anywhere definitive. No, I know now we're getting we're getting closer to the
Potential listening to the episode. I went. Oh, that's probably not I would love to be wrong
Uh-huh. I would I don't I would love to be wrong
I mean what a victory it would be for all of us in a couple minutes if that's where this went
Maybe it's where it's going jason
I would love to believe it's eisner
But I think we've encountered so many things of conventional wisdom
Just being like disney storytelling k-fabe
Oh sure, oh isn't that interesting that's so perfect and it's like yeah, it's too perfect
Yeah, it's not a little too perfect. Yes
So yeah, I asked audience and 60 percent of them believe it's eisner now
I'm gonna solve a mystery of something that might have seemed out of nowhere that I tweeted a couple days ago
I asked the podcast the right audience on twitter
Uh, this is gonna seem heavy and out of nowhere, but it's information we need for a future episode here goes
Do you believe in god? I was wondering what this was. I didn't tell you guys what it was about
every every now and then like like
Sometimes I just plum forgot like the inclinator or like the fake soren discussions
but I was like
Why did we reading about soren around the world and i'm like
We're not doing a god episode
I've heard no people are wondering does this mean we're going back to to the arc encounter or something?
No, no, no, I wanted to compare contrast the eisner believe versus the belief in god
Listener amount of listeners who believe in god
definitively
There's no way this is not accurate
According to the online poll 31 percent. Wow 31 percent of podcast the ride listeners believe in god
60 believe that michael eisner is the golfer in soren. That is the kind of is that is that double that is double?
Yeah, yeah, uh that that is that is what we are
Tampering with here. This is a deep more deeply held belief
Yeah, yeah
Some of the most deeply held beliefs that have ever existed on the globe
That is what we are starting to poke at to go back to talking about aliens and uap and all this stuff
some people feel that
This is information as far as aliens concerned or interdimensional travelers that should not be revealed to the public because what it will do
To them would be so catastrophic. It would affect their belief system
It would completely turn people's brains upside down
So the big argument that people say the people in the whatever the secret government make is we cannot do this
This is too important. We have to keep it quiet. We cannot tell people what's actually going on
so i'm not saying you should follow this as well when it comes to this eisner reveal, but
That's what some people believe maybe as far as the actual disclosure of aliens or interdimensional travelers
That's as silly now. Let's just all take a quick peek inside this arc that i've been sitting next to this whole show
Uh, I don't know you you raise an interesting point michael and now that you've said it
You know what you survive podcast the ride. That's the end of this episode. This will never be discussed. All right
Oh, okay. I feel good about that. No, no, we got it
We gotta turn everybody's brains upside down or not or we confirm right or what everybody and and me the silly the silly skeptic
Is proven wrong, but I start to get a little bit of fuel here because jim hill's backing me up a little bit
This person says I hope my heart doesn't get broken
He says what concerns me about this story is well, have you ever seen a photo of michael eisner playing golf?
I mean the guy's an obvious sports enthusiast
But when I just googled michael eisner and golf not a single image of disney's former ceo holding a club
Came up now. We kind of discussed this in the episode
This is one of my things when I went fishing in the supposed camp interview with larry king
I didn't find that instead. I found him talking to charlie rose and saying that he doesn't even like golf and then
Uh, madame jumbo jumps in there and the actual character from tumbo jumps into the replies
And finds this from disney war eisner had neither the time nor patience for golf
Though he'd occasionally played with his father and had a decent swing six months after joining bel-air
He had yet to sit foot on the course
Joins a country club because that's what you do when you're a ceo, right?
But never put a spiky golf shoe into the grass
Um, so I don't know. I'm jim is adding to it a little bit
But still it does not get definitive here is the biggest thing that jim hill does
Uh in this conversation he uh brings up
Uh, he okay quote jim hill. Thank you jim
Okay, I just pulled out the media source book
I was handed by the disneyland resorts pr team when I attended the grand opening of dca back in february of 2001
First of all jealous of that would love to see that grand opening. Yeah, jim the places you've been grander than igua zoo
And this book says that rick rothchild directed the original iteration of soren. Let me reach out to him and see
Uh rick rothchild is a name. I was familiar with
Maybe we even brought it up in regards to soren before
Uh, this is an imagineering legend. Here are some of the things he was part of american adventure alien encounter
Star tours the adventures continue he led the team that came up with the idea for captain
io the backstory of captain io where they had to think of three ideas to present to michael jackson and george lucas
And one of them was a peter pan thing and thank fucking christ that one didn't get picked
Uh, but instead they landed on one that at the time they were calling the intergalactic music man
And michael and george were like that one for sure
and rick rothchild made that happen led to that happening and then
Uh most pertinent to us is that he directed the soren ride film, which I did not realize until jim brought this up
so now we've got
A pretty particular source that we can start working with here and I await
Jim reaching out to rick to come up with this answer. This does not happen and I don't hold this against jim
Uh a busy man sure, uh as am I
Frankly, but also I had to fucking know this this has been needed. This has been eating me up
Yeah, you guys said let's do soren like I do not want to do that soren too until we know this for sure
So I realized I had to make the connection but rick is not on a lot of the social media
I had to get on what I would call a not primary piece of social media
In order to reach out to imaginary legend rick rothchild
And right as we were recording an episode about phantasmic a couple of weeks ago
Wow, I opened a tab and like we were I was probably in the middle of a sentence and I just happened upon my email
And I saw you have received a written message from rick rothchild and I had to keep talking as if
That had not happened and like I wasn't very excited so professional. Uh, yes that shows you the kind of things, you know
It's like talking through an earthquake like not even letting it get to you
Uh, who knows the allure of tabs like even in the midst of a wonderful recording session
Oh, you try to not get a new tab
Yes, I know dazzling new information could be behind any turn any turn or uh, you know, uh, uh more
Deals for toys and cereal and stuff. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know how you turn off the notifications while we're doing this frankly
I've i've only bought a thing maybe once or twice
While doing the podcast you have purchased items once or twice. Oh, I wish I knew what they were
Yeah, I have not for a long time. Okay. Oh, that's good. You've been in the game
You know, I've been in zoom era. Look everybody got bored in zoom certainly in zoom era. Yeah, but anyway
Uh, yes mid record. I discovered that I had gotten the answer from
Great imagineer rick rothchild. He was there. We finally have an in-person source
Are we ready?
to open
the arc
And discover the answer. Oh my god the official answer
This is where I had a feeling it was going to either you got the call sheet or you talked to a crew member
Yes, you know what and I was pursuing
Another lead and I want to shout out the people who were who were helping me with the lead
Uh, but I uh, let me let me do this one first the big one my correspondence with brick rothchild. Okay
Uh, so, you know, he he said
Thanks for the note. Appreciate it complemented on some things and then we got into the business. Here we go
the answer is
That it is
a myth only wow
Wow, there it is. There it is the full message
Michael was not one of the golfers in the sequence we shot at the pga west golf course in palm desert
What michael did contribute was the additional financing to add a few final cg effects after screening my initial cut of the film
one of which was the golf ball that comes roaring up at us from the golfer who's teed off and
You of course know that when we added the golf ball, I asked for the mickey to be placed on it
It was our not so subtle mick hidden mickey in the film. Thank you for your nice comments
We talked a little more he gave me permission to read that on the show. Thank you rick
There you have it. Wow, wait till now michael eisner is not the golfer but in spirit
Well, this is the I know and as if people are feeling
Crushed by this news as if crushed by one of the now we know very heavy bricks from the pyramids of giza
Though I don't think there's some that aren't so heavy. Uh, but
Um, if if that info is depressing, uh, or shatters your your dreams as people have said untrue. I think jason is right
uh, I think that
By his approving that shot and making the ball fly at the camera
Isn't that in some way him?
Hitting the golf ball there would have been no golf ball without michael eisner giving the corporate. Okay and allowing for that
Uh that effect to be added so in a way
Isn't he the golfer and soren?
The answer is no, but it sounded like a nice thing to say
I thought I would cheer people up if I said something like that
Like lisa giving the book report about springfield and looking out and seeing everyone's faces. Well, look jason
That's something that you said
Uh online when I was in pursuit of this information you said this is like
the classic simpsons episode, uh lisa the iconoclast in which she learns that
Jebediah springfield the namesake of the town the founder of the town
Uh was in fact a murderous pirate and that everyone's myths about him were false and she goes to interrupt
the the big celebration of him
Where they they affirm that a noble spirit and biggins the smallest man and she has to get this information out
And when the moment comes she can't bring herself to do it because the myths about jebediah have meaning too
And that's why I would like to say
Michael eisner was
Great. I've been doing some research and michael eisner was
great
I just I just wanted to say that I just wanted to get that off the
I think look
There should there should have been a line in john lennon's imagine
Like what he's saying imagine there's no religion, you know, everybody would be living in peace today
Well, maybe this is a similar situation
Imagine people don't have the misconception that michael eisner hit the golf ball
Like what would the world be like today? They'd be all living. Maybe it's actually something that's bad
Maybe it's a belief that's actually holding humanity back and what you've done now is free everyone
From it. I hope so. You are a uap coming coming back
And opening our minds. I don't know what that is. But yes, isn't that mike's?
That's well, that's the term for like a ufo now. Oh, okay. All right. Well, i'm not i'm not i'm no mike on this point
I don't know. So
so maybe what you've done now is you've
opened the eyes of the world
And perhaps society will be better from now on
I'd like to think so i'm trying to figure out how I mean, I think that you know, while we don't know his name
We now are not ascribing false qualities to michael eisner and taking away the excellent swing work of a great
day player actor
Right who was we were not nearly close enough to see the face of and I wish that I could tribute that person
Better, but if that person's out there and that's that's your father or someone who matters to you
Then now we can make sure that he gets his due
I mean not in the way not by name or anything
But just think there is an actor out there who was never given the proper credit
Well, then now we can do it
You know
We got to shine more light on the day players of the world and less on the ceos even the ones who we love
I completely agree with you
Um, and there's two things. Yeah, like we at the very least
I would like to know the name of the actor who swung the golf ball. Yeah, number two
I want to find out who created this rumor
Yeah, and I want to get revenge
Yeah for giving us this false hope of this fun thing
Yeah
That we've all been you know, because yeah think about that before you get mad at me before the torches come for me
Really it should be mad at whoever lied about exactly and everybody who is complicit in that game of telephone
That's been going since the mid 2000s. I really do wonder where did this come from?
exactly was it a conflation of
Did some did somebody some was it a game of telephone of the story that rick told me right where?
That was a like special little touch that michael eisner made possible
And then a couple steps later it becomes that he is the one hitting the golf very possible
Is it just like one of the like the guides the disneyland guides or something?
Made it up like I don't like it could be anything. Mm-hmm
I hope that person was was rooted out for their lies. Yeah, because you know look
It seemed like a more innocent time in the early 2000s
But now that we live in the era of fake news and falsehoods, right?
And this was you know, this is gonna have a big impact on our upcoming election if we don't start, you know rooting out
Lies and untruths, you know, these these things happened, you know
September 11th happened a guy who isn't michael eisner hitting a golf ball happened. That's right
Not everything is subjective
I agree and I think
jim
Hill we call on, you know
to find the offender
And to seek the ultimate
Mike is waving around that bowie knife. He usually has when recording
Jim, you know what to do
When you find out this person who created this vile rumor. Yeah initiate operation four
Which is where a blunt object is fired from a large distance at the head of a liar
Well, I call it operation. Uh, that's it exactly
He knows what i'm talking about
I mean whoever did this undermines the entire thing, you know, we these stories, you know
Is that not what this sure this podcast became about uh, uh rants and jokes and sidetracks
But did it not start as a place for us to tell the facts that we know
That we've only told to our significant others who we are bruising in the seats next to us as we pound into their legs
Don't you know that's interesting?
We decided to take that and try to get an audience who wanted to hear it, right?
That's what this whole thing was originally based in is telling these sharing the uh, you know
passing along the oral history of these same three stories that are told about every ride and to learn that one of them was
Fake was completely fake for all this time the whole to quote sally field and mrs
Doubtfire the whole time the whole time the whole time
That's how I feel. I'm sally filled it up
And uh, and that's and I agree so before you get mad at me
We need to because this this person this rat who started this wrong story
Yeah, threatens to undermine the whole thing now. It's like we can't trust the you know
I mean, thank god some that the breck eisner stories
Uh, uh come from tony himself a source that we trust because otherwise I say if we if we can't
Pin these stories to a specific person who's who who we love and we're true
We trust over many decades then we got to question everything. How high up do you think?
Do you think josh demaro knows that it's not eisner?
Do you think he knows?
Hmm. Do you think he's I mean he's heard it at the very least
Do you think why why do you bring up him?
I just wonder like do people in the company actually believe this is because this rumor again felt like fact
Of all the different things we ever talk about this one felt like the most fact it had never occurred to me before
The episode I didn't I didn't expect to be in to end up on this journey
I didn't expect to ultimately be the whistleblower on this. Yeah, although now that I am listeners
Please go update all pertinent wikipedia's and source me and podcast the ride appreciate it. Thank you
Yeah, and for now just say
whoever made the lie
We've got top men looking into it the top man man
jim hill jim hill
Uh disney disney blogger slash assassin
Jim has that on his business card, I assume
Yeah
That's right, that's all right. That's where he's been making his money all these years. Yeah, he uses like assassin work. He uses one of us
uh
galaxy's edge of lightsabers
Or well and he has the john wick. He has the cool the gold coins. He also has gold coins. It will give you
Uh one hotel room or one assassination, you know, if you're if you're backs up against the wall
You could turn anything into a weapon. Um, yeah
We got we got to get him on it and and you know
I I hope that this information is is more interesting than it is disheartening
I hope that I haven't shattered anybody's uh vision of anything here
But one thing I just want to say for all the talk about like theme park journalism
I feel like I actually went did it
We can actually be a source on this thing, yeah, yeah, uh, you know people might be angry at us, but uh, I don't know
Uh this yeah, we we actually maybe for the first time
Yeah, we revealed something that is actually our that's really the victory of it here the things that we
uh
Squeeze people's legs to make sure they know about finally one of them comes from us
Right. Did you know that that golfer is not disney ceo michael eisner?
It's some guy whose name we don't know. Oh what I what are you telling me this? It seems like I need more context
No, actually I mostly yes, I would believe that most people on screen in a movie are like an actor or something
Yeah, well him too. Why would it be him? I don't know because for decades people said otherwise, but in fact
Okay, uh, it's it's like a within theme park where it doesn't this doesn't matter to almost anybody
But it's like proving that the thing about like the munchkin hanging themselves in the wizard, right?
Right, that's not true
It's like one of the like it's like we found one of these long held things and actually we're we're able to turn it over
And I apologize. I'm gonna try to do this
Really quickly because I when when all was seeming lost on this and I was seeing nothing but dis bloggy mommies saying no
It's him. It was people even told me that i've got definitive proof that it is it is him really and then didn't really
Follow up with it. Uh, um, so let me please credit call out the people who said because I I was googling it and
somebody said contrary to popular belief the golfer is not michael eisner and
I reached out to this person and uh, let me see
David kintonia is the uh, who is on
Instagram and does a lot of great parks posting actually. Let me try to find their handle
Apologize for the cut any of this if it's clunky qs underscore trips people might be following david already great
Disney photos and factoids and info
And when I reached out
He said hey, i'm a fan of the show
And I know this because I know somebody who works at the parks and has access to imaginary archives
And they were on the case about maybe I was wondering if this is gonna lead to like finding the call sheet or something
right, uh, um, so that was like
Uh on the way, uh didn't end it but but I think they they would have been the source on this
So I I did have a a backup and somebody and david. Thank you for uh for giving me hope
Uh when I was feeling insane about it, but now we all know and not only that I reached out to david
And he said, uh, you know what? I really love the show and also you're right about that thing about cues
Uh, uh, every cue is ultimately skippable
So i'm feeling fucking great at this point. Let's bring him on bring him on bring him on the show
You come in here and you stand in your position. I'm gonna send jim hill after him
Yeah
So I think I think that's that do you guys do we do we feel okay?
Are we I mean I ask that to the listeners too
Or do we feel now that we've shattered something bigger than belief in god the only reason I feel okay is that I know
That sometime hopefully fingers crossed this year. The three of us will have to separately read michael eisner's camp
Yeah, and then do an episode so I feel like I have fun eisner things to look forward to what if we get into that?
Like one of us reads the abridged version and we're like, okay
Well interesting heartwarming tales the man is fascinating and greaves a great story
And then one of us reads the unabridged and it's like he says it's him
The proof has been in camp this whole time
If you ever see anybody out there if you ever see if that rat rick rothschild ever says it's not me
I
Wouldn't recorded right and please do not ever abridge this publishers of camp do not over my dead body
Do you take this out of the well?
I um, you know talk about doing things while recording
I borrowed both the ebook and the audiobook while we were you had to you had to get ahead of the line. I
Oh, yeah
Especially when this episode comes out. It's gonna be a big rush. Yes in all in all library digital systems across america. Yeah
Has there any guys did they try to adapt camp into any sort of show?
Young michael or do you think that's what the movie camp? I don't think it was the same
I don't know. I don't think that's what that was but i'm just saying michael has company now. They make cartoons and stuff
What's the why not?
Yeah, all right. All right camp. Let's let's party any way you want it. That's the way you need it
And then yeah, he then he's like and he's making out with a couple babes sure
Yeah, and that's the and that's the story of how I saved summer
summer camp island
Uh, the cartoon network show is not based on michael eiser's book. I feel as far as I know
You know
But even but you know the things we thought were definitive now
Who knows if any of them maybe that whole thing has been ripping off stories from camp this entire time
Believe nothing. I dropped a coffee mug in the bottom says actually it is the basis for summer camp
How else are we supposed to think of a bunch of camp stories make them up?
No, we had to steal them from michael eisner's book
Um, well there you have it. I did it. You did it within an inch. Give him a round of applause
Thanks
I it really it it overtook me. Uh, you know, I did I make it to uh, you know yarn all over my apartment
Not quite. Yeah, but I was going to if some of these things didn't come through sure
So I thank rick rothschild for coming through and for all the amazing stuff he did that shaped our childhoods indelibly and for soren
Camp is to come for now. You survived podcast the ride
For three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our vip tier club
Three you will find all of that at patreon.com
Podcast the ride as if I wasn't feeling good enough. Uh this week if you missed it live
Uh the netflix show everybody's in la john malaney's show aired all throughout this week
And I don't actually know if my segments have aired but at least one of them has
If you go and find a segment about uh, terrence howard's math theories, that is one of the pieces
Oh great. Well, then you'll like this one
Uh, oh when you make it to it an honor to do it a full credit writing and amazing jokes to this great
Uh writer and stand-up langston kermann, uh honored to work with him and he's great in the piece too
The other one I don't know if I can say but our buddy ryan perez is in it
I'm really really proud of it one of the coolest things i've ever gone to do
Uh, so check that out on netflix us at patreon.com slash podcast the ride and if this closes out
Kind of the soren conversation proper. I think that we have to end it the way soren ends in a way
That's very similar to the way that most uh airplane, uh commercial airplane flights end which is all right
you may now
Uh remove your safety restraint clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack clack. You know what I mean, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah the unbelievable cacophony one at once. Yeah
You are now allowed to clack clack clack clack. Get me out the fuck out of here
Boy, that was a fun ride. Yeah, but I want fucking out now clack clack clack clack clack clack clack
forever
Dog
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson jason sheridan scott gerdner
Brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on facebook