Oh yeah, alright.
Take it easy, baby.
Take it last all night.
We ate at American Girl for club three here on podcast, the ride where, look, we don't
really introduce ourselves all the time because you know who we are, but I do notice that
a special friend has just appeared while I was doing the intro with Mike Carlson.
I'll introduce you because of your, you can now introduce your friend.
Sharing the mic with me is Kirsten.
Kirsten is here, an American Girl doll who belongs to my sister and is definitely like
30.
She's, her character's age is over 100, but she's at least 30 years old as far as her
plastic and her whatever sweater and everything else.
Okay, well it's, you know, 30, I don't know how much that does for us.
That's a little young, honestly, which makes us not that interested here on podcast the
ride.
But over 100, now that's the age range that we like.
That's what we like.
Yeah.
So wow, Kirsten, it's a pleasure to see you again, I say again because we spent a little
time together.
Right.
Well, she's, hi, Scott.
Hey, good to see you.
Gosh, you winked a little bit while you waved.
My eyes closed and opened too.
Hi, Jason.
Hi, Kirsten.
Nice to see you out of the iron lung that you live in.
Yeah.
It was $200 in 1993 for Mike's mom to buy the iron lung.
For the lung accessory.
The accessory that we needed to buy to make a lung.
But you had to.
How do you, we don't want to be around without an iron lung.
You absolutely need your primary accessories.
That and tissues with blood in them.
Yeah.
There was a lot of historically accurate accessories that added up to over the thousand dollars.
An iron lung, if you would plug it in and it would suck power from the Carlson house,
half of the neighborhood would brown out.
It actually drains.
That's good because you want, you know, you're not doing the American girl experience unless
you're overspending.
Right.
Oh, yes.
And if something is not, if something is battery powered or doesn't take any power at all,
then it's not being, it's not a suck on your own power bills, which is what really helps
you increase those numbers of how much you spent on this set of toys.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Those were about what I expected when I looked at the online store.
But yeah, the accessories really add up.
It's really where they get you.
And there's one that I'll, that I'll shout out in particular is actually kind of a part
of the assignment.
Um, but Kirsten, I'm glad you're here.
I'm glad you you'll be chiming in.
It seems like you're in there.
Uh oh.
I'm okay.
Oh, geez.
Doctor says I don't have too much longer, but I'm okay.
Kirsten.
I think she's Swedish.
She should be Swedish.
Kirsten.
Yeah, yeah.
I should have been doing a Swedish voice.
I'm sorry.
It's not too late to be Swedish, Kirsten.
Kirsten.
Doctor says I don't.
Right?
That's it.
A doctor says I don't have long.
Well, you were a little less annoying before.
Yeah.
You don't have to be.
You know what?
I'm glad you Americanized.
You don't need to be Swedish.
That character.
There's more longevity to that impression, perhaps, on a podcast than the Yakov, Yakov
Shmirnov voice I was just doing.
Yakov Shmirnov, famously from Sweden.
From Sweden, yeah, yeah.
No, it's my fault for not having the accent.
Kirsten has a consumption cough, but Mike and I are both getting over, Mike had an awful
cold and I had a terrible sinus infection.
I think maybe I had your sinus infection.
It is possible.
It could have been either of us gave it to either of us.
I'm not saying you gave it to me.
I'm saying I could have given it to you.
I don't know.
We don't know.
I unfortunately missed this ad and you know I must have been sick if I was missing out
on a chance to have chocolate mousse because I love chocolate mousse.
There's no way you can get that other than going to Century City, California.
Well, you'd be surprised.
It's hard to find, I think, analogies.
Do you have trouble finding it?
Do you have trouble finding chocolate mousse?
Yeah, I think Trader Joe's are good.
I think you can find it.
I guess so.
It seems like you're skeptical about that, though.
So many places just have ganache or different preparations that aren't just like-
There is zero percent chance that there is not, within a mile of where you live, available
chocolate mousse.
I'm positive.
Of course.
Mousse is not some rarity, some rare.
Maybe in Kirsten's time it was, but-
Yes, I can't find chocolate mousse to save my life.
My father needs it for his medicine.
I know that was just a turn of phrase, but just so you're clear, I don't think chocolate
mousse is going to be the thing to save your life.
Oh, that's what my father says.
My father says it's his medicine.
Oh, sorry.
Well, you know what?
Very well.
Actually, you know what?
If that's what he says, they need all the chocolate mousse you want.
I'm sure it's going to help you with whatever it is you're dealing with, and I'm so sorry.
Just one prayer to God and a chocolate mousse and he'll be all right.
He'll survive through the winter.
That's what father says.
Now I'm questioning everything.
Maybe a little more, maybe just double the mousse intake, and I'm sure he's going to
be okay.
Yes.
Yes, he will be fine.
Let me, before we get too far, let me address some Club 3 business.
We are talking about American Girl Cafe here.
The runner-up was a squeaker.
This was really, really close.
Number three, revolving restaurant roundup.
And only in a poll where there's something else that has my permanent allegiance, only
in this case would I not be really vying for revolving restaurant roundup, which presumably
would just be like we pick as many revolving restaurants to talk about all over this great
nation and world.
I love revolving restaurants.
This sounds great.
We'll revisit this one down the road, I think.
Sure, yeah.
So that's great.
Hell of a poll.
I thought all of these were really great.
But the runner-up, which moves to next month, the Beach Boys episodes of Full House.
Now you might be thinking Scott's going to make a pitch here to pick that next month
for him, to make that a choice for Scott.
And I say don't do it for me, do it for you, do it for yourselves.
Speaking for myself, I know I'm going to knock that out of the park.
I'm going to make that the best damn episode you ever heard.
And I don't want to put that on you guys too, but I would like to think that the summer
fun will be infectious.
You'll have your toes tapped into the California beat.
You're lobbying pretty hard and you're making it very attractive.
But that's part of this.
That's part of the process.
I can't make anything.
I can't make Madam and Wailin' Flowers as attractive as that, I don't think.
You didn't in round one.
Certainly there are vocal folks out there who have been pushing for Madam.
But I don't know if it's a birthday shot, I don't know if we can get it into a poll
again.
Again, it was a last place in a poll of all last places.
I wasn't going to do this.
Mike, for God's sake, what is it?
Do I need to put a timer on this?
Okay, put a timer on me at like two minutes.
Two minutes.
No way.
You're getting a minute, a minute 45 at least.
Okay, I can do it then.
Okay, great.
All right, here we go.
A video went viral online of Coldplay playing of a man charging the stage.
I don't know if you two have seen this.
No.
Okay, a man falls off the stage, Chris Martin stops the performance.
This man was protesting something, I'm not sure.
What caught my eye and a friend of mine's eye is that there is a puppet on stage with
Chris Martin during this performance.
He looked into this.
Coldplay has a whole puppet band as of a couple years ago called the Weirdos with original
characters.
They're Henson created puppets.
Here's a picture of them right now.
They also have their own characters that sing songs on like not maybe the one of the albums
in the last so many years.
If you buy a new Coldplay album, you get some fucking puppet band on there.
And I think one of this, I listen to one of the songs.
What happened to Coldplay?
I listen to one of the songs and I know I have time running out.
One of the songs sounds just like Chris Martin is doing the Prince Camille trick and just
pitching his voice up and he's like playing the main weirdo character and I believe that's
the character that was in the video on the concert.
I'll say this, maybe my rap on Coldplay, if you can believe it, if you can believe that
someone has this opinion.
The Coldplay is a tad boring.
What you're describing, while it sounds abhorrent to me, is not boring.
Right.
Do you want me to read the members of the band real quick?
You have 30 seconds.
Angel Moon, Donk, Sparkman, The Wizard, and Bruce Cake Mix is their manager.
Well, now you have my attention.
Admittedly, you had my attention at Donk.
So I believe they're legit Henson puppets.
I haven't fully investigated who's singing what on which album and which character is
doing what.
But if the audience wants, we can put the weirdos in play in Club 3.
I'm going to be so fucking pissed if this beats the Beach Boys.
So I hate to add-
And what are they, the Coldplay weirdos?
If you were going to submit it and someone has to submit it by parliamentary procedure.
Yeah, let's say yeah, Coldplay dash the weirdos.
Again, if that sounds attractive to you, I can't promise that there's a ton of content
there.
We will make the content regardless of what actually exists.
As opposed to not to make this a versus situation, this will be the most robust report you've
ever heard from me.
You're getting journalism, you're getting a true thorough breakdown.
So I can promise materials and wide breadth.
But again, not to, but maybe we are in a little dog fight here.
I guess we are.
What I can promise is if there's not a ton of content here with the weirdos, I will go
through Coldplay's X and Y and explain to you the songs on that album that I like and
why.
Jesus, oh God.
Is that the one with the music video with the, is it monkeys or crabs?
Oh, I'm not actually sure about that.
That's the one before Milo Zyloto, I believe.
I listened to that one in college.
So that's all really I can promise.
I can't promise the greatest episode ever, but I will go through Coldplay's songs I like
and we will investigate the characters from the weirdos.
You're telling me that in an episode where you go through the Coldplay songs you like,
you think that might not be the greatest episode ever?
I'm trying to lower expectations so when it's the best episode ever, everyone's really blown
away.
That's my tactic.
When everybody, when it finishes and everybody's in para, para, paradise.
Yes, exactly.
The weirdos are out there in the audience now.
It's up to the audience.
Unless Jason has a spoiler he wants to throw in.
No, no.
I mean, I thought the weirdo was the guy trying to climb a stage wearing an Israel flag as
a cape eating shit.
Oh, did you just find the video?
But it turns out there was, no, I've watched, I've seen the video, but it turns out there's
a whole band of weirdos on stage.
Yes, and I think he was not going to protest the weirdos being on stage.
I think it was a different thing.
This is, look, I'm not going to, I'm going to be an adult here.
I can't start flagging like it's going to be a problem for me if the weirdos beat Beach
Boys Full House.
I'm just like, look in your heart, you know what's best.
The audience will do what's best.
I told myself on the Elitch Gardens episode, I was like, don't bring up the weirdos.
Don't bring up the weirdos.
But it happened here and it had to, I think I'd had to say it.
You make that special for the, you do, there's a couple levels
of play wall and that's the great stuff you get is the weirdos.
The weirdos.
It's the Coldplay music video for Adventure of a Lifetime has all these dancing CG monkeys.
I know what that is.
I know that song.
I know.
That's a single.
Are we going to have to talk about that?
I don't know if I like that song.
This is pretty funny.
I mostly know it because they would play it above the big, the big screen above City
Walk and the five, the stage.
And only the finest musical materials get to play there.
Let's just talk about that music video, I think.
Yeah.
It's because there's going to be a lot of debate of like, are these better or worse
monkeys than Kingdom of Crystal Skull monkeys?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's true.
All right.
Well, if you want to vote for it.
You know what?
You've heard, I think you've heard, Eyeling listener, you've heard everything you need
to hear and also a couple more topics to flesh it out.
Yeah, of course.
Maybe something, maybe something somehow can trans both of them.
We will see.
But that's possible.
This brings us to this one, which has been hanging on since February and we finally made
it here in June.
This is from Jessica American Girl Cafe.
It's a themed restaurant.
Our two Disney daddies and one small wooden boy can dine at Century City, each with their
own chosen doll companion.
Sweet cocktails where you can add glitter, check.
A set meal where there's a cinnamon roll as part of the appetizer, check.
The opportunity to consider buying a doll sized working Pac-Man arcade game, check.
Opportunity is everywhere.
Thank you, Jessica.
And here we are.
So yes, we we went to this Mike and the wooden boy sat it out, unfortunately, but Mike and
I went went down there.
I guess before we get into our experience, here's the thing.
I know that, you know, sometimes it'd be a good thing to do kind of like a little bit
of a prehistory of the brand and the place and of what we're talking about, but I start
going through that American Girl Wikipedia is the most complicated thing I've ever seen.
It's dense, yeah.
And by the time I saw that there was a heading for an entire section that is labeled permanent
underwear controversy, I'm like, I'm tapping out of here.
It's dolls.
You know them.
They've been around our whole lives.
We're not getting into the permanent underwear controversy.
No.
Save that for the fucking Coldplay Weirdos episode.
We can talk about it there.
We'll kick it to that one.
But you know what they are.
They're historical dolls.
They come from different times.
You don't need us to explain that.
I started in 86 and it's been with us ever since.
And I think it's gotten more and more bougie ever since.
Yes, because it started out very much in like a sort of like this educational actually.
It seems like that was kind of the intent early on when, wait, what's the name?
It was on the menu.
The founder's name checked on the menu.
Oh, yeah.
Why when Pleasant T. Rowland.
Pleasant T. Rowland.
This is shocking.
This is the first mention of Pleasant T. Rowland.
That is true.
Yeah, we should really have been bringing that up.
Yeah, I know.
And I think the only reason it hasn't happened before is that I don't think Pleasant T. Rowland
is a guy.
I think Pleasant T. Rowland is fine.
And I think started the company with the intent to educate and is a true philanthropist from
what I can tell.
Maybe people can alert me to stuff I did that wasn't included in the source materials.
It's not good about Pleasant T. Rowland.
It sounds like a villain's name, certainly.
I know.
That is the most guy name of all time.
Yeah.
Pleasant T. Rowland.
Well, that's the thing.
I think it's, because Pleasant T. Rowland is a woman, but I think if you made it a man,
suddenly it becomes.
It's like an oil tycoon.
Well, hello there.
The name's Pleasant T. Rowland.
Exactly.
How do you do?
I do better now that I've met you.
Right.
Pleasant T.
But I think Pleasant T. is fine, and Pleasant T. was an educator.
So there was that initial thrust to this was to like not only kind of fill this age gap
between baby doll and adult doll, that being Barbie and the like, it kind of filled an
age gap of doll.
But also there was the idea to like, and then it'll get young girls excited about learning
about different historical eras too.
Yeah.
And there's always been a lot of accessories and clothing.
It's always been pretty commercial.
It's never, I feel like-
It's always been expensive.
Yeah, I think.
But it was like a dryer in its vibe.
Much drier.
Brand, yeah.
But there's a like, Kirsten has like, I hear some people saying Kirsten more than Kirsten,
so excuse me if it's Kirsten.
There's multiple Kirsten books.
All the different characters have books and different other ancillary materials about
stories and things they've done.
And that is continuing into today with the new characters and the different brands.
Why, in the recent past, maybe it was 2015, I don't know when this was, the character
Grace, I don't know what era Grace is from, but Grace was in her own movie, Grace Stirs
Up Success, starring Olivia Rodrigo.
Well, well, well.
Starring both of your human conduit to relevance, Olivia Rodrigo.
Wow, I gotta see that.
I'll see half of it.
I'll watch half of it.
Yeah, it's, you're saying like this is a lot, like there's a lot of information here.
I combed through the YouTube and there is truly an unlimited amount of videos that they
have produced.
Any kind of media you imagine, stop motion with the dolls, animation, CGI animation,
and just for seemingly no reason, things will just switch back and forth.
Everything is posted with like CGI that's bad and weird and off-putting.
And then all of a sudden it's stop motion with the dolls and there's Laura there.
And then there's just footage of like people playing music and the music is actually attributed
to one of the characters, but these two human beings are playing music and not playing the
character.
And I'm not sure there's, cause there's like a character named Tenny, Tenny Grant, who
plays guitar, who was released in the last 10 years.
And then there's like just like singer songwriters playing Tenny songs.
I'm like, but they're not Tenny.
Where's Tenny?
Why?
I'm confused by all of this.
So I'm like going through a YouTube trying to decipher like what's been going on in the
last decade and it's impossible.
And then the whole time my daughter is just looking back at me when I would put a new
video on and going, no, no.
And I put a new video on to try to watch something and this is for like little girls, I would
guess.
And then I go, no, no, every video, not a single video did she like, oh, I'm interested
in this.
No, she's turn around at this off-putting CGI like American girl, no.
If she had a little more words at her disposal, she would have said, dad, go back to the dolls
you usually play on TV.
Well, that's right.
Exactly.
There's so much other unnerving stuff she likes.
Father, which one is Tenny?
I am confused.
She didn't care about Tenny.
She didn't care about any of the songs.
And as soon as I saw Tenny, I got excited because I said, oh, I'm going to like Tenny's
songs.
She's got her own songs.
I'm very excited to like Tenny.
And it didn't happen.
I didn't like Tenny.
Sorry.
Tenny Grant.
So I guess you're finding, we're having a hard, we haven't maybe found our full in to this
brand at least before our encounter with the physical race.
Now this, I will say, I previously with my son had just been to the Century City Mall
where we were sent on this expedition and we'd ended up in the store and he had a ton
of fun in the store.
So I have recent positive associations with like, well, yeah, because there's like, there's
so many accessory, you know, there's, there's little cars and little trains and there was
a ton for him to play with and for him to not buy.
Thank God.
But as Jessica said, this is a, this is a themed environment and it's in a lot of places
that it's in like, I feel like in, in elevated malls, you know what I mean?
This is like, cities have their like major American girl outpost, which is probably a,
you know, a more like committed, with more like, a more committed to place with more
like ornate architecture than you're going to find in a lot of typical toy stores.
So this is, you know, I could see why people thought of this for us.
Yeah, no, it makes sense.
Yeah.
These are in the, there's a little more money going around.
They were making sure they put these in a place where people are going to spend a little
more, I think.
And there is so, I guess I was just like shocked at how much stuff is still being made.
I guess I really didn't know how popular this brand still is.
Well, if you don't, because we both grew up with little sisters, so we're aware of it
then.
Right.
And then you're newly a dad of a daughter.
So you're only, who knows if she'll get into it.
We missed a lot of middle, right?
Other than sometimes I'll be somewhere like Chicago, or I remember being in whatever it
moved malls in Dallas, but wherever it was before, I went into that one for a second
and like, Oh my God.
There was like a committed, there was like a valet entrance just for that.
Okay.
Yes.
This is a, like, I only knew it was a big deal from occasionally catching wind of the
stores here.
Yeah.
I remember growing up the books in the scholastic, like catalogs or book fairs, the boring books,
you know?
Oh yeah.
It was all boring to me.
Very brown covers.
Did you read them?
I did not read them.
Okay.
You never read a single one?
I was intrigued because like, clearly there's what we say now is like, clearly there's lore,
clearly there's backstory here, but I was reading very boring historical books of like
the Marvel comics adaptation of the battle of Gettysburg that they sold at the Gettysburg
gift shop.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you want to put that in the club three poll?
Marvel comics Gettysburg comic?
I don't know where my copy is, but I bet we could find it online.
Put that in, someone nominate that to nominate it.
Don't do it because it might split the vote with Coldplay Weirdos.
Put it in because it should be in on its own.
Yeah, yeah.
That makes sense.
Sure.
So yeah, I just, you know, like a lot of things when you're a little kid, you go like, that's
not for me.
I'm not interested in that.
Now, if I had seen stuff like, and I've said this before on the show, where like there
was a Barbie camper that was in like the Sears Wishbook that I really wanted my sister
to get because I knew Barbie was for girls and I wouldn't be caught dead having a girl
story even though I wanted to fucking camper and play with Barbie so badly.
If I think if they had, now that they have all this contemporary crap, I think I would
have been more interested in it because they'll have, they have like a big camper kind of
a thing and they have all these like elaborate accessories depending on what the character
is.
Well, you can get a $600 Hogwarts Express.
Well, yes, that's true too.
And there's Disney versions of the Disney dolls now too.
So if I had gone into this as a little kid, it just at the time I was a dumb little boy
who was just like, history is boring, I want space and I want a Ninja Turtle, like all
that stuff.
I had to read a number of like, I wanted to read all those, you know, basic scholastic
books about the sinking of the Titanic.
So that way when I went on a Norwegian cruise line cruise to Bermuda, I would just be terrified
the first day or so that we were all about to die.
And that happened?
Yes, it didn't dawn on me that there are not icebergs in that off the coast of the
Carolinas.
That's awesome.
That's still how you are today because if we're talking about somewhere with a pier
with rides, you're like, this is what happens to piers with rides and then you show us a
photo from 1915.
Or night.
Well, there is some terrible hurricanes in the mid 20th century.
Yeah, they took a lot of amusements.
My favorite book up until maybe I was, well, maybe it's still my favorite book, was the
Mario choose your own adventure book where you would go and pick which warp pipe you
went in at the end of a chapter.
Those books were, I light up my brain, I can feel it light up like in more excitement than
anything else.
When I think about that book over any book I've ever read.
I was, I read a lot of the original seventies and eighties ones, which would drive me insane
because I was trying to read all the way through them and get to the end.
So I, yeah, just a lot of made up problems in my head.
That was my childhood.
Yeah.
No, I wanted to live permanently in the Nintendo entertainment system.
Sure.
And so, yeah.
Even when you weren't playing video games, when you were forced to.
Did you never, did you guys never have these?
It sounds familiar.
They were out of like print by the time I started getting them.
So like I was desperate to get them all, but they only, I only had a couple because they
had already stopped making them.
Maybe they weren't that popular, but.
Jump pipes in pros.
That's a good idea.
I like that.
And yeah.
So you would jump to like a certain chapter, depending on what your choice was.
And then you would die in the book and go back to the start.
Oh, they just send you back to the beginning?
Yeah.
So I was obsessed.
This is, these are my favorite books.
And then occasionally the book would just start flashing the main menu and you would
have to blow in it and like restart it and try to fuck with it.
You would have to blow on the book if it didn't work.
Yeah.
I didn't do well.
I feel like I never even beat the book fairly because then you would go back and like cheat.
Oh, sure.
You're supposed to start at the beginning and do it.
Wow.
But you could cheat and I probably cheated just to see the end of it, but yeah.
So I was a, yeah.
That's not good boy behavior.
I hope you kept that to yourself.
Not smart boy behavior as far as what I was interested in.
The kind of literature.
The kind of literature I remain interested in.
Yeah.
So, so American Girl.
They, they, and I think in 2017 I saw is when they start the contemporary characters.
Okay.
So it seems more fairly, like fairly recently that they started appealing to dumb little
boys like me.
That's when they were like, we got to go after the dumb little boy market.
And I think it seems successful.
It seems successful.
Yeah.
I mean, there's still the, the historical component, but they just keep updating it.
I mean, the thing that really depressed me and that will depress some of our listeners
too, is that they, I mean, cause they keep stepping up, right?
Like they're, you know, they're like, there's this girl from the seventies and this girl
from the eighties.
And I was pretty dismayed to find that there are these twins who are from 1999.
The 1999 is now like a boy, a way back when, but I, I don't know.
I understand though.
And it's like, when you go into the backseat, wait, I got them.
Yeah, and they are, they're represented.
They have a little like alien with their names, which I like.
That's pretty good.
Actually.
Yeah.
That does kind of, that's an unexpected defining the time.
You would have like an alien sticker probably.
Right.
But one of them is the best.
I think one's like preppy and one's weird and the weird one's like, uh, likes grunge
music from Seattle.
She's the, she's the alt girl.
So weird.
To the Quinn of her preppy sister.
On that recent historical front, there is a girl Courtney.
She is from 1986.
And that brings us to one of the little assignments from Jessica, which I didn't know.
We were passed to that.
I didn't see this in the store.
I didn't pay attention to it in the store.
Oh, I definitely like noticed Courtney's logo and vibe.
And I like, well, maybe Courtney's my, I think if I had to pick one, I think I'm Courtney.
Uh, um, but, uh, the Courtney is the one where Jessica mentioned a working doll sized Pacman
arcade game.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And I looked this up.
And in fact, yes, it is.
This is an accessory you can buy.
It's 18 inches tall.
It works.
It's a little joystick.
That's really good.
And, uh, and it is $300.
Wow.
All right.
Fair.
Wow.
Wait a minute.
It's a working video game cabinet.
Yeah.
You're the most picky on prices person of the three of us.
And that's the first thing that you're like, fair, it makes sense for me.
It would probably be just my size.
So I just keep it on my nightstand by the mockery of regular sized arcade.
Courtney comes with a little bottle of Quaaludes too.
And she's got, if you look closely, uh, like that, uh, shot from Empire Strikes Back of
Carrie Fisher.
Courtney has a little Coke nail.
Yeah.
Yes.
Uh, or catchphrases.
Greed is good.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's, you can get those like one up arcades for like 600 and then I have sitting in my
garage a Simpsons that I bought for 200 that I haven't put up yet, but I have the big box
of it.
So that's still 300 is.
Yeah.
That's the thing.
I think you can buy a real one for.
For 300.
Well, I don't know if it's the right sale.
I'm interested to know how many of these they're selling though.
Because you know, with accessories, sometimes for toys and stuff, sometimes the run of them,
they make so little you would be surprised maybe.
So maybe they only made like 500 of them and that's why it's 300 bucks.
Huh.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
And I don't know if they have information.
This is your area.
Yeah.
I guess you might know.
And the intention is not, it's like this is, we're not going to like, uh, you know, it's
not going to be some gangbusters line for us.
It's just, this is a boutique item and, uh, the girls with the best parents will end up
with that little piece.
Are there 2010s dolls who are really into STEM, like the way they kind of force STEM
into like children's toys in the last 10 years?
Sounds like they haven't gotten there yet, but maybe that's coming.
Maybe that's in the lab.
Get some cat eye glasses and a shitty little working laptop.
You just put a fucking Chromebook, tiny little Chromebook.
Yeah.
Either generic or you partner with Google.
There is a lot of like partnership in these, I mean, the fact that there is like a genuine
branded Pac-Man and Harry Potter is these are, these are deals on a massive scale.
These are licensing.
I mean, it's what Lego did when they, they kind of turned the company around.
This might be, I don't know so much about the history of Lego, but Lego kind of turned
the corner on the company when they just started doing everything, Marvel, DC, Harry Potter
Yeah.
Yes, Pharrell.
They did all the brands, the major brands, you would assume.
So yeah, it seems American Girl went that way and I'm sure it helped them thrive.
The IP, it infects everything.
Definitely.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, so there's all these areas.
There's the dolls, the books is a big area, the movies, your kit, Kittredges.
And then of course, these establishments, which really bring it into our territory.
I think the first one of the, so American Girl Place is the bigger setting.
Some of which, maybe all of which, I'm not sure, have cafes.
98, the first one opens in Chicago.
There's nine locations with dining, including Chicago, Nashville, Dallas, Orlando, and Los
Angeles.
This was at the Los Angeles location was at the Grove for a long time.
I think it was like Caruso's first essential work, the Grove, fancy little fake town.
I don't know what, I didn't know that they left there, but they left there.
And that one seemed maybe a little more like ostentatious in a way, you know, like possibly
bigger.
I don't know, just like, I think the cafe was bigger.
I think definitely it was a bigger space.
Maybe that was the idea is like, we still need to be, so we're going to do business
but I don't know if we can afford like three massive stories at the Grove.
I'm not sure.
Don't know.
But they are now at Westfield Century City, which has come up on the show before because
it's the former home of Dive, the Spielberg submarine restaurant.
I also recently learned that it is the birthplace of the Planet of the Apes in the fourth film
Conquest for the Planet of the Apes.
Of the Planet of the Apes.
Conquest.
Oh really?
You know, because those are 20th century Fox movies.
Which is right, the lots over there.
Yeah, and that's why it's Century City, I believe.
So I think they're, so yeah, pure proximity makes sense to go over there.
But it's also, yeah, it was kind of a new mall at that time, I think, like early 80s.
And it, so they use it to fill in for dystopia and because it's a little futuristic, but
then it's a weird, like literally, spoiler, at the end, there's a speech that's like,
From here, from this point, we will all start a Planet of the Apes.
And then it goes wide and this kind of like stores in the background.
So it is weird, it was in my head, I just watched that, thanks to Griffin naming that
his favorite Planet of the Apes, I'm glad I watched it for that reason, right on Griffin.
And it is, so walking around there, that was in my head for sure, like whoa, this is where
it all began, in that timeline at least.
That's cool.
But so yeah, it moved there in September 2023, and it gave us license to go there,
we got to go to a place we ignore because it's really inconvenient to get to.
It's so inconvenient to get to.
I know that seems weird if you look just at a Google map.
Yes, it's not inconvenient to get to at two in the morning.
Right.
Very easy.
But it's so...
I don't think it's open then.
Hard to get there.
And I still was like prepared, I'm like okay, so I'll leave some time, it'll be fine, and
then, sorry to be in LA complaining about traffic person, but oh my god, god that was
crazy.
And then getting back was even worse.
It was so bad.
So bad.
Oh my god.
What happened?
It felt like a two hours, I don't know.
It was three in the afternoon, why was that so bad?
I don't know, it said like it's gonna take 90 minutes and then it took like two hours
10 minutes to get like 20 miles, to move 20 miles.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I ended up like, it was just, I just did an entire stint down sunset, all the way
down the full sunset strip, which was thankfully a pretty engaging, oh wait, well you know
what, before I get into that, I guess there's something that we have to reveal about this,
about the trip that we took.
With our little wooden boy not there, we also made a decision, here's the, you know, okay,
there's a way, could it have been us adults sitting at this doll restaurant with our little
dolls in their little seats, it could have been this, certainly, would that have only
served to make us very uncomfortable and the server mildly uncomfortable, although I bet
it happens more than you think, so it's not actually that weird, but then also, here's
something to say about the American Girl Cafe.
My old boss, Conan O'Brien, filmed a remote there a number of years ago, that is without
a doubt the funniest piece of comedy that will happen where a person without a child
goes to eat with a doll at this restaurant, so like, you know what, we're not gonna be
in that territory, we have children, let's take our children, let's go with our kid,
let's do this in not a bizarre way, maybe someone will get genuine enjoyment out of this,
so we did, both of us took our kids.
Children, Lindsay was in my place, did, was Lindsay an American Girl doll girl growing
up?
No.
Or did she hate them?
She don't hate them, I don't think.
She was indifferent?
She was a little too old for it and just never did it, so she doesn't really, yeah, she didn't
really have any, like, affection for it at all.
Did you take that doll with you when you went there?
Well, what a good question you ask, Jason, what a good question you ask.
Oh no!
You didn't warn me there was something you wanted to talk about that wasn't the weirdo's
face.
I would say as far as me being on time, I'm okay, I fight against my programming sometimes
when it's like, I gotta be on time, I gotta be on time.
When you add Lindsay and the baby in, it makes it a lot harder.
It's a lot of possibility.
I even was a little, I was like, enough things, I even said, maybe let's all aim, let's try
to be early.
Which I did, which got me there on time.
If I hadn't tried to be early, I would have been there late.
I was walking around the house, every ten minutes going, we gotta be on time.
I was doing this, we gotta get on time.
I'm like, oh, we're running a little late.
I was picturing a very harsh headmistress saying, you are late, what do you mean here?
Your girls are already in class, so you can't join them.
The girls are already eating their tea and whatever, crumpets.
So, I'm like, stressed about being there, because I know it's Century City, the worst
place to go to, and I know that it's hard to wrangle, wrangling everyone is almost impossible.
And so I'm like, all right, we're doing okay.
We're doing okay to be there on time.
We leave, we get about five minutes on the road, six minutes.
I'm like, kind of like, okay, I think it'll be all right.
Google Maps says, you know, we still have kind of like a 15 minute buffer, and I think
we'll be fine.
I realize right before we get on the freeway, Kirsten is at home.
I left Kirsten at home.
The whole point, I made a whole point to get Kirsten from my parents.
I was like, ah, and I'm like, I'm looking at the thing, and I'm trying to calculate
how much it's going to take to get back.
Is it worth it?
And then in my head, I'm starting to imagine, what if there's something that only having
a Kirsten will unlock?
What if there's some part of the, because I'm not even consciously thinking about this,
and I'm like, what if having Kirsten does something for us?
And now we're being sent on this mission for work.
This is work, and now I'm going to do, I'm going to screw this up.
They're going to say, well, if you had Kirsten here, it would unlock the Kirsten celebration
or something.
Yeah.
And now I, Kirsten's at home.
Kirsten's here?
We'll make the edible food.
Right.
The food is going to be 10% better.
We'll try for Kirsten.
Yes, exactly.
Or there was like a song or something.
I just was, all this stuff was flashing in my head.
I'm already stressed just about being on time.
And I go, fuck, we have to go back and get Kirsten.
And Kirsten, you can't feel good about this either, because now you're home alone?
I'm home alone and I had no food.
What she's really English right now.
And I had no food and the winter was coming.
And I was just ever so scared.
This is, you're so, you're so skittish.
We're not even anywhere close to the winter.
But I'm sure that's how it feels to you all the time, is that the winter is always nigh.
Is winter outside this door right now?
Is winter outside these walls?
Mike, did you consider just buying a second Kirsten?
Well we considered, we did consider buying, yes.
It's just an easy 160.
Sorry to say that, Kirsten, but you're a little bit replaceable.
Oh, that's all right.
That's what father says sometimes when he's having one of his attacks.
Oh no.
And father is not Mike, right?
What's that?
Father is not you?
No, no, that's a different character.
We took Kirsten in for just like a holiday.
Separate father, a very ill immigrant.
Father sent me to Michael and Lindsay's cabin while he was going through his treatments.
His father has been very sick.
His leeches and his.
Ever since he was beating for shooting Archduke Franz Ferdinand.
That's right, her father is a guerrilla princep.
Yes, thank you for revealing it on the show.
The man who starred in World War I.
These are all things that Michael doesn't know because he only knows what happens when
Mario meets Yoshi and he feeds Yoshi a few berries.
The book ends because it kills Yoshi.
You have to start over.
No, he shits out an egg.
Yoshi choked on berries.
He shits out an egg.
So I'm just, I'm cursing, I'm upset and I turn around and go back to get Kirsten and
I'm still going, OK, we're doing OK on time because we had, we had a little bit of time.
I think it'll be all right.
Maybe we'll, and I'm, this is the dumbest thing I've ever thought about somebody driving
from Burbank to Central City.
Maybe we'll make up a couple of minutes on the way.
So I'm still, I'm, I'm upset and, and, but I'm like, OK, we still, we have time, I race
in to get Kirsten.
Maybe if part of the freeway is broken, which turns it into a makeshift ramp that you don't
see coming, which will launch you two miles ahead of.
Like a Mario Kart track.
Very possible.
Entirely speed ramp.
That's all I know.
I don't know world history.
I do know how Mario Kart works.
So history began in 1992 when you're us.
So I'm running into the house.
I remember how old I am also, just my, my, my age flashes in front of me as I'm running
into the house.
You feel your knees creaking as you run to grab a doll.
Superfluous doll.
Tripping on many, many other dolls along the way.
And then I get in the car and we start driving and I was hoping that because the 405, I think
there was an accident.
That's really what killed us.
I think there were five on my route.
I think there were three.
I believe it.
But like the 405, like being that thing was shut down.
I think I was hoping that maybe the 405 will clear up on our way there.
Did not happen.
Never happened.
Could just has not cleared up now.
Even a week later.
No, no, no, no.
It's still, it's still crowded from.
So we could go.
Driving.
And then I see the ministers ticking up on the estimate on the car and I'm like, okay.
I still like stupidly.
I'm like, well, maybe cold water will over the hill will catch up.
So early on in the trip, I tell Lindsay, could you read Kirsten's bio online for me?
Because I need to know some backstory about Kirsten.
She says, sure.
That's fine.
She decides to do it while we're on Coldwater Canyon, the windiest, hilliest street you
could possibly do it on.
No, she, she does get motion sickness sometimes.
She starts getting motion sick in the car to the point where I go, do we have to pull
over like in front of like the house of Lucy lived on in Beverly Hills?
I don't know if it's on cold water, but those famous houses pull over to see the house.
Of course I wanted to see Lucy's house driving extra wild to try to get her to get sick enough.
Oh, hello.
Of course.
Yes.
We're like around that area.
The sketch got.
Well, we didn't film that there, but okay.
Well, I mean, it's, but technically I think it's.
I think Lucy, here's the, I think Lucy lived in 17 places in Los Angeles.
And for sure, there's something you really figure out when you live in LA.
Charlie Chaplin lived in 59 places in the city.
You will go, you will.
It's astounding how many places you will go where you learned that Charlie Chaplin once
lived there.
He could not hold down a place for two months, this guy, this tramp.
So we did not have to stop, but it came close where like, I just look in the back and Lindsay's
sitting back there by the baby and she's just like, her head is like this.
And I'm like, oh my God, oh my God, we're running late because of the doll.
And now Lindsay's about to be, she's sick because of the doll.
She simply must learn facts about the doll here, not there.
You got to know this going in, you cannot sit down and be on your phone reading a bio
They'll know, they'll know that you're a noob to American girl.
I just picture, I look, I pictured a casual thing.
We read, she was reading it.
We'd laugh a little and then I would have some information.
Not that it would almost like completely ruin the actual trip to this cafe.
Now she made it.
I'm trying to like, kind of not get like go, I'm not going slow on cold water, but like
I'm trying to hit like bumps too hard.
You also, you're by the way, you're on, you're on the same street where the last time I went
on that, I hit two potholes.
Ruining my chance to attend the opening gala of the Planet Hollywood auction.
Oh, right, right.
I needed a, I needed a tire replacement after that.
This street's a disaster.
I'm glad you didn't get in a puddle.
I had, I was thinking about that too.
I was like, this is a treacherous street.
So I forgot Kirsten and everything tumbled from there.
Everything spiraled out of control from there.
And yeah, so, so Kirsten made it.
She made it.
She was there.
Yeah.
Now, so then that I guess gets us to, I wasn't there that long before you, but enough to
check in and to realize we couldn't sit until everybody was there.
Right.
Yes.
So I'm hanging out, I'm pacing.
Sun is entertained, but you know, could tip at any minute and you guys come in, you
come in with the energy, you're huffing it up the stick cause you got to go up a flight
of stairs to get up there.
So you come up just like, ah, it's been a thing.
We are, it's been a morning.
Stuff is going on.
And I say, Mike, when has there been in the 10 years that I've known you now, has there
been one thing you've showed up at where that was not the energy?
I know.
Where there weren't multiple things going on.
Yeah.
No, I know.
I didn't know any of this either.
He was like, I'll talk about it on the show.
Like this is happening.
I'm sitting in bed coughing, drinking orange juice and taking a Moxicillin.
And I, no one texted me like, oh, we're going to take Lindsey.
Uh, don't worry about it.
So I just like, I hope they're not mad at me.
And then an hour later, I'm like, I hope there's not antics, which I couldn't have
prevented even if I was there.
You thought you would have prevented antics?
No, no, absolutely not.
I was just like, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
I would have been there even later.
Think about the who, the who's on that text thread.
One of the names is Mike Carlson.
There are going to be antics.
Yeah.
There's always antics.
I was trying so, I swear I was trying so hard to not have antics.
I really made such an effort to have no antics getting there.
That's the problem.
I think the more you try, I really felt like I was like punished for
trying to have no antics and the God of Antics.
Who's the Greek God of Antics, Jason?
I don't know.
I don't really know.
Okay.
Loki, is Loki the Greek?
It sounds like the Norse God of Mischief and trickery, Loki, was in your car that day.
He's like, I could, I could handle antics.
Yeah, that'd be in my, I can grab it.
It's not my.
Yeah.
It's not quite what I do, but okay.
I can do it today.
I'll jump on.
Yeah.
So she made it, she made it.
There was no reason for her to be there.
There were no Kirsten unlocking celebration.
Not only is there no Kirsten unlocking celebration, but like, I mean,
maybe you didn't know this going in, but a whole aspect of it is that
you can get a loner doll.
Right.
There's a big wall of dolls.
That felt wrong to me to get a loner doll.
Cause we have, this is in the fam, Kirsten's been in the family for 30 years.
It felt wrong to take a loner doll.
I guess.
I'm looking Kirsten in the eye and I'm glad you're here.
And I had a good time with you.
But I think one of your nonspecific from whenever pals up on that shelf would
have been just as good a company.
Yes.
Sorry to tell you.
And the voyage to Century City was longer than a wagon train from one side of
Sweden to the other when father and mother and I left our home village and
went to the new world, the Century City.
We almost lost me on the way to Century City.
You should have stayed in your time.
I know you're probably like, Oh wow.
They have horseless carriages now.
Well, guess what?
We got a lot of complaints about him.
It's better when you were, Oh, to be in your time, Kirsten.
Yeah.
The Sepulveda pass was better when it was just a pass, not a freeway.
I thought we were going to have to lose our oxen when we were
pulling into Beverly Hills.
I didn't know what was going on and why it took so long.
Well, I guess that's something for you to know that I guess you don't know that
about cars, that cars don't have lots of little oxen at the bottom.
That's probably what you're picturing.
Right, Kirsten?
That is what I'm picturing.
15 baby oxen all under the carriage of the car.
I thought they were carrying it.
Yeah.
15 oxen under this automobile.
Oh, the way some of these mechanics, George and LA, you thought you'd buy an
oxen.
Oh, is that ancient standup comedy material?
Yes.
That's a joke from her time.
Ah, yes.
Thank you.
You remind me of many people I know from my time, Mr.
Sheridan.
You have a way about you.
You like all this popular music.
Like you probably like to to tootsie goodbye and you were a song in my era.
One of my favorite popular songs.
That was that was Olivia Rodrigo to you.
Yes, exactly.
Yes.
You pretended to like to to tootsie to seem relevant.
Exactly.
I didn't quite get it.
But it seemed like every young people liked it.
Why?
Why did they stutter?
You said it doesn't anyone know how to speak in these songs anymore.
That's yes.
Coldplay, of course, now does that with para para paradise.
They do a similar trajectory.
Wow.
I never thought of that.
They really are.
Yeah.
There's a real a real through line from to to tootsie.
Goodbye, Mr.
Chris Martin had too many russes of blood to the head.
It damaged his brain and he started making poppins.
Father also suffers from a rush of blood to his head almost nightly.
It's so tragic.
That's when Coldplay's first hit.
Yellow is the color of your father's skin.
He's very ill.
Sadly, yes.
So Kirsten made it.
She sat in her little seat.
Kirsten made it even though Kirsten did not need to make it.
And maybe you didn't know.
Maybe you didn't know.
But I wasn't totally sure.
I knew that there was that wall of dolls.
But I still was like, but what's the deal?
And is it like an add on?
Or but no, I think you just grab.
Yeah, I wasn't I wasn't clear on that.
I knew like you could get other dolls or be I didn't know if it's a charge,
if it's something else.
So it felt it felt like I could make we just couldn't.
I should not have.
If it was somewhere closer, I could have risked it.
I think it's still been basically on time, not Century City, though.
So that was madness.
You lost at least 15 minutes, if not more.
Yeah.
To get a doll who did not ultimately factor into the experience.
No, not at all.
No waste of time.
A phrase that has been said to Mike multiple times.
That's true. Yeah.
This is only probably the second or third episode.
You've cradled a toy, surprisingly.
That's true. Yeah, that is true.
Yes, you are being very loving to Kirsten as you.
Yeah, you're giving her support.
But I also I do.
I like the that that was the spirit of it.
And I, in fact, brought a doll to my son as a baby doll.
Baby Pete came along.
Not a huge, important toy in our house,
but he factors into into the fun sometimes.
He his main attribute, as you noticed, Mike,
is that he has kind of like built in pants that sag.
Thus, he's often revealing his butt throughout.
That's funny.
And he hang with him.
So, yeah, we both we both brought our own dolls to fill the little chairs.
Let's talk about those official terminology per the back of the menu.
Treat seats like we're we're in real PTR territory here.
Treat seats are the little pink chairs that have kind of two handles
that slide right onto the edge of the table
so that they can, you know, they're right at table level.
Yes, with you.
It is. Yes, it's the menu was fun.
I would say the menu design is fun.
But the menu I liked, I like the menu.
I'll say that.
You mean like the things on it, the things on it, the words
than the corresponding food items that.
Yeah, what is happening to you?
I like the things on it, the words.
I like when there's no things on it, those being like columns in space
which allow you more room to read the words.
You know, the front of the menu tells you the name of the establishment
you're in, and that's very helpful.
And I like that.
Let's me know that I didn't walk into Katsuya by mistake.
Right. I like that about it.
I will say the menus had been through the mill a little bit as far as
like as far as them being beat up.
Like the photo I have of my my daughter here.
She's got it.
And this thing looks like it's been crumpled up a few times.
Yeah, I mean, many, many children are playing with these.
So I guess it makes sense to have them like that and not have like a big,
like thick menu, like a bound menu or something.
Yeah, yeah. Any any reactions to like the environment
while coming in or once?
Well, this is so so so going in a little bit blind.
I was surprised at the aesthetic of the modern American girl.
I didn't think we would be eating in like a like an old time mess hall
or anything or like a gruel stand or whatever you would call it.
Like an orphan.
I didn't think we were going to an orphanage like restaurant.
But I was surprised, like, oh, this is like Barbie ish.
It is very Barbie to me.
Yeah, I mean, I was aware of it maybe from that that Conan remote
that I guess I knew that it's I know the colors.
I know that it's this like this very dark pink.
Yeah. And a lot of black and white zebra.
I knew that. And if anything, I actually once we sat in here,
I was like, this is like a little more subtle.
This is a little more like stately, at least the room we were in
than the one that I knew from from that remote. Right.
Or it's been, you know, Travis Kelsey did a sketch on us
and although it was a parodying this really recreated the environment.
So I actually so to me, I was like, you know, it's a little
it was just kind of like floral back chairs and just kind of white. And
it was low key.
It was. And you know what? Kind of disappointed me. I agree.
I kind of wanted it to be trashier, right?
I want it in some direction to be more something.
Yeah. Like you want it's that it is historically accurate
that you're in like an old tea room that is for most people kind of depressing.
Yeah. Reminds you that you don't want to live in that area. Right. Or
modern, current, annoying in your face. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Erin saw pictures and she's like,
there's a lot more boring than I thought. Yeah, I know.
It is a little bit just kind of like it's sort of just like a modern tea room.
And I was surprised that I felt this way, but I wanted it to be trashier.
Yes, I agree. Yes. Yeah.
Any direction they could go, I think I would have been happier than.
Yeah. But it felt low key.
It felt I wouldn't say it's tasteful, but it just felt like, oh, OK.
I don't know. Like outside of just all the different like
pictures on the wall of American girls, it would I would have been like,
oh, this must be a themed.
This must be something like it didn't feel so specific to me.
Yeah, right. Yeah.
So then food.
So the structure here is
twenty seven dollars a person.
Yeah. Which is which which gets you everything
minus booze, booze is add on.
But it's this whole like multi-course meal where her
imagine that. Oh, my God.
Twenty seven dollars, by the way, if we had booked this
maybe a week or two later, would have been 30.
This is real. Yes.
The prices have gone up. Wow.
Since we did it, it is now.
Yes, it would have been 15 more dollars instantly
if we'd done this any later.
So, Jessica, thanks for getting the suggestion in February.
So but you the menu.
Let's let's go through that and what you get.
The starter, the welcome course also, as Jessica alluded to,
they're famous.
Warm, welcome cinnamon buns, warm, welcome cinnamon.
Our petite cinnamon buns are an American girl tradition.
And this is as I was looking on the menu of like,
what am I going to get here?
This kind of thing. I'm like, OK, I guess all right.
We start with cinnamon buns. That's fine.
That's fine. Regrets on missing this.
You know, I wish more restaurants the appetizer.
The brave course was cinnamon buns.
You wish more people in general would give you a warm welcome
with cinnamon buns.
With cinnamon buns, a complimentary pink lemonade.
That sounds great to me.
Looking at this menu, I am like, this is all stuff I like.
Yeah, you might have like a child.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah.
The childless person might have enjoyed this the most.
Just the food itself.
Yeah. And that's true.
You clocked that pink lemonade juice, soft drink, milk, iced tea, coffee.
So, all right.
Hey, we're getting like that.
Twenty seven dollars is sounding like nothing now.
Then you get this like a multi-tiered little,
you know, plate tower.
Yeah, sampler tower.
Little teed snackaroos,
cucumber bites with borson mousse,
celery boats filled with cheese spread.
Not there. Yeah.
Right. I don't think that was there.
I don't remember no celery boats.
Oh, yeah, I guess you're right.
Not that I recall. Yeah, no.
Fresh fruit and festive fruit skewers,
a.k.a. sticks with the fruit that you least want in a fruit salad.
Yeah, all melons.
It's all. Yes, 100 percent.
I'm all melon, baby.
I love the melon.
All melon. Yeah, honeydew.
Honeydew, cantaloupe.
More than just like strawberries and stuff.
I like strawberries too.
But yeah, we're big melon fan.
We're always excited when we went to a buffet or breakfast and there was melon.
This is weird.
I feel like I've never heard this opinion. Watermelon, cantaloupe, honeydew.
Watermelon is a whole other area.
Well, that's a melon.
Watermelon is a step above, I believe.
Sure.
No, I think to me, cantaloupe, melon, or these are boring.
These are like these these just these are filler.
These fill out a filler to me.
But I will have some sometimes.
OK. But it doesn't excite.
The idea of eating a piece of cantaloupe doesn't excite me.
But Jason, Jason, I love a cantaloupe.
Yeah.
Isn't really best out here.
And they're right around the corner.
There's an old Navy.
So many bargains, you know, waiting for you.
That jumped out at you.
I was looking at the map of the mall and I was like, oh, fancy mall.
It's got an old Navy and it's got chicken tender.
Hang on a second.
You what you clocked about the fancy mall was a store that is at every mall.
Well, I it's at crappy malls, too.
Yes.
Well, old Navy.
Now we're in the money.
Father lost use of his leg in the old movie, sadly.
And I see that he loved the old Navy, though, like this one over here.
He would. So he would have no use for the very cheap shorts there.
Yes, sadly, he had to have them specially made
time off the woman who was having an affair.
Oh, my God. Oh, that, too.
Yes, that, too.
Well, I'm so sorry.
Things are things are rough, rough.
Yes, you stay.
You stay strong. All right.
That's the American experience.
You fight through it no matter what.
Yes. I want to hear more about this.
This one's love of melons.
A delicacy back in the day.
Yes, that's what I think.
Yes. I had cantaloupe as a birthday present when I was five.
Did you celebrate memory and no presents for years after the fact?
Did anyone get kids old fashioned cherry soda?
No, no.
Add on, add on.
I don't know. That's a one dollar add on.
No, I don't know if I'm going to pass that up.
You got to go alone and then don't even talk about it on the show.
Yeah. Do it for you.
The dolls are too cumbersome.
So just table for one, please.
Table. You could go right up to the bar, I think.
They got like a soda bar.
There is a large beer, wine, liquor menu.
Oh, there's a lot of that.
You kind of brought us to that with the so the add ons.
Yes. I mean, it is very evident.
That drinking at this place is a thing.
Oh, yeah. Because it's a full page.
Yeah. To itself is the booze.
Yes. I I was eyeing wine, of course.
I thought, hey, this this this will plus it up for me.
But then I'm looking at what other tables are getting.
Places hoppin.
There's a birthday song every five minutes.
Yes. Places, I think, entirely birthdays.
Um, and like, OK, people got pink drinks.
I feel like I got to get a pink drink.
Yes. And so I asked, what is pink?
They said rose martini vodka, house made sour.
They make it in house.
They make they make that sour.
Wow. They lined up unused dolls
to the ingredients in the sour
and cranberry juice with fresh lemon peel and rose rim.
When this showed up,
I'd call it less appeal and more a lemon wedge.
Like, you know, it would be in a nice tea.
I would call it all cranberry juice.
If there was vodka,
I there it was not the primary component.
Rose rim equaled sugar.
There's just like sugar caked onto it.
Yeah. And you saw as this went on, it just it didn't get me drunk.
It just made me feel weird.
Yeah. I just felt I just felt muddy brain.
Yeah. I don't know what a somewhere.
Like the the small amount of liquor and all the sugar just fought.
And it was I'm not a big liquid sugar consumer.
So it just like fuzzed me out.
Yeah. Yeah. You did not seem like you were like, oh, yeah.
Like you were all of a sudden like on a high from just a little
because sometimes if you have a little alcohol in the middle of the day,
you get a little boost.
Well, that's where I'm like, this is I did what I thought would be funny.
You're in a picture instead of going with what was in my heart,
which is always Chardonnay.
There probably is pure Chardonnay in my heart, right?
It'll be an operation someday to get it sucked out of me.
But I really should have because I think I would have.
I do get a little energy.
It like serves as caffeine for me sometimes in the right setting.
I mean, that's what Disneyland, you know,
you have a car they man at in the middle of the day.
It's like I had an espresso or something like it's some depending on.
Yeah, certain factors like, I don't know.
It's just like it just bummed me out.
It made me feel like the way and probably the food did this, too.
I just remember my like major energy lag when I went to Red Robin
and talked about it a little on the show.
Oh, yeah.
Which prompted the discussion of how I need to be done eating bad beef
and maybe have a bad beef bachelor party.
It made me feel like the bad beef.
It's just like, I'm so tired now.
I just want to nap.
It's not how I want a little fun pink drink to make me feel.
But I also wanted to match you, Mike,
because you got something a little bit unusual.
I feel so that you're not getting every restaurant you get.
Cavie's glittery fizz girl of the year inspired drink
sprite with your choice of a pink or blue glitter bomb
that will bubble fizz and change your drink from clear to pink or blue.
Served with a strawberry straw you can eat.
Now, listeners, if you noted that paragraph,
is there anything that you noticed was missing from that that little synopsis?
Perhaps alcohol, mankind, of course, thus making it Mike's ideal beverage.
Right. A sugar drink with no liquor.
That is yes.
So that did that give me a boost at all?
I would say no.
I would say I didn't dislike it.
You looked pretty.
I never saw a smile during the experience of Cavie's glittery fizz.
I wasn't mad at it, though.
I wasn't mad.
They there was a strawberry straw that was confusing to me.
It confused me. It says you can eat the straw and eat it.
Eat is different.
This is actually more egregious than I thought.
There's edible, which means technically you could kind of consume this somehow.
Right. Eat is like crunch.
And I am eating the straw.
This is Willy Wonka.
I didn't do it in that comical way, but I did try to take a little mini bite of it.
And it was rock hard and not in a way like not in a candy necklace, even rock.
It felt harder than a candy necklace and even a stale candy thong from its sugar.
It felt like it felt like I was like, oh, I can't bite this.
This is going to break my teeth.
So I was like, well, I thought it was edible.
And then as you put liquid through it, it gets soggier and soggier.
And then I would try to kind of take a bite out of it.
But it still didn't taste.
I was like, oh, maybe it'll like turn into almost like a laffy taffy kind of a thing.
And you're kind of eat part of it.
But it still didn't feel right to eat.
There's a part of your brain, you know, you put something in your mouth and it knows
I can't eat this. Don't eat this. Not edible.
That kept going off.
That kept firing in my head of like, this is not edible.
You shouldn't have this.
This is something that this is a luxury that Kirsten doesn't have,
because with the hard time she's fallen on,
anything has to be considered possible food for the family.
That's right. That's going off in my brain all the time.
And I have to ignore it.
That instinct to not eat something.
You might have to just like, you know, try to take a bite out of your horse's hoof.
We ate father's old notebooks the other day.
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
Your memories, all of your childhood memories.
His whole history in Sweden is now gone because you the family had
to eat it, put it in a stew.
I mean, it was mostly memories of the front.
So I don't know if he wants to relive that.
Maybe better, better off.
And he doesn't remember anything anymore because of the.
Because of the mustard gas.
Because of the mustard gas. Yeah.
Archduke. What is that? Right.
Was that the?
I mean, it came a little later, but yeah, close enough.
Yes. Well, our memories are gone forever, sadly.
But I did develop a taste for notebooks.
I will say that prepared just the right way.
A notebook can be pretty delicious.
Oh, well, all right.
Now, that's that plucky American optimism that we like to hear.
And, you know, you could probably I bet there's like notebooks and journals
you could buy at this store, but they're probably prohibitively expensive.
You'd be better off at CVS and they would be more delicious.
You put them in a big pot and boil them.
That's for sure.
You over there, you should try it.
Boiling a notebook in a bloody paper of my time.
Young lady, don't worry about it.
Yes. One of your fancy notebooks would be delicious.
Mike, can I ask how was the glitter?
So, OK, very if you're a podcast fan,
you know that sometimes I'm a little worried when glitter comes into the picture
because I had a glitter bomb in the first City Walk Saga in the bathtub
and I was worried about the glitter going in my urethra.
Because of Kirsten's ears. Sorry.
Oh, no, it's OK.
I've heard the description of every body part from when the doctor came,
when the plague doctor came and dealt with my father.
So I've heard ad nauseam discussion of my father's urethra
and all the things that have gotten caught in there over the years during the war.
Sorry, we're good times are hard.
You're you're going to have to cut off your urethra.
You've got urethral gangrene.
Do they sell plague doctor mask size to the American girl plague doctor?
Father had mites in his urethra again.
So I see this and I'm looking at it and I I think what it was.
And I don't still don't know what the glitter in the bath bomb was
that definitely made its way in my urethra to some degree. Had to.
Not all of it.
It's not like it's sucking in the opposite way.
My urethra, that is.
But it had to some piece had to go in there.
But I don't know what that is.
This, I think this glitter was just sugar, I think.
Certain like, well, it was if they're given it to you to drink,
then it would also be safe to go into your urethra.
Well, right.
It did come. It came out of your urethra.
Well, think about that.
It absolutely came out of my urethra, but it was it changed.
It was not in its glitter, because I didn't notice like a sparkly
gallon of urine.
Not gallon. I don't pee a gallon.
I didn't have sparkle pee when I when I peed.
So it definitely, I think, was sugar.
And it just conveyed.
It was probably more in my poop than it was in my pee, I think.
But not enough.
You don't also you don't remember taking a shit that was glowing.
You know, like a rock candy shit is what you're describing.
You didn't go to the bathroom in the middle of the night
and then realize the toilet was illuminating the room.
And that did not happen.
My shit was like a light source.
Oh, we would have prayed for a shit that was a light source in the middle.
You'd run out of candle oil.
Yeah, you would eat all the candles.
If only a poop would light our way.
Yeah, so so I like I like the drinks, but like with Sprite, basically.
And then you would put this thing in the kind of yes, would like sort of color.
It wasn't so bright.
It could have been brighter.
So one of you had a Sprite.
One of you had a cranberry.
This is essentially.
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, you got it at a premium.
Yeah. So while this put us in the mood, by which I mean, the nap mood,
then we had a big long lunch with our children.
Yeah, who are look, I'll only speak for mine.
He's about as he's he's he likes restaurants, actually.
He's pretty good and patient at a restaurant.
But it's still, you know, but there hits a wall.
Can we go? Can we go?
Clock? Yeah, yeah, no, you could go.
It could go any time.
Basically, what I'm saying, I think we did not have the ideal
ages of children by a long shot to be at this place.
No, because he would have had as much fun, more fun
at a Denny's a mile away.
Yeah, no, I this my daughter is almost two doesn't really have much affection
for the American girl IP and doesn't have the patience to sit around a lot.
So, yeah, she wanted to get up.
Lindsay did a shift and then I would do a shift.
We just like followed her around and made sure she didn't like
jump into the kitchen, which is what she wanted to do.
And I had to snatch her away from doing it.
And she had a fit and a meltdown.
And she just wanted to ride in the elevator the whole time.
She just kept wanting to go to the elevator.
Which then you're like, so we we drove an hour to be in the elevator.
Yeah, I yeah, that's the anything that he had.
My son had a good time at this.
He definitely did.
But the things he had a good time with were like a fork
like talking, talking to people,
things that could happen at any restaurant that doesn't cause this.
Yeah, my daughter, she had fun playing.
There was like a big kitchen set downstairs in the store.
So she was playing with some other kids and she did like that.
So she had some fun there.
Was that available much closer?
If we just like set her loose in a Sears than the Sears and the Burbank bomb, perhaps.
Resurrected also a potential topic in the next.
Absolutely. But like, yeah, you need like, you know, you need like a seven, eight,
nine year old who is way steep, not way steeped, even just a little
maybe steeped in this lore.
And it's their birthday.
Yeah. And you go like, that's the prime kid audience, I think.
And let's be like, well, it's what we were around was like,
we've taken some friends here, like bring, bring friends to come
and to come do this and have your little, you know, your dainty tea items
and sing the birthday song.
Let me let me ask this question.
Did you feel in that room
we were surrounded by, you know, when you see online
a picture of a very specific type of all white girl group
that's like a bridal party and maybe it's like Massachusetts,
somewhere up there in Maine, the main area.
They all have like kind of furry boots on and a sweater.
There's a certain type of white lady that was everywhere in this room.
Yeah, there was.
Yeah. And I was like, we're that we're definitely outliers in this room,
even though we're white people.
There is this very specific type of concerned white citizens
Council five of like emanating, you're saying.
And this is my daughter.
And not that they said this, but like, this is my daughter's specialty.
And this is going to be very, this is very important.
And make sure that everything goes off without a hitch.
Yes, exactly. That's the vibe.
That's not I didn't hear that actually said.
But that was definitely what I was observing.
Maybe you maybe that maybe a lower price point to the clothes
that we're all wearing.
Absolutely. Yeah, yeah.
Yes. And I would just like I made eye contact with these people.
And I'm like, sometimes it's also just in general,
like I have to remind myself how old I am and go, oh, there's so
those are like parents over there.
And I go, these people are probably five years younger than me.
And I have to remind.
But I made eye contact with them.
And it just felt like, what are you like?
They could tell I didn't belong here.
I don't know if that's a judgy thing that I'm feeling.
What cobalt mind you even own? Right.
How have you been destroying the planet lately?
Yes, these are all like, what are you doing to help the wives of CEOs
in this room that we're taking their CEOs that are destroying the media companies?
We've all extensively worked for and try to work for. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Wives who were put in charge somewhere
in the wake in the succession and the mergers actually ran it into the ground.
Half a billion when Quibi went under.
So it worked out well for us.
We're glad it was better than it failed.
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't clock that so much.
But you were facing more people.
I kind of hit it. Yeah.
Yeah. I didn't have as many people in my field of vision.
Mainly, it was just like it was just a room I got tired of being in, I would say.
Yeah, a small room, like it aesthetically, but it also wasn't irritating enough.
Yes. And sorry, Jason.
Oh, I was going to say, what main courses did you do?
Well, let me just say real quick, what's interesting is the first half,
as far as just the atmosphere of this room, it did feel kind of loud in there.
Not like, I don't know, there was this weird loudness to it in a way.
I guess it was just people talking and it was a small room.
Half of the time they played hits from the 90s.
And then the other half, they played what I believe are like American girls songs.
Yeah. But I don't know why there was a shift.
I was confused by that. Yeah, you're right.
I want it all. If we're going to be here, why am I listening to all the small things?
Let's just go fully at it.
I want the most screechy, irritating songs.
Yeah. I want to rip off of all the small things.
Right. Right. That one of the characters.
The togetherness. The Tenny performance.
I would love to hear this. Be the place to hear the Tenny music.
The Tenny version of the punk pop.
Yeah. Yeah.
So like, yeah, not not not quite enough.
I totally agree.
Main courses.
I mean, let's shout out some of the things they have.
Fancy bow tie pasta, artisan, personal pizza.
Right. Best ever chicken tenders.
And I swear, when I was assessing, like, how is this going to be?
Is this something I want to bring my son to?
I I can't believe I can't believe myself sometimes.
I can't believe that we made it through the city walks that we've recently done.
A city walk saga, the most challenging one in a culinary
from a culinary standpoint.
And I'm still looking at this menu going, sounds pretty good.
How did it not occur to me that the food was going to be bad?
I'm there when it showed up.
I'm like, oh, right.
Damn it. I how am I still getting tricked?
You got tricked by this kind of thing.
This is very much a menu for children.
Or like if you saw this at the corner bakery, I was like, yeah, I need a quick.
Yeah. Quick cheese pizza. Quick.
Totally. Oh, turkey club with avocado. Great. Perfect.
I would accept this caprese sandwich at the airport.
It would be. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Wasn't terrible.
Yeah. And for yeah.
For my son, he's just eating chicken tenders and fries all the time.
So as far as he's concerned, they are the best ever.
Tied with 300 other versions he's had.
Yeah. I got the classic club. Fine. Yes. Fine. Yeah.
Airport fine. If it was like, yeah, it was.
You grabbed it at a grocery store to go and ate it in the car.
You'd go, oh, pretty good. Like maybe we've had worse.
We've definitely. Yeah, it's not.
But I did start to feel like the sodium bomb of it.
I said that to you somewhere between that and the sugar drink.
I'm like, yeah, I don't feel sick. I just don't feel good.
And also, here's where like, OK, maybe this is important to say.
Server. Great. Really nice.
Yeah, very good. Good experience there.
But from the from the Conan sketch for the from comedy about this,
I think I thought it'd be like, well, how about some stories?
How about some trivia? How about some riddles? Yes.
Well, that's yes, I thought more even in the Kirsten.
Like I thought there'd be more something.
I thought there'd be more stuff.
I thought that like, yes, then a bunch of weird, funny,
like a T-bone steak comes out for the dolls.
But essentially, you put your doll in that little chair,
and that is the end of the acknowledgement of the dolls.
Any interaction with the dolls is what you put into it or what your kids put into it.
And I tried to force some little moments of like, do you want to feed baby Pete?
I'm numb, numb. But we again, we could do that at home.
Yeah, nothing unique there.
At some point, we did get a little little teacup and saucer.
Well, it's OK. Finally, something has happened.
A little doll sized thing has come out.
And the only reason that happened is because our server, which was very nice,
like forced us to celebrate Lindsay's birthday, which is a few weeks old.
Really held our hand into is it a birthday to say, is it a birthday?
We're like, not really.
And she's like, are you sure it's not a birthday?
Because we were asking questions about crowns and stuff.
And that's so then we said, yes, Lindsay birthday.
She came over with the crowns and then gave us two little like teacups and saucers.
And that's yes, the only we wouldn't have had any sort of fun,
like doll activity if it weren't for this birthday hack.
Yeah, that's the way it happened.
So listeners, I guess know that it's got to be a birthday
or else you're not getting any little doll items.
No, there's no doll silverware.
Yeah, I know.
What do you mean?
There's not a little juice that's for them every day.
This seems like the bare thing you'd expect.
The base of this restaurant is I truly do want that.
And I want that. I want like a fish with extout eyes and a little lemon on the top.
I want like food that's fancier than what I'm eating in plastic form for those.
And she should get a little bill or like they should get a little bill at the end, too.
Yes, that would be funny that they and they pay separate.
You can decide if your grownups want to pay it and then great.
But, you know, or for Kirsten, a little paper stew, a little notebook stew.
Right. Yes.
If you saw fit.
Right, because you really don't want to smear human food on like one hundred
and fifty dollar doll.
No. Well, that's true.
On the loaner, certainly not.
You really really wouldn't feel.
They have a cleaning apparatus, though, I bet.
I bet they can clean those dolls fast.
Yeah, bottle Clorox and a dirty rag.
They're the doll back in the doll.
Yeah, but that's going to look that's going to erase her lips.
That's going to erase the color from her face.
She's not eating anyway.
I do want to.
Can I shout out something I saw on the Web site?
Real big now serving up sparkle.
You're piercing for girls in dolls.
And I got to say, I don't know that I would trust the cleanliness to.
First off, you think that they're using the same equipment on the doll
that they use on a human?
No, I don't think that. No, don't be ridiculous.
I I'm going to say, first off, for that doll,
you're sliding into a three hole punch or a screwdriver and a hammer.
Like you don't need to pay for a doll ear piercing.
That's how my ears were pierced.
Yeah, that's right.
Why, in my day, screwdriver and a hammer.
We just got an angry mule and put an apple right on top of our doll's earlobe.
But I feel like even Claire's in my ear is a little more
cladly, I feel like.
I'm sure it's clean.
What's the clean issue?
Claire? No, I just feel like you go to there's a lot of kids touching toys.
There's a nasty restaurant.
Touch the equipment that pierces kids ears.
It just seems too close to me.
I feel like even you want to at least go to a piercing
pagoda or are those still around?
First of all, I will say from what I can tell, places in the mall
where you can get your ears pierced, I don't really know.
But like, I don't think Claire's is like the.
No, of course, Claire's is fine.
Yes, sanitized for your protection.
Twenty one year old piercing your ears.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
I actually I think this being a higher end location,
I think you're in a better situation.
OK, I do. I do.
I mean, look, I mean, I saw the quality of the salon.
I don't know if the salon is also where the ear piercing occurs.
Probably. But, you know, but I actually
the salon is a high production value area.
Yeah. And if that is any indicator, then yeah, I don't know.
Your your concerns are valid and your ideas of how to pierce
the doll's ear are correct and inventive.
But the cleanliness is not one issue I'd be super worried about.
I don't think it must be easy to pierce ears.
I think it is.
Yeah, I think it's just rubbing alcohol in the leg.
You just go right through and the gun.
I don't think it's that different from all on the gun.
I'll do it.
Chug, chug, chug.
Somebody get me a gun. I'll pierce your ear.
No, the piercing gun, not like a nine millimeter.
I didn't call for a nine millimeter.
I call for a piercing gun.
And I said, I'll pierce your right now.
Oh, OK. It's a fine.
Well, that's a good also a topic for next month.
If you want me to pierce Jason's ear.
Yeah. But if you suggest this, the title in the poll has to be
if Jason thinks it's so easy, let Mike pierce Jason's ear.
I don't I don't mean to speak down.
I think the professionals have very, you know, it's a complicated
craft like everyone else.
The teenager at the mall.
Yeah.
Making money and that's the bar of professional.
I think I've had enough needles and infusions and everything under the sun.
Yeah, but this is for fun.
This is for fun.
Oh, this is for fun, is it?
I see the guy who there was a guy who my friend wanted to get his ear pierced
in Wisconsin by the Wisconsin Dells.
And there was a guy who had a tattoo and I apologize for being so vulgar.
He had a tattoo with a mermaid with a penis in her mouth on his arm.
And this was the guy.
This was the guy who was piercing people's ears regularly.
And he was probably great at it.
Let's be honest.
Well, yeah, I'm just saying it's not like we do like you have to go to eight
years of medical school to pierce someone's ear.
I don't know if I would trust that mermaid.
If it's a siren, likely calling you to the rocks.
And possibly if if there's violent intentions, maybe
snapping off that penis entirely.
Oh, that's what he's getting at.
That was a question.
Do you remember if the penis was attached to a body or just its own thing?
I feel like it was like part of the body.
OK, OK.
Unless we totally misread or missed like we did with something totally.
She had like a cigar in her mouth.
Well, then maybe. All right.
So if it was attached to a body, then that dirty mermaid was probably in the process
of snapping it off. Very possible.
Yeah. Stay away from her.
It was a siren. Jason's right.
He knows that he knows them from literature.
Yeah. For the honesty.
You all. Yeah. You only and you only know the Mario Odyssey.
Not the game, but the choose your own adventure book where you write
the original characters or equivalents.
Yeah. Sirens often.
I believe I heard that due to the sea
madness that would get in people's brains, they would think they were seeing
sirens calling me to the rocks.
In reality, it was likely like sea lions screaming.
Wait, it was a hallucination.
So you're saying in a practical way, in a reality, in the reality,
people would report seeing a beautiful mermaid.
But they think what it was, they saw sea lions, they had sea lions.
Yes, my father thought he saw 10 sirens on the ship from Sweden to Minnesota.
Yes, exactly.
And then he went over to give them all little kisses.
But they were all sea lions and they took pieces out of his skin
with their teeth and their fangs.
Oh, my God. He ended up just like marked up.
Yes, he's cut up like that Batman character.
Mr. Zaz. Mr. Zaz. Mr. Zaz. Yes.
That's a care Jason told me about him.
He puts a hash mark for every person he kills, his body full of hash marks.
Yes. But he married one of the sea lions eventually.
What? Wait, is the whole I don't mean to propose this.
Is your father faking his illness so that he can die,
quote unquote, disappear and then go back to those rocks
and live with the sexy sea lions forever?
He keeps sending all his money to the sea lions.
He keeps saying that there's that there are his wives.
The money for your food and medicine, Kirsten.
He signed the deed to our house over to them as well.
And I'm not going to get anything when he passes.
I did not know the back story for Kirsten was
her father is a Mr. Zaz type and her mother appears to be the sea lion.
Stepmother. That's what he wants is to. Oh, my God.
Yeah. You've read you've read crazier things in your books, I'm sure.
You're earning so all your your little dolly is going to end up
in the via the will given split up between eight sea lions.
That's right. Who may be beautiful, but what do they need with a dolly
kill with eight sea lions?
That's a word Jason taught me.
Well, I'm just trying to explain.
Jason's the Jason's the American girl of, let's say, twenty, twenty two.
He knows all the phrases from two years ago.
He represents that year.
He said he was going sicko mode.
And now I understand what it means.
I haven't gotten up to Sabrina Carpenter yet.
Guys, can you look at your phones now, assuming that this has gone through?
As I talk about the salon, I wanted to bring this up, something that I clocked
when I was in here before being forced to be here by Club Three.
This is the main piece of artwork on the wall of the salon.
You guys both have this? I do. Yeah.
Oh, sunglasses.
Well, do you know, do you look at all the in this big photo montage?
Do you realize what you're looking at?
What all these American girls are doing? Yes.
It's kind of well, Jason.
Are these movie scene recreative?
Yeah, I'm realizing what some of these are.
You got it. Yeah.
So call out call out what you see.
And let's see if we can place all of them.
I think we got nine E.T.
E.T. Sound of music.
Yes. La La Land, La La Land,
all with Little Doll, Back to the Future and La La Land for the listeners.
Is that is one of these a simple man?
This are you talking about?
Which one the two in on the bottom going from the left?
I think I know what this is.
But Mike, do you want to venture a guess? Is that up?
I think it's up. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
This is just this is it's the little dolls recreating.
That's a good guess.
I it was not a simple man.
The Cohen brother.
I know I was thinking of a movie with Julianne Moore, a Todd Fields movie, I think.
Oh, my God. That's even weird.
It is pretty weird.
There's Bueller.
Paratrap. Moonrise Kingdom.
That's what I am wondering.
Is that what that is?
That was my first thought.
Moonrise Kingdom.
Yeah, there's a for the listener.
There's a little there's a boy.
Well, somebody else look up Moonrise Kingdom proper while I describe it.
We'll see if we're right.
But it's a like Boy Scout doll with a canteen and supplies.
And he's holding up a map.
And there's a girl in like a plane girl planes.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, planes girl planes girl planes girl dress in a blue basket.
And I mean, that that's what it is.
It's Moonrise Kingdom.
That's the first thing I thought, too.
Yeah, because all like, OK, you know, anything like this, where we're like,
think about it, Universal Studios, you go to the Hello Kitty store
and you see a Hello Kitty recreation of Back to the Future.
Yeah, I think, too.
These ones follow.
And then you get La La Land in there for something recent and up.
And but Moonrise Kingdom with dolls.
What? That's so weird.
And also, that movie is kind of a creepy little movie with its little romance.
And now we're going even younger with these.
I don't know. How do they land on Moonrise Kingdom?
It's the sunglasses almost famous.
Yes. Yeah. And that's weird, too, because we're looking.
Yeah, we're looking at a doll Penny Lane who got traded to doll
sweet water, still water for a case of doll beer.
Well, yes, that's a very good point.
Isn't there a part where this where this particular doesn't this particular
doll overdose at some point?
Yes, I think that's right.
Overdose on glitter fizz.
The also weird thing about it is just that like all these other movies,
though, are at least are like very popular.
Moonrise Kingdom is not pretty.
Yes. My you know, successful for him.
Sure. His most successful.
You buy all other metrics.
All these other movies are insanely more popular.
Yeah. The Moonrise Kingdom.
Yes. Yeah. Right.
Ferris Bueller. Yeah.
We're leaps and bounds. Right.
How did they land at Moonrise?
That's fascinating. So so strange.
Yeah, they didn't do the
they didn't do a doll Richie Tenenbaum shaving himself in the mirror.
And then things coming to a.
Yeah, that's good.
That would be there was a discussion, I bet.
If there's a there's a Wes Anderson fan,
like, should we dress them up like Margot and whatever his character's name is?
Would you say Richie? Yeah.
Yeah. There was a discussion like on them on the bus or something.
Oh, doll pirates going after Steve Zissou.
Right. Yeah.
That's weird. Yeah.
I'm I honestly I was going to bring that up.
Like, I'm confused. Am I?
I was so dumb when I saw this.
I thought it was Moonrise Kingdom.
And now I realize it was Moonrise Kingdom. Yeah.
Inexplicable. So weird.
We'll post this, I think, somewhere so you can feel mad as well.
Lane kind of makes sense because it's L.A.
Sure.
And for five seconds, it was the best picture of the year.
Right. Right. That's right.
Doll Moonlight would have been a weird one, too.
So anyway, we didn't really experience the the salon, the food.
I don't know. I mean, did that sort of close out?
Then I don't know.
It took a while for everything to play out, at which point
a manager, somebody came over,
I think just because the other tables were being dealt with.
He could tell it was like taking a little while.
And he just gave my son a full, unopened package of Hot Wheels.
Not American Girl Hot Wheels.
No, regular Hot Wheels.
I think this is part of the Mattel family at some point, I believe.
And I thought that was so nice and so sweet.
And the only thing that threw me off about it
is that he was just wearing a regular shirt and no name tag.
And I was like, do you work here?
Did you go take that from the store and bring it over?
I it really threw me with apologies to the guy.
This is a very nice gesture.
I was I was just unnerved in this, like, hang on.
What are you, though?
Why do you if a guy is walking up to me in this restaurant
representing the restaurant, I want him to be in the gaudiest
pink and black and white. Yes. And
and for him to be have an extremely grating voice
when a really normal man walked up right perhaps with an untucked shirt.
Am I making that up?
I wasn't there, remember?
She was gone. We were gone.
So it was so nice.
But I don't know. I figured out what I was thinking of
in that picture, in that thing.
I was thinking of the movie poster for
Uneducation starring Carey Mulligan and Peter Sarsgaard.
Wow.
And I was quite I was really wondering why they chose that one.
Why did they do American Girl and Education?
Why do young girls need an education?
Mm hmm.
I it is about a young woman dating an older man.
And I'm like, they that shouldn't be in the American Girl Store.
Wow. Yeah, I didn't see his manager.
Why did they do Doll Far From Heaven?
That's the other one.
I almost was trying to pull the word far from heaven.
The scene from up is him with the wife who dies, too.
So it's like that's in a montage.
That invokes sadness immediately seeing that picture.
That's from midway through what becomes the saddest montage of all time.
Yeah, I didn't see this manager.
I just came back and there were Hot Wheels on the table.
We didn't get Hot Wheels.
I was a little upset by that. Yeah.
But I don't know.
And then there was I've never saw it again.
There was not a bored girl at that table at that time.
Right. So this you didn't get it.
It was just a representative from five below a few doors down,
trying to get you come in, look around it.
Were you just while you were sitting in your bed looking at all the stores
that you could have gone to if you were there?
No, I was just kind of guessing because most malls seemed to have a five below
somewhere close by now.
Sure.
The let's talk about the desserts, which again,
and we're we're thinking and Jason at home is thinking,
ah, moose, the rarest bird imported from far Europe.
Yeah, that can be achieved here.
I've only heard of one person having it.
It's a delicacy.
And they were far away, the richest kings in America.
That was a kid.
That was the king who kicked you out of the country.
Yes, exactly.
And that's the only person I ever heard of.
Go find go find somewhere colder to live.
Delicacy. You talk.
There is a theme park in action, because that was like a go to
at cafeteria style restaurants, Disney and Busch Gardens,
King Dominion at the end of the line.
There was always like, oh, a little thing of chocolate moose.
Don't mind if I do.
But isn't moose everywhere?
Well, that's this world where moose is only an American girl and theme park.
Looking back, I was like, oh, it was at all the theme parks
because it was incredibly inexpensive to make and of that.
They probably just dumped power and whole milk in a vat and then scooped it out.
But I loved it.
I love my vat moose.
Don't put it anywhere near a piercing machine.
It'll contaminate the ears.
You need to get a vat, a home vat, and make your own moose.
We did get a big pot, like a big pot for Christmas.
So I could start making.
OK, getting closer.
That's getting close, but not a vat.
It's a home vat, you know.
Maybe Kirsten could use it as a bathtub.
Yes, or a house.
Well, it does have a lid.
Turn it over. A locking lid.
Maybe I could grow old in there.
It's like an upgrade from your life now, yes.
The moose comes at the end
and it comes in little flower pots with little cloth flowers that you stick in the top.
I saw a video of, I don't know,
from eight to ten years ago where this moose comes to the table,
maybe at the Chicago one.
Yeah, this used to be so much bigger.
Of course it did.
Now these flower pots come and I don't it's it was a struggle.
Correct. It was so hard to eat this to get the width of a standard sized spoon.
Yeah. Into to fit entirely into the pot.
It was wild.
I don't know what when this changed, but it felt like such
because every time you would go and put your spoon in to pull,
like you couldn't just get a good scoop on the spoon.
It would knock all this different like crumb chocolate stuff.
Like it would knock it all over everywhere.
It was maybe dirt everywhere.
Yes, it was more Oreo dirt cup style.
So, Jason, in your pursuit of moose, you wouldn't have really gotten in here.
I wouldn't have liked that.
No, you would have said it's taken away from the moose.
Yeah, you would have done it like a shot to get all of it in
because I feel like half of it ended up on the table.
It was trying to scoop it out.
I would say these kids were pretty well behaved as far as mess goes.
Yeah. These for and under children we were with.
Yeah. Not until the struggle with the flower pots was their mess on the table.
Yes. Were there worms? Were there gummy worms in the dirt?
That's ridiculous. There wouldn't have been room.
There was not the diameter.
We're talking like like this.
Yeah, flower pots narrow as they go down.
You don't want a full size.
Like even a teaspoon would be too big to get.
What do you mean to scoop out moose?
Yeah, I'm just saying they're like thimble.
We did not have any special spoon to work with here.
We had no straw issue spoon.
Yeah. And the spoon did not fit into the.
I understand. We we talk about Disney all the time. Right.
The show. We know how it is when these things,
when the perks are cut and cut and cut until there is no more anymore.
That being said, just pure mechanics.
You can't get these flower pots too much smaller.
They're going to be smaller than the spoon.
That's also you're not giving us all size spoons also,
which would be more fun as part of the experience.
Well, and also they had done such the cinnamon rolls or whatever were fine.
But there was at least a couple different options for the appetizers.
So I thought, oh, well, when they do the desserts, surely
there will be something on that scale.
This couldn't have been funnier and wronger of my thinking.
And you're sudden and you're like, well, why order an add on dessert?
That would be a plus up. I've already paid my twenty seven dollars.
And I'm getting dessert as part of it.
I'd be foolish to get more dessert on top of.
And then when you see what you get, this is hardly a dessert course.
That's really like dangerous.
I feel like children would like they can't get a spoon in there.
They're sticking their hand. They're sticking their fingies.
Try to scoop out that moose. That seems like chaos.
And then they go straight to the piercing machine.
Touch it with the and suddenly they have permanent
Oreo crumbs in their ear forever.
Well, look, we've all been there.
The salon.
In the many episodes and we've said, Jason, come on,
get the Oreos out of your ears.
We mean it literally. It's a condition.
I'm trying.
Medical science hasn't progressed that fast.
The salon where you can get your nails and hair done
and your dolls shit also done up, right?
Doll shit. Your dolls.
Yeah. Yes, my shit can get done up.
I don't even want to know about your century old shit diseases, Kirsten.
Yes, the doctor would examine it and they would do them up,
I guess they would say.
Yeah. When they would examine them and find the different creatures living.
Inside.
And they and they'd say, oh, look, good for you.
A new pet. I think take care of this worm.
Long extinct, so do take care of it.
But I think he meant them this in a more colloquial way,
like a colloquial way. Is that right?
Yes, correct.
Uh, yeah, there's well, so yeah, we we close out of here.
We had downstairs.
I think I think kids end up having a lot of fun in the downstairs zone.
Uh, you know, stop by the salon, but you didn't.
Well, you didn't treat Kirsten to.
I thought we were going to get something.
And then like I was I was just in such a haze for many, many reasons.
I was just like, if she's not we almost bought our daughter something
and then she dropped it and we're like, she didn't want that bad.
OK, good. Yeah.
So like when they were like, I guess we could get something.
And then I'm like, I don't even know where to begin here.
Kirsten is still dressed sort of sort of modern, but I'm like,
I feel like I'm I'm dropping 150 if I'm dropping money here.
She's not worth it.
She's right here. She's hearing she's not worth it.
What do you mean?
Well, I can get some on Amazon, probably a good knockoff thing for her.
And she won't know the difference.
Like a buying American girl dupes on Amazon.
Yeah, I could buy her some sort of knockoff stuff.
And plus also like she she's similar scale to my quarter scale Ninja Turtles.
So at the very least, I could give her like a guitar to play
or a sigh to wield.
Oh, that would have been most helpful during the wars.
That would have been great.
A way to fight back.
Way to fight back.
Finally, do you have throwing stars as well?
Yeah, yeah, actually.
And a pizza and a big pizza.
Be a good doll, dad, and at least get her a her size shredder helmet.
OK, yeah.
Which I assume transforms the voice as well.
It's me, Kirsten.
That'll be good if I fall in the water during one of the long expeditions
across the oceans and a shark tries to eat me.
The shark will break its teeth on my shredder helmet.
Maybe scrape itself on the pads.
You get the spiked pads.
At the very least, I'll injure it on the way down while it tries to kill me.
Well, you're sinking under all that shredder paraphernalia.
That's right.
Do they have any very modern like like influencer doll or podcaster doll?
I don't know specifically if they have like a selfie stick,
but that's the vibe for some of it.
So while there's girls of the year, which inspired the fizz drink.
Right. And I, you know, I don't know if that means that they are twenty
twenty four girls. Yeah.
Not totally clear on that.
The most fun that I had well, and my son,
I'd say the most that we bonded over this experience was
going to the
there's like there was an ice cream truck
as one of the accessories, a five hundred dollar ice cream truck
branded to Jenny's ice cream.
They made a deal with the specific brand.
Ah, the Listeria.
Oh, is it? Yeah.
Well, that's a joke, but they all of them, I feel like Bluebell,
I think, in a Listeria.
Apparently, if you work with cold dairy, you have a Listeria outbreak.
I have a chronic Listeria infection that won't go away.
She knows.
You have more you have more Listeria than than blood.
That's right. My heart is full of Listeria.
It pumps Listeria in and it pumps Listeria out.
Jenny's, I think, is also the brand.
Remember Nancy Pelosi's ice cream fridge?
Remember, she had a separate fridge for ice cream.
I do remember that on January 6th.
Did somebody poop in there and then like, oh, it's the famous fridge.
I know what I'm going to do.
That's what that guy broke.
Right. He broke it with a hammer to try to get the ice cream.
And then did a very careful switcheroo.
She'll be none the wiser.
Yeah. I mean, to that end, I.
Yeah, the most fun I had is my son is playing with the truck
and then there's like ice cream scoops kind of around.
And then just in the truck is a loose scoop of chocolate.
And just out of context, not in a dish or a bowl, just a chocolate
ice cream scoop did just look like poop.
And I had baby Pete with me and baby Pete's pants come down very easily.
So I was really having fun making it look like he just took a dump on that.
I saw that. Yeah.
And my boy liked it, too.
And we laughed and we you know what we end it like it was a good time.
So I thank the listener for giving us a good time.
However, it was the same good time that we would have had
if we just went to the store and didn't find anything.
Of course, we had eaten lunch somewhere else.
Yes. If your kid loves American Girl or if you liked it,
maybe a worth a trip, but maybe not just for the themed entertainment fan.
That's what I would say. Yeah. Yeah.
Just an enthusiast of themed entertainment, maybe not not for them.
And if you look, if you went into this thinking,
oh, boy, those three dorks are going to I we got them
to go to the place for little girls and be creeps at the place for little girls.
And that's what this episode is going to be.
And I'm going to laugh at that. Yeah.
Then I say the Club 3 poll is a chance to let's go backwards.
Let's make Jason go back there by himself and see if he just earnestly likes the meal.
I would prefer not to.
Everything you described, it sounded like from, you know,
from getting your your rare moose to an Old Navy stop after.
I think you would have had the time of your life.
You need to get the food to go.
Oh, yeah. Do they have prefix to go?
Is there a go? Oh, Jason Post made an American Girl Cafe again.
So it's your it's your now thirty dollars just to get just to the entry fee.
And the taxes and fees are astronomical.
Yeah. Well, and then to Postmates all the way from Burbank,
her century city, by a reasonable dinner time.
Yeah. A thirty dollar
barely edible pretzel burger food is not even cold.
It's like dry ice cold.
Like it's dangerous to touch. Yeah.
Well, still an interesting time had
hope everybody had fun.
You survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club Three.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
Kirsten, thank you for being here.
Thank you so much for joining us as well.
Mr. Jason, I'm very excited to learn about your new song.
You were telling me about Hooray for Hollywood.
Yes, it's a celebration.
Kirsten, you appear to be bleeding from the nose and ear.
So I would get that looked at.
Yes. No, that's normal. That's OK.
If I was bleeding from anywhere else, that would be a problem.
Oh, I see.
I want you to meet my father, though, Jason.