FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcasts may contain
accidental testosterone checks,
bad food that scarred an entire city,
podcast host blood feuds,
and spoiler alerts for a restaurant?
Ah, but not just any restaurant, it's Casa Benita,
the greatest restaurant in the world!
On today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
a podcast about theme parks
that might be heading for its
most sincere episode.
Whoa!
Wow!
That's my joke, at least on my part.
I am Scott Gardner, who I think is
I'm going to be talking to,
given what we're talking about
and what I got to experience.
Any jokes or jabs or cynicisms
are going to have to come from Mike Carlson.
Okay, I'm here. Will I cry on this episode?
From hearing a tale?
Well, see, I don't know, sincerity
I think comes in a few. It doesn't mean
I don't think I'm...
I came close to tearing up
in one part of this experience, I actually did.
I don't think it's going to cause tears
for anyone else, such as Jason Sherrod and I.
More sincere than the Ocean City boardwalk.
That was pretty sincere.
Tearing up, naming dots pastries, you know?
You were lit up in a way.
I was lit up.
I didn't even get talking about so many
Thetlissaka subs, all these wonderful places.
You've been pacing around for the last week
going, I'm going to find a reason to say
seven more of these restaurant names.
I will insert them somewhere, come hell or high water.
You were more jacked up than talking about
Toon Lagoon or Marvel Superhero Island.
You were so revved up.
Did you start punching walls and stuff?
I did start punching walls.
I was jacked up enough.
I took care of a lot of outstanding
medical bills that I hadn't gotten around to paying.
Wow, just a flurry. They're flying around the house.
Just a tornado and then they're all done.
Writing personal checks.
Just five or six personal checks.
I'm going to take care of it until they stop bothering me.
If you didn't hear last week's
episode about the Ocean City Boardwalk
with Alan McCloud, Alan talked about
that's an area that you grew up with Jason
and have a lot of nostalgia for.
Alan was talking about how it's new nostalgia for him.
It feels so classic that it made him feel
like he grew up with this place.
That's how I feel coming out of this experience
with Casa Bonita.
It's as if it implanted memories.
Some of the teariness that I'll talk about
is the emotion I felt experiencing.
Wow, I'm going to do this thing finally.
I'm getting this entirely from a TV show.
Which is just a credit to what these guys have done.
On the note of that TV show,
I was thinking how, given that South Park
is a big part of what we're talking about,
that I should perhaps rip off another podcast
and say hi-de-ho to Clifford Nation.
We are today talking about Casa Bonita
per their own copy, but this would also be my review.
The greatest restaurant in the world.
A staple of the Denver area since 1974,
attributed in a 2003 episode of South Park
and today owned and recently rescued
and renovated by South Park creators
Trey Parker and Matt Stone.
Here's a question at the top.
Is this a me thing?
Am I the only one of the three of us
who's had a lingering obsession with this place?
Or have you guys also dreamed of it?
Have you followed some of this story
of Trey and Matt's purchase and renovation
of this restaurant?
Oh, I followed it for sure.
I do remember in 2003 this episode coming out.
Yes, that's a big one for me.
I think the story can emanate from that episode
because it's certainly where my awareness of it began.
It's kind of like right when I started watching South Park,
I wasn't into it in the early days.
I found it really abrasive and I was kind of late
getting the memo that, oh no, it's actually really smart
and clever and great stories and how sharp it had become.
It was season seven that they did this episode
and there had been a wave of episodes
that were getting a lot of press
for being so current and satirical
and they'd begun that production process
of doing it with only six days before air
so it can be relevant in a way
like only SNL can otherwise.
That was the hype of South Park at the time.
Then they do this Casa Bonita episode
which has nothing to do with anything.
This is not topical.
This was not about George Bush or the Iraq War or anything.
This was just pure silliness with the kids
that heightens to this crazy degree.
This was my episode of the show
regardless of it being about a themed experience
although I'm sure that helped.
I watched it too at the time
and I thought it was fake. I didn't know it was real.
I thought it was made up a place
and I liked all the specifics of it but I didn't know
and I don't think at the time I looked into it.
That's kind of my journey with it as well
because it's so hyperspecific what they go into
and you just are wondering
did they just invent the craziest most specific thing
that a kid would be obsessed with
and a horrible kid like Hartman would be
this place that would drive him to commit fraud
and endanger and entrap his friend.
Like cliff divers.
That didn't seem like a place. That didn't seem real.
It's so specific that you think maybe it has to be real
but how can that be real? What do you mean?
There's a Mexican restaurant with cliff divers.
I'll start getting into that but let me just say
at the very top
and if I haven't done this already
sometimes we like to build suspense
with our reviews of an experience
if you missed this I got to go to Casa Benita
in Denver a couple weeks ago
and sometimes we like to kind of like well did we like it
and actually oh and then I don't know then it made me sick
and it was a terrible experience.
I cannot do any building of suspense in this episode.
This place fucking rules. It was so great.
I kind of already spoiled it on Twitter. I was so high
off of this place. I can't pretend
and part of the reason I want to get that out right at the top
is it's very complicated to get into Casa Benita
as I discovered and you know
our episodes go a little while. If this is 90 minutes, if it's 2 hours
I don't want you to wait that long.
Listener if you have any thought that you want to go to Casa Benita
get it going right now. Don't wait till the end.
Don't wait till the plugs. Go to Casa Benita
Denver right now and sign up for the
mailing list and eventually maybe in like
9 months to a year. It's going to be a while.
But I don't want you, you know you add 2 hours on top of that
that's an extra. You might miss an entire night with that.
So go there. You guys too. If you have any thought
I'll forgive. If you guys want to stop talking for a couple minutes
go sign up for that waiting list.
I would encourage it.
You know it's complicated. It's weird. Then you have to like
claim it and then buy plane tickets after the fact if you don't live there.
If you're anywhere close, if you're drivable
get on it right now. Let me just, I just want to like
hype this place up as much as possible right at the top here.
Yeah that's, I mean I wonder how long that'll last. How aggressive
it'll be for it. Maybe for at least a decade. I don't know.
I don't know. It could be. I don't know.
I just saw, now I'm getting algorithmed like
local Denver news stories about
what's the deal and how do we get in. And I think maybe they're even
maybe considering right now still like previews technically.
Oh really? Yeah I think possibly
and I think they might change this process and make it a little easier
to get into sort of soon. But
either way I think you want to play it safe.
You're gonna need, wherever you're listening to this episode
you're going to need to travel to Denver.
If you don't do anything else, if you stay there one night and turn around
and do it all in one day the way I did San Jose a while back.
Just whatever, however it's got to work for you.
Get it done. Yeah. Get to Denver. This thing is
exemplary. It sounds great. I would love to go.
Yeah I think you know if you honestly
if you start looking for like family vacations
that's kind of where it came from a little bit was like
well we want to get him used to planes because we don't have to travel
anywhere to go visit family but he thinks planes are neat.
So we wanted to give him a fun little plane ride. It's why we went to San Jose
last year. We thought well Denver's a little bit further
and then we can go to Casa Bonita
but then a bunch of other complications happened.
Highly highly encouraged and also
listeners to motivate you
to go to that website and sign up right now there are 600,000
people ahead of you. Jesus Christ.
And you add, yeah that's the stats.
Are they only open on weekends right now?
No I don't know if it's every
night. I was there on a Thursday.
It might not be every day of the week.
I'm honestly not sure about that but yeah that might limit it
a little bit. And no walk-ins I'm assuming.
I can't imagine. I mean unless
it is like a you know like what happened
when we went to Blue Bayou
and like there was a lot of stress
about like wait you gotta book that six months in advance and then
Magic Mitch just pulled it right then and there.
Well didn't he just say hey can I get in?
No there was like a I think it was like checking
it might have been Kyle I'm not sure. Somebody pulled
it like Mitch just saying like come on
let's just try let's try and it did work.
He does have a he has a magic in that regard.
So anyways
as kind of we were saying the South Park episode
November 12th 2003 season seven
episode 11 kind of
where this place was popularized was where
a lot of listeners might know it. It's probably where all three of us know it
from. Let me play a quiet low
quality version of the of the scene
that maybe made a lot of people first aware
of this place. Apologies for the quality.
That's that pretty much.
Yeah I mean before you even like gotten
into the story just that like hyper description
from Cartman is very like
what are we talking about? The Disneyland of Mexican restaurants.
The Disneyland of Mexican restaurants get like Cliffjumpers
and Black Park's Cave and it's like such a perfect thing for him to be
I know it all about. I also want to say
as I play that clip that I'm going to try my best to say
Casa Bonita throughout this episode
but please understand that for 20 years
this has been in my head in Cartman's voice
Casa Bonita, Casa Bonita
so it's hard to unscramble that
I also noticed in an interview
with NBC News about the opening of this place
that Trey Parker also calls it Casa Bonita
well that makes sense
he does the voice is
whitefied in his head so I'll try my best
but that clip has been in my head for so long
and that song wanting to feel as excited as he is
by this place
so the story becomes that he's not
Cartman doesn't get to go
because Butters has been invited instead
the long suffering Butters and this is one of the great
Butters torture episodes where
in order to get to go to Casa Bonita
Cartman convinces Butters
that there is a meteor on the way to Earth
and he has to stay down in a bomb shelter
and later in a refrigerator
with a broken off handle in order to survive
the apocalypse he has to stay there
at least till the end of the week once this Casa Bonita event
has passed
at the end of the episode they arrive
it's finally time for Casa Bonita
and the police show up there after Cartman
before trapping Butters and
frauding the city
and Cartman then has to do a speed run
through everything in the restaurant
and this is one of these just delightful
like getting to watch him as quickly as possible
all of the many fun attractions that this restaurant
apparently has again we're all watching this we don't know if it's real yet
or not but it's so like
wait a minute so they've got like a whole indoor city
and there's like a little bridge when you come in and then there's
a puppet show and there's cliff divers
and there's black rights cave eww scary
and sopapias whatever
sopapias are I didn't know about sopapias before this
I didn't know about sopapias no
okay cause that sounds like something you would pull out in an episode
and we go what are you talking about and you go well you never had sopapias before
we had them on the show all the time I don't think I've ever had sopapias
period sure I could have seen it
this is not something I have seen at a restaurant
personally yeah and in the
in the episode you can't really tell what they are cause it's
Cruddy South Park animation so they're just like little
white things I don't know what I've wondered
for decades what sopapias are that's probably my
favorite part of it where Cartman's in a mad dash
and the police are after him and he sits down and he
raises a flag manically up and down
and says sopapias is sopapias place and
I'm just like what is what could have
possibly inspired this level of mania
from from the guys
like I mean well I mean and just the question of is this place
real or not that's really the big thing as you were saying Mike
that you wondered at the time
so I feel like I remember some
moment of discovering yes it is real and there were YouTube
videos you could watch of the
pre-COVID pre-Trey Matt and Trey
Takeover
so real stuff about the place founded by
a guy named Bill Waugh who is just like
I forget if he's from Colorado or not
but he had just traveled to Mexico
and fallen in love with the culture and the food and
and all the specific like subcultures
Puerto Vallarta and Acapulco and he wanted to bring
all of these cultures and his travels
to America in a bigger way than just a
regular Mexican restaurant so he starts this chain
and it was a chain there were a ton of these
let's say Oklahoma City
Little Rock Tulsa
then this one in Lakewood Colorado
Fort Worth kind of briefly
so there were a ton of these I don't think all of them had
all of the bullshit
but at the base it was just like a fun especially
well themed place
first one and then Denver's 74
I was talking to
Josh Fadum about this who
grew up in Oklahoma and he had fond memories
of it he raved he didn't know any of the other stuff
didn't know that it was on South Park didn't know about the Takeover
but his memories were so fond
and he just voluntarily like so papillas
the so papillas are so great
this holds alright so and I think it was a big big birthday party place for him
he also mentioned a place called Crystal's Pizza
which I guess was also in Tulsa
or maybe Oklahoma City
this place do a Google image on this this looks incredible
this is like a weird like Victorian turn of the century
it looks like a casino for kids it looks nuts
it's a pizza place but like arcade
and a make your own Sunday bar and a cartoon theater
where they would just be playing Pinocchio or whatever
and it's great for kids but apparently it's like
became like the middle school make out spot in the later
senior years of the place
this that's Josh mentioned that independently
it was just like similar place started by the same guy
Bill Waugh so he was just this entrepreneur
of like passed away
passed away yeah like maybe
five years ago or so
so this guy like clearly brightened
Oklahoma and Colorado for
tons of kids but especially with this
and especially with this location which is built out of a former department store
52,000 square feet
the best and biggest of any of them
the main crazy feature being a 30 foot tall
waterfall and lagoon
with cliff divers with cliff diver shows
every 20 minutes to half an hour
you ever seen cliff diving anywhere
I like only know this from themed bullshit like this
or the Mexico boat ride I mean I've seen like
Instagram like you know when you're surfing through
Instagram they show you random things and I'll see some sort of like
extreme sports I'll see like bike guys that have like the
POV of like a little camera on their bicycling
mountain sure sure I see stuff like this
but I don't see a cliff I don't seek out
cliff diving I just see it on accident
algorithm wants me to see it
and I'll say okay I'll take a look at this
I've seen footage of like people on
vacation doing it
I feel like like maybe smaller scale
there's one video I feel like I always come across
on the internet with a dog who can
cliff dive like a little dog who like
his owner like hauls him from the water
or so and it runs along and like jumps
out and into the water
wow wow okay that's good
it's too bad that's just like a dog that's out there not something they can charge
tickets for yeah Jason is that a cliff would you want
to because you're a height miser oh that's right would you want
is the water part of it I think the water part
of it is too much you'd rather have a bungee cord
attached to your leg yeah
you would bring back up because I guess
if I had little floaties on or something
or an inner tube it would the impact would probably
deflated oh yeah I don't think little floaties
hold up when they smacked against water
yeah they would not hold whatsoever yeah
I also I never particularly liked
diving into even like pools
I like jumping into pools but like
diving I was never terribly good at I can't do it for
shit I've always been awful at that yeah I always smack
something yeah yeah yeah just a big flap
belly leg yeah it's
it's just yeah just nailing my penis
on that dive yeah nothing like when you're
holding a whole dick flap right on top of it yeah
big hard flappy bottom body of water I wasn't able to
dive until I started backyard wrestling in high school
and then I was able to dive off of the low diving board
I don't know if I might have reverted I might be too scared to do it
now I don't know can you go off the top rope or did you
well we didn't have a real ring oh okay
so it was like we would go off the top rope with like
what with an elbow no no like
like a frog splash yeah
swan ton bomb
well I have been in a ring in the last ten years
and I think I did do a swan ton bomb off
the top rope but it was there was a mat also on the ring
oh okay so I didn't do it on the canvas a little unforgiving
that canvas it sure is
you're telling me I took a shoulder block from a guy
from a real professional wrestler and I fell on my back and I went
holy shit do this in front of crazy I did
in front of a real life pro wrestler who's a friend of mine
but you did there was this was on a show this was this was not a show
thank God because I would have been embarrassed it would have been
embarrassing to see how much I was like wheezing after I
took one back bump on the mat
yeah I mean you say that but I
I imagine any of us would be wheezing oh my
God yes instantly there would be no way yeah you'd really
I guess you build up the tolerance for it but jeez
so we're saying we're not proposing
any sort of PTR wrestling events in the near future
well I wouldn't go that far I wouldn't say
we're not proposing that this is news to me
well I'm not I'm just saying like even though this hurts and it's not
good for your body especially this advanced age
not ruling it out is all I'm saying I'm not saying I have an idea
either I'm just saying you said that phrase and I went well
like the feeling of of officially boxing out the notion
of a podcast the right wrestling exactly yeah
I don't want to put it off the table yeah
who do we who are we evenly matched against
it's a very good question I mean I know for trio
podcasters but like let's be honest the sloppy boys are in
better shape than we are hmm probably that's true
and they do like aggressive rock and roll shows so
they must be that maybe they have some real these are some rock
and roll out of us with their rock and roll energy
and they have high tea I bet too for there were all the similar
ages but they were probably more aggressive than us too
you just had your tea checked and it was it was accidentally checked
but like because somebody wasn't the doctor wasn't sure why this nurse
ordered the full tea but I got my tea checked and I was just
normal and I was disappointed about it
because you thought it'd be high I don't know what I want
you thought the nurse put in the test because
she's like oh man this guy must have
high tea I gotta know what his tea is
she was on the phone
look I'm not going to hit on him yet but
if I get that if the tea is what I suspect
let me see those stats
and well maybe I'm going to have to like get his phone number
from the files this interaction with the nurse was on the phone
I want to be very clear about that
from the sound of this guy's voice
his tea must be through the roof
wait I misinterpreted that you mean you were talking on the phone
to them no I'm saying the nurse who ordered all the blood work
was on the phone it was not somebody I was in person
with so she didn't get to see you meant she was distracted
like she was on the phone while putting in the test
but then that might be even better if she's talking to you
on the phone and she's like yeah I gotta know the tea's
coming through the phone I gotta test this
if I could just swab the air around the receiver
I think she checked the wrong box on a computer I think that's
really what happened but my tea is normal
that was not the point of any of it but my tea is normal
but I bet those sloppy boys have high tea
that's what I'm guessing so that being said
now we're the underdogs in the match yeah that's true
so we're obviously we're going to be the
guys in that we're going to come from under yeah we're going to work from
underneath oh they're going to they're barely going to boo the shit out of them
of course yeah look at these three weaklings
fighting these aggressive aggro guys
that's what that's what's going to sort of be the narrative of the match yeah
this is our we've now we've suddenly painted them as the roughest
the roughest three dudes yeah we know yeah
of course these guys are wild you have no idea we've been
around them and these guys are they are they are loose cannons
they might just like yell or something yeah these guys
one of them drives a car there's not even a roof
on the car yeah
I mean it's a good look it's a good match up and we should think about
doing it that's all I'll say Jason you want to
weigh in on that how anxious are you to get into the ring right now
it is the sort of
thing where it's like I would be fun to hit someone with a cane
but I'm like oh shit I need that back
I'm going to need a hard grip on it
I guess I do have a back up at home so
well we should get a cane that will like it's a breakaway cane
yes we should get you like a stunt cane and then yeah you can
smack it over someone's head and break it sure
you want me down doing headshots immediately
oh yeah we're not we're going to like we're going to
we're using props and we're playing dirty oh okay yeah
well but it's a stunt cane too I guess it's a breakaway yeah
it should be fine
get hyped for this this is
well we said it here it's a one sided
one sided podcast one sided for now we just started
Scott started the feud he brought up the sloppy boys
trying to think of another trio he's right he's right
that's the match
smartless is not going to you know
well maybe we should take a couple shots and see
you're going to have to hit Bateman with a cane
I mean I feel like Bateman would be down for it
oh okay he's a pro
you know cause your answer was pro
I asked why he'd be down for it and you said pro
he's a pro totally different he's a pro is a great
answer of why he'd be down for it yeah it was a compliment
why does that make him down for wrestling I'm a little nervous that
of the three he's probably had some
training and fighting like stage fighting
stage but stage fighting
I mean you get a little bit of real fighting
I don't like how Jason's dropping the kayfabe here and acting like he would be
into the act of fake fighting we're trying to start a real
feud here yeah yeah you gotta say yeah I'll bean
that motherfucker with my cane I'm gonna yeah I'm gonna
I'm gonna try down to Ozarks right and you're
gonna be like I don't I saw his movie Bad Words or
whatever it sucked like you have to start like a real feud here you can't be like
well I think you'd be down to have some fake fighting
that's not how you do a wrestling angle yeah okay
smartless you're gonna be legless when we're done there you go
that's what you do ooh that's good that's a good guess yeah
why is it so blue in here Ozark huh
there you go why is it so blue what is this the sky
great now that's good now the feud has begun
Bateman you're no pro right no way you're gonna be
down to get in the ring with us exactly yeah right now
okay I got a good diss
coming up ahead in the notes here because so
alright so obviously
early cause like 70s
Casa Bonita must have been just like
the dreamiest funnest place and I think by their
own admission this like this is what Trey and Matt grew up
with I think this place was like without precedent
and immaculate and if you're in the Denver area
you're not close to Disneyland or whatever
like this is the best thing you got and I think it's far
beyond Chuck E Cheese or whatever too
this place clearly next level restaurant
where you get a Cliff Diver show unbelievable
but I think 90s into 2000s
are not kind to this place by like 2000
it's falling on hard times in the current restaurant there's like
a little history of the place that you can read
and the fact that they were willing
to be upfront about this
and put this on a sign in the rest and own
up to I honestly speaking of
feuds I feel like Trey and Matt are like kind of like
like picking a fight with the previous owners
a little bit cause this is how they summarize
the 2000s for this place diners express their
disappointment sharing tales of bland sauces
soggy tortillas reheated dishes and expensive
hospital visits people
it is definitive that that's really got so bad that people
went to the hospital it became apparent that the primary
focus lay on creating a memorable experience rather than culinary
delight or even tolerable food the restaurant
suffered numerous rumors of serving subpar
food and one persistent rumor about dog food
quickly earning the nickname casa no
Ida whoa wow
yeah this is real like in a way that I feel
like you know a Disney thing is not going to like they
like you know we I think we shy away from the dark
moments in history of our themed experiences
but they put it right there because they want to show off how far it
came wow yeah so this place
you know it is a basically
it was a heavily themed restaurant where the food was
at best terrible and worse could
give you food poisoning and at this point I feel like
you guys might be disappointed that
it's no longer that way well
the ideal Mike and Jason restaurant well
it's less exciting the way where it's consistently
good food you don't have yeah you don't have the risk you're not like
you're not you're not playing the slots but then you know right you know
the first time oh it's fine it's good okay
well you're not rolling the dice next time you know what you're getting
I know what you mean I guess they have kind of lost the sense of adventure
that's right yeah yeah the great blandening
of the casa no Ida experience I said
this I said this a couple of months ago I think we were talking about this on the show
is that they didn't have ovens
uh-huh everything was steamed yes
all the food was steamed not really discovered
by Trey and Matt until they were
owned it and went in the kitchen to start figuring out what they had to do
right and it was just so much more than they thought like it was
in such bad shape it was so strange the way everything was laid out
and by the way the menu has not radically changed
I mean they just serve basics it's tacos
and enchiladas how do you make those entirely
with steam I don't know it's confusing
but yes it sounded like a real strange thing it was already dangerous
too I'm sure you probably get to that yeah yeah but like it was everything
was very dangerous set up in a way where like you're like the people
could easily get set on fire the cliff divers
very dangerous the way they were doing it yes yeah
employee like a constant endangerment to employees
at minimum just like
guests possibly breathing toxic fumes
and as I said you know
the tantalizing to you guys but not to everybody
risk of getting food poisoning yeah
here are some quotes about
the previous food situation
wait let me find okay this is from
I think it was in a Denver Post article
Victoria Gagnon it was 57
there's got to be a place in hell for people who serve
food like that oh wow she said after
she and her family got food poisoning after a visit to
in 2013
the diners are condemning the food
preparers to hell wow Matt Stone
said the previous owners deferred
maintenance in an almost superhuman way
they just didn't take care of anything and they ran it completely
into the ground
the previous owners are named on the sign summit family
restaurants I do feel like
I feel like Trey and Matt
were genuinely angry about the arc of
this place they say in an
interview how what they are doing now
their ownership of this place is not a joke
it is it's very sincere to them because they are
upset that the place had become a joke right
because it wasn't when they grew up with it and I
kind of like that they're just like calling out
summit fucked up they
ran it into the ground it was already in a lot of trouble
obviously COVID was like the final
slam on this place but I think they were in plenty of trouble
even before that sounds like it yeah
and this also goes back to how like Matt and Trey are like
sincere theme park guys like these type of guys
yeah and you've noted that before
we've talked about like the imagination episode
which clearly nods to the imagination
yeah yeah and the song imagination
obviously a nod to Epcot
and that's what I will
that's what I was so excited about once I discovered
like the full deal with this place what you're describing
their sincerity them being theme park people
has never been more evident than when you're in this place
it is that is what is so exciting
about what they did here so anyways the place is not
doing great through the 2000s
and I think it's propped up almost entirely by their association
with South Park so this episode airs in 2003
per YouTube video
filmed a while back the people then at
the restaurant say how they could count on a
10% boost in
in business anytime the episode
like so they would track oh that one's back up and reruns
well which is all the time I mean like
Comedy Central now almost entire they kind of only show
South Park so that things probably air in once a week
or so and like the next night like clockwork
so they would have to staff differently they would
they would bring more people on knowing
that that episode had just aired
yeah so the association becomes
like very deep
South Park's offices where they make the show
has been called Casa Bonita for a long time
and then pandemic
this thing closes August 2021
they announced that they are purchasing the restaurant and saving it
which almost certainly would have just gone under completely
so they have paid 3 million dollars to
own this thing outright they start
getting into what it's going to take to
to renovate it and you know
make it everything you know like plus it up but also just
like make it basically functional for
for guys like to get it up to modern health code standards
the initial estimate is 10 million dollars
they are going to have to put into it to get it to be the way they
want it that expands and expands it ends up being
40 million dollars they put 40
million dollars of their own money into this place
the cost of a motion picture yeah yeah
yeah they could have self-financed
a new Team America easily with that money
yeah yeah but they are
they've done some very canny moves with like
licensing their back catalog
did they didn't they do
where like a lot of the new South Park are
are made for TV movies essentially
and like they sold those to one streaming service
and they chop it up into episodes and sold it to another
streaming service well it's all on both I mean
South Park's moved a couple of times it was all on Hulu
it was on their own site South Park Studios and now
the new movies come out on Paramount Plus but the archive
lives on Macs and anytime
that is resold I mean I don't know the numbers but it's like
they own half of it they it's like so it's the
the greatest margins of ownership yeah
yeah it's very modern television history they will
you know hey I try to sell animated shows
I watch the process everybody tries to make sure
that no one will all lawyers work together
to make sure nobody ever gets a deal remotely close
to what these guys have ever again
yeah so they've every anytime and it's going to keep happening
they keep moving from venue to venue and they will make
half a billion dollars every time it happens
it's crazy yeah these guys are so
loaded and so much of what excites me about this
is using their loadedness
just to make a fun thing happen for us
for the world and for the town they grew up in
Trey Parker said somewhere it would have been
they would have spent much less money and had a lot more
fun if they had used this money to go hang gliding
over volcanoes but instead
they pumped it into a restaurant where apparently the stats are
they would need to get like a million
guests every night in order to turn a profit
on this plate I don't think they can fit that many
I think we're dealing with a thousand tonight and yeah
I mean it's doing gangbusters but still how do you make
like 40 million it seems hard yeah
yeah it's the kind of margins
that we usually are talking about
when we're mourning a restaurant that has gone away
we're talking about a place that was so crazy
it was never going to work and yet
just because of their finances
we're able to tell like this is a brand new thing
that I mean I'm sure they want to make their money back
but I don't think they have to immediately
like it is not we're not remotely in the territory
we're usually talking about but like yeah how in the world was
NBA City ever going to get out of the red
it's great it's magical
and there's no there's no there's no like awful bullshit
companies involved and it's just these two crazy guys
it's the only time when mega rich people like
they do a cool like we've talked to Quentin Tarantino effect
like he's preventing these theaters from being turned
into like apartment buildings or condos in LA
it's like that's when if that's the only time I like it
when somebody has a ton of money like this yes yeah
just like if you're going to do something fun okay great yeah
yeah I think the only thing comparable absolutely
is Tarantino yeah I know and that like
they're putting their money where their mouths are
and like doing things that reflect their sensibility
you know Tarantino giving back to
film and these guys giving back to
crazy Colorado bullshit it's wonderful
so all right what other details in there
a lot of this money went to unsexy stuff
it went to like HVAC system plumbing
electrical gas
I think they were they were talking about a book of Mormon
and how during or kind of anything they do like if they're
they if they're going to spend a lot of money they want it to show up on screen
they don't want it to go to boring between the lines kind of stuff
but in this case it had to like it was never
they just had to like replace the table tops
because they were filthy and yeah just old meals
are caked between the tiles after decades and decades
so all this boring stuff but again you're in there and you
really feel it and I'll get into that but yeah Matt Stone said
we're talking about just health and safety stuff like so someone won't
die yeah I imagine
there was a lot to be redone for the cliff diving
Porsche like I'm sure yes that pool
and stuff needed a redo that's
that's definitely a huge area
okay apparently if you went there
you know circa 2019 maybe for decades
and decades decades
horrible chlorine stink right around there
especially but probably through the entire restaurant
and you just like took that as a given like alright I'm going to have fun
but it does smell in Casa Bonita I can attest
it does not smell today it was ice cold
water those guys had to do that show
and then just and then dive straight into
so they've they finally put in heaters
for the first time in history so the divers are comfortable
and then here's also from Denver
Post other features like the old cliff diving pool
actual physical hazards it turned out that divers once they leaped into the
pool could only exit through a 30 inch wide
underwater tunnel brimming with pipes
then they emerged from the water into an electrical room
oh god yeah I read that that's
that's pretty wild said somebody I don't have the first name
shoemaker who was helping with this process there were 200
amps of power directly to the left when I
saw it I called Matt and told him this is the most
dangerous room I've ever seen
of any type of room
he has never been in a room with as much
capacity to murder people room full of spikes is
less dangerous yeah this is like this is a Batman
villain trap right this was their day to day was
something yes if it wasn't people
if you were pushing the people off instead of them
diving on purpose that's the only shift you'd have to make to make this
a literal torture device that's crazy yeah yeah
so insane so they did all of these
and imagine and like their feet like
I'm sure they thought this was a risky dumb thing
when they got into it they're probably like I don't know
a lot of money will we ever see it back I don't know and now
we got to put in money for innovation then that number quadruples
and in the middle of this they are probably like
what the fuck are we do why yeah
how was this really that important to us
and they made an episode recently
that depicts their that kind of
like is a stand in for this process I'd seen
this episode and didn't realize that's what it was
where Cartman buys a
hot dog restaurant wait he's living in a
hot dog already in recent seasons he and his
mom fell on hard times and they had to move into a hot dog restaurant
and then he flips it into like a fancy
restaurant with water slides and zip lines and stuff
and I didn't realize while watching it that it is all an allegory
for the annoyance of having to
having to do this just the relatable story
of when you buy a restaurant and then the cost
overruns are enormous
so anyways that brings us to today there's articles for a long
time about like you know
when is this going to open and is it going to open is it going to be
more complicated than we thought but also rumors
are flying that they fixed the food finally
Dana Rodriguez the lead chef
is like a lauded Denver
chef so maybe that's finally been fixed
they've plussed it up thematically in a huge way as all this is forming
I'm like I want to figure this out I want to understand
Cartman's excitement I want to see if they fixed it today
I got to get here so
as I was saying I wanted to take my son on a reasonably short plane
trip so we bought we bought plane tickets to Denver now
to figure out Casa Bonita went to the website huh
there is nowhere to get tickets or reservations
wait you just sign up for the mailing list and that's all
you can do and you don't know when they're going to email you back
and I reached out to some other people who I know went like
our friend Doug Jones my friend Joe Carnegie and they're like
oh yeah I booked mine as soon as the website was up and running
god crap shit how did they know about this
and I didn't know about it so now I'm trying and I complained about it
on an episode of the show is there any way I could figure out
and I have the plane tickets already like there's no way this will
line up I guess 600,000 people
are in line ahead of me do I have to cancel this trip what do I do
friend of the show Landon
Zachheim heard my plea
who you know from immersive style he's like a
he's a film festival he was there with he was there
at the Minotaur incident oh he was one of the participants
yes and he was despite that he did not
turn his back on the podcast the ride boys
I would have understood he didn't shock us all up as
Minotaur fearing cowards that's right he wanted to help out
he worked a few angles with his connections in the
Denver area he was trying to figure out a way so helpful
like I really want to figure this out for you I said why
this is so nice of you why and he said
I just want to hear that episode of podcast the ride
bless you Landon here we are now
really tried his best
and emailed a ton of people for me none of it ended up working out
this was just like an unscalable wall I thank
Landon for trying everything but in all
that time I never canceled the trip and then suddenly
Joe Carnegie one of the people who told me the deal with the
mailing list said guess what my date is
up I can't do it anymore
do these dates happen to work for you for a table
for three for cliffside dining
and I said that is exactly when I am booked
to be in Denver and I got to do it thank you
Joe you rescued this experience and you get that it was a table
of three so it could be a family thing I could take
my four year old son to experience cliffside
dining a miracle so great
so we we go to Denver we
spend a few days there find a lot of fun kids stuff to do
but we build up to this this is the last night this is the
the main attraction and we head over to Lakewood
kind of west of downtown Denver
in the episode of the show
when Cartman and everybody
Kyle's mom when they arrive at Casa Bonita you can see
in the background like it's a subtle thing that
everything in the background is all like pawn shops and strip
clubs and stuff it's just a subtle thing that's not
referred to and I was like is that going to
be consistent with the deal with this place and sure enough
the entire drive in through Lakewood is just like
seedy motels and vape stores
it is like it is nothing like it is not like
some charming drive up to this this charming place
and then you you get there and it's just in a
strip mall that's just like a Ross and a dollar tree
and a Planet Fitness could not be less
glad it's just right next to like a big dentist's office
but shining above all of that this beautiful
pink tower what a pink oh
it's a perfect yeah such a 70s pink
they apparently had to try 27 shades of it
to get the right kind of pink
it's like it's I mean it's like the Carthay Circle
Tower it is a theme park weenie
a shining beacon over Lakewood
it's so beautiful right away I feel like Cartman
and I'm not even in there yet spectacular
fountain outside which was also completely redone
all of these thankless things they did this fountain was going to
crumble entirely but they had to
and the mood outside is just
amped up everybody is buzzing it's
families that just came out of their families who can't get wait to get
in there like boy the spirits in this place
which is what I've just I just tried to retain
and keep it here in this episode get inside
we gotta go straight to the bathroom just the bathrooms are great
the tiles just the choice of tiles and the
colors and I'm like if I like the bathrooms this much
this is going to be unbelievable yeah
then get a bigger better sense of the lobby it's like this little it's like this
indoor village and this you know this little flags and the strings of
flags and fruit carts it is immediately
so Epcot Mexico Pavilion
and like rendered in that it is like
clearly instantly theme park quality
if this place was ever kind of like funny
cruddy like a miniature golf course
or something not today this is like
I don't know who they got to work on this production
design wise but it is so high caliber
it's incredible it's also got
I feel like the coziness and the intimacy of like one of my
favorite little parts in theme park them and I'm so sad this
place is gone the little town in the
Norway ride when the ride is over
little town that you have to rush through to go see the
boring movie right right
you know what I shouldn't call such a shot I'm fond of the boring movie
but we have to admit it's a boring movie I when I was
younger I thought you had to watch it to get out
yeah yeah and and I think in later
years they had the doors a little more propped open
but as a kid
crack a light so you know I could leave
I didn't know I thought like well the doors must be locked
we had to be respectful and watch this movie
I think I thought that about all theme park doors like there's no way
I can leave I assume it's just steel clonk
it's prison doors and then I understood how
fire safety in public places
works yeah sure yes and like that you know
people with little kids need to be able to exit due to a freak out
and go to the bathroom whenever they want but I know what you mean
the little town you would the boat would pull up in
that is what it is about that
it's like so cozy and you know it's an unload area
so you don't get to spend any time there
I could have just like we sometimes we talk about like where would you want to get a drink
in a theme but I would just I just want to like pull up a chair
in that little town and just sit there for a while
just watch boats come in and out
yeah that was not an option nor do I know what a
Norwegian cocktail would be
do they drink schnapps I feel like a lot of
countries in Europe let's say schnapps it just defaults
to a schnapps or some sort of liqueur
I mean it's got to be a beer culture
right you would think I would think so but I don't know
that's not something I learned about in the Norway
yeah that one's really looming Norway Maelstrom
that's a big sneaker that we've never
gotten to yeah that's a family favorite
the neighboring country
Finland I learned about
and then never bought or tried
the Finnish long drink
which is a can they sell
in America they sell cans of it now
and an early investor was
Miles Teller so when we were on our
celebrity liquor trick I was going to show up one day
Finnish long drink and when I went to buy it
it was out they didn't have it
Finnish long drink
Finnish long drink I think it goes back to
there was an Olympics
after World War II in Finland
but like alcohol was still kind of hard to come by
so they figured out a way to
mix a liqueur with like grapefruit soda
to make it stretch a little more
so I think it's like a grapefruit soda like
liquor drink and is Miles Teller Finnish
why is Miles involved
he was at an event where they were giving out
samples and he really liked it so he bought in
okay well I would love to see him
reprise his type of role as maybe he could play
himself in a mini series like the offer
that is about him putting together the deal
to make the Finnish long drink
the offer is on Paramount Plus?
I can only hope
I forgot all about the offer
but I do newly have Paramount Plus
watch Ninja Turtles
and watch the offer
which Ninja Turtles are you going to watch?
I'm like last year
you gotta go straight to the offer though
I think I can play this part
that sounds good
not a bad impression of that
anyways we got
end of Norway ride vibes right in the lobby
it's cozy I look in a window
and there's a little retro TV
it is an ad from the 70s
for Casa Bonita starring
Ricardo Maltobon
I'm missing the L
I was like Maltobon
I just wanted to make sure we were talking about the same guy
no Mike I'm talking about Ricardo Maltobon
without an L obviously
like a different off brand Ricardo Maltobon
he's a white guy
I'm sorry I meant Richard O Maltobon
less exciting
Denver's hottest henchman
he was big in Denver's theater
this is the man of course that starred in Fantasy Island
and was con on Star Trek
villain of naked gun
I didn't know he did ads for this
you have to look through kind of like a frosted window
and then the TV's kind of fuzzy
and that's where I'm like oh I see what they've done here
they have just kept the 70s-ness of it
and probably amped it up
I imagine this place felt kind of eternally 70s already
but just probably due to not replacing anything
I don't think it was like a choice
but in that way that we kind of just want Disney
to say tomorrow land equals 70s or 80s
or whatever
that's just what it is don't run from it
I feel like what they've done here
they just decided it is perma 70s let's not fight it
and it's this like dreamy 70s
it's like a storybook 70s
it's the most pleasant sun-hued 70s
mixed with like vibes of Tony Baxter's New Fantasyland
it is so charming storybook
and with some of the atrocities we've seen of like recent flipping
you know what was in my head was like
boy we really gotta update Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen
for modern you know
they don't understand all these railings and this New Orleans vibe
what do modern people want?
well they want like plain white walls
and the word jazz written on the wall
I don't think we talked about this on the show
that is so brutal what they did to Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen
at downtown Disney
I haven't walked around there but I was just there the other day
and it does the personality is gone
with some like the odd agenda
of like modernizing
and that being I guess that a restaurant has to look
like a Property Brothers flipped house
I don't get it and I think we're gonna look back
and go like the atrocities that we have committed
ripping out all the personality
when you should just like enhance what it is
start with its core and then like make the core shine
and maybe I'm wrong I think they
think they're making it more fall in line with the future
aesthetic of that downtown Disney which is very like
and that's okay I like that some of that downtown Disney stuff is kind of
retro from the 60s that's close to what I'm describing
because that'll sort of stay timeless
and feel modern but future but retro all at once
so I feel like they're like well if we make it like this at least like it's white
it falls into like the color scheme of what the art
shows I don't know to me it just looks like
you know it looks like a frozen yogurt shop from 2009
yes I don't disagree it's like it's out of date
in the wrong way I don't disagree
there's a new like entry sign I just saw
went up for downtown Disney
and I saw it describe this that's okay yeah
it's entry modern but I was like that's just the
isn't that just the Dodger Stadium sign
oh maybe a little did you see
the Din Tai Fung is really coming along
where is it it's right where the movie theater used to be
so you come in there and there's a big and they have a it's a big building
it's really well themed okay and I was like very
we walked in there like a couple weeks ago I was like very impressed
so that's something to look forward to
it seems like a mixed bag some of these redos at downtown Disney are all right
because look downtown Disney not all of the aesthetics
were I'd say we've I'd say we quest
I'd say we questioned a lot of the aesthetics all over downtown Disney
and the replacement and I forget the name of it for the
bar for your beloved and I can't think of the name of the old bar
oh yeah Centrico Centrico
fuck Centrico yeah it kind of looks nice it's probably fine
yeah it looks nice oh wait kayfabe no fuck Centrico
I will I'll I'm gonna get a lot of
equipment ready to burn it to the ground on opening day
I feel like there were and maybe there's not like a little fire pit but there were people
just kind of chilling out there's more room sort of to hang out out there
and it felt like when you're when you see people like having a good
time at a place and it feels like a fake commercial where they're all just like
laughing and like you're looking at the concept art right
but that's what was happening when I was we were walking by there I was like
everyone's having such a fun time here it's almost hard
to reconcile the places at downtown Disney being
actual places where people gather right and have fun
right but that's what was happening so I mainly
associate a lot of them with like families of eight being like
we need to be fed yeah this is we are
absolutely mowed down by this day
yeah but no that's not always yeah I saw
I saw people and they were not maybe they were in their 30s
the early 30s and they were having a blast wow
and then there was a chime and they all stopped what they were doing
and turned and looked at you oh everyone
in downtown Disney did that yeah it was just
the horror movie it became like an 824
horror movie where it's just like unnerving
right not super scary yeah that was a tell
that maybe it's still not a normal place
until that was fine yeah
anyways I just love that they
embrace the 70s it is the 70s and then
we are ushered up to our
cliffside dining location which by the way I have to
if listeners if you would tend to go to this place
it's a little bit extra I think just spring for it I think you gotta
do the cliffside dining you know
because if you're they went in Rome I think you gotta do it
and so now we get this like incredible entrance where we're like going
upstairs and there's like tiers and you start to get a sense
of the of the space and how many like little
areas and rooms there are in this
in this restaurant and then we arrive
in kind of like the main atrium where you can really
see everything and it were two steps in
and we go holy shit they did it it's
perfect you can tell it is there was no question
I think we were like there's still a possibility that we
get in and it's kind of cheesy or that maybe they actually did
cheap out a little bit on the renovation not at all
the vibes are incredible we have both
our jaws are both dropped from second one
we we go we walk past a mariachi band
and which is I remember from Cartman's speed
run that he like stops and dances for two seconds and then
keeps going and I stop and dance for two seconds and then
keep going and we get to our cliffside dining table I think as
soon as we land there is a cliff diving show
in progress it's insane
it's so great I think you can watch it from down on the
bottom and there's like and they call it a splash zone
it's a splash zone you will get you you can get wet and you do
get wet but you can also watch it from up on the top
this moment especially and I'll post
a video of this there is a moment where
I grab my son to take him
all the way to the edge as close as we can get to
get a full vantage point of the cliff diving and the diver
walks he climbs just onto rocks it's not even
like sea world style like you can see the little platforms
they just walk on like jagged looking
rocks bare feet they just
explore wherever they want and one of them
comes up two feet away from us
and you know Aaron's not trying to like
be a cinematographer here but the
built in lighting is so
immaculate on camera it's just this
cascade of glowing and amazing
theatrical light and then like twinkling
stars all over the ceiling which I know they didn't have before
they didn't have any of this before lighting incredible sound
incredible they like pumped Broadway
stage money into this place it is
so Disney level it's insane
and then watching the cliff dive my son's been talking about it
ever since he's never seen anything like
cliff diving and let alone how close you get
it's just again
we're heading into half an hour of me going and then this was great
and then this was really great I feel
if you're sensing I feel insecure about just how
sincere that I know I'm really thrown
off guard here but what else can I do it's just like
I think I knew it would be
cool but I still thought maybe it'd be like cheesy
cool and the fact that it feels absolutely
Disney caliber that was the shocker
to me and then the cliff side dining seats are next
to rock walls so you're next you're
in a fake rock it's like it is somewhere between
Mexico Pavilion and Pirates of the Caribbean
I will say there's absolutely quarters of this
that feel like the caves in the beginning
Pirates of the Caribbean and I can't believe they pulled that off
it sounds like nonsense when
they say it in South Park it's the Disneyland and Mexican restaurants
I bet at the time that was said kind of in jest
but now it just is it fully is
that it's been it's incredible that's that's wild
yeah I would be so interested to know like because there's
not a ton of great footage of it inside from
30 40 50 years ago no not really
yeah so I do wonder like obviously it looks I'm sure
it looks ten times better now I do wonder what it looks
like opening day yeah I I don't
know and yeah I don't have the best sense of the vibes
previously I mean I think this place I think some of the
magic of it is it's like modern money supporting
really good bones and the the photos
I saw made it the old those photos I could
find made it clear that like all these features were
there you know they're like here's the little like
here's the town square and a fountain and a
dedicated so papillas stand and then
like the every beat of black parts
cave which I will get into was all there they may
have fully ripped it out and started over but I
don't think they reinvented the space or I mean
I think they they like pretty perfectly recreated
what they had been ripping out you know right
so I'm sure it was awesome when
it opened I mean just like it's what you want out
of it's in the league of I'm trying to think of like the
best Disney example this it might not be this but like that
Snow White redo I think is wonderful yeah
I think you know it doesn't stray far from
the ride that was probably there in nineteen fifty five but
they subtly use modern technology
they don't like make it fully screen ride but they just like
support and amend and I think it's
insane that I'm putting this in league with like
some of Disney's best ride redo's yeah I
absolutely do well and also I
think it would be harder to make something that would continually
impress like I guess what I mean is like
you have to sit there and eat so you're watching everything
and you're existing by it for an hour or whatever
yeah you got time to stare right and so like see all the
seams yes right because like a ride I'm sure
there's fake rocks that we love that you would sit
and eat a meal by them and by the end you would be like well the some
of some of the magic might be gone because I can see that it's
actually a little cheaper the paint isn't so good oh absolutely
yes and it requires like a like a blue by you
which I completely does hold up like it's got to be
but it started in there what's that dark in that blue by you
that's true that's true well you know it's it's dark in here
too yeah but like I'm not as dim
they definitely aren't like hiding any yeah yeah now
one thing I will say
about like you know you just said
well you know because you like you know you
sit there for a while you sit there for an hour this is not
necessarily true I feel like the what they encourage
essentially is fairly quick turnover
because there's so much interest in this place yeah
but also alright the
food this is a big question yeah what did you have
well here I'll get into it but just vaguely
let me say the foods not
great they didn't get it to grow interesting
now we're not in dog food territory we're not in casa
noita territory but it was pretty quickly
broadcasted I would say that the food might not be great
because here's how this played out the reservation
was at 6 p.m. and we got there a little earlier
so we were seated at 6 p.m. we ordered
the food arrived at 6.08
wow really jammed this out
and I feel like that communicated this place is
not about the food you will yeah you know eat up enjoy
it'll be fine but
the fact that it was out that quickly and that there are constant
PA announcements for all the other things there are to do
kind of let us know oh I see
food is like a technicality here we provide it
it's like at a wedding or something but probably it's more
about the other stuff gotcha
so yes food wise
I mean this is something
I talked to Doug about this he was like because he
got to go a couple months prior I think I asked him about
food and he said I think he said fine
but boy if you ask around Denver if you're in Denver
and you talk to locals and you just bring up I'm
here for personally for Casa Bonita they will
all say oh that food oh Jesus that food
and we experienced that we went to a Trader Joe's
and we got exactly that and somebody said it that Trader Joe's
you know what I don't think they fixed it
I still don't think it's any good so Denver
is definitely like a Denver thing they were they are so
like they have not forgotten how terrible that food
and so much of the like mystery of this place
is did they get the food better and like kinda
Erin's was worse than mine she got something
vegetarian and she said it was like a
serviceable microwave meal
and it's not Taco Bell quality even
well look we're on different I don't know what to say to you
to that because you put Taco Bell in the highest caliber food
did you eat the big Cheez-It yet Mike?
I have not had the big Cheez-It Taco Bell thing yeah
there's a big Cheez-It at Taco Bell
can we put an inch amount on that
like I think like
if you've ever had a Crunch Wrap at Taco Bell
it's kind of like I would say it's like this big right here
and I think the Cheez-It's sort of a similar
like this you know when Steven Spielberg's making the lens
when he's sort of imagining a shot in a movie
with his fingers imagine an onset
of Last Crusade finger frame forming
with Steven Spielberg if you want to Google the image search that
that's about how big the Cheez-It is
a Cheez-It in Steven's hand like that too
if somebody wants to make that I would appreciate it
you were making me wistful for the magic of cinema
just doing those the hands
I guess you could do two you could do these you could do this
there's a big Cheez-It so you can get the big Cheez-It in a Crunch Wrap
or you can get it as a Tostado
or you can just buy the big Cheez-It
have you done it? I haven't yet
you have a disgusted face but I don't think you meant to convey that
no I was just burping yeah
oh you were burping that was a disgust
did you have a couple of sodas this morning?
no Jason's been saying he's been meaning to eat more big Cheez-Its
we'll get there
I have been eating organic Cheez-Its though the Annie's organic Cheez-Its
that I've been buying from Sprouts
or you gotta go organic with your Cheez-Its
you do you know the ingredients are organic
that means good for you that means healthy
I just get Cheez-Its but I like the extra toasty ones
they need a little extra burnt a little more carcinogen in there
you throw them in a fryer you put a little oil on
oil and butter if you want it really crispy
you do it yourself you throw them in the oven
you make them extra
extra toasty and then I crisp them up
that's a bummer though
maybe it is Taco Bell quality
I just don't know how to answer that because I know you regard Taco Bell very highly
as far as garbage food
it's high up there
I would not call it garbage food
I think it's kind of common
I feel like I've had a lot of experience with the
I've been here for decades Mexican restaurant
where the food is not that good and it makes you feel kind of bad after the fact
where you just feel the like cake thon gunk
in the back of that maybe like oh well part of it
being open forever means they haven't replaced this or that
so I was not surprised when I heard that the food wasn't great
and nor like look I will go back to those places
maybe this is my area of the city walk
loyalty where your guys willingness
to go back time and time again to places that make you sick
or try to put plastic in your food
maybe I feel that with because I do just like the
ambiance of a classic Mexican restaurant
which made this the ultimate
it's probably why this of all things really spoke to me
you're describing like what I call like
margaritas enchiladas sit down Mexican restaurant
as opposed to just like a taqueria
yeah yeah yeah
where it's maybe it's dim and there's decor and the walls full of stuff
yeah it's a little dark
there's stained glass probably some inherent kind of 60s 70s feel
because it's when a lot of them opened
maybe a lemon rind with like 151 they light on fire
sure I haven't had that but that sounds fun
I forget where that's in like Echo Park
I forget the name of that place
I don't know if it's an Acapulco or an El Torito
like some of the local chains
probably closer to that which I and I have plenty of fondness for El Torito
I will like tolerate that kind of
but it's shockers that like I can't believe I didn't like the chips
the chips is kind of my big
tortilla chips are I try to eat healthy in every other area
so that I can just shovel tortilla chips
you know possibly multiple times a day
wow I didn't know this
yeah fair enough
but I will absolutely go to town
what type of chips like what are you have a brand do you have multiple brands
I mean lately it's just like I try to go
it's like Trader Joe's unsalted gluten free
like let's step it down as many levels as we can
but I still am going to eat like the full meals worth
for no reason it's the biggest thing I should watch
I will just like absolutely tear them up
I was shocked that these I did not want more of them
so I'm like oh man are we in a bad territory because Aaron didn't really like hers
mine I went with Carnitas tacos
which was recommended by a
food blog that I read and I definitely liked it more than Aaron did
fine totally fine I think this is a place
where the sauces are doing a lot of heavy lifting
so if you go here make sure that you're doing something that is sauce forward
I think Aaron's was rescued by it being Christmas style
just make sure you're seeing a sauce
in that listing because like I think that
I think we're dealing with pretty basic I think like inherent
flavor and juice of meats is not
necessarily incredible what do you mean
Christmas style is that like a wet burrito
green sauce red sauce I think so now I have to remember
because I didn't have something
Christmas style I know I've had that somewhere
I thought it means that it has a little piece of reindeer in it
Aaron famously vegetarian
but she makes an exception
for reindeer
she makes an exception for Christmas spirit
what is it I know I think your
I think your description was fairly accurate
yeah red and green sauce
but it's fun you know like not bad
and I didn't feel bad after the fact
I've seen reviews and I've seen vloggers
go to this place and get it out of the way
as I got stuff out of the way at the top of this they started by saying
and I'll tell you all about the food spoiler didn't make
me sick I think the possibility was
so high before that Denver locals like that's
the first thing you have to address is I'm like
I understand I'm like probably everybody wanted to be here
it's so fun I'm sure it was fun even pre-train Matt
but like if that possibility is so high
again other than for you guys who I feel like would have been
at the prior version on a monthly basis that's true yeah
extra steam please I would say
I'm trying to figure out
how to steam carnitas Scott good move
I think carnitas usually pretty safe
I think the worst thing you can do to it it's just dry
it out yeah well I think that's how it was
but then they put like a decent that's what you see
yeah that's what the steam is well that's moist
yeah maybe I might have liked it more if they'd I hope they didn't take out
all of the steamers they should have in tribute to the
to the original process they should have kept a few steamers
but anyway it is also also shockingly
neither of us really cared for the drinks
we found the drinks pretty sugary and like
okay that's too but so we're a little like oh we're loved but are we
are we in the territory of theming is good but the foods
not great and it's improved but there was nowhere to go but
up from like you might go to the hospital
the drinks were redeemed a little bit later by
again this is from the same review said to avoid the
margaritas and get something called El Diablo which is
a mezcal drink and that I thought was
actually spectacular I thought it was a really good drink so again
being that mine are stolen from another
food review I thought they're they're fairly vetted
I don't think I could speak to don't take my food recommendations
but I took mine from another one so listeners if you're going
El Diablo and carnitas tacos and what
strain of sticky Colorado Cush
did you enjoy beforehand
yeah yeah
no I got the yeah I got the Grateful Dead
specific varietal yeah they've been working up some
personally approved yeah yeah yeah
that's what the guy did you see the new store I met
send it the guy who snuck a bong into
the sphere and got been banned
and has been banned from all Madison Square
MSG oh no Mike's
greatest fear he's on Dolan's Dolan's no list
yeah and I haven't been put on there thank God but I
won't try the bong now I know Dolan's no list is really
something given that his yes list contains some of the
worst human beings who have ever walked the earth
yeah
anyways you
also you don't have to get all your drinks at the table because there are four
bars all over this place which I don't think there were before
on the way out the door a local said that there are
activations that when you order a drink asked about
the activation and I was running out of time and I
didn't get to do it so I don't know what it is so listeners
when you order a drink ask about the activation
I really want to know what that it's some something with lighting or something
pops up some little secret I don't know I wish I knew
now we're starting to review this thing not
in the best terms food wise but we're being kind of forgiven
because we're in the best mood ever yeah
and then the soap appears
stage comes the soap appears are free
with the meal as our sodas I thought that was funny
free with the meal
but so
soap appears change everything these are this is everything
that Cartman made them out to be this
it was like the definition of great taste in your
mouth on the way out the door I don't care that we were disappointed
by the first step these are incredible I don't even know how
to they're like Mexican pastry bites
and they're so soft intent like they're hollow inside
so they just like crumble as soon as your mouth
touches them and it oh my
god just so so delicious and like
like covered in hot like that like they're all just like
fried up they all just do like a little fire bath and then somebody's like
squirting honey on it as it goes
just like really simple I think this is like a
three ingredient item I don't know how they do it
but like these are they're they're unbelievable
and this was the most satisfying in terms of like what
South Park promised soap appears soap appears please
watching his like drunkenness on them
and and the flag and you get to do the flag I don't know if
this place invented the flag I don't know if they
I mean obviously they predate Bubba Gump I don't know the
history of the thing that waves the server down
but it's great and they put new flags
at every table the beautiful that are like
like really well chosen fabric
a beautiful pattern the logo I love the
Casa Bonita logo so much I found the flag
so charming I wanted to take one home with me and I did
they sell the flag wow smart
flag at home and my son plays with it and we play like
let's play dinner time and he raises the flag and we
it really stuck with him and that's all you want is you know
my you just want experiences that they are still talking about weeks
later you're talking about so many aspects of this
as am I that's what happens when my daughter wants to watch
the Chuck E. Cheese me and my friends video again
as she comes up to me and she goes she just starts
flapping her wings like Helen Henney and then points at the TV
that's the signal she just flaps
she gets this like little smile on her face
and she starts flapping and then she points to the TV and I go
you want to watch me and my friends with Chuck E. and she's like nods
wow yeah wow geez well
she's a Tiki Room fan now as well because she went there
so then she'll go like Tiki Tiki Tiki like she'll say it a little bit
but then she'll like if you just play the song on the
like boombox then she will be like
and she'll point to the TV she wants to watch the video
of the Tiki Room wow wow so she'll give
there there's yeah she will do the thing where she's like remembers
this I don't know that she really remembers being there in person
but she should she should probably some if she
remembers those things obviously are memorable to her I think
the this morning because I was
refreshing my memory on some of this stuff and of the South Park
episode and I was like filming that scene off
the TV and then my son said
can we watch the one with the guy running from the police
yes we can yes he remembered
watching the clip of Carpenter doing the speed running
he knows that he was there
so anyways soapapias highly
recommended I don't know where else in the world serves soapapias
I'm sure there are places I've just never been to one before
but like so much better than the little white
triangles that were depicted on South Park
like truly transit really really great dessert
did you guys eat a plate of them and then call
more call for more soapapias I wanted
to really badly just to do it I think
they aren't endless I think it's like a dollar more
which is still the price is right on that yeah and you could go up
to the dedicated soapapias stand at any point
and just like purchase them piecemeal even once
you've left your table because by the way when you leave your table
the table is done don't leave a jacket
there as a blogger said it's not your home base
for the night you what you know if they see
nobody there they're turning that table right right there's
600,000 people to get through you can hang out inside
you can go to the little yeah yeah that's what you
do you can stay in it as long as you want
and that I guess is the area that I'm getting into I'm going to
back up a little bit to the cliff diver presentation
because there's something important that I forgot about first
of all these divers are so great not just with the dives
which are obviously very impressive and that they're on these precarious
rocks and right next to us so cool
also part of it that they're wearing these
very 70s like
burnt orange shorts that are
specifically what Trey and Matt remember
and they requested these to be made again to just
keep it firmly in that 70s zone
so the shorts are custom and they're so you know
besides the dives themselves it's wrestling they've
got the audience in the palm of their they they hype everybody up
yeah like almost do it and then they don't
they like just like everybody is
enthralled with their every move these
guys are so great the interplay the way they work everybody
up and then there's
there's an aspect of this and this is what and here's
maybe a little bit of spoiler I might I'm going to issue a few
spoiler alerts because I think the audience deserves to have some
things that I don't yeah run for them I were
in like Tokyo Disney territory there's things that I don't want
to say right because I think it's fun to just
discover this so I'll issue one of those right now it's a small thing
but pretty cool there are as I said
PA announcements throughout this like
kind of encouraging the flow and like you know
to go check out the other things to check out the puppet show and then also
like hyping people up for the cliff diving and
these PA announcements are done by
Trey Parker himself oh that's funny he put his
own voice into it and I am such a fan
of him vocally and I'm such a fan of that
thing he does where it's like aware and like
cruddy on purpose and being just like you know this
like full of shit announcer guy and he gets to do
that thing that he's so good at and it plays
all night every night in this restaurant
the part of me that so badly wanted to be in the fries
electronics I'm like god damn it this guy
did it he did like exactly my dream
like creating a place where his voice
is the voice of everything in the place yeah that's awesome
and like and it just it adds to the comedy
of it because it's sure he's got
that tongue-in-cheek thing about the way the way he pronounces but
also it feels really sincere
too it's just it's like the awareness that it needs
so that you to communicate that yes the place is a little
hokey but we're all going to just have fun with the hokeyness right
and there's stuff like he there's a big
buildup you know sometimes the divers just do like a fun
show with music and then there's one where there's suspense and the music
is a little bit scary and he builds it up and like all
right ladies and gentlemen your attention to the cliff
lagoon the our divers are about to attempt
the never before the most dangerous stunt in all the world
the bala de canyone and and the
silence we need silence please focus everyone
and then then the diver gets to like you know
he like cracks his knuckles and gets ready and like you know
brings everything down for a second everybody silence
get a pin drop and then cannonball
and then he just does a cannonball that's funny it is like
and that's a thing that I think is funny but kids
get that is a for everybody that is
them writing just good theme parky stuff
so great and then also he's
guiding traffic to the other stuff are you on your way to
the puppet show you should be it starts in three minutes
and now that's my son's hearing that and now he's starting to tug
our sleeves and like yeah are we gonna miss the puppet show I don't
want to miss the puppet show yes all right he's becoming like
Cartman I don't want him to be like Cartman any other capacity but you know
what I mean in that one I wanted to be like Cartman in
that one moment but without the crimes
so anyways now we're starting to explore the other stuff oh wait shit I
forgot that also while you're even though we were only at the table for like 20 minutes
you get so much stuff happening there's the cliff diver shows
and you're raising the flag but then also
like a monkey walks up a monkey comes up to you
and he's wearing the diver shorts
like the divers he it's like communicating that he
wants to be a diver too and he asks
their name and then he spells your kids name
in sign language and then he spells his own name which is
moco so we got original characters is a real monkey
no no it's a guy oh you know what
it was important to clarify because with everything I've described
certainly possible
it's possible they just have a loose monkey in there
I'm glad you asked that no it's a guy in a suit
and the suit is like it's a get like you know
you know that they can pull things off really well and not hokey
so you know it's a choice that you can just see the
break from the head to the body
and this clearly was a tradition of
I think the monkey would like go get in fights next to the waterfall
and like punch the cliff divers off of the cliff
and stuff like that and Trey has said he wants
to go there sometimes and do shifts as moco
sure it could have been him I don't know
maybe that was the moco I think there were
balloon animals there was like a I didn't even understand
this story that like a female pirate
was going around like recruiting pirates and that was just
too confusing to us and food was coming and like
we'll talk to you later pirate so I don't know you can follow the pirate plot line
now we're getting it's like now it's we're in immersive
territory yeah really
so then we start walking around let's go see what else
there is to do you go into a little town square
there is a wishing well I just walk
past it listener don't walk past the wishing well I found
it in a video later there's a face down at the bottom
there's a guy talking to you at the bottom of the wishing well
there's so many I missed a lot of things and I was there
for a while then we get into
kind of like the main entertainment zone
which is home to the puppet show and
Black Bart's cave the puppet show
I will also issue a spoiler alert
because they don't
allow you to film it wow they're really
strict about not filming this puppet show I
not exactly sure why that is but I don't
I want to respect their rules and like I guess
they just really want people to come experience it for themselves
yeah a puppet show one of the things in Cartman
speed run I think he doesn't have time to do it I think the
cops block his way so I got to see
it and he didn't the puppet show is
so much fun it is a little like
puppet show variety show hosted by
Mexican food again the narrator is
Trey Parker and he does a big build up of
ladies and gentlemen your host a taco
and then it's a mix of pre-recorded stuff that
they do and then live performers
who are there right operating puppets in this weird way
where it's like they're pulling the trigger of a gun like you just
see like they just have like a black glove
over some kind of black mechanism and they're just pulling it back
and forth so they're like they're operating a puppet gun
and then you get like little variety show
acts with like there's a chip
that does a cliff dive into
a really teeny bowl of salsa
and a big build up to that and then when he hits
it goes black and they're screaming an ambulance
sounds like he didn't make it and then
whatever Trey Parker narration like oh no so sorry so sorry
I had to see that not only is his voice in it
there's like a living rock
and a tree and it's their two voices
and we are now in country bear jamboree territory
this is where I started to get like really
emotional I knew that they made this restaurant
look nicer I knew that they fixed the paint
and made the food better I didn't know
that this is Trey Parker's opportunity to do his own
country bear jamboree so cool
again rich celebrities
spend money they spend their money on the most inane
shit and like brand expansions
who is doing anything as cool as setting up their own
personal country bear jamboree
that's the dream yeah that's the dream
they really did it they did it and it's what whenever
Cartman comes into a lot of money he does stuff like this
he bought an amusement park at one point so that he didn't
have to ever wait in line he turned his hot dog
place into a fun restaurant they like they did what
Cartman did yeah it's crazy
so that anyway the show is just so fun my son and I
are both laughing like Walt Disney's dream
it works for both of us it's bringing us all together
then they encourage all the audience to say
more sopapias please together
and then from the ceiling of the puppet theater
comes a sopapia swinging
on a swing like swinging teddy bear wow
really yeah yes they fully do
real country bear jamboree stuff I was gonna say
up until that point you could
maybe a plausible deniability that that was country bears
or that they're in like there's other versions of shows
yeah they're in Chuck E. Cheese territory or something
I still have yet to find some sort of an interview with them where they
just talk about like Disneyland and stuff yeah
and I don't know that they're I don't
I'm not gonna guess that they are nerds to the degree
that we are but I think they took trips that had a big impact
on them could they name all of the bear rugs
probably not I know the full history
of Figment but clearly they locked into
that song I think they had like really formative
Disneyland or Disney World trips
that like added for all of the first four South Park
being like super cynical
and super dirty and profane and whatever
there is like just sincerity at times to the
entertainment and to the storytelling and I feel like I don't know
I think they have that theme park gene in them that probably helps
I'm just curious yeah about how far it goes
because it's clearly pretty far
I mean yes I was thinking about you as soon as I saw this
and you having identified that like alright
it felt like a sequel to them doing a clear tribute to Journey into Imagination
yeah they have put money
into a Swingin' Teddy Barra tribute
yeah the Journey into Imagination specifically
because like you know we've seen country bear parodies here and there
there's a country bear parody in The Critic that I really like
and when Duke has his own country bear
like Jambri in his office I don't remember this
I forget I think he's talking to Jay's I forget the name
of some of the characters Jay's girlfriend what's her name
yeah I remember and he's talking about how you know us southern people
people all think that we're a certain way or whatever and then he hits a button
and then like these janky robots come home
like where are the bears who sing for Duke do da
and then one of the bears burps and I think Duke goes like that dumb
belching bear or whatever really funny
so like there's stuff like that but I don't know
the Imagination one always hit me as like wait a minute
so you've never seen a reference to that anywhere
and again it's the thing you had you could only
it wasn't even in the other parks you had to go to Disney World
exactly yeah Dreamfinder specific country bears made it into like the popular
like the lexicon yeah calling things a Jambri
is like kind of you know kind of like
you don't have to be a theme park to know that but
but now it's called musical Jambri because they're worried people don't
know what a Jambri that's what the new version and that ride in Tokyo is
called fairy Tinkerbells whatever
busy buggies is that what it's called I kind of almost like
that one I just don't understand fairy
no I know it's the same we really don't understand we haven't communicated
that Tinkerbell is a fair like superhero
Avengers campus yeah I guess they
just do some testing and there's like five percent of the audience doesn't know
it so they're like we can't take any chances finding Nemo parentheses
fish submarine voyage yeah
that it does feel like the way it's going where you're like it's called
country musical Jambarino really
does it have to be called that Matterhorn Mountain with a
monster inside right Matterhorn
Mountain like a thing you can see
on earth for real
rocks but not really right
Alice Jay Sherman's girlfriend is
Alice oh thank God thank you I was checking
just to make sure it wasn't Helen oh yeah
she's pretty well developed
yeah anyways
also the sopopea
which it was as I said the shining
part of the meal the sopopea being the
beauty of the show was so the
glamorous the Miss Piggy of this was
so perfect and it also came right after another one that's like
the beef combo and the beef combo just like
looked like what the food really looks like yeah
done very like it's just like very mundane
kind of brown food and it kind of like couldn't figure out anything funny
to do and that felt like their comment on like kind of
the plainness of the food sure but the sopopea is the star
of the show the elegant sopopea
I was so excited in this moment my son is having
so much fun I am like I just I'm so
high on how well they pulled this off and
the personal touches from them and then I get to
walk a couple of feet and go into Black Barts Cave
again I've never been in this place before I
didn't grow up with Black Barts Cave why am I
tearing up the site of Black Barts Cave
all I know this from is an episode of South Park
where it's said really flippantly by the worst child on earth
well Black Barts Cave scary and he goes through it and
it specifically looks terrible it's like a very
as they portray it on the show it's an almost empty room
with two skeletons lying on the ground and yet
just the mythology of this and the build up and that
we are like you know in another part of the
country in a place we've never been and I don't know
maybe the maybe the high elevation is making me more
misty or something too I don't know what it is but
either way I swear I tear up in a way that I haven't
maybe for a themed experience since like
opening day Galaxy's Edge where they were all
applauding as we were coming in or being in Disney
Sea and seeing the volcano for the first time Black
Barts Cave made me feel that way and now
I'm like dashing in there and
dragging my son and missing the fact that it's very
dark and he's afraid of dark places and there's
signs that say like maybe too scary for youngins
and he's like what is this I'm like don't worry about
it's gonna be fun and then Aaron has to go up and like
no Scott no he's like this is
clearly too scared he's scared and he's not even in it yet
okay fine sorry I am so just determined
to get into Black Barts Cave I have blinders on
so he is seized back to the front of the line
I go in it myself boy is this not disappoint
this is like it's like the Snow White ride it's like
it's like the way those Fantasyland rides are kind of
like claustrophobic like the way like I forget which one
is more like cavern and you're just like going through little turns
and it's really creepy or it's a little
bit and you know actually you know what it starts a little bit Snow White
and like Dwarves Mine and all that and then it becomes
like Mr. Toad because they
had to do a little bit of like figuring out okay
the people who thought of this did not do any math about what
Black Bart is but we have to because like
wait hang on he's like is he
a pirate or is he an old west guy and why does
he if he's an old west guy then why does he have a cave
and why like it was just it was too many mythologies at once
and I think they did a little clarification but I think Trey Parker
like they put like the head of South Park's story on this
like the guy who conceives of the stories for the video
games right he is working out the story
of Black Bart's cave and I think Trey ultimately encouraged like
I think it is just ten things all at once I think let's just
like lay into the confusion and that yeah you go into an
it's an old west guy's cave but
then there's a dragon in it and you go into the
dragon's mouth and it has a beating heart so what
like you sense that they were just like I don't know
just like kitchen sink throw it all in whatever
they kind of see the idea that like
Black Bart is like hiding his treasure and
putting up fake booby traps to stop you from going
in to get it and like so there's like jump scares
which I'm glad my son got out of there but the jump scares
are fake and set up by Black Bart so you don't
get his treasure and you keep hearing like
full throttle Trey Parker voice as things pop up
and like there's no treasure in here turn back
and then you get
to the treasure and it is like
it's very pirates and there's this wonderful shimmery
light and it's gold and glowy everywhere so it's
like coins and gold bars but then also
a 70s evil Knievel lunchbox
so it's like a 70s child's idea of what the
ultimate treasure would be. That's funny. But then
it starts to say like say your prayers varmint you're done fur
and then you go into a very Mr. Toad hell
dragon's mouth. Again they've
like they've already done their pirates in their Mexico pavilion
and now there's like a tiny walk through that's like a fantasy land
ride. Wow. I am just so lit up
and then like alright
well I guess we're wrapping up and it's almost bedtime
so we better get out of here. Wait what's up those stairs?
Giant arcade. Still an arcade to go
and we walk up the stairs okay here's arcade and
a shooting gallery and a root beer bar.
There's root beer on tap.
Now I'm interested. No he's crying he's crying
he's tearing up. I'm just sobbing.
Root beer on tap what a good idea
for kids that's awesome and they don't get to go to bar
I always love that I feel like I don't ever
drink root beer but I romanticize the idea of it
like I wish it was more like I imagine
where it's big and frosty and cold mugs
do either of you get
root beer at restaurants I guess but
he pours root beer in a cereal every morning. I love it on tap
yeah I love like real tapped root beer.
Where else are you getting tapped root beer?
You see it so rarely I feel like maybe nots
or like places. Maybe somewhere yeah.
That do root beer float do like
a lot of root beer floats in a frosty mug.
There was an A&W in Woodfield
and I feel like maybe actually I don't
I'm trying to remember in my mind they had that but maybe it wasn't
maybe it was shitty. I think I was driving
from Ithaca to Pennsylvania once and I pulled into
an A&W I went inside and it was just
like it was bad unlimited no well the food was
nothing yeah but they had a keg of root beer
and they gave you a frosty mug. Oh a keg
and you did a keg stand on it.
Doing a keg stand on the sugar root beer yeah.
I'm thinking like well you know what like the
video the old video game Tapper that
factors into Wreck-It Ralph oh yeah yeah
Is that beer or is it root beer? Do they make it root beer
because it's for kids? Probably right? I don't know the answer.
I'm not entirely yeah I'm not entirely sure but I always like
I guess I've never thought about this before that like
you know you can't drink I didn't want to drink beer when I was a kid but I love the idea
of like kegs, wood going up to a
bar, saloon style like I wanted
like the 1910s idea and that a guy with
a twirling mustache and a bowler hat would serve
it to me like root beer as the in between
of like it's like a I don't know I don't know like
a bar that a child is allowed to be at that also
feels like the old west. Yeah maybe Huckleberry Hound is
around he's on the. That absolutely works yes.
The cowboys of Mumaesa did not drink alcohol
but they certainly sidled up to a bar
or two in their day. Did they make a point of being
straight at were they specifically sober and talked about it?
I don't know if there was any beer in the world.
Mumaesa was a dry mesa. Baby X's on their
hands if you're wondering. This is a question I guess
in a lot of cinematic universes
do they have alcohol? Which is
it's very satisfying when it's answered like Star Wars and then when
you maybe get to go experience it to some extent for yourself.
I mean everyone has a different answer.
I don't know we could go through them quickly but
the MCU does but it's they you know
Tony Stark was drunk in one scene in Iron Man 2.
Okay. That was as close as they were getting to his
demon in a bottle alcoholic arc. Is there a prominent like and I'm not
talking about like getting a beer on Earth in the MCU
which is like one of the planets have a drink.
Is there a prominent MCU like weird space drink?
Oh that's a good question. I don't know that off the top of my head.
And if not would you like to invent one? Yeah I mean is like
Xandar. Is there some sort of Xandarian drink? Maybe.
I'm trying to remember. I mean in Star Trek
there's Romulan ale. That's the big one.
It's an illegal drink. I don't know if it's
been made legal in other like other future Star Treks
or I should say recent Star Trek. Picard has a
winery. Picard has a winery but wine yeah wine is
legal. Yeah. But Romulan ale is like absent
or something. Oh I see. Oh that's kind of exciting.
There's like somebody will pull it out behind like I got a little of this.
Has there ever been a physical place like the Vegas Star Trek experience
where you could get Romulan ale? You could get it at the Star Trek
experience. Wow. But I don't know if there's a current place.
What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.
Got my hands on some Romulan ale. I really really
want to go on a Star Trek cruise or finally go to start
the big Star Trek con in Vegas in August. I don't know that
I'll do it this year but. It's never occurred to me that you would go on a
Star Trek cruise. I mean I remember your enthusiasm
similar to mine in this episode when we talked about the Star Trek cruise
but I don't think I thought through that you kind of want to do it.
I do want to do it yeah. All the oldest
character actors are there.
Mike's recipe for good party as we know. Yeah.
Free alcohol and possible presence of Armin Schimmer.
Armin Schimmer. I think he'll be at both. I think he's doing
the rounds. So yeah yeah for sure.
Well they have to serve some equivalent of Romulan ale you would have to imagine.
Yeah so right. Maybe it's not like Paramount
approved necessarily but someone is doing it.
Someone is making Romulan ale. Thank God. When Paramount's
away the cats will play. Paramount though I do
think licensed an official Picard winery wine
at some point. Oh well that'd be worth it. I should try that.
This is a whole area I guess. The Star Trek. Star Trek
beverages. We should see if we can get our hands on them do some taste test.
Sure. That sounds like an episode to me. Yeah.
Anyway at this point I thought I was wrapping it up and when
I just saw that there was a root beer bar I was like
get another drink here we go. And I went and got that old Diablo.
Oh yeah. And I sent out a bunch of fun with
Ski Ball and like it was just like well chosen arcade
games and there was a shooting
gallery which was having only done the first
shooting gallery of my life several days prior.
I've just never really done them. Like kind of old style shooting
galleries where there's a little set and they like you activate
little effects and I discovered in this one which I'll
get into in a future episode how precise they are
and how bad I was at them. So then several days
later I'm in the Casa Benita one it's very forgiving. Right. They just want
you to like turn on all the stuff. Sure. Like you know
there's like a big bear and a sombrero and
like you know snakes you can make kiss and then a skunk
that spins around and sprays. It has spray in it.
That's great. It's like beyond like you know
deep down in the list of cool things about this. One of the
coolest shooting galleries I've ever seen. Next to the root
beer bar this whole zone was so charming and then I
saw like an outhouse door that says knock
first and I was like that's a clue. That means I'm
supposed to knock. And then I told my son to do it
and I'm like I bet I know where this is going and quickly
there were big farts and poop sounds
and a guy saying I'm going to be a while
and this is the most up my four year
old's alley. He has lit up ever since he's been saying
let's play knock on doors and we have to
respond with poop or fart sounds. So that stayed
with he took so many things back home with him from
this situation. We're just
like truly in a dead. When we round that other corner this
is where it starts to click in like I think over the course
of really we've done a lot of it this year because this year we've talked about
Bullwinkles and Rainforest Cafe and all the
stuff in the city walk Orlando Saga and this idea
of like the restaurant that's so huge
that it has like twists and turns and corners
and that's up there and you can't possibly do it in
one visit. I feel like you know so often these
things get worn down and like you know bought out by
something else and it gets shittier and like the dream of what it was
like wow there's five rooms and all this stuff.
This is like the most I've ever experienced
this modern day and certainly the
got to be the only one that is like new
in twenty twenty one or whenever I think it would open
last year I guess actually to the public but like
at the height of its power
possibly. Yes it is like what we're
describing. This genre of restaurant all reached the height of its power
in like nineteen eighty three. Right. With the exception
of this place. This is the only one that is
at its best right now. Right. It's so cool.
It's everything we want. It's the detail
like it's all the details and the extra shit
that if a computer were to crunch numbers
is superfluous. Yes. This is the whole thing.
It's the first to go. How does that help the bottom line?
Actually it might specifically really hurt the bottom line
and I understand at some point the need to be
profitable and to run a business that makes sense.
I don't care about that but yeah go ahead. Well I
don't care about it. I shouldn't care about it.
I understand the concept of that.
I understand on some level the idea that you would start a restaurant and want to make money
on it and that's why
I think we've run into this before. The only way
we can have these places that we want is if they are going
to lose money. Is if they are going to be big financial
disasters. God bless these guys
for being willing and seemingly excited to set up
a big financial disaster. Sure. I saw it too
that like so the weights
it kind of makes sense now learning about the quality of the
food that rather than the wait staff
relying on tips everyone's just making
$30 an hour. Yes, yeah. They just like
really upped the standard of what everybody makes
which helps the speed of everything and that's great and
they kind of retained the staff
when they bought it and everybody who was still on board
when COVID hit they kept them employed
and they just like you kept them on the payroll and sent them
to like volunteer and go to soup kitchens
and like places that
helped the needy. So yeah, they like they employed everybody
up their salaries sent them out to do charity
work. Cool. Great.
So that aspect of it too. They're like they're treating
people right. At this point the night actually
is winding down. We got to put the kid out of bed. How long have you been here?
Two hours and we could have easily we were saying like
at least one more. I think there's I think there's possibly
a four hour version of writing in this place. I don't
think that would be a stretch at all because then there's entire rooms
that I missed. If you don't do the cliffside dining
you probably end up seating sitting in a whole area that I just
ran through really fast which was like you're in a
mine and there's explosions that go off and there's
a love tester down there. There's a fortune telling prospector
named a Sayer Joe. Whoa.
And I don't know what he is but I bet if I put money into him
he might talk with Trey Parker's voice too. Probably.
Like you also part of the dream of this kind of restaurant we've
we've described in like pine forest and that we've never gotten to go to
is the possibility of getting lost. And I did get lost.
I couldn't find Aaron. I don't know where they went.
This is exactly what a restaurant big enough that an adult
can legitimately get lost in there. They pulled it off.
They did it here. I didn't get to see
Sor Soro the magician. I don't know
what the hell that is. I missed that there is a place
to take a picture with Cartman that they gave him
permanently. Whoa really. The booth where he
ordered sopapias. That just now has
a big weird Cartman at it and that's kind of the only
real South Park nod. I think they were very
spare. They put their own voice in but it's like feels very organic
to the experience. They didn't make it like subtly South
Park the restaurant. Right. And I appreciate that about it. I think
there's somewhere where you can find Man Bear Pig but I didn't
find that either. Stuff I missed. I barely saw
something you put money into and a bunch of puppet monkeys
dance around. I barely got to see the museum. There is
so much. I've never seen a restaurant
with this much stuff to do. I think you're underselling
it even calling it a restaurant. It's like an indoor theme park.
It is the Disneyland of Mexican restaurants. They absolutely
earned it. I also I appreciate
that they didn't like you know again
that I don't think these guys are that crass in their need to like
make money at every turn. They didn't like fill it with like South
Park merch. I was like will this be then will you get to the end
and it's South Park merch. Instead you get to the Mercado. You get
to this like wonderfully rendered gift
shop and it's so
many items with the logo on it and
boy is it a great logo. It's a beautiful website.
I love everything about it. Just like perfect 70s
aesthetic. I've never spent more a gift shop in my entire
life. I bought so much stuff. I got the flag.
I bought a bar mat for my friend.
I bought a shirt. It's an old banner
like very like 70s theme park style or
like pennant I guess. Yeah that's what I meant.
And for you gentlemen
I got a couple of Costa Veneta
shot glasses
of the bubble wrap.
They're kind of like
warm yellow adobe style.
Yeah really cool. The tower of the restaurant is in the
logo. And it looks old.
Yeah it feels very 70s but it's made nicely.
You're welcome. Even though I know I made the
assessment in the moment in the past Mike you have
been flummoxed by why somebody
would have a shot glass in the home because you're not really doing shots
at home you said. But I still made the calculation
that you might be able to get your head around it.
If you want to have a precise pour.
It's a perfect yes.
Exactly a one shot drink.
If you want to not over pour.
It's usually one and a half tablespoons
or two tablespoons. So you could
use it for like measuring coffee too.
Coffee beans.
That's true.
Are you relieved to hear that there are many
things that you can do that aren't doing a dreadful shot
in the comfort of your own home? I am relieved to hear
that yes. Many uses you see.
You could bathe your daughter with it. You could also measure
out if you want to drink it home you measure out a shot poured over ice
or poured in a glass.
That's true. No need to do the shot act.
Did I do a shot in the last six months? I feel like I did
and I can't remember where. I feel like I did but
I don't remember why. Well that means the shot worked baby.
I guess so yeah. Well I can also just make
an upside down hat for one of my plushes.
That's very good yes.
Or I hate to summon more drunkenness in your home
but you could put it over the head of
party animal Michelangelo.
Or party Angelo as I call him.
And make it look like it's kind of like a lamp shade
over his head. Well it would work for my quarter scale
Michelangelo because he's this big.
Perfect fit. I bought guitars for all my quarter scale turtles.
You bought separate guitars really?
Yeah because Fender will make a tiny quarter scale guitar.
So you sized out what will match? Exactly.
You bought special guitars
for your four special guys. That's correct.
And now that's the second round of turtles that have guitars
because I have of course the quarter scale coming out of our shells turtles
as well that came with their instruments.
But in this case you had to make them
musicians. Exactly. That's nice.
Okay well yeah enjoy those.
I just wanted to have the logo in my house a lot
and have the memories of this place a lot.
If it's not clear enough I was so blown away by this place.
I felt exactly like Cardman after the speed run
after he himself did the cliff dive.
Just in an absolute daze. Was it worth it? Totally.
I went 100% there. I didn't want to leave.
I said goodbye wistfully sadly
like I was leaving Disney World as did my son.
None of us wanted to leave. I'm dying to go back.
If I could figure out a way to go back.
This place, I think what's so beautiful about it
it's like the dream of one crazy guy
and what happens to the dream of one crazy guy.
Corporations, it just gets run into the ground
by some bland weird entity and it gets worse and worse
until it becomes silly and not what it used to be.
This is the only scenario I've ever seen
a crazy guy and then two crazier guys
did something even crazier with it.
I really commend them for it
and also for, as you were saying, it's in the Tarantino zone.
Celebrities, look, everybody's trying to be an entrepreneur.
Everybody's trying to expand their brand portfolio
and it's all with a bunch of boring shit
because everybody just slaps their names on
and I'm sorry I don't want to say fighting words
but things like tequilas, everybody just slaps their names.
Well, everyone copied a certain couple guys' tequila
so I agree with you post-Casamigos.
Some people just slap their names on something
copying the roguish act of two renegades
riding through the countryside
perfectly synced up on the coolest hogs you've ever seen.
It's, by the way, all we're talking about here
is out of control.
Every single person has a coffee.
Robert Downey Jr. has a coffee.
Dolly Parton announced a new wine.
Every single person of any prominence now
has some grift that they're in on.
And there's always been that but it used to be cheesy.
It used to be corny that Ed McMahon had some item.
Now we want it, we celebrate it.
We love hustle and some of these things are fine
but usually it's a bunch of shit
and at its worst it's celebrities all doing ads for crypto
and I don't want to get on a high horse about this
but I was just thinking of the juxtaposition
of today what we encourage, if you made your money
with creative stuff, you were then supposed to put
a bunch of money and make a bunch more money
on just worthless landfill crap, right?
That's the idea. It's what we encourage.
It's what we are dying to get all of our top stars to do.
In this case, these guys,
they did something that so reflects who they are
that is like giving back in a way.
Yes, it's for profit.
You got to pay a bunch of money to go there
but it feels like they were like trying to retain
the magic of the Denver that they grew up with.
It completely reflects who they are creatively.
They didn't just slap their name on something
and go to make a bunch more money so they can invest
more money in some other crap.
It's just cool. It's really cool what they did
in a way that in this area
what famous people do anything this cool?
Yeah, if you're going to be a millionaire, I guess in this case
they're probably billionaires.
You may at least be eccentric.
That is valued at a billion at least.
That's what's insane.
This is nothing for them.
Just an easy 40 mil.
A lark, an eccentric lark.
Tarantino's rescued two movie theaters at this point.
Also, there is, I want to say,
a good on them but a team
of 25, 30 filmmakers saved the Westwood
historic movie theater.
That's good. That's cool.
There's 30 of you.
There's one of him. He rescued two.
My question is when is Jason Reitman
going to start saving some Chuck E. Cheese's?
On his own.
Maybe Gil Keenan can help him out.
We know he loves his 80s stuff.
We're trying to bring back the 80s and his child.
Put your money where your mouth is and save a lot of those robots.
I'll give him credit because he does a lot of those stage reading
of scripts at LACMA,
at the art museum, and I believe tickets for those
that he's usually funding.
That's the only end to that sentence.
I was going to say funding the art museum, but I'm sure they get to
allocate some of the stuff.
He should pay to flip that art museum into
a revived Chuck E. Cheese and showbiz pizza.
Put them all together.
Only then will I be happy, Mr. Reitman.
I will say something very Chuck E. Cheese at LACMA.
There is an art piece that is just a boulder
and you can walk under the boulder.
I've seen the boulder. That's pretty cool.
George Lucas is doing this.
He's doing the museum, but you know what I'm talking about.
This giant museum that's being built in LA.
I don't know what's in it, though.
You've seen the picture, though.
It's crazy looking and it's huge.
I think he's financing the whole thing himself.
Was that supposed to go in Chicago?
Then it was supposed to go in San Francisco, I think.
I don't think it will, but it's big enough
to have something fun in it.
It's going to be good. Something is going to be cool.
He is using his billions.
I've just started to think that generationally.
A Spielberg or a Lucas have put money back
into the arts.
Saving things that are important to them.
When have you seen it in the last decade?
People spending their creative earned money
on something really cool doesn't really happen.
Here's another thing I was thinking about.
These guys got very, very rich from animation.
Now they have spent a bunch of money
on a really risky enterprise.
A themed enterprise that is partially
to recreate the little town that they grew up in
and to bring back some of the spirit
of the town that they grew up in
using their cartoon money.
Does that sound familiar?
Who else did something like that?
Maybe a gentleman named Walt fucking Disney.
Maybe that's who did that.
Maybe these guys are the only people
following in Walt fucking Disney's footsteps.
You have to have an insanely rich person
that's in charge of all their money
that just forces something crazy.
I don't know where themed entertainment
would be if the precedent wasn't set
by Walt Disney to put so much extra crap
in Disneyland.
Just performers and details and everything.
They got every bit of it right.
You turn a corner and there's this thing over here.
I've said this before.
If the bar hadn't been set there,
I don't know that we'd ever have anything else
approaching it.
What comes before Disney is
Carnivals and Coney Island and stuff.
You have to include the stuff that inspired him.
Tivoli Gardens and Knott's was on its way before him,
but not fully what it became.
The first out of the gate,
but really the first modern theme park in a way.
You're right, if they hadn't set the bar there,
we would allow theme parks to be
much more rinky-dink, much crudder.
There's the whole talk right now
because of this union agreement.
Have you seen this where Disney is canceling
live performances in the park?
You're speculating.
Some people are saying, Dr. Strange,
those performers were AGVA,
which was a contract that was already in place.
It could be canceling live entertainment
to get quarterly profits,
quarterly revenue in shape.
They canceled Club Pixar,
which is something that was supposed to run for all summer.
All that stuff is extra stuff
they don't need to be doing,
but there's still enough at Disneyland that's extra.
I'm just saying you start out up here,
so when they start taking things away,
and they have taken things away in the last so many years,
it's just like, well, they started out here,
so it's still pretty great,
even though they start canceling stuff that's all the fun extras.
The first things to go are live performers
and people with special skills
or just who are really fun to watch who make the place special.
Casa Bonita is a new place.
I was there for two hours, and what did I see?
Bunch of cliff divers, puppet show, live performers,
a monkey trainer came up to my table.
I didn't even get to see Sor Soro,
whatever Sor Soro is.
There is a current Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen
that kept one thing.
They kept the cliff divers, but then it's only on Fridays,
and it looks like shit.
There is a version where Casa Bonita comes back,
and it is just a little fun nod
that we sort of nod to that this place was fun
instead of making it twice as fun as it was before.
What I'm saying is Trey and Matt did a better job
with the modern Walt Disney Company.
This is the best thing I've done for the show in a couple years.
One of the best things ever. We've been doing this for a while.
This is one of the most excited I've ever been about anything.
I'm just sorry that it wasn't with you guys.
I'm sorry it was a little solo mission, but if you can figure it out,
get there, listeners go.
It is such a special thing and so neat that it can happen
that we don't need to rely on our gods at Disney and Universal
to Dane to do something cool for us,
that these guys were willing to waste a ton of money.
They described them so they said,
you have to be as rich as us and as stupid as us
to get something like this done, and I thank them for their stupidity.
God bless you, Casa Bonita.
And I look forward to what is apparently a documentary coming
by the end of the year, Casa Bonita, Mia Moore,
in which they go into this process,
I want to know everything about how they put this together
because the word, I said it as soon as I walked out,
as soon as I left the dim hues of the restaurant
and was harshly let out into the still bright Colorado sun.
It's like it's still light, you're kidding.
And the first thing out of my mouth was triumph.
This is a triumph.
And how great does it feel to see a new triumph
in themed entertainment in 2024?
It sounds closer to Meow Wolf in execution.
Yeah.
Yes, that it's like off the grid,
that the money comes from a weird place, that it is in Denver.
Now, I didn't get to do that.
I did not go to Convergence Station,
which is the Denver outpost.
I did experience the Meow Wolf ride at Elitch Gardens.
Oh, right.
We're going to talk about that on The Second Gate.
We're going to talk about Elitch Gardens soon.
Elitch Gardens is another thing you can do in Denver.
But let's end on a positive note.
Let's make it a hard split.
God bless you guys.
Thank you for making this great place for Denver
and for America and for the world.
Wow.
Check out three bonus episodes every month.
Check out Podcast The Ride The Second Gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride,
including, I think, Elitch Gardens, although I'm going to have to,
I mean, like, could be Maine.
It's buckle up for Elitch Gardens.
Elitch Gardens is something.
Listeners told me to buckle up.
I guess I can't do Casa Bonita.
Well, I can still do Elitch Gardens and people went out of their way.
Listeners went out of their way to communicate.
Don't do that. If you can't get into Casa Bonita,
don't just go to Elitch Gardens.
And thank God it worked. Thank you, Joe Carnegie.
Thank you, Landon. And thank you, listeners.
Get on that list.
If you didn't do it at the top of the show, do it now.
Go to the website. Let's get it done. OK. All right.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team
and liking our page on Facebook.