FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning the following podcasts may contain unified taffy agreements
Chuck E. Cheese's skeleton wearing the skin of a different animal
A very rare mention of F-troop actor Larry Storch
And the danger of teens claiming too many boardwalk benches
All that plus Alan McLeod joins us to talk the Ocean City, New Jersey boardwalk
On today's podcast, The Ride
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, but today alt title, Taffy Boys
I'm Taffy Boy Scott, there over there is Taffy Boy Jason
I was wondering if you were going to go for Seaside Confections
Or the title America's Greatest Family Resort
Which is heavy marketing
Jason, I could not go too, this is deeper than I can go
Because this is not my place, it's not a place I've been
It's a place you've been, we've talked about before
Basically a second home
Yeah, and a place dear to our guests seemingly
Mike Carlson, I don't know
Never been, but I am a Taffy Boy
You don't have to be in Ocean City to be a Taffy Boy
Catch all of this, I feel like Ocean City boardwalk is that kind of the way to
I think that's right, Ocean City, we need to clarify Ocean City, New Jersey
Because Ocean City, Maryland is a very different town
Is another thing, yeah, and I got confused in some research where I started
Because it seems like there's like two main parks that we're dealing with on the boardwalk here
And then I bumped into a third and like, what are you, hang on, what?
A whole other, and then really got a little bit into it and realized it was Maryland
A whole different history, Ocean City, Maryland
So that means, Trimper's Rides, you're out
Out on the Trimper
Enjoy getting air right now, because that's it for you, Trimper
Not till we make it to Maryland, but we're in New Jersey here
And this comes courtesy of a great guest, somebody who, it defies logic that he has not been here yet
And I'm happy it's happening
Being on the show, you'd have to say, it's a no-brainer
Very glad to have
He's got a great new podcast called Walkin' About
And I'm excited to talk about that
If you're a Doughboyz fan, you know him as Molasses Boy
It's Alan McLeod, hello
Hey, oh my gosh
I'm so happy to be on
I guess it does, everything's so crazy in the world
It does seem logical now that I am here, you know
Yes, finally, finally, there's something, things make sense
This crazy world of ours
It's good to be here with all the taffy boys
I am a Molasses Boy
Which is also available
Aesthetically very close
It's very close and it's available at the same shops that you might find along the boardwalk if you're getting your saltwater taffy
Sticky and sweet, both molasses and taffy
Well, and I saw a big line, I watched a video that filmed a big line of taffy barrels
At the place you've talked about before, Jason, Shriver's is the name of it
Shriver's, yeah
Home of Mr. Taffy, a mascot character, you brought us a toy that my son loves
And I saw in that line up of taffy barrels some molasses taffy
There you go
It all ties together
Happy to be in second or third or fourth place, I don't know how you would rank the chewy treats
Oh, Jason should have this on the top of his head
In terms of taffy or in terms of Shriver's?
Shriver's, yeah, yeah
I rank Shriver's pretty high
No, I mean, just as far as like
You're talking more taffy versus molasses versus
I don't know what else
Molasses is not really just you eat it on its own, right?
Do you just drink a cup of molasses?
You guys don't do that?
I can't really picture, I don't have a clear image of if I'm looking at just molasses, what is it?
You don't do that? Well, molasses is like the leftover stuff after you make something good
They're like, what do we do with this shit?
Put it into some cookies or something
It's got a fun name
How do you feel that the nickname that's stuck to you is that it's
Now you're equating it with leftovers
Does it feel like it?
There's something good in everything, you know?
I mean, I don't know, it's a very utilitarian nickname maybe
Use every bit of everything
I've fully accepted that
The name originated from me being slow
Being a slow boy and turned into a slow man that's accepted that name
Did it come from, did they name you that? Did Doughboys name you that?
Or did you come in, has that been floating around?
That's an old football nickname
From being too slow on the offensive line
It's not an easy going attitude
It's now become more of a lifestyle
You've owned it now
That's my brand
But it is nice to see that molasses is available at Shriver's
Which is a place that I love
I love looking at those machines
I love just kind of going to see what they're doing
In that little factory through the window
Yeah, yeah, those like 100 plus year old machines
They're still using
They don't make them like that anymore
So you get to see people doing
It's like on Disneyland Main Street you get to see people making candy apples or something
So you get to see people like doing it, churning it out
Yeah
Working on the taffy
Yeah, it's great
This is wow
The mind meld that happened
Not since you were paired with your own past self
During the City Walk saga was there such agreement
Yeah
I mean this is great
I love that this is where we're starting from
And that you brought us this out
That you wanted to talk about this
Because perfect for Jason, this is great
I love that
But we were both like
Where does your Ocean City, New Jersey fondness come from?
Because you grew up Alabama
Yeah, so this is
And so the
I do
I have a huge fondness for Ocean City
And it's from my wife's family
They do a family reunion there pretty much every year
And have done it since for decades and decades
And then so when I kind of came along
I started accompanying Stacy on these family reunions
And just fell in love with Ocean City
And you know had never really been to
Spent any time in New Jersey like at all
So
And you know I just
I like
While I don't have a nostalgia from being a kid there
I embrace
It's automatically a place you just become nostalgic for
Because it's so stuck in time and just like
Oh sure
Such
Just a fun environment
A fun place to go
Of course I love walking around
So it's like
If you don't like walking
Then I don't know Ocean City might not be the place for you
Yeah
Because not only just
I mean parking is not easy
Like once you kind of find a parking spot
It's like you're not driving around much
Like you just kind of make your way around
And then of course the boardwalk
Which is about two and a half miles long
I think it's eight miles
Oh really
Okay
When
I think two and a half for like
You know
Amusement parks and restaurants and stuff
But the boardwalk keeps going in both directions
To like houses and stuff
Houses and beaches
But the like amusement zone
The amusement zone itself is like two and a half, three miles
Something like that
That's pretty good
That's good
Blocks and blocks
Wow
Of it
Crazy
Yeah
So it's just a place that from getting to go and see my wife's family
And get a sense of like hear all the stories that they've had from when they were kids
And that their parents had from when they were kids
You just kind of develop a real appreciation for it
And taking tours
I remember we took several years ago
Took like a ghost tour around
And it was just hilarious
You know
Because you get to know a bit more about the history of the area
And it was just really funny
Like the guide was just a very old man
Who sort of made an attempt at a costume
With sort of a pirate shirt
And but he kept trying to recruit my friend Chris
And kind of like pass the torch to him
You know
Like who Chris was living in Philadelphia at the time
And he was like
You might be a good guide
You know
And he kept trying to convince Chris
To take over the business
Yeah to take over the business
Like on the tour
It was so funny
Was he doing that like to every group he had
Like finding one person in the group
And going maybe this person will get me out of this hell
Maybe
Or there's a pyramid
Oh yeah perhaps
That's what it is
Yeah
Just give me 10%
But otherwise you control the business
That's a good point
It's funny you say that
Because I never took the ghost tour
But my memory in the mid to late 90s
Is the ghost tour company
And I don't know if it's the same company
I don't know if it's popped up and gone away
But I remember they had a building
Or they had offices shared with
It was ghost tour and internet cafe
And I was brand new to the internet at the time
And I was like mom mom we gotta go over to the city
We gotta check out this internet cafe
And I just remember the signs outside
Like ghost tour slash internet cafe
That's so awesome
I don't know if this ghost tour had a brick and mortar office
I can't imagine
Yeah
And I can't remember that
Sadly I can't remember the name of the tour that we took
But it was very memorable for that aspect alone
Internet cafes are gonna be one of those really hard things to explain to our kids
Now that all cafes are internet cafes
Yes
These had to be specially designated
Okay imagine you're borrowing a dirty desktop computer
Okay a desktop computer is
Let me go back
Well now they have cafes that are specifically non-internet right?
Like I mean
Some places yeah
So you can really like interact with humans I guess that's the idea right?
You're not all on your device
Right so you can like get into that book you're reading
Or really like you know be present with your friends
Right
Well Med like all of the great you know think about Seinfeld, Frasier friends
All of them cafe central location
Right yes
And today all of them would just be they just sit down and plop right down on their phones
That's right yeah
No hijinks would ensue
No relationship discussion
That's so true
Yeah
There'd be no stories would occur we're all missing out you might say
I would say
The existence of Wi-Fi makes it so we don't get into any capers at that one place that we go
Right
I mean it ruins a lot of horror movie stories you know
Yes true
You would text
I would just text the policeman
There was an episode of Studio 60 that took it right up to the wire where like
We're deep in cell phone era like but they wanted to trap some characters on the roof
And they like so they have to write it into it like
We're in the one place in Los Angeles where there's no cell reception
Sorkin has just said on it
Figure it out
I want we gotta trap character there's romantic tension between the characters
We gotta put them on the roof
Figure it out
There's pockets where there's no reception
Wouldn't a roof have better reception?
I don't know
Fuck it
Couldn't they have just left their phones in their office?
No that's a good one
Jeez
Well you should have been in there
Yeah you should have
You should have
I tried I tried so hard to intern on Studio 60
You actually did?
Yes I did
That lined up with your like Okwood summer
It lined up with my out semester in LA
And it was like everyone was like oh Aaron Sorkin's making a new TV show
And it's shooting right at Warner Brothers and on the street from the Okwood apartment
And if you can get in on that you'll be there for 10 seasons straight
And I did not they didn't hire any interns except one person
Because her mom was Bradley Whitford's cousin
There you go
How close did you get?
Did you just how did you learn that about like oh I was rejected
Like did you have an in did you have an inside person?
Oh she told I she was another student
Oh you knew her?
Yeah no I knew her and she was like oh they didn't hire I just got in
I just got in because my mom is related to Bradley
Oh wow
You still got that number?
Give us that contact info we could get in with Bradley Whitford's
Oh I mean I guess so I never really thought about it
We're really close with her
This could be a ticket for all of us
Except when you were like what are you holding out on her?
I want that internship
Okay wait where were we?
That was from cell phone so it was from internet cafes
Okay well speaking of like you know harkening back to times gone by
Am I correct that Ocean City is a dry city?
You are correct
Dry as a bone
Dry as a bone the thing that always makes me laugh
There's I think three bridges into town and at the foot of all those bridges
Cause you can bring alcohol in you can have alcohol in your homes
And you can drink it at home you can't drink it on the beach
But at the foot of every bridge on the mainland is a giant liquor store
Oh as soon as not even one foot from where you get to
Oh yeah we always stop at I can't remember the name of this show
But it's just like that you stop cause you have to fly in for I mean as far as I know
Either from here you fly into like New York or Atlantic City or Philadelphia
Or Philadelphia yeah yeah
So yeah generally the drive from any of those areas you got to stop at one of these bridge liquor stores
Well to also get generally their groceries and stuff too
So you're kind of stocking up for a week or whatever
But yeah that's where people just have carts full of booze
And there is a lot of controversy in the last few years because some restaurants
So for the longest time you couldn't do BYOB
In the last few years some restaurants established membership supper clubs
Where if you paid like 10 bucks 15 bucks you joined the member
You were a member and then you could BYOB
This dance you have to do to what are we retaining here
Because doesn't it just cause because I saw that you know like despite being a dry city
That Ocean City was declared the drunkest town in New Jersey
Does it not just create more
People overcompensate for that maybe
Yeah but also like as I was alluding to at the top
Like at some point I think at a travel channel special it was deemed like
Number one America's greatest family resort
And they just took that moniker and just they have stamped it on beach tags
They've stamped on t-shirts they stamped it on marketing material
Something the travel channel said once
Not any official there was no voting body for this
There might have been voting or it could have been a poll
But I was like I was having trouble finding the origin of it
But I just remember at some point in high school I started to see
Just one day there was all this stuff about America's greatest family resort
Well what was the town what's the town where Bruce Springsteen is from
That's Asbury Park that's further up North Jersey
I feel like there was a time when Asbury Park was a dry town or something
Like a long time ago or something
And then they introduced they made it not a dry town anymore whatever
They made it just a regular wet town
And then it all turned and that's like when the rock and roll scene really like took off
And the people that kind of the the forebearers before even Bruce Springsteen kind of and what led to him you know
So I feel like there's like this new you know the neighboring towns or whatever
Because I don't even know if Atlantic City isn't that probably not a dry town
No Atlantic City and even if you go either direction to either Sea Isle or Margate or Venter
Immediately there's yeah bars so like Ocean City New Jersey is like we're doing our own thing
We're not becoming one of those rock and roll towns
You know we're always drunk coming out of the Taj Mahal or whatever Trump building in Atlantic City
We don't want any global rock stars being born here
Maybe causing tourism
It goes back to the founding because the town was founded by like Methodist who wanted like a wholesome place to go on vacation
Gotcha
And yeah it's just kind of kept the wholesomeness kind of vibe the whole time
But it's funny I say that like Cape May New Jersey which is at the end of like the coast
Also a lot of historical stuff and like you know very focused on preserving the old houses
And a lot of restaurants have been there a long and long time
And people have their traditions family trips family reunions that they do and stuff
But Cape May is like a wet town and it doesn't seem like grimy
Some towns are very wet towns and seem very grimy
Very wet
Yeah
The wettest and the grimmiest of towns
But we just passed Memorial Day weekend and I saw there were at some of the beach towns like Ocean City
At like you know there were a bunch of teens like roving bands of teens
There was only one stabbing which is unusual
Because there's more usually or it's unusual
What's that?
Because there's more stabbing
Usually a number of stabbing
Usually it's just rowdy teens and they just get arrested for what?
Drinking or weed and then they just take them to the police station
And the parents can come pick them up and there's no charges if they do community service
Like this is a thing
But like in Wildwood which is a much larger like wilder Jersey Shore beach town
They declared a state of emergency
There were so many groups of roaming teens
Shit's going down right now in both of these places
Like it seems like the Ocean City thing is more mild although a stabbing
But then yeah the headlines are dramatic
There's a headline from the inquirer.com
Jersey Shore official says unruly teens won't be allowed to steal summer
There's a concern, I mean there's a tension as we record this
I didn't realize what a hot button issue we were talking about
We're at the top of summer here and there's the potential that summer could be stolen
Wow
We gotta stop these teens
I remember when I was in high school
This was a headline then
Like the teens are taking over all the pavilions
Those old people need those benches by the boardwalk
You know the benches on the boardwalk that they can sit and stare at the ocean
Like it's full of goths
It's full of goths
There's makeup and hair dye rubbing on those benches
So what do they do now?
It's like all the beaches are closed at 8pm
But it's like well now the roving bands of teens are on the boardwalk
Just let them go wild
This is a dirty dancing scenario
I was going to say it's like oh yeah
There's some reverend behind this
It's like oh I don't know these teens whose childhood happened during covid
The socialization might be a little off kilter
I mean if anybody would just go out there with a boombox and start playing the Footloose song
They'd just start dancing and that would be the end of it
They wouldn't get violent
That's what I was thinking of with reverend
It is, reverend's the Footloose, that's right
That's what they need
It's a town that banned dancing
Yes
They banned dancing in Footloose
I think that's right
Dirty dancing must be about a town that bans dirty dancing
No they're like at a camp or something
There's just this dirty dancing occurring between people
It's just a bit of a conservative vibe
So dirty dancing incidentally was made at my
It was shot at two different hotels in Virginia
And one of them was a hotel that my Aunt Sharon and Uncle Mac used to be the managers of
Wow
Whoa really
It was at the time so I was going there as a kid to Mountain Lake Virginia
To this hotel even before dirty dancing
Like as a little kid even before
So when dirty dancing came out I was like oh my gosh look at that
Wow that's surreal probably
It was very surreal and it was like just
It's still one of my favorite movies
I can't really separate the two
It is objectively a great movie
But it's one of your favorite home movies
Yeah it kind of brought Hollywood home to me
Because I recognized it and it was just the best
That's pretty exciting
Not even just some movie
Because sometimes it will be like some movie
I mean like lots of stuff filmed around me I guess in the valley
But you know just like Monday
That's just like a living back lot
I'm like oh you know hey Blast from the Past filmed one scene down the street from you
Brendan Fraser
What is that?
Not a time case in like a bombshell
But dirty dancing a pretty like timeless
Where the setting brings a lot to it
So like and people must travel there to go to those places
Somebody Jason and I know grew up on the pond from on Golden Pond
Really? I forgot that one
My big one
And it was very surreal because when it came out I had not traveled back home
In a little while due to the pandemic
But Mare of Easttown is filmed like where I grew up
Like she got in the first or second episode
She goes to an aquarium supply store and I looked up where that was
I was like oh just a quarter mile from the middle school I went to
Like just down the street
Where you manage the football team
The fact I remain obsessed with
You manage a football team in seventh grade
I haven't watched there is there was a movie starring Kristen Wiig
An indie movie that shot in Ocean City
But I haven't watched that one yet
Were they worried about all the Hollywood roughnecks coming in
Bringing their their left coast ideals
Well no I think they were very excited
Because I believe it probably shot in the off season
And I'm sure they were happy for the money
That anything is happening there
Is this a place that is dead when it is not summer
Oh yeah it like contracts
It's like a college town where like
Oh during the school year in this case the summer season
It's like oh there's like 100,000 people
And then the off season it shrinks to like 20,000 people
Okay okay
I have another logistics question
Is any of because I'm keeping
I've had a hard time keeping all these straight
All the Jersey amusement places
There's Ocean City
And then there's these two parks that we'll talk about that are here
Then Wildwood and Maury's Pier
That's way south of everything we're talking about
Correct
I believe Wildwood is south
I forget what's north and what's south
But it's a separate district
Atlantic City is a whole other thing
That's like a little bit up north
Is any of this the Jersey Shore
Or is what you call the Jersey
This is all considered the Jersey Shore
Yeah okay okay
But there is North Jersey Shore
Which that's where you get to like
Asbury Park as we talked about
I believe Long Beach Island
Aledo country is
Oh
That's I think North Jersey where they're flying weird flags
Okay
I've never been anywhere here
I've never been to any of the Jersey Shore
No I haven't done any of this
You've never gone down to the shore
Is that what they say
Yeah you go down
Go down to the shore
Some people
Go down shore
Yeah
Yeah that's the thing
They just
That's the like
Show me way of
Go down shore
Oh we're going down the shore this weekend
Hope them rain
Hope them rain don't
Ain't bad
Wow
When it's
That's great to hear
When it's the off season
Are they still making as much taffy
As they do during the peak
Shriver's is one of the boardwalk businesses
That are open like all year round
And I don't think they're making as much
But they certainly are
But are they shipping out
Or are they making taffy just for the boardwalk
Sorry to go back to taffy
No they have a big shipping business
Yeah they have a big online business
Okay so they're working in there
But they're shipping a lot of that out
That's not just being made for the patrons
Of the boardwalk
Okay
Yeah no they have a big shipping business
Some listeners on our discord
The discord that fans made for the show
They sent me a Shriver's gift basket
Really
A while back
Yeah
Wait a minute did the gift basket include
Because I'm going into Shriver's
And I'm looking up Mr. Taffy
He brought that toy
And in the Google images
I'm like wait a minute
There's a book called The Birth of Mr. Taffy
First of all you ever seen Mr. Taffy Alan
I recognize Mr. Taffy
You've seen him around
I've seen him around
I didn't know about this book
You've seen him stroll in the store
Oh god was there a book
There might have been a book
I'm upset I can't like find even a preview page
Because I want to know his story very much
I mean Jane and I both
You know we have insane sweet tooths
So we like just like rabbit
You might have eaten the book
Animals we tore through
We might have eaten it
Yeah it's very possible
Insane sweet tooth tore through
I like the word choices
I really appreciate it there
I think there is Taffy in the freezer
Because you can freeze Taffy
You know if you have Taffy in that freezer
I know I know I still have Taffy in the house
I'm not sure if it's in the cabinet
I don't know
I know I still have Taffy in the house
I'm not sure if it's in the cabinet or freezer
You just don't know where it's located
Yeah I don't know where it's located
Or if you're like hiding it in the toilet
You know the compartment over the toilet
In case any burglars break in
And then they wouldn't think to look there
And steal your Taffy
Well and it's too Taffy too
So like it doesn't really go
Because Shriver's has info like brochures
And they're like if it gets hard
You just rub it between your hands
You warm it up a little and it softens it
So Taffy stays good forever
As long as you roll it and rub it
It stays good for a really long time
You have to rub it twice a year
You rub it every other six months
You roll it every other six months
You warm up your Taffy when you change
Your smoke detector battery
If you hear the chirp of the detector
It's time to roll the Taffy
Also functions as the Taffy detector
Okay rub rub rub rub rub
And we're set
Alright I'll see you in a couple years buddy
Keep aging
Am I crazy to sit like
Maybe not really growing up with a lot of Taffy
Taffy's the thing I will
I'm fine to have one thing of Taffy
Every three years
By that I mean one piece of it
One inch long piece of it
Is that insane?
Am I missing out on great Taffy possibilities in my life?
I like sweets
I'm not buying a lot of Taffy
If somebody offered me Taffy sure
But it's not my go to
And also my teeth
It's not good for your teeth
No this is a jersey
I'll take it out of your mouth right now
For audio fidelity
You probably should have stopped chewing it
I'm experiencing tremendous pain in my mouth right now
You have Taffy in like a dip
I feel every tooth
Like it's like chewing tobacco
You just have a Taffy in your lip
All at all times
Alan has been dipping Taffy
Since he walked in
This is a Jersey Shore thing
Jane I'm wearing an Ocean City t-shirt right now
Nice
I should have worn my hoodie
I have a little hoodie
And I think that's how we first
I was wearing an Ocean City hoodie at a party or something
You came up to me
Talking about Ocean City
And I was so surprised
Because I'm like Alan's from Alabama
How does he know all this Ocean City stuff?
Yeah no I'm very fortunate to have the Ocean City connection
Through Stacey's family
I like this new nostalgia too
I like that you can have an equivalent of childhood nostalgia
Or something you're discovering in your 20s 30s
I'm sort of coasting off their nostalgia
And now I have a bit of nostalgia of my own
And then also having a kid that's gotten to go there
Every couple years
That's nice
Seeing it
Because a lot of it you're viewing through
And me if you're a parent there wandering around
There's plenty to enjoy if you're not a parent
Once you start seeing the kids run around
And their reaction to stuff
That's super fun too
So what's he into? What are the go-tos kid-wise?
Well he loves the two big amusement parks
I don't know if they're exactly on either end
Oh yeah they're a few blocks apart
They're like maybe a 10 or 15 minute walk apart
And we can get into them
Just to say what Gillian's Wonderland Pier and Playland
What is that clunky name?
Playland's Castaway Cove
It's the newer name
We always just call them Playland
And Wonderland Pier we should
It is not a pier
It runs parallel at the boardwalk
And the ocean
That confused me getting into all this too
I don't see no pier
There's no pier here
Well it is a pier that juts out into the sea
Morris Pier is a pier
And if you were in a car
I think it was Seaside Heights
Another town
During Hurricane Sandy
I believe a rollercoaster fell into the
Like the pier broke up
And a rollercoaster fell into the ocean
So that was at Ocean City?
No that was at Seaside Heights
Oh okay Seaside City
So those and we'll get into those a little bit
Okay so those are kid hits for sure
Oh yeah so those are like the big things
I mean it's like you said in the beginning
Like the whole boardwalk to me feels like
You're not just going to one place
It's all kind of a continuum
It's all like you're popping around
Like we're gonna go to Playland
And we're gonna go to this arcade
Or we're gonna go get a calzone
Over at this place or whatever
It's all kind of like
It gets mixed up like when you're in
Just specific spots like it's never gonna be
Just that one thing that you do
Because you're out there
And you're gonna pop around a little bit
But yeah
Mini golfs to look like
A lot of mini golfs
You go to the music pier to use the bathroom
Has historically been the most reliable bathrooms
Oh yeah that's a good tip
That's a great spot I like that
That's a neat interesting architectural
Like little location that music
Yeah that just does jut out into the ocean
And it's like a big event space
For a long time
Beach Boys have played there
They're playing this summer
If you can believe it
Yeah the Beach Boys are getting out there this summer
And they're taking their friend John Stamos with them
Can you believe it?
They're becoming a regular
Presence at the music pier
Bacon Brothers
I bet it's been 50 years
Some of this stuff goes back 50 years
Jane saw Gradley's shirt for me this morning
And she's like
Oh it's coming up at 150 years old
And I was like
Oh what did they do for the 100th
And I was like oh I wasn't alive
Okay not that much of an old man
I was not alive for the 100th
Beach Boys soon enough to
150 years of surfing
These boys are 150 years
And OC Con there or something too I think
They just did a comic convention
Okay and I remember last time I was there
I saw a picture of
Giancarlo Esposito
Was gonna be
Oh cool
This is not
Not too shabby
The stars come to shine
Mike Love
I went to the schedule
Mike Love coming
Kenny G coming
Starring Peter Noon
Peter Noon
That's how it's built now
He made it up to starring
Like the Jimmy Fallon tonight show credit
Yes
So all the up-cotties
To the beat grades
Another Ocean City connect
I just started writing down
I was like oh I don't have to
Research a lot cause I just started writing down
No
Alan do you know the term shoebees
Oh wow
This is probably like a 100 year old
Thing
Shoebees were the name
For day trippers who would come down to the beach
Cause there used to be a train
From Philadelphia
There used to be like a train or a trolley
Sort of thing
And people would pack their lunches
In a cardboard shoebox
So you knew they were shoe
Oh my god
How have you not revealed this to us before
Shoebees cause they had the cardboard lunchboxes
So they got the name
The day trippers got the name
Shoebees
So a shoebee is
Just somebody who brings their lunch in a shoebox
That's coming to the pier for a day
That's the origin of it
Coming down to the beach
But now it's kind of like
I feel like the locals call the people
Who come
Is it all derisive
Is this a slur
Should we be bleeping this term
Shoebee
It's like sis on twitter
You're on X the everything app
You can't say it anymore
Can't even say shoebee anymore
Shane Gillis said shoebee
On the monologue of SNL
Comedy is back
I do stand up sets
And I say shoebee and the whole audience is silent
I don't know what's going on
It never gets a laugh PC
I think it's like
People don't know
They don't know to go to
Mancos for the best pizza
Or they don't know
That you need beach tags to get on the beach
So these are kind of like rouges
These are naive people that come down
For one day they don't know this fucking place
They're eating the wrong shit
They're fucking lunch in a shoebox
Get out of here
We're the people who live here
We know what the real stuff is
You've been enough
You know about the beach tag
Now I've learned about the beach tag
Is Alan a shoebee though?
Not anymore
At one time I hate to say it
I really am flattered with that compliment
At one point you had to have been a shoebee
Oh of course
You gotta be a shoebee to not be a shoebee
You were getting mocked behind your back
By these locals
I don't know
If I'll get to an honorary
Not local stats
I don't want to presume anything
But I do feel more comfortable there
I am aware of the beach tags
Although I often forget them
But that's a thing
The moment you get there
The relatives are passing the beach tags
Around
You're sticking it
To a towel or your backpack
So beach tags
These are little
I don't even know what you call
They're almost like bottle cap
Size or something
Yeah bottle cap size is a good way to put it
But it's really sturdy
Paper
Kind of vinyl-y
It's like a pin
You pay to access the beach
And this is kind of split
The beaches are free in Wildwood
Because it's half a mile
To the water
But the beaches are a lot smaller
In Ocean City
So to pay for upkeep
And like
Just maintaining
The beaches
A number of towns
Cape May comes to mind
Ocean City
You had to buy a beach tag
You could buy them for a day
Or for a week
Or for the season
And you just got to show it
There's usually a bored teenager
And you just show it
And then sometimes there's beach tag
People walking around the beach
Like hey can I see your beach tags
And if like
You walked
If you just walked on and sat down
And you didn't know about them
They'll sell you a beach tag
Maybe that's why that kid got
Stabbed or whatever
Because they didn't have a beach tag
In which case
What else are you going to do
Yeah a little bit
Isn't there a Cape May cafe
It just happened this week
Sorry
Sorry to make a joke about this
I hope you've recovered from the stabbing
Isn't there a Cape May cafe
At the beach club
Yeah there is the Cape May cafe
And the beach club is above fame
Disney World Hotel
So is that why you like the beach club so much
Because it kind of reminds you
We just like the seafood buffet
Like fish family
You were a big fish family
And that's more what it was
My parents liked the shrimp and crab legs
And that sort of thing
And you're watching big fish
Yeah I'm always
Constantly watching big fish
I remember that I saw
Big fish the day it came out
And we did a
Double feature where we saw
Big fish and 21 grams
Wow
We didn't
We were just excited for Oscar
We love movie nerds in high school
And thankfully we saw 21 grams
First so big fish
Really helped cut the
Edge, take the edge off
Wow
If you'd done 21 grams and then seen
Big fish
No that's why I'm saying
We did 21 grams
If you literally did 21 grams
To pre-game for big fish
21 grams of taffy
Not enough
I got a high taffy tolerance
I'm gonna have two
Souls in my body
And one's gonna be made of taffy
There's also, there's a whole other term
Benny too, you got shooby and then you got
Benny
There's an Alice Obscura article that says
Are you a shooby or a Benny
I'm having trouble figuring out Benny, Benny's just like
Fucking people called me Benjamin
Come down here
Is that what it is? I think so
I'm not reading this terribly carefully
But yeah, I think
Or it's people who come to the shore to soak up
Beneficial rays
Thus Benny's
That seems like a stretch, people who want
Beneficial things for their body
I only want the vitamin D
I'm a Benny
This is strange
It depends on where you are
Apparently in Michigan you call them fudgies
People come in
Just all they want is the fudge
And then they want to leave
This is like Howley's in Hawaii or something like that
What is that one?
Howley's is
Like you're not
Native to Hawaii
Or you're
Native blood
Like indigenous to Hawaii
Anybody out of that
Guys like me would be a Howley
Anyone yes
By virtue of how anyone visits Hawaii
We're all Howleys
Apparently there's a version
In Jaws
They make one up for that Jaws
What's the Jaws town?
Amity
Summer dinks they say
People who pop
Into Amity and don't even care about the rich
Amity culture
Summer dinks
There's a connection between Ocean City
And Southern California
In that
Pasadena and Ocean City both have
Duda parades
Oh I remember the Duda parade
Right
It's like a silly parade
This is an off season thing in Ocean City
They used to have like
A famous
They would have a famous grand marshal
Every year like I think Mickey Rooney
Was at least one Duda parade
Great grand marshal in Ocean City
But this year
It was a guy who I think used to play
For the Flyers
So a little less exciting
I mean probably exciting
I think it was mostly partially
Rained out the Duda parade
Are they considered sister cities Pasadena and Ocean City?
I don't think so
Can we get you to be
The grand marshal of one of these Duda parades
I would die if I was the grand marshal
Of the Ocean City Duda parade
This has got to be possible
It's kind of the star caliber
And get ready because I'm going to say
Some of the names that we all love to hear
Please I love to hear the names
Mickey Rooney is in there
Soupy Sails is in there
This is the Pasadena one?
This is Ocean City
Larry Storch who we just talked about
Just passed away from F Troop
Of course
Show from 70 years ago
I don't know
Jason for
Theme park podcast fame
He's no Larry Storch
These are all people that died 30 years ago
Well not Larry, he died a couple years ago
Jason doesn't have a leg up on them
And that he didn't die 30 years ago
Being alive, that's
Number one on the resume
I've got that going
But I did not play for a tri-state area
Sports team
But you managed your high school's football team
And I don't think the season went that well
It's my memory
How much is that
Your fault though
Well
I told them I was
Alan, what you would know
What do you call the little orange thing
You put the football on to kick it
Oh gosh
Well I wasn't the kicker
But I should know this
It's not a tee, but maybe it's something like a tee
Something like that, we did this the other day
We could have figured it out
It might just be a stand
But if anybody should have known this
I hate to say it
They were like, okay you run out
And put the stand out there
And I would always just not be paying attention
Because football is kind of boring
And I don't really know
How it's played very well
Were you too slow putting the stand out
So like
It's a similar thing to Alan
You guys are kind of equivalent here
I was a bit of a molasses boy
Yeah
Both Ocean City beat two molasses boys
Together
If you'd been in the same game
Alright, now
Manager, go set up
The first name what the thing is
And then go put it out
I'll just grab it, I'll name it later
Then slow run out
To the middle of it, okay last boy
Get in there, take the kick
Slow walk out to the
We would have lined it up perfectly
Yeah, wow
There's still time
You're gonna get you guys on the field together
We gotta go back
The slowest game
Ever played
Alan, let me ask
Because you know
We mentioned the amusement parks
My
I feel like Ocean City
And maybe
Stacy's family does this too
Where it's like, oh we go here
We don't go there, we go to Mancos for pizza
We don't go to Preps
Or it's like, oh no, Preps is better
You gotta go there
Does your son have a preference between
Playland and Wonderland?
That's a great question
And I do believe that Stacy's family
Is more of a Manco family
Mancos always comes up
I would say
That right now
And this could just be an age
Thing that he's more of a
A
Sometimes I mix them up, Gillians
Like the one that looks like
The castle with the red top, Gillians
Because that, I feel like
The majority of the rides there are more
Geared towards smaller kids
That's the place that he's
More inclined to go
And then when we go to the bigger one
Which is
Playland
That's got
That's got a little bit more faster rides
And stuff like that there I think
This is so
Funny you say that
Because when I was growing up
Playland was the one for little kids
And Wonderland was the one for big kids
And now it's swapped
And I'm like, oh yeah, Playland does have
A lot of big rides now
And they've built
It's a little crazy walking around there
Because they've built a lot of things
On top of other things
You know, there's a lot of rides
Packed into a smaller area
Yeah, there's coasters going
From different rides that are just right
Next to each other
Flying by
And right next to hotels
Which it's probably like
Right across the alley
Rattling windows
For sure
So they've like, are you saying they've kind of like
Jammed in coasters
That there was kind of a modest
Layout of little kid rides
But then they've had to like court the adult
Market so they just kind of like, alright
What every inch of free space
Free space gets a coaster now
And Wonderland is still pretty
Spread out, a lot of kid rides
Definitely a lot of kid rides
Yeah, monorail
A small, little
It's a train
It's like a ripoff Thomas
It's kind of a ripoff Thomas
It's always been a ripoff Thomas
Like what, 20 feet in the air?
It goes above the park
Which is very cool
Why would Thomas do that? That's strange
Don't worry about it
My son is all about the logic
Of Thomas, the most logical train player
I've ever seen, he'd be so bothered that he was
Up in the air
The ripoff aspect is
Kind of the non, I mean there's almost
There's no
Real IP there as far as I
Can tell
Like it's all
Sort of faint
Representations
Of things that you kind of know or have
Heard of, you know, like there's something
That's like a, just a structure
That they can run across with a bridge called Raider's Ark
Raider's Ark
I love Raider
I love that
As a kid
It's not specifically, there's no Indiana Jones
Stuff necessarily
Raiders of the Lost Ark, but like you're
The ride that you're on
The Ark of a Raider
Why does a Raider have an Ark?
It's like a fun hack
There's rope bridges and tunnels
And that
The logic
The logic is airbrushing
A lot of the giant airbrush mural
There's like a worm one, I forget what it's called
But it looks like the worm from like
Alice in Wonderland or something
But it's not
The caterpillar you mean? Sorry, the caterpillar, not a worm
It could be a worm that looks like a caterpillar
In their world it's a worm
But he has like a joint instead of a hookah
But like
My favorite ride is there's like a haunted
A haunted ride
Yeah, that's new in the last few years
I watched a ride through that a while ago
And it's pretty good
It's very effective, it's very good
And Sunny is still haunted by it
Two years later
When he rode it when he was five
And because
We're going to go
I don't want to time stamp this episode
But we will be going this summer
Back to Ocean City
And so I was asking him
What do you think about that haunted dark ride?
Do you want to get back on there?
I don't know dad, I don't know
Really, wow
Stuck with them
One of his little cousins in front
And the seats on that are reminiscent
Of the haunted mansion
Kind of high back chairs
Yeah
This is a fine Jersey Shore tradition
Of intellectual property theft
But like
Don't worry about it, who's going to say it?
There is
In the last few years there is
A candy shop
Called Candy Land
That just uses giant like
The board game font
It just uses Disney
It uses the Disney like hand written font
And then it just has like
A giant photo
You know
Printouts of the castles
And stuff in the store
Wow, how close can we get?
That's crazy
This ride is just called a haunted house
Dark ride, I think
They don't really, they don't put too much on
That pretty much gets the whole message across, it's dark
It's scary
Kids are likely scared by the horrible metal
Noises that affordable
Basic animatronics
Make
Yes, they're natural creaking and screeching
Yes, in addition to like
The copyright free
Haunted house music and screams
And stuff
But there's skeletons, there's clowns
That glows in the dark
I believe there's maybe even a couple of times you get
Wind blown at you
So
There's a lot of screaming from what I saw
Just like loud scream
In which case
Your role of course is going to be
That's just upsetting
Yeah, yeah
Has he been on like
Haunted Mansion and like a Disneyland and stuff too?
No, I
I hate to tell y'all
Really, this might
Turn the tables on me
We have not been to Disney World
Disneyland
This is like his exposure to
Amusement parks is
Something along the lines of this
State fair kind of quality of stuff
But at that age also
It's you know
So I think he's really going to appreciate it
I'm sort of like
I justify going like I really want him to remember it
When we go, you know like
Oh sure, yeah yeah
I feel the same way about on my
Hardcore fandom
Scale, I say the same thing about
Going to Tokyo Disneyland
But like we were
You know like I've been talking about maybe
Like Universal with him this summer
And he
We were listening in the car
Not too long ago to y'all's
You know Universal
To the Mario Land
Oh yeah
I'm sorry if we cursed
Oh yeah, no I did have to like kind of
Car
And I'm sorry if I said something
That I was attracted to Chase Meridian
From Batman Forever or something
You had to explain that
For like 15 minutes, very graphic
I mean, he really loved it
He really liked it, he really liked hearing y'all
Recap it and talk about it
We just heard the show
And enjoyed it, what?
He enjoyed the show
It's fun, he's kind of
Into podcasts
I do have to be careful
And you guys don't have to edit yourselves or do anything
Obviously it's for whoever
This is a very explicit
Show
Very, very explicit
That's how we're labeled on
Apple Podcasts
Most shows have the
E next to it, we have the
VE
It's bad parenting on my part
To do that, but
The topic was so juicy
For us that, you know, we're excited to get
Into these things now that he's like really
Kind of in his zone of, to appreciate it
Did he like, did he ask
How old we were and say like
These guys are like closer to my age, right?
They're your age
They sound so young, like if they're not kids
Then they are just barely not
Kids, right?
This is like, I mean, it's often
Like
Me going something like, these are
Some of dad's friends
Or you've met this one guy
Before, you know, such and such
As birthday
So he vaguely
I don't know what that's like to have some sort of a
Tangential connection to the
Media you're listening to or watching
You know, as a kid, but other than
Dirty dancing
Anyway, that's generally how I
Kind of describe stuff
One of daddy's friend's shows
Is not
Appropriate because there's a lot of talk about
Sucking your own dick
You can't play all
Of them
Yeah, no
That's just for daddy
Some of daddy's friends just do it for daddy
Uncle Nick has a little mouth
He says some naughty words
In the topic of
In the area of kind of like
Rip-offs
To me, the juiciest thing
Not knowing anything about this park
Was discovering something
In Gillian's
Wonderland Pier
And that is that there is a little area
Where you can put in a dollar
And you can activate
An animatronic band
That is clearly
A re-skinned Chuck E. Cheese
Robot band
And you guys are both familiar with it
Did you run into this too, Mike?
I saw a picture, yeah
Awesome, so cool
I judge a lot of these places on
I don't expect a place like this
To have animatronics
But it's certainly a bonus
It's cool, it's like
Now we're talking
So yeah, you can
Activate
You guys have seen them
But here they are, they're on kind of like a little
Western porch and they are called
Rocky and the Railroad Ramblers
So good
Right up, you have to go up
A level to board
The railroad that goes around the park
Oh, so the monorail
Passes
Yes, the Thomas monorail passes
Behind them while they do their show
And it
Is just so evident
If you're into these characters
As we are, it's so
Obvious that they just
It's like the same facial shapes
As the Chuck E. Cheese and they just put
New felt on them or whatever
The gestures are the same
They took Chuck E.'s skin off
And they put new skin on
There's going to be a lot more of that I feel like
Because Chuck E. Cheese
Has got to get rid of a lot of their
Animatronics
They haven't smashed them off
They have to kill them
They're like alive enough
You have to separate the head from
The spine
And it has to be like
Like Wolverine, you're killing Wolverine
You have to kill Wolverine in the comics
You have to separate his head off his body
But then you have to separate his body from
So he doesn't grow back
Because he's a healing power
So it's similar to the Chuck E. Cheese robots
It's the same
It's the same gestures
And they are all
Their limbs are contorted such that
They should be holding instruments
That they are not
So they're clearly gesturing as if
They're playing the keyboards or a guitar
It's just that they have severely bent
They just look mangled
Yes, yeah, they're playing phantom instruments
Air guitar, I guess
Let me quickly go through
Okay, here's equivalence
Okay, so again, the band
It's not Munch's Make-Believe Band
It's Rocky and the Railroad Ramblers
Chuck E. is Rocky the Panda
Helen Henny is
Henrietta Hatpin
Mr. Munch
The monster one is Bubba
Jasper T. Giles the dog
Is Hank the Dalmatian
And Pasquale the pizza chef
Is Antonio
I didn't stray too far
He looks like an old mayor
I think the mustache
Is built into the mechanics
So he has to still have the mustache
They just made him old
They didn't get too far from the original characters
They're just like one little generation removed
Still a bird and a dog
Chuck E. maybe changes the most
Chuck E. might have the face of
Or one of them has the face of that
Elvis one
Oh, the king?
Yeah, the king
Do you think there's a way to track
Where that can't
I wonder if there was a showbiz pizza
Or Chuck E. cheese that was
Closed down
Why in fact
That is exactly what it is
Actually it was one that I think closed
And was fully done in the 80s
It was like an early
Went under
Didn't have the Chuck E. Cheese license anymore
But the restaurant, somebody came in
Redid, I think I'm getting all this right
That it was the Chuck E. Cheese band
Then it closed
Then some other enterprising people came in
And said, well you've got a perfectly good band here
We'll build a restaurant around it
And I think this is all in Scranton
And there was a place called
Wow
Oh man
They have been through
It started as the Chuck E. Cheese characters
Now it is Rocky and the Royal Ramblers
In the middle it was
Whatever, Zach Perry Winkle's
Panda band, I don't know what it is
I have to do this list again
Chuck E. Cheese was Zach Perry Winkle
Helen Henney is Henrietta Hen
State Henrietta
Jasper T. Giles, Dudley Dog
Pasquale
Was Pasta Pete
I really like that one
And then my absolute favorite
Mr. Munch the Monster used to be
Thirsty Jones
The best born name
I've heard in a long time
Wow
That's great
I wish we could get some old robots
And just change the characters a little bit
That would be so fun
Oh, invent our own?
But not go too far from the originals
Yeah
I always thought that would be a great
Talk show band
To have a talk show band
That's a really good idea
Especially as the bands disappear
The first thing that talk shows are losing
Is the band
So you can't
We can't pay humans anymore
Why not? But then it's boring to just play
Pre-recorded music
And then we play into the animatronic
Oh yeah
And then now we're cooking
Just enough to say like
Haha, yeah, Trump is screwed
Don't forget to eat your small rock every day
What?
That was one of the
AI Google results when people were trying
To get it
It said like, someone asked how many rocks
Should I eat every day
Google is broken right now
So you can find people
For certain AI prompts you can ask questions
Is it okay to eat glass? And it says
Yes, it's okay to eat one liter of glass a day
So there's all these errors
Going on when you search things
The funniest was someone
Asked how do you make pizza
Or how do you keep cheese from falling off pizza
And they're like, you know
It could be too much sauce or not enough cheese
Try putting some glue in the pizza
And Katie
Natopoulos used to be
At Buzzfeed, I think it's at Business Insider now
A very funny
Reporter, she made the
Glue pizza
She made Google's glue pizza?
She made the glue pizza
She got like non-toxic
Elmer's glue and put it
Mixed it in the sauce
And made the pizza
Did she eat it? She did
She's like
Well it smells a little
Chemically cooking
But she made the glue pizza
Really taking their word for it with that non-toxic
Really
Trust the Elmer's people
Think about all the people that are doing that
Not ironically
Just because they look for
They were looking for the recipe
That's why
My pizza is not tasting right
A lack of glue
I think she actually
Not Elmer, she used the up and up
The Target house brand
Version of Elmer's non-toxic glue
Interesting
Kind of bold
Kind of bold going with the
Up and up like the Rouse
It's like the sauce that you spring for
Buy the right glue
The glue makes the pizza
I think she went with Francesca
Rinaldi, which is an East Coast
Brand
Alan, you mentioned like there is not a lot
Of IP here
But there is a mascot for Gillian's Wonderland
For many years
Wonder Bear
My son
A female, either partner
Or girlfriend or wife
Or stuff
I don't want to assume
You don't want to label it
It's Wonder Bear's girlfriend or partner
It's a long term relationship
Did you find the name of the girl bear?
Her name is Landy
Landy, interesting
In honor of the man who saved
Brian Wilson
Dr. Landy
But Wonder Bear and Landy
I was like, alright, when you get to Landy
That might be a lack of imagination
It's just confusing
I like it, I guess
I just don't know where
Wait, it's from Playland
From Wonderland
Landy
But I didn't put that together
It's so basic
It's just looking at the other half they had lying around
Yet I still missed it
Landy
She's a girl bear who loves land
She's like a land baron
She may not like being so close to the sea
Given that she
She's named after a piece of
Family property or whatever
Land, oh yeah
Interesting
Stacked generations deep
Yeah, the current generation
Jay Gillian
Was a little busy being
The mayor
The mayor of Ocean City
Okay
A number of Gillians have been mayors
Oh, really
Ocean City, there's a history of
They control the park and they control the town
But Gillians, I feel like
I feel like my dad the last few years
Has been like, well
Gillians might have some
Back tax it
It seems like there was talk of
Sheriff's auctions
And it seems like it always
Gets resolved
Thank god
This looks like Gillian
One of the rides you can ride inside
Gillian's guts
Are you talking about Wonder Bear?
Is that Wonder the Bear?
Is it a different bear than Gillian?
No, Gillian is the family
Gillian's not a bear, Gillian's the family
I don't know that
I think that might be from
A ride called
Bear-A-Fair
I got that in front of me
So that's Wonder Bear and you can go inside
Wonder Bear's guts
Yeah
And have a Bear-A-Fair
You can get up inside
Wonder Bear and have a Bear-A-Fair
I guess it's not that weird
Sitting inside Dumbo
Sitting inside Dumbo in Disney
It's not that weird that you're inside the character
It's almost like
Close to
You're riding on top of them
You were in a hollowed out stomach
And now we've put the cloak of a fair
Over it as well
There's a lot going on in Bear-A-Fair
Wonder Bear has been killed
His guts have been extracted from its body
There's a hole in its chest
And now you're getting to ride in there with your family
I was going to say
This is a Revenant situation
They could call it Revenant the Ride
This is kind of like a mech suit situation
You get in there and he just gets up
And you're walking around as a big old Wonder Bear
Don't tell the teen gangs
There's mech suits around
They can stab a lot more efficiently
So there is
It's just like a block away from Ocean City High School
They're asking for it then
The kids
It was always wild to me
They go to high school by the boardwalk
That's so cool
They go to high school by an amusement park
Beach volleyball
That would be cool
It's iconic looking when you see it
It's the first big thing you see
in that direction
Usually our path
Maybe something like
We've gone to
There's a restaurant called Oves
My family loves Oves
Who doesn't love Oves?
It's delicious
Everybody loves Oves
That's where the boardwalk is kind of narrowed
And then you walk from there
And then it gradually widens out
widens out and then boom, there's, there's Gillian's right there.
But, um, one time, last time we were there, Sonny started kind of doing,
there was like a family dinner there at Oves and there's like a big balcony.
And, uh, you, so you can see over the boardwalk.
And then my son went out to the boardwalk and started like dancing around on the
boardwalk for some reason, just being a cute five-year-old dancing around and his
cousins were up on the balcony, like cheering him on, like, yeah, yeah.
And then some people walked by and they threw him a dollar.
Wow.
There are a lot more buskers like the city approved buskers along the
boardwalk playing saxophone or keyboard or there's a lot of full bands on like
family nights along the boardwalk or something like that.
Watch out for those beach tags and watch out for you.
Make sure your son is permitted for his own beach tags with his dance.
Or his own buckets and like shovels for the beach.
This time put them to work.
Remember that dance from last time.
Get down there, pay your way.
Does he like the, cause, uh, Gillian's wonderland known for the massive Ferris
wheel and that's kind of like an icon of ocean city.
Does he like it?
Oh yeah.
No, he loves it.
He loves the, the Ferris wheel.
Okay.
Love that Ferris wheel.
I mean, that's the best way to like get the bird's eye view of the whole, like,
uh, uh, yeah, I mean, that's, that's how you get the only other tall thing is
like there's landers or portico hall.
Yeah.
There's like a couple of tall rides, you know, but this is the one, the
most kind of serene view and especially at sunset or at night when everything
lights up, you know, it's really pretty way to see the city and all those
beautiful old houses that are over there.
Full of the mean people that are judging you.
Well, if people that have gotten their liquor from across the bridge and they're
just sitting out on their porches, judging you, what are the night, what are
you doing when the, what are the evenings?
When, when the pier is closed, what are you doing?
You're just like,
Folks are like riding their bikes up and down, you know, taking walks.
A lot of walking.
Oh, I feel like, oh, uh, uh, is in the fine tradition of like Jersey shore.
Like you get a platter.
So you get soup and salad, uh, soup or salad sometimes, and your
entree occasionally dessert.
So it's a lot of food and it's all fried food.
It's like, besides the corn on the cob, it's French fries or big potato.
And, uh, fried fish or, uh, broiled fish, which is kind of, uh, flavorless.
It's the version where it's nothing.
Okay.
Butter and paprika, but that's like a lot of food.
So yeah, you walk it off.
You eat a big fish dinner and then you walk the boards to walk it off.
And Oves is also a bicycle rental place.
It's bicycle rental and like donuts.
And I think it even started that way.
Maybe it was like mostly a bicycle rental and like the guy had a grill and
then it became more of like a restaurant, but it's also a bicycle rental.
Yeah.
So he's just like, Oh, I'll take my girl to work today.
Business started bringing the George Foreman out there.
That's what it started 20 years ago.
Um, I, I don't know if this is on the Ferris wheel, but you know, like, look,
you get like the incidents page of these places and I never, you know, I never
want to go too much into the, you know, deaths or grim things that happened.
There's no, I don't think there's any deaths here.
No, there are.
I, I, oh, no, I, I know the story I'm about to tell.
Oh, right.
Constant fires.
If you build very, every, every, the locals know, as long as you're not a
shoe B, you know, there's a fire every day.
If you have very old buildings with very old electrical setups next to a
wooden boardwalk, you're going to have some fires, you know,
whenever these places come up with you, you have a lot of concern.
It's always, it's going to flood.
The ride's going to fall into the, you're like, you're, I think you're like
concerned generally about the seaside amusement park.
Yeah.
Uh, well the Jersey shore is, uh, subject to hurricanes, uh, some of the year.
Uh, I've had, I've seen a number of fires.
There was a fire when I was in elementary school at this place, Fisherman's
Wharf, which like, was like my favorite shop.
I mean, it was mostly at the time, like seashell knickknacks and Simpson's
toys, cause it was 1992.
And they weren't, they weren't using reputable factories back then.
So those, those, uh, those Moe's would light up, uh, second flash
paper, the worst made Barney's you've ever seen.
There was, there was one, uh, Coors brothers ice cream.
There's a number of those on the boardwalk.
I don't know if, uh, the family like Coors frozen custard.
There's like, yeah, multiple of the ones.
There's a little one at Gillian's, right?
Yeah.
Is that the place where, is it Coors where they do like the flattened ice?
They like flat when they're making the rolled ice cream that was, that
was like a trend that popped up one summer and it was gone as quickly as it arrived.
I was looking for the rolled ice cream.
We had Coors, which is delicious, but it was kind of a fun novelty.
Yeah, I hate to say it.
Say, I don't know the way it sounds to me, this rolled ice cream
sounds like some shooby shit, flashing the pan go in one summer and out the next.
That's a real Jersey shore that where it's like pops up and either becomes
ubiquitous, like dip and dots.
I remember when they showed up and then they, you know, big aim everywhere.
They stayed.
They had what it took tasting terrible.
They actually got their, the footholds somehow there.
There was a movie theater there too, that I don't think was
working last time we were there, but it was broken.
The Moreland Terrace, uh, was bought by a local chain and it's slowly being redone.
It's supposed to reopen.
And the other movie theater that was down the block in town became the big
Manco and Manco pizza headquarters.
Oh, it was a shitty family fun center that kept one or two movie screens going.
And then the pizza, you know, Shane wanted out.
None of these businesses started.
They, none of them started as what they became.
This is a place where you can like, just start some, just get something going.
And then it turns out, no, I sell t-shirts.
I, you know, I thought I was selling, uh, beach tags, but now I sell taffy.
But you can always kind of see the remnants of what, you know,
what was there.
Skeletons are in the corner.
From when they thought they were, they were a skeleton manufacturing company.
Like open to a movie theater, but I actually just turned into a place
that makes kettle corn.
It's a, it lets you grow.
It lets you change.
Let's evolve this place.
I was going to say from the incidents page, just this one, this one, non-fatal,
thankfully, uh, in June, 2007, the park was closed for two hours after a 17 year
old girl had fired shots from a 22 caliber gun into a sand dune from one of the
pier's rides, thankfully just into a sand dune and you're like, what's going on?
What did, what did this 17 year old, what did she, what was she mad about?
Turns out investigated, uh, uh, that she just found it on a seat,
accidentally dropped by an off duty cop.
Left their gun on the Ferris wheel.
Oh my God.
This is, this is something straight out of Brickleberry.
We had a fun, a funny, a funny incident, which I was like worried about at the
time, but it is in hindsight when Sonny was a very little baby, we, we went to,
this wasn't a violent incident, but it was like at just one of the little stores
on the boardwalk, old, you know, the old timey photographs.
Oh yeah.
That old timey photo place has been there forever and ever.
And it's great.
Cause you know, it's like, you get a family photo and everybody's like, we're
all old timey bank robbers, gangsters.
So there was like a, we were getting all the little cousins together.
And, um, at this time, Sonny must've been like one years old or something.
So, so, um, some of the, the, the, the, one of the nieces, I think was like
pointed to a picture, there was a variety of choices and it's like, let's
do the pretty flowy dress thing.
Um, and so that was from in the category of like an old South portrait or whatever.
So they start getting their gear on and the girls have these big flowy like, uh,
dresses on and then there's the boys putting on soldier outfits and a little
Lord Fauntleroy thing, and they're kind of getting in the pose and the
photographer is setting up the thing.
And, um, and then nothing's dawning on me.
And I'm from Alabama until the photographer unfurls the Confederate flag.
And he's like, Oh, it's an old South portrait.
And I'm like, Oh, well, can we, can we just do, can we do the version without
the, is there an ocean one?
Saloon backdrop.
Yeah.
Like the saloon thing with the chimney is perfect.
It doesn't make any sense.
These people wouldn't be in a saloon.
They're not at the same.
This is antebellum and they're over in the old West.
They were, it's okay.
I'm not worried about accuracy here.
It's okay.
I mean, and that was just like, that's the Jersey shore.
Like this is the old South.
These are, we're hitting all the little traits of the old South thing.
And they're not wrong, but it was just like, uh, and if you look through the
photo book, yeah, there's a lot of like families that are like, we're old South.
You know, we're in front of the Confederate flag, but anyway, it was like,
it was just the funniest thing.
Cause it was just like, oh yeah.
All the cousins are about to be in this photograph now.
Which is that would damn him forever.
He could be running for office.
He won't be running for some offices.
Some kind of type of a councilman one day.
Yeah.
But it was just like one of the funniest things.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Why did they have?
I know why they wait, except it's wait, but it's, it's Jersey though.
Like, uh, I, that's so weird that they would.
It's just sort of weird.
Yeah, there's a weird, I wouldn't say therefore it erases or they, I think
they were just like, these are the touchstones of the old South.
I think there was a time.
Yes.
We're like, I mean, everyone's always had the agenda of the Confederate
South, meaning something very specific, but like, I think there were also, it
was just like, the flag was around as a, that equals South and that.
Yeah.
Sure.
I just ran into guys like me coming in there.
What's going on?
Putting all of your kids and cousins into giant puffy bouffant dresses.
And then you raise a fuss about the Confederate flag.
I just watched.
Uh, okay.
So there's an old, uh, there's a full house where a, uh, uh, pop star comes
to visit, uh, Stephanie for her birthday.
I think I've seen that.
It's a guy named Tommy page who seems like made up.
That seems like a fake guy, but I like to know it's a real guy.
And I'm looking up the Tommy page music videos.
What was his deal?
All right.
Here's his song shag.
Okay.
And I'm watching this music video and by the core, the chorus kicks in and he's
Tommy page is busting moves in front of a Confederate flag.
What is this?
Why?
And I think it's, I think it's a song from a movie called shag that maybe
takes place in the South and thus, but it was really disconcerting.
Like I did not expect this around this corner, just to cool, you know, like
a Rick Astley style guy and he's busting moves in front of all.
I found that Chuck E cheese clip from like the early nineties where they're
flashing flags and the Confederate flag flies up on that.
We talked about that in the episode.
I think there was a time where you just, people were just like, this is
iconography of a thing that it doesn't, there's sort of an innocence about
to them, that this is just a thing that's like, you know, and then as people
started, you know, maybe not a good symbol, more context about that.
You know, they're surrounding it.
You're like, going like, Oh, maybe, maybe we'll find some other, maybe
an old, uh, uh, oak tree.
That's all I can pull.
I can't think about driving.
What's the most innocuous picture?
I know depending on oak trees, branches could be bent in an offensive shape.
Oh, here we go.
There's always something.
Oh, it could be bad.
One of the six, one of the six flags, at least initially was a Confederate flag.
Right.
Yeah.
That's a boardwalk t-shirt shop scaled back.
They just replaced all the like Rick and Morty with a Confederate flag.
They were like, Oh, just make it the Supreme logo.
Don't worry about it.
We do not have the license for this, but Rick and Morty and Goku can
wear the Supreme logo.
Uh, um, what have we met?
What are fun details?
I mean, this, this has all been super fun stuff to talk about.
And it's, it's very relaxing to, I don't know, just even hear about,
Oh, the nice and the pizza place.
And it's picking, Oh, I don't know these places, but
stealing your popcorn or whatever you may have in your hand.
Oh, I will say my face.
I will shout out my favorite ride, which is at the other, the other place.
Not at Playland, at Playland, uh, uh, the Gale force.
That's, that's, that's the big roller coaster.
Oh, okay.
It's kind of like advanced coaster, right?
Like it's, it's, it's sort of a good one for being a
yeah, it's, it's like, um, I forget X number of tickets where you
buy $10 just to ride it and I wrote it a few years ago and it's like a real,
I think, intimate coaster and it rocked my shit.
Like I was not prepared for Gale force Gale force took years to construct
and then it opened and they, some stuff was installed wrong.
So then it went down for months and months, but Playland is where we
were talking about fires, uh, in early 2021, right before we were about to
record the episode with Avery Monson, I learned about, there was a massive
fire burning on the boardwalk and it was at Playland and they are still
reconstructing their like entryway arcade and stuff, but it totally destroyed
my family's beloved, uh, hamburger construction company, construction company.
Yeah.
So it's businesses close or flip because it's like, well, a lot of the
comic stores closed because the comic bubble burst, the collectible
bubble burst in the nineties.
Uh, a lot of the bookstores closed.
There's still the bookatieria, the used book store, my family loves.
And once at Ithaca, I was like, is that the fucking bookatieria van?
And it was the guy and I was like, I love your bookstore.
My family loves your bookstores.
Like the man, wait, sorry.
The man from the pure bookstore you liked was in a van by you was
in a van down by the river because his daughter was going to the college.
Okay.
So what was his name?
I actually do not know his name, but I've been going there since the stand.
Bookatieria.
Yeah.
Um, but businesses flip cause either bubbles, uh, burst or like
fires certainly will close businesses.
Bookstores.
Uh, I think the Atlantic books just went bankrupt.
Um, and, uh, yeah, trends just change.
Kindles, you know, can I ask a hard question of you right now?
You love this place.
Yes.
Okay.
On the second gate, I started asking some hypotheticals here where I have a
giant missile launcher that can blow up the whole launchers back.
I'm going to have to train my missile launcher on one thing.
Toon lagoon or the boardwalk here.
Unfortunately, in this case, it is to lagoon.
All right.
I have a second question though.
It is now trained on either Marvel superhero Island and islands of
adventure or ocean city.
I don't know if ocean city is going to make it.
Oh, you have to decide.
All right.
We need an answer.
The entire city.
Well, no, just the boardwalk and the two things.
What did they do?
Some people just live there.
All right.
They're mean people though.
Maybe like in their snooty about the local.
Man, we're mad at the shoe.
If you've ever spoken ill of a shoe be that you're in the missile bath now.
All the business is gone.
The boardwalk gone.
Uh, it's probably got to be Marvel superhero island has been destroyed.
This is like, like I said, it's like a second home.
Well, that's why I, that's why I was the Marvel superhero island is also
a second offices of the daily.
Whatever.
Where does Spider-Man work daily?
Daily bugle.
Those are, yeah, you sleep under one of those desks.
That's a second home to you too.
Wow.
This is like an impossible scenario.
This is a Kobayashi Maru and Star Trek.
It is a Kobayashi Maru, but you actually decide it.
So we're fine.
It actually, I just got to read.
Oh wait.
I just had to read on the test.
Oh, I didn't know I could cheat on the test.
I'm a good boy.
I don't cheat.
So anyway, yeah, yeah, I would be very interesting.
Wow.
The other I was, I wanted to propose one of these with Alan, but I
don't know how to do it.
I don't know how to like, if you had to be in a missile train scenario, I don't,
I don't know another, I don't know another old place that you're endeared to.
I was going to say play land or wonderland.
Like, what is Stacey's family?
Where does the loyalty lie?
Well, I would have to ask them to evacuate before anything.
Well, yeah, no, they get out of there.
They.
Okay.
Right.
Um, um, let's see, uh, which one would I blow up?
What?
Yeah, yeah.
And it's, that's a pretty carefully guided missile cause these
places are close to each other.
So there's not going to be a big footprint to these, these explosions.
Uh, I guess I would, uh, I would probably train it on, uh, play land.
Keep wonderland.
I really like the iconic, um, spires and castle.
Like, yeah.
And maybe the less spinning letters that spell out wonderland are really
nice to the spinning letters.
Those are really cute letters.
Really good.
If, if you're looking listener for a visual representation of all this, there
is an Instagram account or, uh, they, they professionally do this now, I think
called OC and J, uh, drone, um, and they do drone photography of the island.
And, um, uh, the theme of the amusement parks, I think they've been doing a
lot more, uh, yeah, OC and J underscore drone, which the drone has the POV
that a missile in the air would have.
You can watch the videos and can go pew and pretend that you're a missile on
the way to blow something up.
Yeah.
But also beautiful photos of like the Bay and the marshland and the bridges.
Look at that.
Into town.
Wow.
Um, I also did a couple of years ago, a little, uh, a little video, uh, not
an essay, I wouldn't say, but just some, took some photos.
I get some photos on my walking about pod thing from a couple of years ago
that I, that I made of ocean city.
I was so, um, moved by the experience that year that I made a little video
oven, took some pictures, you know, that out, scroll down.
It's a pleasant place that inspires nice photography and tributes, which
ties nicely into, into the pod, which we could talk about a little bit, but I
get, well, like for, unless like a one more, just like, do you, anyone want to
give like one more out of context name of a restaurant or shop that you like?
I mean, I, like I said, I've been coming here basically since I was born.
I do have a list of, I was tossing it.
Great.
Close to restaurants.
Uh, shaftos, spadafores, shaftos, shaftos, shaftos was there for like 50 or 60 years.
It was like an old school kind of like dinner, you know, soup, salad,
entree, dessert kind of place.
They would do a choice of restaurants, but no, I'm saying you
order and you get all that.
I, I like at a restaurant.
Yeah, I mean, like it comes as a meat and you get it all as a meal.
You get it all for one price and that was probably far too much
for a child to be eating a shoe.
Shoebees don't know about shaftos.
Uh, that, uh, likely closed, um, because people either want to retire or die.
Um, because they've run a fish house for 40 or 50 years.
Like, yeah, that ran it.
Um, toyarium was collectible store.
I love growing up, hamburger construction company, green grill and Flanders
grill.
When Flanders grill closed, uh, they opened the green grill and then they
wanted to retire.
And I think a lot of the staff went to work at the varsity or at Reddy's.
And those are breakfast lunch.
Well, Green Grill is a hotel, right?
It's interesting.
The Flanders.
Yeah.
It's a massive hotel, uh, built, I think around in the 1930s named after, you
know, the battlefield Flanders in tribute, the field of Flanders.
From world war one.
Interesting.
No, not the Simpsons character.
Not the Simpsons character, not dead.
No play land as expanded over the years and built into what used to be
the massive Flanders pool.
Hmm.
So they shrunk the pool.
Oh, they just built another pool.
Okay.
The first pool felt ready to retire.
It had been a pool for 50 years.
This was a giant.
Ready to die.
You know, in the mid 20th century, when people would go to the seaside
resorts for their health and do, you know, uh, bathing in the, but you'd,
the sea is so rough.
So we have the pool.
So people would go to bathe because they couldn't bathe at home, you mean?
No, no, they could bathe at home, but like for a vacation.
Ah, be purified.
Yeah.
I forget whether it was a saltwater pool.
Uh, I should know this.
It might've been.
Hmm.
Do they have any of the stuff Steve Harvey does?
Like a red light machine now or a ice plunge?
Modern equivalent.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Now thousands of people don't want to take a red light bath together.
Yeah.
Like a red light things.
Oh, oxygen bars.
Those were big trend on the boardwalk in the nineties.
It's going to be so funny in like seven months, Mike, when we discover
like red light treatment causes massive tumors like Steve Harvey
walking around his head bulging out.
Steve Harvey's head grew five times its size.
It looks better on camera.
Yeah.
He wanted it that way.
Matches the size of the suits.
Fortunate to the ties.
Uh, another try.
I think there was like escape rooms that like, I know, there are, yeah, those
have caught on the last few years, like an alien invasion one or something.
Yeah.
Um, but, uh, restaurant I would shout out is uncle.
It's a pancake house.
Uh, uncle Bill's pancake house.
Uh, there's always a line.
Yeah.
They don't need my help, but how old is uncle Bill?
80, 85.
Is he ready to die?
I don't know.
He might just be an idea.
Yeah.
He's a little cartoon man on the side.
Oh, he is easy.
Yeah.
Uncle Bill.
Let me see how old the cartoon is and if the cartoon's ready to die.
Well, the fish people were really ready to die.
You do fish for 40 years or more than ready to die.
Sure.
Um, uh, did you say you're going out there?
I, I will probably, yeah, this summer, I think besides one summer when I was
stuck in LA for work and then, uh, 2020, we said, no, no, fuck, no vacation.
Jason, we got episode.
We got to do an episode about King Arthur's carousel.
You stay here.
I would love to hear our 2010 episodes, but there are only two summers.
I've not gone back to ocean city since I've lived here.
Is this uncle Bill and he's got a woman next to him.
Yeah, he's, yeah, they're making pancakes.
Who's the lady?
I don't know.
Landy.
All right.
Look, that one's this.
They look youthful.
They're not ready to die.
Um, youthful, a diet of just pancakes.
Uh, um, but we're, we're probably ready to end here.
We're ready to wrap it up, but what a pleasant journey through this place.
Um, I'm so happy to say Alan McLeod, you survived podcast, the ride.
Uh, what a, what a pleasant one.
And let's, let's, uh, let's stroll on into the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Hey, check out my podcast walking about.
Um, I, uh, I love walking and, uh, hopefully as you've made clear walks in the name of
it, uh, you can walk while you listen to it.
You are allowed if you want to.
And, uh, yeah, yeah, I got to check out the show yesterday.
It's great.
It's so charming listeners to this show.
You love Eva Anderson, I'm sure.
And she was great on it.
You guys went to Hollywood forever cemetery and it's, uh, just what a pleasant, I mean,
you know, it's, it's fun history, but also just hanging out with you guys.
And it's like the way, the, the way you cut it up, that it's like, it's like more like
little audio documentary than, uh, than the normal podcast.
I get, I just like the formatting a lot.
It's very charming.
And also that you, you're like the, like interstitial narrations you do, I think are
really great and funny.
And the thank you here with your, with your, uh, pleasant Southern lilt.
I was like, and we're going to like LA landmarks.
I'm like, we're in a little bit of like Huell Hauser territory.
Oh, I mean, Hey, I'll take that.
I mean, I, I mean, I love Huell.
Huell is like the only sketch comedy character, like impersonation.
I ever did.
Oh, that makes so much sense.
Starting at, like at, uh, doing like any kind of sketch stuff or character bits.
Like it would be, I remember I had like a sketch that was like, I was just going
into like a restaurant, some restaurant and it was Ryan Perez was the cook.
And I was like bugging him as Huell, you know, just because it came from a place
of love, because I discovered Huell when I moved to LA and I was like, Oh man.
So yeah, it's still alive when like, cause he wouldn't, wouldn't, when he
passed away like mid 2010, maybe 10 years ago or so longer.
But, uh, yeah, no, I mean, I think it's, I think it is that just, uh, you know,
there's something about coming from another place and you're just the
excitement you feel over like discovering new places and stuff.
And yeah.
And so, so, uh, huge, huge fan of Huell, huge fan of Rick Steves.
I love Rick Steves.
Rick Steves is the best.
Yeah.
And, uh, so I mean, yeah, there, there's, there's another guy that used to do like
another presenter, like LA presenter, Ralph Story, who used to do stuff.
So,
Oh, is he, is he things that aren't here anymore?
Yes.
That has come up on this show for some reason.
I don't remember what it was.
We've assuredly, we've talked about some things that aren't
here anymore in the show.
So yeah, I mean, you know, it's, it's definitely like, uh, I've, I definitely
like love all those types of, uh, formats and presentation and just kind of got a
kick out of figuring out like, maybe this is a way to do it.
It's sort of like an audio diary sort of captures the sense of like a place and
time, you know, and just like, uh, or a person, you know, that, that I admire a
friend, you know, like, you know, so it's just, uh, it's been really fun.
So thank you so much for
absolutely.
It's, it, it turned out great.
Highly recommended to our, to our audience.
And I haven't gotten to hear the Mitch one, but Mitch is on it.
So people you like, uh, already from our show and other shows.
And, uh, I'm excited to say, I'm excited to check out the rest.
So, uh, yeah, thanks for, thanks for chatting with us here, uh, walking
us through the boardwalk, uh, uh, as for us, uh, you can get three bonus
episodes every month, the podcast throughout the second gate, or get one
more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three, you will find all of that
at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
And because we moved on, I was like, maybe I'll save it for the end.
I have, I have to go back and say that was not the last of the reskins
Chuck E.
Cheese's that I went through.
Thank you.
Because there's also, wait, yes.
All right.
Because, uh, uh, the Chuck E.
Cheese fan community is like, all right, this is a little confusing because
ocean city has Rocky and the railroad ramblers, but that is not to be confused
with Rocky and the Ramblin rascals, which you can find in the enchanted
forest water safari in old forge, New York.
Wow.
And let me speed through those in that one.
Chuck E.
Cheese becomes Rocky the rabbit.
Helen Henny becomes Henrietta hat pin.
She's Henrietta in every, we have our thing, the Helen test where a lot of
like a very bland name to give to a lot of like female characters who don't bring
a lot to the table is Helen and I think Henrietta is maybe another really weird.
Uh, yeah, yeah, uh, uh, a bland name.
Uh, um, let's see, uh, Pasquale becomes Antonio.
That one's the same.
Jesper T.
Jowls is Jacko the donkey and munch becomes bad bonga the monkey.
Oh my gosh.
Uh, so we have all these, I can't believe how much the family tree.
Yep.
Thirsty Jones is really fantastic.
I don't know how to see a picture of, I mean, thirsty Jones is just the purple
monster from Chuck E.
Cheese, but like that, I mean, munch sounds like, ah, I don't want pizza, but
thirsty Jones has got to be thirsty Jones is slick.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
There's a different vibe.
There's a mess in town.
I call thirsty Jones munch is a clown.
Yeah.
Thirsty Jones is cool.
Thirsty Jones.
I'll slip it up for you.
Slip, slurp.
I'm feeling a little thirsty.
When are you not thirsty?
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production, executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Cilio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to
our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.