Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, where today we're doing what I consider a
spiritual heir to the 1995 film Things to Do in Denver When You're Dead. This version is called
Things to Do in Denver That Make You Wish You Were Dead. I'm Scott Gardner, there's Jason Sheridan.
I thought it was gonna be a spiritual sequel to Wild Waves, as in a theme park that causes
people to have a lot of complaints. I mean, yeah, definitely, and it's a bit, I would say
there's a connection in a way to Great America, which I went to up north, and have a similar
syndrome where it's a dead park walking, which might kind of impact the level to which it's
being kept up. There's Mike Carlson. I'm here, yeah, this is interesting. I'm very,
I bet it's a spiritual successor to a lot of episodes we've done. Yeah, possibly owned by
many parks. I sort of lost the ownership at some point. Yeah, well, it also, I mean, really
specifically, it's sort of a sequel to the episode that just came out about Casa Bonita,
and that this is kind of part two of my experiences in Denver, my travels to Denver. And really quick,
I don't wanna derail it, but if we're talking about things that came up in the Casa Bonita
episode, I'm curious to throw something your way, Mike. What in your mind was the proof
or evidence that you had particularly high T? Because in this episode, you accidentally ended
up with a T test, and your disappointment was that it ended up normal. But in your mind,
you are just bursting at the seams with testosterone. You're coming out of your skin
pores. Well, I don't know. You know what? I don't know that it was something that there was evidence
that I had it, but I wanted it. I almost wanted it in a way. I think it was aspirational. It was
aspirational T wishes. Unless that in your mind, you were shocked by the number, that the number
was not in line with what you felt about yourself all these years. You were just really hoping that
that number would be high. It was like finding out I didn't have a mutant power or something
from X-Men or Hey, what's the Harry Potter? I didn't get called into the magic wizard school
or whatever. It's like your T is normal, sir. Maybe there was... Oh, sorry, go ahead. No,
I don't know. That's really all I had. Professor X, I know you won't be coming to my school for
gifted youngsters. Oh, this was being denied that you're not gonna be one of the T men.
I wasn't going to be one of Professor T's. Professor, what is it? T-Xavier? Tech Xavier?
This is a rare... This is a porn parody where weirdly X is taken out of it. You just tip
the X to turn it into a T and you think, no, X, doesn't that make it less pornographic? Well,
no, because it's about all of them doing feats of T, all proving how... Right, how much T they have.
And especially more impressive as you get older yet to still have a lot of your T without,
in a natural way, because I'm not taking any of the Joe Rogan T supplements that I so desperately
want to take. Not yet. Not yet. Yeah. Well, you're waiting for us to start getting those kinds of
sponsorships, which requires a slow turn of our politics, which is what we're kind of working on.
Right. We'll workshop some of that stuff on the second game. Or turn the other way, get the goop.
Well, that's what I was about to say. We could go the other way because a lot of the goop,
Gwyneth Paltrow, it's probably politically on the other... Toward the other way. I don't know
exactly what it is because she's a big Rick Caruso politics fan. But I think that there's
definitely other versions of the T supplements we could be advertising. There should be a nerd T
supplement, quite honestly. There should be sort of a theme park dork supplement. Well, don't we
need it the most to get out of this awful normal territory that you're stuck in, Mike?
Right. Because you would do the ad and you would say, well, are you ever tired by 8 p.m. when
you've been doing a big long Disney day? You feel like your T is dropping. Well, here we go.
Well, the problem is, Jason would hear that ad and go, no, I'm tired at the end of any other day.
But if I'm at Islands of Adventure, I could stay up for 48 hours past that. But he has...
I'm fucking juiced. I don't need no pills. He's got a mutant power, though. He would have been
taken. And I suspect his T is higher than mine. Do you know what a number... I don't know what a
sample number of T count is. Do you want me to find it? I'll open it up. Are we going to find
your actual number? I'll give you the number. Let's just say I don't even know what scale we're
dealing with here. But I think on a typical... Let's say that average is 500. Maybe on an average day,
let's say Jason gets 500. I think you do that measurement at the end of an Islands of Adventure
and it's 4000. It breaks the scale. It's like gamma radiation for Professor Bruce Banner.
That would be great. Yeah, if they could put a quest diagnostics at CityWalk or just at the
exit of Islands of Adventure so I can test my T. They put it on top of the Faroes lighthouse,
and then you get to it by climbing to the top, which is also a test of T that... Wow. He just
with his bare hands crawled his legs and never even touched the tower. It was all upper body.
Climbed all the way to the top to be greeted with, we're actually not taking walk-ins. We're booked
up solid. So please schedule an appointment online. No, you can't talk to anyone on the phone.
No, it's all automated. I'm pulling it up here. I get the number. We'll get the number. Yeah.
Does it have a lot of... Which they probably shouldn't, but my chart and everything have
red, yellow, green. It explains what the levels are that would be normal, the range that would
be normal. So testosterone normal range would be 240 to 871. And then, excuse me, I don't know what
NGDL means. I don't know what that is. I just know there's a number. I know they tell me what's in
the normal range. I have a four... Not gonna damn lie. Your T is through the effing roof.
I have 465. Okay. Wait a minute. Say the range again. You're kind of right. I mean,
it's right in the middle. It's a little lower than the average, but it is average. Oh, it's certainly
in the... But it's a little lower than an average between those two things. Now, I don't know what
the average person has. I don't know that, so I don't know if I'm lower. You think what the average
person has is different than what they're showing you there? I don't know. I don't know the answer
to it. An average amount of T is... I guess it would have to be the average. But let's be honest.
Most people are down in the basement of 50. Well, I also don't know. I don't know if the scale
changes depending on your age either or depending. So here's the thing. I am not happy with it.
Yeah. I'm unhappy with it, but I haven't been exercising very much in the last few months.
I will vow to everyone that I will get my T retaken in a year's time and that I think I can break
550. I think I can do it. Wow. And I won't take any of the Rogan stuff. I won't take any of the
supplements. No red light? I don't know how the red light affects the T. I don't think the red light
has anything to do with your T, but I think the red light should be in play if I can get a hold of a
red light machine. But I will vow a year from now, I will ask the doctor to retake my T
and I believe I can break 550. That is my goal. Wow. I don't know if that's even possible.
Also, is insurance going to cover this? You're going to have to go out of pocket for a T test
that you don't need? I will if I have to. Okay. Or I'll have to tack another Patreon tier here
for some of the listeners to pay for my testosterone test. Yeah, yeah. But if listeners
could start covering medical expenses, that would be ideal. Quest Diagnostics is now,
I had to unsubscribe from the emails. You think about Quest Diagnostics so much at this point
that it has to spill out into the show. Sorry listeners, you're hearing about Quest Diagnostics
now. Well, because I haven't explored LabCorp enough, I guess. But there are a lot of out of
pocket tests that you can get nowadays. That's true, yeah. But I don't want, I'll see if the
doctor will just order it for me. Okay, sure. Sure. Yeah. I just think, I think a funny thing
about this is how, for a long time, the Doughboys have made fun of how they probably have very low
T. Right. And then it feels like that's, well, that's the joke you make if you're a podcaster
and you're in this kind of pale guy sit around field that you probably have low T. And Mike,
you're like, ha, ha, ha, very funny. Seriously though, I think I have high T. I'd like to have
high T and I think it can get higher. Mike, up your ground beef intake for more than a pound today.
I'm definitely going to go paleo for the next year. Oh boy. And mostly just ground beef. Just handfuls
of raw meat. I'm going to go paleo. I'm going to start reading a lot of Jordan Peterson books
and we're going to see what happens to my testosterone. If you want to improve your balls,
have all of your food in ball form. Just ball up a bunch of meat. Just take a big bite out of it.
Eat a lot of balls. Eat a lot of balls. And then yeah, your T will grow. And then maybe I'll get
taken to professor to Xavier and his special school for gifted older men with high T.
Well, God, I hope God speed on your journey. It's an old boy. It's an old man's school. If you didn't
notice gifted older men with high T, that's where I want to live. And the older you get,
like professor X himself, the higher that what you want is that it climbs as your age climbs.
Yes. Maybe that may be the issue here. Yes, I think that's right. Well, something that I
did not get to do on my Denver excursion that might've helped you. Maybe you need to get to
Denver ASAP. I did not have any Rocky Mountain oysters, which are what, bull testicles. I did
not go anywhere to have though, but that, if you go on an all Rocky Mountain oyster diet for a
little bit, you'd have to think that would have some impact eating testosterone. Were they on the
menu at Casa Bonita? No, because the Casa Bonita menu is very pretty simple. That's like, yeah,
that's like eight things because they're still, I actually didn't really, I was in one of the only
cliffside dining is where you actually order from a menu. I think everywhere else you still go to a
counter and it's sort of the Chipotle style kind of do it right in front of you on a tray. So it's
all such that it's like, you know, whatever, a couple dozen things that were rearranged.
I wanted to shout out at the top, some other stuff that I did in Denver because Casa Bonita
was the primary reason to go. But, you know, we found a lot of fun things to do on the food
front. The one I wanted to call out, there's a place called Cherry Cricket and that is a burger
chain. Again, don't know if there's Rocky Mountain oyster burgers there. I did a bison burger as a
thousand things you could do there. I'm sort of off burgers in general. This place blew me away.
This made me want to stay back on. If the burger quality typically at places was as high as at
Cherry Cricket and just like Charmin, great place and cool old sign. I wanted to shout that out if
you end up in the area. The Denver Zoo is fantastic. One of the best zoos I've been in a long time.
They had a train. Trains are important, as I've said, for my son's particular interests,
which are trains. To that end, the Colorado Railroad Museum in Golden, which is a little
bit west of Denver, was really wonderful. Maybe fun even if you don't have a train crazy kid. You
get to take a cool old real Disneyland style train around in a couple loops and Golden is really
beautiful in general. I didn't think I knocked it out of the park in terms of where we stayed. We
were in office park. I don't know. It wasn't particularly charming or anything. I kind of
wished I'd stayed in Golden because that's where it's beautiful hills getting closer to Rockies
and it's where the Coors Factory is. We did not take the tour. I wanted to just pop into the
gift shop, but you had to get on a shuttle to even be in the gift shop. We didn't want to deal with
any of that. If anybody's going and taking a trip specifically for Casa Bonita, which I recommend,
I had a good feeling about the Golden area and I bet the Coors Factory is fun too. The other thing
to shout out, again, a little sequel episode. I got to say, one of my favorite things I did while
I was there, Bass Pro Shops. We did Bass Pro Shops pretty soon after the airport because we
wanted to do a stop and have some lunch between airport and hotel. Have you guys ever been to a
Torchy's Tacos? No, I've heard about them. This is a good chain. I really like Torchy's Tacos. It's
not a Colorado chain. I think Austin it started and we'd had it before in Dallas and it left a
good impression. When we saw it there on the map, like, oh, Torchy's, let's do Torchy's, really good
queso, good weird kinds of tacos. We stopped at a Torchy's and then like, wait a minute, very,
very close to this Bass Pro Shops. It's a big one. It's a good one. It has one of the amenities that
not all of them have, which is a shooting gallery, an upstairs shooting gallery. This was so fun.
I realized that I've never really done, maybe I've never done a shooting. That's what you said on the
Casa Benito. Oh, yes, because it came up there. Yes. Oh, right. Yes. That was the second one I
had ever done. The first one being a few days prior in Bass Pro Shops. I've never done the
Disneyland ones. Those aren't episodes that we've done. Are those good? Do we like what the Disney
World one is? Frontierland one I just saw is getting pulled out for a vacation club. Oh, yeah,
it's going to be a lounge. Boy, isn't that the current company? I think the Disneyland one was also
closing. Is that right? Is it? I don't know. I thought I saw something. Maybe not. Maybe I'm
confusing the Disney World one. I've done a lot of shooting. I was a big shooting gallery kid.
Okay. We had one on the Ocean City boardwalk. Both parks had one. And of course, the Playland one
burned down during that fire a few years ago. It was populated with monsters. They used to have a
haunted house. Oh, that's cool. Okay. So they converted a lot of the monsters where you would
shoot a target and a casket would open up or a Frankenstein would move or something. Oh, that's
a different one. Yeah. They don't all have to be old west and you're looking at old shit and shooting
cans and stuff. Although I'm also, I like the classic too. Now I want to know what the Frontierland
one is like, because I did really like this. It's funny because I was just in Disneyland and I
don't remember if the shooting gallery is open. I think it's open. I think so. Yeah. I never heard
anything about that. If you're here otherwise, Jason, let us know. I think I've only done it.
Let's do an episode. I've only done it once. I did it with, I was there with Aaron Whitehead
and Marissa Strickland and we did it I think like six or seven years ago. Who's the best shot?
I don't remember. I feel like we have like photos of that though. If it's not you giving this tea
conversation, man, I would hate to be. Maybe you know it's not you and you just don't want
to bring it up after all that. I wouldn't want to bring it. No, you know what? I am so honest on this
show. I would absolutely explain that I was the worst shot if it was true, which I don't think
it is. We just don't know. We just don't know. We just don't know. We'll figure out who's the
best among the three of us. Very possibly Jason given his shooting gallery history. And his high
T. His assumed high T. My assumed high T, yeah. Well, we have to, I don't know if, there's not a
shooting gallery in Alliance of Adventure, is there? Because that, again, you would, you would just
blast a hole through the actual. We should do a live show where somebody extracts our blood and
does the T test right in front of the live audience and sees the three of us. How quickly
do you think it comes? That's the, are we going to have to keep that audience there for six hours
overnight? If it has to be that, it has to be that. It's going to be a lock-in. It's going to be a
post-prom party. You'll see the blood transform live. Yeah, you'll see the machine wheel in.
We will have to pay for the licensed phlebotomist. Is that the term? Oh, maybe. For someone who draws
blood, I believe, phlebotomist. And then we'll go, we must have a phlebotomist in the audience.
Either, either. This is one of those situations. Either Jason is dead on or it is not even close
to phlebotomist. Or that's somebody that like studies rhinoceros. This is like, what was the
one that, oh, we're phalatists? Phalatists. And we're saying, we were getting our heads around
that word for five straight minutes and then it was philatelist. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Stamps,
stamps is phalatelist. Stamps. We will see. So anyways, really good shooting gallery and
best pro shops. You know, you make like a duck fly around or a big like mountain lion move back
and forth. Do you get points? It's points, yeah. There's no particular reward there,
unfortunately. You know, there's no prizes available. And it was not as generous as the
Cospadina one. Yeah. As a kid, I just didn't like it when there wouldn't be points. I think I got so
video game-pilled as a child. Wow, okay. That like for some reason, it wasn't enough if like a can
fell. Oh yeah. Even though now I would appreciate the can more than the points. I'm not a points
guy anymore. No. But. You're a credit card points guy. Well, amen to that. I am that. But
not as far as as far as like a shooting gallery. I'm much more wanting the theming and I won't want
the antics to happen once you shoot. Well, what you've described then is going to be a mark
for you against one experience that I had in Elitch Gardens, the main topic here. Anyways,
main thing best pressure, like just the basics, even beyond the general thing, you know, like
it's all the same stuff. Waterfalls, so many animals around and my son's going nuts climbing
on ATVs and pontoons. Yeah, he just he really loves it there. This is a particularly great one
and this one did not let us down. We bought matching hats. I don't think we've ever bought
anything matching as a family. We're so excited. Those those hats there are priced to move.
Those are much like six bucks. Wow. Wow. Like trucker hats. Jason's tea just surged
50 points when he heard six dollar hats. Well, you want to I forget if I tagged you on this
when it was happening. But if we really want the tea to surge giant like truck, like flatbed truck
filled with dollar moon pies. Oh, well, yeah, that's a great price. It's broken the scale.
It's like I need I need to leave for a second. Please don't look in my crotch area while I get
up. But anyways, so yeah, a lot of fun stuff in Denver, really high on that Bass Pro Shops.
And then that leads us to Elitch Gardens, for which I will do a little bit of history before
I get into my specific experience. It's one of those like well, I mean, Jason, I'm glad you
you know, you've been a little sick and we almost had to do this one without you. I'm glad you're
here because this is one of those like I think this park is in the tradition of the kind of thing
that you like, which is like it's that Kenny Wood model of it's a theme park today, but it grew out
of a it's been there since 1890. Yes, it's moved locations. It moved location. There was a hard
reset in like 95, I believe. But yeah, like now just clearly like, you know, in the mold of Six
Flags kind of theme park. But it started as like, you know, charming place for, you know, for events
and fairs and just grounds and gardens. And then they slowly add carousel and ferris wheel and a
little kiddy land and a wooden coaster called Mr. Twister. And it had like a music hall. It's the
Trocadero. It's that, you know, where it was like the kind of place where there'd be like a there's
the bandleader named like Cap Flappy, that kind of guy, Cap Flappy's Orchestra. So like, you know,
very much I feel like what you like on the East Coast, I think is the lineage of this place. But
then reset in 94, original location closes, moves to new location, which is really close to downtown,
maybe like the closest theme park to a downtown I've ever seen. It's a little unusual. Yeah,
it's bizarre to see video footage. Like I saw one vlogger who's like, there's the football stadium
and there's the basketball arena, you know? Yeah. And here's the Lich right between. It's next it's
right next to whichever was the stadium where Obama did that particularly gigantic produced
acceptance of the nomination. Okay. Remember that? Yeah. A lot of columns. And then that was the.
Yes. That was the Republican hit. Like, geez, who is this guy with the columns? Does he think he's
Zeus or something? They got him. Yeah. Yeah, nailed him down. Anyways, we've I think mentioned it
before on the show due to it being the filming location of three ninjas high noon at Mega Mountain
for fine feature film Hulk Hogan. Yes. Jim Varney, a good Jim Varney performed one of those that
reminds you like, is it a good movie? No. But is he if somebody given him the dramatic chip because
he they were not in the earnest ballpark at all. Right. He had range. Lonnie Anderson. Oh, yeah,
Lonnie Anderson, too. Good and silly in it. Anyway, in this time, it was bought by Six Flags.
It was then unbought by Six Flags and it goes one of the ones that they shook loose in like the Dan
Snyder era, which is a tumultuous time. So like 2006, it's not. So anyway, the like, I think we
my guess is that if there was a lot of charm to this place ever that some of the charm shook out
in that when it literally moved locations. Yeah. Usually the when you see moved locations,
it's like and in 1930, it moved locations. It's rare to see. I feel like 1994 on the big we've
taken all of the attractions and moved it down the road. Yeah. Yeah. It feels like ancient history.
Yeah. Usually. And I think that opening it in the 90s and that it had a vibe that worked for
something called High Noon at Mega Mountain and that it had a vibe that made sense to Six Flags
in the 90s. I just I think like something happened there. I bet like the architecture
was more charming before the grounds were more charming before. I don't know. Maybe if you're
local there, you grew up there, you could say that, no, this place was pretty like charming and good
in 95, 96 or so. But today, perhaps a little questionable. And I was maybe a little bit aware
of this going in. Now, it's it's very much as I was saying, like in the same neck of the woods as
Great America, which I did up in Santa Clara. It's actually the same format of my San Jose trip
where I did. There was one episode about an extremely charming place that I got to go to,
like shockingly charming, which in the San Jose case was Gilroy Gardens. And then there's that
now there is a park that is on death's door that is being redeveloped to be condos or something
that I, you know, I'm not even sure what it is exactly. But like this strange situation
where they've called it, it's going away, but we're still going to run the place.
Yeah, it's going away. There's no listed closing date, I think still.
Yeah, even the other one, Great America has like, you know, whatever, five years. This,
we don't I don't think we know. We don't. It seems like a redevelopment project, which
always fall apart a million times before something inevitably gets built. Yeah. Maybe.
Yeah, well, like three passes of it gets like crappier and more boring.
Yeah. So but this is the one of the parks. I think this might be the one we've been
warned about the most or like, you got to look into this one, you know?
Yeah, yeah. Well, and that'll factor in the way I tried to remind myself the warnings was
that was in a particular funny point. But anyway, I'm now like,
you shouldn't do this. You should. You should close the park or not.
Yeah, don't let it just like run itself into the grass. It's like it's like letting a car
run up to I think I can get this up to 200,000 miles and like it's all like every part is just
wearing down and wearing down. And if you like didn't replace any of it. Yeah, it's fine. I
don't I don't need a window. No, that rattle is part of the charm of the engine. It's all good.
The overheating is how I know it's working. I saw at least one or two videos where someone's
like, well, I want to try to hit all the coasters. But a number of them are closed.
And I was told it was because of staffing issues. It is the day after Fourth of July.
So that's a little confusing. Yeah, that's that's exactly the situation
I found. And in my head, I was like, well, this must be like a post covid thing. Like we're,
you know, we just aren't running as much. We'd rather it be open than not. But we just don't have
the staff. And then I watched one of those videos and it was exactly what I encountered.
And that was in 2018. Yes. Yeah, I think that same video. Also, they're like, well,
I know a little bit of sway is common with coasters, tracks, especially older wooden ones.
But this seems like a lot. And they just show footage of like a roller coaster, like the whole
thing, like swaying in the breeze. Yeah, really swaying. And I'm like, oh, my God.
Well, yeah, it sways when a, you know, just when a coaster car goes on top of that part of the track,
it just the entire all of the support sway. And I know that because I was in that line and I saw
that happen before I saw that video. But I'm going to do that. I'll get to that in the narrative of
how this this played out. Anything else about that you noticed that you found about like it's
interesting about the place before I get into how my day went? Well, I you might have be prepared
to do this. But are you going to explain this insignia like the logo? Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's
right at the top. That's great. That's a good sort of a place to start. Well, let me just let me just
say this also that like so what what did get communicated to me by people who know the Denver
area well is that it would not be a good idea to go to Denver with a young child and not have Casa
Bonita as the like to where it would not be smart to go. We'll go to Denver for a little bit. And
the big centerpiece will be Elitch Gardens. This much I clocked from what people got back to me.
So I was really teetering on canceling this trip. But thank God Casa Bonita worked out and you heard
how that went and how lit up I was about that. So it was great. Then what happened was I was so
wired from that experience. And that was the last night of the trip. Truly, I felt like I had just
done like five espresso shots. I was I was purely for I mean, a little bit of alcohol, but also just
like it the raw enthusiasm about being there. So I slept terribly. We were all sleeping bad,
just hotel room. We weren't used to it and it wasn't the most comfortable. So like awful,
awful night of sleep. And then but we got a day to kill. Like the flights not till 4 p.m.
But like boy, it was really like I don't know if I feel like being in a theme park and especially
one that we've like been warned about essentially. But we got to kill time somehow. It's like on the
way to the airport and we land at. Well, what if we just go for three hours? Let's see if we can
keep it to three hours and just do like kind of kind of the quick version. And I'm sure there'll
be something, you know, cute for my son and it'll be good. But this is this is, I think, important
that we were like on the fence coming from a really exemplary themed experience. And then we
arrive at this place. We pull up and notice a couple of things. One is what you mentioned,
Jason, that there is a sign that is a very like, you know, fifties beer sign feel like
there's a few of these on the way in that's very traditional looking. And here's a picture of me
with it and what it if I were to read how they intended, it would be not to see Elitch's is not
to see Denver. But it's like it's presented with a circle within a circle. And the way that
naturally you want to read this and what you pointed out, Jason, was that like the human eye
like reads the middle and then reads the outside. So you go you start with the middle and it says
Elitch's is not to see. Yeah. And then another not to sit like they're warning not to see. And
that one's and it's white text over black. That feels more not to see Denver. It looks like it
was on a list called not to see Denver. Yeah. And they had to display it like you have to display
a health code violation. I did see footage of someone reading it yesterday and I was like,
OK, not to see Elitch's is not to see that. So it's like the spirit of Denver. Like you have to
if you come to Denver, you have to see Elitch. That is what they are trying to convey. But yes,
given that you read what's on the brighter color before the outlay, like what we all naturally have
chosen, how we choose to read things presented like that leaves us at Elitch's is not to see.
Yeah, you also shouldn't have not to see so close to your whether it's even if you're saying like
don't miss it. Yeah. Like it's also a sign that's like comma part splintering. Like the photo I'm
looking at has like multiple like, OK, this needs paint. This needs to be cleaned up. That gutter
doesn't look too cleaned out. I'm like, no, there's like notice five flaws just in this photo of the
sign. And that sign is in the dead center of the giant Ferris wheel, too. Oh, that's right.
So you're not to see Elitch's is not to see. Skip it. Yeah. And the fact that that's outside.
There were there were three things that were tells to leave before we even got in. One was
this sign. One was the parking, which was thirty dollars. Really? Even for this place? Yes. We are
at Disney Universal. It's exactly what I paid on Hollywood Boulevard the other night when there
was like there were multiple shows going on. Yeah. Pretty cocky. Right. And then the other thing is
that we pull in and it's we weren't too concerned because it was right at opening. We were rope
dropping it. But there was a big line out the door and we were like, well, maybe that'll clear
because it literally is opening. But then we realized there was a commonality between almost
everybody in the line. And that is that they were all 12 to 13 years old. Everyone, everyone
outside like what is going on? I mean, we were anticipating teens for sure. But then we're putting
it together and like, OK, wait, it's like 12 to 13 year olds. And then like one one per hundred
middle schoolers has like a stressed out person with a clipboard. Oh, this is this is a chaperone.
This is that this is like the middle school trip day. We have chosen the middle school trip day
to go to this place that we were already on the fence about. Oh, my goodness.
It's better than a grad night, I would think. Yeah, because it's not. It's not. Yeah. I mean,
it isn't only teenage. Like, it's not exclusive. Right. Because these teens aren't as like fully
comfortable being teens yet. You know, they're not they're not giving off that scarier teen
energy, not necessarily. Some of them are more mature. Mm hmm. But I'm just saying I could see
if they were 17 year olds, I'd be extra scared as an older man. Sure, sure. You know, well,
in your current in your like 400 range T world. Well, if I get up to 500 and you're clocking teens
left and right, you're picking them up and throwing them at each other. Certainly. Yes, that gives me
more fear when my T is lower. I can feel it. Work on this and then you can go to then you can finally
go to grad night at Six Flags Magic Mountain and they'll let you in because you'll pass as a teen.
Exactly. Not that you don't now. So youthful and so aggressive. They won't know the difference.
Youthful you have, aggression you're missing. Yes. Looking for aggression. Well, you're right that
they aren't all of that like intimidating. Yeah. Ilk. But there are what we figured out is that
there's a there's a range, right? There are alphas and the alphas have to prove themselves. And
you know, we we get past this pretty irritating line where it is nothing but 12 year olds and then
and just like the stressed out the chaperones going like guys, guys, guys, that kind of so it's
this is a frazzled energy. And I think my son is the only like little kid in sight.
Oh, that would be scary if I was a little kid. Yeah. And it's all older kids. I don't think he
could. I mean, he's it's all older. Yeah, that's true. Well, like I'm the same. I'm 12 too.
You may as well be. Yeah. Yeah. But anyways, we get to the stroller check in. We go to rent
a stroller for the day. That is right next to another check in, which is like animals that you
can ride around. You know, this kind of thing. Yes. In the Burbank Mall. Oh, my God. Yeah. You
get like tigers. Oh, no. Wheels or whatever. Oh, you could just ride one of those through a theme
park theme park. Yes, I've never seen that before. It's really controlled in a mall, right? It's like
doing this little loop, do it in a pen. But here, yeah, 12 year olds are renting tigers to ride for
the day to ride into each other on the presumably broken as well. I would imagine that's not a good
idea. But that to me is awesome. Sure. Yeah, I would love to do that. If you could, if you had
control of the area and then, yeah, we could. All right. It's tiger versus zebra versus mountain
lion. If you could ride like on a panda through Disneyland. Holy shit with that rule. That's
pretty cool. Yeah. Yeah. Well, look, they're they're looking for upcharge experience. Right.
The modern Disney company is just going to loop around to Six Flags. All right. What is some dumb
crap that we can get 20 extra bucks to pop for? They're jealous of Six Flags in a lot of ways.
They might be looking at Six Flags. Right. How do we this is the idea? How do we get there?
Johnny Rockets is so expensive. How do we how do we get our audience to pay this much?
There's a whiteboard and it just says cigarettes question mark vapes question mark.
That's next on the agenda. Once the once the Disney sports betting mechanism is fully up
and then the the Main Street Cinema is replaced by just like they're just playing boxing matches
and you're putting money down. They were gambling is coming. I think it's coming.
It's already with ESPN. It's kind of like find any piece of footage or any media where Walt
says the word gambling, just show that this is what he wanted. And if not, make it up,
plant it. Just go age it. Just go like we'll Photoshop a picture of him. Yeah. You know,
just like like doing craps and then just go like bury that in the dirt for six months and we'll
pull it. Look what we found. Walt did want gambling to be part of this. I read a thing
a while back. I don't remember the exact specifics, but like I think some of the
like the Seminole tribe maybe and that the tribe that owns the hard rock, they were trying to get
gambling off the ground in Florida. And I think their lobbyists kept getting blocked
by Disney's more powerful lobbyists. Like Disney has tried to keep Florida out of at least the
range of central Florida, like gambling, gambling, free bubble because of just the family friendly
image. Yeah. And I guess they'll be glad they did that when they finally introduced it. Right.
They're going to do well. But also you can't. Now, if you watch sports sports games now,
you get the fanatics bets, ESPN bets. So that is slowly creeping in. Yeah. Well,
you got to admit and unless I'm wrong, you tell me, Jason, is it does it betray the Mark Twain
that you love if you can do riverboat gambling? I think it's in the spirit. I mean, if I would
love to get in on a craps get like, you know, ride the river. But there are some kind of,
you know, segments of the river with not a lot going on. So I'd love to just pop into a craps
game or get taken for a ride on a three card Monte. This is a table and smoke a cigarette while
you're doing it. Oh, yeah. It's not going to be casino games. It's going to be three card Monte
tables, which have been retired from New York and turned into weed tables. As you've told us,
it's going to be dirty tables just sitting on the outside of the deck. It's going to be
con men. Yeah. It will be Disney sponsored con men, but there's going to be shady characters.
All right. Where's the follow the coin for the coin? And then if the boat stops suddenly, like,
I saw what's cup. I saw the cup. And they're like, no, it doesn't count.
I've got a billion dollar idea for someone, probably not universal because they have Nintendo.
Let's do Sonic casino night zones where you can actually gamble because that's one of my favorite
level in Sonic and just let it be real gambling. What's the ownership there? Sega owns it. Okay.
But who owns it? Do they have any theme parks? That's a very good question. And it's a lot of
Sega. I feel like in theme parks. Yeah. And there's no interventions had Sega and Sonic stuff.
Paramount. Yeah. Okay. Well, that's kind of a fucked one. I wonder if there's not like a
big licensing deal yet for a theme park with Sonic. Yeah. It feels like a big character not
to have represented somewhere, but he sort of feels that this feels like maybe the move that
like puts six flags officially on top if they put casino night zone. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. It not
only is it just full on gambling, but it's with the Sonic property. Yeah. Which I think matches
the vibe of six flags in general. I think that's right. I think imagine just seeing like Robotnik
and Mr. Six hand in hand. Cause they're both similar. They're like brothers. It's never
occurred. Or is his dad. That's a great idea. They get along great. Yeah. Is Mr. Six maybe
that they could tie it together. The reveal that Mr. Six is Dr. Robotnik's grandfather. Yeah.
And he's in a little egg too. I feel like we're starting to see like early 2000s nostalgia. It's
been 20 years. Let's get Mr. Six back. Isn't it starting to, wasn't there just something?
There was a little bit of Mr. Six, wasn't there? They're teasing something,
but I don't know. A while ago already. I don't know. We're like a granddaughter of Mr. Six.
I don't know, but I want him, I want him back. Look, we got Shaq and the general are fully back.
They were gone and now they're back. Yeah. They're, I think they were gone for a little while. I
don't know anything about them being gone. I do know they are around. I saw them the other day.
My daughter seemed to like the general Shaq commercial where they were like dancing in a
club together. Okay. So they're at least around. I just don't know if they went away. Yeah. Right,
right. Did Six Flags merge with Cedar Fair? What happened with that?
I think it's still in the works. That's still trying to figure that out? Yeah.
Anyways, back to the animal writers who basically, as Aaron is trying to get a stroller,
there's both things involve a form. Like, okay, well we need your info here for what she's doing
with the stroller and then right next to her, the teens are doing it to take their tiger out
or whatever. Yeah. And if you can imagine that the teens are not as patient with forms as a mother
and they just kind of like, they just start going and the woman behind the counter like,
wait, wait, wait, guys, guys, guys. And they're just off. They do not, they are not registered,
whatever had to be done, deposit, I don't know. They are just off and writing. And I don't know,
I never saw anything, I'm not building any big story here that I saw anything bad happen,
but it was just one of those unnerving elements through the day where you'd be walking around
and then like, oh, it's them. And you could feel an energy from the other teens as well,
where it's kind of like, they're like the apes who are riding the horses and have control of
the Falcons as well. There's like, how do you elevate yourself in this society, in tween society?
Well, riding on tiger back definitely helps. There was a fear and an awe around the tiger
riders all day. So the other thing that was happening, this is a syndrome I realized I
don't think we've ever talked about on the show, even though this is a very common theme parky
thing. And this sort of, you know, the coaster style parks, we saw this one little booth,
like a little tent with a couple of things on top of a folding table. And I went, oh,
this takes me back. This is the physics table. This is the physics justification of why the
middle school is just fucking off and going to a theme park today. Like, see, we did it. Physics.
Look, there's like, I don't know, there's a couple of balls on, those are molecules. See?
Molecule, without molecules, we wouldn't have roller coasters. Is that close enough? Great.
This is a physics day. That is what we're doing physics. Did you guys ever do one of those?
I was, we may have, and that I maybe sat out because I was too coaster afraid.
I don't think we actually did. That would have been great, but we didn't.
It was a big LA high school thing. Like, just like get through these months because we will
find a really thin justification to just go to Magic Mountain.
Yeah. I went to Hershey Park a few times, two or three times, as part of Song Fest. Like,
the band and the chorus would go sing and compete. And then they would unleash you on the park for
not enough hours, for my taste. Song Fest didn't give you enough hours?
Are we roped up to close? Is this a roped up to close today?
The one time me and my dad came up and picked up me and my friend early so we could go to the
freshman formal that night, which sucked that that was on the same night. And looking back, I'm like,
why did I leave a theme park to wear an ill-fitting suit and go to a dance? Yeah.
Were you participating in Song Fest? Yeah.
So you sang at Song Fest? Yes.
What, do you remember what you sang? You know, probably, I have had this,
it talked with a few people about this experience. The main song I remember singing, the two main
songs were a choral arrangement of Blackbird, the Beatles song Blackbird, and then Ease On Down the
Road from The Wiz. Oh, you said this from The Wiz, yeah.
And I have had multiple people go, like, I had a very white chorus too. I had a very
lily white chorus too. And we also sang songs from The Wiz. We sang Ease On Down the Road as well.
And you did this at Song Fest. I think we probably would have. Like,
that's what I can remember. And now with a Sly and the Family Stone medley.
Jason. Jason Solo.
Singing the spiritual classic Wade in the Water. We shouldn't have been singing that.
I like this song. It's about fishing for pond deals.
Yeah. Fishin' for Jersey pond deals.
So then now I am making my way, you know, while being cautious of the Tiger Riders,
I'm making my way up their main street. And this is, like, the most committed to attempt
at, like, a little charming turn of the century area. There's an old carousel as you enter.
There is a, you know, like, you know, little shops and avenues attempting a main street vibe.
And then, like, little signs, just like Main Street, where, like, oh, it's implying businesses,
the barbershop or whatever. But even these have kind of an unnerving air. Like, this very old
sign that's falling apart that says Mekeska Insurance, the widow's friend.
What? What?
Weird. So that stuff is a miss.
I guess it's funny, though.
Yeah, it kind of is. It's a dark funny joke, so I can appreciate it.
Yeah, yeah. But then the other thing that's weird is that there's, like, you're on the,
there's, like, lampposts with, you know, signs on either side saying, like, stuff that's coming up,
but, you know, all right, upgrade to a season pass. And then there's, like,
events that are coming up, like fireworks on Labor Day weekend. And then over here,
Friday, July 19th, Wonka. And I'm like, Wonka? Is there going to be, like, a Wonka experience?
Did they buy the Glasgow Wonka experience? Is it officially taking up residence at
Delich Gardens with no change? No, what this is is seems to be the movie Wonka.
That's their big event for the summer. Friday nights. Elitch Fridays. We got Wonka.
We bought a DVD.
All our employees are sharing a max password. And then, like, Friday, July 26th, Monsters Inc.
So they're just, this is a big summer. They're just showing old Disney movies.
They printed out a sign, too, with their logo on it and with Mike and Sully, which is interesting.
Isn't it weird seeing Mike and Sully at a different theme park? And it's just because
they're going to play the, and then we were going, like, given the jankiness of this park,
do they even have a screen or are they just going to play it on the Ferris wheel?
Like, this is the biggest surface we have. Granted, it's moving and there's lights and stuff,
but, like, come on, it's bigger than any screen's going to be. We're going to play Monsters Inc.
On top of a Ferris wheel. You did not get that question answered, I assume.
I don't. I'll try to, you know, I'll try to stay on it. It could be on the side of a building,
I guess. Yeah, maybe so. Well, yeah, it'll be on one of these with, like, awnings and railings
and stuff. Worthy to wait for a real cloudy night projected on the clouds.
Onto the sky? Yeah.
All right. Eyes on the sky, everybody. What movie is it? Toy Story? No, it's Sully. Look,
it's Sully. So, you know, weird stuff still abounds. And then now where do I land? Oh,
well, I head straight to one of the big reasons we've talked about this place before,
the Meow Wolf ride. Meow Wolf did got the opportunity to take over a dark ride
at this park. It is called Kaleidoscape. Yes. Not Kaleidoscope, but Kaleidoscape. Okay, great.
It used to be a Ghost Blasters. It used to be a Sully Dark Rides. A kind of, like, generic,
like that's something they've put in a couple of parks, you know, shooting gallery type ride.
And they got to, like, you know, take it over and, like, build custom installations and, like,
you know, specific artists got specific rooms and kind of the stuff they do. So I want to see that.
That sounds great. I split off from family to go check that out. And I get out and the pre-show
is running. And I'm like, this is a little neat. This is almost like a little Epcot-y. This is,
like, a little bit like, you know, like, you know, inventions, I might say. Like, there's a robot
kind of without, like, where you can see all the mechanisms inside, which is very interventions.
And then it's like cool synthy music and this kind of, like, a vapor wavy thing going on. Like,
okay, well, now we're talking. You know, that doesn't seem all great here, but this seems a
little bit cool. There's an employee up by the cars by the loading, but I can't quite get to her.
And then I'm like, oh, wait, I can't. Like, all right, it's blocked off. I can't. So I yell to
her over the music, you guys aren't open? No. When will you be open? We don't know.
Oh. You don't? You don't know? Implying that, like,
this is coming from somebody up top is going to pull the trigger on this thing. This is the
opening of the day, the, you know. Sure. So, all right, maybe I will not get to do the
Meow Wolf ride. And then this sets in motion something was alluded to in one of the videos
that you should, like, on the outside of the park, it says this ride closed, that ride closed.
I start poking around. It is so much more than those rides closed. There are a lot of rides
closed. And I don't know if that's just going to come throughout the day. They will start expanding.
That happens even in Universal or something. This ride opens an hour late, but I'm like,
I'm a little bit suspicious of how this is actually going to work. And then I learn about
a new policy because I quicker than I expected returned to my family where I left them in kind
of the kiddie zone. And Aaron informs me that there are five rides in this area and they are
all operated by one employee who is just waiting for lines to form. And whichever one has the
longest, you will then have to say, excuse me, go run the bus that goes around. All right. Now
there's a lot of people at the train. Sorry. I'll be at the train. That's a new one, right?
That's a joke we've made. I'm sure about six flags or something before. And that's reality here.
Even at smaller Jersey Shore parks, unless it was a really small family
fun center with a couple of rides and a mini golf course, that's the only time I've seen
something like that. And it's usually really empty when that's going on.
You should not pay $30 for parking and then get into a place where one employee is running five
rides, all of which look of questionable quality. My son's in a pretty like not trying stuff,
easily scared kind of era. So he didn't want to do any of it. And in this case, we're like,
that's fine. That's, you know, probably better, probably for the best. And also just given this
policy, like, geez, poor guy. At least he's getting his steps in for the day.
Yeah. Could you have offered to help? Could you have said, hey, do you need any help for an hour?
Because I like I've kind of always wanted to do some of these park ops thing. Like,
do you think that person would have been like, yeah, I think he would have cut me off before
that second sentence you said. OK, because I kind of like, yeah, go. Yeah. Red button, go.
He wouldn't be in such a haze that he doesn't even occur to him that I don't work there.
He would see that I was wearing a collared shirt and that I'm twice his age and go,
probably works here. Or at least knows what he's doing in some regard. He would have thought you
own the park. That must be James. You must be a multimillionaire, sir, with that collar on.
Man, you can afford a collar. Must be nice. That's extra fabric and those buttons it takes to
attach your shirt together. Those buttons ain't cheap. Are you a Coors?
All right, you got me. I'm Scotty Coors. This will all be mine one day. But yeah, so really,
Shay. So we're like, what else can we do? And we find an arcade and my son's in arcades right now
and we go to an arcade that is the most caked on dust I've ever seen. It is a view outside to a
log flume ride with the brownest water I've ever seen. It is truly vile. It is also not running,
if you can imagine. And I'm like, well, I got to do something. I think I owe one ride, at least,
if I'm going to come here. And I know that when I was in what I realized was a pretty equivalent
place, which is great America, I was pretty down on it in that experience. And I think I even
noticed people saying, well, it's kind of a coaster place, and you can't just go there and
not do coasters. And so I got to do a coaster. I sort of chickened out of something called
Mind Eraser, which might be maybe the main thing to do, a Vekoma suspended looping coaster,
which means, I don't know, I can't actually tell how it's like, I don't know, you're hanging and
then it's like lots of loops. But I can't tell how that's different than whatever the knots one,
what's the silver bullet? I can't quite tell. If you haven't noticed before, I zone out pretty
easily on these coaster differences. That is not what the podcast is.
The mechanical difference. Yeah, yeah. But it seemed like a good one,
certainly, although then I watched some video that was like, oh, well, for a Vekoma SLC,
this was kind of a weak, not well-kept Vekoma. All right, sure. Jason, there's something at
Maury's Piers called the Great Nor'easter. You ever done that?
I have seen it. I don't think I ever wrote it.
Okay. Same breed of coaster if you are there. So I didn't do that. Not to mention, I do not want
to be in like super teen dense lines, but I do brave something that's like, I'm like, I can do
an old wooden coaster. There was one I wanted to do at Great America. I didn't get to do. So I'm
going to go for this old wooden coaster. This is called Twister Three Storm Chaser.
Are they on to three? I thought it was two. Oh, you saw a two. No, it's three. We're up to
three. This is kind of a, I mentioned way early in the episode, I think the first coaster this
place ever had in the old school form was called Mr. Twister. So it's all like a spiritual heir
to that. Again, I even like type, I don't, I guess it's like, I don't know. It's a wooden coaster
that's especially twisty. I don't know. I'm terrible at this. This is not part of the theme
podcaster job that I like. And someone from BNM is going to, it's coming for your ass.
That's okay. Cause I don't know what that stands for. Sam Pearl. Oh, Bollinger and Maliburn.
Oh no, they're mad at you now too. I've heard that name. I don't think that's how you say it.
Maliburn. I don't know. They're coming for your ass too now. Whoever's mad now had to wade through
20 minutes of testosterone discussion at the top of this to get to the point where we talk about
the technical aspects of different roller coasters. And now they're let down so thoroughly. They're
shut this podcast off. The person who wants that podcast and it keeps trying, like I feel like
it's going to be that if I will it hard enough, I just want them to say that it goes up to 39 miles
an hour. Why don't they say it? Why don't they read a Wikipedia? The heavies from Zamperla are
going to send their goons. So anyways, yeah, it's twister three and I went on a Reddit to see what
the deal with that was. And like a lot of people on paying attention to this kind of thing are like,
I don't know, this seems like an overextension to even call this a sequel. I don't know. Cause
they didn't like, maybe they, they didn't replace the track. They maybe just took out the parts of
the track that were like going to break entirely. But they also did add a, there is a kind of a theme
to this and I'll give them a little bit in terms, this is not a park where theming seems like the
main deal, but this twister three storm chaser, the title implies that this is about storm chasers
like in twister or the upcoming twisters. It's like storm tracker guys. And so you're walking
through a roller coaster and it looks like it's the remnants of like that a tornado has just
happened. So they like took a boat or a bike and they wedged it upside down into the wooden slats.
That's good. It's kind of good. It was a little bit good. And there were storm tracker vehicles,
that kind of thing. And then like kind of a, you know, like a little fake facts about, maybe not
fake facts, but facts about like what storm chasing is all about and a soundtrack of like, okay, go on
whatever. Like, okay, we kind of got something here. So there is a little bit of theming.
Then I get up to the top of the stairs and I get stuck for a lot longer than I think. Like I thought
this thing was moving and it's not. And then I finally get up to where I say how many in my party,
which is one and the team just goes like, and then just kind of like half-hearted sort of moves her
arm in the direction of just kind of like a general pen where then I'm not directed into a row or
anything. It's just a disorganized like, you figure it out. So then I'm there and I'm watching
cars go by. And it's then that I notice, Jason, what you brought up from that video,
there are supports that are just fully shaking every time one of the cars goes by.
Yeah, I think it's, I looked up my YouTube history. I believe the video is called worst
park in America, question mark. And that's by the channel airtime thrills. And they had a very
similar experience to what you were experiencing. And they seem very enthusiastic about coasters.
And most of the ones they wanted to go on were closed. I felt so bad.
Yep. Yep. Yeah, I think that's the deal there. And again, that was from 2018. This is not a new
thing. Yeah. So I'm watching this thing shake and like, Jesus, I don't know. And then that's when
I start going on the Reddit and like, I'm just looking for any info that will tell me like,
will this ride kill me? Has anything happened here, you know, in the last 20 years even? I mean,
it did somebody get a splinter. I just, I, anything would be nice to know.
Has the roller coaster fallen over ever? Yeah.
They put it back up like six months ago, the whole thing fell over and they had to put it back up.
Yeah. Did it tip all like almost fall around somebody Buster Keaton style.
And then he had to tip it back up himself. And nothing was that crazy. But it's then that I
start going like, what the hell did the audience try to tell us? And I start, and I'm like,
I know people told us something, but I don't remember if it was Twitter DMs or emails. So
I'm like searching all of our various media. And then I find an email. I find an email from
listener Dylan. Dylan, and this was after I had mentioned my Cosmonita situation. He wrote a nice
email and gave a heads up, but I clearly should have like absorbed the email better before I was
stuck in this line. Okay. So Dylan said, as a fan, I have to warn that Elitch Gardens is awful and
not worth your time and money. Let's see. I mean, a lot of details, but then ride maintenance is
shrugged off to the point that it feels like half the park is closed. It's absolutely filthy.
And the indifference by the teens working there is palpable. Honestly, it's insulting. They are
still charging $65 a ticket. No, I think I thank God didn't pay that much. Was there like a Groupon
or something, or you had a Coke can? I don't know. Whatever. I did something. I think they might be
like cutting those prices to get anyone in for any reason. I think there's a discount if you buy
online. There was that. There's often that. That's a good tip for listeners. Do that and look for
those triple A discounts if they exist. I don't think they did for this. So thank you for attempting
to warn me, Dylan. Although honestly, wouldn't you rather have an episode about it with crazy
stories than not? That felt to me like he probably would like the episode, but then he was trying to
save me the personal struggles. And I wish I had listened more carefully for that reason. Also,
he said, and other people who know the area might be thinking this too. However, when it comes to
theme parks, I cannot recommend a spot enough just outside Denver called Lakeside Amusement Park.
I didn't get to do this. I think the timing didn't. I was there kind of right as like summer
seasons were opening up. So I didn't get to do Lakeside, but that seems like a charming good.
It's like what you think this might be. I think you cannot be one of these parks that's like post
corporate ownership because you know Six Flags ran it into the ground and then now it's just
going further and further. It's just spinning on bald tires.
Yeah. Sometimes when you see the owned by one company operated by another, it's like,
uh-oh. Sure. I'm sure there's exceptions to that rule, but it's like not a good sign necessarily.
What is the vibe like sitting on a bench? Oh, that's a good question. In this place?
What is trees? Is foliage? What is going on? What is the Six Flags ask in ways? Definitely Six Flags
ask. I think that you could find corners that feel like a park. If you were part of a Three
Ninjas type production and you needed to shoot it from angles where it seems like a charming theme
park, I think that could be done, but you'd have to do a lot of cheating and a lot of we're only
looking this way and not this way or this way and definitely not this way. Yeah. Do they have
dipping dots here? I think so. Okay. Good. Yeah. And food. Look, we didn't want to find out the
answer to food, quite honestly. Okay. And long story short, we didn't, but I'll start explaining
that. But the vibe is like no vibe. And it's just, you know, it's like it's just playing,
you know, the pop hits of 2004. If you want to hear Avril Lavigne's Girlfriend or whatever.
I wouldn't be opposed to hearing it. Did they play any songs by The Fray? Did they?
The Fray's too obscure. That's a deep cut. Yeah. Well, they had a couple of hits. We're talking
Black Eyed Peas. We're talking, they might just put on the album. Actually, you don't want to play
the album cuts of at least one of those songs, but they put on the collection of radio edits.
Yeah, that's exactly. Yeah. I don't know. Maybe there's maybe there's a Mr. Brightside,
maybe. Okay. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Book the trip now. I mean, I get we are. Look,
this is me versus you. We're talking about Mike. If you want to be in a place where food is
questionable and Mr. Brightside is playing, which I think you do. I do. Yeah. Village Gardens may be
your ticket. That sounds right. Yeah. Yeah. So anyways, I've now like reading this email
and I'm already in the line and I've put the time in and like, boy, I wish I'd like taken this into
my heart better before. And I'm looking at a track that's shaking. What am I? I don't know. Look,
I don't think it's going to topple over. I really don't. I'm going to give it a go. And hey,
what a way to go out, huh? Yeah. Wow. And then you guys are doing the posthumous episode like,
well, he died doing what he loved, I guess. I don't know. Did he love this? I actually don't
think he did like roller coasters and then one killed him. So actually, that's kind of,
and I writes just further proof he shouldn't have ever done roller coasters. So it's kind of,
I mean, we're going to do an episode on the haunting of Hill House 99 anyway, because it's
filmed a couple scenes at Islands of Adventure and a roller coaster flies off the track.
And then ironically, Scott was in a roller coaster that flew off the track.
Really excited about to talk about this movie. But first, a few quick words about one of the
hosts death. And now introducing Mr. Morrow to replace Scott as the permanent third host
on podcast, the riot. Gee, guys. Sorry to hear about that, guys. Hey, thanks for keeping me in
the loop and, you know, checking in once a month or so if I still wanted to replace Scott. Just,
you know, you gave me a big heads up and I'm glad you did. Sorry about the roller coaster thing,
but. So anyways, I get on. I'm just going to do it. I'm going to do it. And then it pulls up
and it stinks. The ride stinks. I mean, like smell wise. It's like, no, it's like burning
rubber. It's not really foul. Like much worse than Autopia. It's right in the Autopia. Yeah.
Yeah, I'd say. But then that's like many cars as opposed to one of two coaster vehicles,
the smelliest coaster in America. Yeah. Yeah. At least look, you want like laurels in your theme
park. You know, you want to be able to tout something and they can tout that. So get on it.
What I like is that you got nice views of Denver. I like that you can see mountains this way. You
can see the city this way. And then it's just a very like clackety, you know, it's just, again,
Mike, you might like it. It fucks you up a little bit. Yeah. I like that aspect of it. I don't like
the smell. I don't like the sound of the smell. Not good. Not a good smell. I like to be physically
fucked up and not olfactory. Yeah. Fucked up. You don't like to huff. Yeah. Yeah. The theming,
I think they kind of lost the theming a little bit in the ride itself in that there was no theming
at all in the ride itself. They truly bailed on that. And I saw the people on this Reddit going
like what they're going to they're going to call it Twister three. What this they replaced a little
bit of track and then like put some theming in that tunnel and that's it. And you call it a sequel.
And I would say to them, no, they didn't do that either. If there was ever like if there were like
loose nails, I think those are gone. Yeah. Still not totally sure. That is a good for parks looking
to a little bit of theming. Broken vehicles and just garbage is any ease if you just make it
disaster themed. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. A good call. Although you might confuse it just for
being the rest of the park. Yeah. Lots of loose garbage. But if you if your park is overrun with
garbage, then take it and work with it. I say I mean, I think so many of these parks could be
elevated with just a fresh coat of paint on the main street and a little bit of landscaping.
You could really like trick people and justify that like sixty five dollar price tag.
You say that Jason, but I went and this place needs nothing short of an exorcism.
I mean, it does help to have your rides open. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. That would have added to my
guest satisfaction. But now after I do that ride, which was also like, OK, look, I don't know. I
went on a roller coaster and it was a fine boy. Was it OK? Well, what was it comparable to ridewise?
Uh, you know, it's like a ghost rider. I don't know. Ghost riders pretty, you know,
ghost rider kind of fucks you up. It fucks you up a lot. Yeah. So probably. Yeah. I don't think
it's like markedly worse than Ghost Rider, even though parts of the tracks ride away.
No, Ghost Rider is like. I don't do that really ever. So it's kind of out of character that I did
this at all and that I got on something that was swaying. Did I tell did I tell the story in the
show where my friend who had a pretty decent headache before going on it, I accidentally
allowed us to all go on Ghost Rider. Oh. Her headache was much worse because it rattles like
crazy. It's an old wooden coaster. Ghost Rider, I think, has actually been retracted. I believe
it has. And it's pretty good. Like it's intense, but in like the way they want it to be.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So but it still rattles the hell out of you. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Not my
favorite genre. I like them for the charm. I like I like just like looking at it. Yeah, of course.
But I don't always like going on them. But I was OK. Right. Ghost Rider is the only like usually
if I ride a wooden coaster, I keep my glasses on. Ghost Rider was the first one I ever had to like
hold them on to my head because I was like the glass was going to break in the frames.
Yeah. Well, I mean, I was just worried they were going to fly off as if you were a dad whose son
is playing too loud of rock and roll music. Oh, yeah. The fray turned down.
I'm afraid. Anyway, this this does this takes me into what I would call my favorite part of the day
where I'm like strolling back to go find my family again and see what they've gotten up to. And I'm
like, well, let me cover this corner of the park while I'm here. And I start walking up to a ride
where this coaster looks a little fun. It seems like something that's tame enough for me to do.
Don't think it's running. Actually seems eerily quiet around here. And I walk up to Disaster
Canyon and it says Ride will open in May 2024. And I say, but that is now is currently. Why are
you not open? And nothing else around there is open. There was just a guy like reading on a bench.
I don't wish that to your point, Mike. It's charming enough that I can read a book on a bench.
Well, all this place needs is a coat of paint on that bench. And I think they can charge 65 bucks.
I like this reading on a bench ride. That sounds great.
What's he wearing? Was he was he was he reading like a mystery novel or?
I don't know. Could have been a physics book. OK, might have been some might have been the one
student who was taking the race seriously. Well, that's good. I like to hear that.
So anyways, then I like like I walk into this area and I'm like, am I backstage in the park?
Why didn't they block this off in any way? Then I turn one more corner and realize,
no, this is just now I'm still in the park. It's just oddly industrial. It's just like
corrugated metal. And then I go through this weird tunnel. And this I know I'm not supposed
to go into. But I'm like, I got to see because I don't think anybody's going to stop me.
And I keep walking and walking. And by the end of the tunnel, I am in the middle of their stunt
arena and no one has stopped me from being in their stunt arena. It does not seem like there's
been a show here in many years. And it's just like a bunch of pigeons. And I, you know, I really,
I think I could have hung out there for a couple of hours if I didn't have a family to get back to.
Well, if you had a good mystery novel with you, you really could have posted up.
Again, it's, you know, actually, in a way, I didn't realize how we,
Lich Gardens were getting back to this kind of like what Walt want. It's like a place,
you know, sure, there's roller coasters, but, you know, sure, we could either run our roller
coasters or we could have, you know, just a nice, simple 2000 seat stunt arena that just you can
sit in and read, you know, seven to 10 chapters. Yeah. Hercule Poirot. It's almost like Hercule
Poirot is in the park. He's there with you. Who is that? It's the character that it's an Agatha
Christie's like Belgian detective character that Kenneth Branagh keeps making the movies.
That's that character's name? Yeah. What's the character? Say it again. Hercule Poirot.
Hercule Poirot? Poirot. Poirot. Sorry, sorry. Hercule? Hercule? Yeah, it's strange. It's like
Hercules, but you stop before the end. It's shortening if you're really familiar with
Hercules. I think Peter Ustinov played him at some point. Albert Finney played him, I think.
So he's like a Joker character. He's very much a Joker character. Yeah. I'm just saying it's
a famous role that a lot of different famous actors have played. Yeah. Presumably the source
material for whatever stunt show was in there before. I would think, yeah. Yeah, yeah. We got
Hercule. We got the Hercule live. Actually, what was in the stunt arena was, get ready, Mike,
a Batman Forever stunt show. This Batman Forever stunt show ran from 1999. Many years after the
film. That is two years after Batman and Robin. Right. We have turned it over entirely
and then it ran until 2006 when they lost the Six Flags and therefore the Warner license in general.
So this thing, it didn't even start. I've watched this video before. Of the. Of the
Batman Forever stunt show. It was at a number of Six Flags. Yeah, there was a water one too,
which was not this. Yes. Yeah. I think they got it after a different Six Flags closed it. They're
like, well, this is out of date now because it is Batman and Robin and we need something with Mr.
Freeze. Right. What do we do with the joke with the Riddler in Two-Face costumes? I don't know,
ship it down to Denver piece of crap. We got all these, you know, tanks of propane and like
fire starting effects. Yeah, send it to Denver. Either they'll use it in the show or the teens can,
you know, I don't know, go buck wild with them. Or use it to just cook some hot dogs.
It probably is how they do the thing around here. Also that it ran until 2006, which means we are
now with the full crossover has occurred into the Nolan era straddles the by the time it starts,
the Schumacher iteration is canceled. Right. And then this runs all the way through a sea change,
not only in the Batman franchise, but in comic book movies in general. Yeah. And we're still just like,
riddle me this. The dark, it went into the dark ages is what I call it.
The realism era, the dark ages. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The, the meridian Lissera. Right. So
I finally end up back with the family. My son has been held over by ice cream,
but even that is an ordeal. If you can believe it, like I will take a single scoop in a cup. Nah.
You know what? Well, we only do two or three and it's cones. We can only do cones.
So you don't have any situation where I can like scoop the ice cream being that I'm with a child.
I can't, there's no, you don't have a cup. No. And then some, and then another guy's like, yo,
we got bowls bowl. That sounds good. All right. Great. I will, then I will take two scoops in a
bowl. Nah. Huh? What do you mean? No, no, it was just Sunday's only the bowls are for Sunday.
The bowls are for Sunday's only we lit. Well, wouldn't okay. The main purpose of a bowl in a
Sunday is to hold ice cream, right? So transitive properties imply that a different kind of ice
actually it's doing less bowl work. There is, it's less likely that the bowl will fall. I
don't know if we're talking about, you know, uh, edible bowl or not. Right. But like in terms of
structural soundness, not having to deal with fudge and cherry, the, this bowl is probably more
primes to be used for two regular scoops of ice cream. So therefore can I please. Nah.
Well, I don't know. So they got a cone and I ended up eating most of it and nine dollars.
And this again, this is where this occurred to me definitely when I, when I actually went to
magic mountain to try to do that justice league ride and then not do it where I met
bug main buzz buzz. And we parked in the, uh, next to a five below it so that we could carpool.
And I was like, the five blow parking lot is a better environment than what I am paying an
up chart. Like if I'm paying for a gate that implies that's like a country club situation.
Is it not? I, but the main expense is that I am behind this gate behind which things will be
ornate and landscaped and higher quality. But no, I have paid for an incredible downgrade
from a, what a Baskin Robbins a mile away could offer me. It's so crazy. Why does every part of
these places have to be insane? Um, so then like, okay, it is clear, like we're there.
Everybody's itching to get out of here. And I'm like, I got to try this Meow Wolf thing out.
I must bring this back to, I must bring it back. A robust collide escape trip report to our
audience. Uh, and my wife says, okay, fine. We will, we will do the carousel that seems comfortable
with carousels. We can do it. All right. So great tip over. Uh, no, sure. Well, everything that
we've taught us so far has taught us that everything on the carousel will be fine. So
here we go. Uh, I go off and do the Meow Wolf ride. It is now open. I get on it and I do it.
I don't know that I have two minutes of material. Whoa, really? It's fine. It's fine. But it's like,
I don't, if anything, because we've talked about how it's cool that like, you know,
artists get to put their stamp on it and this wasn't just like cranked out in a corporate way,
like people physically made these robots that lean towards you and these cool like intersecting
invite, whatever. And all it does is make me feel bad. Like one of them might hear this
and I don't want to say that none of them did a bad job. It's just like, ultimately I think the
idea is fault. You could, you still just feel like it's this, it's a janky ghost blasters thing
and they painted cool colors on it. I like that it's like outrun. I like that it's those like
80s retro future grid hills. But even I don't, I made the show Moonbeam City and I'm still over.
That's not enough for me to, that's not going to win me over. All right. Yeah. I like Purple Grid,
but it's still like, I don't know, man. It's an interesting psychedelic, like
surreal, kind of not quite clear what it, I watched a few ride throughs and it's like,
yeah, no plot. It's more about vibes. I don't know. It's kind of a shooter ride,
but you're not really shooting. This is what you were saying. You shoot, but there's no score.
And I looked it up in the literature. They justify it as like, well, those are the cosmic
thrombulators and it's not about a weapon. It's like, okay, well you didn't convey any of that
in the experience itself. It just felt like the ride vehicles have guns. You want to keep the
guns or not? Let's keep the guns. And then there was nothing. I don't, I mean, it's better than,
I'm sure it's better than what was there before. I think you're going to get the Meow Wolf experience
much more so if you go to the actual things. I did not make it to Convergence Station,
so I don't know. It's probably, I don't know. I wish I was, again, I'm a little beaten down though.
Sure. You wouldn't pay $9 for ice cream. Yeah, yes. The vibes are not good, so I'm just not,
and it didn't do anything wrong, didn't do anything wrong, but I would say no one listening should
make a trip just to see the Meow Wolf, unless you are a just Meow Wolf absolute complete super fan.
Well, what you would pay to get in this park will get you into the Denver Meow Wolf installation,
and that's going to be much more. I texted you the first night you were there, and I was like,
did you know there's a full Meow Wolf there? I did, and I ultimately, I think I would have had to
split off from the fam to do it. I think dark spaces are going to freak my son out. So,
in that way that closer to your daughter's age, Mike, maybe more oblivious to things. Maybe not
scared because you don't know to be scared. He's a little bit north of four now, so he's sensitive
to things, and I'm saying all this because this factors into where this story is going next.
So, I complete this ride, and it's fine, but I've done it, and I'm like, I don't know, well,
I don't know if it's a lot to talk about for the show, really, but all right, I'll go through the
carousel, and we'll see what's up with them, and we'll start making our way out of here. Then I get
a phone call, and I'm like, well, this means that the heat is on. You're close to done,
we probably want to go. Instead, the phone call immediately has a tense error, a very tense error,
and the call is like, hi, we're fine, but you need to get to the gate right now. Something happened.
There is an air of urgency. This is not what I expected to be getting. Luckily, I'm not too far.
Okay, okay, I'll be right there. I get to the stroller return, and the stroller is being
returned as fast as possible. I can't get a story out of either of them because Aaron is shaken,
and my son is screaming, bloody murder. It is so bad that I'm like, I'm going to have to wait a
little bit to find out what even happened here, and Aaron says, really quick, if you want to know,
go look. You'll see the aftermath of it, and I saw the aftermath of it, and now what I'm going to do
is, I don't know, I can't recall this happening on the show. I think I have to issue a content
sensitivity warning. Oh, no. Oh, my God. It's not so crazy, but if you don't want to hear about
harm occurring to somebody, then maybe stop listening here for a little bit.
But you guys don't get to go anywhere. No, we're stuck in this room with you.
You're stuck. Now, I will get into, all right, content warning has been issued.
Um, so they are on the carousel, and things are going fine. It is a normal carousel ride
that is proceeding, and Aaron is just kind of looking off, and because she's looking in the
distance, she does not know what has caused the two jarringly loud thumps, like really, really loud,
to where, like, just from that sound, there's a problem. And her first thought is, like,
did this thing run over an animal? Did something get under the thing? She doesn't know,
and she starts putting the pieces together. And what it was, was that a woman fainted,
fell off the horse next to the one that my son was, yeah, she is on a carousel horse.
She fainted, fell off the horse that was right next to my son's horse. The second thump was her
hitting the ground. Oh, my God. The first thump was her hitting her head on my son's horse. Oh,
God. On the way down. She is now lying motionless under my son's horse. Oh, God. Gives me no
pleasure to tell this story, but I tell it because, boy, has the air been bad this whole time.
Imagine that you are not having a good time at a park in general, and then this happens,
the craziest thing I have ever witnessed. Aaron has to yell, stop the ride, call 911. She starts
that. He just doesn't even know what he's looking at. Nobody knows what they're looking at, and I
still don't know. I don't know where this situation was left. I don't know what. I know that
paramedics had arrived pretty quickly after this happened. This is the scene that I encounter.
Once I put all this together, it's like, go, go, go as fast as we can possibly get out of here,
and everybody is rattled. It's really crazy. I will not, I don't think this was the park's fault.
I can't really count this against the park. I can't put it on the list of Eulich Garden sucks
because of this, except maybe that then we were putting it all together after,
and my son said to Aaron, Mommy, buckle me in, and she went to do it, and there was no strap.
There's no straps on these horses. Again, Aaron brought up that you will sometimes go on carousels
that don't have straps. This is not so unheard of. Yeah, adults generally don't have to strap in.
Oh, that's the deal. And kids, there will be a strap for kids generally, I believe.
Okay. Yes, we were once on the carousel at California Adventure. I started to strap in,
and I feel like Mike went, you don't have to do that. That's cute. That is, yes, that is,
I do remember that now. It's part of it. I actually like it. It's like a good leather strap,
that's like putting on a nice old belt. Yeah, you put a little diaper on, whatever.
A little thong-ish diaper for your... Sure. It's absolutely the same as that. Putting a strap on
on a carousel is the same as putting on a diaper just for the hell of it. Yeah, I think so. Sometimes
you got it. You're a lie. We all remember. We have diaper memories. Why not put one on now?
Anyways, that is where we... So it's like, it doesn't need to have the buckles, and maybe they
aren't meant for adults. Might have done something. I don't know. I can't really blame the park for
this, but holy shit. Oh my God. That happened. And I really, I do not know where this situation
was left, but just a minute. So basically now, what started as three hours... Let's see if we
can fit our experience into three hours. We are at the 90-minute mark, and we are getting the fuck
out of here as fast as we can. Wow, this is all 90 minutes. That all happened in 90 minutes.
That's a lot of 90 minutes. Wow. Yeah, yeah. Even with a lion where I got stuck for a little while,
but there was no desire to stay longer, even before this happened. I don't want to go into...
I know that's just in a disturbing detail, and I take no pleasure in telling you, but what are the
odds? If that happened to you on the ride, you'd be freaked out. Let alone, it is his horse of all
the places. If we had... You know what? If they'd given Aaron the fucking bowl, if there hadn't been
a butcher to run around with the bowl, she would have arrived there later or at a different time,
and then maybe not been at the exact spot for a woman to hit the horse. This is so crazy. So
anyways, we are driving out and truly rattled, and now it's like, do we just go to the airport
insanely early? What else do we do? We just sit around the airport, and then on the way to the
airport, we realize, wait a minute, what did we do on the way from the airport previously?
Oh, wow. Again, he's upset, and she's back in the back seat with him holding his hand,
talking him through everything, and then it's been silent for five minutes, and then I'm like,
hey buddy, you want to go climb on the boats and the ATVs at Bass Pro Shops? Yeah! We pull up,
we go back, they run around on boats, we're romping on boats, we're having a wonderful time.
Smart. He's playing through the scenario that happened. We are acting it out. Oh no,
something happened to the lady. Oh good, the doctor is here, and the doctor is going to save
everything, and we're like, oh sure, probably, fingers crossed, hope so. But the point is,
after a really janky experience, Bass Pro Shops, which is brand new to me,
this is new this year, I've been newly high on this, we've just done the episode,
Bass Pro Shops, not only do I enjoy it in general, it was there for us during a true crisis,
it saved the day. I went back, did a little bit more shooting, felt newly confident from a great
shooting experience at Casa Bonita. Now I'm like, bless this organization, bless them and everything
they spend money on and that their founder spends money on. Another round of hats for everyone.
Everybody in the store, all the animals too, put them on top of the books,
put them on top of the squirrels, it'll be great. Whoa. So that's that, Bass Pro Shops saved the day,
unquestionably a vastly better themed experience to the city of Denver than Elitch Gardens,
which now faces the question of where do we relocate the park, what do we do with Elitch
Gardens, where does it move, and can I suggest, I don't know, maybe in hell? Maybe Elitch Gardens
can be rebuilt in the seventh circle of hell. You know, I just searched the name under news,
Google News, and the first story, Elitch Gardens won't move from downtown Denver this year,
so it's hiring 1,500 workers. Doesn't seem like they're all hired yet or they're not properly
allocated. Yes, yeah, yeah. Well, I hope that one of the things they're looking for is over 16
in that way. Just might be not to say that an under 16 person is not capable. I just know I saw
a park that was all 16 year olds assisting 12 year olds, and it sure seemed like bedlam to me.
So let's try to up the age there, and let's get through these last summers, and then you know what,
if Elitch Gardens, maybe it's not meant to be. Maybe it's a lot of trouble to rebuild a theme park,
you know? That's going to take a while. Couldn't that money go to anything else? How about put
that money into Casa Bonita? Expand it. Just let it take over the dentist next door. Let's double
the size of Casa Bonita, and maybe we let Elitch Gardens live in our memories. I know it'll live
in mine forever. Oh my God. I don't even know what to say. Yeah. Yeah, how about that? I'm sorry.
How bummed out is everybody? I'm pretty bummed out. That's a crazy one. I can feel my tea lowering
even as we talk about it. Well, that's because you're a sensitive person, and you heard about
a bad thing that happened, and you're empathetic, and you're not a raging tea holic of the past. You
can't turn it off. You can dial that tea down when you know that there's people in need.
That's true. Yeah, very true. I didn't think about how I can control my own tea. That might
be a good Tony Robbins style thing. You could go on a speaking tour where you teach young men,
Jordan Peterson style, to control your tea. You actually have power over your own tea. You don't
know that. I don't know if I want to out the person who went to see Jordan Peterson at the Forum.
Seems like a barn burner of a show. Seems like, boy, a hell of a time. Forum really came back when
Prince did a bunch of nights, and that really lit it up. It sounds like Jordan Peterson took it to
the next level. Yeah, you will believe a man can cry when he's just going through the Disney Plus
app and just every new- Cursing out different characters by name. National Geographic,
it's now partially owned by Disney. I know that was one of his gripes, but okay. Could be.
Fine publication ruined by the owners of the Acolyte. Yeah, well, anyways, that's that.
Dylan, I should have listened harder. Yeah, he warned you. He really tried, not even knowing.
The fact that multiple people tried to warn me, not even knowing. It's almost like they didn't.
Maybe somebody didn't. And they were like, it'll creep them out if I said that I saw a vision
of an event happening. That's too creepy for me, a listener, to say that I foretold this. Like
I'm Adam Webb, a carousel crisis, but I'm not going to leave that out of the email. I'm just
going to say, like, I think the price is a little high. But anyway, thanks for trying to help.
And thanks to you guys for hearing out these multiple trip reports. Ultimately, I had fun.
Ultimately, we all survived podcasts, The Ride, The Second Gate. If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month and our
regular episodes ad free. And you vote on those episodes and what we're supposed to do in them.
We are banning voting us into going back to Elitch Gardens. This will never be put in a poll.
That's yeah, we can vote on that, remember, because we can amend different club three rules.
So yeah, we'll vote on that off, Mike. Yeah, yeah, but don't waste your time. Don't throw it in there.