Five, four, three, two, one.
City of duckbills, city of web feet, city of quacking, and big old feathery seats.
We all need it, can't live without it.
Quacky Duck City, oh yeah.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me is always Jason Sheridan.
That was so nice.
Thank you so much.
Scott Garner is here as well.
That was really nice.
What a sweet, lovely song.
Who wrote that song?
It's an original song.
You just made up that song?
Yeah.
I made up the melody and I wrote the words.
Wow.
Okay.
That's great.
I would hate to think that anybody unsavory wrote something so savory.
That's an original song.
Yeah.
Wow.
Do you mean like Big Pete?
What?
An unsavory character like Pete?
Oh.
Oh, you mean the cat Pete?
You call him Big Pete?
I've heard him called Big Pete.
I think he's called Big Pete once in a while.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know he shows up in this and yet my mind did not go.
What I fleshed too is that that is a hip hop or R&B artist who I am not familiar with.
Big Pete.
I don't know about Big Pete.
What did he do that was so bad?
Made a mouse drive a steamboat in a way that he didn't want to do?
Yeah.
He dumped some pudding on a character one time probably.
Was he a slightly more abrasive father than his dog neighbor?
Yeah.
He's a bad guy though.
Big Pete.
So yeah.
We won't talk about him.
But anyway, that song, yeah, well, if anyone wants to use that song, yeah, just credit
it to me.
Yeah.
I wrote it and the melody.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Lovely.
So today, you know, I brought this up a couple of weeks ago, this topic, and I really before
I say it, I just don't want it.
I don't want this to be a jealousy episode.
I don't want this just to be me complaining today, but I was in the cards, but jealousy.
Well, I'm jealous of that.
We always talk about the Tokyo parks and we're always talking about how you're jealous of
the Japanese.
Yes.
So I'm just going to get out of the way.
This is so fun to me.
It's Donald's Quacky Duck City.
And I'm so jealous of the people who go to Tokyo Disney regularly because they get to
experience this.
And I just went to Disneyland.
They have Pixar Fest there, which is fine.
It's fine.
What happens at Pixar Fest?
Well, there's an area over by that theater where they did Mickey and the Magical Map
where they have like some characters and there's a little dance party and they have some like
they have I'm trying to think they have a parade at California and they have a parade
and they have special food items that maybe are bad.
I've seen people say that they're not very good.
The unique food items this year at Disneyland.
Believe it or not, something they made for a limited time is not so good food wise.
Looks good.
Impress photos, but does not taste good to the regular folks who go.
Yes.
Believe it or not.
So and there's like a there's like kind of a weird statue in the middle of the Esplanade
that's like a Pixar, like a tribute to Pixar.
And they got there's a lot of stuff.
I'm not saying there's not stuff and I'm not saying it's not fun, but is it as good
as what Tokyo is doing, which is something called Donald's Quacky Duck City, which transforms
Tokyo Disneyland into Quacky Duck City?
I believe it's not.
That's my premise for this episode.
It's Donald getting his flowers, getting his credit, getting his dream.
It's part of a series called Palo Palooza.
It sure is, Jason Palo Palooza, which I actually didn't even realize until recently that it's
a series of events highlighting the different characters, the big five or six.
I'm not sure how many they're going to do.
Surely not Mickey.
He's had plenty of lauding.
We're talking about his pals.
Yes, he's taking a back seat.
He wore like a polka dot outfit for the first Palo Palooza, Minnie's Thunderland.
Yes.
So that I didn't even realize was part of this.
Minnie had her own event, which now I feel bad because I'm now just so excited about
Donald's Quacky Duck City, but I should have been excited about Minnie's Thunderland.
Pretty sexist, I'd say, of all of us that we did not properly highlight Minnie's Thunderland.
I agree with you.
I feel like-
The male gaze, huh?
Well, yeah.
Wait, no.
The male gaze is like-
No, the male gaze is not technically-
No, I mean the kind of male gaze where we gazed over it, where we gazed so far to our
duck boy that we gazed past the woman.
Right.
We saw that feathery seat and we gazed right at it and just totally missed that Minnie
was there.
Yeah.
When we say male gaze, we mean at a duck seat.
I feel like they're going a lot harder for Quacky Duck City.
It feels like it, yes.
I agree.
It feels like they're going harder for Quacky Duck City, but Minnie had a lot of stuff and
she has her own original song as well, so we have to talk a little bit about it as well,
but I apologize to Minnie.
I was not aware of your Thunderland.
Oh, you're going to have a fight when she gets home.
Oh, in my where I live with her?
Well, yeah, you have a secret family.
Oh, yeah.
I have a secret family with Minnie Mouse.
You have a secret family with Minnie Mouse.
Mike asked us not to talk about that on the show, the fact that he's been quietly, discreetly
seeing Minnie Mouse officially when I have finally made it official.
And then I have kids with her like that Fox TV show that lasted like two or three episodes,
like 15 years ago.
I don't want to say this, but look, I really I think that your human daughter is beautiful,
but that son you had with Minnie, I'm sorry.
It's just weird to only have the one big mouse ear and then a much smaller human one.
I'm still getting used to it.
And again, this is just like, you know, it's a human centric view of things.
It's a different standard of beauty, because by my standard of beauty, your son is a freak.
But I'll get through.
I'm sure that in three years time, I'll be saying the opposite.
Well, it's weird that it went half and half like that, half one side, half the other.
That's generally not what happens when you mix genetics.
But I guess it's obviously it's possible.
You never know.
Yeah.
On territory, you know, that you're brave enough.
I've never fucked a sheep, so I don't know what that would lead to.
I don't know what it would either.
But one day maybe we'll find out.
Well, little little little we call them Mickey, which is weird.
That's weird choice, I guess.
It's a real power move.
It's really manipulative.
Now that we're revealing that this has actually happened here, a kid, OK, what's what's his
name?
Really?
I mean, I'm I'm flattered, but I'm weirded out to another room.
And you just hear crashing, crashing, punching the wall.
Mickey Walton with one of their shirts that says, I'm not the stepfather.
I'm just a father who stepped up.
Would you not want me as the dad?
I'm the richest being on earth.
Yeah.
I'm the richest animal in the history of America.
You want to cut me out for some podcaster?
Oh, Patriot.
Very good.
Yeah.
How about I'm a fucking trillionaire?
How about that?
Number two is that dog from the artist and he's passed away.
So it's only not even in the same bracket.
Whatever the dog's name was, I don't remember.
Yeah.
So anyway, yeah.
So that's I have a lot of explaining to do to Minnie, but Minnie had her own
Funderland where they celebrate it.
So this is great.
They celebrate all the other characters.
And I don't know, maybe maybe I'm crazy or maybe I'm just nostalgic for like
Mickey's birthday land.
But I like it when there was an event that felt kind of specific to Disneyland,
like we're only going to be able to do this at Disneyland or Disney World this
year, this summer.
And we're going and it felt specific.
Mickey's having a birthday.
All right.
Well, we got to go down to Disney World to check this out.
We have to see what's going to happen.
Do you think you're did your family go specifically to see Mickey's birthday
occur?
I think they decided the year.
And then when I looked and saw what was happening, I said, well, we got to see
this, we got to see what Mickey's up to.
It's his birthday.
So no, I don't think they were particularly moved.
They were happy to see it.
They were happy to ignore it.
Mickey acknowledged it, whatever the cake antics were at that show.
But to me, this don't you think Jason, Jason, come on, don't you think this
sounds better than a Pixar fest or a Seasons of the Force?
I'm not throwing that.
I mean, like, well, this is another OK, I should have said that before.
Seasons of the Force is their Star Wars event.
What does that mean?
Yeah, you know what I mean?
Like, it's not like, oh, Chewie's like Hootenanny or something.
If they had like Chewie was having a party and you got to go down to Disneyland
to check it out, doesn't that sound more fun celebrating the Star Wars characters
birthdays? Absolutely. Right.
Yes. It's Babu Frick's birthday.
It's Babu Frick's birthday all summer.
And you have to come and celebrate with him.
You're all going. You're buying the highest annual pass you can.
Frick Fest. You're getting the best.
You're paying 1800 bucks or whatever for the annual pass.
So you can go all summer.
Get your Frick on. Yeah. Frick Fest.
Yes. Better than like Seasons of the Force, where like we're very reverent
to the force and the wills and the midichlorians and stuff like.
No way. We want to blow.
I would also argue that there's no way that they are reverent to the will.
I know. I know. Seasons of the Force.
Some people there are, though.
Sure. Attendees. But it's not an official.
It's not a workshop where you go learn the wills work.
You're right. If it was will, if they were celebrating the wills,
also, we would be down there almost every day.
Big Willy style. Big Willy.
Be a name for that. Yes.
But the question was posed to Jason.
This is this again.
I think this is another one of those, Mike, where you're you want someone
to be arguing. Yeah, that's true.
And I don't think Jason Sheridan is the person who's going to argue.
No, I prefer Pixar Fest.
Keep Quacky Duck City in your pocket. Right.
You know, what I what we like, Jane and I liked about
the Pixar Fest stuff was they had people
playing all the girls from Turning Red and they had the boy band.
Well, that's great. I'm a big Turning Red fan.
And you can meet May and her mom.
But I don't know if it's enough, you know.
Well, it's just there's too much.
It's too generalized is what I'm saying.
If it was just like turning red, like I like the specificity of now,
if it was all the Pixar characters and they all suddenly had red hair
or panda ears.
Now we're talking.
If you start mixing up the characters, you know what?
They do have that.
They have like cars dressed as Woody and Buzz.
So they do. We're getting there.
We're getting there.
Again, there's fun stuff, but shows.
But how else do you? Yeah, that's a way.
If there's any feeling of like turning red didn't work
and we don't like these personal movies, we're not doing it.
Oh, God, I don't get me started.
Oh, boy.
Like, you know, well, maybe you didn't give it the full college try.
Maybe it may be if you said turning red is part of the family.
We're going to own it and be proud of it.
And all the characters are going to have red hair in the parks.
Now and now we've all been educated that turning red is in the canon
and we have to pay attention to it instead of this way
that they're releasing things, which is like, yeah, we put a movie out.
I don't know. Maybe you'll maybe like it.
Maybe you won't buy everybody like, yeah, the Disney people,
like the marketing people, like shield their eyes as they write
at the premiere, they're covering their faces.
They have done it in the past where they they are doing like more fun stuff.
Like the
you could buy cars, toys dressed like Star Wars characters
or the Muppets dressed like Star Wars characters.
That's done. Yeah, that was done.
Yeah, yeah. No more fun, of course, than the hyperspace hoopla.
Oh, I mean, so that's what everyone agrees.
And not just two people in this room.
What everybody agrees is one of the pinnacles of I've seen
a couple of people recently talking about that hoopla very wistfully online.
I had people I don't know. Yeah.
People that I didn't prompt a couple of people.
A well, I guess it is a phenomenon of all phenomena.
The sample size is representative of a bigger sample somewhere, I think.
But I'm just saying three people equals three thousand people.
That's what I'm saying.
So, yeah, I don't I don't think any of that stuff is coming back anytime soon.
Seasons of the Force is too serious.
It's too serious. We need more fun.
We need more fun.
Well, tell us about the fun before we get mad at the not fun.
I know I came in hot today.
I'm sorry.
So there's a fun thing.
OK, now, what would the fun thing remind?
We're getting that out of the way.
That's why I gave the qualifier.
I was going to get it out of the way.
We're cooling the room before we cool the room before you heat it up with fun.
Fun, fun, friction creates heat.
And that's what we're going to do now.
Fun friction is something that would happen at Babu Frick Fest. Right.
You get your freak on, have some fun friction.
Oh, man. Imagine they had like a little Babu Frick, like breakdancing
and like a circle, like during like a happy like a remix of Happy Birthday
played by like size noodles and Max Rebo.
We're we're going we're going Babu Frick work in the workshop.
He does. John Williams, isn't that?
Isn't he right? John Williams cameo.
So that would be John Williams, a bartender.
Yeah, I thought he was like a guy with like he's got like, you know,
the multiple lenses, like a guy who's going to like work with microscopic toys.
I don't think I knew this. He's in it. Yeah, yeah.
They finally. Yes.
Well, among the better things in Rise of Skywalker is that like a guy
and a cloak turns around and you're like, oh, it's John Williams, I think.
But they didn't, you know, if then he like Geppetto style,
made all the gadgets wherever they are.
I'll perform a big song to say Happy Birthday, Babu.
Oh, God. Of course.
Are you finding what he was?
This is John Williams' bartender.
He was a bartender, really.
So I think maybe he just I thought he was like a mechanic.
I thought he like slid out from under a space car.
Well, he has like I know what you're saying,
because he's in the workshop and he's got like a little thing over his eye.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah, right.
That made me this as Barton.
So I don't know. Yeah, no, no, no.
That's that's probably right.
Kajimi is the plan.
I thought he was all like smeared up, all tarred up, like even working with with oils.
Yeah, he's an older fellow.
So I don't want him on the ground like that, because it might be hard.
It might get up. Yeah, yeah.
I know. I'm glad they didn't stage it that way.
Might have been a droid bartender, maybe making oil based drinks.
Yeah, that's true.
So, well, yeah, get him in there, get him in there.
Walk around, face characters of John Williams, unnamed Barty.
There's no way he's unnamed, right?
They name everybody in Star Wars.
I don't see his name.
I'll figure it out and I'll shout it out while we talk Quirky Duck City.
OK, so well, let's let's start.
I just so so they have like an original song, they have original parade,
and they're sort of a similar template for like I think the parade is basically
the same floats and then they just put some new stuff on them for each character.
So I assume. And this, by the way, just to say, Quirky Duck City
is there is a parade that's like the center of it,
but then it's this park wide celebration. Yeah.
And it also includes special menu items and merch and just decor
all around, especially the outside, the castle and World Bazaar,
which is their mainstay in the whole.
It's Golden Idol of Donald Duck and World Bazaar.
Wow. Golden Idol to worship their Main Street. Yes.
And the and the and the flowers outside the park is fully Donald's face.
Yes, which is fun.
And they did that with many as well.
I really like their do you call that?
That's I don't know if that's the Esplanade, whatever.
You know, the like entrance patio.
Yeah. Whatever is very unique.
And it doesn't look like the other parks.
It's not like because you don't have a train going around.
So it's just kind of a different layout.
And they send a lot of characters out. Right.
You're getting a lot of activity before you're even at the Main Street
equivalent or even seeing the castle. Yes.
I don't know if I ever shouted that out, but I really like whatever
you call that entrance plaza in Tokyo, Disneyland, I think is great.
And I really like it that they got Mickey out of there for a minute
and did a big Donald Topi area. Yeah. Great.
There's a lot of care.
Like it feels like almost like mingling, like you're at like a party or something
and you're being greeted by the people who live there.
It's kind of like, yeah, like casual drinks refresh.
It's like the thing between the wedding ceremony and the wedding party. Right.
Does everybody mingle cocktail hour? Right.
To know who you'll be hanging out with at your table.
And in Disneyland and over here, they have it
like when you walk into Main Street,
usually they do have a bunch of characters with lines and stuff.
So they kind of have it here, but it's on Main Street and it's still a little busier.
This one feels more casual in Tokyo. Mm hmm.
Mm hmm. More space to the Tokyo.
I was watching the Tokyo Disney Explorer.
That's his channel, Jason.
Yeah, Chris. Yeah.
Tokyo Disney. So a lot of the stuff I was watching and he's
he's got some good videos talking about.
He also tries all menu items.
Yes. Yeah.
Yeah, there is a TDR Explorer write ups about the thing.
And then just the TDR Explorer.
Excuse me. I said, yeah. Yeah.
And then Attractions magazine is a pretty good write up about it, too.
And Omar Trez is the name of Tress Trace.
Spelled like the number Trace is John Williams.
And yes, he does have a name. Oh, wow. What is it?
Omar Omar Tress.
Omar Tress. Wow.
I've also just learned from this full IMDb of episode nine that
radio head producer Nigel Godrich is the voice of a droid,
as is George Harrison's son, Danny Harrison.
Really? Yeah, apparently.
Then they don't say which or maybe it's just like a background.
Oh, it's FNT, FN2802 and FN0878.
I should have known they name everything.
So John. So, yeah, Omar Tress.
OK, Omar Tress. Wow. Yeah.
My top 10 Star Wars characters for me.
Omar Tress, the bartender
who can act a little bit, but who can conduct really good.
Well, that's center.
He should team up with Senator Grubbleebs.
Yeah, something tells me they'd get along.
Something tells me they might have collaborated in some other form.
Yeah. So let me read here.
This is the press release for Donald's Quacky Duck City.
And it takes place, you know, if you're if you're going to Tokyo Disney,
you still can do this.
It's it's through the 30th of June. It started April 9th.
This event series is all about having a blast with your pals
in the park in the park in a party like Palooza environment.
Following the first installment, featuring Minnie Mouse,
the second event, Donald's Quacky Duck City stars Donald Duck.
Guests can enter the extraordinary world of Duck City,
Donald's ideal world where he reigns as the ultimate superstar.
With this event, guests can enjoy the world of Donald's
imagination as the park undergoes a transformation
tailored to fulfill Donald's wildest dreams.
OK, now I love this.
I love what you have just read.
I love that it's Palooza like, but not necessarily full Palooza.
Full Palooza measures your expectations.
But also that might be accurate that it's only Palooza like
because this notion of like we are entering the ultimate Donald verse
in which he reigns supreme and all bow to him.
You get in there, I watch some video, unless I'm missing some things.
It's kind of like this four statues of Donald.
I don't know that the immersion of Quacky Duck City is so full and complete.
We are not like, I don't know.
There's not like a like a big, scary throne
that's part his face and the skulls of his enemies,
those being goofy and Pluto. Right.
Well, if you were eating the fettuccine and you were looking at like
the wall of merchandise, the immersion might be more.
If you at peak Quacky Duck City, you would feel more immersed.
Yeah, you'd feel more immersed.
I really like this drawing that I think was along with the press release.
Donald is wearing a crown.
Everyone else is wearing outfits inspired by Donald's sailor suit.
And then Pete is in the corner, kind of put out as usual.
He's upset. Good. You're not invited.
But Mickey seems like he's having fun with his friends.
Like he and he's wearing a Donald suit.
Like he's humble, you know.
Yeah, he could give the spotlight to someone else is the spotlight.
It's a little bit of a break for him.
Fine. Yeah. Hundred years of me.
We could do three months of Donald.
Well, what do you mean?
It's going to be a year of all the friends celebrate.
What do you mean? What do you mean a year?
What did I sign off on?
You know, I don't read that shit I sign.
I thought this was just three months and then it was back to me.
I was already mad enough about the things in America.
Seasons of the Force and Peck's Office.
Yeah. Where am I fitting into Seasons of the Force?
Who cares?
Giving Pluto a thing.
Pluto. Look, I love he's my dog.
I love him. He's my pal.
He can't do shit.
He sleeps in poops.
You're going to get a parade out of that.
Like to see you try.
Yeah. Make a golden statue out of one of his shits.
That people come from miles to see it.
Idiot can't even talk.
He's constantly outsmarted by Chip and Dale.
Chip and Dale are getting a month to fuck.
God damn it.
Oh, good. Yeah, big deal.
They're they outsmarted dog.
I'm very impressed.
There is so the I think the thing is you're referring to,
there is one like big, like a decent sized statue that Jason references,
golden idol of Donald in the middle.
But then there are other like they're like, I guess
they're not poster.
There's there's other things in that sort of area that are like trophies,
essentially, like posters of trophies or pictures of trophies
that Donald has won, declaring him the best chef or the strongest.
Best chef is really funny.
Chef. Yes. What is it?
What is the what back?
So these are Donald's deepest desires to be thought of as the best
chef is the strongest.
There's a picture of Donald's dressed as like a disco singer
or a dancer on the outside.
So I assume he wants to also be thought of as the best dancer.
And he's been awarded in this sort of weird scenario
where we're now giving into all of his deepest desires.
And it's more about we're all getting together to help our friend, I guess,
or to really boost our friend up.
But if we're going to really all right, like having having to be surrounded
by totems of his achievements is something.
But I kind of want what was described in that blurb that you read.
Mike was very, you know, that felt almost we're getting into
like North Korea territory.
And I think if you want to like really show your might
and that you're in charge, what do you do? Missile parade.
You got to do a missile parade.
So what I would like to see as much as I like the parade,
I'd also like to see missiles painted in Donald Duck's sailor suit patterns
go by just to show like, hey, you know, you know, Donald's got a temper.
If he if he decides to fire, if he gets mad and does one of his
like these things could go off and then boom, no more fantasy.
So there would be a trophy that says like best military strong man or something.
And Donald is dressed in like a general's outfit.
Yeah, yeah, yes. Yeah. Strongest military might. Right.
Yeah. I mean, I'm sure he has other fantasies
that weren't fulfilled by Quacky Duck City. Mm hmm.
He's starting.
We're starting with the PG fantasy. Right.
And then we'll get a little.
Yeah. Best like vanquisher of enemies.
Best. Yeah, like Mickey killer or something.
And it's like he's standing over Mickey and reigning supreme in Disneyland.
They're not going to say the darker stuff, I don't think.
Best. Well, you know, decapitator from Mr.
Duck Steps Out, one of my favorite shorts where he's basically just trying to get laid.
And he's getting messed up by the nephews.
So I guess like you'd have a trophy like best sex have her, I guess, potentially.
Sure. Best. Yeah.
These are all stuff I'm saying they're not doing.
This is all in the deep recesses of his duck brain.
Yeah. Yeah. So they maybe if there's a Quacky Duck City, too,
but that's best to ratter out of dumb nephews.
Right. As he like puts gets them in juvie.
Yeah.
These are longer titles for trophies,
but I think you could fit him on a couple of lines.
I'm going to make sure. I'm going to make sure.
I was starting to do Mickey and then I tried to switch to Donald.
Well, I've been trying to put off doing my Donald voice this whole time.
God, that's Stitch.
It all sounds so good.
It's just not good voice you choose from.
Yeah, which way? Good.
I'm going to get uncle Scrooge to change his will.
What did he say?
He said he's going to get uncle Scrooge to change his will.
Oh, that's good. Yeah.
Just during you sound like the I feel like that's what the villains
and Ernest scared, stupid sound like. Yeah.
OK, Scrooge.
But Scott, your point, yes.
OK, they didn't transform the castle necessarily.
That's something I obviously would prefer if he had the castle
look like a little sailor suit or something.
They're still dealing with the fallout of Stitch covering it.
And, oh, did it do that in Tokyo?
No, no, I just mean in Florida.
They're still you're saying that that people still grousing about that through.
Well, castle disrespect.
Right, because we talked about Castle Cake and stuff.
And that wasn't disrespect.
That was sanctioned.
But like maybe a takeover, maybe a character.
Yeah. We don't know how we feel because they haven't.
Yeah. Have they done anything like that since?
I guess the Stitch thing is the last time when they like
fucked with the castle.
I think besides like just adding more and more.
Yeah, they change the colors and like for the 60th.
They put that big Lone Ranger mask on it.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
Yeah, that was weird.
Changed it to like kind of like a richer blue during the diamond.
Of course, the diamond celebration.
Or Scott remembers the diamonds.
Oh, 60th. Yeah, of course, Jason and I know 70th is coming.
What did we call that? What's the name of that?
What's the I don't know.
What's the 70th anniversary called the 70th anniversary?
I think this Disneyland 70th anniversary will be called disappointing.
Oh, we got what we could afford.
Is it next? When is it?
What year is it next year? Wow.
Oh, yeah. Nothing news opening for that.
No, they don't have time for.
Yeah, got jack shit for that.
Oh, round. Well, we did.
Tiana member. Oh, yeah, that's 13 months ago.
So that's what we did.
That's true. Aren't you happy with that?
We did it. And it was for.
Oh, I know it was for the 70th.
Yeah, no, we're going to know it.
It was all that. So we're getting a jump on the 70th.
Yeah. OK. Wow.
I can't I didn't even think about it being 70 next year.
Wow. We're going to do a lot of content for the 70th celebration.
Are we? Well, it's a big deal.
70th anniversary, Jason, have you found the name of it yet?
I'm looking up what you give.
Oh, what you give for?
Like, well, because that's what diamond.
Oh, is that what diamond means?
You give it. I think on the 60th anniversary.
OK. Traditional gift for the 70th anniversary.
Platinum. Oh, the platinum celebration.
Platinum celebration. That's pretty good.
That is cool.
The sound of it seems like an expensive material, though.
I don't know how many platinum decorations they're going to make.
I don't know. But yeah, so so they haven't.
I guess I guess my point was they haven't touched the castle.
Really, in a severe way in a while.
And I severe sound here.
Yeah, let's touch the castle in a severe way.
I want that sounds like carving it up.
I want that cake castle back.
I really, really do.
I want a cake castle again.
I don't see why not.
Yeah, I because I don't think they do anything that interesting.
Well, look, when they cover it in platinum, that horribly reflects
in the eyes of sunlight.
Yeah, it'll look like the houses in the curse.
And we'll have to go see it.
Everybody will flock for miles to see it.
OK, so in Quacky Duck City, though, they do have a lot of little stuff.
It's not big stuff. It's little stuff.
It's garbage cans.
It's it's a garbage can that shows Donald's front side and his seat.
So have you seen? Yeah.
So that's just cute little stuff.
There's topiaries of Donald.
They're sort of weird.
And we just talked about this with Mickey Mania.
There's there's decorations that look kind of like weird abstractions
of Donald deconstructed, right?
Just just like a white sphere and a duck bill hanging.
OK, as a as a fan of Mickey Mania, I like that we're heading
into this territory at all. Yes.
So we do have stuff like that.
I have some photos here.
I should have loaded them better.
But so it's a lot.
It's a lot more like little stuff.
It's like you're going to go and you're going to eat something.
And on the tray is a cartoon of Donald dressed as a chef.
And we're also we've got this aesthetic that's consistent to all of it.
That's very comic book.
Yes, which style and that kind and that that sort of printing with the party.
Yeah, which I'm sure is part of why I like it.
I do really obviously like that style.
But yeah, it just seems like I mean, Tokyo in general,
like the packages at the different like quick service food are different.
You do get more like detailed stuff.
So like this time they have like a specific Donald packaging
for your like chicken sandwich that you're getting at different places.
Well, at some places like you got a souvenir place, Matt, or a souvenir
coaster, yes, you are like pasta that look it's got some little stuff on top
that looks like his little seat. Right.
Yes. Well, look, the seat factors heavily into the food.
There are most things have like a Donald seat and like sticking out of your ice
cream, your dinner, your floats.
There's a lot of seat stuff happening in the food over there.
And there have been I had some sort of a seat like cone
when I was there a few years ago, where it's like sort of the ice cream is
is Donald seat.
And then there's a couple of little like cookies that look like his feet.
So it looks like he's upside down.
Like you put him in a trash can or you put him in the cone.
And now you're taking a big bite out of his seat.
And how do you do you like eating Donald's seat, Mike?
I did. The ice cream was really good.
And it's a fun little thing because you're eating his little feet
and then his seat.
I did like it. Yeah. Eat and see.
We have it. Look, we haven't done a lot of seat talks.
Got banned seat. I was got banned seat talk a couple of years ago.
I really shouldn't reveal.
I don't know if there was a bang.
Hang on. I think we're we're exaggerating that.
Perhaps a bit. There was no ban.
There was no ban.
Maybe an encouragement to take the temperature down on the seat.
I mean, people were spraying us with those, you know, spray bottles
you get for a cat and go, hey, that's a no, no word.
Yeah. Well, it just it started to feel like our following online audience,
like that there were, you know, like a new episode getting posted
would get one comment and then like seats would
there be some seat threads like, yeah, 75.
Everybody was so seat crazy.
I thought maybe we just needed to like, yeah, just let's just cool.
Just to take a break and then we'll be able to really appreciate seats more.
Right. So it's time for seats again, which I guess is now is today.
Today is the time for seats again.
OK, it's you know what it feels like is happy 90th anniversary
to our seat runner on the show.
That's that's how long it feels to me.
It does. Soon we're going to be celebrating
one hundred twenty five years of saying King Features Syndicate.
The platinum anniversary, the platinum anniversary of this podcast runner.
So, yeah, so so I was looking, especially that TDR Explorer.
I was looking because he had tried all this different stuff.
And, you know, you get like a little ice cream Sunday
and it looks like Donald's feet are sticking out.
I should have zoomed in. There's a lot of the whole seat thing
came out of Mickey's Philhar Magic and the moment where Donald propels
from the screen into the back of the theater and his big seat
and his kicking legs are like stuck in somewhere very, very much like
Winnie the Pooh in that famous short.
And I guess it's something that happens to Donald a lot is some catastrophe
like firing him into something.
And that's I feel that I do like that about these desserts,
that it feels like the dessert is a tableau of some kind of Donald disaster.
As if he was reaching for something and then fell face
first into a pudding or into a carbonara pasta.
Like I like that we are seeing like the immediate aftermath
of some kind of disaster. Yes, I like that a lot, too.
Sometimes it gets a little grim, because like if you let your drink
go a little too long, everything starts to get real melty.
Yeah, it's kind of not there.
So, yeah, you start to think it's like it's like he fell
into a vat of acid. Yeah, so is no is no more, Donald.
This drink here, this is a picture of what I assume
we're supposed to be as two feet and a seat.
But man, they have melted.
And it looks like Donald just got put in the dip.
Yeah, Roger Rabbit.
Well, you were you were showing kind of a later stage of the carbonara pasta,
which is like maybe the most primary savory depiction of Donald's seat.
And which is so.
So, yeah, duck dive pasta, duck dive pasta.
That is that. Yeah, that was that on that picture as well.
Where it's in that case, it's an egg.
And then like little little pieces of cheese that are the feet.
And then you're meant to mix all that up.
You're meant to like crack into his ass and mix up the innards.
So blue cheese or not blue colored cheese.
I think spring is confusing, not blue, not blue.
But blue colored.
Yeah. But what is that in this?
What I'm showing right now?
That's like a trail run.
What is that? Is that a discharge coming out of his seat?
What is the blue meant to be?
Well, it all comes out the cloaca.
If what? What was that?
I said it all comes out the cloaca.
The voices are getting worse and worse.
I still have an attempt.
Like what, how, how, how bad of multiple car accidents occurred
to whatever character this is to her?
This is somebody who was in multiple car accidents
and had the like throat taken out due to smoking.
Well, it's Mickey's.
It's Mike's mutant son.
Oh, that's what Mickey sounds like.
That's what he sounds like.
That's what young Mickey sounds like.
You're right. Yeah, I get me.
Something's wrong with my cloaca.
What are you saying? What is the?
Why does the mouse have a cloaca?
Like birds, birds have a cloaca.
What is a cloaca?
It's like where like poop and pee come out for birds.
But we don't have cloacas.
We do not have cloacas. No. Interesting.
How do you know that?
Just from just from nature, from being smarter than nature documentaries,
I feel like.
Did they? Does a bird have seen a diagram of one on a frog?
All right.
Do birds have vas deference?
Oh, I don't know. I can't speak to that.
OK, listener, don't Google image along with this.
I'm looking at some terrible things.
Oh, God, I don't want to see that.
Jason has brought cloacas into the conversation.
And maybe they're being disturbed.
Maybe that will replace seats from here on out with the little cloaca.
Donald's little cloaca.
Oh, you managed to.
All right, if this is all a
this is all an effort to give me a like seat talk.
This might be like when you put stuff in the movie that the MPAA
is going to rule out just to soften it.
That's right.
I guess you brought me back around to preferring seats.
I don't know.
Look, if the listeners pick up on it and run with it, that's not.
That's not our fault.
Social media is all about cloacas now.
What happened?
What have we harbored here?
Yeah, you're talking about the pasta, Scott.
Did you see the rice?
Did you see Donald's special set omelet rice with meat patty?
Is this where this is like a big this is like a hamburger patty?
Yes, it looks it's very like sloppy.
It's a very sloppy.
This is at Grandma Sarah's restaurant,
which is the restaurant next to their Splash Mountain.
And this is I will I think I like it,
but this is the most horrifying meal you can get at the Quacky Duck City.
It is just disgusting looking.
And then on top is a little egg with Donald's like two pieces of cheese
that are Donald's feet.
And then it just looks like a messy pile of like vomit with rice on the bottom.
I think there's egg and then a big like hamburger patty really does not look good to me.
I could see it tasting good, but it certainly doesn't look good
because the food in general is better at Tokyo.
But this one looks like a messy.
This looks like Donald was in some awful accident.
Yeah, it's deconstructed Donald.
Yeah, this looks like he was shot in somewhere and he exploded
in just a bunch of like brown blood.
Like like all that's left is his bottom half and his feet.
And he just is a mess on the ground.
This is if you're at the if you're at the funeral and that's what's inside the coffin.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe we close it. Maybe we got to close it. Right.
Donald is best chef, best actor, best exploder.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
And this is yeah, you cut into a seat here and the egg,
the inside of the egg runs out into the already messy dish.
Well, I know omelet.
I think you you basically it's an omelet on top of rice.
Sometimes I've seen it done
where you cut open the omelet and kind of folds out.
But this seems like a different execution.
It seems like Jason, are you interested in eating this?
Oh, give it a shot. Sure. Yeah.
I'll tell you the food that I don't want.
At one of the table service, I believe there are some duck dishes.
And I think that's too morbid for me to eat.
Donald eating to eat, celebrate during the Donald's best duck.
Yeah. And I love duck.
You're a duck guy. I'm a duck guy.
I don't know that I've ever had.
Really? It's like a dark, like really greasy or dark meat chicken
or turkey meat guy. Oh, that's interesting.
You wouldn't like to.
Yeah. If I go to Zankou chicken, I'm usually clicking that at a dollar.
And then you only get white meat.
Oh, I make it all dark. Really? Yes.
I didn't know that about you.
Yeah. Interesting.
Just because it's like a it's more it's richer, it's like fattier.
Yeah, yeah. A little fattier.
And Jason's been trying to eat fattier this year.
So does. Yes.
More dark meat. Yes.
More dark meat. More sodas.
Doctors orders more duck juice.
We're just drinking a sip.
I'm in every recording.
I'm drinking a big like bottle of duck juice.
You hear a slurp know that that's pure duck juice.
Got the double walls.
It stays cold. The double walled bottle.
I guess you want it hot unless you're doing it caffeinated.
Is a. Oh, yeah.
Too acidic. It's hot.
Is Logan Paul released a new duck flavored prime energy drink?
That might be. I don't know.
Yeah. Would you try?
Um, I I've tried some prime.
I've tried. Oh, you've tried.
I haven't tried. Have I tried prime?
I tried like the rocket pop flavor prime.
I've seen that.
It's delicious. It's like chemicals.
Why are you trying?
You're trying Logan's Logan Paul's energy drink.
He is. He is.
I don't think I tried it because I bought it.
Somebody maybe offered it to me or maybe I haven't tried it.
I miss or maybe I'm remembering mundane situation.
Maybe I've tried it because it was offered to me or Jason brought me a prime.
That's what it was. Oh, I bought you some.
Bought me a. I bought you some prime and some Zoa.
And now because of what's happened recently on the show where there's been
a couple of times where you have said that you only wanted to buy one,
but you were forced to buy a few.
I'm wondering maybe if you were forced to buy multiple primes that those
I think I picked up at a liquor store where, like, they just have individual.
I'm wondering if every gift you have ever given me was just because they
force you to buy more than one.
This is me. I have clocked that there has been two things recently
where you give us a gift and then said you had to get it because there were.
It happened twice in the last couple of months.
Oh, wow. A gift. Oh, wait.
The markers were forced.
The markers and the markers.
I just wanted to share the markers.
Oh, I thought you had to buy more than one.
You do. Yeah, there it is.
Well, no, it was a box.
I ended up with a box of them that I wanted to share.
But if you had the option to buy just one.
No, you didn't have the option.
You wanted that. That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. Yeah.
If you had been able to buy just one of the pens and just one of the noisemakers,
I think you would have bought just one.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, I wouldn't spread it around.
I wanted to have some fun, you know.
Well, we know that. We believe you.
We believe you.
So I don't know. I've lost my place.
This is one of the pictures that's on a couple of different pieces of merchandise
that I really like is this Donald with like kind of a furry cape.
And he's holding his trophies and he's just on cloud nine.
He looks he's elated.
And it's like a very comic strip style.
Well, do you like seeing him get some wins?
Is that what I think on some level it is?
It's it's the same thing where like
the Trix rabbit or the Lucky Charms guy is a kid.
I always wanted them to get the series like the whole bit was generally that.
Or was it the Lucky Charms guys bit?
He couldn't get it.
The Trix rabbit couldn't get it.
Lucky Charms guy was giving it out.
Lucky Charms guy, as we all know him.
Lucky that Lucky Charms guy.
The leprechaun.
So Trix rabbit specifically, because they had a contest where like kids would vote.
Do you want to give this rabbit his cereal?
And I was like, yeah, of course,
because it was so frustrating to me that he wasn't allowed to have a cereal.
So when Donald usually loses, it's funny to watch him get frustrated.
So it is like, oh, like, did it become like Jim and Pam where the
the show got a little worse after they finally gave the Trix rabbit cereal?
Right. But I didn't know you lost that under the underlying tension.
If I was a kid watching the office, of course, I wanted Jim and Pam to get together.
I wouldn't have known that that was going to sort of take the wind out of the whole show.
I didn't know that. Yeah.
I was naive.
We have a rabbit running around who wants cereal.
That's like something that would come from the twisted mind of John Krasinski.
Only his crazy imagination can conjure such a thing. Right.
If if only if you could think of something that crazy.
Yeah. So I think part of it is that Donald is a perpetual loser,
which is what's fun and relatable about him, I suppose,
if we're really breaking it down here for deconstructing him.
But yes, he this is a time for him to win and for all his friends to get behind him.
And it's fun.
It's it's nice because all the other characters get wins.
Even I mean, Goofy gets his ass kicked a lot.
But I feel like Goofy gets more wins than even in the sports things
where there's a lot of calamities.
Maybe, you know, maybe he ends up eating ice cream while in traction.
You know, right.
There's there tends to be a happy.
But you're more likely to leave Donald in a situation like we see in the desserts
and the food. Yeah. His seat is stuck in something.
Right. Going back.
And you yeah, we're for once, you know,
giving him a happy note to go out on before they retire the character forever.
The plan after this.
Yeah, they're retiring.
This is a good buy to Donald.
They're retiring all of the. All of them. Yeah.
I'm making sure I'm retiring to myself.
They've been here too long.
They're threatening my throne.
I'm going to move up a couple of C Lester's.
The Danny DeVito character from Hercules.
Danny DeVito from Hercules.
The Wizards of Waverly, please.
What do you mean they're adults now?
I don't give a shit. Make them kids again.
The book with the eye from Hocus Pocus.
He's going to be doing a lot more heavy lifting from now on.
Some character from one of those old point of vista pictures movies.
I don't know. Just find one.
It doesn't matter. They're the big five now.
Taylor Negron, the helper of the angels in the outfield.
I know he passed away, but we'll be.
It'll be a facsimile of him. Change the part.
Big five. Change the parking garage to reflect the new five.
The levels will be.
Four of them are skeletons from the skeleton dance.
They'll do anything.
Don't don't name them skeletons.
Two, four, five and seven.
They get cocky when they get names.
They got to wear numbers because I get real fucking skeletons.
You can't tell them apart.
John Williams doesn't shut the fuck up since we called him Oma Tress.
Oma Tress is number eight of the big eight.
He's a new parking name.
The new parking lot after him.
Oh, my trash parking.
Babu Frank is not involved.
He jumped in Netflix. Too popular.
Fucking too popular.
An hour long special two seasons straight to series.
This is like when Letterman put Tom Snyder after him.
He didn't want him to overshadow him.
He wanted something less.
What a weak lead out.
Send people to sleep.
The so so they haven't announced.
I was going to say, I don't think Pete is getting his own celebration,
but I don't know that, actually, now that I say this out loud.
Oh, he so I think it's he's in the parade.
He is in the parade. Yeah, of course he is.
At Tokyo Disneyland for the first time.
Yeah. So you know what? Let's do this.
Let's play the song.
Oh, yeah. OK.
Did you hear the song already, Scott?
A little bit in just a bad shooting of the parade.
I heard it in nice quality and beautiful quality.
Uh huh. Yes. So this is a big part of why I like this.
I just like an original song theme park exclusive song.
Yeah. And there there's you before we hear it.
Would you as you've called many pieces of theme park music,
would you call this cool?
That's a good question.
I guess I for theme park music, I would call it cool,
but it reminds me very much of like kind of J-pop or city pop
or whatever you would call it.
The mini now the mini song, which I will play also,
is much more even in that vein. OK.
This has what I believe in American influence.
And I'll see if you guys feel the same way about it,
because there's sort of singing part.
And then there's more of a rapping hip hop
spoken word type of section.
And it reminds me of a certain individual.
And I'll see if I'm crazy about it or see you crazy about that thought.
More and.
I'm gathering that they love Donald Duck.
Yeah, here we go. Here's this part I'm talking about.
So that to me feels very diverse, there's feels very pitbull to me.
This is not I was if you had asked us to name it,
I don't think we would ever we wouldn't have gotten there
because Jason and I do not have pitbull on the brain as much as you do.
Well, that's true.
I'm not saying it's not part of why I think that is because I'm thinking
about pitbull a few a few minutes during the day every day.
I'm pretty familiar with pitbull.
And Jason was insulted, by the way, that you said that.
But I took you out of I don't know.
I just don't seem to be the pitbull head that Mike is.
Well, I know.
No, I can't.
I rarely leave the conversation to be about pitbull that wasn't about pitbull.
I mean, the way this episode came about is I got in Mike's car one day
and he started playing the song and he's like, you know what?
This is Quacky Duck City.
And and we talked about the pitbull ask influence.
Yeah. Now, you were primed for this in the mix, though, that is low.
I don't know why it feels like that should be a little bit louder
to hear the lyrics about how crazy Donald is.
And but I don't know.
So that song to me is is cool for a Disney Park song.
Mm hmm.
Like I'm glad you there's a little bit of you backed it off.
I backed it. Well, I usually say cool for Parks Music,
which I called Mickey's Mix Magic Song cool for Parks Music.
I don't think I said cool.
I don't think I just like it.
I think there's been some unqualified cool for songs that then you put on
and like we're having a celebration today.
Lots of magic.
There's no I've never called this one of those songs where they're like
magical wishes and dreams are like tape.
But all it would take is if it was just that, sure.
But if it had to, you would say, it's kind of cool.
I think it's a little bit cool.
Let me play Olivia Rodrigo a little bit, a little bit of pitbull.
Let me play Minnie's Funderland, because this is much more like J Pop stuff.
Cool or cool for theme music.
Let me hear it again and let me assess in real time if it's cool.
Maybe I will take off the cool for theme park music to say cool. Hold on.
Like a lot of video game sound effects in there.
We're gonna have to force that laptop out of your hands to get this song playing, aren't
we?
This file is 28 minutes long.
You know what?
I'll call it cool.
I won't even qualify it.
It's closer to what you're...
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder if the Quacky Duck City was made for the idea that maybe they could put it
in the American parks somewhere, because they've done that before where they take music from
Tokyo and use it elsewhere.
Obviously, this one is much more in Japanese and very specific.
Yeah, I don't think you can easily drop that in America.
Yeah.
Because it is Donald's 90th birthday.
That is what...
I don't even know if we...
Did we say that?
Yeah, you said it.
They're half celebrate...
They're kind of celebrating it in the parks here.
There's a little merchandise area with some stuff, but they're obviously not going all
out.
You shouldn't even give them that credit.
I know.
That doesn't sound like a celebration to me.
I'll edit that out, that I just said there.
That's not even close to being Palooza-like.
Yeah, but obviously Quacky Duck City much more like it's in English and maybe we'll hear
it here and there.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
But this one, yeah, this is really...
You go and hear a Japanese Disney song.
In this one, yeah, this has level ups and power ups and it's good.
It's just good.
I don't know what to tell you.
I can't even say anything else.
I'm fine with it.
Yeah.
But are you...
No, wait.
Actually, I kind of glazed over something.
Yeah.
Do you just drive around and listen to these songs?
That sounds like that's what was happening when you picked it.
Or did you put it on because Jason was getting in the car?
I think it was that.
Okay.
I don't think it was that.
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
You just had Quacky Ducks.
You were just blasting Quacky Ducks City.
Now that I have a child, not the Mickey child, the human child, I use it as an excuse to
play some of this stuff more often.
I see.
I have to be playing.
Right.
I listen to a lot more Chuck E. Cheese music now because I have a daughter.
She's little and she likes it.
Because of her.
Yeah.
So she likes the Quacky Ducks City song.
She dances to Quacky Ducks City.
You're not going to believe me when I say I haven't pushed this, but boy has my son latched
on to a lot of Beach Boys and not even good Beach Boys, the people.
He just got into one of the 90s ones.
Wow.
Lahaina Aloha.
Well, you're playing it though.
You have to take credit for this.
I had it on.
Yeah.
But it was not put.
I swear.
None of these are put on in a way of like, hey, check this one out.
Just I happen to be listening to admittedly terrible, early 90s Beach Boys and then he
walks in.
My daughter does latch on to stuff like she likes Can't Stop by the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
I didn't force her to like it.
And there's plenty of like Wilco songs I've played that she didn't seem to be as into
as Can't Stop.
So it's not like it's not like I'm like you need to like Ashes of American Flags.
You know, it doesn't work.
It's what I'm saying is that doesn't work like that.
We're obviously the reason you're hearing this.
But the like when she dances to stuff, it's her own choice.
I'm not moving her arms around.
Yeah.
Well, I can't get my son on board with any of Pet Sounds, but he did latch on to the
song Santa's Got an Airplane, a Beach Boys Christmas song that was actually rejected
by the record label in the 70s.
That's how bad it is.
Did it make it onto any?
When did it finally come out?
In some like, you know, Beach Boys CD collection, you know, in the 2000s when it's like, what
else is in the vault?
Right.
We put out everything good.
What else we got?
We got an airplane.
All right.
We'll see if these fuckers will buy it.
And I'm one of the fuckers and I do bought it.
Yeah.
And do you like Santa's Got an Airplane?
I don't.
I put that on because he likes airplanes.
So now just year round in May, I got to listen to Santa's Got an Airplane.
Yeah, I did it to myself.
I am getting my Beach Boys Just Punishment.
Right.
Yeah.
And then my wife is caught in the crosshairs who doesn't deserve any of this.
Do you think you should take him to see the Mike Love Beach Boys?
No, no.
You don't think so?
I don't think that would read.
Really?
Okay.
Do you think you should take him to see S.E.A.?
What?
Do you think you should take him to the sea?
To see?
Oh.
What does he mean?
The Society of Explorers?
To the beach?
Yes, he's been to the beach.
Oh, okay.
Why did you call it the S.E.A.?
Well, you know, it might be more Jimmy Buffett like being, I don't know, who sings more about
the beach and the sea?
The Beach Boys or Jimmy Buffett?
I don't think they're calling it the sea that often because they're the Beach Boys.
They got to stay on.
Yeah.
They got to frame it as the beach.
Right.
Well, the S.E.A.
He's been the S.E.A.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
I think, well, you know what?
What's good is like maybe he's not ready for it now, but in 10 years, you can take him
to see the Mike Love Beach Boys.
I know.
I think I will still be able to.
Right.
And then he'll get it.
It'll make sense.
I don't feel great about Brian's current health and I don't know how much longer we got on
Brian Mike, I think.
But whatever it takes, Android parts, no matter how much Steve Harvey red light it takes to
get him, he will be, he will drop dead on stage at a hundred and maybe later.
He'll be like Frankie Valli.
I think Frankie Valli is doing his last show soon.
Good.
Having watched some recent Frankie Valli, I forget if we've talked about this on the
show, but I somehow got algorithmed a recent Frankie Valli performance in Las Vegas where
he is Mr. Burns.
His arms are hunched over.
He walks like Mr. Burns when he performs Walk Like A Man.
This needs to stop.
Does he not?
Well, and he's lip syncing.
Whoever's making this happen, let him rest.
He's lip syncing.
Oh, yeah.
He's not singing and it's in, yeah, Vegas.
And I think I saw him maybe final performance, but maybe, I don't know.
I fingers crossed not because I want him to, if anything, I want him to live a long happy
life without having to do these same old songs.
But when people stop, sometimes that's it for them.
So maybe you're cursing him.
Maybe you should do this show for another 10 until he's a hundred.
Well, and we got to, we got to do the same thing.
We got to be up there.
We got to be out talking about seats and King Features Syndicate.
Jason lip syncing lines about King Features Syndicate at a live show in 60 years.
And I like Scramble.
His mouth didn't even move.
Trying to eat like Dagwood's sandwich, like, oh, isn't that funny?
He's got a big sandwich and my jaw just falls off.
Right in Stimpy Joke.
Why did they bring out a curtain and put it in front of him right when he had to eat the
sandwich and then it was gone almost instantly?
Enough time for even a young man to eat a sandwich.
We'll have young hosts, though, as well, too, to keep up like John Stamos of the show or
something.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, just like seven anonymous.
Hosts.
Guys who sort of look like us.
Hawaiian shirts.
And those guys haven't been born yet.
Yeah.
That's a thought.
Listeners potential job opportunity for unborn children of yours.
All right.
The last thing, I guess, really, just to talk a little bit about the parade itself, which
I guess is sort of the big, big piece, I suppose, of the whole event.
And it's all the friends coming together to wear, yes, as we said, wear Donald's colors
to celebrate him.
And it's not as weird.
I wish it was weirder like Mickey Mania.
That's a criticism I might have.
It is definitely not.
Yeah.
I mean, you've got your character across, so you've got everybody dressed like Donald
and you've got like beautiful young women dressed in Donald Duck sailor suits, which
made me feel very confused.
Oh, yeah.
There's all sorts of.
And they have like I was just excited for the video to be over, so I don't have to ponder
anything.
It's a real dad, a real dad comment.
And they have like big like kind of blue hair, like wigs, like very like I feel like Nickelodeon
style.
Buffon.
I guess that's that's kind of like a feather equivalent of hair.
And they have is is yeah, there's a well, there's a couple different looks for the ladies.
Some of them have the full seat and like yellow leggings and then a top hat as well.
That's what you're talking about.
Strangest.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
No.
Buffon wigs get us into a territory that I well, it's because like your brain is reading
it as the ladies are wearing little shorts, but they're really wearing Donald's feathers.
Bright yellow duckling.
Yeah.
So that's what your brain is to put this video in a closet.
Your brain is getting confused.
Your brain is getting confused with it because you want to celebrate your friend, but also
you're a dad.
So I don't know why dad has anything to do with it.
Just I guess it doesn't have anything technically to do with it.
It's just as we've talked about before, the dad at a theme park.
Well, it's something dad's there and he's he's got a couple of things he likes air conditioning
and there's like a nice looking lady and these are things that's what's happened.
I mean, I guess I can't say a woman is attractive without it being a dad thing to say this comes
from a dad.
Well, but it was specifically about the ladies dressed as Donald Duck in a Disney parade.
Yeah, I know, but I think I would have been as as weirded out by this when I was 23.
All right.
I don't think I don't think leave my child out of this observation.
If you had been saying, you know, I was out at the club last night and there were some
dynamite looking ladies or something, I would say, well, that's more of just a regular heterosexual
man thing to say.
But when you're talking about the ladies dressed as Donald, to me, it feels very dad comment.
There would be no comment to make if it wasn't women dressed as Donald.
Sure wouldn't have been a story.
If my story was I was out at the club last night and I saw some fetching ladies.
Why am I even saying that?
What club are we talking about?
I don't know.
I'm just saying that the the Disney Park specific to me makes it feel like a dad.
What I was watching, it was my job.
My job today was to watch a video with some weird Donald costumes.
That's just my feeling about it.
Jason, I don't know.
What do you feel about this?
What do you feel?
You don't have a kid.
Did you did you have odd feeling seeing the ladies dressed as Donald with the leggings
in the seat?
Hey, look, we all got needs, even daddy's, you know, sidestepped that question that was
not answered at all and it made it much creepier.
I mean, I never called myself a daddy.
I think the outfits look nice.
I don't know.
I think everyone looks fun.
Neutral thing.
Everyone does look fun.
I agree.
It was confusing.
They looked attractive and they looked attractive in wardrobe that was Donald Duck.
And then I was like, why that's why do I stand?
I get what you're saying.
Heard me out.
I hear that.
Let's let's let's move away then.
Quack quack sticks.
Well, we're still talking about the we could talk a little bit more about the parade or
you want to know.
You know what?
Never mind.
Who cares about the parade?
Quack.
We're talking quack quack sticks.
Oh, I just didn't want you to forget quack quack sticks on the quack quack sticks.
They're little parades.
Little there are little sticks you shake.
And it says and they make quack sound and says on Attractions magazine, Disney encourages
guests to shake their quack quack sticks during performances of quacky celebration.
Donald the legend.
So I was out of the nightclub and I was, you know, just getting out there shaking my quack
quack stick.
I saw a couple of very fetching young that has nothing to do with being a dad.
And you're really part of it, not supposed to shake your quack quack stick out in public
or a private thing, but they're encouraging it in Tokyo, Disneyland.
I don't know.
There's, you know, I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
Yeah.
Scott's had a kid.
He still goes out to nightclubs and getting his quack quack stick wet.
Maybe it means something else.
I don't know.
It means something else.
That's for sure.
Also, by the way, you wouldn't have found it weird if I was, if I was just telling you
about going to a nightclub and looking at that's fine with a kid in that world.
I would think it's a little weird because it's about a character.
Would you think it was weird if the music they were playing was the music from Minnie's
Thunderland, which is cool?
I would think it was cool and weird.
I would think it was both.
Scott's a little weird, but also cool because he goes to that nightclub that plays Thunderland.
Yeah.
Did they exclusively play music that seems like it plays it with the end credits of anime?
Or the first, the front credits.
Or the opening credits.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
There's, okay.
Yeah.
You want to go to merch?
Let's do merch real quick.
I don't know.
You probably picked up the funniest merch.
Honestly, Jason.
Quack quack sticks.
Yeah.
I mean, they got a lot of good plush.
It's like all the merch at Tokyo Disney also is like they make a lot more like specific
stuff for events.
It's the same gripes I've had forever.
They do.
They have like little towel.
You can get little towels.
I feel like you can't get little towels here anymore.
Like a dish towel?
Like a decorative towel for the kitchen?
Like a little hand towel.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
You can't really get, can you get a hand towel at Disneyland?
I think you can get linens, but I don't know about souvenir, like a souvenir spoon, souvenir
towel.
When you say linens, you mean?
Like, a nice napkin?
Like towel sets, like towel sets or sheets.
Oh, maybe.
All right.
Maybe you can do it then.
I think some of those Disney spring stores have more like home goods sort of things.
Oh, yeah.
Disney Home, which we didn't cover because we had, it was after Downtown Disney Ordeal,
I believe.
Does anybody remember?
I think so.
Everybody's missing out.
Everybody's missing out on Disney Home.
It's never going to happen.
We're never going to cover it.
So your complaint is you can't buy Disney hand towels in this country.
A little washcloth.
Tea towels.
There you go.
And there's just a lot, like there's, you can get a beret with, that's Donald's seat
with his feet in the air, which is cute.
I'm not wearing it, but it's cute.
You don't think that's cute?
I don't know.
I think that, does he have a little hat?
Is that like Donald's little hat?
Well, he's got the like.
His hat's like a hat.
It's his hat with his seat on it.
It's a butt hat.
It's a seat hat.
If Jason's, your knee jerk would have been, it's cute if you thought it was cute.
Yeah.
No, he's right.
Jason doesn't think.
I think I was trying to figure out what kind of hat it was.
Like if it was, if he's the best chef, maybe it was a toque.
It was what?
What's that?
Is that the type of chef's hat?
Those chef's hats are called toques.
Are they really?
I didn't know that.
I believe so.
Toque.
How do you spell that?
I am not sure.
Canadian term?
I didn't know that.
Toque.
Well, he's the greatest chef and he has the greatest toque.
Those can be like knit hats though.
At least that's the Canadian.
I mean, probably a chef's hat works for that, but.
All right.
Well, how long, we can, here's, here's what I'll say.
Like I think that on this podcast, sometimes we need to celebrate each other more as well.
So I think that we should, at least for in the future, we should celebrate Jason in a
way, Jason the legend.
And I don't know what city he wants us to sort of like brand the podcast, but I've talked
about Jason month for a long time.
And when we eventually do do Jason month, which we will, I would like to brand it in
a way that mimics this Quacky Duck City.
Can I just steal Quacky Duck City?
Can I say my city?
You could.
Can you change one word at least?
Quacky Duck.
Quacky Jason City?
Feels a little lazy to me, but.
It's lazy.
A lot of Jason might feel a little lazy.
That's the spirit.
So I'll come up with a song.
I'm all for Jason month.
If Jason chooses all the topics, does all the research and edits them all or I'll, I'll
do that tomorrow.
Let's do it next week.
Oh, okay.
Well, we'll, we'll, we'll be less on board with the Jason.
We'll be in deep discussion about what Jason month means, and I'm not saying it's coming
soon necessarily, but there will be a Quacky Duck City style song, original song for Jason
month.
I like that.
And when it happens, composed by Jason and performed by Jason, correct?
Yeah.
Great.
All right.
Whoa, whoa.
We love Sheridan.
Whoa.
It sounds like he just recorded it.
I think.
Yeah.
We'll just play it there.
So eventually, yes.
So that's what I kind of, that's the template.
Quacky Duck City, I think is the template for Jason month.
Could there be Mike Scott month?
Yes.
But the priority is Jason month and Jason's Quacky Jason City.
People will be coming eventually.
I don't want to promise it.
Why are you, why are you quacky though?
Oh, I'm just always quacking up a storm, you know, I'm always grousing and quacking.
I guess I see it.
Yeah.
I mean, I see it.
I mean, it's, but it's up to, ultimately it's his wish fulfillment.
We don't have to eat pasta that looks like Jason's seat, do we?
If we, if he wants it, if he wants to do it.
Now that's a month where it's okay to eat duck dishes, you know, it's not so morbid.
Right.
So there's going to be a lot of duck.
So one of Jason's decrees is that we all eat a lot of duck.
He wants us to eat a lot of duck, a lot of dark meat chicken.
Let's get real sweaty with duck.
No white meat.
Right before and during all these records.
Yeah.
And we, and Jason, you will have to come up with a couple of dishes that will rival that
weird omelet thing that is just like a hamburger patty on top of an omelet covered in salt.
Is it just like a, that looks more like loco moco, a Hawaiian, a Hawaiian dish with a hamburger
patty and gravy.
Maybe that is what it is.
I guess.
Seems like in that world.
Yeah.
But you'll, you'll, you can make one of your pies, I guess, for Jason.
Oh, I can make a pecan pie.
Yep.
Do you make pecan pies?
I can't.
Yeah, I have.
That's his specialty.
Yeah.
Really?
When was the last time you made a pecan pie?
Not in a while.
I have.
Yeah.
Really?
How is it?
It's good.
Wow.
And can you put little feet sticking out of it?
Um, I think I could, man.
I mean, I think I'd probably shape some of the pecans to just like make little feet.
Or you could just buy two, you could just buy baby shoes and stick them.
Oh yeah.
Just want some baby.
Either way.
For sale, baby shoes worn in pie.
Used in decorative pie.
We'll be making that reference constantly.
Yeah.
It's a really short story, so you can make it very easily.
Well, eventually.
I'm not saying it's this year.
Maybe it's for our platinum celebration.
I don't know.
I don't know how long it'll take, but I would like to declare it.
I would like to declare it here.
It might take 68 years.
We may do it when we're 90 and singing walk like a man.
Our version of whatever that means.
So yeah, I don't know.
Any other thoughts on Quacky Duck City?
I'm jealous.
I wish we had Quacky Duck City here and I'm not going to get to see it.
I don't think.
I don't think I'm headed to Tokyo in the next three weeks.
I don't know.
Maybe, maybe if some like divine intervention happens and somebody like forces, I don't
know the scenario where I have to go to Tokyo, literal hand of God picks you up and takes
you there.
Yeah.
I wake up there.
Somebody drugged me and took me on like a cargo ship.
You're all for it.
You would love to be drugged and dragged as long as you're planted in the middle of Donald's
Quacky Duck City.
Yeah, I would be freaked out and then I realize where I am and it's Quacky Duck City and I'm
happy.
Donald gets a trophy for best human trafficker.
I guess we did it.
I think we did it.
Yeah.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three, where you
get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
I don't know.
I don't know if you do feel good.
You hear you're also you also have this energy of sadness.
Yeah, you started and ended sad.
I'm upset.
You said this is how it was going to go.
I feel like you said like I called it.
Yeah, you called like I'm just going to complain.
We don't have this here.
Yeah. Well, you recognize that it could happen.
Didn't change your behavior.
No, I leaned into it.
In fact, it got worse because I did the episode.
Wow. You know, you're supposed to have like talk like therapy and talk it out and stuff
and it's supposed to make it better.
Not this time.
This made my feelings worse and it will cast a shadow over the rest of my day and maybe
weak. Yeah.
So I want to listeners, I hope you have a better week than Mike does.
Yeah, I hope you do, too, because it's going to be bleak.