FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcast may rattle and grind so much it renders your speakers unsafe to use.
You may encounter claustrophobic hallways and a nail-biting round of picking numbers from one to three.
Today, we examine the notorious, barely-opened, Tomorrowland-destroying 90s Disneyland attraction,
The Rocket Rods, on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about theme parks where conversation and riffs fly
at breakneck speed and then, you know, slow down every six seconds or so because you don't want to go at too breakneck a speed.
I'm Scott Gertner, this is Mike Carlson.
That is really, that sums us up so perfectly.
Yeah, yeah. Big runs and then kind of, and then just, you know, take our time.
We'll find the next one. Okay, there we go. Here's another run. Good.
Yeah, some funny talk and then, you know, we talk about I Love Lucy actor William Frawley for a while to slow down,
to cool things down, to make sure that we don't get too hot, too fast.
This is very humble of you to call Frawley a slow down as opposed to one of the fastest tracks could ever do.
Well, it excites me internally, but I don't know that it does that to the audience.
That's a speed ramp to you. The mere, even like thinking that you're going to say him, that gets your heart palpitating.
And then it coming out of your mouth and then watching Jason light up when you say it and then watching me be indifferent,
which lights you up further. That's true. Yeah. Frawley was always too exciting for me.
Frawley was like a straight away. I think the windups, like the curves are more like saying things like 25 million,
May 22nd, 1998, saying the items. That's true. That's true.
But I guess it's the connective tissue. It gets you from the straight away to straight away. Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi. Yeah, today we are continuing the as kicked down the curb Tomorrowland series.
Now in its third or fourth year. Yes. Yeah. As delayed as the real place.
And here's kind of what brings us back to this.
You know, we wanted to do like kind of the essential steps in telling the story of what brought us to the Tomorrowland we have today,
which is to say the ghost town.
And Mike has pushed recently to get back on the Tomorrowland train in advance of D23.
Yes, which is in August where the big Disney convention where there is the thought that maybe we will finally get some announcements.
Well, that's what the feeling is, because of all this movement with Disneyland forward being approved and with Rhonda Santis and Disney making nice.
They're now they've dropped a lawsuit against him.
And now it seems like they're they're paving the way for a big expansion down there as well.
And they've booked what they booked the Honda Center for the actual theme parks panel at D23 this year.
Yes. And just a reminder, the Honda Center is one of those venues that has the no bag rule unless they are clear.
Right. You have a clear plastic bag as if you're going to visit Magneto in prison.
You just have to make sure. Well, hold on.
They could do some damage with those zippers, you know.
Oh, that's a very good point. So you should have a plastic zipper if you're visiting Magneto in prison.
Is this they don't want people filming the panels?
I don't know, because they live stream it. It's I don't know.
This is also like certain venues have this rule.
Yeah, this is Dodger Stadium when we went to see Elton John, like they kind of did this to my mother who had a purse.
So it's venues just in general.
I don't know if it's easier to see if you have a knife on you.
A lot of baseball stadiums have have that.
But what if it's a clear knife or a clear gun and you're back with clear bullets?
Well, we're back to square one now. Erase the whiteboard.
Yeah, you've changed everything. So I wouldn't put it past Disney to book a very large venue and then not deliver.
That's possible.
It is kind of the current Disney way to take a big space communicator and then sort of do nothing with it.
Yeah. So it's possible they're going to get it, drag everybody over there.
Everyone's going to get really excited, like worked up in the lat into a lather.
And then they're going to say, well, we're thinking about doing a few things and then they'll float a few ideas.
And then they'll send everybody home with like a poster, like a poster of the new country bears.
And then like half the people there will be like, I think that was good.
Yeah. And then the next day they like sober up and they go, what was that? I paid four hundred dollars for that.
Some of them, but some of them never will. Some of them stay drunk forever.
Some of them will drink the Kool-Aid and the Kool-Aid stays in me.
So yeah. So what you're saying is I believe there's a chance.
I believe there's at least a percentage of a chance that new Tomorrowland stuff will be announced because they need to do this.
So I want to get our Tomorrowland stuff out of the way before because I want to see what our see,
because now we can then gauge our predictions versus what might be announced.
So we'll get to see who is right or what. Maybe we'll all be a little right if there.
Yeah. And if we if we pull things out, because what we're building to is this episode where we we fix Tomorrowland and all the different paths to figure out how to do so.
And yeah. So if we accidentally predicted some things or if we said some things that are vastly more exciting than what gets announced.
Right. Yeah, that's that's a good call. I still I hear you saying maybe this is the year we get to Marland.
And I think about like an Angels in the Outfield scenario where there's like an orphan who's like, maybe my dad will come back this time.
Maybe my dad will stick around this year. I know my old my pops.
He cares about me. He loves me. I know it, even though he's got a leather jacket.
He's not just going to keep writing this time.
I guess if we really want to gauge that there's a bigger chance they'll announce that like Disneyland forward stuff like over by the hotels, which is where they're going to expand.
That's more likely that they just announced a bunch of stuff from like over there.
I think it is. Then saying Tomorrowland is going to finally get its redo.
I think. Yeah. And I think new is going to be more exciting than redone or fixed, even though we know this is like, you know, if I were a homeowner, which I am not sure.
I would imagine that, you know, there's things like the it's more exciting to try to add to turn the, you know, to turn the garage into a guest house or whatever.
But when you've got like when the plumbing stinks, when there is a terrible sulfur smell in your house, it's not an exciting way to spend the money.
But you sort of have to do it right. That's true.
They did announce that they're going to make the vehicles in Autopia electric.
So I think that's also partly why some people think, OK, well, there's some movement in that area of the park.
That's at least an indicator that what the clue that that unlocks, I feel, is that Autopia and subs don't get demolished because if they're investing in there at all.
Yeah, right. It's not like that is going to become Avatar.
So that news is a disappointment to me because I would love that area to go in for it to become.
But I know. But at least I remain excited.
And I don't know if we'll get an announcement soonish.
But Avatar is the thing that they have shown. Yeah. Yes.
I know. I don't know if we'll get it this year.
But it seems like a given that there will be something Avatar coming to the park.
But it's a matter of is it over in Disneyland forward?
It's probably not Disneyland proper, which maybe doesn't make sense.
There's weird DCA rumors too. I don't know. I don't know.
Well, you'll be excited to know that some of the houses at the Katino story living will have shutters, not just blinds.
What if they do that? They drag everybody into this big Honda center room and they just mostly talk about Katino.
They talk about their different like housing developments, their building seems really possible.
I posted about this. I noticed a really mundane Katino video.
And so it might be like, ladies and gentlemen, welcome the designers from Shea Holmes.
Very well. I don't know. Yeah.
In between like Jon Favreau coming out and doing nothing.
Yeah, they do a lot of that with people.
Of course, they brought Dick Van Dyke out to announce the Mary Poppins thing that never happened.
God, they did. Yeah.
In 2019, they brought him out and they're like, Dick Van Dyke.
Dick Van Dyke. Everyone goes nuts, of course.
And then they're like, and of course, in Epcot, we're doing the Mary Poppins thing,
which it turns out that was going to be nothing, basically, like a spinner ride, maybe.
Really? And canceled. Oh, man.
People are like, oh, is it going to be like that Tony Baxter ride he developed,
like before he worked in Imagineering that there's a video about and it was like on the carousel.
And then things would leave the track and they would go along a dark ride. Have you ever seen this?
You start on it. It was the idea that you would start on it.
It feels like you're on a carousel horse that's on a carousel and then it departs.
Right, like in the movie, the first movie, yeah.
The first movie.
Yeah, well, you remember the sequel.
You mean the only Mary Poppins. Let's come on.
No, no, wait, hold on.
Quit fucking around. You mean in Mary Poppins, the only movie.
Mary Poppins 1.
I refuse.
Mary Poppins 3.
Is it Topsy Origins?
Do you think we're going Topsy Origins?
Well, that's more of a Disney Plus streaming series.
Oh, okay. It's eight episodes. Topsy Origins.
In which Topsy doesn't appear until the very, very end.
Well, how did she become Topsy is the question everyone's asking.
That's the question.
Yeah, how did she turn? Is it Turning Turtle? Is that the song?
I'm so disappointed in you for not remembering the name Topsy or remembering her famous song.
Okay, it's a lot of T's.
It's a lot of T's.
So disappointed in you.
That should be on the forefront of your mind at all moments.
Turning Turtle.
It's almost like if you can't quite remember it, maybe that means that it's time for the runner to be retired.
Is that a thought? That's something, isn't it?
Well, Jason can't. So I guess if Jason can't remember it, then fine.
I'll only bring it up three times a year and not six.
What's the name of Madame's owner, the ventriloquist?
The long dead ventriloquist. Well, Madame's not my thing.
Yeah, but it's been said. This is my new rule. If we can't all remember it, it's out.
You don't remember who operates Madame?
This is not fair. This is not any sort of barometer.
This isn't fair.
It indicates a lack of interest among all of the hosts of the show.
It indicates that if it is not penetrated, everybody in the room, then why are we...
No, no, no, no, no. Put the phone down. That doesn't count.
I'm just dismissing some notifications.
About what?
A pill reminder.
Of course it's that.
I didn't want them to interrupt my notes. I have my notes over here.
Okay, okay. So moving on, no more Turtle, no more Whalen Flowers and Madame. There I said it.
So today, I think this is kind of a crucial piece of what brings us to the Tomorrowland we've had for so many decades now.
This is really the culprit, and it's also something that is kind of a dwindling resource in this show.
We are running out of things to talk about, topics that you could possibly call Disney's worst ride.
And here we have a definite, very solid candidate, and that is the Rocket Rods.
I've been looking forward to the Rocket Rods a lot. I remember it very strongly.
This was in 1998, Jason's Slowdown Facts you said earlier, May 22, 1998, part of the new Tomorrowland redo.
And what I remember strongly, and I think I've talked about this before, is how this was right around...
I was clearly, I was a big Disneyland kid in this era, and where getting to be a kid then in the early 90s,
in the first half of the Disney decade, where it seems like things just keep getting better and better.
There's Toontown, and then there's Indiana Jones, like the ultimate just like raise of the bar of themed entertainment.
Where are things going next? What are they doing next? And what they did next was take away the Electrical Parade,
replace it with light magic, this upsetting thing about Pixies, then this, then new Tomorrowland.
And all this in the same time that the Simpsons got bad. This was a time that let me know that institutions can fail me.
That maybe I can't trust the long running hallowed institutions that give me the entertainment that I enjoy the most.
The end of innocence in a lot of ways.
It kind of was. In a time that's already awkward, upset, I consider it part of, sure it was middle school bad,
because I didn't know how to talk to girls, and I didn't know what current music to like.
But I'd say equal to that was Disneyland starting to not be good anymore.
Oh wow, we were still cooking on the East Coast. We had Animal Kingdom, we had the Islands of Adventure Preview Center,
and Islands of Adventure after it.
You put Preview Center in the running of the park itself?
I was going chronologically.
I know Mike that the Islands of Adventure Preview Center had a big impact on your adolescence.
Yeah, it really, all the girls loved hearing about the Preview Center, so that helped me with girls too.
And I guess there's going to be some kind of jazz club at their city walk? They're not calling it E-Zone anymore.
It's pretty cool. Anyway, how about a smooch?
Also, the Scott Bale song, How Do You Talk to Girls, helped me out a lot too with that.
Rick Springfield wrote it, of course. That helps too.
Instruction manual, song instruction manual.
So, okay, you know what, you do paint that, that on the East Coast, this is not so much your problem.
It was my problem. I'm a big Disneyland guy, and this was highly anticipated, and it kind of all undeniably was let down.
Did you clock any of this at the time? Were you aware that Rocket Rods and a disappointing New Tomorrowland were going on?
Or do you not clock it until you start going to Disneyland as your park and there's still kind of the remnants of it?
I don't clock it at all at this time. It's not even on my radar.
I'm more focused on Islands of Adventure, and I don't even know if I knew what Rocket Rods were until like late 2000s.
Okay, wow, wow.
Yeah, kind of the same. I was thinking about, because eventually Tomorrowland 98, eventually you get Buzz Lightyear after it a few years later.
And I was like, oh, the first time I went to Disneyland is like 2006.
And I definitely was like, so that used to be the people mover, and it's just empty.
And then it's dawning on me like, oh, that's coming up on 20 years ago.
And that track remains empty.
Yeah, yeah. Well, in that, I mean, it's been empty technically since 2001.
So we have, what, 23 years of empty track. It's wild.
Right.
That's a good basic to bring up kind of before we get into the whole history.
But Cliff notes of it, Rocket Rods were a high speed replacement for the people mover, which we did a few episodes about.
Slow moving, very pleasant trip through the second story of Tomorrowland remains in Disney World under a different name.
But kind of this just like, you know, hey, that's something like a something the whole family can do, an attraction that really wasn't hurting anybody.
Yeah.
Be hard to complain about it, I think.
Right.
Somebody somewhere gets the idea.
What if this was a rip roaring roller coaster rocket ride?
Yeah, it's just a funny thought to have, because it's like, what if somebody was like, why don't we make the train around Disneyland go super fast?
You're like, I don't think that's the point of this.
I like going fast, but why would you use the same track and change a thing whose point was to like, look at everything in a pleasant way?
Yeah, it's just a funny idea.
And then to carry out it like it was cursed from the beginning.
The idea itself is flawed.
You're right.
Yeah.
Let's take the Columbia River boat.
Let's take that.
Let's take the Mark Twain.
And yeah.
Yeah.
Rockets on the Mark Twain.
Jason, what if Mark Twain went really fast?
If it went from a 12 minute ride to a two and a half minute ride or something.
Yeah.
What if it spins around and shoots around the lake really fast?
They do not put in any chairs or restraints.
So everyone is nauseated.
People are just constantly thrown in the water multiple times a day.
Unless you hold on.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's just.
It's up to you.
That system would reward someone like Jason who knows the ship very well.
You would know where the railings were and the secure items.
But you wouldn't grab like a life preserver because that's going to snap off.
Yeah.
And he would get to hug his favorite ship too, which is nice.
For dear life.
But you would give a few kisses while you were there.
Well, if I'm already there.
Yeah.
And I'm already hugging.
Exactly.
If you're already hugging, you might as well be kissing.
Yes.
So yeah.
No, I just like, he's like, why don't we take a thing that goes nice and slow and make it
fast?
It's a really good point.
Yeah.
Take the castle and put it on a pole and have it like go up and down.
Shoot.
Like huh?
Turn it into a big swing shot ride.
Hey, these horses are interesting who we have down Main Street, but what if we made them
like race?
What if we had people like racing on horses down Main Street?
Like, I don't know if that's the point of the horses, but okay.
Yeah, boy.
Well, you've really driven right to the core.
That's true.
I mean, it's like they're there and that's what they're doing.
They're doing a 180.
They're trying to turn one type of experience into another.
But the question is, did anyone want that?
And if you're going to do a new roller coaster, why wouldn't you do that from scratch?
Why would you?
Yeah.
Just do a different thing.
Of all the things to fix in Tomorrowland, I don't think the people mover was one of
them.
Right.
And that's where I'll get into kind of Tomorrowland 98 history because, okay, so it's the early
nineties and it's clear that in all the parks there is a Tomorrowland problem, but especially
in Disneyland.
I think that one was struggling the most.
And this narrative that's said a lot by Imagineers is just like, you know, keeping things futuristic,
trying to predict the future is very tricky because the present catches up to the future.
And I feel like even like staying current, not even aiming for futurism, but staying
current is really tough.
Yeah.
Which has led to all of these, like we've touched on some of them, but these like kind
of like inane exhibits that get lapped pretty quickly.
So always sort of a struggle.
But what's weird is, I mean, I think it was kind of a fraught land always, like the Tomorrowland
at the end of the 50s seems real rough.
Right.
Then 67 is the first big redo and they put in, you know, some of the primary pieces,
you get Carousel Theater and you get rocket jets up on the platform and we're getting
closer to like the building blocks of a land that can't really go anywhere.
Past that, we finally start getting locks.
There are attractions that are locks that you can't do anything with, maybe like aesthetic
plus ups or new movies or whatever.
But that's something I think is so strange about the land is that it's a fraught land,
but Space Mountain, lock.
Star Tours, lock.
Magic Eye Theater, what's in it is not necessarily a lock, but at least there was a time where
it being a movie theater is a lock.
So, you know, if you're going to redo an entire land, you've got trouble here because there
are locks to work around.
There are rides that you probably want to keep open as much as possible.
Hard to just blow up the entire thing and start over, which is sort of what they did
for Fantasyland, the Tony Baxter's very successful Fantasyland redo.
It was all just demolished and rebuilt, but something you can't really do here.
The things that they need to change, Mission to Mars, we talked about that.
That is like a 70s view of space travel.
And that's true of a lot of these things.
You've got America Sings, which is a show for the Bicentennial in 76, which was there
until 88.
They finally clear it out.
They kick all the robots out and send them over to Splash Mountain.
That's been sitting vacant since 88.
Circle Vision, still not a lot.
I remember that was feeling like a Ghost Town by mid-90s, and they're playing a movie from
84.
This is a messy land.
But of all the things, PeopleMover is not one of anyone's complaints.
You change the vehicle.
PeopleMover there had tops on it, unlike Disney World's.
So you change the look of the vehicles, perhaps?
That is something.
Neon stripes.
This is before they realized the answer is always neon stripes.
Right.
Yeah, put a neon strip or something on the sides or something.
You could do that.
Well, yeah, and that almost could have saved rocket rods.
But it got cost cut, and then it was going to get in, and then they just shut it down.
That was a possibility.
It was some lighting stuff.
So around this time, they're starting to solve the Tomorrowland problem in other parks with
kind of this notion of future that never was.
Not trying to be literal sci-fi future, but kind of a more fantastical version of it.
Euro Disney, they don't do Tomorrowland at all.
They do Discoveryland, which is this steampunk European fantasy, Jules Verne, H.G. Wells,
pseudo-Victorian kind of vibe, a lot of bronze and gold and copper.
Of all the things in Euro Disney that were there from day one, this land is a banger.
I think it's still really great.
There's been some changes to it, but I think essentially the aesthetic has remained,
and it's really good.
I could see why they started clocking this as the answer.
We're not going to try to keep up with whatever rockets are being used in real life anymore.
It was just aesthetically really great.
Tomorrowland 94 in Magic Kingdom is fantastic.
That is this other kind of sci-fi, more routed through 50s, 60s, kooky B movie, Buck Rogers, Flash Gordon.
We're starting to get some examples of how we do Tomorrowland that's this fun,
always relevant sort of, where they don't have to keep updating it.
Which brings us to what they wanted to do here, which is Tomorrowland 2055.
We haven't talked about this a ton.
This is one of those things that's very haunting, because anything you see, concept art, logo, boy, this looked really cool.
Yes.
Yeah, I know.
I guess it's imagining what it would look like now, and I'm like,
it would probably make Tomorrowland my favorite part of Disneyland maybe.
Yeah, I think so.
I think.
Yes.
It's really glowy.
It's crystals.
There's kind of a story, and the crystals are part of it.
There's potential for a whole, we dig into everything about this and speculate what this would have been.
But there are all these exciting possibilities, especially of what the non-locks become, right?
Mission to Mars becomes Alien Encounter, which we got in Florida, but this might have been a better venue for it.
It might have made sense.
Carousel Theater becomes Plekdu's Fantastic Galactic Review.
Again, I think there's a whole, we need to try to find every drop of information about this.
Yeah, this is its own episode.
It's not a lot.
The Circlevision Theater probably gets the Timekeeper show, which went to Florida,
which finally gave a story to one of these 360 Circlevision movies with the animatronics and Robin Williams here.
The successful show, really good show.
I assume that's what it would have been here.
So big possibilities, cool possibilities, very distinct and different from the other New Tomorrow lands they've figured out.
But Euro Disney fails, and this is part of the, there's the most frequently recurring words in theme park history,
but Euro Disney fails, and then X.
Yeah, it's really, it feels so much more dire now, knowing that they're not going to ever do a big land that has a bunch of original characters in it.
It almost feels like if you had the time machine, it would be so important to go back in time and either stop Euro Disney from being built
so Tomorrowland 2055 can get built, because we know in the future it will be impossible.
So it's the last chance for us to have something crazy like this with a bunch of original characters and not just a bunch of movie rides.
I have a time machine. I know where I'm going. I'm going right to Europe in the mid 20th century.
Oh, Hitler, you're going to go kill, no, no, no, no, no, no, way more important.
I'm going to go, I'm going to find Michael Eisner, you're going to kill Michael Eisner? No, no, of course not.
No, I love Michael Eisner. No, I'm going to shake his hands, say fine work so far.
I just have some information that you might want to see.
And then I'll let him keep doing his job, because he's doing a bang up job.
And then you would, I would also like tell him, like, they're going to come for you in the late 1990s or early 2000s.
Like, here's how we get around that. Here's how you reign as CEO until you die.
Like, I would also, there's the other stuff I want to do if I'm going to talk to him in the time machine.
And yeah, make sure that he's still running the company now.
Oh, man, that's a very good idea. Yeah, yeah. Just give him all the answers to the test.
And then you know what? You got a time machine. Let him go back and kill Hitler. Give him the glory.
Yeah, right. That's good.
Because imagine how that shores up support for everything he wants to do.
You're going to argue with this guy? This is the guy who put in Star Tours and killed Hitler.
Hello. I'm here in the bunker. I've just strangled Adolf Hitler.
With his own hand. He strangled him.
That's right. I killed him. No big deal.
Are you Adolf Hitler? Goodbye.
I'm Michael Eisner, chairman of the Walt Disney Company, and your killer.
Now it's time to go back to the future, where I may reign until I'm 120.
God, I do it. CEO of Disney.
I know, because without, you take that piece away, and then it keeps, and we get the full Disney decade.
But basically, there's still now, you know, they need to do something.
There's literally empty attractions.
You know, what was a big plus up in the late 80s now is a somewhat outdated 3D movie,
a singing and dancing show starring an accused child molester.
This needs to go. A lot of things need to happen.
So they need, we have to figure out some version of a Tomorrowland redo,
but I don't think it can be Tomorrowland 2055.
But let's keep all the people on it, because it's the best people on it.
It's Tony Baxter. It's Bruce Gordon, who was part of Splash Mountain.
So this is part of what's heartbreaking about it, is that there's like the best of the best,
but they have been severely handcuffed.
They are given a third of the budget that they wanted,
which probably still like trickles, like gets less and less as they do the whole thing.
That is interesting to think about.
Like, well, even before this redo, there was some Ghost Town elements of Tomorrowland.
It's like history rhyming.
It's like, well, still a Ghost Town now, but was also a Ghost Town before the ostensible redo.
And some of the things that remain the big problem areas today were the problem areas then.
I mean, it's like it fixed it, you know, like a ride that they were tired of running
or that they might have stopped running entirely became a restaurant, which makes them money.
But it's not the most exciting thing they could do.
Carousel Theater is the biggest tragedy area in the history of Disneyland.
It's insane. Yeah, it's like these places are cursed.
So look, because it's Tony Baxter, you have to imagine that this is part of it,
that he was kind of the main voice behind Discoveryland, which was very successful.
And that's where it becomes, well, what if we sort of Discoverylandify our existing Tomorrowland,
which is why we get Astro Orbiter.
But Astro Orbiter has all these pieces that are too complicated and too heavy to put up on top of that tower.
So you got to move it to the front of the park.
And we've complained about this before. Nobody likes this.
This is like a big traffic bottleneck and it's crazy.
And then they just took the bones of the old rocket jets and set up a show that they don't run anymore.
Right.
This is all crazy.
Captain EO is replaced by Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
That is fine, but it is not new.
That has been running at Epcot for a little while.
Yeah.
So yeah.
InnoVentions.
This is not the same InnoVentions from Florida.
I might argue worse, right? Right?
Seems like it.
Do you think? Yeah.
I guess only I went of the three of us.
Yeah, I didn't go, so I don't know firsthand.
It was pretty inane.
There's a big tree in the middle and this kind of unpleasant Nathan Lane-voiced robot.
It was not a good deal, I didn't think.
Yeah.
I saw it later in the 2010s when there was a throwback House of the Future
that was mostly bad Windows touchscreen that the iPhone had already lapped it.
Yeah, those touchscreens did not work.
It's Marty McFly's house in 2015 where the fake windows break
and he gets into fights with the mechanics of it.
There was an hour-long wait to try a segue.
Again, we're talking 2010s.
Occasionally, Awesome-O would come out, very rarely,
and then there was some testing stations where you could test out Disney Infinity.
Is that what it was called?
That was that video game.
That was the Xbox game that you could buy little figures for.
Yeah, the little figures.
This was a few rounds of Disney Interactive layoffs ago,
and it was like, all right, all the characters get together and they meet,
and they gave up on that idea.
All companies eventually did, like, fighting game where all the characters meet.
Nickelodeon does it, Warner Brothers has it, but it's mostly for free on your phone.
This wasn't a fighting game.
This wasn't like a Street Fighter.
It was like an adventure game.
People might have liked that.
People might have played it.
It's too successful of a genre for them to do.
Was that still called Interventions when it was that house?
I think so.
I believe so, because I don't think it changes until it's,
it doesn't change fully until it's Star Wars launch bay.
Launch bay.
With no offense to the launch bay.
We always wanted to go to a Star Wars launch bay when you see the movies.
Remember when they kind of like had a corner of a room painted like the Cantina bar?
I do, yeah.
There was no characters there.
There were no characters.
There was no drinks, seemingly.
So that being said, meeting Chewie was fun and we did it a few times.
Well, good news, I think you can still do it.
I think that's probably right.
But this entire building and the only thing that's good about it is like a room the size of your bedroom where you meet Chewbacca.
Yeah, in 30 years, that's all that's been good there is meeting Chewbacca.
And if you go back to America Sings, you might say it's all that's been good there in 40 years.
How long are we talking?
50 years?
If you have that perspective.
Mission to Mars, the attraction is replaced by a restaurant.
And the restaurant that it was supposed to be was a Tony Baxter conceived restaurant that was like a Planet Hollywood of all the old Tomorrowland vehicles.
So you could eat in a people mover car or what else?
A rocket jet or an old monorail car or whatever.
It was going to pay tribute to the past and reuse all these things.
But in a clever way, everybody wants to pop into one of those, eat pizza in one of those.
But that got cut and it just became a cafeteria.
Yeah.
Hey, put a pin in those old ride vehicles because they'll come back later on.
They do.
They do have a way to get all that stuff out of the junkyard.
The main thing that happens here is a paint job.
We are going to turn Tomorrowland into Discoveryland via paint.
So everything gets paint that is supposed to be like bronze, gold, dark brown, some emerald green.
And this leads to something that I don't recall if we've ever talked about on the show before.
The brief strange era where Space Mountain was brown.
Yeah.
You guys ever see brown Space Mountain in person?
Not in person.
Not in person, no.
It was really strange.
I saw it.
I went to Discoveryland.
I like the colors of Discoveryland.
It's pretty astounding and they've kept it up.
This looks like, I don't, it's just, it's a very shit brown, right?
Yeah.
It's not gleaming.
It's not gold.
It's shit.
It looks like it literally rusted over.
Or like, it just looks like something's wrong, I guess.
That's really what it is.
It looks like Space Mountain is sick.
Space Mountain is sick.
Or it's like.
It's reverse ET.
ET gets very white when he's dying.
When Space Mountain is dying, it gets un-white.
Well, sick ET Space Mountain is, I've never thought about it like that.
Me neither, yeah.
Yeah, it's just, it looks like, yeah, the park is decayed or something.
It's post-apocalyptic.
Post-apocalypse.
Yeah, yeah.
You found Disneyland 200 years after anyone's been there.
Rust-colored.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's odd.
It was so weird.
It also, I swear, had an effect of making it look smaller.
Like the mountain looked worse.
I believe that.
Yeah, really weird.
I just like, even going by Splash Mountain when seeing it now being changed to Tiana's,
I'm just like so amazed at how much it fooled me, how big I thought it was.
Just taking some of the pieces away from it make me go, oh, wait.
I, in my mind, it's like huge and it's way back.
And if you look at how it is now, you're like, oh, it's much closer than I think it is.
Oh, interesting.
And it's much smaller just because it takes away some of like the whatever laughing place stuff and the whatever.
What do you call them?
Briars, I guess that's what they're saying.
Briar patch, yeah.
So like all that stuff.
So like I would imagine that even changing colors on things sometimes you would now be, oh, wait.
It's not as big as I thought it was.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I guess that log did a lot of heavy lifting at the top of space in terms of like it added an extra 10 or so.
Yeah, it really did.
So yeah, seeing this a different color would be interesting.
Yeah, it was all really weird.
Just like this case of this was the plan.
The plan was some different paint and then a lot of attractions from other places.
Yeah.
And if you just viewed all of this and they're calling it New Tomorrowland, we don't have a lot here that's genuinely new.
And that's why the heat was really on the only genuine new attraction, the brand new e-ticket they were calling it.
Wow.
Rocket rods, the new high speed.
And that's like in this Tomorrowland tradition of inventing types of technology, showing us what the future will hold, why in the future we'll all be driving around in rocket rods.
It actually is sort of like now that some cyber trucks are around, it is like as dumb and clunky as a cyber truck to some extent.
That's true.
Might rather drive a rocket rod around.
That actually, let me bring up that because that's something, okay, that Tony Baxter restaurant where you're going to eat in the vehicles.
The bar at Disney is very high for how cool a new vehicle looks and a futuristic vehicle looks.
The rocket rod itself.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is really, it's just so functional.
It's like kind of an ATV or something.
Yeah, it looks pretty ugly.
Yeah.
Like if I'm being nice, it's somewhere in the world of like, if I'm squinting, we're not that far from like the journey to the center of the earth ride vehicles.
So that's now I'm being, I'm really stretching to even get it there.
But if you see it from a distance, because that's sort of a similar, kind of this odd, long, you know, past but future vehicle.
But like, would you want a toy of rocket rods?
Would you want a toy of rocket rods?
Well, now because of the kitsch factor or the...
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, but no, it's not like a particularly cool vehicle.
If you were judging it against like the Ninja Turtle vehicles, this is not even in the top five or ten.
As you judge everything, as you judge the people in your life against.
Right.
This is not as good as the toilet taxi.
I love my dad, but is he as cool as the toilet taxi?
No, he's not.
There's so much contradictory stuff with Tomorrowland 98 and rocket rods, especially because it's like, it's new.
It's like people mover before us.
It's a potential future transit.
And each vehicle holds as many people as a Toyota Corolla.
Yes, and is like a third as long.
A third as long, and it's heavy.
Like it is heavy and it is destroying the road it's on.
Yeah, yeah, really grinding it up.
And the start stop, don't worry, it's destroying the engine inside of it.
Yeah, it really, God, it really is just a like a self-immolating ride vehicle.
Yeah.
But at least it's whisper quiet.
Actually, no, it is the opposite of whisper quiet.
That was the big thing when these were running.
If you were on it or if you were just in the park, because like no attraction was more present than the people mover.
It's silently going by while you're in the line for star tours or in a shop or something.
Now rocket rods are up and running and it's just, it's somewhere between fireworks and a leaf blower.
These were very industrial, unpleasant sounds.
Watching a few like three or four different ride through videos, I wrote down the note of like these sounds are caustic.
Like this is, I don't like, I don't like hearing this.
And I can't tell because there is some sound effects along the way where I'm like, oh, that's pumped in.
And then I'm like, how is some of these sounds I think are the requirement?
Like this is the sound it makes to move.
If you were on it, there would be fake motor sounds and kind of bleep, bleep, bleep, bleep, bleep.
But if you, yeah, you know that they were real sounds because you would hear it so loud if you weren't on it.
So now you're in Tomorrowland. You're just walking around.
So what do we do next? I don't know.
Maybe we head over to Dumbo.
Just like so jar and which and the fact that we kind of like shake the tracks is so you're like you're in a war zone.
Now Tomorrowland, this is, this is, this is a future in which a war is going on and like I assume these things are armed.
I assume there's cannons in the front. Yeah. Oh, but they don't work.
They don't work consistently for the opponent. They don't.
Yeah. Is there anything?
What's the most annoying like sound a ride makes when you're not on?
Like, is Autopia the answer to this?
Like when you're like, I'm walking around to be here.
You're like, it's like kind of unpleasant.
Is there something that beats that?
Maybe depending on where you are when you're like on the universal tram or waiting for the universal.
Just be given that it is like a, you know, actual heavy duty motor.
Yeah, maybe.
You know, like a poorly kept up, you know, like a drop tower ride.
Yeah, they do that like hiss and then the launch and then they don't really make a sound when you're bouncing down.
The Magic Mountain Superman ride sounds horrible.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, but Magic Mountain in general.
Yeah, that's a different category.
They aren't concerned with noise pollution.
You'll get all sorts of interesting noises in Magic Mountain.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, it's Magic Mountain is just a chorus of irritating hydraulics and then people go in like, fuck you.
He's screaming at a Tweety Bird.
He's screaming at his life size Tweety Bird.
Fuck you. Birds aren't big.
He won the Tweety Bird and now he's spent all day cursing at it.
I'm going to pretend this is my mom.
I'm going to do this what I wish I could do to my mom.
Well, Magic, well, we could do a whole Final Four of Magic Mountain.
Unpleasant ride noises.
Yeah. Yeah. The worst. Yeah. Yeah.
The worst real sounds that I actually hear.
This is this is going to lead me to it to a Final Four thing.
I'm going to play here now that all the pieces are in place.
Right. And we've said what they have.
And this this kind of shows you why they needed a new attraction, a thrilling attraction and why they could.
So that Disney could do kind of a like aiming at 11 year olds, almost Six Flags esque commercial.
Right. This is how they presented New Tomorrowland back in 98.
If you think the coke machine is cool, you can see the rest of the place.
If that was probably pretty indiscernible to a listener.
Yeah. But here's a whole other thing.
This. OK. Tomorrow. We got a new Tomorrowland.
What do we want to feature first?
Well, we have a coke machine that shoots coke out from that launches it up into the air and then a cast member grabs it.
Right. You guys know this was there.
No. Launching Cokes. I think they might still have this.
Do you mean it works?
I mean, I saw a recent like like YouTube short showing one of these.
Really? I think you can launch your soda.
If you want to get your soda real shaken up, if you want to drop nine dollars on your soda and then lose half of it to bubbles bursting out.
How would that not have happened by now?
We got a soda launched at us or in the air.
I mean, like that.
I feel like we've I've had a soda in Tomorrowland a few times.
Have you ever had a soda launched to you?
I don't think so.
Well, it's not at you.
It's up in the air for the cast member to catch.
Right. You watch a soda launch show.
This is one of their genuinely actually looking back now.
This might have been their biggest attraction in the most successful one.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a way if it remains listener.
Have you seen the soda launch?
Where can we find the soda?
Let's find the soda next time.
So it's like a rocket.
The Coke is a rocket.
Yeah. Yeah.
So they do have rocket Cokes.
You got to give them that.
Here's what else they have.
Tomorrowland is now at Disneyland.
You can go 3D with honey and shrunky audience.
Blast off on rocket ride.
A unique experience in speed.
Wow. Exactly.
The new Tomorrowland is now at Disneyland.
Windblown kids.
Wow.
It is.
It's like a surge commercial.
Or like, yeah, like you said, like a Six Flags commercial.
Yeah. They're going for extreme.
There's a little bit of fish on it.
Yeah.
The on the rocket rides.
Which shows you how much they're pushing it.
And like a honey and shrunk the audience is kind of secondary to that.
And here's what I wanted to bring up.
I had an idea and I was like, let me just workshop this on the show.
Yeah.
See if you like it.
We didn't do a final four this year.
We were doing the saga or taking a break from the saga.
I had an idea for one and maybe this is obscure.
Maybe there's a mini one on the second gate or something.
But here's my idea.
The frequent footage final four.
What this would be is a competition.
We all watch a lot of Disney specials and parades and ancillary material.
This would be the ultimate showdown of the footage that they show you all the time.
We're talking Walt pointing at the big map.
Oh, right.
We're talking Walt's given opening day speech.
A lot of Walt.
We're talking Walt stepping on the train tracks and like pointing out where they're going to be.
We're talking Mickey on top of Spaceship Earth.
We're talking making it look like the big lion is coming out of the screen in honey and shrunk the audience.
Fozzy with the big pie.
I don't know if anything comes to mind for you guys in terms of frequent footage.
Wouldn't we like to know what is the best frequent footage?
There must be a reused family reacting of mom, dad and 2.5 kids going like, oh, probably being startled by something pretty low key.
Yeah, I think if we thought about it, I feel like there's also things where like in the foreground, there's like a fire eater and then it like zooms past the fire eater into whatever fun.
Yeah.
Or like Indiana Jones with the map and then he closes the map and then heads into the temple.
Oh, I got a good one.
Tower of Terror guests.
Oh, yeah.
Standing.
Terrifying a generation of neurotic children.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then like the arrow pointing to the floor is going haywire.
And the footage of like just the hydraulics, like just the mechanics of it and dropping way faster than the ride.
That's really good.
I feel like if we put our minds to it.
Well, let me I'm just throwing this to listen.
I'm not married to this idea, but I figured I'd workshop it here.
If you like that, if you want to hear the frequent footage final four or submit ideas for the frequent final four, because I think we have to know how far would Walt on the train with the stuffed Mickey waving it with his hand, like peering out Ronald Reagan.
Yeah.
Like there's a lot of, you know, that's why I'm like maybe this is second gate because this is really like this is for this is this is like a fellow travelers kind of idea.
We all know.
Yeah.
If you're listening and you know what I'm talking about, then you're as versed in it as we are.
Footage of the parade with the big inflatables.
The big inflatable like when it was the Mardi Gras.
Yeah, the Mardi Gras kind of thing.
Yeah.
I'm sure if we put our minds to it, there's a lot.
It's gonna be very 90s tape heavy.
Yeah.
This is when the media explode.
This is when it went from like we've made.
We made three Disney World specials through all of the 1970s.
Right.
We produce 300 hours every year.
Yeah.
Some of its parades on TV, some of its specials, some of its vacation planning VHS.
You know, I don't know if this is frequent enough, but this footage that I really like from downtown Disney where there's a guy playing.
There's like a guy alone playing a saxophone on cobblestones and there's a Mickey spotlight that he's standing under.
I don't know.
I know.
I guess that's familiar.
I imagine Pleasure Island footage.
It's got to be.
Specifically.
A bunch of fireworks going off.
Yeah.
Like helicopter shot.
There's probably like two parents dancing that they use.
Yeah, that's what I'm imagining.
Yeah.
Dutch angles of the neon sign of each sign of each club.
Definitely.
Yeah.
I think we'd get there.
And listeners, I really would.
If there's, if you've got one in your head and you know you've seen, there might even just be like the one shot of Rex like waving from, like there was, there's a lot of footage or the same audience all like swaying when you go into the Death Star.
Yeah.
I think it's definitely an area.
Oh yeah.
Summit plummet.
Both in the two, like someone who all nervous in the tube and then outside of it with the water shoot.
Yeah.
Like you see the water spraying.
Similarly Splash Mountain, but the camera does a thing where, and Jurassic Park at the right, where it makes it look like there goes the thing and then it looks like it goes upside down.
Like the camera, the POV goes all the way the other way.
Also scaring neurotic children.
So, well, there we go.
Let us know feelings about that.
Yeah, that's a good avenue.
Anyways, and to bring up somebody who might factor into frequent footage Final Four, I was somewhat upset to discover the answer of who in the world wanted a faster people mover.
And I will now read this quote as a type a person.
I wanted something faster than the people mover quotes Michael Eisner CEO and chairman of the Walt Disney Company.
So this is one of those misguided.
This is why we need the time machine.
I guess it does drive to him because he, we know this.
We know that he was as CEOs are he's a Steve Jobs type.
I have a big idea.
I'm going to drop this into the room and then leave and then assume in three months that you figured out the very difficult to pull off idea.
I would say he, you know, was a more for good version of that than a lot of CEOs are and better ideas specifically within it than other CEOs that said this was not one of them.
Although is well, hang on.
Well, that's what I think.
But we're going to make the same point.
Maybe like it doesn't have to be done this way.
That's it's the thought exercise because when you hear it a fast using those tracks for now a high speed ride is not the craziest thing in the world.
That kind of sounds good, right?
Yeah, I just track why I like it could.
It didn't have to be like they could have added to track like they could have.
There's other versions of it.
You potentially could have made work in a better way than than just dumping a fast thing on the existing track.
Yeah.
I know that's kind of what he was thinking, but which is giving him some credit.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, that's what happens.
And maybe maybe it's worth going into the end of the history here a little bit.
So, yeah, the notion was not slow moving little tour on the people mover, something fast and thrilling and for the teens.
But it's also they start planning something.
It's not like maybe you found some of this, Jason.
This this all was information from the season pass podcast when they talked to Tony Baxter.
But I don't know that I really heard this, that the original pitch was something called fast track.
Fast track was the notion here.
And this was happening concurrently with test track.
And this is to be sponsored by General Motors, the very same sponsor.
So with a sponsor, you've got money.
They're already in it on this other thing.
The long working relationship thanks to World of Motion.
And this is where it gets frustrating is hearing Tony's description of what this could have been designed to be three times the budget they ended up getting.
Rocket Rides was a wire frame vehicle at night.
They were all to glow.
And one of them did.
We had one on the track and it looked so great.
It looked like a dimensional wire frame design come to life.
Tronish, I'm assuming.
I bet Tronish and kind of predating that second version of test track.
And mainly communicate.
It was going to communicate something.
The idea that at least at night that you would understand that you're looking at a blueprint that came to life moving around.
Because as what ended up happening was it's just these like big weird clunkers.
They don't seem like anything.
But like, OK, that's something.
I see what this could have been.
Also, would you believe it was all this stuff?
Guests would visit a design center where they would customize their vehicles and the attraction would capture a photo of them riding in their design.
It was going to affect the colors.
And now it would all all of that stuff, all the stuff the test track ended up doing in the second round.
Right. And it seems maybe I miss.
Remember, it was it supposed to be affecting the lights and the colors on the actual vehicles because test track does or did this.
And it was unspectacular because you would just get like kind of a mocked up photo of it at the end.
Yeah. Yeah.
But would this actually affect the exterior of the vehicle?
Because that's actually a really cool idea.
If you like, I want a purple vehicle and it's got orange stripes on it.
And then you would see that from the from like down.
I don't I don't know.
And if you have somebody, if your mom didn't go on it, she could see what your vehicle looked like.
She could take a photo that would not turn out well at all because it's night.
Right. Of course.
And with a lot of difference in light.
But you would see all the vehicles would be the very least.
You would see all the vehicles be different and unique that everyone.
And now we're in more backing over territory where the colors are different.
Yeah. Autopia.
Or here comes a red one.
Here comes that orange one.
Cool idea if that wasn't what they were planning.
Maybe I don't know.
I don't have that.
There's not enough. Yeah.
I can't remember that because I heard this interview.
But we need to talk to him again.
But I mean, that's yeah, that sounds really great.
And now it's like, yeah, every guest shows it.
And now we're in the realm of Indiana Jones where you like the experience is customized
and a little bit different every time.
That's something.
That's pretty good.
But here's what happened across the country.
Test track.
We've talked about test track.
Test track was a big mess.
Right.
Like testing went very badly.
They delayed it a bunch of times.
And apparently General Motors was so worn down by this process that they're like,
you're on your own with that other one.
We're not doing another one.
Finish up this track.
And then that is the end of this.
So they pull out.
Now there is not money to make the vehicles glow.
Well, that's OK.
Right.
Because we'll still be able to make a cool high speed attraction.
Yeah. Well, about that.
And then here is the real killer that they can't bank the turns on this.
They have to use the literal same track.
This is a high speed roller coaster type ride with no banked turns.
And it kind of serves as a living illustration of why curves need to be banked.
Can we define banking?
Because I kept seeing this and I couldn't quite picture what it meant in my head.
Like turning the track?
Yeah.
It's angling it.
Angling it.
And this was very helpful that Tony illustrated this in Credit to Season Pass again.
He says, we all knew the track needed to be banked in order to keep the speed up.
Once you made the reduction to go with the level of the people mover track,
so that never banks at any point.
That's just glad.
It had to slow down to take each curve.
That was to keep you from flying out.
Now that's a very interesting little physics lesson.
If the rocket rods didn't slow down,
like gravity would want to take the people just like out into the right.
I guess, yeah.
It's really weird.
It's interesting.
Okay, yeah.
So banked turns are in order to keep the speed going.
You can do just a straightaway fast, but then at some point you have to turn.
So that's the idea.
So they would have had to like, maybe they could have kept some of the infrastructure,
but at least the turns they had to.
And now if you start thinking about that track, it's all turns.
Yeah, constantly.
Constantly, yes.
It goes around the round building, Space Mountain.
It goes around the round building, the Carousel Theater.
Yeah.
Nothing but turns.
This thing is all turns, and it had to be slow.
The new high speed ride has to be slow way more often than it's fast.
That's why.
I would have been like, I guess you could just put the new vehicle on the track
and then just do the test track thing and build another section of it
that's new track to go fast at the end.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Oh, you do it like test track.
Right.
That at least you still get the people mover experience.
You don't have to put in a new track in that part.
That's true.
But then you can find, I don't know where it would go exactly.
You could still even keep it like a little tour as you go.
Right.
So you can actually enjoy seeing the star speeder in that room.
You can still do the projection tunnel.
And then at the end, you just get a big ...
Because that's all anybody ... I mean, this is going to be blasphemous,
but that's all anyone cares about in test track.
Let's be honest.
No.
People don't like demonstration to precision tires.
Some people like it.
I know they're going to be mad at me, but that's all I ever care.
Not Radiator Springs.
Yes.
No.
That's a slow tour through Radiator Springs.
That's got a bunch of fun stuff.
Yeah.
And then you go fast at the end.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
They could rebuild the last chunk.
They could have rebuilt the last chunk of it, Mike, to do what you're saying.
I mean, they rebuilt the monorail track, God knows how many times.
Yeah.
I don't know where it would go.
I'd have to look at it.
Yeah, I don't either.
Maybe this will be part of my pitch for tomorrow.
I don't know that they have rebuilt them.
At least the layout has remained the same, the monorail track.
Haven't they moved?
I think they have tried to not move the monorail as often as possible.
Yeah.
I think actually, and I could be wrong about this, but in my head, the route that it takes
through California Adventure and then back to where it lands, what used to be the hotel,
I think they've kept it roughly the same because they want to not move.
That's major heavy duty pylons.
Yeah, that's tough.
I mean, it's never, it hasn't shortened, right, around Autopians?
I don't know.
That big, long, that too long kind of-
It takes a long, yeah, really like a helicopter landing or something.
No, I think they've probably removed parts of it but then reinstalled it where it was,
I think.
You might be right.
I actually, because I think that, yeah, park and downtown Disney changes have all sort
of happened around the, they've tried to not blow up the monorail because that's a big
expense.
But it is interesting then, that idea, they couldn't have tried not to, I guess they did
try to not change the people mover track.
That's what they had to do.
I don't think it changed at all.
Yeah.
It's a problem and it's still a problem.
It's still there and I always thought like, you know, you always hear, oh, they can't
just reopen the people mover.
You can't reopen the people mover.
I always thought it was because of OSHA regulations because there are parts in that first section
where you can just kind of touch the walls and if they had left the people mover, it
would have been grandfathered and I realize Rocket Rods did so much wear and tear on this
track.
Yeah, it really wore down-
It destroyed it.
Yeah.
Yes.
Because when you have the, and this is where it all, it just all emanates from that initial
decision of let's try to do all this on the cheap, all of Tomorrowland and this attraction
especially.
Like, you know how we save money?
We don't bank the turns.
That's what we do.
Well, it ends up costing the money in the long run because now it's a ride that has
to slow down and then speed up again constantly and in kind of an erratic way.
So there's parts of a track that we're not expecting to have like a, all right, now like
really heavy cars are going to like and like maybe stall a little bit in this area.
So thus like plasters starts falling down onto, I think there were situations like this
where like pieces of that track were falling down on our nearest.
Yeah.
And it's not, it is like, it is old building, old infrastructure now is having like an
earthquake every five minutes that it has not been prepared for.
It's not been built for essentially.
No reinforcements whatsoever.
Right.
Like I don't know if this thing's going to make it through an earthquake.
You worried about that?
Not only that, we're going to do our own earthquakes here all day, every day.
Yeah.
Every few minutes, not even every few hours, every few minutes.
Ten earthquakes and it will be as loud and annoying as earthquakes are.
This is again, this is contradictions because it's like every now and then, like when you
said, the CEO comes in, droughts a big idea and you figure it out.
That sometimes ends up with something interesting.
Sure.
Or like working within restrictions ends up with something interesting.
But there's so many confusing parts of this of like, oh, Euro Disney, you know, it ate
up all our money.
So it severely restricted the budget for this.
Well, okay, we're going to do this tomorrow land like the one at Euro Disney.
Well, wait, wasn't it?
That's a contract.
You just said it lost a bunch of money.
Well, this was an ecstatic victory, though, but you mostly are going to have the money
for paint.
Yeah.
The money's got to go to pit.
What are we going to do?
What are we supposed to do?
Not paint Space Mountain Brown.
The audience has been loud and clear on this.
They want Space Mountain Brown.
Yeah.
They don't care if the ride, they'll be fine with a ride that slows down all the time.
Where if you watch that ad that I played earlier, that's something I didn't say about is that
like, you know, rev up on the all new Ragged Rides.
And then it like it's you watch that initial launch, which is exciting.
And it's funny.
When do they cut?
When do they cut away from the excited teens?
Maybe exactly where the curve and and that's true in all of it.
If you watch like press footage, they did like a CD-ROM press kit and all of the footage
ends precisely at the point where it does the very first curve, thus indicating that
this is not a truly high speed ride.
It also starts by doing kind of an odd looking wheelie.
I guess in theory it's a wheelie, but it's such an odd looking thing.
It's like, oh, is it supposed to be doing that?
Is it wheelie or is it problem?
Is it unbuckling at the top?
Is it starting to come loose?
Is it going to flip over all the way?
Right.
No, initially it did wheelies because that's what like maybe we need to pick up at the
premise.
What is a rocket?
What does this phrase mean?
Because they're kind of, once it's up and around, they're like, it's like a race car
of the future and Mario Andretti is going to ride in it when we open it.
So it's a race car and that's why it does a wheelie.
So in the future, you will be in future race cars that will get you.
But then what's a rod?
How much did that cost?
How much did it cost?
Rod is what they're going for.
Yeah, I guess.
I assume.
Okay.
Rocket rod.
But how is this a viable public transportation solution?
How are we all going to be?
It takes a lot of muster to ride in a super fast race car.
How do you like this?
This can't be how we get down to the civic center.
Yeah, no, we can't.
It doesn't even look cool.
Even if it was unrealistic, as we said earlier, it's both not practical and uncool and too
loud and too loud.
Like it should be if it's a rocket rod, it should look like the neutrinos and Ninja Turtles
car, which is like a flying hot rod car.
I don't know if you guys remember this.
They had a toy to the villains.
Actually, it was a villainous toy, but it was like a it was like a old car and then the
wheels would like fold up into it and fly like that's like a cool space hot rod or
something that you would want to go on this.
It doesn't look like a rocket rod because I think you would know if it was like an old
time car that could fly, you would know exactly what a rocket rod is and what it was supposed
to be.
Wait a minute.
I'm remembering something.
There is another history and maybe that's what this is, but there's probably some other
episode.
Maybe like Unbuilt Tomorrowlands is kind of the idea here.
But I believe in Tokyo, there was something that is much closer to what you're describing
where there's still like kind of a 50s thing, right?
50s but future.
I think and maybe this was rocket bikes.
I don't know.
I think Tokyo had something that's pretty close to what you're saying.
Interesting.
Where like it's fun now.
Well, you know where we are.
We're in the Dexter Jetstar area.
I didn't say it.
But I thought it.
Yeah.
My man.
Am I right about it?
I'll try to figure out Rocket Bikes Tokyo.
But that's the name.
That's like the name is bad name because it doesn't it's not showing you what the name
is.
Like you're right.
Rock Rod is like you have to represent 60s.
Right.
You got to represent whatever the song shut down by the Beach Boys was about.
But there's no 60s to it.
Yeah.
It's just a big clunky thing where you really see that engine.
By the way, it's just like you really that's a very present.
Just make it makes it so industrial.
But like yeah.
And other things you're like where do they hide the mechanism on this thing?
Like you see it.
You really see it.
It looks like a go kart.
If it explodes.
Yeah.
Sometimes you see the service vehicle on the monorail track at Disneyland.
Yes.
Which looks like almost like the hobo car on a train track to some degree.
But this looks like a service vehicle more than it does an actual ride vehicle to me.
It's like a thing that would push a train that's broken.
Yeah.
Right.
Send a rocket right out to fix a people mover.
Yeah.
That's just the way it doesn't.
It doesn't convey fun to me.
It looks like some sort of completely functional vehicle like just perfunctory vehicle that just like sends a maintenance worker out.
I was correct that there were there was Tomorrowland was going to become or at least part of it was going to become sci fi city.
And there were going to be and it looks like flying kind of hot rod things.
Interesting.
This is good.
I mean maybe you know maybe that's the other episode.
It's right unbuilt.
But that might group enough together.
But as for the one that was built and built on a budget, something we haven't talked about is the queue.
And I have very strong memories of the queue.
Did I say that I did this?
Yeah.
And another thing that hasn't been said is that as far as those blank areas in the non locks and Tomorrowland circle vision theater was one of them.
And a circle vision became the line for this.
It became the queue for rocket rods.
So a former attraction is now a line.
I was thinking like when I started looking up videos and like posts and stuff, I was like, man, what was the queue for that?
I've never quite understood it because I know you entered at Buzz Lightyear.
But where did you get the answer was anywhere Buzz Lightyear is end up in a circle vision and then go through a tunnel to then go upstairs.
That is correct.
Yeah. So the door that you still would use for Buzz Lightyear, that was like the same thing.
That was the pre show of circle vision.
Circle vision became after this, it became the bulk of the Buzz Lightyear ride.
And then, yeah, then you would have to like go through a very dark and claustrophobic tunnel that would get you down to the bottom of that tower to get you to the loading area.
So instead of because you used to have remember it's still that way in Disney World that it's those little speed ramps.
You go up a nice little ramp and now I'm instead you got to go under it.
Now I'm under the earth.
And I remember being in there and like that's what they figured out.
This is so weird.
And by the time that you're at that point, the narrowest area with the least entertainment, you have probably been in this room for at least an hour.
This was a punishing line.
This was crazy.
Maybe 90, maybe two hours.
There is a great video online and I started watching it and I was like, what account is this?
And then I started laughing because the answer was a longtime theme park designer, David Cobb, had he he is YouTube is calling like an archive because he just digitizes like his like videos and just put up like 30, 40 minutes of going around the islands of adventure construction areas.
When he was working on Men in Black, Alien Attack.
And you ran, I believe, as I recall, you rented out a theater to to watch that.
Well, now there's this cinemadome is empty right now.
You know, there's some real cinema here.
But Cobb's old movies.
He records the queue.
He's with someone and they're in the Circle vision.
And I believe it's person he's with goes.
We've been in line for about two hours now.
We've seen this Circle vision movie about three times because it is such a weird looking room.
They were only using all of the screens occasionally.
And the main cue part is so it looks so cheap.
It's so dark.
Yeah.
And they're playing old Disney like Walt stuff or old Tomorrowland footage.
That's fine.
But then there's old ride vehicles.
They paint it wireframes over.
It's just well, that's yeah, that's where that idea came in.
And also Tony Baxter's notion of could we use the old vehicles in some way?
So, you know, you have a couple of things you have like here's literal blueprints.
You're almost supposed to be in the Imagineering Lab or they're dreaming of new futuristic.
So you've got like here's blueprints for a Space Mountain sled.
That's what they're called.
Never knew that.
The Nautilus submarine, the Mark III monorail and then a rocket rod.
Then you've got actual big vehicles like a monorail or a rocket jet or a submarine.
But they're all there.
Now they are painted like living blueprints.
So mostly blue and then with like orange electrical tape.
And by Tony's own admission, this thing was so bootstrapped that it was like him doing it.
And all the other guys were like, we got to turn this into something.
We can't just like open this up and it's an empty room.
All right, everybody put some tape on this thing.
So it's like it's Tony hand making.
Yeah, yeah.
It's so sad that it came to that.
But he tried.
He tried for us.
He did try.
It is an interesting experiment.
There is also at some point there is like a board that says future expansions, like future stations.
And it has both Angel Stadium and the hockey arena listed as a future station.
It's really confused.
This piece, this I like a lot actually.
I mean, I'd buy like a poster of this that shows you all the places where the rocket rods might go.
Right now, you're in the central terminal, but it might go to Innoventions someday.
Oh good.
It might go to, what's that?
Might.
Might, maybe, maybe.
It might go to Disney's California Adventure before it opened.
This I kind of like that it's like a nod.
And there's little symbols representing these things.
And California Adventure is represented by an orange.
That's cute.
The orange was the symbol of the park.
I like the big orange.
We haven't done an episode about the big orange.
We know you like the big.
He's talking about the big orange.
Yeah, I like the big orange.
There was some point.
You wish it was there instead.
There was some point in like 2015, 2016 or so where I was like, should I go back to the big orange?
And I was like, oh, it's gone.
You thought for a second the orange was there?
For a second I thought the orange was there.
And I'm like, well, Silly Symphony Swings is a better experience.
But I'm like, kind of like the big orange.
Is that where you sometimes like you had like a dream where you were in high school again.
You wake up and you go, oh, my test is.
Oh, I'm not in high school anymore.
You forgot the big orange.
Yeah, but it was a waking dream.
Oh, OK.
I was like, did they take away the big orange?
I see.
Did they take away the Malibu?
Oh, they did.
Yeah.
And then a single tear rolled down your cheek.
Single.
Yeah.
A poor one out for the Malibu.
Some of they'll be like, Jason, you're going to a better place.
It's a place that still has the big orange.
You'll see as many big oranges as you'd ever want.
But the queue, the wire frame, you could kind of see that it's like, well, they were trying something.
They tried.
They tried to make this something.
Even like you could tell it's like, what is it now?
All right.
It's like we're experimenting with a mass transit.
Come on.
Is that anything?
Maybe that's something.
It'll take you to the beach.
You'll go to the beach on a rocket rod.
Rocket rod.
What a beautiful Los Angeles where you take a, you ruin everyone's time.
But when a rocket rod pulls up, kicks up a bunch of sand.
Gasoline on your shoes somehow.
Scares a bunch of seagulls.
They all shit and fear onto families.
If it doesn't bank, it shoots a lot of the humans out of the vehicle.
It throws them from the vehicle.
What a wonderful piece of technology.
Experience Los Angeles by getting tossed onto its curbs.
There is, okay, it's not the exact, we were talking about the repeated footage,
but there is a lot of the genre of people just off the ride going home.
It's great.
You go so fast.
Oh, I loved it.
You know, that is a certain type.
That could be its own Final Four.
It's just people going like, this was a trip.
Oh, I had such a good time.
Best reactions.
Yeah.
Or just saying the name.
Rocket rods!
You don't have anything to say.
Can you just yell rocket rods?
Can all ten of you teens yell, when you're done clowning around,
just yell rocket rods and we'll just keep rolling and do whatever after that.
We'll never be done clowning around, bitch.
Okay.
All right.
Well, here's your ticket for free Coke and you can go on your way.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, give me five more.
Okay.
Here's six.
You didn't do what I told you.
You're going to die.
But so, yeah, it is really weird.
It's a, you know, we got some stuff.
They're using like old.
They've showed some of the Timekeeper movie in the Circle Vision.
They're keeping you entertained.
We gave you 20 minutes of footage that will loop seven times.
And then you go through a very dark tunnel.
I don't remember the handicapped access situation here.
It's so weird.
And if you were claustrophobic, this was a lot of problems.
A lot of problems.
Also, it seemed like people were just kind of ambling about
or sitting on the floor of that Circle Vision.
Like it seemed like.
Yeah, probably.
It seemed like in movies, you know,
it seemed like in a Jurassic World or American Godzilla
where everyone's just kind of shaking off what just happened.
And like the National Guard is trying to usher people.
Everyone's in the solar blankets.
Yeah, everyone's got solar blankets on.
Central casting member.
It's like they have the Band-Aid on their head.
And they're trying to make a meal of, oh.
Can somebody do balloon animals?
Can we cheer up people in here?
Yeah, yeah, that's the vibe.
No, people needed therapy after making it through this line.
But yeah, the buildup was like insane.
You're just like, boy, is this going to be.
And then it's a little hard to talk about this ride experience.
We've alluded to it.
But yeah, you know, you if you're there in the first two months,
you get a fun, fast launch with a confusing wheelie.
And then you slow down right away and you go into star tours.
And then it is just like speed, not speed, speed, not speed.
But then you get into like, you know,
imagine now you're in like utopia area where you're a little more free.
And here's what I remember is that like, all right, we're not.
We're not curving as much here.
We're getting some straightaway like that area and it's open.
And you're not just in weird.
You watch those ride throughs and you're really like, this is just.
This is like a industrial hallway.
This is like see cracks in the.
And then you're like, well,
wouldn't have been cool if they had like kept that tron tunnel.
And then you're going super speed through the trunk.
No, no, took that out.
That's gone. No more of that.
In fact, sometimes you can just look into an active construction site.
Yeah.
Because this open before all.
Well, I was going to say all of intervention.
Like there's footage of people going through what will become interventions,
but it wasn't ready yet.
Oh, so it's just work lights.
Half on my God.
And there was, there was something.
Did you catch them?
You might, you saw it in person, the mirror at early on.
There's a moment where.
When it would look into one of the buildings where they just put in a giant mirror.
So it looked like you're about to hit another,
that trick where it looks like another car is coming at you.
But then you start to slow down.
So the effect doesn't really work.
You know,
God,
how did imagine the morale?
Imagine being Tony and you know,
this has come to pass and you're like,
yeah, we lost that one and we know,
and they knew they knew this was not going to be,
there's people,
like there's bean counters going,
it's going to be fine.
It's actually,
it's a little bit different.
It's kind of predictable that a roller coaster would just go faster and faster.
The longer you were on it.
This,
this is a crazy,
you know,
this,
this is a loose cannon ride.
We don't know what's going to happen.
I almost think it would have been cheaper to redo this Tomorrowland with a scaled down
Tomorrowland 94 theme.
Sure.
Yeah.
Just repeat some stuff,
repeat some elements.
Yeah,
sure.
That's why the people mover technically is different in Florida.
So they wouldn't have been able to clone that.
Like they wouldn't have been able to just change the ride vehicles.
Just keep the old ones then.
Just keep the old,
because if they had left Tomorrowland alone,
that white mid-century aesthetic would have come into fashion again.
Yep.
And they would have been able to milk the nostalgia bucks.
It still looked a little,
it wouldn't look,
it would look old though.
The way that it looked back then.
It was very,
it was very eighties and I'm fond of it.
And they've kept the elements that still work,
like the neon Mickey's,
but it was kind of a hodgepodge.
But then they just put in a new hodgepodge.
It still has that rocket.
Yeah.
I'm not saying it's good.
I'm just saying the aesthetic,
even if you look at the old photos,
I'm like,
it's still,
the aesthetic has come back around.
It just looks old.
It would look old now.
I'm not saying it's better or worse.
I'm just saying,
I don't know if they could have done nothing
and it would still have,
I mean, I guess maybe it would be right.
It would have been better,
but it would still feel old.
It would still feel tired.
They've tried to change Tomorrowland in Florida
where it's like,
oh, let's replace that busy sign
with more minimalist sign.
Yeah.
Let's take out some of the neon green and purple
and some of the fins.
And I'm like,
I think it looks chintzy or like,
why did you take that all out?
Yeah.
They really can't,
I mean, what they're aiming for now
is neither here nor there.
They just, yeah,
they need to like really pick a new aesthetic
to all this and stick to it.
Yeah.
Here's,
let me get to this though,
is that at the end,
you know,
there's kind of like a pure tunnel that's,
like the Matterhorn is on the right of you
and you're kind of up above the queue of the rocket rods.
And at this point,
you actually do pick up some speed.
You are going pretty straight.
You get hit with a strobe light
and a blast of air.
And that's one of the last things that happens.
And I don't know,
I was 13.
I was not a thrilled junkie
and I'm still not now.
But around that point,
I was like,
it's actually kind of all right.
You know what?
That little part,
I didn't expect the hit of air.
I didn't expect the,
and then you get one more little straight away
before you finish it out.
It like,
it actually,
I think it closed with its best stuff,
which still sounds very chintzy.
I'm still,
I'm describing like haunted house stuff.
Right.
But it was at least,
it was like a little bit of a jump at the end.
My,
I've alluded to this like,
this might be an insane opinion.
I mean,
I'll at least land at this.
I liked it enough to not call it the worst ride they ever did.
Still in your memory.
Yeah.
And I don't,
now I can't,
I'm not fully qualified to say,
I didn't go on superstar limo.
I,
I don't know.
I got enough of a little charge out of it
that even with all of this,
I was kind of,
I,
at the time I was kind of like,
rock n' roll is not so bad.
Yeah.
Well,
I can't,
cause I didn't go on it.
So I'll never fully know,
but it's a lot of the stuff surrounding the building of this
and the failure of Tomorrowland at this time
does get attached to the rocket rods as well.
Yeah.
Well,
it's like,
it's the nerve center of the entire thing.
Yeah.
And the nerve center shut down.
And the fact that the track is just sitting there
makes it worse.
And like,
now if that had been just like track ripped out
or in,
or they just replaced it with something,
maybe it would be like,
oh yeah,
rocket rods.
But rocket rods now has such a connotation to
the epic failure of Disneyland.
When obviously like there were more unpleasant rides,
the flying saucers famously didn't work.
Stuff that I'm sure was less fun to actually go on
than rocket rods,
which might've been a bit frustrating because of the bank,
the slowdowns.
Yeah.
But of course going faster on Tomorrowland
to some degree would be fun.
Yeah.
There's at least some fast.
Some fast happen.
I mean,
to me,
no question,
rocket rods better than current journey into imagination.
Oh, interesting.
I'm declaring that for my personal taste.
Well, like that's another thing though,
cause what came before was so much better.
It's hard not to compare it and really hate the new version
or dislike a lot of the things in the new version.
I think though,
that even if I didn't know the original,
maybe even more so like,
okay, what is this?
I know nothing.
It's called journey into imagination.
Yeah.
And a shrill dragon looks like a skunk
and then it has a buzzer.
I'll say this.
I've never been on rocket rods,
but it's better than mission space.
Ooh.
People are going to be mad about that,
but that's,
I really don't like mission space.
You're not,
my opinion wouldn't be far from you,
but I would notch mission space up
because like better place making,
better videos,
Gary Sinise despite my issues with Gary Sinise
and grappling over the daddy award.
I still,
there's enough like production.
That's all,
you're right about all that,
but I find the actual ride so unpleasant
that I bet I would say,
I would rather go on rocket rods than mission space.
Yeah.
You're right.
The building is cool
and all that stuff surrounding it is cool,
but the actual ride itself,
I'm sure it was way more fun.
Is your choice mission space,
you think of worse,
at least Disney?
I think so.
Yeah.
I just,
especially doing the hard,
the one that's tougher on your brain,
I just like left it like disoriented
and like claustrophobic.
Yeah.
I think I might still go,
unless there's something I'm forgetting,
I might go current journey.
Jason, you got a thought?
I don't know.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think on this.
Mission space is a good one.
Rocket rods is just so much.
I keep thinking about how they took out a people eater,
the people mover,
like people mover was a people eater.
Yes.
It was people eater
and it just never had too long of a weight.
Florida has a little bit of a long weight
occasionally nowadays,
but it feels like people mover
never had too long of a weight
and it also added a huge line attraction.
Like it added a huge weight.
Yeah.
That's all true.
The effect you do not want operationally.
But pure fun of the experience.
Because what I'm saying is I'm shocked
and as much as I wanted to like get into
the confusing and irritating history of this thing,
and the line was horrible,
the line was awful to be in,
but I came out of it still a little bit
like notching this right up higher than I thought that I would.
So I'm like in terms of things you've been on,
just like the experience itself,
forget any context,
do you have a knee-jerk of like,
man, I hate being on this.
It would be cool to race around the railroad track at Disneyland.
It would be cool.
It would be cool, especially at night.
Yes. Yeah.
If they were like, oh yeah, by the way,
now you go like 50 miles an hour around the train tracks at Disneyland.
I go, I'm interested in doing that.
Yeah, yeah.
So I can see, yeah,
there would be fun elements of this.
Yeah, it's a bullet train now.
Still use train tracks, it's a bullet train.
Yeah, and I wouldn't have been so precious about it
at the time of like, oh, the people movers going on.
Like now, of course, it's a blasphemous thing to do,
get rid of the people mover,
but at the time I was like, yeah, cool, faster, great.
I was for it then, yeah, too.
I just didn't know it was going to be this.
If they said we're making every ride at Disney
25 miles per hour faster,
I would have been for it.
Every ride is going to go faster the summer at Disneyland.
We're turning up the juice on everything.
And I'd be like, hell yeah, let's do this.
Well, because you're hoping that like when they do that,
they'll put the chili peps back in, you know?
Well, I'm hoping.
I'm hoping for all.
You get an appropriate soundtrack.
Chili Peppers took over two rides at Disneyland
15 or 20 years ago.
I'm hoping for all the rides at Disneyland one year.
You want full discography.
Full chili pepper.
No repeats of songs, every single.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Yep, so every ride will have a chili peppers song on it
for a summer, that's my hope.
Pirates of the Caribbean, you just hear,
by the way, seven times.
Yes.
Don't interact with the song whatsoever.
Yeah.
Yeah, on the first drive.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just a lot of like long intros too.
Like jam.
There'll be live tracks where they like kind of jam out an intro.
Sure.
It's a small world has just has a four minute fleet bass solo.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Because you've got to get it's an eight minute ride or something.
So how are you going to get that length that song?
Chilly summer.
Oh, please.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, every ride goes 25% or 25 miles an hour faster
and the chili peppers are on all the rides.
That's my dream for a big event.
If we're not getting Quacky Duck City, that's what I want.
Well, shocking news, Disneyland has closed.
Disneyland finally, permanently after many decades has kicked the bucket.
Okay, wait a minute.
In this scenario, is it because people don't want to go
because of the red hot chili peppers or is it because all the rides broke?
Oh, I don't know.
Because people are like, oh, I don't want to hear those red hot chili peppers anymore.
We'll call them A, we'll call them B.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think if, well, if you got, if you like didn't know what you were like,
it's the storybook land canal boats.
It's really nice.
You're going to see little villages where all the characters live.
All right, let's do it.
Mommy, mommy.
They didn't bake the curves.
I'm flying out of a boat, mom.
Is there a ride we think we could legitimately make faster and it would work?
That's a good question.
Well, railroad is pretty funny.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
You could make that go a little faster probably.
I understand the physics of trains and I think I do from the film Back to the Future 3.
You just have to throw in different colored logs
and that makes the train go progressively faster and faster.
That's a good point.
Different color, oh, into the engine?
This is Dr. Emmett Brown's system.
You just get, you know, all right, now you go to yellow.
Now you go to orange.
Now you go red.
I got to rewatch his movie.
I do not remember the logs.
No, it's a color based log system and that gets the train up to 88 miles an hour.
You got to have your colored logs.
Regular logs are not going to do it for you.
Right.
So get some colored logs.
Start cranking that thing.
That makes sense for the train, yeah.
What's the train song?
Oh, which song with the red chili peppers?
Yeah.
Oh, let me think here.
Song pairing.
I'm trying to think of a good, what's on blood sugar, blood sugar sex magic maybe.
The title track from blood sugar sex magic.
I think that makes sense.
Just for family friendly, could you change the name to blood sugar train magic?
Yeah.
That would help.
Oh, great, great.
Everybody can enjoy that.
That at least has one of the Disney words.
That's true.
It's kind of the most Disney friendly chili pepper song.
Maybe they build the whole firework show around the song blood sugar sex magic.
So like it would at least fit the brand.
Did they say the phrase in the song?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Blood sugar baby, she's magic, sex magic, sex magic.
Train magic.
Uh huh.
Story.
Blood has to come out.
Blood sugar story magic.
I think blood has to come out of it.
Story sugar train.
Story sugar train magic.
Wish.
Wish magic.
Wish magic maybe is the line then.
Yeah.
I think that's good.
Yeah, you're going to have to make some edits.
You know, actually we're thinking sugar is a little dicey because there's kind of a sexual,
like, hey, come here sugar.
Oh.
Can we make that imagine just to be safe?
Okay, yeah.
All right.
So the song is now dream imagine wish magic.
Dream imagine wish magic.
Wish magic.
Yeah.
It's kind of a hard, a hard one of the harder songs in their catalog I think.
It's a tougher sounding song, not as poppy.
Not when Alan Menken puts his new lyrics on.
Alan Menken will get on it and I think it'll be great.
Anyway, not to avoid the question, but I think in terms of unpleasant and maybe the
Astro Orbiter at the front of this land.
Is your least favorite ride?
Really?
Wow.
I'm trying to, I just keep going through rides and I'm like, well, I like all the vehicles.
I like all the trains.
I'm pretty good with mission space.
Although I feel like, I feel like last time I rode out was okay, but the time before that
I was pretty beat up.
And living with the land is not your choice.
Huh?
Scott's choice is not living with the land.
Maybe my choice is something I don't feel comfortable saying in public.
Oh, okay.
Excuse me.
Maybe I, there's certain things, certain areas where I can't express myself in this
country anymore.
You're being censored.
Yeah, you're being censored.
Because I woke.
I do think genuinely, I don't think you guys have been hard enough on that journey.
And it's not even like the dream finder at none of that.
I think in and of itself, that thing is such a piece of shit.
I don't like it.
Don't get me wrong.
But I would rather go on it 10 times than do one mission space.
I think I just really don't like it.
I might be on the same page with you there.
Funny how so many of the choices are in Epcot.
What a bummer.
That is interesting.
Yeah.
But thank God Epcot now has a corn hole.
Corn hole and hula hoops.
Just to get to the end of this situation.
They knew right away this was not going well.
Operationally terrible.
Shut down all the time.
We're in the rise of the resistance zone of shutdowns probably every day.
Because of the slow down, speed up, computers are going to manage how we track where all the vehicles are.
Wait, that vehicle isn't where we thought it would be because of the slowing down and speeding up.
Computer, what do you think?
Malfunction, malfunction, steam.
The computer system breaks down, every car stops in its tracks because they couldn't pinpoint exactly where everything was supposed to be.
Everybody get out of your rocket rods.
Really precarious, elevated, scary for kids to evacuate from.
Almost no clearance.
So that's all a disaster.
Then like they, I mean I think they did a big shutdown.
Three months.
Early on.
Wow.
Right after.
You know what?
One month.
In one month, they scheduled a one month refurbishment which became three months.
Then it opened and nothing was fixed.
It limped along like this until fall 2000 and they said, guess what?
Seven months.
It's going to go down for seven months.
We will see you in spring 2001.
And then some reporters start asking the people in charge of Disneyland, hey it's spring.
What's going on with that thing?
And they're like, yeah, all right, you got us, it's not happening.
Rockerguys is gone forever.
Cynthia Harris, I forget what she was, if she was the president or somebody big at the resource, she was the president.
Said to the press, said to a newspaper, the high speed attraction was never able to perform to its design show standards.
The problem was a budget conscious decision to run the high speed rods on the people movers unbanked track.
Can you imagine a current Disney executive saying what really happened?
Not saying, well, we are imagine upping, imagine upping some new experiences that we're going to dreameroo for you by 2032.
Like there's no, there's no way they don't just like censor, censor.
Cynthia Harris, a real, you know, she shoots from the hip.
Yeah.
Oh, she's a whistleblower.
The cornhole has been shut down as a trunk man in his thirties, wung a bag at a six year old's head.
It did not perform as expected.
The verb wung can only be described as wung, an action so violent it has never occurred until now and requires a new word.
I mean, that's crazy.
And this is where you really have to like imagine if they look, it's had its problems, but it's clearly like a hit and it's working very well.
But you like imagine if they two years in rise, the resistance is gone.
We're not doing it.
It broke. It didn't work.
It never worked.
Like never mind on rise of the resistance.
The chicken that was going pretty wild.
Fully.
Had emetronics.
The statue keeps vomiting.
The Gleason, the statue keeps vomiting and we don't know why.
Dommel Gleason spews bile and he's up above the guest.
So it lands on the guest.
And if you're asking, does he exorcist?
Yes, he exorcists.
He spins around and around and around and there is no way to stop him.
No, we don't even want to get near him.
The well, that's sort of the rather cannon room is I think rocking itself because that's never going to run again.
I've heard those cannons are never going to run a rise of resistance, which is my favorite room with most people.
That's what I've heard.
Because it shakes the foundation.
Like we're talking about gives earthquake, many earthquakes to this building.
And that's what I've heard.
I'm not an expert.
I've never talked to an engineer about it, but that's what people say is that, yeah, these things are off forever.
Make them out of balsa wood.
Like make them out of a light particle board.
I think they're lighter than we think they are, but still the mechanism for making something that big move so much.
That's a bummer.
Yeah, if it's true, that's a bummer.
Yeah.
It's like a mini rocket rods within.
Right.
Yes.
So yeah, there's partly of like this isn't working.
And luckily for their sake, it's only one room.
Yeah.
And they're using that on a bigger scale.
It's really crazy.
That should be in a Mario ride also, by the way.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Because it feels like such a Mario level.
Oh, true.
Yeah.
Where you go in and out.
Swamps that have more of a risk of actually hitting you.
Yeah.
I saw that 2000 to 2001 refurbishment.
That's when they were going to put on the glow in the dark.
Like the glowing night lights.
Oh, that's interesting.
Wow.
So that would have felt, maybe there's a version where they got it there.
I like to imagine a world where like, all right, so let's see.
We're going to do, we'll pop over to, you know, we'll go do Haunted Mansion.
And then I think I got a two o'clock rods.
We'll do rods.
And then.
Sure.
I mean, I think it's, yeah.
If they, they were probably like, the track is going to fall apart.
We can't, we will have to rebuild the track and then just no one ever was interested in
shutting down that big of a chunk of Tomorrowland.
And then.
They had just done.
Right.
This had just happened.
And you know what else is, here's, here's where it gets depressing too, is that part
of new Tomorrowland, we got a new ride.
Then that goes down.
Once you've seen, honey, I shrugged the audience.
You've pretty much seen it.
I don't know if you need to keep doing that over and over.
Submarines gone.
Submarines gone with new Tomorrowland.
So we've lost one.
Right.
I mean, and that all, and nobody likes the bread.
The Brown gets repainted very quickly.
Right.
It's almost, almost if you take away Astro Orbiter, there's almost no signs of new
Tomorrowland in general.
Buzz Lightyear came in there, cleaned up that area.
So it was this big, this, you know, cheap for them, but too expensive for something
that didn't stay.
Wow.
What a giant waste of money.
I know.
And just don't do the rocket rods if you're going to cheap out on it that much.
I wonder how soon into development they realized.
Yeah.
Like, oh shit.
And they had to put on a, and then Tony had to go do all the press clips of him.
Like, because the future is the land of dreams.
And that is where, and he knew he's dying inside and started him crazy.
He has to go be the face of it.
Yeah.
Awful.
What are you saying, Jason?
That sign that rocket rods closed, I believe sold at one of the Disneyland auctions.
Ha.
At the, at the, I think I saw it at the, I remember remembering it was at the exhibit
in the Burbank mall, one of the more recent auctions that is kind of set up as if it
were a museum.
Right, right.
I'm like, it's a rocket rods thing and it's the rocket rods is closed today sign.
The sign promising the rods will be back.
Yeah.
But the rods did not come back.
There were.
There is no rod.
I have found on eBay or Depop, there are rocket rods t-shirts and the sellers know what they
have because those t-shirts are always 80 or $90.
Okay.
Those are the real deal.
Yeah.
Those aren't remakes.
Those are the vintage.
They're vintage.
Yeah.
Wow.
True vintage rod merch.
I like just calling it rods.
Like if it just stuck around.
Yeah, just turning the rod doesn't have a reel.
That's what would have happened.
Like, all right, so just yeah, quick, quick rod and then we'll do space man more over
there if we have time.
I'd rather, if we had to pick, I gotta do, we gotta do rods.
I think rods.
I would do rods.
Yeah.
So let's do it before we go to the pizza restaurant.
Cause that pizza and then a ride on rods, you're going to feel a little gnarly.
And the pizza restaurant, which is called Rod's Rocket Pizza Port, they changed the
name due to the now beloved success of rocket rods.
It's part of the rod universe.
Right, right.
And they'd have had a movie too probably by now.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Disney announces.
Disney's rocket rod movie.
Yeah.
Verbinsky is back.
Cor Verbinsky is doing rocket rods, yeah.
Now that by the way, still could happen from some of the announcements recently where you
go, I don't know why they're doing that.
Oh, I know.
Club 33 movie.
You're like, oh, why not a rocket rod movie?
Talking about.
Yeah, I know actually, and with rocket rods, you could be a little more freewheeling.
That's right.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm kid brained.
I'm thinking about Thomas the Tank Engine, but like, you know, like a plucky upstart
vehicle named Rocket Rod who wants to go fast, but he doesn't know how to bank on turns.
So all his passengers always go a flying.
Rocket Rod doesn't mean to cause concussions, but he just gets too excited on the straightaways.
I like that Rod isn't a guy or a character.
Yeah, yeah.
Give him a little face.
I'm Rocket Rod.
That's their, yeah, rebooted just as a friend.
I'm seeing it right now.
Kids are crazy for transportation.
My pitch is more of an American graffiti with rocket rods racing and stuff, you know, future
American graffiti is my pitch.
What if they just, what if all it is, is you climb up there, it does just the straightaway
and then it doesn't bank.
It's like a, it's a race to the end of the entrance at Tomorrowland and then you just
back it up and you do it again.
15 seconds.
Rocket Rod drag races.
Okay.
Fine with me.
Yeah.
Some kinetic energy there.
And a sexy girl robot waving the flag in between.
Now I'm very interested.
Gentle bots, start your engines.
Gentle bots.
That's the other rule, women can't go on the rocket rods.
Women are not allowed to go on the new rocket rods.
It seems a little odd, but okay, I'll allow it, I guess.
I don't know how they'll enforce that, but all right.
Yeah, it seems confusing, but.
Can I say, there's been a lot of teases about rocket rods, about the people mover of the
years, 2010, a former Disneyland, I think president George Kalogridis is quote, what
I do know is we can never bring it back as it was originally, but don't worry.
Everyone understands the passion everyone has for it.
Hang in there.
So keep hanging in there everyone.
What year was that?
He said 2010.
2010.
Okay.
A lot of hanging.
Roadie walking along the track a while ago.
People spotted him.
The legend of Roadie walking along the track of the people mover a few years before.
We don't have footage of this, but this is a frequent and a frequent anecdote.
We're supposed to get hope because an Imagineer went to a place.
We need more than this.
We need hope that's big enough to fill a Honda center.
The Imagineering documentary is holding a model that looks like it possibly could be
a space mountain and Roadie's in charge of the new space mountain.
Roadie fired.
Nevermind.
He's gone.
He's been fired.
Early retirement.
He's been put into early retirement.
He goes to Virgin Galactic, but he's not there anymore.
I don't know if that's going already.
Imagineering for a seminar or a master class.
He was in Epcot a couple months ago.
So everyone wants things to be real.
This is the saddest hunting for us.
Swish cast as seeing a guy walking through a place.
Oh my god, Roadie's walking through Epcot.
Wait, in terms of history rhyming, new Epcot, it's done, commuter core hall, the picnic
area is open, then immediately test track 2.0 closes.
Like you were saying, well, it's closing.
They are redoing it.
Yeah, the new test track is down, or excuse me, going to be built now.
Oh, they're doing the full refurbishment.
Yes.
But when you said like Tomorrowland 98 and the subs are closed, it just reminded me of
That's how they do it.
Look over here.
This keeps happening.
They roll it.
Yeah, they roll them over.
It's my favorite theme park aesthetic is Disney Future.
It's one of the things I think they do the very best, maybe the thing they do the very
best.
Why is this the most problematic area?
Why do these have to struggle?
Why are these the areas that don't get the infinite budget?
This is what I'd like to see change.
And just to tie the Tomorrowland story back together, it really, unfortunately, you have
to say if it's I don't want to blame Rod himself now that I've humanized him.
I don't want to put this all on Rod's big clunky and loud shoulders.
It's the decision making to cheap out on Rod's that has still left this decaying husk of
a track that now they're back to where they were.
We're exactly where we were.
Space Mountain a lock, Star Tours a lock, everything else not a lock, all these spaces
that need to be filled.
You could blow up any of these things any second and nobody would care.
It's a land you got to get rid of that track, even if you don't replace it with anything.
The track has to go.
But also you want to keep people going to Space Mountain.
It's a we've gotten nowhere since 1988.
It's really crazy.
Is there what percentage of hope do you have that this is the year at D23 that we finally
hear something?
Okay, what I think is going to happen is that we will get a 50% new Tomorrowland announced
in the set.
There'll be maybe one that maybe it's a version of Tron.
Maybe it's one thing that's like a big shiny thing and then a lot of little things.
That's kind of that's what I think and I think there's a good chance of that.
You are doing a parlay bet that they do something to Tomorrowland.
Because the Autopia I think is kind of a hint to me.
The announcement of Autopia being electric in what 2027 is a hint that we're going to
do stuff but it's not going to be some massive thing that we kind of want where they rip
out the subs in Autopia and build a whole crazy new big thing over there.
So I kind of think they're going to do half and half.
It's going to plus up some stuff there.
It's going to make it look better.
We pull out the people mover track and then I don't know if it's Tron or if it's some
maybe it's I don't think they're going to do a Tokyo and rip out our Space Mountain.
I wouldn't hate it.
I would.
But there's things they need to do first.
That's the thing.
Of course I'd love that.
But we got a big list.
My guess was that they were just going to put the Guardians coaster in there in Tokyo.
But apparently that's not the case.
It's a new kind of coaster.
I was wrong about that.
Yes.
Wow.
So it's a totally new and I don't know that they know what it is yet.
Cool.
Yeah.
So that's I think there's a very good chance we'll get like three small announcements for
Tomorrowland and then maybe one moderate to big announcements and they'll tie that as
well.
Now we're doing something with Tomorrowland.
That's my guess.
I don't think I can go with you.
You don't even think that's happening.
I'm too hurt.
But I think maybe in two years we get but I think priorities are specifics about Avatar.
I think in general you could feel that they are pushing like and a lot of this isn't
forward.
It feels like about how they're going to get frozen and tangled and that kind of thing.
Yes.
I think that we're getting all that first.
I think that's all priority.
But I almost and maybe I'm wrong about this is I feel like they're going to hedge some
bets still on what they're fully doing with all of it.
I think they'll show more of the Avatar and they'll say it's but I don't know that they'll
us where it's going yet.
I could be wrong about that but like that all feels like that is still a little bit
emotion.
This is all complete guess.
I don't know what I'm talking about but that all still feels like we're not quite sure.
It feels like some of the Magic Kingdom stuff is a little more close to reality beyond Big
Thunder stuff.
OK.
I keep hearing rumors about that.
So I almost get a sense of like I bet they know where that stuff is going more than they
exactly know what isn't it forward is if it's a third park if it's just extensions of the
two parks.
I don't know.
It's an episode is just is us betting.
Oh betting.
Yeah.
And putting actual putting actual money on.
I'll put money on it.
Yeah.
That's fun.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
It's going to do it along with us too.
I don't exactly know how to structure that.
I don't know how to make a betting.
That's going to be tough.
Well with fanatics dot com and ESPN you can use ESPN bet and keep it in house at Disney
somehow.
You know what we'll probably have to do is we'll each come in with sort of a guarantee
of like OK I believe they will show concept art of a frozen land or mini land with a new
frozen rock like we'll have to come in with sort of a bet and then you the other two will
have to say I will take you up on that I don't believe that's happening.
Like I think we're gonna have to do that as opposed to like figuring out an official board
of all the different because like yes you're right.
Tangled frozen avatars we know how do you determine odds that are in the mix is a mess.
It has to be just like between us.
But yes it would have to.
I would have to say like OK I believe they will show Wakanda and they will show a Black
Panther ride specifically.
And it's in Disney.
I don't know you could say it's in Disneyland forward and that's where it's going to go
or something like you would have to.
I'll have to bring in a specific thing that you will have to either agree or disagree
with me on.
Yeah.
And I guess it can be as specific as we want it to be.
Right.
But it's still going to be tricky because maybe maybe it has to have a qualifier like
it'll have like it's tough because it's too hard.
We shouldn't really work it out on the air because it's boring.
But it is like when you're betting on some of this.
You're betting on the Super Bowl and when you bet on the Super Bowl bet on football
games in Vegas you can bet on the coin toss.
You can bet on like like whoever is doing the halftime show like what songs they will
sing.
Like we could go.
Yeah.
It's more like that I think.
I think it's more like that.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
You could bet on.
Yeah.
Like is like is does the score have like a nine and a six in it.
Right.
You could go that.
I think that's what we do.
What if it's.
Hey let's simplify.
Bingo.
OK.
Yeah.
Bingo cards.
OK.
And it's either how many do you light up or if you get lines.
That's funny too.
Yeah.
So we got Tomorrowland 2055 episode.
We've got repeat.
Frequent footage final four.
We've got potentially unbilled that could go into Tomorrowland 2055.
We've got prop bets.
Yeah.
We've got a prop bet episode but then we also have to fix Tomorrowland which I.
We've got fixed Tomorrowland.
We can assign our assignments right now if you'd like.
Do you have that worked out.
I do.
Well yes.
It's a very it's pretty simple.
It has to be randomized doesn't it.
Well right.
So I have no I have assigned one through three.
Oh.
And I could just have Jason pick a number and you'll pick a number and then I'll get
whatever is left over because I chose the numbers.
OK.
So this is pretty random.
This is a little nerve wracking.
Right now.
So remind remind everybody what the system.
So the fixed Tomorrowland basically we're each going to have a different assignment
in a different budget essentially and a different mindset in a lot of ways because somebody
is going to have to fix Tomorrowland in a budget.
So you're going to have to have a budget that's going to be less money than this rocket
rod era.
OK.
Or at least similar.
At least similar.
At least similar to a rocket rod where like you can kind of do a rocket rod type overlay
or change to one existing ride there but it's going to be a lot of paint.
You have to be you're going to have to really like like figure out economical ways to make
Tomorrowland better.
Yeah.
Somebody is going to get the budget for a realistic twenty twenty four Tomorrowland.
But what would Disney in twenty twenty four do?
It's going to be a lot of IP.
It's going to be a lot of cloning from other parks.
So all that's obviously the other two people will have to police you if you decide to like
act like you could put in like a goofy movie ride or something.
We go that is not what twenty four twenty four Disney would do.
But it also doesn't have to be that a bunch of it just turns into grass with corn hole
and hula hoops.
It doesn't have to be but there will be a when in doubt yes future grass portions of
Tomorrowland.
And then the third is maybe I don't know maybe the most fun big budget blue sky and you can
maybe put a few originals that like you have a massive budget here.
Yeah.
It's maybe like they sold ESPN.
You have all that money now.
Right.
The Albatross is gone.
Uh huh.
And you really I will like whoever gets that I think will be able to sort of have carte
to do some IP maybe some original bring back old stuff like that's maybe the most fun one
and that's that's going to be a big that's going to be I think the one that I want the
most.
But it's we're going to have to trust that you aren't lying over there and I well I
haven't written down what the numbers are so you guys can see that I'm not going to
give myself the thing.
So I have numbers assigned to each one one through three.
Yeah.
I will let's just say Jason picks first one two or three and then I will give you your
assignment to Jason.
You got budget tomorrow and and now it's up to between Scott and I and one of us gets
realistic healthy budget but they have to be within the sort of confines of what Disney
does in twenty twenty four and the other gets the fun blue sky one.
Scott you have to choose either one or three.
What do you choose.
This is very important.
Three choose Scott gets the blue sky.
Yeah.
Tomorrow.
That was the order you read them.
I didn't think you would give blue sky to three.
That was the third one you mentioned.
That's why I thought exactly how I had listed.
Oh wow.
Jason has a problem with the with the mechanism.
I honestly think I got the worst one.
Huh.
I would have had been budget would have been my second choice if there's some way we can
trade if you want to like one day to come up with a reasonable trade I have realistic
twenty twenty four what they might announce at this year's D23.
So mine is the most boring one because it's going to have to be IP it's going to have
to be a lot of cloned rides but I'm open to a trade with you now with Jason.
Oh no I got a budget.
I got my assignment.
I got myself and I love that you got budget but I but you have no yeah you have to be
the most creative with little money to fix Tomorrowland.
Okay.
So you're really going to have to get in there and imagine what you would do with with just
paint and again you can do sort of a rocket rods ish level redo of an existing right is
maybe the bar.
Yeah.
Or maybe build a very small kind of ride using that money.
It could be I'll even say it could be like web slingers level.
Oh okay.
That's still expensive but it's a smaller ride.
It's not they would never have called that any ticket.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Maybe either like either of you I'd say could allude to a ride that is a giant lie that
will never get done.
That's true too.
That's all that's always a big option with the modern Disney to yes I can lie a little
bit but yeah so so yeah you guys have the better assignments I think mine is the most
boring.
Huh.
I believe.
Well thank you for being.
It's an interesting thought.
It's an interesting thought experiment yeah yeah well thank you for being a randomized
martyr.
Sure.
Well hey that's great well I'm glad we've done the connective tissue we've identified
the problem maybe this has all taught us something that we can use in our in this eventual episode
which should be a lot of fun.
I agree.
We'll get to that before D23 happens before either we get some stuff we want or we get
our hearts broken.
But for now you survived podcast the ride for three bonus episodes every month check
out podcast the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club
three you'll find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Now I get to go outside and look up at the big beautiful blue sky and Jason gets to look
down at the ground the dirty ground the space mountain brown on the ground start counting
my dirty pennies and not the fun way I usually count my dirty pennies.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott
Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.