FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast may include
Leather Daddy Aliens
Oddly understocked
Rainbow Food Stuffs
And the serving of a C-Word
That doesn't stand for what you think
Henry Gilbert from Talking Simpsons
Brings us a special trip report
From Disneyland Pride Night
On Podcast The Ride
Music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
And you know something? You can't spell
Podcast The Ride without Pride
I'm Scott Gardiner
Yeah, that makes you think, right Mike Carlson?
It does make me think of all the letters that are involved in the name
Kind of the primary
It's been in front of us the whole time
We've never thought about it
Jason Sheridan
Yeah, and we're only giving
We're only putting out two episodes
In all of June
Just as this event gets two nights
Out of a whole month
Yes, I think if listeners think back
They will note that we only put out those two episodes
Because we wanted to
In order to line up with the Pride
Event. How else do we show our support?
It doesn't sound right but it is right I guess
If Jason said it
Go check, go check, you'll see
So today we're talking about
Disneyland Pride Night
A fairly new event
A recently held event
As we record this and as you're hearing it
Just a couple days later
An event that was just attended by our guest
Who is in town on Podcast The Ride
For the first time in person
For the first time solo
From Talking Simpsons and what a cartoon
Hey, hello
Clarabelle the cow super fan
Alright, let's see
Bust those Clarabelle moves
I know the listeners can't hear it but
Oh look at it, wow, he's going wild
It is so Clarabelle-esque
That would go viral on TikTok
If we posted it but we weren't filming
Thanks for joining us
Henry, it's good to see you
It's great to see you guys too
We recorded in person
On the Talking Simpsons
Podcast like 6 years ago
When you guys
You like rented a little
Airbnb by Warner Brothers-ish
So it's been that long
Since we've seen you in person
I've been a
At home podcaster
Remotely for so long
I feel like you guys are still on
A screen away from me and I can't
Physically touch you
Well that's the thrill
Anything can happen, we can all get up and
Touch each other whenever we want
That's true
Make something happen
I poke Jason a lot during recordings
I have the bruises
To show for it
Even just doing two episodes this month
He's like upped his poking
If we say it enough
Oh yeah it'll work
So yeah
While you're in town giving
Non-screened podcasting a try
Which we're happy about
But you've done
A ton of theme parking
In addition to Pride Night
We were talking a little bit before we started
You've been at theme parks
More than we have recently
Anything from your travels you want to shout out?
Man I've done so much
I had been a Californian
For 17 years
And now I've moved to Seattle
And I was in the Bay Area
But it was nice back then to know
Oh an hour flight and I'm right here
And can go to a theme park
And my husband and I are big
Theme park people
But we hadn't been
In a while
We did go to Tokyo Disneyland
In January
We spent Christmas Day at Tokyo Disney
That's a smart use of Christmas
That's good
It was great
This was our first big trip in a while
And we did
The Mickey's Runaway Railway
Man what a good ride
That was so good
Yeah that seems pretty
Universally acclaimed
Other than by my 3 year old
Who was really
Terrified by it
Imagine that tornado sequence
In the eyes of a 3 year old
When you're just afraid of the dark
In general
He held it together then we got off
And just erupted
It was an effective and immersive ride
Because he thought it was really happening
A lot of dark in it for sure
That is true
And the line is like
As a person who does animation podcasts
The line is so full of little details
That are so cool
Also I'm a huge goofy movie fan
There's like 3 or 4 posters
That are just goofy movie references
Like the
Freaky Friday one
And the High School Musical parody one
They're just like characters from goofy movie
That is so cool to see
Which themselves are more recent references
You gotta like that they are
Acknowledging the last 25-30 years
Of Walt Disney pictures
And not just kind of like
It's Mary Poppins and then it's nothing after that
Yeah though I also felt
Old in the line because there was like
There was a lot of people in their 20s
At pride night there
And when they're in the line
And see the Mickey's Playhouse
Show
Which was like came out
There's a Mickey's Playhouse section of it
Which came out when I was like in my 20s
And then they are looking at it and going
Oh my god that's my childhood right there
Wanted to die
Some of these get rough
These generational switch
Goofy movie is no longer the like
Cool hip reference anymore
It's more for the 30s and 40s
Mike this is news to me
I don't want to say it
I don't want him to say it
But I'm just saying that used to be like
Oh you know what's actually good is Goofy movie
And that's what the hip young people were saying
Something with Pauly Shore in it is no longer considered hip
I'm sorry to say it to the audience
If you haven't thought about it
Think about it now
Oh but outside of Disney
I went to Universal
To do the 60th anniversary
Tour which is a lot of fun
It's really good though it makes it
It makes that last bit of the Fast and Furious ride
Like it's like the last
Because basically they have a few updated
Things and a bunch of cool updated videos for it
And then they have a stop down to like
Get photos for like the
Gram like all of these you know
Like oh pose with they put the
You know the big Bruce the shark like
You can pose with it like you used to
In Orlando you know and
And here's Dominic Toretto's car
And get in King Kong's hand
Is it just one zone
That's the like get out take pictures zone
Yeah yeah basically you do earthquake
Which that was cool that earthquakes
Open again too
And then refreshed although that
Bums me out because it doesn't look like 1987
Anymore yeah it's sad it looks like
Like 10 years ago BART
Station now instead of like 70s
At least it's not current I just
Don't want it to be current that's my main point
You were happy there's like a Cinderella
Man poster yeah yeah yes
The theme parks are meant to be at least
A little bit out of date yeah yeah
I like our guide presented as
Now this is
I think it's studio 15 he's like studio 15
Now this used to have the earthquake ride but
We've changed it now and it's we're
Shooting something else here and now
Hey wait a minute uh oh uh oh
Like so that's good
The tour guide was great
Like he I really
Look I don't want to get into sexuality though
This is the pride episode but he was
He called himself a southern bell
When he was describing how much
He loves like being in the western set
So I was like he seemed like a very
Feminine guy was having a good time
And uh it was I
Love that in the tour guide oh that's nice
That's good but but yeah you get
You have a stop off to get your
Instagram pictures and then
You get back on and then the only
Thing they got left is the fast and furious
Part and I'm just like god I wish I could just get off
Now and just save
If they gave you the option yeah would you like a golf
Cart to take you the rest of the way
Skip what you know is coming oh and Ted
Ted has a new sign
That's like we celebrate 60 years
Of the tour oh wow
I was like oh my god Ted's got a new sign
Wow wow
Malamute Stacy isn't he
Wow yeah I feel like we oh go ahead
I was just gonna say it's in the same spot Ted has always been
I think yeah Ted's in the same spot but now
He's got a sign what was celebrating
60 years of the studio tour
I'm sure there wasn't a new Ted
No I don't think it's a new Ted but yeah
You know what's been a nice thing
Maybe you guys have noticed this because we
All live pretty near Universal
Studios and just kind of
A fun little like
A dash of color
In the surrounding areas right
Now is that sometimes it happened to me right before
I came over I was at a coffee shop and a bus
Went by and the bus
A lot of buses around here are decked
Out like the glamour tram
Like full bus wrap
Of the red and white
And like it was parked this morning
In such a way that I couldn't even see the front and there was a
Minute where I kind of bugged out like
Is that did the tram get loose
Is it lost is it out on the street
But it's not and the
You know and our beloved Kara beloved
Woody Woodpecker you'll see on it
Just brightens up the town
You know yeah it was really
Great and I also did the
Warner studio tour which I'd never done
Before which is fun you get to see all
The things back when Warner Brothers like made movies
Instead of like shelving them and not releasing them
Tax write offs
Although they should I mean how cool would it be
To see the like and in there are the
Is the shelf that
Coyote versus Acme is sitting on
There it is you want to see it do you want to help us
Destroy it we got hammers
This is the Lee C drive
The orange rubbery
Hard drive that used to contain
The screener copy
There's like an urn full of the back girl hard drive
Just to have sitting on a shelf
And they're like that's the remains of back girl
Unreleasable
It was fun
Though the right though they really
You can see how they market it towards
Like the international folks who are coming
There because they're like it's like
Half friends they're like there's
An entire like here's we built a central
Perk you can take pictures in and
Here's like the friends fountain and a
Couch that they've and
Though they have to admit like this
Isn't the real fountain we
Had to move the fountain from where it
Used to be and this is where we put it for
The reunion special
And all that oh yeah
And then also like a ton of Harry Potter stuff
But I'm just like no thank you and then
And then though I think
I think the Warner studio tour is stealing
Valor because they have
Like a whole Lord of the Rings section there
And I'm like now come on like that is a new line
Thing you guys didn't green light this
Like that is not
They released it though technically like I
Know the association they
They released the Hobbit movies and
I mean new line was owned by
Warner by the time return
Of the king came out so it's not like they don't
Own it but I I'm a real
Stickler about that
Like with Fox stuff are you like
Disney doesn't own alien oh man
On pride night I I was
Saying to my husband they play a song
From they play
This is me from the world's greatest showman
And I was just going like this isn't a
Song this is a song
I saw a video of that
And I was like wait hold on
Yeah I guess yeah like
Doing the math in my head I
Mean well and it's like oh now it's I guess a
20th century film like
That's the branding for it but yeah
It was but yeah the Warner tour the most
It was also fun you get to hear
Different patches of people in the group like
Ooh and ah and stuff where she'd say like
Our tour guide said this is where
This is where like 800 episodes
Of the Gilmore Girls were filmed and some parts
Were going like ooh and then then the Big Bang
Theory section and then the and then
I love that she was like a big
Trekkie the and she
Is like now there's no the only Star Trek
Thing here I can name is that the
Episode Next Generation with
Data in the Old West was filmed here
Like for a fistful of data I think
It's called yeah fistful of data yeah
Is there Old West
Stuff there I'm sure
Well she was saying it used to it got torn down but she's
Like this was the Old West section
And it what this is where that was filmed
I think every lot
Because like all in the same
Neck of the wall pretty close to each other
Disney Warner Brothers
Universal and Universal still has some Old
West Disney's is all gone Disney's
All offices I didn't know until
Right now that Warner had Old West and
Got rid of like so much real
Estate in the Burbank
Toluca Lake whatever you want to call it
North Hollywood area was once
Western sets valuable land
But every studio needed
The way that was the thing because that's something I had to say on the tour was it
Six points Texas was
Where because there were six different streets that you could
Film six different westerns at the same
Time and can you imagine
Are there six westerns being filmed at the same
Time on the globe today
Kevin Costner's
Rust
Kevin Costner part one Kevin Costner part two
Kevin Costner part three
Is Yellowstone a western?
Sure let's go with it
They got cowboy hats
Well they got the 1893 the spin off
Oh yeah the Harrison Ford so that's
There's one
No yeah I mean the
I feel like they film western
Movies about westerns like
Once upon a time in Hollywood that's what they used the western
Set for
So there still have to be sound stages
Towering over the western set
It's got to be kind of a double set
I wonder if the tour at Universal is the reason
That stuff is still there because it's almost like
There's an incentive to have a
Western part just to say oh that's the
Western part of the tour it's also sort of perfectly
You know if you haven't been on
The tour you don't know the area like
Big swaths of the back lot are
Kind of are turning into studio space they're
Like tidying it all up right if it
Land it used to be switching back
And forth between sound stage and theme park
And now it's kind of like theme park
Stuff goes over here
Studio stuff is over here sound stages are
Over here
But yeah I think maybe the western stuff has survived
Just because it's like in the middle
It's like protected but they probably
I don't think they need the flash
Flood a lot
Like for filming day to day I don't think
That's getting a lot of use they probably
Would be happy to rip it out but
It's sealed in the bubble
I feel like movies and
TV shows are using the crash plane set
More than the
Than the old west
I do see that where people do try to
Reappropriate that here and there
Like on CBS like procedurals
And stuff I feel like I think maybe
Will Trent is combing through the
Wreckage like looking for stuff
Sure yeah
Oh and the
Saddest thing on the Warner tour
That they actually showed us was like
And here's the they could
Show us an empty sound
Stage that we wouldn't be interrupting
Anything and when they got out of there
And you know what was filmed here
The Conan show
The TBS Conan show
It's just empty now
It's just really nothing ever went in there
At least currently nothing is in there
It's also weird that like
Cause I remember wondering like
When will this show end and when will they
Like turn off the lights on
The place where I worked and where I have like a lot
Of fond memories and the answer is
It was just like abandoned everybody just dropped their
Pens and papers one day during
The pandemic they were just out
And then it went home and then it was done
At Largo for a little while
And nobody ever went back to that studio
Or did anything there
Just a weird unceremonious
And bizarre
Conan's show endings besides the first one
None of them are
None of them are done with the proper heralding
Well that's sad
That's sad to hear I'll try to bounce back
Well here's a happier memory there actually
For when we sat on the friend's couch
Let's get the friend's couch picture wasn't that important to us
But then the
Tour guide pointed out oh and you know over there
Those steps up to a bank
That was used in
The Batman 66 show every
Time he went into City Hall he ran up
These stairs
I could like sit on there sometime
When I had like constant back lot access
Like I'm just gonna take a sandwich
Over to the Batman steps that was
That was a good deal
It also reminded me how one time I saw a golf cart
Tour go by once
When Conan was outside the studio
And I watched him just give
Scarily what anybody
Would want if you were on the tour which is
It like stopped at a stop sign and he said
Hey everyone it's me
Conan O'Brien from television
Your eyes don't deceive you take a look
Take it all in take photographs
And it almost like
Was probably purposefully too much
He's like can I be so willing
To participate in this that it's scary
And it was very fun to watch that show
You freak them out
Yeah there's a lot of
Like a lot of the sound stages are Batman and Robin
Like if you go and look at
The like little plaque and stuff
They used like everything and I think they used Universal too
And it says like
What I love about it is it's like Casablanca
And then 70 years later
Whatever 50 years later Batman and Robin
No yeah there's
Our tour guide
Said like and this is where Chris
O'Donnell drove the stolen Batmobile
Down the streets
There was also the tour
Guide had another very funny part where she said
And you know this area this is where Austin
Powers gold member
Filled like she had like a pause
Pregnant pause
Bring everybody down we're like oh gold member
That's still good kind of good
Strong cast
Britney's in it
We got to see the alleyway where Spiderman
Did his upside down kiss that was also
Where Purple Rain's cover was
Photographed
I didn't know either of those
Oh that's fascinating
There's so much Hollywood history
I love all the little
Trivia like that's I've really come to love
Tour guides on these trips now
Like who are ready to be
Asked a really dorky question about
Like was any of the Matrix shot here
Which is what I asked and she's like
I guess some I don't know like
Now I'm saying
Like she had lots of good answers and now I'm saying
The time she had no good answer
Hard to know everything
Try to keep as much in your pocket as you can
There is a very
Ominous thing by the
Warner Brothers lot right now which is
There is like a three
Story vertical billboard that always
Had the big summer release
The big release
Barbie and the last time
I drove by it was just white
It was just nothing
And it's like that's a little
Too on the nose
For this company if you stare closely
It's actually it's just really fine
Print and it's all of the details of
The tax write off forms that says
Oh yeah they had to post it somewhere
Legally they had to post it
Technically you are looking at the
Poster for Batgirl
It's one of those things where you select all
Text and you turn it white
But it's on a white background
Stare close
It's there
What a fun
That's something we need to do in the near future
Well that's great
Great travels but it seems like the main thing
Or at least the kind of unique thing happening
During your trip specifically
Was Disneyland Pride Night
Which you went on
There were two nights of it you went on Thursday
You said
I went on Thursday yeah so the Pride Night
NITE
We had been
Thinking about going
So it started last year I mean there's a whole
History to it but yeah it started
Last year this official Pride Night
At Disneyland and our friends
Went to it and our other
Gay friends and they
Who are big theme park people including
Nick and Alan who I bet are listening to this
So hey Nick and Alan
But they told us
How much fun it was and
That we were like okay we gotta
Go next year and
Also it coincided with my
Husband's birthday so it was kind of a fun
Fun birthday trip
And we're such park people
That we're like alright let's
We can now see the differences that we
Watched enough park contents
Of the
Influencers and what not to know
Like the terminology now but so
Yeah we went
You could get in as early as six
But the stuff didn't
Start till nine and so it's one of those like
Official like wristbanded events
And everything but
They kick everybody out all the just the regular
Day riff raff
And this is Disneyland Park
Only there's not a California
Venture no no it's only California
Venture which I would it's the
Most heterosexual California venture probably
Is that that six to nine moment
When all the gays are in Pride
Night
And there's no Orlando
One yet
Not yet yeah I mean you know
That's a big thing
I mean it's Florida so
Yeah and I
Personal background here I can make fun
I can make the Florida's racist
Jokes because I grew up in Florida I was there
Lived there from ten to twenty five
So I can make these jokes I'm not just an outsider
And I imagine stolen
Valor
I think it started at Disneyland
Paris though I think they did an official
Pride night first
And then California was
Decided to get on the you know the
Rainbow Bucks bandwagon
And do it but
Well that's a question are you were you like
A little cynical going
Is it a mix were you more
Cynical or more excited
Yeah I mean boy yeah it's
So yeah as a gay man
To preface things no but
No I mean obviously
I'm tired of like rainbow capitalism
And people put a rainbow on a thing
And they sell it to you because they know gay people
Spend money like of course like
I'm very cynical about these things I'm
I'm a pretty left wing cynical guy
Yet I do love the
Parks and I
Like to buy things and they
Have like and there is some level
Of like ironic detachment
I brought to it too but
There is something about
Feeling wanted to buy the corporation
That on some level
I can't fully divorce myself from
They're like oh Disney wants
Our money now like that's a form of
Acceptance like that's nice
And being open
To getting money
From a type of person they don't reject
Our money is as gross and
Disgusting you know it spends the same
Like yeah I mean it's different
Than yeah like I don't know you know
You know Keurig
Putting out like turning their
K into
Rainbow color like you don't need you don't
Care necessarily about there's things
That seem a little more cash in but
Disney like I guess you probably want
It to all coalesce into
Something because it's part of your childhood
No matter how cynical you get or
Like are any of our opinions about the
Company today well yeah we
Are tied up in these stories it's part of our
Childhood no matter what it's also like a struggle
Because like the corporation itself
Is always almost always
Evil and just wants money
But the people in charge of
Disneyland I'm sure there's a bunch of people that are excited
About it and are gonna like oh that's what's
A fun cupcake we could make like
People who do the little projects
And who do like who are like
I don't know like now there's a press you can do a
Cool display in this main street window
Like that's the weird relationship
We know there's people in there who aren't
Evil and who mean very well
Sure no and the general
Vibes are so fun that night I mean
Especially like there are so many people
I was watching videos from people
Who went the previous year and
Like they were in tears going like thank
You Disney for for recognizing us
And then accepting us this is so beautiful
Thank you and you can't
Not be touched by that like even as cynical
As I can be sometimes and
The general vibes are just really great the whole
Time like everybody is so excited to be
There and get their pictures taken with
Every possible thing and everybody
Dressed up and they're wearing their like rainbow
Clothing or
Red shirts as well which has like a real
Historical background to it
That it
It's hard not to be but occasionally
I will have moments like
That way that's pride representation
Why does this like I have a list of things
Like that doesn't seem like
Pride representation to me
But okay like there's
There is there is cognitive dissonance
But it's a fun time though no
I wish they allowed any alcohol
In it I guess I could have gone into
Ogas to drink but that's the one thing that didn't make it
Feel like a up till 1 a.m.
Pride night thing to me
Of like I can't drink at all like
That was my
I'm wondering yeah like well I mean
I guess they don't want to change the rules but
Would it be worse though at California Adventure
Just because it doesn't feel as big of a deal
Because you're not having this event
In the main part yeah
The fairy tale perk yeah that's true
It does mean more
To do it have the rainbows on the castle
And down main street and everything
It does mean a lot more than
The California Adventure yeah
So they lit up the facade of
The theater in Hollywood that they only
Use sometimes
Like the sound stage that hasn't
Been anything for 22 years
Has my back that's great
The confusing looking bear rock
Formation has a rainbow on it you can kind
Of see the thing that I assume is a bear
From its name but it doesn't always look like a bear
It supports me whatever it is
It is a bear and
Tonight we're also going to use the
Other definition of that term
Well I'm humble with that
That sounds good
It made me sad that
As it always does but the country bear
Jamboree has been gone
For so long that like
That would be all the bears would go there
Like that would be just so beautiful like when I
I was looking up history of like
The gay days at Disney stuff
In prep for this and like
There's a great video it's like from 2010
From gay days in Orlando
And those are the unofficial
The unofficial gay days yeah
I was going to ask about that
Have you ever gone to either the
Anaheim or Orlando because they are at both
Places now the gay days
No I have not but I have a funny
Story about that with that history
Of it so yeah so
The gay days in Orlando like I
Believe 1991 is the first
Unofficial start of it and
It was you wear a red
Shirt you attend Disney and wear
A red shirt to indicate you are
An LGBTQ person who is there
To celebrate it is a it was started
As you know a stealth thing or
Not exactly stealth but like and obviously
Not sanctioned by Disney
That's why of all the pride
Shirts they had I bought a red shirt
Oh acknowledges that history too
Yeah and I know they made I am
Certain whoever made the shirt
Said we have to have a red shirt because
Like we want to recognize
Unofficially that thing but sure
Sure but so at 90 so I
Never got to go to Magic Kingdom even though I
Grew up in Jacksonville Florida
We didn't go to Magic Kingdom
Until like I was like
16 or 17 but we almost
Went as
Part of an end of year
School
Trip like end of year school trip and it
Was going to be the first weekend
Of like the first Friday of June
And then some
Nosy parent or
Teacher discovered that
That was gay days that had lined up with
Gay days and so they canceled
It so I here I was excited to finally go
To Magic Kingdom like I finally
Get to go and then
Homophobia cancels it they're like
We're not bringing a ton of school kids to gay
Days no no no like
They cancel it we go to Busch Gardens
Instead which for me
Like I do not like roller
Coasters that are unthemed and it was
Like just it had nothing for
Me it was like you took away the thing
I liked and instead put me in a place where I'm
Incredibly nervous and anxious that somebody's
Going to make me ride a roller coaster that scares me
As a kid yeah
Oh that's hard so yeah you lose
Disney world you don't get to
And at this point in time
Where are you at on your
I'm like 10 then so I don't even I'm just
Learning what a gay day is even
Like I suppose this was
Another of those I remember as a little
Kid like or when
I was nine or so I think my mom
Rented Philadelphia on VHS
And I had to ask her like
Well wait why are people mad at Tom Hanks in this
Movie and she had to explain
What AIDS and homophobia was
To me I didn't understand
So I was this was another of those
Like oh people don't like
Queer people and they don't want to be
At Disneyland because of that or Disney
World because and then you don't
Get to go and then I get
Confused about your feelings about all of it
That like now it's like school telling you we're
Not going because it's bad to be this
What a night what a double nightmare
I can only imagine what a lady
In the 90s especially thought
That was at Disney yeah
What a nightmare she thought oh yeah
I mean they I'm sure they thought
Like there's like live sex acts
Happening down Main Street in Magic Kingdom
If you go on gay days at the very
Least it's just like
Everyone is buff and in
Thongs you will walk around
At least you will not see a shirt
All day yes at
The least I my
Family ended up at gay days
In 95 or 96
Because we just happened to be
There in June and
I don't know I was 10 or 11
And I had no idea
What to make of it because
Yeah I had seen like
I think I had seen Philadelphia
At that point because
I was like hey we live by Philadelphia
I want to watch this movie
It's going to be a romp
There will be some song
Like I love LA
Philadelphia city of
Freedom city of cheese steaks
Why isn't
Why isn't the movie about our town
Happier so I
Didn't I didn't really
Know what to make of it
But it was probably a good like
For you know
A little 10 year old from the suburbs
Go like oh it's just a big tour group
They're just doing everything like
We are yeah yeah yeah
It's just gays who like theme
Parks and we're trying to I do think
It was it was done you know
In opposition to Disney a
Little bit though then when you look at the
History of like Disney and
Gay stuff in the in the 90s
Let's just say that like they
They were both trying to
They had you know Howard
Ashman among many who were
You know these prominent gay men who
Prominent gay men who did major stuff for Disney
But then also they have
All of the conservative
Christians back then saying
Oh Disney's trying to make your kids gay
Like and and so Disney's
Trying to they want to like
Still in the early 90s
So yeah they were so
Read old news articles and it's the same
Shit even on the gay days
Wikipedia it says controversy
And I was like what is it and there was like
One or two sentences about
Like oh the travel
Company was doing the Orlando one
They ended up canceling the one year because they
Started doing gay days and they didn't want to be
Disrespectful and compete but most
Of the section was about religious
Cranks just being homophobic
Yeah well and also
Like they had in Disney
In the 90s was one of several
Corporations that did like
You know extending medical
Benefits to partners
To life partners and so
Just that was a
Talking point of like they're recognizing
This and they like making a part
Of their business they're hiring these people
Like yeah so Disney
So having gay days
Unofficially there wasn't helping
If I'm thinking like a
Disney PR person I'm like well this isn't helping
Us not look like
A bunch of homosexuals
Here having gay days
It's like even it feels like
They're sanctioning it even though
They don't even though it's not really
It also seems like as years went on it was like
Oh yeah we don't participate
In this wink wink and then but they
You know of course you organize it
Officially through a Disney person
At some point but yeah
What a strange thing I mean it's
I don't know it shows you how far it's
Come that they have a sanctioned event
Anywhere and well and then
Last year even with all of the
DeSantis stuff with him
You know like using Disney
And queer
LGBTQ stuff as
His main talking point like
Gay days was a huge
Like it was getting more pressed last year
Than it had in a while because like wow so
You're still doing this even with DeSantis doing
All this stuff like are you scared
To come to Florida for this you know
Destination vacation thing and
And the people they interviewed representing
The gay days group and planning
Stuff they're like oh yeah we're not going anywhere
They're not going to scare us
Away and then my funniest
The funniest one in the clip I saw
Was this bearded gentleman who was
Explaining all of the gay
Day stuff bald in a beard
And he's like yeah you know I love going to gay days
Me and a bear group we go down to
This and see this stuff and then the
Reporter goes like now bear
What does that mean and then the
Guy goes like
Well
Where's the sharing
Yeah
Yeah it's funny that like
I mean looking back
Now just how
The success that DeSantis had
With this as a talking point as
His primary pillar the way this
Mobilized the country really shook
Us up and reminded us of our American
Value he rode it all the way
To maybe
A double digit in one
Election one time primary
Yeah
Primaries maybe tops like
And certainly he's on the short list of the
VP right like
He's gotta be
They aren't saying his name on the news but you know he's in
Trump's head we got the guy wearing the weird
Shoe lifts we got the woman
Who kills dogs they're all still
On the VP list
No yeah
The country bear thing I was mentioning
You can find I think it's
On YouTube you'll find it it's I think 2010
At the country bear
Jamboree it was
It's labeled as like huge group of bears
Like as in the gay
Community bear group they are
They're in the audience watching it and it's
Them singing along with everything like
They love I'm
Sorry I don't know the names of all the characters
Like you guys would
I'm upset go ahead
The guy that turns me on turns me down like they are
Loving that song like they
Though based on the audience
Reaction I think their favorite was Big Al
I'm gonna say
You can watch a video
Of the like
Of the response yeah the audience reaction
Singing along and when Big Al comes up it's like
Wolf whistles like whoo
Like yay they were so
And it was funny at the end of it
The cast member
Presenting it was like we thank
You so much you guys were such
Big fans thank you we love having
You guys there like they were being
Very nice but not
Not recognizing the level
Of gay irony to
This attendance of country bear
Jamboree vocalizing the common elements between
This excited crowd
There is some very good niche
Programming on gay days
Of just like yeah bears go to
Country bear Jamboree
Women who love women
Go to this restaurant teen
Meetup go to this restaurant
You know and it's all
It's so fun it's so
Like the gay days look so fun I want to
Go like now I never win as a
As a kid and then I've like
But I am a real this is
After moving to California
I am so much more a California parks
Person than an Orlando parks person
Though maybe it's just like Florida
Weather reminds me of being like an
Unhappy teenager and so like
Just feeling it it makes me unhappy
How does this square Jason
I feel like Florida weather reminds you of
The happiest you've ever been or will
Ever be
Not teenager
Okay it
Reminds you of the only times you were happy
As a teenager yeah that's true
Well
The weather in California and the East Coast
Had been very similar the last
Few weeks
Just less humidity or some
More humidity than we used to have
Due to our changing
World
No Jason I as a side
Like your love of Islands of
Adventure I totally vibe with that
Because like one of my the first
Trip my family did to
Universal was I
Want to say 94 95
But it was when the welcome center
Was there for previewing the
Stuff and that when I saw
Like I was excited just to write all the
You know especially back the future so excited for that
But when we went that welcome center and saw
I saw there was a spider-man right there I was
Like wait when when is this when is this like
I was and the four years of
Waiting until that was the longest
Four years ever sure and
This is a brag that only matters on
A podcast like this but like I
My mom won
A radio contest to
We got to go to Islands of
Adventure April 99 we got
To go and like preview
I got to ride spider-man before like
Anybody and all the other stuff too but
Sure yeah myself
Oh and then Jason's seething
Jealousy is just a subtle tension
Through the entire rest of the episode
It just probably whacks the Island
Skipper tour books
The spider-man did
Breakdown a lot that day not on
Us but it did break down a lot
It is
The past being
What I feel like people don't remember
How much
Every big new like
Technological breakthrough ride
Breaks down a lot
I remember we were waiting in
Spider-man's line for like three hours or more
Yeah
And even though I love
Being in the Daily Bugle I'm like
It's starting to even stretch my
Love of being in the Daily Bugle
I've read all the file cabinet names
I've explained to my family
So much the differences between Ben
Yurick and Charlie Snow and
Randy Robertson versus Robbie Robertson
Every member of the Daily Bugle
Staff I've listed it for them
It's their I'm sure great amusement
Yes I know what every reporter
Makes I know their yearly salary
And benefits
Can I call out
The thing this is fascinating
In a
You know where things were back then
You brought up the red shirts
And that's how everybody identifies each other
With these events but I read how
You know in order to
Basically back in the 90s
Disney employees had to
Be ready with all sizes
Of white shirts to
Hand out to regular guests who
Happen to be wearing red shirts
That day
So that you don't dare
Associate with
Could not be included in the group
Wow I had heard that
That's amazing
I mean I know I've gone to a Target
Wearing a red shirt and going like
I look like an employee here
It's like blue polo in a Best Buy
You gotta watch out
No that's funny
To think of some you know
Disney family just they're like
Well we're red today for our big trip
That's how we won't miss each other and then
They realize that somebody whispers
In there like that's the gay thing
Oh no
And then they just strip
I'd rather be naked
Alright sorry kids
Trip ended in 15 minutes
On the Warner tour I did
They have a clip package
Of all the things that were filmed there and
They did have a section of it that's like
Ellen saying like and I love filming
Here it's great and we all
Just like snickering to each other
She loved it yeah
It was a great time on the Ellen set
Famously happy yes
But yeah well
It's also come a long way
Disneyland wise
Because there's all of the
Disneyland
Well first of all that
I think it's any sort of
Like
Private event it started in 78
I was looking up a lot of it was from
Diznet.org just to give them
Credit but in 1978
There was a private party organized by somebody
named Scott Forbes
Who was the owner of a gay bar and
They like they basically did it
Without saying here's what it is it was like
A bunch of restaurants
Came together booked Disneyland
Out for a private party which was more common
Back then and it was set up
And done before
Disney without ever any indicator
That it was like a
Off the page gay day basically
So it was set up that way
In this sort of like piecemeal way
And then it was booked and like great alright
Checks have cleared good now what's this event all about
And they figured people figured out what it was
And then there was this like you know
In this still somewhat homophobic climate
Some Disney people are saying
Wait a minute that can't happen we can't
Do that there can't be one of those
And others are saying why not
And then it's the struggle to like
Find a reason like well
It'll be a debaucherous
Affair won't it
Why what do you well don't when they
Get together don't they all
What what do you mean what do they do
It's gonna be cleanliness
That's it that's the issue
The park will end up too and then
The next morning some of this is
Recounted by Bob Gurr that
He said the next morning after the party was over
The manager was ready for extra clean up work
Extra it's gonna be extra
And then our head of custodial came
And said who were those people they said
Why what's wrong there's no trash
This is the cleanest we've ever had
The park
That's wonderful so this seems like
A key moment of like
Oh just get in here and I don't know
There was no end to that that sentence
And then and also
Retail sales were four times
What they usually are for a private
Party so I think from that point on
Things kind of changed in terms of those
Relationships well you know
Another part of that gay history I was reminded
Of by one of the
Friends I went with was the
The homosexual fast dancing
History
This phrase
Yeah which is you know
I'm not the Videopolis expert
Here but yeah when they one of the
Controversies of Videopolis
Or Videopolis was that
Same sex dancing
Was like prohibited
They're like wait boys can't dance
So even if it is not obviously
There are friends who just it's a group
Of girls dancing together but that would still
Break the rules and two
Men were
Ejected from the park for
What was described officially as
Homosexual fast dancing
And this I think
I think that was a freestyled phrase
By a security guard that was straight
Off the dome what a memorable
That then is used in court
Proceedings yeah and also told
This is a family park we do not put up
With alternative lifestyles here
Put up with ejected
That's great that's thrown out
Yeah that is and this is 1980
Just to put it in the timeline
It is always insane
Some of this stuff where it's like
Hey did you not just think
To go down the hallway
And ask Eric the gay man
Who works here like so is
This a thing is this a thing
We should be concerned about
And he would just go no
That's a thing you just made up
I think that was the thing
You made up a thing to be mad at
I think in 78 some
Of the feeling was like well I don't
Know a bunch of gay people in
Disneyland and then a lot of employees
Are like yeah
Maybe it has always been
That way familiar with the creative
Industries in America
Well especially like I
Was really feeling that on pride night of like
If you not I'm sure there
Are lots of heterosexual cast members but
If you like are an adult who
Loves Disney who also is like great at
Dancing and performing and
And you want to it's like your dream
To work at Disneyland it is possible
You are an LGBTQ
Person like you're not
You're likely gay
And so with that trending
Towards it like there definitely was a
Feel of like on the night cast
Members were really enjoying
It and feeling like extra
I felt an extra energy from them
Getting to perform on pride night
Watching those videos even it's like
Everyone seems like in the parades it's very
Excited which yeah same thing I was
Saying before we were like I bet
Even if the corporate over the corporation doing
Like everyone in the parade is like this is cool
Like you can feel something there
I also just to close the loop on
This thing I guess I'm realizing that particular
Thing if it was 1980 then that's pre-videopolis
But then years down the line
Basically like they Disney lost
That and they had to pay the legal fees
And apologize to
Those two who got kicked out
And then
Like not long after
They ejected more people
I was like wait what happened there was that lawsuit
Well no that was just that applied to the two of them
Wait a minute what so you've set up a
Situation where there are only two
Men who are allowed to dance you didn't
Think that was like that like set a precedent
That you had to follow for no no that was
That we gave two men a
Special ability that no one else has
And then the policy becomes like
Okay well no that was about
Fast dancing slow dancing is still
An issue and that came to a head
With a different lawsuit
In videopolis era
So it took two rounds
Of this throughout the whole
80s
I just rewatched the
Defunct clan video on it
And his history talks about it a bit
I think he's like well by that point
Videopolis was on its way
Out anyway and so they're like
They're like yeah we'll just stop
If we're gonna have to allow
Same-sex dancing let's just have no more
Dancing let's just kill the thing
Let's just end it and if this is
What it's come to
No it's yeah I
I mean also on the gay days thing too
Like I think the fun of it
Or one of their coolest things I saw
On their promotion of it like
By the gay
Days representatives is there are
There are tons of families
With you know two moms two dads
Like that with with their kids they want
To take them to Disneyland and feel
Welcome instead of having to
Be like oh well this is I'm
I'm the father and this is his
Uncle or I'm the aunt
Or whatever I'm her roommate
All of these things like you can
Actually like have fun as a
As a family then too like it
And I have to remind myself that like
I obviously
America is very homophobic very
Still but that
The progress made just in like
Ten years of just like seeing like
Like gay parent
Like gay parents with their kids or also
Like LGBTQ
Of like kids and teens
At this event being welcome at it like
That was not my childhood growing
Up at all and I I'm
Jealous of these kids on a certain level
Like like man you you guys
Not not in like the old man way of like
I had to go through all this stuff you didn't
But just I'm
Like boy I wish I I wish I had that
Childhood yeah the chart of like
How fast like gay marriage
Was accepted by at least like sixty or
Seventy percent of the population I forget what the number is
But like it goes so fast up
Like I it is pretty shocking
Like to go like oh yeah all of a sudden
Just a couple years this massive
Change kind of happens yeah it's almost like
Some of these crazy opinions
That come down as edicts are
Minority opinion
Extremely minority
We can look forward to a lot
A lot more minority opinions governing
Everybody yeah
That was
Last fall
When we went and
Hit up some of the parks and
Did our shows in Florida
When I was flying back
A dawn on me I was like huh
I didn't talk about
Politics with anyone
The entire week we were in Florida
Because anyone we met who lived there
Was just going about
Their life they were just doing
Their thing they were just going to work and going
Home and going to the grocery store
Like yeah it's
I met a ton of DeSantis super fans
I don't know where I don't know what you were doing I guess
They were yeah they were they were all at Aventura
Every time I got in an elevator it was at
Half like half of the room was DeSantis at our
Live show I don't know if you noticed that
DeSantis supporters that's weird
They like when we do
The impression of him actually though
Because we actually capture
What they like about him he's a foolish figure
It was all the people in the audience
With the very sweaty faces
They purposefully make their
Faces extra sweaty
In homage to their king
They have a little bottle they keep squirting on
I'm getting a little dry
The thing I
Watch for in like how
Conservative is this like
Airport I'm going through is
I count like Punisher t-shirts
That's the one like especially in Vegas
That's the one I'm like Punisher or
I guess just like any like
Iron sights or like Target thing
But definitely the Punisher shirts which
Maybe as a comic nerd
That is why my eyes drawn to like
A fellow comic oh wait no
That used to be
Such an easy like
Comic convention or Islands of
Adventure Suvid like
Now the Punisher shirt that on
The back says Islands of Adventure
Like oh that's less of a keep
I don't think anyone needs
That keepsake anymore
I would think people now think the Punisher logo
Has always had the blue stripe for
The blue stripe
Oh that was how it was designed in 1971
Sure
Stanley approved that in 1971
You must be a fan of John Romita
Senior and Ross Andrew
I had to consult with him
It's the first time he's been called John Romita Senior
His names mean nothing to me
I know Scott you're much more
Of a Steve Ditko guy
And that's Big Divide or you're a Romita Senior
He likes
Romita Junior though
He does like him
Titan yeah
I in terms
Okay well this is we were starting to
Allude to this area but like
Performers
I think really bringing it
At pride night this was a big thing
This was very much noticed
Last year this made it out if you were
Not at the events themselves
This really like spread around
Online Disney fandom and Disney
TikTok
Just like
Just the suited character performers
That just like
And even regardless maybe of like
Any prior like associations
Of their sexuality it's just like well
Part of it is the dancing is
Just fire it's crazy
Did you find this to be true?
Absolutely like that was
Those videos last year were a big reason
Of why we wanted to go like if
It was just regular performers
And then you know like a rainbow
Cookie we were like eh we don't need to go to that
But no it really was like
The difference you see in the performers
Because like yeah they and this year
Even more like I think they saw the response
And they pushed it
Even farther like as
In like cause you could totally feel
How did they get disapproved?
Like you I was thinking like
Okay they got disapproved but not that
Like they played
Songs like they played I Will Survive
There which you don't normally
Hear at Disney but there's no
Swears in it or they played you know
Shania Twain's Damn I Feel Like a
Woman except it's the man
I feel like a woman
Wait I didn't know that was it damn
In the album
I don't have the full album
Still the one
Is the album still the one?
I don't know the name of the album
The performers are feeling
And this year a huge
Improvement too was that
I also think I do think the RuPaul's
Drag Race has helped like
Expand what mainstream
People view gay culture as in
Accepting it and there were
Like straight up drag
Style outfits on performers
In the cavalcade
Right in the cavalcade they had I believe
They didn't have this last year this year
I believe it was five different
Women dressed in
Drag style outfits that
Were basically it was like this was on Drag
Race the challenge would have been build
A costume based on each of the
Lands like your frontier land
Your tomorrow land and they were
Dressed up as it and they all like they
Look so great like the Adventureland
One was like it was like green
With a big orange hairdo
To you know
The bird the old
Oh that's cool
It was great they were all and they were having so much fun
And the performers in the
Character costumes really especially
The queen of
Disney pride is Clara
Belcal like she
She rules it whoever is
In the Clara Belcal
Mascot costume is a great dancer
They know what they are doing
With their dance performance that it is like
These are moves Clara Belcal does not dance to
Any other day of the year
I don't think
That really does feel like a
Like if I had come in and said like
Oh of course Clara Belcal is a queer
Icon that would be
Such a confusing joke
But reality no
She's awesome she is so
Fun and she is like the queen of Pride
Night this is fascinating new mythology
And really quickly come on over
As the album my apologies
I was very disrespectful to
Shania to Mutt Lang
Come on over
But not the Christina Aguilera
Song come on over come on over baby
These are unrelated
Oh and Aguilera was
Represented there that they played her version
Of reflection
The fireworks the opening
Welcome fireworks
Oh that's smart
Clara Belcal though this is fascinating because
Clara Belcal is a character I think
With no prior
Facets of any
Kind and I think it's right I mean
Like let's all remember something
That Clara Belcal did in one of the cartoons
Or that she's done in the parks
This is a pretty like it was a blank
Canvas and how fun
That they use this canvas
In this particular way
They had a newer suit I think because they had
Put her in a more recent cartoon
She had been back with Horace Horsecaller
Because I definitely have a photo with the two of them at like
Thanksgiving we went to at Disneyland Hotel
That's awesome like eight or nine years ago whatever
So like I feel like she was there but yeah
I don't know that she had such a
There was not that strong personality
It's an implied
Relationship with or marriage to
This is a
Cow-Horse relationship
Okay I have a lot of opinions
Because I had to
Look I looked this up to confirm it for me
To me mentally yes
Clara Belcal and Horace Horsecaller they are
A couple like Mickey and Minnie right
Clara Bel and Horace they're a couple
But because Horace Horsecaller
Even more than Clara Bel is like not
At the parks and have been diminished so much
That for branding
Purposes she is usually they are
Not officially a couple or anything
But she is she is put together
With Goofy yes it is Goofy
And her I'm you know I just Google
Image her she almost like you almost
Could just map Goofy's face on
To her yeah they work as a pair
But to me Goofy is a single
Father of Max
He's not with Clara Bel or he's
Dating like another dog person
Like the his girlfriend in the
Extremely Goofy movie like
He's and he's stealing Horace's gal
In and by getting with
Clara Bel like also Clara Bel can be an
Independent single woman she does not need to be
Defined by dating a guy
Well it's unfortunate that Horace never
Like manned up like they were
In a situationship for so
Long so Goofy
Goofy was going to step in
You know and then other certain
Continuities his wife is
Dead there are multiple Goofy
Storyline like I need this
I've been sad for years
I'm so lonely to start
Over now that Max is
Out of the house
I got nobody he yuck
My yucks are sad
Don't look at them
Yeah I found yeah
On one of the videos I found a picture of the two of them
And I went oh interesting okay
At the good night
Wave good night on the steps thing
And Clara Bel
My husband shared me a picture of it we were
At a different area
So we missed the good nights at 12.45
He showed me the video of like when Clara Bel
Got there to wave good night chance
Clara Bel Clara Bel
And she's like
Bashful doing the bashful
But then Goofy is like
Like comforting her like it's
Yeah yeah you like almost like it
You deserve it and I was just like oh it shouldn't be
Goofy doing this it should be Horace
Was Horace nowhere to be found?
I didn't see him anywhere he was not listed
On the character list or anything
Do they even have that suit?
I told you they did I met him
But they are using it today I see
I see
Last year from the videos Clara Bel was just like
In the mix but this year
On the cavalcade she
Was presented as like she was
Santa Claus at the end of the Macy's parade
Like she was the last one
And like and Clara Bel like they
Didn't have Mickey's in the middle of
The parade waving at people like Clara
Bel is at the end because they know
Everybody loves her
This is like a populous movement this is
Like People's Joker this is like
Fully just done like a
Grassroots that it's like
I don't know
How it happened last year but does it not
See I don't think that there were meetings
In Disney about like
We're pushing Clara Bel
We need to get a great dancer for Clara Bel
I feel like whoever was Clara Bel was
Just like this is my night
I feel like somebody who's
I think anonymous
Made it happen that's just a guess
And if that is what happened that's really cool
I wonder could we get the name could somebody out in the
Audience give us the name
And would they get in trouble if the name
I wonder if Disney policy just in general like
Would that be bad? This is like how onion writers
Don't get the credit
You just have to live you have to have the
Satisfaction if you know that you did it because I would love
To know but is it yeah
Is it like a met where like the
Audience is just so into it and
Then backstage or like
It's like in wrestling where like an audience
Will hone in on
A specific wrestler backstage or like
The movement of the crowd sometimes
If the crowd is certainly up in a certain
Mood they could just like buoy somebody
Yeah on a night I do
Think I I know that
Wrestling stuff too you have
Like one you pick out one guy like oh
We all love Zack Ryder tonight or whatever
Yeah like
We love him every night yes
Matt Cardona yes we love him yeah but
But I do think for
Claire Belkow there was a feeling of like
She never gets a spotlight she is
Kind of like the odd duck of
The group yeah you know she's got her
She is her character is like you look
At her giant shoes like she is supposed to be
Awkward like goofy too and
She's she is kind of like
Or like from Archie comics
They have a similar thing with Ethel
The girl normally coupled
With Jughead that she's supposed to be
Like the awkward girl with big teeth and everything
And like she
Was supposed to be like this is the
Ugly girl like in quotes
That's the and so when you have that kind of history
Then the gay fans
Are like oh no we love you like
You know nobody loves you enough we
Love you like there's that that feels
Like a very like traditional like
Just gay tradition
Of you know we lifting someone up yeah
Uplifting the the misfit of the
Group who even though Claire Belkow
Is nominally a straight woman
As far as like if we're if we're guessing
At the sexuality of the Disney characters
A heterosexual cow with
A relationship with a heterosexual horse
As far as it had been taken
Minnie is bi
This is eight years ago Thanksgiving
There's the new or horse horse collar
Outfit. He's kind of scary. Yeah he is
And I would say that Claire Belkow
Is a little bit like kind of
It's not the best photo of her either
Stiffer, weird. Oh yeah
They've like friend lead her up
I feel like in animation
Sometimes people hone in on it cause each
Each of them have
Interesting character designs
And that can be enough to buoy
Something I was saying as we're guessing
About other characters. Minnie is bi
And she should not be bringing
Her straight boyfriend Mickey
Okay this is a discourse
Going around. Mickey should stay
Home. Yeah. He should not go to
Chapel Rowan shows. He should
Not go to Disneyland after
Dark Pride night. You don't want
We don't want Mickey there at all? No one
Mickey no. Back of the line Mickey
This is what 19 year olds are
Man about on Twitter. You get
Every other night Mickey
I own the place okay
I'm not allowed
In my own living room
Well that's
You know the no kink at pride stuff
That's why Horace isn't there. His horse collar
Is seen as kinking
I never knew the collar
Was kinked. He won't take the
Collar off. He refuses
Yeah I mean
He shouldn't. I agree
The last cool Claire Belkow thing though
We didn't get to see her waving good night
The rest of the group and getting her flowers but
Based on the timing it must have been
Right afterwards they walk her
Through there's the final people at
1am we're there at like 12 55
1am they're clearing out and there's the
DJ on Rivers of America
Right in front of the entrance to
Pirates and he's playing his last
Songs and when he starts
Up a dance club remix
Of when you wish
Upon a star like this dance remix
Then Claire Belkow comes in
And like actually I've got to show you guys
The picture if we're showing pictures here
My husband sees Claire Belkow
Walking towards here to get
To do her dancing and so we
Stop her for just a second and like that's me
With Claire Belkow. You got a moment
The excitement on my face that's the most
Excited I was all night. Oh my god Claire Belkow
And then she
Danced to the full remix
Of when you wish upon a star
And the brilliant
Person who ever was working there
In charge of this. At the DJ booth
They had a spotlight. They shined a
Spotlight on her as we're encircling
Her and then a spotlight on her halfway
Through the song and she's dancing to
The song and it's just amazing
She does the full dance routine and then
Heads off for the night so that was like our last
Big moment. It was so
Great. That is like a magical moment
Really. It really was. This is one
Of the cooler. I would say
The last few years have been fraught with
Not fraught. I feel fine about it
But there's been a lot of Disney parks
Complaints from us. Oh sure.
I'm hearing all this. I'm like this is
Some of the coolest Disney parks
Stuff in a minute. Yeah. Because
It does feel so like
Populist and so like a new
Generation taking over the mythology
And like doing something new with it
It felt like natural. I feel
If they
It's gonna be a hard line with
Disney I think for how
Much they embrace it or not because
If it gets too corporate then it
Maybe this is also my wrestling sensibility of like
Oh wait this is what the
Booker wants now? I don't know anymore
You start turning on it
If it starts to feel
Unnatural and not organic from
The fans but I would
I would love Clarabelle to get like
She's the gay icon of the
Of the main characters
Of the Disney family
Instead of just being like we need a
Third girl in this picture we've got Daisy
And Minnie but a third character
Who else is girl?
Do we have another one?
I don't remember. Does girl exist?
More? Does more girl exist?
It's like how in Looney Tunes stuff you only see
Petunia Pig when they need like some
We have to have one other girl right?
What do we got here?
Let me bring up another
I mean I think this occurred
Last year but it seemed more
Prominent this year and this is something that you mentioned Mike
I feel like
In terms of virality this time
Around Stitch
There's been some Stitch stuff
Stitch has a
Leather costume
Which I feel like I've seen in other
Media. He wears it somewhere
Yes. It's not completely invented
For this. But it lines up nicely
But it does line up nicely
Specifically I think it's
The hat and jacket that Marlon
Brando wears in the movie
The Wild One
Which is if you don't just for the
List it's kind of the precursor to the bike
Riders. Just to put it in
Current pop culture. There wouldn't have been bike
Riders without the Wild One. I can't
Believe that's the name of that movie
Branding wise
I thought it
Was about a bunch of teens
Who rode bikes around their neighborhood
And then I found out it's a greaser movie
I did right before I came here
Saw a clip of
The promotional tour
And they had a bunch of
Motorcycles on an all white sound stage
And I think they gave the cast disposable
Cameras and they were just kind of
In slow motion goofing
Around the motorcycles
And I was like I don't think
This is the tone of this movie
I'm confused
That's a great viral stunt
But you know just like The Outsiders every generation
Needs their like
Homoerotic-ish
Like 50's biker movies
Sure yeah and The Outsiders I believe
Just won the Tony the musical version
Produced by
Angelina Jolie I think
Wow I had to say that
You say that in a bunch of bike guys
What? Homoerotic
What? What do you mean?
That never occurred to me
But no if I had to say
If it wasn't for Clarabel Stitch would be
Number one of the night for us
Oh so you had a Stitch
Encounter then
My husband
Loves Stitch
Loves Stitch so much like he is a gay
Icon to us too like I think he's
His gay popularity has felt
Like a long time
For him because I think it's
A mix of things one the Hawaii
Setting like is like Hawaii
Hawaii was one of the first American
US states to legalize gay
Marriage, marriage equality I should
Say so there's that
Stitch is he's a weird
Little monster with his own like
Found family kind of thing
So like I think that is also attractive
And on top of that one of the two directors
Dean Dubois is
An openly gay man of the
Leone Stitch movie so you have
You have all that in the mix I think that makes
Stitch have a lot
Of gay fans I think
Wow huh so
Stitch at the last
Last year and this year it's listed on
The events here as the Ohana
Family dance party
And it's a great
Setup they have this DJ there
Who is really having a good time he's
Keeping the energy up the whole time like the
The dance performers are sorry
The costume performers they cycle in
And out like for about 30 minutes each or so
He was doing it the whole
Night from 9.30 to 1
The whole time
Stitch was? No no the
The DJ partnered with Stitch they
There's a new well I'm sure it was the
Same Stitch every time but
No there was time for a new Stitch
Performer to cycle out every like 20
30 minutes but the DJ
Was spinning tracks and dancing around the
Whole time and getting the energy up and
DJ Tetris
Is that right? I have the
Undercovertourist.com
I haven't seen DJ Tetris
It names DJ Tetris
Now that could have been last year could have been a different
There's the one DJ I know at Disney is DJ
Wendy Walker who does a lot of the
Different things and we've seen her a million times
At different like she's DJed
Everywhere and only after I was around
We ever went to was that like 80s night and she
Was there too so I wonder if she was doing something
I'm sure she was I just don't know where
DJ Tetris that sounds right
He was he was great it was at the Tomorrowland
Terrace so right by the
Galactic Grill
Which is where I had like colorful
Churros I will say they gotta
Get their food stuff figured
Out next year because this happened last
Year it happened this year not that
They ran out of all themed food but
They had three things that were literally like a rainbow
They had a rainbow trifle
At Jolly Holiday I want to say
They had they had a rainbow just
Slice cake at another one
And they had
Oh and they had like
A rainbow churro thing they all sold out
Immediately like you could if you didn't mobile
Order it at nine o'clock on the dot you were
Not eating any of this stuff
Oh jeez
I saw they had switched the gray stuff
To the rainbow stuff
The rainbow stuff gone immediately
That sold out really quickly
From what I was reading
Gray stuff is kind of good too so I bet rainbow
Which I don't get why how do they not get
This is the second year and the
Second night of the second year and
The tickets for the event sold out
Immediately like we were lucky we have an
Annual pass friend who bought our tickets
On the early annual pass window
And when it sells out
That fast how do you not make
Enough rainbow stuff
To at least last till ten
Like how do you not make it
It's literally called stuff
Like you're making it in vats
But yeah the Ohana dance
Party was really great
Because I think too they
There is a general sense for Disney
I think when they're like well if we don't have
A gay or queer character
If the story is
We're one family
Everybody's a family
If that's the message that's gay enough
So that makes Ohana
We round that up to gay
And so he started in his Elvis
Costume dancing to songs
Even some current stuff and also
Brittany danced to Toxic and then
And then this
This is me guessing at why
They programmed it but then Angel
Comes out Angel the Stitch's
Girlfriend and that to me didn't feel like
That Disney was trying to say Stitch is not gay
Here's his girlfriend Angel right here
And they
Angel get booed
Some of her characters are allies
Throwing stuff at Angel
So and then Angel dances
Some and it's fun and she's you know a big
Pink character that's fun to see on gay
Night and so starts in Elvis
Angel comes in and then
After Angel dances then
Back comes out Stitch and that is
When he's in his biker outfit
Which we called Stitch of Finland
But yes I definitely
Think that the planners
Looked at here's all our Stitch
Costumes these are approved to walk around
The park it's already been signed off on so we
Don't have to get new permission and there just
Happens to be one who looks like a gay 50s
Biker so let's have him come
Out and dance to stuff and
Yeah it but this was
The darkest point for me at the night though
Because I missed
I came back I my husband
Stayed at the Ohana dance party for like
Two hours that was his main thing
He wanted to see he wanted to see every dance
But he told me oh if you want to see something
You can go but I'll tell you what I saw in a sec
But before I did that when I
Left I didn't come back
And he tells me he's texting me like
If you can get back here right now get right now
I get like five minutes after that
And he's like oh you missed him dancing
To eye to eye from
I was like oh that burned
That burns to miss eye to eye
But when I got there
He it was the gayest
Moment of it I would say because it was
Stitch of Finland dancing to
I will survive
Okay yeah yeah
I was like okay this only has gay connotations
The clip that went viral
Was him dancing to Rush by Troye Sivan
Yes yeah my husband got a
Footage of that too the dance
Which I learned that Troye did you know
That Troye Sivan was a child actor
Didn't I send this to you that he was little Wolverine
He's little Wolverine
Wolverine origins
Wolverine oh that's fascinating
Since he's so successful I don't feel bad making
Fun of a child actor now but like his
I felt so bad from rewatching the scene
Of like when his claws pop out and he has to
Like look up to the camera go no
It's really funny it's so bad
I have a little bit of a proposition
You know we haven't
Brought this up yet
Was all this Stitch talk but we are
Graced as always
By one of the great Stitch
Impersonators
Mr. Jason Sheridan
Is Stitch in the room with us right now
Can we speak to Stitch
I've just messaged you
The lyrics to Troye
Sivan's Rush
Do you think you might be able to grace us
I'm so sorry I am not familiar
Oh I don't know the melody
No I think this is a
I think this is a spoken word piece
I know the melody because I listen but Jason
Just spoken word I think is the best way to do it
Because last time you just said you'd heard of
Troye Sivan so you've gone further
I like the album a lot
How about it
I didn't say I'm just saying I thought
No let me say it Mike
It's very hip
Jason I think any part of it
I think anything that strikes
I'll just do
Chorus
That seems to repeat
I feel the rush
Addicted to
Your touch
I feel the rush
It's so good
Addicted to your touch
Ohana means family
Wait how did that get in there
That was great
Can I maybe ask
Me verse 2
Oh sure
Here we go
Past your board in the heat wave
Recreate the sun
Take me to your feeling boy
You know the one
Kiss it when you're done man
This shit is so much fun
Pocket rocket gun
Well now I'm intrigued
When I first heard
That song I thought the line was
I feel the rush
Addicted to your touch
Which is a better rhyme with rush
But it was not the line it's touch
Wait it's not better
Rush touch it's worse
It's spelled the same
But it's just a little different
You think it's a better line though than touch
It might be a better line
Rush touch is a better rhyme
It's better for me and I think it's better
A better line
And by the way there's no more hip way
To say butt than tush
Well I thought it was funny that you were saying tush
Wow 2024
We're bringing tush back
Which we should do on this show
You know what I'm the first one
To say I'm done with seats
We're calling it tush
Tush is the new seat
Fine
The thing that made me miss eye to eye though was that
The one list on characters I wanted
To see was
In Galaxy's Edge
C-3PO was going to be there
And I was like well this is the closest to a gay
Thing for Star Wars
And I wish it was at Star Tours
But it was at Galaxy's Edge
And it was empty Galaxy's Edge
Because nothing was running
Most of the rides were closed down
Only the big oldies
Were like Space Mountain Star Tours
But the new stuff not running
Rise was not running
Was Millennium Falcon running?
Well okay but in Ogas you could walk in
Ogas was a walk in
And you probably could have gotten just a seat at any time
How empty Galaxy's Edge
Completely empty except for the few
People who were there to get pictures were like
The Mandalorian and Grogu were also
Walking around and this is when I learned
I don't know if you guys have ever been told this in
Galaxy's Edge with trying to meet a
Character there but when
C-3PO came out we were looking
At the cast member of like
So where's the line cause that's how everything
Was aligned this night and the cast member said
There's no lines in Galaxy's Edge
So just you know when you can get in there
And I was like there's no lines at Galaxy's Edge
For character meets so it was just
You just kind of had to like shove past
Like I feel like it's my turn
This person got their time with 3PO
So I'll get my picture with them like so
But yeah it was just it was a free for all
It's just kind of a happening there
That happens when Chewbacca comes out
And you just turn around and Chewbacca's
Right there like giving you a hug
Also it's irritating to me
That that suit is
Just sitting backstage at Disneyland
And he doesn't come out during
The regular day ever
They have it it's just sitting right back there
Bring them out! It's a perfect
3PO costume like
Which you'd want to see
Cause then it's really reflecting everything
Around you they also really
Should dye the Chewie suit rainbow colors
There was that Christmas toy they made of a wookie
I think that was like Christmas colors
Oh really?
There was a life day robe
Christmas ornament
Yeah I think there was actually a dyed
For a man I just remembered
But of course they can't have too much fun at Galaxy's Edge
Can't have too much fun
It's not about fun
I do have a list of the characters
And when you look at Galaxy's Edge it is funny
Cause it's like Mandalorian Grogu
Ah Ahsoka
Okay yeah they have television show
See 3PO
Yeah
That's the closest to recognizing
This is the game though my friends I was with
They were like well then it should be R2 with him
It should be the gay couple
But no it was just 3PO
By himself
And yeah
I was very happy to see 3PO there
And he was by the garage
Where the land speeder is and everything
So also he's like
Behind the gate too
And of course he only says canned phrases
Like the guy ahead of me
Did say a funny thing like
Well it looks like you just had an oil bath 3PO
You're looking great and he's like yes thank you
I think is the canned reply
That can apply to anything
Do you think he was ever
Do you think he ever had eyes for BB8
In that run in the time when R2D2
Was like under the sheet
For most of the first movie
For most of the movie
He was too sad to run
That's right 3PO
He'll never know
He can't wait a decade for R2D2
To wake up like he's got a life to live
Frankly I don't know when this is going to happen
The second he's back I'm back with it
Another situation shit
Maybe that's why 3PO got his red arm
He was trying to dress up
Oh yeah very good point
I had a question about specific
Characters
Did you meet
This is one of the most specific characters
That's been brought out in the parks
But it has storyline that makes sense
Ethan clad from strange world
Yeah okay
Let's talk about Ethan
So strange world is a movie
I haven't seen either I don't think many people have
But he is
They made it very
Tough to see or to know it existed
Pretty well reviewed
From what I read about it
Visually looks very nice
But Ethan is officially one of the
There's a joke that there's always
The first gay Disney character they've promoted that
Like a dozen times
But he is canonically a gay man
In the movies
I believe it is a step
Higher than
Two women hugged each other in the background
Of Rise of Skywalker that's the first gay
Star Wars character
So he's there
Also this was in Tomorrowland
This is where they put all the canonically gay
Adult characters
And these characters are not
Princessy characters they were in Tomorrowland
He was there as was
Fastos everybody knows Fastos right?
Fastos
From the eternal
He was
Brian Tyree Henry's character
And he was also the first
Major gay Marvel hero
He has a husband in the movie they kiss on screen
Which you don't see in many Marvel movies
It was a very intentional move in that
Movie because they're like this always gets
Cut out of Marvel movies or they're always
Scared of having a gay thing for international
They always hide behind like well international
Audience is a little scared so
But Fastos is gay in it and so
But also Fastos takes responsibility
For like the bombing of Hiroshima in the movie
Which is kind of a doubter with the first gay
Marvel character like yeah
So there's pluses and minuses to
Fastos there's good things and bad things
Very confused cause like
Oh Brian Tyree
Henry
Brian Tyree am I getting the name right?
I think that's it right yeah
He's a very good actor
Chewookie Young White
Who is the voice of Ethan
Clad very funny guy
But yeah there's
Some of these characters
These movies you're like wait when did
Yeah that did come out
And the third of the canonically queer
Characters there for the photo op in Tomorrowland
Was America Chavez
From
I do remember America Chavez
Yes Multiverse of Madness
America Chavez is a canonically
Gay character queer character
In the Marvel comics
They put her in the movie and the extent
Of her queerness in that movie is
If you look really closely she has on
A rainbow pin on her jacket
And she also does have
Two moms in the movie just like in
The comics but you see your two moms
For five seconds and then they die on screen
In the movie that's the extent
This is what
I've been saying Disney
What Disney has done in the last
Five ten years is they've pioneered the
Subliminal gay kiss
The gay kiss where the shot
Is faster than the speed of sound
And you need
To load the characters with some of the most
Upsetting trauma
Imaginable
Responsible for Rochma
Your moms definitely died
We showed them dying on camera more than your
Pin on camera
These two women are part of a montage showing how
Lightyear was foolish with time
How he let his whole life
Pass him by I think there were two women in there
So I don't think about it we're moving on
Forget it it's in the past
But Ethan he is this
Interesting thing of like well
As far as characters are going to have there
They either have to be canonically
Queer or it's
Mickey and pals wearing rainbows
Or it's evil queens
Those are the three like they had the villainous
Is there like they had the
Queen of hearts the evil
Queen from Snow White Maleficent
Of course Maleficent like you can see her having
A big gay fandom but
The queen of hearts she was great
We this was another of our silly photo
Ops they you know the
The stationary teacup outside of
The teacups right
They had for photo ops
They put a little sign above it that says like hashtag
Spill the tea
So we're like well we gotta
Get a picture in this stupid thing
Once again Disney with the
Phrase ology of 2018
But then when we sat in it then we heard
Somebody like shouting and we're like whoa what's going on
But it was the queen of
Hearts screaming like get out of my way
I need to get to wonderland
That's cool
She was a face character that night she was
Really having fun
So the evil queens were having a good
Time though yeah the official
Gay characters of Tomorrowland like Ethan
And Festos they were just very much
Like yeah you know I'm just
Here and let me name my
Male partner character from the movie
And so you know that I'm gay
And hey isn't this nice get a picture with me
Like yeah it was just a casual chat
With Festos but though
Another queer friend of mine pointed out
Like you know where was
Mulan in this if we're gonna have
Like you know they're gonna play reflection or where's
Loki who is a gender fluid
Character in a magical
Sense like where's where's Loki who's
I don't know about MCU
Loki how queer he was I didn't
Watch season two but I feel like he
Is written to not not to be straight
But I mean he's he has that like magical
God thing like of all gods
Are queer anyway I don't think a heterosexual
God seems weird to me of like
All the Greek gods fucked each other right
I think so
But yeah where was
Loki where was where why was
Mulan represented there
Or or the big one I was
Like wait shouldn't Timon and Pumbaa be here
Like come on like or
At least Timon like but that
That felt like the line for Disney
That they're like well we don't want like
Mulan a princess here
To represent it though though I will
Take you know step that back a little bit because
They did have a frozen section
They did have Elsa
Olaf
Kristen Bell's character
Anna
Anna Elsa Anna
Olaf and then
The another blink and you're missing
This guy technically is gay character
The owner of the
The
Bath house or steam room the
I'm saying bath house
The bath house in frozen
No it's the remember in the middle of frozen
Where they they stop over the guys like he's
Selling stuff they're like a rest stop
Yeah yeah yeah yeah that guy
Yes yeah he's he's there
And in the background of that shot
It's him with a with what seems
To be his husband in a photograph so
Technically a gay
Character
So he's there for
He was there for photo ops too so
You're like person the logic
All night of who's there and why
And you're like somewhat satisfied
But like
Could be more I mean maybe this is the progress
That's made over the you know we're only
In year two of this but maybe by year ten
And beyond we're just we're
Kind of fully identifying
A lot more characters yeah
I know there was I also
On there was another one I wrote down
Like oh this is where they felt like they were really
Stretching their Disney history of like
I notice this anytime I watch those
Documentaries on the history
Disney on the official one on Disney plus
Which usually have been taken down for tax purposes
You can't even watch them now but
They always have to even when it's a Marvel
Thing that Walt Disney had not one thing to do
With they have to show a clip of like
And Walt Disney also sort of felt
This way about things like
Like are in the star I remember
On the star tours one they did
They have to start with George Lucas
Actually was there the first week of Disneyland's
Opening as a kid he went there I was like
So this is how it connects to Walt Disney
And so at the start
Of the big fireworks
At nine thirty over the
Over the castle they play a
Clip of Walt and I'm like what
Possible clip of Walt could see it
Sounded all inclusive to gay people
And it was
To all that come to this happy place
Welcome and so they play
That clip I was like I guess
That could sound
That's inclusive sure
But it's like I've
I'm not even saying I think Walt Disney
Was like an especially homophobic
Person but as a man of his
Age then I would have to think
He weighed in particularly
He would just like I'm sure he's no more
Homophobic than the average man
American man back in the fifties
Which would be extremely homophobic
Your base register
No long hair fellows
No suspicious facial hair
Think you're a gal
Exactly yeah but so when they
Played that clip I was like oh they had to check the
Box of like show
Have some way to portray that this is
Connected to the long lineage from
The opening day when Walt was here
I guess if you if you think
Of that speech as the
Constitution of Disneyland and if
We're going to be literalists about like
It is all who come
Disneyland is your land
And there's no I kind of like using
That as a wedge
To say well look look what he said
Let's interpret that as
We have to be accepting
It's the Bible you're reinterpreting it every
Few hundred years that's what
Walt said now we reinterpret it
And other people are like well
But he was giving that speech to a group
Of as far as we know all heterosexual
Men so he only meant it's your
Land so that
Only applies to them there I found my
Way to justify there's traditionalists
With Walt and then there are the progressives with Walt
Who reinterpret his language
Well that's what I was hoping was because there
Were so many I think
The user I watched
A video Patrick Dougal there
Was so many
Remixes and stuff being
Played I thought they were
Going to read when I started to hear that clip I'm
Like oh that's going to be great they're going to
They're going to scratch over welcome
They're going to remix like
Well well well but they would never
Do that they it's
So on such a high
Pedestal but it would be very funny
To start remixing like
The beat drops during a walk
If the DJ had done that during
The Ohana dance party that he shut it down
They'd have cut the lights
Like no that's too far
I think the crowd but that's a thing where it's like
The crowd would have lost it
I just was like what are
Other Walt Disney quotes is there anything else
We can interpret and I think I found one
Right here this is the one I just don't know if you ever
Said it on tape I love Mickey Mouse
More than any woman I have ever known
If you need
Something
That's perfect
They should have AI recreated
And play it loudly in the parks
They'll never stop using AI Walt if they
Start oh yeah I did have one other
Bit of food I wanted to mention too I was
Going over my notes like other stuff I did it was
The what the
Kids today would call the rainbow glizzy
But it was the a loaded
Corn dog was
So the little red wagon was
Selling it was selling regular corn dogs
Too but it was the
Rainbow corn dog which
Let me find that here
Is that just relish and
Ketchup and mustard
And some
Peppers on it too so yeah they had
That too and also I had
The rocky road funnel cake at
Hungry Bear which was good and
Which was just like a scoop of rocky
Road ice cream on top of the funnel cake though
The pride rainbow
Funnel cake unfortunately sold out
Which is too bad that sucks all the
Rainbows went immediately like and
I also I am normally not the type
To buy the $27
Cup to put things in
But my husband was like we gotta get the pride cup so
I even mobile ordered it and
Then when I got the hungry bear they're like
I'm sorry we're out of the pride cup we sold
Them all out you gotta like
But they at least gave me a refund
But they're shooting themselves
In the foot this is strange
Did you by any chance stumble into
The golden horseshoe with the line dancing
No I did not see the line
Dancing unfortunately I missed out
On that there was too many
Too much stuff to do
I missed out on the
There were singers
About a 20 minute singer thing in front of
The small world where they're
Singing a lot of like Disney hits
Including like reflection in front of it too
Another one they counted as like
A gay song
Was the one
Two worlds one family from
Tarzan
Yeah that was among the musing too
I saw a photo op that was yeah
That's folding in Tarzan and like
You could stand under a scroll
That's a Tarzan quote which is I won't pretend
To be something I'm not
Which is kind of a strange Tarzan
Which is of course about being like a man
Surrounded by apes
Same thing being an ape man
Is kind of the journey
Queer people go through all the time
They're raised by apes
It's very strange
I don't know if sexuals are often broodish
So yeah
Yeah
No I mean I guess
Tarzan as well it is a story of like
Oh my adoptive father doesn't love me kind of thing
Like I guess you could like see that
And his mother loves him and his dad's mean
Like sure fine but yeah
Sounds close
Oh and then yeah
But the This Is Me song using that World's Greatest Showman song
It did I grumble
About it being a fox song
Though I did see other parts people say
This is a big moment
Because they're playing a fox song
At Disney
On Main Street
And apparently that was like a first
When they did it last year
They did it again this year but last year
Apparently was the first playing of a fox song
It's hard to conjure
What other fox songs are
What else is now in their
Arsenal
There's not like a predator song
Sound of Music
Any Sound of Music song
Don't Ray Me
Yeah they aren't really making music
Could we have Sound of Music in Disney Forward
Sound of Music Land
Oh yeah you could be in the hill
You can track this vehicle go up the hill with her
It'll speed you around
Yeah that's not bad actually
That is good
When we did The Simpsons
With all you guys here in person
And there was a Planet of the Apes reference
With the music
That's when it hit us like oh wait Disney owns that now
That's a fox song
They can do an apes ride
At California Adventure
I wouldn't think they do the apes ride at Disneyland
There's an apes ride
At the Fox Studios Malaysia
Park with the weird
That still has the fox license which was left in this
Weird limbo of can we still
Do it but they have a full
Somewhere between I forget if it's trackless or not
It's Rise of the Resistance
It's Resistance-esque it's Transformers-esque
And it's all about Caesar
It's kind of like the second movie
That exists in Malaysia
And nobody acknowledges it
Those apes will never age
They're CGI apes you're not going to look at
When you go on a ride now
And you're like well that's not what Dominic Toretto looks like now
Or whatever
Caesar is timeless
Daniel Redcliffe is a little boy forever
Yeah we're all every day
Watching a particular age
Of this very famous movie
That is true
The rainbow
I mean I love the corn dog in general
It seemed like last year
Their churro choices were better
They had like a sour cherry one last year
This year was just I think it was like
Cake batter
No it was cereal milk
Frosting with it and pineapple
Sprinkles which it was fine but
I kind of wish they had the sour cherry one
I think they have also they had popcorn
Lucky Charms in it
Yes yeah which I didn't get that
Because I watched that St. Patrick McDougal video
You mentioned Jason
He pointed out the like yeah
All of the Lucky Charms
Or rainbow
Yes rainbow cereal bits
He said they all just go straight
To the bottom instantly
Like they just all fall
That doesn't feel like that would work
Not very even distribution
They need to work on that for next year
The food is more interesting and fun
Than a lot of the Disney food
It does sound like the operation
Side of it needs some fine tuning
Yeah I
I did want to try
But I was like I don't want to overload myself
But like the oh I had the
I did have the watermelon Mickey Beignets
But that's because we love the Mickey
Beignets
We went to the Mint Julep
Area and got that
It was one of the last things they were closing down
Though also you talk about Disney things breaking down
We had bad luck
That night on things breaking down
Like we
On Mickey Runery where I had no problem
And my husband and I
Split off from the group
The rest of the group were like oh let's all do Space Mountain together
But Space Mountain was like an hour long thing
And we might miss the cavalcade
So we're like no let's not do Space Mountain
And then our friends who did it were like
They made us switch cars, the car wasn't working
So we had to get in a separate car
We went on Star Tours together
I have never had Star Tours break on me before
It broke like it did the first
The first light speed jump
It goes
It like wrenched us forward harder than usual
And then the screen
Went up and
They turned out
And they took us all off the thing
And put us in another one like I've never had that
That's good they just reloaded you immediately
You essentially got the real life
Millennium Falcon experience
Yeah and my back hurt
While I assume Han Solo's
Back must always hurt
Now you know what it was like to be him
And also the worst for our pals
Were we went on Big Thunder
Because I was like oh we got to do
Big Thunder at midnight I want to see nighttime
Midnight Big Thunder, but our other friends
Went on Pirates
And they were stuck on
Pirates till after close
They had to be
Escorted off Pirates
We cannot move again
That's how we got the Clarabelle video
Because we were waiting outside Pirates to meet up with them
We were like well surely it's going to start now
And then it hits one and they're like
Everybody clear out and they're still
Stuck on Pirates
You know where they got stuck and had to walk off from?
I think it was
I do think it was the big
Group area, you know the auction
Area
That's where I want to walk off I think
We got stuck there for like
10 minutes once under the box
That's almost about to drop on you
We were under that box for like 10 minutes
Toward the end
They got escorted off of it
They missed a few things
The transcendent Clarabelle moment
They missed it, but then again I got to be jealous of them
Because at some point
Their group, they met
Harvey Gian from
What We Do in the Shadows
Oh he's so great on that show
He's great, he's
A queer performer and his character
Is the greatest, I love him
I have a celeb crush on him
And when I saw
Photos later that he was like
He was there on the night with us
I saw that and then friends later said
Yeah we actually bit him and we
Got to take pictures with him
I missed that, so if the
Cost of being stuck, I don't know if I'd make
The trade of like, I couldn't see the Clarabelle
Dance and a couple other things, but I could
Have met Harvey Gian if I was being
Stuck on the Pirates ride
I don't know, I might have made that trade
He was in like a
Disney bounding even I think based on his outfit
It was like a Donald-ish outfit
He was white shirt, blue
Side cap kind of thing
Very knee high socks
To represent Donald
He's got it all on his social media you can see
Wow, so an accidental meet and greet
Yeah, I think that was the only
Celeb I knew of who was at it
That night, but yeah
I was very jealous of my friends who got to meet him
Gavin Newsome was there last year
Oh, okay
He tweeted about it last year
I don't know if he was there this year
And I didn't, I got to see
I wanted to get the Andor part of the new Star Tours
But it was the Ahsoka one
Which I only had to guess out of
I didn't see Ahsoka, I watched
Andor, I didn't watch Ahsoka, but
I know there's like space whales in it
So the space whales are very central to that
New section of Star Tours
That way the space whales further
They apparently show up in a lot
Yeah, it's all connected to that
Rebel show and stuff
It's such pure Filoni things
As a Star Wars fan
Of a certain vintage
To be told that Clone Wars
And the related things matter
Like in the cartoons matter that I totally
Ignored, I was like, I don't like this
I didn't, I
Confused, there's too much to take in
I have been told these didn't matter
All these characters from the Clone Wars show
It's confusing to me
Imagine my feeling where my entire canon is
Star Tours, the rest of it
Like wait, so I gotta know about who these other
Who Han Solo is
Ugh, I'm exhausted
I'm out, I'm just saying
Rise of Skywalker, it seemed like they were
Looking for something and if you
Just put some space whales in there
Might have gone a little more smoother
It would have fixed it
Well, I mean, sounds like
Sounds like a great evening
Sounds like a particularly fun
Just like, I don't know, like a pretty
Juiced up, good desserts, good performers
Just kind of like
Like a best Disney has to offer
Sort of thing, besides all the rides being
Open or working
Yeah, the cast members were, the vibes
Are great, I would, yeah, if you've not done
It was my first time doing any of the
Dark, Disneyland dark events
And I'd say it was a lot of fun
I mean, it was like, I believe it was
160 a ticket and it's good
6pm is when you can start mixing in
So you get 6pm to 1am
And most of the stuff's
Running and you're there
You're not doing this to ride Rise of the Resistance
Anyway, you're not coming there for doing that
So you're not gonna miss that
But yeah, the food, I just
And even the, just the people at the
Churro carts were like, so excited
They had like glow sticks and were like
Dancing to all the songs at the
Churro cart in Fantasyland
So, oh, sorry, one other character I meant to mention
Was the, again, this is for
People younger than me, Tinkerbell
And her many Pixie
Pals from those direct videos
Pixie Hollow, yeah, the characters
All the Pixie Hollow characters were out and they were being sassy
They were also having
Some fun
Within reason of their characters
I don't think they were breaking any character rules
But they were being a little extra sassy
Which was fun
But yeah, I would say it's, I bet it
It certainly grows from here, especially because
I think the, you know, the finger thing
Means the money, like they made
They made good, they made some bank
On this night, and I think Disney can see
It's worth it to get those
Rainbow bucks more in the next
Year, like I'm, the red shirt I bought
Is oversized for me, because they were out of my size
I had to buy a size up, like
Oh wow, you are decked in, you got
Several things, yes, I'm wearing my white
Pride night 2024 hat
It's the official one
And also the, I have
My fanny pack as well
That's a new thing
They got you, they got you
For my husband and I, we really are into
Fanny packs are our now walk around thing
For the parks, like we just like having it side
On the shoulder, it's our favorite
Thing though, he, my husband wore a
Stitch backpack
From Tokyo Disney
Which is, it's stitch upside down
So it's like he's like showing his butt to you
As the thing, it's like
That little rascal Stitch, like
His tush, his tush, oh I'm sorry
He's showing his tush to you
It's 2024, it's tush
And that was great, while dancing
The Stitch performer loves seeing anybody
Wearing a Stitch merchandise
Would pose extra and be like, do the heart
Signal and point at you, like it
That's my tush
Look up all the videos of the dancing
At least, and you can see how much
Fun the performers are having
My gaydar was going off on all
These performers who are like, oh you've got to be
You've got to be some part of the rainbow
Having a great time, finally getting to
Not have to tamp down
Your, yourself for
The family daytime performers
Not yet, not give like
You know, just 40%
Which just reads like regular good dancing
You can actually take it all the way up
You can't serve as hard
On a regular Disney day
They were serving C-Word
That night, Claire Bell was definitely
Serving C-Word
C-Word is cow
I'm glad someone else said it
I didn't do my notes
He said it on the way over in the car
He said the word
He just was saying, he said the phrase
And he hasn't said it
So I just brought up serve
I know what it means
But I was just trying to prompt Jason
It means cow or it means Claire Bell
Yeah, she was serving cow
Jason should say the word on the show
That is another of those like
I'm starting to feel old things of seeing like
TikToks that just use the C-Word all the time
That content is like
Wow, we just say this now?
That's okay
This was almost the biggest no-no perhaps
Yeah, and now it seems fun
Jason's in the car just yelling it
At people
I'm doing the Claire Bell dance
He rolled the window down and started screaming at people
I said Jason stop
I'm not doing it right
Are you out of the car?
He's sort of throwing things at people
Hey, let me do a round of it really quick
And he got a bullhorn
He put the big bullhorn from the Dukes of Hazzard on the top of my car
And he started shouting it
He brought a horn and attached his own microphone to it
Yeah
Well, it's all the new words of 2024
They're all in play
For all of us
But jeez, what a blast
This is a very fun thing to thank you for doing this
And bringing us a trip report
It made me feel like I was there
Maybe I've got to do one of these in the future
It sounds really fun
Henry Gilbert, you survived podcast The Ride
Thank you for joining us
And making time in a trip that had that
And a bunch of other park stuff and podcast stuff
Let's exit through the gift shop
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Thanks for having me
I always love
Being on Podcast Ride
You guys are the best
I co-host the podcast
Talking Simpsons with Bob Mackey
Where we talk about The Simpsons
In chronological order
And we are in season 4
Slash 14 right now
We kind of bounce between the two
To be classic and
And keep going forward though too
But yeah, we just
I guess the most recent guest appearance
Of one of you guys with Scott was on
Our one about the EPCOT
Where they visited
Teacher of the year
Little Richard
He got a lot going on on that one
The show really hates EPCOT
At least back then
They don't hate EPCOT now
They love it and think everybody should go there all the time
But go to Disney Plus
And you can find all of these scathing
EPCOT jokes
These jokes about EPCOT being boring
The Simpsons almost is like all the
And all of that
There's that one joke especially in Itchy and Scratchy Land
About like Nazi supermen
Or superiors or something
That was their equivalent of Walt Disney
Made that
The Simpsons maybe
Takes credit for the only subversiveness
Anywhere on Disney Plus
It's kind of amazing
It's impressive yeah
If you want to know all the history
Of every joke and every change line
And all these things
Our job too I think is to explain
When there's a Crystal Pepsi
Joke in there and people are very
Confused by what Crystal Pepsi is
We will explain it
Yeah we do that every week
And we are sponsored at
Patreon.com
Where we have a ton of bonus stuff
That's also where we do the What a Cartoon podcast
Or we also cover
Futurama and King of the Hill
There's just as in depth
And each month we do a super long
Podcast about an animated feature film
We just did 5 hours and 40 minutes
On Mulan
Which led me to do a ton of research on
The Orlando
Animation studio that was also a ride
Or an experience
Yes
Mulan was one of the ones when that was still up and running
It was their major
It was the first one done primarily in Orlando
I read stories of the
Animators saying
It was like 7 day a week
Production crunch
In the last 6 months
Being there until 11pm
Hearing people screaming on
Tower of Terror as you're going home
From animating all day
We haven't talked about that
As much I feel like even though that is a fascinating
Thing and Loom's Large in my head is a
Kid going and being like oh they're making
A movie in there
That was such a good deal for me
My parents had a tour group
Past and I like
They let me wait and join up
With the next one
Because I was like stuck I need to like keep looking at this stuff
I was so enamored with that
That's the big one we've missed
There's a great doc on YouTube now called
Beyond the Glass which is like a
90 minute interview with tons of the animators who work there
They have a funny story in there about
How if a tour group would
Go by and there was a particularly attractive
Woman in the group
One animator at one end of it would go
Swing and that would let other
People know like a hot ladies
Coming through and they'd all
Say swing through the
Because they were working there when Wayne's World
Was relatively new
And we finally had a sound
To associate with a certain
Thing that our body could do
That's what Jason was saying when we were in the car too
That too
Claribel pictures
She's on the program
Oh I love that's good mythology
I'm going to break up the new situation
Goofy broke up Horace Scorescaller
I'm getting in there my hall pass
My hall pass is Claribel
My hall pass is a fictional
Animated character just starting to pile up
Jason can serve C word himself
Yeah
But anyway yes
Talking Simpsons podcast and patreon.com
Talking Simpsons then and most social media
I'm H-E-N-E-R-E-Y-G
So yeah thanks. Thank you so much
For having me guys. Of course thanks for doing it
Yeah jeez what a blast
And all the episodes we've been on
On Talking Simpsons have been a lot of fun
And what a cartoon you guys are so nice to smash
Oh Saturday morning All Star Hits was so
Fucking great
Still on Netflix
It's there. Netflix isn't one of the
Places that yanks yet
We were talking about Max and all that earlier
Thanks Netflix for not yanking
Everybody's in LA
No yank for that either
I love that show so much
That everybody's in LA was so great too
Thank you for my small
Percentage of I'm a massive
Fan of the rest of it too
Alright fast for us for three bonus episodes
Every month check out podcast the ride the second gate
Get one more bonus episode on our VIP
Tier club three you'll find all of that
At patreon.com slash podcast
The ride
Could we ask
Stitch
To change the lyrics
The way I want Troye Sivan's
Song Rush to sound could he say
I feel the rush addicted to your tush
For me. Would he be so bold
Let me see if he's still here
Ok please check
Just make sure
Ok sounds like he's here
Sounds like he is here
Could you just say
I feel the rush addicted to your tush
Is what I want him to say
I feel the rush
Addicted to your tush
It sounds better
I think it's better
Two notes Troye Sivan one tush second
Do it as Stitch
Forever
Dog
This has been a forever dog production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner Brett Bohm
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit forever dog
Podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple
Podcasts, Spotify
Or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news
By following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team
And liking our page
On Facebook