Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Pod Dome here on Podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
Hey, let's open up the dome and let the people come in, to quote the refrain that is done hundreds and hundreds of times in a row at the end of this special.
Scott Gardner's coming in. Mike Carlson's coming in.
I'm here. I'm in the dome. I am coming in.
Watch out, I'm coming in.
Either through a wet car or through the sky. Jason Sheridan, hi.
This is very exciting. Scott, what age did you see this at?
Oh, man. I know that I saw this when I was making Moonbeam City, which was like 2014.
I think Tommy Blacha exposed me to it and kind of helped make me more of an aficionado of like Canadian oddities.
OK, like this. He like we're watching this and I'm like, holy shit.
And then he's like, you got to go to Canada and just go and like, don't even worry about doing anything.
Just go like watch TV. Just go see what their news is like.
Yeah.
Which and then I did do that trip and I I did spend a lot of time just watching TV and I fell in love with an old game show called Bumper Stumpers,
which is a game show where you guess what like truncated like novelty license plate you get like its clues.
You know, I'm trying to think of an example of a you know what I mean?
Like if puzzles were embedded in novelty license plates with twos and us.
So you would just decipher what what it was trying to say or they would hide part of it?
No, it would come up and you would have to guess what the phrase is.
And there'd be like little codes like I'm like I'm trying to think of one.
If it's like like two lips, it wouldn't spell it out like two lips.
And that's too obvious. That would be like maybe like less to use.
And that's somehow too.
That's this is not good for an audio medium to just Google image.
It's adults with like boring kind of like communications jobs in Toronto,
had to go sit in little cars with each other and and guess what, you know, novelty license plates meant.
Wow. OK. Bumper Stumpers.
Was it a famous Canadian game show host like somebody we should have like not on the show,
maybe on the show, but like as far as radar?
Well, you know, it's an alternate universe up there.
So it's hard to know. You know, probably not like Al DuBois, Al DuBois.
I don't think famous here. Yeah, I could be wrong.
You know, maybe he's made his name in America since then in a way I don't know.
Check it out, though. It's just, you know, to see some adults take, you know,
pals and co-workers getting together to sit together in a tiny car and solve puzzles.
Well, of course, we stumbled upon the littlest hobo last year.
Yeah, I must have found that around the same time.
Many years of this show about a dog that goes around solving people's problems.
Yeah, within a matter of, you know, 20 minutes fixing everything that was wrong in a series of people's lives.
Maybe I haven't even said this in the show. I was watching some littlest hobo like maybe last year.
And there's an episode where a man has a theory about the littlest hobo that he's a metacanine, a new super species of dog.
Does he then try to like exploit him because he might be smarter than other dogs?
Does he try to put them behind bars or like take them out on the road?
I don't think so. This is season five.
So at a certain point, somebody's like somebody actually is like, hey, this dog has solved a lot of people's problems.
What's going on here?
This is sort of like the Frank Grimes episode of like, let's comment on the fact that this guy always gets his way and has won a Grammy and been to space.
That's like where we're deep in.
Can we address please that this dog seems to just like move newspapers from here to there and somehow in doing that solve entire family crises?
So I don't know. I mean, we will eventually get more littlest hobo on the show because I think we all like.
I'm glad it stuck with you.
Yeah, I'm a big fan.
There was like, boy, there was a time where that that that that whistly song was just like such comfort to me.
There's a voice just inspiring.
Hey, it's a real calming agent.
Yeah, as a lot of Canadian programming, especially from the 1980s, seems to be to me.
A song I feel like is not played in this special, despite how long it is that the littlest hobo theme is not played.
I mean, yes, absolutely a big missing area there.
And then also, like at the end of the special, lots of famous Canadians are trotted out in open top cars and that one of them is not the dog that played hobo.
Yeah, exactly.
Littlest hobo.
Now's your time.
Open up the dome.
I'm excited to let people know what all of this refers to.
Hobo didn't parachute in.
Man, I mean, look, spirits were lifted.
This is a heck of an event.
But imagine if they had shoved the littlest hobo out of a helicopter and you might think that sounds danger.
No, I don't think so.
I think he's landed on his feet.
And I do think he's landing on his feet.
Oh, you think no parachute?
Parachutes fine.
We can slow him down.
You said you pitched basket, though.
Is that what you just said?
In my mind, the dog was in a little basket with a parachute.
A regular dog, maybe.
But the meta canine that is the littlest hobo.
And I know that was pretend in the show, but even the actor dog who played him is himself a meta canine.
He could have conveyed that much emotion.
He could be in a basket.
He wouldn't have a parachute.
He would flip the basket around.
What do you mean?
Oh, using it as a parachute.
He would put the handle in his mouth or her mouth and use that to slow down his descent.
Absolutely.
I think you're right, because that's a resourceful dog.
Can I say something?
This is sort of tangentially related.
Did you know Bubbles the Chimp is still alive?
I didn't.
Yeah.
This is something I just saw yesterday.
I think Bubbles is 40 years old.
Michael Jackson's monkey, Bubbles the Chimp, is still alive.
Living on some sort of...
Was Bubbles born into Michael's custody?
That's a very good question.
I wonder how old he was when they first encountered each other.
Yeah, that's a good question.
I think the thing I read said Bubbles is 40 years old.
Hopefully not an old article.
Hopefully not from three years ago when something bad has happened to Bubbles.
Oh, yeah.
I got some big PTR curse potentially.
Bubbles is not in his 90s though, so that's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But is he in...
I don't know monkey ages.
Is he in his monkey 90s?
Yes.
Very good point.
I'm not sure.
The Wikipedia says is a chimpanzee.
Yeah, yeah.
Not was.
1983 born.
A chimpanzee.
Nice.
Retired of Florida.
That's the dream of any chimp.
I was thinking Bubbles had passed away, but no, Bubbles still alive.
That is fascinating.
Captive chimps look like they can live longer than chimps in the wild.
So Bubbles is old for a chimp if he's like 40 or 41.
Yeah.
I mean, Little Mama, the chimp Little Mama was over 70 years old.
Who is Little Mama?
I don't know.
This is just Wikipedia.
I'm just giving basic info.
Little Mama, 79 she made it to.
Wow.
Good for her.
Geez.
Well, something for Bubbles to aspire to.
If the oldest chimp was also the most famous chimp.
Right.
If that is the case, I'm taking Bonzo out of the running if Bonzo is a chimp.
I don't keep my species very straight.
Yeah.
But yeah, hey, something to aim for.
Bubbles, if you're listening, maybe are because you're a smart chimp.
Of course, yeah.
Retired chimp.
Nothing much to do.
Catching up on my podcast.
Wearing like a tracksuit at an animal retirement home.
Pretty good.
It's a pretty good premise.
Like Jordan and Jesse Goh, actually.
Yeah.
That's my dignified chimp voice.
All right.
Let's get into what this is, what we're talking about.
And it's something you might be a little bit familiar with because we've seeded this before.
What we are focusing on here is the Sky Dome.
And it's some percentage the Sky Dome, the Toronto sports venue, which is now called Rogers Center.
But more primarily, it is a TV special and live event that took place called the Opening of Sky Dome Celebration.
We're doing it right now because we kind of promised it last year.
And now it's landed perfectly via parachute into this is the 35th anniversary of that event.
It happened 35 years ago this week.
So this timed out very nicely.
This is something that was kind of backdoor piloted during a discussion of Alan Thicke and the Ninja Turtles
rendition of Santa Claus is Coming to Town, which itself was kind of a backdoor pilot for Alan Thicke's music,
which is something I've been wanting to get into for a while.
And one of the big pieces of it, absolutely, is his performance in this hours long TV spectacular
celebrating the opening of this incredible new arena.
And we got into it in the episode and it was clear that there was it was going to have to be a rush job.
We weren't going to be able to give it the full amount of time.
And I was so happy that you guys were both you just signed off right away and like, OK, we'll cover that later.
We'll get we'll get to that later. Put on the list. Yeah, of course.
I'm glad it was like enticing enough for you because you weren't familiar with this event previously.
Oh, I know of it. I never sat down and I can't remember if I sat down and watched the full special.
This is doing this in that episode was like doing pandemonium circus in our happy birthday Islands of Adventure.
I know. So it's the same thing would have been as ridiculous as the clowns at a circus.
Why? Yes. I mean, they had enough time.
They should have had like no throwing a Betty Boop would have been at this too.
Yeah, I think they could have squeezed it in.
Yeah, yeah. It might have been between the horniest beer commercials I've ever seen.
It might have been happening deep in the background.
You might have like you would have to like this is like a really complicated for you.
Remember that R.E.M. video from a long time ago where it kept like it keeps zooming into different details that are all happening in the same eight seconds.
Imitation of life. Yes.
This is like that. If you go to wides of the Sky Dome opening, yeah, you see murders happen.
You see like, you know, somebody serving papers to a criminal and then being taken away by the feds.
There's so much happening in every frame.
Compression is the word I kept thinking.
I kept feeling like like a 10 minute segment felt like I had watched it for like four hours.
Yeah, there's so much going on jam packed in these segments and in the audience.
And it's like too much. It's almost cut away.
And you can't really like look away because you might miss something big.
I think I might have. We should all help each other.
Make sure that we remember all pertinent and strange details.
I wrote notes down, but I was like, oh, my God, I should have started watching this four weeks ago.
I this is not enough time for me to like comb over this footage because of how much stuff is going on.
And as the special goes on, we might be missing details due to the torrential rainfall
that just keeps seemingly getting worse and worse or like every camera cut.
I'm like they they shouldn't be holding an electrified and held microphone.
They're going to get electrocuted.
Well, yes, this is kind of the key detail of this tale and of the special.
I've come to the table with behind the scenes info about how all of this played out.
And rain is really at the heart of why there was a sky dome made at all.
So before we get into the special, let me say some of the backstory that brings us to this moment in June 1989.
So I said some of this before. Sky Dome is today called Rogers Center.
It's the stadium in Toronto that is home to the Blue Jays, their baseball team.
And it is the world's first stadium with a retractable roof where you can decide we can flip this roof on or make it go back the other way,
which means that you can play baseball or whatever else you're going to do there in rain or shine.
Key detail underlying that part.
That is the entire reason that it exists is so we can do events without the threat of rain.
And why does this place get built other than just the functional, you know, that makes sense as a thing to have?
But also there's been domes, there's been the Astrodome.
Why do this situation where it could go either way?
Well, in 1982, there was a Canadian football game.
The Toronto Argonauts were playing.
And it was like a big high pressure game where like all the most important politicians were there.
And it was being viewed by the largest audience in Canadian TV history.
And it got rained out so hard, aggressively hard, brutal amount of rain.
The bathrooms overflowed.
It all ruined what was supposed to be a great day for Toronto, a great day for Canadian football.
Every day is a great day for Canadian football.
We're all big fans here.
And this is Americanized.
This is the tackling football.
The tackling.
I believe so, right?
Yes, yes.
No, I have it up.
I'm just saying this to differentiate from American football versus rest of the world football.
Which is soccer.
Which we call soccer.
But you did it in a way that made all three of us look like the most non-sports-knowing guys possible.
You exposed us.
I was trying to be as...
The audience did not know by this point.
They didn't know until now.
I was trying to be as simple.
This is the sum-kicking football?
I understand your intention.
You said it in a funny way.
And then Scott and I just went, uh, duh, I don't know.
And then we still didn't know.
That's the thing.
Jason looked like a fool in one way and we looked like a fool in another.
He set all three of us up perfectly to look like we didn't know anything about sports.
I don't think it's expected that we know a lot about the Canadian football league.
I assume this will be the last time this ever comes up.
It better be.
We're trying to protect our masculine image, Jason.
Because it might help Jerry Seinfeld like us more.
Oh, I know. I want him to.
He wants to restore that traditional masculinity.
And if he ever hears this show, we're fucked.
We could beat him.
The three of us could beat him up.
Single, each of us.
At any time in his life.
I just like, yeah, he's, I guess he's saying.
I don't know, but dude, that guy seems like so rugged and tough and not that just like
seeing video of somebody not being pleasantly received at a college 23 years ago
would be enough to blow him over like a leaf.
Yeah.
And also he thinks Hugh Grant is like the prime masculine man.
You're like, oh, OK, I guess.
I don't know, what do you think?
Our problems with this film and this guy run so deep that we haven't even talked about
the bizarre treatment of Thurl Ravenscroft.
I know.
This is not the place to do it.
But if he thinks his way back into relevance in 2024 is to pedal a bunch of inaccuracies
about voice talent, great Thurl Ravenscroft, it's got nothing coming.
It's got nothing coming.
Maybe this is a backdoor pilot for the full Thurl second gate episode.
That's true.
We've been talking about forever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know from the beginning we were saying like, let's highlight these guys who we like.
Yeah, why not?
Let's do that.
Yeah, sure.
Absolutely.
All right.
More old men to come.
And maybe Jerry would like that.
That we tribute old men.
Tough guys.
With rugged wrinkly faces.
And deep voices.
Like Hugh Grant.
So a bad day for Toronto.
And this must have been a thing where they couldn't, as I'm wrong, maybe it's a thing
that they couldn't predict, where maybe having the option to close it or to keep it open,
because I think it's a place where weather can whiplash back and forth.
I experienced really nice weather there.
I experienced really terrible weather there.
So the next day, a bunch of people who were at the game showed up at City Hall and chanted,
we want a dome.
We want a dome.
And that began the process and earnest of figuring this out.
Now, a bunch of not interesting logistics happened from 82 to 89.
But by 89, it has happened.
In May, 87, a contest was held to name the arena or the stadium.
And Sky Dome was chosen by 2,000 people.
So then they had to take those 2,000 and put them in a big lottery ball thing.
And then Kelly Watson of Ontario won.
And she got two lifetime passes to every event held in Sky Dome.
Really good prize.
But there was also some scorn because Lloyd Mosby, the Jays center fielder, did not like the name
and in fact said they should ban that person for life for coming up with Sky Dome.
What?
This is strange to me because so much of my interest in this event and in this place is the name.
Sky Dome, it's so fucking awesome.
That name rules.
Also, slow your roll, buddy.
You play for the Blue Jays, okay?
It's an MLB team that's not even in our beautiful country of the United States.
Oh, your problem with them is that they aren't in America?
I was just talking.
I was going to go along with it so I knew what I was talking about when sports were involved.
I was going to go like, yeah, notoriously bad Blue Jays don't look that up.
We'll be proven wrong immediately if I something, I'm sure.
I have, talking about being on the sportsman, I have watched a lot of Phillies games this year.
And I still have no idea what the infield fly roll is.
What?
What is the infield?
I don't know.
Why are you asking him?
He just said he doesn't know.
I think when you hit a pop fly into the infield, but I don't, it's something the way.
We can't unpack this because either I know exactly what that is or I'm going to just embarrass myself so thoroughly right now.
There's no way.
We can't do this.
Thoroughly.
I only, a few weeks ago, cemented understanding of what a sacrifice fly was.
You mean like when it pops up and the guy in the outfield catches it and then the people on base still can run?
I don't know.
You don't know generally what we're talking about at all.
There's a bunch of unwritten rules of baseball and I don't even know all the written rules of baseball.
But I've been enjoying it.
I don't know.
We are getting on the path to 15 minutes of fumbling through Wikipedia pages.
This is not Jason.
This is for you to look up on your own time and then do a book report later about what you learned about the infield fly roll.
Yeah, but I don't know.
I agree with you, Scott.
The name is just great.
It rules.
It's so James Bondy.
It's really, isn't it?
And it's like combines the, well, wait, no, Thunderdome is not James Bond, but it's cool movie titles.
It's Thunderdome and it's meets Skyfall.
I wish it was still the Skydome and I don't even hate Rogers Center as a name.
I think it's a fine name.
I do because it took away Skydome.
Yes, it took away Skydome.
It's not the worst.
It's not as bad, like nothing, no naming device, I hope, I shouldn't say will ever be as bad.
Currently, no naming device is as bad as crypto.com arena, which we should be.
We should be ashamed as Angelenos.
We should be ashamed as Americans.
We should be ashamed as human beings that we all didn't do enough to stop crypto arena from happening.
Yeah.
And really, I've said this before.
It's the dot just as far as name, like things that sound interesting or cool crypto, obviously the association.
But the dot com is the thing that really fucks it.
Yeah.
You know what, because Crypto Dome is good.
Crypto Dome is awesome.
That sounds pretty cool.
I'm totally on board if it's the Crypto Dome.
It's the dot com that makes it seem like not classy.
It's like the Disney name mechanisms where we can't, like, look, I'm not bringing this up to hate.
I think all the footage coming out of the Tiana ride is looking great and I can't quite, or is it Tiana's Bayou Adventure?
Tiana's Bayou Adventure.
It still feels like, couldn't we call it Tiana Mountain?
Like, what is it?
Why can't we have our stupid names anymore?
Yeah.
Tighten these names up.
Bayou Mountain would be pretty fun.
Bayou Mountain's all right.
Because that's like silly and whimsical.
Princess Mountain.
Whatever.
I think Keep Mountain.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
We're always talking about this.
But yeah, the hyphens and the dashes and as many words as they can pack in.
Please simplify it.
Yeah.
And truly all would be forgiven.
I think everyone's going to call it the Tiana ride.
I think so.
I think that'll be like Star Wars land is the thing people call Galaxy's Edge.
Tiana ride.
Oh, you want to go into the Tiana ride?
Yep.
So we'll see.
Maybe it'll change.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Or we all finally start acting the way Disney wants and saying their big clunky titles.
Maybe we'll all finally fall in line.
So another thing that happens in the intervening years from announcement of this project to
opening is that they start adding a lot of shit to it.
Already, they have to invent this retractable roof situation, which has never existed in
the world before.
And it's like pretty efficient and cool, but extremely expensive.
And then they start throwing like, well, what else can we do?
And this place, when it opened, they threw a hotel on.
They threw on a health club.
Like you could go to tennis courts in the baseball stadium, which is all in the unit.
It helps create this kind of like urban hub where it used to just be like rail yards.
But also now this price tag is shooting up and up and up and bringing up the pressure
a lot for this place to deliver.
It is home to what it opened as the 600th McDonald's in Canada.
Wow.
OK.
And I think at the time, the most expensive McDonald's you could find almost anywhere.
Wow.
So those prices are crazy.
So that made people upset.
And then also a Hard Rock Cafe in Wright Field.
There was a Hard Rock Cafe with windows.
What?
I didn't see that.
There was indeed.
Holy shit.
And I will also show you this T-shirt that commemorates it.
I'll show it to you, Jason, who is wearing a Hard Rock Cafe City shirt right now.
And that is cool.
But it's hard to beat this different Hard Rock logo with like more sleek underlines.
And it looks more like a chrome ball.
And then it says Sky Dome Toronto at the end.
And that Sky Dome logo is good, too, with like sun rays going into.
The D turns into an open dome.
This shirt is great.
It looks like a production company's logo or something from the 80s.
Oh, yeah.
Like a Vestron video or something.
Yes.
Do you know it was a full Hard Rock or was it like kind of a little airport style?
I think it was full.
I believe so.
I was looking.
I couldn't figure out merch in there.
I don't know.
I don't know if they had maybe after the ceremony, they got all of Glass Tigers.
That was my next question.
What did they have in there?
This is 1989.
Glass Tigers Tambourine.
Lover Boy?
Did they have a hit?
They're Canadian.
Yeah, Canadian, right?
Did they have a hit, though, by 89?
I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
Another stuff was in the early 80s.
Yeah.
Corey Hart.
Need some Corey Hart.
Yeah, yeah.
Was this a Hard Rock Cafe that was only accessible if you had tickets to a Sky Dome event?
I'm not sure.
And there is still a restaurant there.
And I think you, I believe, friend of the show Bugman Buzz Buzz has been in whatever
that restaurant is now.
And I think you can go and like kind of see the game.
I could be wrong.
I could be totally wrong.
But I think there's parts of this facility where you can like get a sliver of a game
even if you didn't pay for the game.
Really?
Just a hell of a hack.
Interesting.
Again, tell a listener if you're in Toronto.
Tell me if I'm totally wrong.
OK.
So this is an ambitious place.
Just one facet is the Hard Rock Cafe.
And when it's ready to open, they cannot just say, hey, everybody, it's open.
They have to do a big, mighty TV broadcast, something that is like the Olympics opening
ceremony, but just for Canada.
That's kind of what this is.
It's the size and scope of that.
And I'd say more entertaining than some of those that have existed here and there.
Those are pretty good every year.
But I mean, come on, this is insane.
They're not as tacky, I think, is the problem.
No, no.
They are still in the same zone.
Tackiness will always be a part of these things, even if it's not like 80s, 90s style tackiness.
You know, I feel like at least every Olympics opening ceremony will have things that are
somewhat embarrassing four or five years later, which is good.
That's true.
That's what we want.
Right.
Because if they aren't taking big swings, if it's not embarrassing, that means they
aren't taking big swings.
Right.
So that gets us to this broadcast, the opening of Sky Dome, a celebration.
Now, I have played probably a lot of the same clip on the Alan Thicke episode, but I'm going
to do some of it again because I can't help myself.
Big opening titles with all the stars are going to be there.
Glass Tiger, David Clayton, Thomas, all the stars, all the stars are out.
But then we get into Masters of Ceremony, Alan Thicke and Andrea Martin.
And then thousands of people run out and come out.
Thousands of people run out in glittery uniforms.
Again, repeating some of this, but I mean, how could you not?
This is such a clip.
What a moment, right?
It feels like so many Simpsons bits come from that.
It feels like so many Simpsons writers saw crap like that.
Yes.
And what made fun of it in various times during their tenure.
Now that we have a show that we can comment on things, the first show, seemingly, that
has any sense of irony.
Just making fun of this type of thing.
That chunk of the lyrics of the world's largest retractable seal.
Words that have never been in a song, ever.
They are having trouble getting it in one breath.
It's so cumbersome to even say.
Multipurpose.
I mean, yeah, that's a part of it.
And they need to fill that line with something.
But multipurpose, you'd also say about a gymnasium.
You'd say that about your high school gym.
You can play sports in there and you can do a dance in there.
So it's not a very sexy word to put in the song.
80 stories, high dome.
That's also very, I said last time, it's so Christopher Guest.
That feels really Christopher Guest to me.
That they would rhyme Skydome with such and such high dome.
And then it reminds me so much of the Fred Willard, Catherine O'Hara, Midnight at the Oasis
audition piece from Waiting for Guffman.
Namely, this cutesy thing.
And they kind of like, you know, that's Catherine O'Hara's SCTV castmate.
And he's kind of a cheeseball like Fred Willard.
Yeah, a number of SCTV people in here.
Oh, yes, we got another one later.
I was looking, this made me look up, like, hey, whatever happened to that documentary
or roundtable Martin Scorsese was going to make?
Oh, yeah.
And it just has been delayed due to his other directing gigs.
And making lots of things.
Yeah.
He had to film his TikToks with his daughter?
Come on, man.
He had his TikToks with him.
Maybe if he'd make the movies a little bit shorter, he could fit more of them in.
I thought it was supposed to be like a roundtable and then Netflix uploads all the episodes
because I have not seen a lot of full SCTV, maybe little segments.
There's DVDs.
You can track that stuff down.
Yes, Timelife.
Timelife was very big in selling DVDs of that.
SCTV recommendation, Rick Moran is performing downtown, you know, pink leisure suit
in the style of Michael McDonald.
It's got that famous Michael McDonald sketch, which is really good.
But then there's this other one.
He just does downtown like Michael McDonald with odd stray Michael McDonald backing vocals
while he walks through the least glamorous part of mundane Ontario you've ever seen.
Maybe it's one of my favorite sketches I've ever seen.
And this one I saw last night where Bill Murray is Joe DiMaggio.
Who is he playing?
Have you seen this one ever?
That sounds familiar, but I don't know.
He was running a restaurant and you eat for free if you pitch him a ball that he can't hit.
Oh, I did see this.
Yes, I did see this.
He just slams them all into all these full people.
Somebody just talked about this.
Was this on like a fly on the wall or something?
This came up somewhere for me to see it.
Possibly.
I don't know.
Flying Wall, Dana Carvey and David Spade's podcast that we're often discussing off mic.
DiMaggio's on the wharf is that sketch.
That's a good one.
Okay, but so that is so insane.
Some of the strangest lyrics that have to serve us so much that you've ever seen.
And that this is being done, this is what, a 50,000 person venue?
So crazy and a perfect place for Alan Thicke to shine to give that perfect Thicke cheesiness.
And we've played little clips here and there.
And I'll play one more.
But the thing to say is that this opening alone is 10 minutes long.
And that's really where I got the feeling of like compression where I felt like I had lived a year in 10 minutes or something.
Your daughter was a different size when the song began.
It was like interstellar.
I came out of the room and I had gotten like, she had gotten older, but I hadn't.
Because I was in like a time warp from watching that.
Like the atmosphere was different where I was watching it.
Lightyear happened.
All of your family aged and died.
And then similar looking equivalents showed up many generations later.
And I only experienced 10 minutes of the opening of Skydome.
The world's largest kickline sent you through a wormhole.
All those flapping of legs created this cosmic effect and whipped them around the earth.
When the football players referred to their feet as Tootsies.
500 years passed.
Now I rewound that a lot because I was like, are they saying Toosies or Tootsies?
I thought Tootsies.
Perhaps it is Toosies.
I think it is Tootsies.
I think Toosies makes more sense.
Tootsie is also Tootsie Goodbye.
Like that's an old time song too.
Not that it was this, but I'm just, I don't know.
That's why maybe I heard it that way.
Is that one of your songs by the way?
Tootsie Goodbye?
I've certainly heard it, but I don't think it's not one of mine.
It's not one of yours.
Not a Desert Island disc.
No.
We need to do, we need to make that Spotify playlist of your top 10 Desert Island discs.
Oh yeah.
But I think after maybe you're hearing Tootsie Goodbye, whatever it's called.
If he sits down and listens to it, it might do it well.
That could enter the top 10.
I got a clip of this and I might have cut it off mercifully before it gets to Tootsies.
But I picked it kind of to keep underlining the point and to the point.
And I think we can all tell where this is going.
It's like what's going to happen in Act 3 is so clearly broadcasted over and over again in Act 1, including by the song.
Just to stop it there.
And we can close the roof whenever storms are due.
This is the most specific song ever written.
And it's about how we got a roof and we can close the roof.
And when there is rain, it's a cousin to if the song was like, it's like now a musical salute to the general concept of being dry.
Oh man has loved being dry for years.
Safe from water, safe from beers.
So then then some football players join and we get close to the Tootsies.
OK.
Like all the dancing football players are.
Tackling.
I don't know what they said there.
No bucking.
No football is the one with bucking, right?
Right.
Bucking is bucking.
I assure you the middle school football team really didn't have any interest in hearing about singing in the rain in my experience.
You would have signed up to play if they were doing singing in the rain.
Well, I I never played, but I was the manager for what football of the high school football.
No, the middle school.
Pretty good.
What does the manager role entail?
Getting ice and water.
So you were the P.A. is what you were.
Yeah, I was the unpaid P.A.
And I think I was they were they wanted me to place the what do they call the orange stand that you put the football on the kick.
You're going to fuck us again here.
Well, I didn't I just said the stand was fine.
I don't know the rules of I watch football and it's like I at least played baseball.
I understand most of baseball.
I never played football either.
But they at some point they gave up and having me run out to place it.
Oh, because you had to like you had to keep the pace of the game and run at all.
You were like a ball boy.
Like that's like how the ball boy tennis ball.
They don't have those like a thankless job.
How did you get yourself in this position?
Yeah. Why would you do that?
The science, the sixth grade science teacher, a man who would occasionally fall asleep due to his narcolepsy.
I had a narcoleptic teacher.
He asked me it was like you got to do this next year.
And I was helped.
I was where I was doing the yearbook.
I was.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, absolutely.
That makes sense.
And then I was also managing the football team and football season course ended.
And then the play started.
I want to say I think I take Umbridge with you saying I was managing the football.
Because it sounds like you were doing something.
Being this manager role.
But I was managing implied that you like could say something and they would listen to you.
Scott, look, I kind of I kind of take my kicks where I can get it.
OK.
And you did.
It sounds important.
I bet.
That's what you're saying.
It sounds like I'm managing.
But like I guess a manager could just be really like a functional job.
It was mostly dragging the bag of balls and occasionally filling up the cooler and the
water dispenser.
But you were never in.
I had to use like a hand cart because like a person can't lift a full like water.
Right.
It's incredibly heavy.
And I was like tiny.
I was like four foot.
You're the size of the water.
And then every now and then, like the football players were like, oh, we're going to give
you a swirl.
And that thankfully never happened.
They threatened swirlies that didn't come to pass swirlies.
But it's like this guy thinks he can manage us.
The Roughnecks on the what is what's the seventh grade team?
Whatever the what was the Chichester Eagles?
The Chichester Eagles manager.
Did you but you never got in the huddle?
No.
OK.
Even like I just want to say, do a bang up job.
And just playing is winning.
They as well have a ball like they're like, all right, we're going to do.
But I'm going to blow it here because I don't know anything like we're going to go down
the field.
We're going to do this.
Yeah, I want this to pop.
And he goes, hey, fellas, we're all going to it's starting to rain.
How about a little song to cheer you up and get you motivated?
I bet you all got pretty gals out in the stands.
Be sure to wave to him and blow him a smooch.
And if one of them accidentally hits me, I won't complain.
Let's wrap this game up.
I bet we all got to go home and do our homework and read Mark Wade's newest issue of the Flash
comic.
My tootsies are getting stuck in the muddy ground.
It's cold out here.
Why are we out here at all?
I also I think what happened with that with the narcoleptic teacher is that you were on
one side of the room.
Then he dozed off.
You at casual speed walked to the other side of the room.
He went came back to.
Whoa, how did he?
What happened?
Speedy Gonzalez here.
How did he get from here to there?
Right.
You should be down on the football field, my friend.
I think it was the first science class, too, where we're in like the science classroom
with lab tables, big black like stone tables.
Yeah.
And beakers and chemicals.
And looking back, I'm like, I don't know that you want a guy with narcolepsy.
In a room full of children and chemicals.
Well, if someone spills something, it'll presumably wake him up.
Whatever.
Yeah.
What if he falls asleep on the Bunsen burner or something when it was on with his tie right
in there?
Yeah, really bad.
He didn't fall asleep standing up, though, I guess.
I guess not.
You'd have to be sitting down usually, I think.
I guess it depends how bad your narcolepsy is.
I mean, he was very old, too.
So he might have been sleepy.
No, he told us he was a narcoleptic pretty early on.
Did he ever fall asleep while standing up right into a standing skeleton model?
And then it looked like the two of them were getting it on.
Did that ever happen, Jason?
Well, the skeleton model would put in the DHS tape if he would fall asleep.
Oh, he was rigged up like mousetrap style.
In my absence, here's the plan.
I will fall asleep into the skeleton, and he'll push in a copy of...
What year did Kevin Klein's Dave come out?
I feel like every classroom had a copy.
Well, what year did it come out?
And then add six years.
The hottest movie in Hollywood, Dave.
The hottest movie.
Wow, I didn't know that you were a manager.
That's incredible.
We keep finding lines.
I know.
Wow.
So a bunch of stuff is said in this song.
They claim that it's multi-purpose.
They're like, we will do operas here.
No, you won't.
I bet if I looked that up, there's never an opera in Sky Dome.
I mean, it sounds cool, but that's the kind of thing they have to tell people in the neighborhood to get them up.
They told people there would be operas at City Walk, I bet.
Okay, then very good.
Build away.
I feel like Sky Dome does not have the best acoustics for an opera.
Most likely not, or it really lets it shine.
That voice can really travel all the way to the rafters.
And then there's also, there's going to be Broadway, which is the excuse then to give all the baseball players and football players...
I forget now what they sing.
That's not the worst thing that I forgot.
Do they all do like, memory?
I mean, that's performed later.
That is performed later in a very confusing fashion.
Memory medley.
Yeah, it is a memory medley, because I was like, why is, she's from Cats?
They say she's from Cats.
But she's singing the way we were.
Yeah, yeah, really through me.
And then it goes into the Cats memory.
And then it kicks into the hit.
Yes, Trump's favorite.
But so, yeah, this thing goes and goes and it's full of like brassy singing and that kind of stuff.
It's just like, you could tell this was like the dream come true for whoever was putting into it.
Like, ah, finally, this is what they'll remember me for.
And this part goes off without a hitch, I got to say.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's like crazy and corny, but boy, I'm eating it up.
I love it.
And then like when you think they're out of moves, then they do like, give me an S, give me a K, and they spell the entire name.
And then this is really where it gets like super Christopher Goose Simpsons that they, it's sky dome, sky dome, your dome, my dome.
Incredible.
People just used to write stuff like that.
It wasn't supposed to be laughed at.
I know.
That is so weird.
So weird.
Yeah.
Did you find the writer of it?
It says in the credits and somewhere in the special, I think they, I found interviews with the choreographer.
There's nothing terribly interesting in there, but the person who put together the world's largest kick line, which does also occur in the midst of all this.
Right.
There's also that part where they interview a bunch of like, you know, the kinds of people who would go volunteer to be part of a big kick line for weeks and weeks.
Well, that's an interesting part.
I don't remember.
Yeah.
I didn't write down any of their part.
Maybe I could find it really quick.
Do you remember any of the, that is, that is some just like real good old regular Canadian.
Yeah.
Mundane folks.
But some people are like high, like some people are like hyped and like a little odd.
It's the dream of like civic engagement, but I'm like, wait, they all volunteered for that?
And they, Alan Thicke just said this cost half a billion dollars.
It's really important.
There's money around.
Get paid, folks.
We got, we discussed this with Super Bowl halftime shows that I think still a lot of roles in Super Bowl halftime shows are bad.
Halftime shows are volunteer positions.
The people that run, like the fans that run onto the field, I think, specifically.
In a way I get that, but I think, and this might not be sure anymore.
Maybe now just like logistically, it's like we are paying dancers.
That is like a Canadian job.
But for sure in that crazy Indiana Jones one, it was still like an all volunteer group came out to Joe Robbie Stadium to what?
Why?
It's Disney plus Super Bowl.
What is the need to volunteer for this?
In this case, I'm like, you're right.
They should be getting paid because there is a giant corporation, which I think is literally called Stade Co.
I'm saying that because it's short for stadium, but it looks more like Stad Co.
That's easier to say.
Yeah.
The Stad Co.
Corporation, unfortunately, has gone over on building the right field Hard Rock Cafe.
We had to we had to purchase some expensive locks of Geddy Lee's hair.
And thus that and that money was going to go towards playing the kickliners.
But out of the question now, a thing that bumped for me.
So they had the little the musical number with football players, a little musical number with people in baseball uniforms.
And then it just cuts to a medley of Broadway songs.
And I started to get really hyped because they go into 42nd Street, but it's just 42nd Street.
It's not Sky.
It's not Sky Dome lyrics.
Yeah, they didn't change the lyrics.
They didn't change the lyrics, but I have.
So if you would humor me.
Wow.
The most micro specific parody.
Are you kidding me?
Wow.
It's just a couple.
Get hyped, y'all.
Are you singing it?
I'll sing it.
Please. Yeah.
Go ahead.
Sky Dome retract on the Avenue.
I'm taking you to one Blue Jays way because that's the actual address to the Sky Dome.
That part, too.
Yeah, because that's the address of the address.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
You were inspired to write a little song because it was you were hyped because it's what you like.
Yes.
That's amazing.
Is that what's the name of the song?
That's 40 seconds.
It's called 42nd Street.
That's the title.
I've seen it.
I apologize.
I don't know the name.
Is 42nd Street on your 10 Desert Island Discs?
I think so.
Yes.
All right.
That's pretty good.
Because the original cast recording got Jerry Orbach doing a couple of numbers.
Sure.
That's good.
And he's great.
And the only modern song is which Postal Service?
The what?
The only modern song on this Top Ten?
I know.
It gets up to what?
2013.
That is.
There's one new Pornographer is the one Postal Service and the rest are all.
Yeah.
It's 42nd Street.
Postal Service New Pornographers, Ding Dong Daddy from Doomis from the Nathan Veehler,
Nathan Reuven finale.
Oh, yeah.
Ding Dong Daddy from Doomis.
Let me try, you know, if that wasn't enough razzle dazzle for you from Jason, I just landed
randomly in the clip of the auditioners.
I meant to curate a clip of this.
I haven't vetted this, so I don't know what we're going to land on, but I think we can't
go wrong.
Let's see the kind of people that would volunteer for a kickline for weeks.
I feel this is going to be a good one.
Here we go.
You all set?
Thank you.
We have some good thorns here in Sky Dome.
Being a Sky Dome dancer is wonderful.
Oh, it's wonderful.
All right.
What am I going to say?
It's wonderful.
I'm just playing a little bit of the town of Covert to Sky Dome.
Hi, Covert.
All right.
Mr. Rowland taught me how to move in this Sky Dome course, however, I still didn't lose
my accent.
All right.
Great.
This is wonderful.
We got a strange melting pot here.
Those two who talked exactly in that pleasant Canadian clip tone, they would have been great
bumper stumpers.
That's what they're all like.
Oh, yeah.
They're the most mild-mannered.
Right, right.
I'm stay-at-home mom.
Well, my favorite wasn't in that clip, of course, the woman who goes, there's only one
thing I'd like to do more than Sky Dome.
Oh, that's what I-
All right.
Wait, I'll find it.
I'll find it.
I love Sky Dome, and let's go course.
Let's break the world record's longest kickline.
I can only think of one other thing I'd rather be doing than Sky Dome.
Wow.
Fucking.
She's talking about fucking.
Wow.
That's the most scandalous thing in the whole thing.
We'll have some fucking here.
We'll look the other way.
Did they get fined?
Did Canadian government fine them for that?
That was the body of thing ever on the CDC.
Right.
They had to have meetings.
You know, it was a little risque.
It was a bit risque, but we'll let it slide this time.
But that's a warning.
We're giving you a flag.
You can't be on TV again in six weeks' time.
Now throw to the La Bat Bleu commercial, which is the dirtiest, the second dirtiest thing
we've ever seen.
Okay, you say that, and I noted that there was a La Bats commercial, and when I went
to Toronto, I had some La Bats.
I love drinking some La Bats.
Sure.
They had a little like base beer they got, but what happened in the ad?
I don't remember the ad.
Well, there's one where they're talking about like, you know, meeting people and going out,
and then there's another one.
There's a Molson's ad where like it's like three guys at a table, of course, are all
dressed in denim, and then two sexy ladies walk by, and the one guy's like, him?
And they're like, no, him?
No, and he points at himself, and they go, yes, and then it cuts, and he has joined their
table of two, and he's giving a thumbs up, you know, holding a Molson's.
Is this yet another Jason's interest in thirding coming into play?
Look, how if we got to, if it relates to thirding.
Ah, a rare male unicorn, interesting.
Because they're different in Canada.
The challengers, there's an old challengers thing there.
Yeah, it's reverse challenges.
Oh, is it this one?
I'm trying to find it because I was-
Oh, this is the Molson's one.
This is the one you were talking about just now?
Yeah.
Okay.
They're like all dressed like Blossom or something.
They have like big kind of hair and little hats.
You get good ads in whatever version of this.
If you want to follow along with us, the YouTube user is David Dixon.
I don't know, there's probably multiple versions, but that's one I saw.
Good ads throughout.
You get an ad for Ghostbusters 2.
You get an ad for an equally well-liked film today, Lou Diamond Phillips and Kiefer Sutherland
and Renegades.
Renegades.
Oh, yeah.
Multiple Renegades ads.
Cool aid ad here that says, having kids means having cool aid.
Oh, yeah.
You can control the sugar because it's on sweet and cool aid mix.
Yes, it's on sweet and cool aid mix.
Yeah, yeah.
So you control how much-
Is that still how cool aid works?
I haven't- Jason, when was the last time you had cool aid?
I haven't had cool aid in a while.
I might have had it-
March.
Every now and then you see it at like Southern Food or something or restaurants.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
But you haven't had a canister or a little packet in a while.
I have.
I don't remember the last time I had it.
I think I sent it to you at some point, but we tried the Sunny D Hard Vodka Seltzer.
Right.
Which does taste like Sunny D.
It's kind of weird.
I'm surprised they're even doing that to confuse the brand, which is a child drink.
Cool aid hasn't made a hard cool aid.
No, yeah.
So it seems odd for them to do that, but yeah.
So I won't be supporting this is what I'm saying.
Everybody's doing what they can in this economy.
I won't be supporting that kind of drink side.
Turning to the drink side.
Bidenomics, right?
I loved cool aid as a kid, I will say.
I was like, oh my God, are we getting like three packets of cool aid?
It's so exciting.
You watch that ad, having a kid means having cool aid.
And I was like, it does?
We're back, yeah.
When?
Yeah.
At what age is that allowed?
How soon can I put that in this bottle?
I think we were more of a country time lemonade household.
They controlled the sugar.
I was going to say that-
In fact, they controlled the sugar on that.
That was a sweet ass lemonade.
That was sugary lemonade.
Which we couldn't get it, I think, because it was too sugary.
We very rarely had country time because my mom felt it was too sugary.
Did you have a soda fridge?
Well, my grandma had a soda fridge.
We did not.
She had one in the basement where you'd go down and there were like six different varieties.
Sounds like bribery to me.
Yeah, well she had a Super Nintendo and a soda fridge.
Well, my grandma had the Disney Channel and we didn't.
That's pretty good.
And an endless amount of Fruit by the Foot.
So you got to do what you can to get the visits.
Did she have a Fruit by the Foot cabinet?
Not a dedicated Fruit by the Foot cabinet.
Jason, did you have one of those?
My grandma was so lame she didn't even have a full Fruit by the Foot cabinet.
I think it was mostly stale hers or Ut's chips.
Okay.
Have you thought about getting at least a mini soda fridge?
We have a shelf with a lot of beverages in it right now.
Okay.
So it sounds like maybe you're headed that way.
Coke Zero.
Maybe you're headed that way.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, it depends.
He has to increase this campaign of drinking more soda.
Right.
Is that going well?
You know, it helps me keep my constantly flagging energy up.
Okay.
We're trying to stay on top of more healthy choices.
Sure.
Well, we're all trying to do that.
Yes.
Well, so Kool-Aid and Sunny D.
I'll pass out your assignments.
Jason gets Kool-Aid, you get Sunny D.
We did have Sunny D in the house a few weeks ago.
Regular Sunny D.
Yeah.
It was good.
We're not doing orange juice.
Living it up, boy.
Now that was a weekend.
I would love to see a picture of your drink shelf.
Oh, I'll take a picture.
I think the listeners would as well.
I think they would too.
Leave them out.
You don't need to clean it up, you know?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you also get an ad where an Oreo retracts like the Sky Dome.
Oh, okay.
Don't forget that one.
Yes.
It conveys the process in a pretty realistic fashion with an Oreo.
That ad would not play in LA or New York.
No.
So opening sequence happens.
Then we get some Alan Thicke stand-up.
Thank God.
We aren't done with the Thicke material.
This is part of the big push.
We're going to put Canadian baseball on the map.
We're going to prove once and for all that our Cubans are better than their Cubans.
Yes.
He gets laughs in this.
He does pretty good.
And I think stadium stand-up.
Look, this wasn't a thing at the time.
This was not the Sebastian Maniscalco era.
So Alan's doing what he can.
I think he's just working pretty good.
He's working pretty good.
Are those laughs real?
Because Dave Thomas later gets laughs, but I think those were piped in.
They feel kind of fake, don't they?
Yeah.
Especially because that Dave Thomas bit is insufferable.
He also does some of his bits like twice.
Yes.
He repeats one.
Because the bit is that he's on the Jumbotron and he says like,
Oh, hello, all you little people down there.
I could eat you up if I wanted to.
Om, om, om, om.
And it gets a laugh.
But I think it's a fake laugh.
I think they have like, because was this aired live?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Well, because it wouldn't have played out the way it did.
Oh, right.
Of course.
Jesus.
Yeah.
I think they have a button.
I think somebody's hitting a button.
Yeah.
We didn't talk about the other host who appears on the helicopter at the beginning.
Brian Williams.
Oh, yeah.
Another Brian Williams.
Yeah.
For the helicopter.
But for real.
Yes.
This one was on a helicopter.
That's why I was going to say this is a properly remembered helicopter.
But is that another Brian Williams or is that?
No, that's not that Brian Williams.
No, no, no.
It's not fake helicopter Brian Williams.
This is Canada's Brian Williams.
Or shot at in a helicopter.
Brian Williams probably was in a helicopter.
He just wasn't.
He was allowed to keep the name in the news medium because it's two different markets.
Wait, but I think the IMDB entry for this lists Brian Williams, the news broadcaster.
Well, IMDB has some problems such as listing Michael Eisner as the golfer and soren despite
me having proven this incorrect.
So you can't remember, folks.
You can't trust IMDB.
And if you look at my IMDB and see a bunch of old Funny or Die videos that I would rather
forget the existence of, remember those might be false credits.
Yeah.
Remember that.
Some of them are.
I've tried maybe 20 times, no exaggeration, to get rid of something called the Bachmann's
You've Got Mail, spelled M-A-L-E.
And I had nothing to do with the sketch.
I don't know what it is.
It's about, you know, ancient GOP candidate Michelle Bachmann.
Oh, right.
I do not.
And no one is looking at my IMDB and carrying them now.
I guess, OK, look, if I'm going to bring it up on the show, audience, we just go and
click on the Bachmann's You've Got Mail and get the star meter up on that so that, you
know, maybe somebody will click on me to direct the next Thor or something.
Can I guess who plays Michelle Bachmann?
Is there a Michelle Bachmann in it?
I think so.
Is it Kathy Griffin?
Good guess.
I think this might have been an Aaron Gibson recurring character at The Tough Fellow
podcaster and nice person, Aaron Gibson.
But I could be wrong.
Maybe there were many different Michelle Bachmann's at the time, like because the era
spanned four years, maybe different people played her.
Yeah, possibly.
Look, you know, it was tough in front of your dad.
We never landed on a Romney.
We never got our Romney.
Rob Delaney did it just once and then he never came back.
He got too busy.
It's why it was a tough election and it's why when 2016 rolled around, we've got Trump
and Trump is funny and we could all finally have fun with a political campaign again.
Yeah, finally.
Here's something interesting about what Alan Thicke talks about is that he says, you know,
hey, maybe we'll win a couple of World Series here.
And the way that we tend to, you know, if we're talking about a place, it tends to be
cursed.
We were just talking about the Bass Pro Shops pyramid, which used to be where the Grizzlies
played.
And I think they had a pretty not good run in that play.
So I'm hearing Alan Thicke say, we're going to win some World Series.
And I'm like, let's see how that worked out because I bet they put too much money into
the McDonald's and then failed.
Two years later, they won two World Series in a row.
The Skydome worked out spectacularly.
This was what they needed.
Yeah, Thicke called it like Babe Ruth.
If Thicke hadn't said it, it might not have happened.
But yeah, this is a case where a big dumb themed event did not damn the stadium for
all eternity.
They won a couple of World Series right after.
Oh, right.
They beat the Phillies in 93.
Oh, I'm sorry to remind you.
We were so excited for that series.
Apologies.
They came back in 2008, the Phillies.
Only took them 15 years.
So then the other acts start pouring because we've got a full evening's worth of entertainment
planned.
The first act up is precision police motorcycle riding.
Oh, I wrote that down.
They put spotlights onto police motorcycles and they kind of like weave in and out of
each other.
OK, it's the Ontario Police Golden Helmets Precision Team.
I believe that's the same thing you're talking about.
Yeah, Golden Helmets Precision Team.
Golden Helmets.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Golden Helmets made it much heavier, much tougher to drive in, but it was worth
it.
Made it read to the back row.
But they don't stop there.
They pair the Golden Helmets up with Canada's presumably hottest band at the time.
Welcome to our Sky Dome opening celebration.
Capital recording artists and Juneau Award entertainers of the year.
Glass Tiger.
Sounds like a coming out of our shells tour song.
Big Pyro burst there.
Sometimes Canadian entertainment is like Christian entertainment.
That was the exact same thought.
Just like what is it that is not hooking up here?
There's definitely like, you know, not always, not in every case, but in this case, I would
say, just like with Christian entertainment, like maybe an inherent lack of sex appeal
is that that might be what it is.
Whatever.
He's fun.
But he's just, you know, he's kind of this like, he's kind of this doofy guy with doofy
hair.
Telephone rings and I'm coming for you.
I'm feeling the night in my veins.
It's just nonsense.
Van Halen is happening and it's like cool.
And at the time, yeah, it's almost yeah, it's almost like a like royalty free music library
was tasked with.
Yeah.
Come up with something that's like Van Halen.
Right.
And that's what they did with no personality.
We are listening in that case to the song searching.
Glass Tigers hit searching number two in Canada, number 31 in America.
And they won Junos to Junos.
That's a whole other.
I love the Junos.
Yeah.
I've never watched somehow in all of my old TV wanderings.
I've never watched a Junos broadcast.
You better bet when I do.
If I see anything interesting, I'll bring it to the podcast.
I don't know that I've ever watched a full one.
I've certainly seen my share of bare naked ladies win a Juno.
Oh, there you go.
You know, right.
Right.
I've seen them get into the hall of fame.
Now, look, that's good Canadian music.
That's a big, popular, legit Canadian band in the pride of Canada.
They crossed over, yeah.
Does it break from what I said about inherent sex appeal?
I would say no.
I would not, of all the, I know it's, I like a lot of bare naked ladies songs.
I would not put in the list of qualities about them as sexy.
I think that's probably correct.
They are a bunch of dorks and remain sexy.
Dorks.
And remain a bunch of dorks.
Which, hey.
Hey, welcome to the, yes, present company.
Yes, of course.
Appreciate the dork representation.
Yeah, and they probably know more about sports, chances are, than us.
Almost anyone would.
Glass Tigers performing and our motto of rollerbladers comes out, a lot of whom are in Christmas colors inexplicably.
And that's what we're dealing with.
It's like using all that.
We've got a three tiered stage and we've got pyro on the stage, but we've got to use that bottom area too.
So what else, all right, just like how about a thousand rollerbladers.
And all of these, this is really where the spirit of it is, is that like they fill that extra arena space with so many people.
How did they possibly coordinate all of these?
Where did they all go in the bowels of Sky Dome?
Right.
It's not like, yeah, like what is the average thing happening here, a sporting event?
Let's say it's some football teams, where they have 30 people on each side.
Again, I'm embarrassing myself here.
Not on the field.
How many people on a football side?
I know there's special teams.
But like, what is it, a couple hundred people that need to be around?
Obviously there's production people and all that, but like there's just so many changing out of what they're doing.
I agree.
Where are they all going?
Are they in the parking lot?
I don't know.
It's weird.
I think everyone in Toronto was, you know what?
I don't know if they were in the parking lot because complaint about Sky Dome, not very good parking.
I think Alan Thicke makes a joke about that very premise.
You know, he does a little bit of J.
He like, and this place looks expensive.
He like commented on what was on people's minds.
You know, comedians today, we don't go for it like Alan Thicke used to.
Who inspired Alan Thicke to get into show business?
I am fascinated by his delivery.
And like, is it Robert Goulet?
Like, where does that kind of over the top cheesiness?
Is that a depper gentleman kind of thing?
A big explosion of volume and then kind of a trail off back to where you started.
Right. But he's not doing that ironically.
That's sort of his just normal comedy delivery.
Yeah.
Normal showman delivery.
At some point, is it him that says-
It's normal showman delivery?
It's showman ships.
Is it Amu that says, it's a way of life and a national sport?
Of course he is talking about aerobics.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we get a big aerobics chunk where I'm starting to think,
are we going to get another Alan Thicke aerobics song in the spirit of sweaty and hot?
Right.
Which I talked about last time and we don't, but it's still nice to see him up there.
He clearly was intrigued with the notion of aerobics.
Wanted to be around aerobics people.
Ladies were wearing tight clothes.
There's a joke about that.
Now, I guess that makes aerobics sexy,
but also there's no less revealing clothes than what we're looking at here.
Yeah, of course, but it was the 80s, so that was, you know, that was the-
That's on television. We can't be scandalous.
Right, and it's Canada.
He's got the windbreaker suit on, pants and jacket,
which I had, me and my brother had outfits like that.
Like the matching track suit kind of a thing?
Yeah, like complimentary.
And you were both wearing the same outfit?
Yeah, the same.
Like one was blue and like aqua green and then one was blue and red.
Okay.
Well, it's not matching, but it's like the Royal Tenenbaum's kids.
Oh, yeah, can you find a photo of it?
Aren't those matching?
Those are matching.
Yeah, those are matching.
I don't have a photo close by.
Do you want us to go get matching sort of track suit type things?
Oh, boy, that'd be fun.
Yeah, we could do that.
Yeah, I think that would read, if we did that on stage,
we all wore matching track suits.
I think it would definitely read as fun and cool and not as Miami Beach retiree.
That's right.
Yeah.
What's the thing?
Like, you know, so if you want to turn your buns into tiny little croissants.
Love it.
He's real Troy McClure.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
I think it is probably right.
Is it right before or right after this?
There is like a commercial break where there's an oil of the lake commercial
where a woman is talking about like, I am fighting off AJ with the oil of the lake.
Like, it's really like crummy in the way she's like, they say men age gracefully
and women just age.
Oh, I saw this one.
It's just so brutal.
Well, she's fighting back against what she feels are the.
With oil of the lake, of course.
But then the next commercial is about losing weight.
And I'm like, what is that?
And it's like, with special K, you can.
It's like a healthy breakfast.
So are you telling me, a man is not concerned with his aging,
that if I just get oil of Olay and eat special K, maybe I can fight back against aging?
You should fight back against aging.
OK, because I have been trying to fight back.
The full sentence is men age gracefully, women just age.
Mike Carlson does not age.
Well, you're right.
Not at all.
Sure.
OK.
Well, I.
Olivia Rodrigo records keep me young.
My daughter loves Bad Idea Right by Olivia Rodrigo.
It's a favorite song.
I also love Bad Idea Right.
It is her favorite song.
And she starts like mashing and she stops right before the chorus comes in.
And then the full thing comes in and she starts like going like this and like going wild.
It's great.
It's really fun.
I didn't force it, by the way.
This is just a song she likes.
And does it end?
And do you say now this is this is a current song.
This is a song from this very decade that your daddy knows and likes.
I haven't said.
Well, I have probably once, but I don't say it after every time.
Now, daddy and some of his friends were never in the position to sing the ballad.
But I have not.
There's some cursing in there and some adult themes, but she's too young to understand those.
Yeah.
So I guess at a certain point I'll have to put the clean version on where she didn't say, it's fine.
What is the clean version of that song?
I have to know.
Well, there'd be no F word.
OK.
I assume.
But maybe she said like slipped and fell into his bed.
Probably still in the clean version.
But maybe it's like slipped and fell into his arms.
I slipped and fell into his arms.
Fell into a bed.
Yeah.
Or into a bed.
Alone.
Yeah.
It got eight to nine hours sleep.
Good idea, right?
One good idea in this event was the booking of Andr Philippe Gagnon.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Boy.
Who's a truly unique entertainer, the man of a thousand voices.
So after all this, after like stunts, they also, I mean, it comes right after a bunch of police officers all dive in from ropes.
Oh, and they look.
Or he's up in the air.
They all look like strippers.
They all have this like cheesy 80s mustache on.
And it just looks like they're ready to take the clothes off.
They don't do it, but they look like the hot cops on Arrested Development.
They're like, oh, and they're all big smiling.
I mean, I assume they're.
That would have been a show.
That would have been great.
But yeah, that's the first thing I thought of.
And this is all during the part of the show where the roof is still up.
Right.
That's important.
Also, real quick, I feel like there's a part where they go, and now welcome martial arts children.
I saw the martial arts children.
Before this, yeah.
Yeah, you're not imagining.
And I go, huh?
Again, I lived a thousand lifetimes watching this clip.
Yeah, geez.
I know.
I missed big swaths of it.
Andre Philippe Gagnon.
I forget.
I might be fucking up the last name.
But he takes you back to a time where it was fine for white people to do impressions of Louis Armstrong.
Sure does.
I found that a little.
Something else recently reminded me of that.
There is a lot of this going on.
Oh, I saw something crazy.
I don't even want to talk about it because it's too creepy.
When I was looking up acceptable wedding entertainers who I could book for my wedding.
And these are the people that the venue works with.
You can book any of these.
And one we clicked on.
And it was a white guy.
Click off.
Nope, gone, no.
That will not be how we celebrate our most special day.
Did slash does Rich a little do one in his show?
I can only imagine.
I bet he does.
I could be wrong.
This guy's premise done in French Canadian accent.
Do you know that there are a lot of ghosts?
There are many ghosts.
Let's see who will be the next ghost that I bring to Louis Armstrong.
But then he can't think of Elvis Presley.
But then he can't think of enough dead famous Canadian performers.
So the ghosts have to be alive for the rest of this bit, yes?
Roy Orbison was not dead yet.
He was very recently dead.
I'm trying to remember.
Did he add him to the dead part of the act or the non-dead?
He might have been in the dead half.
I think this is a moment where I add this playing in an air pod and went to the bathroom or got a glass of water.
88 Roy died so he was dead.
He does Traveling Wilbury's song Handle with Care.
So he does George Harrison first.
I could not place which Wilbury he's trying to be.
George Harrison sings most of that song or at least the first parts of the song, the verses and stuff.
But then he says he's setting up Roy, but then he does that first part.
I don't know if he wanted to make sure you remembered what this song was.
And then he goes into I'm so tired of being lonely.
That's the Roy part.
But I was like, OK, this is kind of a confusing one.
George is not dead at that point.
Yeah.
So then we have to start doing Living Canadians.
And boy, a boy, the moment where he starts singing spinning wheel.
Blood, sweat and tears spinning wheel.
And then you hear a second of the same voice and it's the real David Clayton Thomas.
Who is apparently the singer of Blood, Sweat and Tears?
I do not know the name of that guy.
My, oh my.
What comes up?
Obviously, I know it sounds like I'm singing that sarcastically, but that's on the Desert Island Discs for me.
Ten Discs?
Yeah, yeah.
That's top ten.
Are Discs singles or albums, just to clarify?
I think we gotta go singles to Parrot Town.
Oh, yeah.
When we do your episode.
Right.
Yeah.
Single songs.
Right up in it, bone it.
So how about that?
I mean, what is it?
Andre and David Clayton together.
And then you get into this zone where now the process is going to begin of opening up the dome.
And they take a little time to explain concisely how that is going to work.
It's run by computers.
The computers are not fully operational.
The button will activate a laser beam, which will in turn signal the computers.
And there's a man, three men, a man in each of the three sections.
And in effect, what they're doing tonight is working a joystick in each section.
And that's how this giant roof is going to retract.
Simple.
The computers are not functional.
So in essence, what we will do is point to a man who will nudge a joystick, which will signal the computers.
But the computers are not working.
So the people at the computers will instead wave a flag, which will cause somebody to flip a spotlight.
And a girl will start a series of dominoes, which will create a nice array of colors in the Canadian flag colors once flipped over.
And then seven horses will all drag different apparatuses behind them.
And those will generate heat.
And the heat will rise.
Which will melt a series of computers, which are not functioning on the floor, so that they will be heated up, start a fire, which will cause a rope to burn up, releasing it, and thus beginning the opening of the dome.
He really struggles through that.
And that's it.
That's how it's done.
Yeah, that's it.
At some point, do they say it takes like 30 to 40 minutes to open and close the dome?
I think that is what it takes.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, we can open the dome, or we can close the dome.
But it has to be decided with that much force.
The life of the littlest hobo broadcasts, commercials included.
It only takes one hobo's time.
But yeah, with that clunky explanation, what it does become is that then Canadian Premier David Peterson has a laser pen.
That's what it ends up becoming.
He fires up a laser pen, but then I ended up looking into the backstory of how this all came together.
And they were like, yeah, we made a prop with an upside down Dixie cup that we painted.
There was nothing interesting that actually required the dome.
Somebody pressed the dome start button.
Yeah, the laser beam part made it sound like it was sophisticated, or the technology was interesting.
Laser activated to keep thieves out of the...
I'm sure everyone in Toronto is concerned about what if thieves airdrop into the top of the sky dome?
Will we be able to stop them?
Or if they do make their way in, can we quickly crunch the dome, which will crush their spines, crush the thieves right in the middle?
It does make it seem like a bond base, or a bond villain base, excuse me.
No, it is so...
Laser beams.
Also calling it laser beams is funny.
Laser beams is such an old school way to call lasers.
Sure.
Yeah, we should bring that back.
Laser beams.
Yeah, laser beams.
Laser beam arena would be great.
Laser beam arena, yeah, please.
Oh my God, if the crypto.com became laser beam arena, the joy that would spread all around the globe.
Yeah, it would heal.
There'd be the confusion about, wait, so is it just a big laserium?
No, no, no, it's where the Lakers play.
Yeah.
So the Lakers play at laser beam.
Wow.
Not Laker?
No, laser beam.
Not just laser or not just beam?
No, it's the full phrase.
They, at some point, they talk to a person who designed this, and he says he was inspired by the Houston Astro Dome.
Okay.
Is that dome not retractable?
It's not retractable because this is the first retractable.
Okay, so that's just a big dome.
Yes, inspired by it, but we, through this marvel of engineering, we will be able to have it either way.
Because again, as the song is said over and over, we can open it up if there is no rain, but we can keep it closed if there is rain.
And at this point, with the laser activation, this is where the opening of the dome begins.
And the opening of the dome quickly reveals what anyone with the ability to look outside of the dome knew, which is it was raining very heavily.
It was raining a lot.
It was apparently, this whole thing was like, it'll keep us dry, but even when closed, the rain was apparently leaking through.
Yes.
So this now sets off discussion among the people who have put this event together over the course of seven years, who had the dream of Sky Dome.
This is Sky Dome's grand debut, and it is raining.
What do we do?
Yeah.
And where it begins is, here, I'll start revealing this, which is that I looked on the website of a man named Toby Simkin.
Toby Simkin was the stage manager of this event.
And Toby, I want to say bang up job, and I apologize that this event aged you presumably six years in a matter of two hours.
So Toby reveals some behind the scenes stuff about it.
They went into this event, as any smart production would, with backup plans.
There was a dry version and there was a wet version.
And the wet version was, we will open it up a little tiny bit just to show that it can open.
And that'll be in the middle, which is mostly on the field, and we will not cause all the people in the stands to get super wet.
And this will prove what the other, what the people from Stadco were worried about, which is like, what if we do this live broadcast and everyone in Canada is watching and then we don't open it up?
And then people will say, it failed.
It didn't open.
It couldn't open.
We have to show that it can open.
This is bare minimum.
Even if it's pouring, we got to open this dome up a little bit just to show that it can.
So that is what this point of the broadcast is.
They start opening it a little bit and jazz legend Oscar Peterson performs and it rains mostly on him.
Yeah, this man towards the end of his storied career gets to play piano in the pouring rain.
But you know what?
But it's all right.
And we're getting, you know, you're at the dome opening ceremony.
You want to see the dome open.
That's OK.
And he does a nice performance.
And then we go back to tux clad Brian Williams in the booth.
And he gives us an update on the roof plan behind me.
They are announcing that the roof will be closed.
And I'm sure you'll hear the booze.
Booze.
Boo.
Don't.
We do have a look at the CN tower, though, they guess on how long it would take to open the roof was anywhere between 37 and say, 50 minutes.
But as of right now, the roof was open a little way.
It is going to close back because of the rain and lightning storms in the area.
Stay with us.
Dave Thomas will join me here.
Just doing it live is wild, too, in hindsight.
What's that?
Doing it live is like airing it live.
Yeah, really?
Why would they do it?
The hubris.
Because we gotta get all eyes on this,
so we gotta get people knowing you can come here tomorrow
if you wanted to.
I think there was a Blue Jays game,
if not the next day, then the day after that.
So they are, because they need this thing to get,
they need this thing to get off the ground running.
As I said, with the Hard Rock and the hotel
and all that shit, they have spent so much money,
so they need the gaudiest ad campaign ever,
and they need to show that it can open.
But then he comes on and he says, don't worry,
we're gonna close it because of the lightning,
and don't boo, obviously everybody's gonna boo,
but we have to close the dome.
The dome will be closed.
Then it goes to a commercial break,
we presumably learn more about renegades,
and then it comes back to Alan Thicke's center stage,
and it is pouring.
It is like the rain has gotten two times worse
just in that commercial break.
We're illustrating the kind of crazy weather,
which is why we have to have the retractable ceiling at all.
So, you know, well, we gotta probably hold the show
and just kind of air some pre-taped segments
until we can fully close it up again.
No, we are going full blast, and the procession,
everybody go, get out there, and this is the part
where everyone who built Sky Dome
all have to walk around the field.
And this is like the Olympics opening ceremony
where the groups all arrive from the nations.
Here's China, and here's Sweden,
except it's just groups of people from boring companies
who put the Sky Dome together,
and my favorite part is when they introduce,
here's this group, Trilon Financial Corporation,
and as that is happening, they are showing a guy
who took his shirt off and is revealing
a full back tattoo of Sky Dome.
Maybe it's painted on temporarily, I don't know,
but again, it's pouring rain,
and this guy takes his shirt off to reveal this.
We're getting full close up on Coast to Coast TV
of this guy's Sky Dome back, a guy presumably from Trilon.
I thought he was from Team SIRS.
Could have been, I mean, there and there.
But I feel like there should have been some commentary on that.
Like, I'm wondering, maybe there wasn't,
like, Brian Williams was not by a live mic,
because I'm like, wouldn't you just be talking
about this man with the back tattoo?
Oh, yeah, no, it's not, no, they just let it play out.
Yeah, yeah, they just let the majesty of the sequence play out.
You don't refer to the guy's bare back.
It's a Sky Dome, and it has a perfect Sky Dome drawing.
A lot is happening now,
because there's not just, OK, we've got to introduce everybody.
Everybody who made this, their thank you
is that they get to march around in the pouring rain.
Now we've got to let Domer out.
Domer's here, Domer.
Who's Domer?
Domer is the Sky Dome mascot.
It's Domer.
Domer, in this case, is an inflatable turtle
who is let loose to fly up into the refters,
but he struggles to fly because it's raining so heavily on him.
It's just kind of like chipping around like a boat in a storm.
Domer is getting his shit rocked.
You can see the rain hitting Domer.
He is wobbling.
Domer's going to throw up.
Pray for Domer.
Confusingly, Domer is the mascot of the Dome, not the Blue Jays.
That doesn't make sense.
They would have a Blue J, right?
So when Domer comes out at a game, he does not speak for the team.
He speaks for the Dome.
His opinions are his own.
The views of Domer do not reflect the views of Toronto Blue Jays
baseball season.
You heard I speak for the trees.
I speak for the Dome.
Domer, around this time, did some personal appearances
to promote the Dome, including hanging out with Michelangelo.
Yeah, baby.
Wow, the two great turtles hanging out together.
I love that suit, too, that Michelangelo suit.
I would have loved to have been at this.
The colors look great.
And then Dave Thomas makes a joke about him being a Ninja Turtle.
Oh, teenage, what's it said?
He does these.
One of his things was his Bob Hope impression.
And I've seen better video of his Bob Hope impression.
Boy, he just forgot.
Maybe he just felt too much pressure.
He's performing on a jumbo trill.
Look, it would freak me out, too.
I'd have trouble placing that impression.
But what would your old pal Bob Hope have to say?
Well, I'd say, hey, welcome to Sky Dome.
We didn't really try too hard on that at all, did we?
We didn't prep so much for that.
But it's great to see Domer.
I love Domer.
Way we were.
Katz has performed.
And this woman really gives it her all.
And then not until the end of the performance
do we go wide and see that the whole time,
this kind of dopey tall guy with an umbrella
has been standing over her.
And this is where it becomes clear,
this Dome is not fully retracting.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, actually, I have the note
somebody says they will now begin to close it.
But as it goes and goes, it never closes.
And the rain just gets more and more brutal.
And I was thinking about a thing that we said on the tour.
This is probably said in the Disney MGM tour, too.
Very common kind of Hollywood tourist
trivia, which is sometimes in the singing in the rain
sequence, in order to make the rain appear more clearly
on camera, they'd have to put milk in it.
And I was thinking about that trivia
and how like, ain't no rain, ain't no milk in this rain.
I was thinking about 20 minutes ago, like, man, this rain
is so hard, they don't have to put any milk in it.
You thought of the milk in the rain, too?
Well, because you can see the rain in grainy video footage.
And it's like, it was so much rain.
It is so glaringly clear.
Coming up on camera so clearly.
Makes you question the idea.
What do you mean there would ever be a world
where you couldn't see rain?
This is the clearest rain I've ever witnessed.
It's pouring.
It's so bad.
And you start to see that it is pooling on the stage
and in the bottom, like down below the stage.
And you really hope that they don't send out thousands
more people to start performing on the very wet stage
with the slick surface put down in order
to protect the baseball dirt.
Uh-oh, look out.
1,300 people are coming out.
And this is the part where it is the dancers
who represent indigenous and international communities
in Canada.
Oh, the Folk Arts Council represented it from Jamaica,
Serbia, Croatia.
Everyone's doing dances from their home countries
around the world.
And it's a small world lineup.
All comes out to celebrate and to do their local customs
and dances, which all involve parts
where they have to dip to the ground for a little bit.
Yes.
Yeah, every dance involves dipping to the ground.
There's a bunch of people from the Philippines
all doing some kind of like hopscotch with logs
that they're like jumping in and out.
Seemed hard to do, yes.
Extremely.
And they have to get really low.
And now the limbo council from Croatia.
Well, like it's so perfectly cursed for what should not
be happening at this moment.
Now we start getting into it.
Let me go back to the behind the scenes of the guy who
worked on it, Toby Simpkin.
So he said how basically at this point in the broadcast,
behind the scenes, there is discussion.
It is like, OK, do you realize that this
is where all of the indigenous outfits are going to come out?
And many of these outfits are ancient.
They are very old or like artisan, handcrafted,
like maybe borrowed from, maybe taken out of museums
and being worn for the first time in decades.
That is what is coming up in this broadcast.
This could ruin important artifacts.
Not to mention, did I say that this was a suggested blue tie
event?
So where people in the stands are in nice dresses in Texas.
I didn't know that.
So 50,000 people, lots and lots of them
are dressed to the nines.
But now we introduce the character skydome president
Chuck Magwood.
And he has been working on this for years.
Everything is on the line for Chuck Magwood.
He's like, I'm sorry, come hell or high water,
this is what needs to happen.
We have a national audience.
We've got to open this dome.
Are we going to not open the dome?
And he basically kind of crazed movie president style,
overrode everyone else to say, do it.
Open it.
Keep opening it.
And I think there might have been some situation where
the people actually pushing the buttons
were ordered barricaded so that nobody could
come in and stop the dome.
It was very nuclear bomb.
Three people in different rooms all across skydome
had to open up the roof separately
and all do it at the same time.
And they all were told by David and Chuck Magwood,
lock the door so that the process can't stop.
Oh, wow.
Lock the gates.
Lock the skydome gates.
We're doing it.
Fuck it.
I didn't come all this way for a dome to not get opened.
I'm Chuck fucking Magwood, OK?
We're opening the fucking dome.
You know he said that.
That's not a joke.
No, I am.
I'm fucking Chuck Magwood.
Tensions were very high.
There's no way they weren't.
The segment where the news reporter
talks to someone who worked on designing the dome,
and they get in a replica and show how it will retract.
Yeah, they all stand in a tiny dome.
He seems very shaken that designer or engineer.
He seems very tired.
And he alludes to it, too.
The guy's also like, how has no one died making this thing?
And he's like, oh, yes.
There's a weird moment there, too.
A big discussion of, yeah, it seems improbable.
Well, that interview in which the notion of death
is discussed is an interview with fucking Chuck Magwood.
That is who is being talked to.
He is interviewed.
They cut to a prerecorded interview with this guy
while his orders, given personally from him
on behalf of STADCODA, open the fucking dome.
It's happening.
Everybody's getting rained on.
Indigenous outfits are getting destroyed forever.
History is being erased live on television.
Canada, not terribly good about that sort of thing.
They're not?
No.
Kind of par for the course that they would like.
Let nature destroy it.
I didn't know this about Canada.
But anyway, as if that's not strange enough,
then they ask him about a plain question about,
how do you think it's going to go?
And here's the response.
Is it like you imagined it would be?
Is it?
You know, I guess in some ways I've
been, like many of the rest of us, a bit afraid and not
prepared to really imagine it.
So we have not consummated that imagery.
And why is that?
Maybe it's a bit like sex.
You're afraid it isn't going to quite work out
the way you hope.
One of the weirdest Android-like responses.
What?
Like, well, I don't know.
I haven't imagined it.
I haven't consummated that imagery yet.
If you consummate the.
You're walking along the road in the desert.
You see a turtle on its back.
Do you flip it over?
I don't know.
I'm worried it will be like sex.
And it will never work out for me.
And then his image flies away into a little fray.
Do, do, do.
What?
It's so weird.
Yeah.
To keep his metaphor alive, it is actually what happened.
Plans were laid in play.
A plan to protect the dome was put in place,
but there was a breach in the dome,
thus allowing liquid to get through,
thus creating kind of an accident in the scenario.
Sure, yeah.
That is, ironically, where we ended up here.
That man has a quiet intensity in that clip as well.
Plans.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, much like Oppenheimer, I suppose.
Can we get a Noah's Oppenheimer movie
about the man who invented Sky Dome?
Yes, yeah, about that moment.
I'd love an Oppenheimer style.
I'd love to do it Sorkin style.
That's all that took the 90 minutes real time leading up
to the moment of pressing the button.
But anyway, that decision is made.
And what that leads to, per this guy's website,
is 50,000 audience members in black tie
getting soaked while the show did its best
to perform in a leaky boat.
Stage dancers sliding down ramps like waterfalls
to the concrete floor.
Roller skaters with metal rollers
sparking on the steel plates, which
are covering high voltage electrical traps
in the stadium floor that are now covered with water.
TV cameras are being covered in plastic sheets.
Millions of dollars of audio lighting
and other technical equipment scattered
throughout the stadium being frantically shut down,
either being successfully covered or exploding.
There were electrical explosions
during this live broadcast.
Like a Bonvillain base now.
It's like everything is treacherous.
Magwood has gone rogue.
Yeah.
It's every man for himself now.
And no more if you don't mind killing a few people on your way
out, too.
They shut down everything electrical
that wasn't absolutely required for basic safety.
Even our communication system failed.
And they migrated to walkie talkies only.
And they started conveying announcements for everybody
just through the, they just had to go through the announcer,
who earlier was going, ladies and gentlemen,
David Clayton Thomas.
And now he's saying, ladies and gentlemen,
move away from the electrical gear.
You will be fried to a crisp.
Open up that, too.
And yes, OK, so now that we've laid all of that,
what does this line up with in the broadcast?
This lines up with an even longer musical number
with Alan Thicke and Andrew Martin and more people
that is entirely about open up, open up the dome, open up.
It'll haunt me because they repeat it so, so many times.
But time to let the celebration begin.
Open up the dome and let the people come in.
And so it's a song that they have locked and loaded
about opening up the dome.
If I could go back to the beginning
and say how this whole thing came
from a bunch of rain pouring on a Canadian football game.
And then a bunch of angry people from Toronto went to City Hall
and said, we want a dome.
We want a dome.
Seven years later, they are now in the dome.
The dome was built per their request.
And there's a song about opening up the dome.
And they are all yelling in unison, shut the dome.
Shut the dome.
Be careful what you wish for.
Be careful what you chant for, perhaps.
That's the lesson to be learned from the Sky Dome opening
ceremony.
Careful what you chant for.
Yeah, indeed.
There's lyrics in this song that are like,
we don't care if it rains or pours.
As they cut to angles where raindrops, thick raindrops,
are all over the lens, it's rendering it like unviewable.
But now, it's a bunch of open top cars
with all the most important people in Canada
being paraded in, many of whom are elderly, legends who've
given their rights, their life to civics and transportation
and getting great sports programs.
Now, their reward is getting just poured on.
And there's this endless, this also
feels like it goes for 12 minutes,
that there's all these really inane rhymes saying
who everybody is.
She's a star on skates.
Elizabeth Hanley, you are great.
Open up the dome.
This goes for so, so long.
At some point, they cut back to one of the karate kids.
What were they called?
Karate children?
Karate children.
Yeah, karate children.
They cut to the saddest, coldest, wettest karate child,
looking like, Mom, can I come back in, please?
No, for the good of your nation, you need to stay out here.
My favorite quote in that is, now that Metro man is cruising
in, wave at him.
It's Dennis Flynn.
Wave at him, not to him.
Yeah.
Wave at him.
So luckily, then, there's not much more
to do so that we can wind down the broadcast,
and everybody could get dry again, and we can wrap up this.
Nope, sorry.
Time for skydivers.
That is now where the pre-planned part
of this broadcast, where eight skydivers will drop
into the top of Sky Dome.
This part starts.
There's no way to contact the skydivers,
because they are in the sky.
All the comms are going out, so there's
no way to say, actually, hey, X-Nay on the skydiving part,
they have to do it.
There's no choice.
So they just start, and the people filming the broadcast
are like, oh, I guess skydivers are happening.
OK, here we go.
Does the rain stop, though?
Footage made it seem like the rain.
No, the rain's like, no, it's maybe a little bit better,
but it doesn't stop, and they have
to land in a couple inches worth of water.
Yeah, someone falls on their bottom, I feel like.
A couple of them.
Right on their bottom, yeah.
Flash right down.
They slip off their tootsies and fall on their bottom.
Right off their tootsies.
Some of them might have twisted or broken their tootsies.
Who knows what the state of these tootsies
by the end of this thing.
Guy in the PA is saying, please keep the area clear.
Open up that dome.
Fireworks start going on.
They still do fireworks.
I'm like, wow, you can do skydiving and fireworks
in pouring rain?
I mean, all of this, I guess I can't fault Chuck Magwood.
He's not so incorrect.
This was a spectacular.
He was right.
Magwood was right.
Predating Prince at the Super Bowl,
how much the rain added to that.
Yeah, it just really, or the other day,
Metallica performing with a perfect lightning
strike behind them.
Yeah, that's cool.
We're allowed to say that this was a cool thing that
happened that was cooler because of rain,
because nobody got killed.
People did.
There were, I think, a number of lawsuits
in the wake of this.
Oh, sure.
But that's no.
But that's to any event there's going to be.
There's going to be some quiet ones here and there.
$500 stadium added to the list.
Not to mention that by the time this thing is up and running,
Sky Dome starts $40 million in debt.
That is enough debt that it was estimated that in order
to get back on its feet, Sky Dome
would have to be functional and hosting events
600 days a year.
To me, that seems impossible.
I think so.
Yeah, but that's really the failing of the year
for being too weak to have 600 days in it.
The year could get its fucking act together.
Yeah, no, you double book.
Baseball game in the afternoon, baronet ladies at night.
That's right.
Yeah.
And opera at 3 in the morning.
Yeah, it's not like it's a major ordeal
to flip a baseball stadium to a stage or baseball or football.
Right.
No time.
Can't do it.
Just slippery wet grass.
The opera's going to have to happen on slippery wet grass.
They did.
So then a baseball game is being played two days after this.
And because they didn't shut the dome,
it was incredibly wet.
It was really muddy and bad.
And they had to, whatever process it takes to dry dirt,
they had to do to get ready for the Blue Jays' opera.
I don't know anything about drying dirt.
Jason, maybe?
Yeah, that's your territory.
A football manager might know about that.
Yeah, the answer is tarp.
And they could not do that due to the massive singing, dancing
spectacle.
So dirty games, lawsuits, costumes ruined.
David McWood resigns in disgrace.
I think he wasn't even in charge by the time
this opening special was airing.
Maybe James Dolan's fate at Sphere.
Well, just come on after a year, maybe.
A man ahead of its time.
Sometimes you burn out bright and then fade away.
Better to burn out than to fade away.
A Canadian.
There we go.
Thank god he wasn't trotted out in this.
I just have one last ad hit, because this one
felt like a personal attack.
Close together, there were ads for Anbisol and Perp Plus
pretty close.
And I was like, oh, no, I have both of those
in the house right now.
That's an attack?
What's the first thing?
Anbisol.
OK, Anbisol is an oral ointment that you can put on canker sores.
Oh, I need that, actually.
I swore I've recommended or given you Anbisol.
Yeah, I probably tried.
It probably doesn't work.
New drop of what canker sore medication Jason is using.
Let's fucking go.
No, I haven't used this for like 10 years or so.
And then just recently, I was putting Tari to wear together.
I was like, I wonder if they still make Perp Plus.
Well, these ads didn't say, hey, loser, do you use Perp Plus?
But it was the logo I always liked as a kid.
And I was like, it was a good attack.
It was a nice thing.
Are you a fuck up because you have canker sores in your mouth?
Yeah.
In fact, only losers get canker sores.
If you're a loser, buy this, I guess.
That's right.
Then drink the whole bottle.
Because what else do you have to live for?
Anyway, it's just called Pert America now.
It's had like three or four different owners.
They took out the plus?
They took out the plus.
I think let it in internationally.
Pert is no longer plus.
Pert is normal now.
Pert Plus has now took away plus.
Pert Plus is some sort of a streaming service.
That's my recommendation, Anbisol and Pert.
You have canker sores, get Pert.
No, don't get Pert.
That's wrong.
Yeah, don't put Pert.
Don't put Pert on.
Put Anbisol, it still works.
Anyway, this special is a blast.
If we didn't convince you to watch it already by doing this,
I'm glad that we did a full deep dive here.
I was so happy to get to go to Skydome myself in 2015.
It was Roger's center by then.
There was no way I wasn't calling it Skydome all night.
Skydome had the most narrow seats I've ever experienced.
It made me feel like a man twice my size.
It was like an optical illusion.
This is what I got?
My god.
What did you see?
Blue Jays, I saw Blue Jays game.
And it was a Blue Jays game where if they won,
it would be the longest winning streak
in the history of the franchise.
They lost.
When it was down to the wire, every pitch counted.
Everyone is on their feet.
The tension was so heavy in this room.
The most tension, more tension than there
had been years ago when everybody thought
they were going to get electrocuted to death.
And then just all of a sudden one pitch and that is it.
Now I'm just watching everyone in town
file out sadly and silently.
I don't think they played any music.
I don't think they said have a good night or drive safely.
It was so sad.
So I witnessed a very grim end of a game here.
But I still had a great time.
I was so happy to call it Sky Dome.
And this quote, this is on a Reddit thread
about this event, which I think this says it all.
The youth today with their hyper cool synth wave
aesthetic pop culture view of the 80s
don't know the true 80s.
This in all its cringe inducing agony was the true 80s.
Wow.
That says it all.
And I love both sides of what he's talking about.
I love the cool, I love the vapor wave reclaiming
ends of the 80s.
But I also love the skin meltingly embarrassing side
of the 80s too.
It was all there.
Everyone was there.
You called it in the Super Bowl episode the razzle
dazzle crap of the 80s.
Yeah.
And this is some of the razzliest,
dazzliest crap I've ever seen.
Listener, I hope you enjoy it if you check this thing out.
And you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us in our VIP Patreon
tier club three where you get one more bonus
episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
You can always send us to watch inane stuff like this.
We love a good special.
We love talking about all of it and the commercials in it.
If you know something as bonkers as the opening of Skydome 89.
Let us have it.
Yes, please.
We don't want to go one day on this earth
without knowing about it.
I have to think there's something from the millennium
that we haven't like a special like this.
Listeners, let us know.
Yeah.
You know?
And if there's an ad for canker sore medicine
that attacks Jason, let us know about that too.
Well, hey, but it helps you.
Well, nothing helps me with my canker sores.
You and me both, brother.
Amen.