FOREVER
DOG
Howdy y'all
This here episode has got some chit chat
about little outfits
Crystal palaces
and realistic moose eyes
Yeah, it's the Jamboree Weekend Show
cause we're back talking country
bear musical jamboree on today's podcast
The Ride
Jamboree Weekend Show
Welcome to Podcast
The Ride or as Disney would call it
Podcast The Podcast Ride
I'm swinging Scotty Gardner
joined by Big Car Alson
Yeehaw, hello
I'm doing that because I have a canker sore today
and it's hard to close my mouth
So if I'm trying like this today it's cause I have a bad canker sore
Yeehaw is just a good sound to make
to try to like swish your mouth around
and like that's just what came out
when you naturally lapped your tongue
That's right, yeehaw
I see, well I'm glad it happened in such a folksy way
Hey, and sit over there
there's an old familiar face, it's Jughead
Jason Bonnet Sheridan
Hi
Hi, yeah, I have a slightly less impactful
canker sore, so
Two of the hosts
Two of the hosts today have canker sores
What about it?
The gradual march of this show
into medical ailment complaints
continues
I often have one, it's just that today
it's so impactful and it hurts
and it's right on the top
It's right on your instrument
It's like if you went to a country music show
and there was a canker sore
on the fiddle
Yeah, I know, my mouth fiddle is
injured today
This is impacting our odds of pulling off a jamboree
Bear with me today
Bear with, oh I like that
That's great
I dusted off those names
I went and looked up what our names were
in Country Bear Jamboree Week
and if we pulled off what we vaguely talked about
then you have heard
the Country Bear Jamboree Week
theme music
and general overlay
from I think towards the end of 2022
and as well as
the art, courtesy of
Tony Grasso, one of the great pieces of art
of us we've been lucky enough to receive
because we're
kind of nodding back
we're back to Country Bear Jamboree
as we celebrate the new show
at Disney World
the Country Bear Musical Jamboree
Yes, we're here
So why not dust off the old
let's refurbish
and gold plate our old
materials, treating this
now refurbished attraction
That's one of my, that's maybe my favorite
of the alternate themes
I went back and re-listened
I hadn't heard it in a while, it's very good
Well that requires some musical dexterity
on your part, unless that was all plugins
Well
there's one thing I was playing on the keyboard
that's like a fiddle or something
or I forget what it was, a banjo or something
but I was playing it, but then you can go back
and you can fix it too with MIDI
I see
No, there's like guitar and stuff, it's not like it's all robot
or anything
But, unlike the show
This is more robotic than
Played live, no no, great job
I did like that a lot, I refreshed my memory
and I think maybe
just right before we dive into
Country Bear Musical Jamboree
going back
to this old
theme and overlay just made me think
are there
this is a sound off in the comments
kind of situation, are there
series that we've done before
that you want to return in some form
are there
attractions that you think merit
a little event beyond
just doing one big long
episode about it, because I remember
being very happy with
Jamboree Week
that's something I'd be curious about
you know, mini
events, which we're always on the lookout for
and events involving
mini as well, certainly
front of the line for those
and I even
because I had a thought way back when
and I wasn't sure about the title
but I'm going to pitch it now
to you guys, let's just workshop
it here now, because this seems like
it could work as like a little more meat on the bone
kind of little event
and that is this, Enchanted
Tiki Wiki
could be
yeah, could be, yeah, yeah
sure, sure
I'm trying to agree
I'm trying to agree with you
and as soon as I
it was like half way through, I was like
it's going to sound shitty
it's going to sound critical
it's not bad, it's okay
we'll think it over
off mic
I think it was Cankersaur's effect
I think the Cankersaur's somehow puffed
and created an attitude
people grumpy, they make me grumpy, I was just cursing
through the house this morning like
shucks
screw my seat
I did not yell screw my seat
this morning, I swear
but I was thinking it
your daughter just walking around copying screw my seat
no
her first words
oh no, it's not even normal
profanity shit
I'd rather she just say fuck
I think she said oh shit yesterday
when she dropped something and she goes, oh shit
I go, did she just say oh shit
it wasn't directly after I said it or anything
I was just wondering if she heard me drop something
once and exclaim
I've had some lord's name
in vain make its way
in there, which is a difficult
situation, I'm just like don't do it when I'm
not around with my
pretty religious parents
and family
I try to curtail that one
anyway
so this
this show, Country Bear
musical jamboree
the somewhat
confusingly titled
or actually lack of confusingly
just a weird title
I can't hide from that
I think the title is weird
it is weird
I did look up the dictionary definition
of jamboree and it seems to be
a raucous large gathering
it doesn't have to be musical
it doesn't have to be music
but I thought it did
I was like I always assumed jamboree
probably because I learned it
from a young age
from the Country Bear jamboree
oh if this is your association then you assume
a jamboree is a big hootin hollerin
musical celebration
this was a conversation that we had
the other night pre-episode
and we were talking about the feeling that the title
is redundant
and that putting musical
this must have been what was in your head Jason
isn't it redundant to put musical
or jamboree
and I guess now we've determined music
doesn't have to be part of a jamboree
though you'd have to think it would help
any jamboree is going to be better with music
I agree completely
I kind of agreed with you
when you first said it
and then I thought
there might be several generations
deep that have never encountered
the word jamboree
this might be kind of a
as with you Jason
if the word jamboree
was not in this attraction
would we be using jamboree
yeah
when have you encountered, when do you see jamboree
out in the world
the one time I encountered it was in the Boy Scouts
and it was like a big meet up
of different troops
yes that's a big one, Boy Scout jamboree
which is also why there's a jamboree
road in Newport Beach
because it's where the biggest jamboree
occur really
yes yeah apparently
but if you're not around there
if you're not passing by jamboree road all the time
then why is it in your head
there was a Naughty by Nature song called jamboree
but that was like 25 years ago
I don't think there's been a pop jamboree
since
there should be
it's a fun word
I really like the word
the victory is that the word is still in the title of this new show
that is true yeah
well that's going to be a common theme today
there's victories here
I think there's a lot of victories here
that's the theme today
but even that implies
that we are kind of like
looking for bright sides
or at least on the lookout for
dark sides
which has kind of been the hesitation
since this show was announced
there's a double edged sword here
the country bears are returning
they aren't getting kicked out
that's the main thing
they aren't getting fluttered
they aren't getting thrown to the trash heap
or getting changed into different
I don't know presidents or something
like they're not being changed to other robots
they're not being put in Tiana
and reskinned or something
they're there, they're still there
yeah
as much as I feel like there are some presidents
who could just be
like these bodies could work
some of them
some of these 1800's guys
or if certain presidents
return and the policy is
that we need a second one
instead of just bringing the old one
back up to the front
but that's not the
there aren't two Grover Clevelands
again another one who probably could be
a country bear body could work
but for now
they all get to be themselves
so the existence of this thing
I think is great
I think that they even
have to do kind of a
what would you call this
a C ticket D ticket type
refresher
that's not
going to be a headline
grabber
it's not something that like
moves the needle in a massive
way for non theme park fans
right?
but it's like a nice thing
it's the sort of thing we want them to do
all the time, plus ups and
downs
so it's cool that they did this
it's kind of like the tree house out here
which they did half for practical
reasons they moved the entrance of the tree house
over in adventure land
they moved it back so people could walk
but while it was happening
unfortunately I hate to say
Tony Baxter's street cloggers
I mean
Astro Orbit is still there but we got rid of the rocks
he loves to clog the streets
it's all interesting
I like when Tarzan's tree house
opened it was this odd little outpost
that gives you extra
an extra walk to do
it was interesting but it just
sort of becomes impractical after a while
but they took that opportunity to
now re-theme that tree house
it's a nice little walk, they added like animatronics
we should do a little episode on it
eventually
but that's the thing where you're like
they could have just ripped this out, there's no reason they couldn't
have just taken this out, there's no reason
they had to put money into it but yes
it's a de-ticket little walk through
it's a little refreshed
these little historical society
type
that you want
the little museum that shows you what life was like
a hundred years ago in the town
you want them to have the money
to put new wigs on the mannequins
who
show you how old
phones used to
operate
and by old stoves
we want these things to work
we want those little museums to have the hundred
dollars they need to replenish the
wigs that spiders have
laid eggs in
I'm picturing a very specific type of museum here
so the Disney version
of that
that's not like
building an entire new
big trackless ride vehicle
which we also want them to do
do everything
but yes, there's generally
a push and pull, there's a trade off
there's a reason stuff happens
too, so it's like
I understand that from
a practical way
I understand that there's a trade off
you put money in here
you scratch our back, we scratch yours
a little bit, that's what's happening between
Imagineering and the executive side
the bear area
make it so people can walk
in Adventureland and Disneyland
and we'll give you a little money to like
make a little narrative about
a family that's not the Swiss Family
Robinson, but they're inspired by them
that's what it is?
kind of
it's not them, but it says it's inspired by them
I'm not sure
so modern though?
or in the same era as
the Swiss Family?
it's kind of splitting the difference
I walked through it twice and now I can't remember
I think it's modern?
family that read the books
or saw the movie
I believe so
that's baffling
are you not baffled if you're there?
if you're there you're just charmed
if you're there you'll read the thing and you go huh
and then you walk up and you go oh that's where
sister looks at the sky in her little
like astronomy
machine or whatever
this could be called a telescope, but I called it an astronomy machine
you got there in your own way
I respect that
they're lucky with that one
I think
I think everybody would like the tree house
to be there in general
but I don't think a lot of people are like
you took out the Swiss Family?
who?
Robinson presumably?
do you think there were people
going like you took out Tarzan?
yeah I don't think so either
I don't think there's a lot
I think you had to be
if you were like
12 to 15
when Tarzan came out
and you like the
early CGI they used
to make him skate down the vines
and I do
that was one we didn't see
in theaters
but I remember renting it
I remember all the Phil Collins songs
I was like I like this
it's just not
were you upset when they removed him
from the tree house?
doesn't seem like you were
fine with it
I don't think anybody
I think they're very lucky they're dealing with
two properties that nobody could be too mad
about
here it's a little more delicate
I feel like
there was another type of
Disney company
we've been pretty Disney critical
recently, but it feels like there was an even
colder version
that might have ripped this out
I'm picturing like late 90s early 2000s
in the era where it left
in Anaheim
I feel like there's another version
of the company where it is just like we're going to move more
we're going to make better numbers
if this is something else
and I think it just
wrote it maybe they just didn't have the money
to rip it out in the colder time
and in that time
that's like one more generation
that has grown up with this thing
theme park nerdom is a little bit
more common and accepted
and I think people
they had enough here like we liked in general
the show we liked the characters
and there was enough that they had to kind of like pay
homage to and be respectful
of to where like this
I think this could have been so much grosser
imagine if like
back when they owned American Idol
or whatever I mean they own American Idol now
but you know like what if they hadn't
thought of the American Idol experience
in studios
and this became well we need a music show
let's have robots of Sanjaya
or whatever
let's make Henry a little more Simon Cowell
let's make him a little meaner
well yeah it's like
or they keep the characters but they put
bear judges in the front
and somebody and it's like
I like I wasn't feeling a dog
and then it's a literal dog
I feel like
it's like luck that that didn't happen
I feel like I've read
something like that before
that they wanted to do something like that even though
like it just feels right is what I'm saying
that they would have done that in a certain era
you're describing sort of like an under new management
tiki room situation
where like depending on
what the era was which I don't know if it's
what year does that come out
that's early 2000s
that's sort of what I'm picturing
I think we're really lucky they didn't touch country fairs
where they would have done something like that
where the taste was bad
as much as current Disney is
very bland then Disney
was more likely to be shitty
yeah and like even like the
the Ellen energy overlay
we were like ah this feels
like there's such a specific
90s feeling to some of like the humor of
that and then it goes into
like the year like the superstar limo
era of comedy
the Stitches great escape chili dog burps
I think that's the era
I think the fairs are really lucky
they skated out of the 2000s
this is too
my memory
is not like
cause I Disney
is getting like
weirder or shittier
in like not great ways
and I'm like entering
high school and going through puberty
so I'm like
it's less at the forefront of my mind
yeah no the regrettable time
we all had where we thought about Disney
a little less thank god it's rectified
now that we are adults
some of whom with children
but I did think about the parks a good amount
and I think that's a thing that
comes up like one of the criticisms
of this is like oh I'm a little
bummed cause when we were talking
about it the other night I'm like oh
they're taking away
the country bears making like kind
of dated references
kind of dated comedy
and they're taking out these weird
old country songs
they're like sanding off the weirdness
yeah right right yeah
well this is the debate I'm
sort of curious to have and as we dig in
and kind of focus on
what did we lose here
did we lose things that make it
what it is or were there things
that just had to go and that is
the only way that this could have
gone we should say we did not go
in case it wasn't clear oh yeah
this is a Zapruder film
we're watching videos
since it's a we made the call
that since it's not like you physically have to
experience it it would have been nice to be there
cause I think the speakers are upgraded and whatever
but you can kind of tell
the show without being there
so just to be clear I think you're
right that the big I definitely
realized that the big thing that we're
that we're missing and
that we should mention and properly honor
them for is the refurbishment
of the theater I think it's new seats
it's new carpet it sounds great
apparently the
that it was sort of muffled before
was largely because
the speakers were behind
a very thick old 70s
curtain and they like
lifted everything and rearranged
everything so that I think
there are still so just the way
you know Disney doesn't want visible
speakers really in a show like this you
still got to hide them but just they were able
to like pick a new curtain
figure it out to where like some
of them are like some of them are way up
here and then the ones that still have to go through a curtain
it's just a better situation
more sound is making it through
I got some of this information
I don't know if you guys watched any of this basically
like this so this show as we
as you're hearing this the show
is open to the public two days
ago I think
but they did a preview for
D23 members
and there are videos
of this and I thank all
of the people who took the videos and posted them
and made this episode possible without
going there being in D23
but as part of that
there was a little Q&A
before the show began
and I'm glad I watched this because
it kind of gave me a bigger appreciation
for what they did
and then also there's like backstory of the
show that I didn't know in general
that was covered here and just
general oddities and then stuff
like that for sure that like okay here's how
they redid the
and that there's gold
plating on the proscenium
there's gold plating outside on the
marquee the sign is gold
I think this all probably looks great
in person and adds to the
feeling of like this is a very refreshed
show
there's little things like
so what I watched was an interview with
it's an archivist talking to
I think Ken Ricci
who was the main producer of the show
and he
was clearly really excited about everything
they did and
just these little things that you'd never know that
Max Buff and Melvin
the heads on the wall
he said their eyeballs
were stickers before
they were just little stick on
pupils and just little things like that
that like alright now they've rendered that
that's actually a sculpted eye
that looks better
and this guy Ken is clearly
a fan that's what you get
from it because he's considering
every possibility
of what would you miss that we might
take out and he
here's the degree of fan that he is
is that he said you're gonna notice
a lack of clacking
and we even talked about
how do we retain the clacking
I think people like the clacking
and this is incredible to hear
Disney Imagineers say because
clacking comes into play in anything
like this that we talk about
going back to see the ones in
the Make Believe band in Northridge
the Chuck E. Cheese band you're like
maybe I want to hear the clacking
the clacking is part of it or I'm creeped out by the clacking
or my kid doesn't like the clacking
clacking is part of the old animatronic experience
I feel and apparently
especially with them with the heads
they were like maybe we can keep the clacking
maybe there's a charm to it
and they didn't because
and I didn't get this
from the videos either that apparently
the heads talk as soon as you
start coming in
I think they didn't do it
in the videos that have been posted at this
juncture but instead of
they're just there creepily and maybe
clacking a little bit
they're making comments
and telling you to like sit your beer butt
down or whatever
from the second you get in there
and I think I don't know there's something about
like the clacking was going to compete
with the music but they actually
like maybe we keep the clack we might want to keep
the clack I mean I love that that's a
conversation I love that they probably burned
hours on keeping
the thing that shouldn't be
that feels like a mistake
but some mistakes become part of it
because we all love animatronics
and we all have an affection for the clacking
like if you hear clacking
in this episode from both of my co's
canker sores
that's where we keep that in there
because it's part of the charm
it's part of it
we could edit it out but
I can't
hear it from here but if the listeners are hearing
Mike's microphone
if somehow it was really
ASMR
in my mind it is but I hope it's not
in your brain
that's how you're hearing it
anyway but they did put
electric motors in the eyes
and the mouths it's the old
casing and bodies but
electric instead of
what hydraulic is what it would have been before
also part of this
Q&A some history
that I didn't know I don't think I knew that
we definitely talked about that
thing that this was supposed to be part of the mineral
king resort that this is going to be a show
for this Walt Disney
Run ski resort I don't think
I didn't feel familiar to me that
the original plans was for it to be called
bear band restaurant
and that it was going to be outdoors
which sounds pretty hellish
at this point I was going to say that sounds like a bad idea
I think so
I've heard bear band restaurant but I didn't know it was outdoors
that's what they said yeah that initial
plan because wait I'm forgetting now
was this opening day Magic Kingdom
or was it a little later
I think it was opening day wasn't it I think so
I think so it came to
Disneyland later yes
when it was well received
so that's why they built the double theatre
which was sort of an undoing
there is a reference to
mineral king in the show
yeah it's a fun little nod
that's where one of the guys used to
play there's
one for the heads
but yeah bear band restaurant
outdoors was one plan and then
they enclosed it
and here's really from the Q&A
what I wanted to
address which is that
the show is based on
Mark Davis
caricatures who was
the most well known for
putting so much
character and
humor in his concept art
which was retained all the way through
the animatronic but if you're looking at it like an
inherently funny silly looking
animatronic especially in the old days
it might be from Mark Davis
so these bears
who are trying their best but they're
they look a little silly they have silly proportions
and they're playing their instruments funny
I think the initial concept
art from Mark Davis was very successful
and Walt Disney was brought in
to look at this
you know in November
and it killed it he laughed
and laughed boy did he love
it didn't kill him though
that's a good point
if you recognize the date that I said
he laughed himself into the grave
people think cancer
what it was was he laughed at the country bears
it weakened his lungs to the point where
he couldn't handle a big laughing fit
and sure enough
yes and his body was slumped
over the art of the bears
no just like
great and he's like thumbs up you're heading in the right
direction I love it
and then in the Q&A the guy's like
you know after not too long
he had passed so we refer to that
as Walt's last laugh
what?
isn't that freaky?
yes this is part of the mythology
now we're learning so much it's Walt's
lamp and he loves Palm Springs
and Cotino and now we know about
the country bears caused his last
laugh oh my god
Walt's last laugh if you google
Walt's last laugh does it come up is that like a
I haven't tried I don't know
um that's a good
well it looks like people are
well what you get is a lot of breaking bad
oh yeah
because he because Walter
White kind of dies
manic laughter yeah I see that
oh wait there is a little bit okay yes
we call it actually this is from 2012
we call it Walt's last laugh because of
the nice chuckle Walt got after seeing some
of Mark Davis's drawings
that said
pretty weird mythology isn't it
and how do we know that he
didn't laugh at something at his house
before he died
what if one of the doctors treating
him slipped and fell
or some loose medicine
yeah what about the woman who
would treat his polo injury
every afternoon she had to give a couple laughs
I would imagine in between rubbing
the injury yeah that's part
of it isn't it I would think it would be
right bald jokes
yeah I don't think we can say
this definitively I you know
I hope Walt got a lot more laughs
in but it's interesting mythology
to know about I also
like to think about him laughing like
Walter White
in the crawl space laugh yeah
that it starts as like
oh good Walt likes it and then it continues
for a sustained minute and a half
vaguely psychotic
should we
leave maybe we leave Walt here
okay
so Walt's last laugh
the saddest phrase
here's the other stuff that because
if you watch videos of it you know that something's
up with the animatronics
you know that it is improved but they also
look so much the same
which is a great victory right that
and again that we didn't end up in some
area like actually I just thought of
a new one
Country Bear musical
and it's high school musical style
and all of the high school musical songs
and one and one of the Bears has Corbin
Blues hair this is also
something you could see them doing in
2011 maybe a little
bit they would have done it a little late like a little
post like they just missed the
popularity of their own thing
but thank God they didn't do anything
of this nature you know
but they you know
you could tell that they're refurbished
but I wasn't really sure how and now
I've figured out what happened
it's the same bodies
it's the same if you ever see if you've seen a stripped
animatronic if you've been so lucky
it feels like you know
there's like there's like big
glass or plastic pieces that make
the you know like a big rotund tummy
or whatever it is I think that
stuff like the molding is the same
but it's new fur it's
new skin it's a modern
control system
so it's basically
it's a weird these all the robots are a weird fusion
right where like the you know
the outsides are new
and the base is the same but
it's like it's a hybrid
of like some hydraulic
but some of the newer technology
right
and I hadn't heard any of this
phraseology before
tell me if we've ever talked about this but I
don't feel like we have that the original
original animatronics
were considered A1
audio animatronics
this is what all of the old school ones
would have been classified as
A1 and now these are
A1 A100
hybrids
and A100 is
defined maybe by
Wicked Witch in Great
Movie Ride remember how great that
animatronic was I think all the others
in that ride are A1s
they're a little more simple they turn their head a
little bit but that one gesticulates
to this kind of shocking degree
where it you know feels very
photorealistic
newer presidents I think
at least Obama and everything
after have been
A100s and then
A1000 starts with
Hondo Onaka
and maybe
Lieutenant Beck and
Kyla Ren in Rise of the
Resistance I think like it's not all new
animatronics but a lot of them
are A1000s
now I like this numerical system
I like that it is
done with Terminator
logic I was going to say it's
Terminator numbers yeah
to where yeah eventually
all out of the 3D
movie we end up with A1
million and
A1 million tries to haunt us
down in Killitz it's a
partial liquid it starts out
reaches out and
caresses your cheek
like
Mike imagine
Mike getting you know I'm proud
of you from Optimus
and it like he wipes
away a tear
yeah that'll be the day well Michael
will be in great support of
Michael will love the
A1 millions I will love the A1 millions
we certainly I don't think
had time to talk about this distinction
on the Great Movie Ride episode I
will say that I don't think there was enough
room it was in my notes and
this guy came in and messed everything up
and before you know it we're all sucking on jewels
it's one of the things that's torn me up for years
that we didn't get to talk about A100
and A1 million maybe we just have to do
another Great Movie Ride episode
and then just like lock the doors
yeah yeah and there will be
no shenanigans that episode is called
Great Movie Ride 2 this
time boring yes
and there will be no shenanigans and we
we are very clear there will
be no other people than the three
of us getting into that one
yeah and certainly there's not some way that
he could come in through the vents
no as far we'll do our best
burrow a tunnel through the ground
like a Bugs Bunny
situation
I started in China
and went all the way through
at first I busted out of
Xing Xing anyway
so that's what we're dealing with here is that now
they are they have like half
leveled up they're almost
wicked which but not completely
but they can sure do a lot more
than they used to be able to do there's also
there's a thing that came into play with A100
that I'd never heard of before
which is a new control system
control system called compliance
and here again we are
in kind of scary sci-fi movie
compliance is just like a way that
they could like basically
like an old
Abraham Lincoln original Lincoln
robot could not suddenly
do a karate chop right
because then the entire body would shake around
in this weird way but compliance
is this level of control or actually gives
actually it gives a little bit of freedom to the
robot where it can like stop
a little bit past where we say that
you can stop that's what's happening with these
robots is that like what we'd like
you to stop here but that's just like where you need
to start slowing down so they
so it's like
what's the like
it's like a car
being able to like
slow to a halt as opposed
to basically
like newer robots aren't
faster they're just they
have more they have more control
and they can slow they're more precise and they could
slow down kind of
of their own volition apparently
yeah yeah so it's not
even though some of these robots feel very
like a big sweeping motion of the
shaman of song
like well
the rumor is one of the rumors for
D23 is that there's going to be
a Walt animatronic coming
to Disneyland this is still really
I've heard a couple that's what people are saying
at the very least they did like some presentation
where there was like a hologram Walt
which kind of looked like deep fake Walt
which I am not as interested in as
an actual robot because like they
there's apparently been like some sort of patent
filed or work permit
for like
putting in another spot on the Lincoln
stage so when it flips over there will be a
spot for a robot or something
there and people are speculating
for the 70th anniversary
you're going to get like a little Walt presentation
and then it'll spin around and do the Lincoln
so he'll explain this was his idea
very country bear that there's a little like side
stage yes Walt does
a little side show so I like the idea
that there like this is a Walt is going to be
an A1000
Walt if that's if the rumor comes
to pass or or
hopefully a million hopefully it's hopefully
it's a Walt that can liquefy
and then also something I'm worried
about Bugsy doing yeah like
yeah Walt can split
into 10,000 pieces
and then reform yeah and climb
into your water bottle go home with you
and then give you a scare oh man if the
at the Honda Center you reveal liquid
Walt to like
10,000 15,000 fans
he goes they send liquid Walt
through the sprinkler system
and then he reforms on stage
and starts picking up audience
members throwing some devouring
others no I was okay that we were probably
not going to D23 until now until
we hear that yeah shit so
liquid Walt well they're
look they need bodies they need bodies
to begin the battle against
the Walt one million well I want to do
it somebody get us in now to
somebody get us on the press list to D23
because I want to get that's why
they
are doing the Honda Center
like the different kind
of compliance of like
no bags unless they're clear
plastic and this size and this
size because they want to make sure the
liquid Walt perfectly fits
oh yeah yeah oh yeah
smart yeah yeah
he can perfectly divvy up little
pieces of himself to every audience
member that would be a real show stopper after
they explain when the portos is opening in
downtown Disney and then they finally go right
when we have one more thing and then
liquid Walt for Disneyland
that's the main yeah yeah
that's the I know we once again we're building up
D23 to be a lot and yeah it could be
like the Lego store is getting a new
sign
well we will see
now didn't we
address when we did an episode
about the partner statue yeah
but the statue of Walt holding hands with Nicky
in several of the parks
did we didn't we discuss
that one of his wishes was to
not be yeah yeah portrayed
in a physical form in the parks or
in anything and now they're gonna make a robot of him
mm-hmm okay yeah well
well he did the statue and that broke the dam on
it I think yeah yeah it was like well
fuck him whatever
here's the statue of
him dreaming and
it's like taking a crap
you can touch it it's
scalding hot metal in Florida
sunlight hot there's hot Walt
in Epcot there's a liquid
Walt in Disneyland
there's all the different varieties
and cold Walt's
head yeah yeah
freezer somewhere so yeah no they
he's he's really
rolling in his grave mm-hmm and
also something that they will portray soon
that he's rolling yeah goes yeah
our new technology that our
our new electric motors
allow Walt to spin in his grave
in the haunted mansion
oh yeah
much faster than any robot could have fifty
years ago that's cool
so anyways
that's a lot of the stuff they did
I found that a little interesting
that it's like because you could tell
something's up they these are improved
and again a big victory something that I don't
think would have happened in the 2000s I think
they would have just like slapped wigs
on him done something disgusting
and but here we get like
kind of I think thoughtfully
revamped animatronics
and that's cool and if people
want to do you have a
account for a good quality
version of this Q&A
I think laughing place
posted one oh cool
there is a there's a cell phone that goes off
for a full pass and maybe
one more during the Q&A so just be
warned about that but that's not the fault of
laughing place or them engineers or anyone
no they're usually pretty reliable I single you out
whoever in the audience let that go
for the whole time rude
oh also it's literally
programmed by the these
animatronics were programmed by
the guy who programmed the first
A100 the wicked witch his name's
Doug Griffith who was like the
master in the 90s he's the guy
who did all the programming of all the most fluid
robots that moved it all
forward you know when we were
kids and soaking it all up
journey into imagination was him
American adventure was him kitchen cabaret
horizons
the sword fighting
pirates that are just in the Pirates of the
Caribbean in Disneyland Paris
which were kind of a big next step
step forward in
animatronic fluidity this guy's a legend
he is a legend and this is his final
work in the parks he is retiring
after this that's cool we are seeing
like a master who really knows who
redid the country bears already in 92
so he knows the characters and he's given
him one more go
that's really cool he was already like
settled in on his houseboat
in Florida and they're like we need you to come
back for one more job
it's like I don't do that
anymore
what if we told you
they were going to sing you've got a friend in me
god damn it on him
sounds good can I just say them calling
the D23 parks presentation
horizons is really
setting up the expectations
like crazy you saw that right
they're calling it horizons
that building they
bulldozed and it might
have a permanent sinkhole
around there
but I just had to say that because I'm like
you can't do that you cannot
set us up like this
the expectation wise I know they're not bringing
back horizons but still
that would be a shocker wouldn't it
I would fall on the floor yes
the longest ride with the most animatronics
just brought back there's no way
we're going to rebuild the future of the 80s
but I guess maybe they'll replace the other
build like maybe that's the announcement but still
like calling you can't call it that don't do
that to us that is mean
what is on the horizons new
experiences new
dumplings perhaps
it could be anything
new strategic partnerships with big box stores
ladies and gentlemen the CEO
of Kohl's
we've got many
Sephora stores in
our stores we've got many
champion stores now
we've got many Disney
stores horizons
and they're playing like the horizons music or something
could be
you can't do that we have to my
expectations are now
in the toilet
D23 tied with
Biden's electoral chances
and if either goes better and I'll
just be pleasantly surprised I want
to be I want to be front row at D23 now
the Honda Center to boo if they do
like horizon bait and switch
so now if somebody can get us in
D23 all I want to do
is front row so you have to do that for
us so we can boo when
they like say something about her
horizons you go oh yeah and they're like we're
putting a Kohl's where horizons used to
be in Epcot well
I hope you're ready for the Walt
one million to
form its liquid arm into
a giant ice pick
and just like nab you in the forehead
really fast in less than a second
and that's the end of that threat
I'm nervous about the panel because I've got
a parlay bet on what color
Josh tomorrow's bomber jacket will
be so if
I'm brewing if it's not
black it's okay okay
we talked about Brown's see you
can't count out Brown because Brown's a little
homey that's like launch pad
that is cool yeah
we talked about betting right for the 23
yeah yeah we'll have to figure that out
yeah yeah I don't think we've we haven't
gotten the nitty gritty on that
so that's that's
some backstory to the new show
and I did appreciate that that Q&A and everything
and
I don't know where we go from here do we start
talking about this about the show
I mean there's personnel also
but that could kind of come as we go
I mean I think it bears mentioning
that
one of the big reasons
for hope and excitement within
this group of three especially with
one of this group of three was
the involvement of a name
that feels so coincidental and so
up Mike's alley
that it feels
like a simulation buzz buzz
that one of your favorite
people human beings
yeah yeah as part of this
of this refresh is this a good time to talk
about that of yeah Mac McAnally
Mac McAnally Jimmy
Buffett's right hand man and you didn't
need to say that because again most listeners know
that well yeah that context
is not needed but but yeah
a long time coral reefer band
member Mac McAnally
who's really
having seen Jimmy with you once
is the real musical muscle
of the show
one of my complaints about
the show that I saw on some
of Jimmy's songs in general is the feeling
that it's not the most
musically ambitious it's a little
it's laid back which is what his vibe
is so I shouldn't be surprised
but it's you know alright it's
alright and C to A
to D
if you get any musical bang out of
those shows it is Mac McAnally
a stellar musician who
gets like a moment to shine
has his own robust body of work
in time country music
CMA musician
of the year
how is that I don't
confused by that isn't there more
pop are there more popular
country musicians than Mac McAnally
to give this award to
I think he's written a lot of
he's written like back where I come
from
I just got this email
that says that this morning
I guess I don't care but who did back where I come from
again we say these things
I don't know what that is really
I know that song and I'm
blanking on who did it
well there you go y'all he did back where I come from
who's the artist of that song
silence for one straight minute
Kenny Chesney
I could kind of hum it though
that's something
Mac does it too when he plays
he did it when we saw
Jimmy
did he do it with Jimmy or was that when Jimmy
Jimmy leaves the stage for a second or two
or a second or two like ten minutes
to chill out
yeah and Mac plays his own shows
he's playing solo he's doing a tour
now
now how do you know that Mike
so I
forget because I follow him on all the social medias
I assume this is where we're going with this
yeah and
I've been waiting for him to do a California date
for years and he hasn't done one
I think since I was aware of him
he hasn't done one and I saw that he was playing
California he's doing I think the troubadour in Los Angeles
but he's also playing Buck Owens
Crystal Palace
which is in Bakersfield
and man this is a place I would like to go
it is kind of a drive
dude let's get an episode out of it
let's get an episode
I think there's enough bullshit in Bakersfield
I was talking to Scott about this
and I said this is interesting
because these dates are in August and I said
let me take a look at the dates
I wonder if Mac's going to be
at D23 because
that's what the second weekend in August
and sure enough his
D23 weekend is free
the troubadour is on like maybe the Thursday
or Friday before and then the Crystal
Palace is let's say Tuesday after
D23 and the D23 dates
are opened up
so Scott thought I was stalking Mac by
tracking his tour
I thought it was funny that you said
I think Mac's going to be at D23
he's free
and I was like well he's free
unless his grandkids having a birthday
how do we know
you don't know everything about what Mac
is doing
the chances of him being he's in Los Angeles
already those dates are open
I'm saying it's highly likely
I didn't go through like some records
I didn't hack his phone or something
I'm just saying it would make sense
that he would be at D23 with this ride opening
that he produced and is a voice on
I think it was the phrasing he's free
what if he's got a medical appointment
I mean I don't know what he's doing in the morning
but in the afternoon or night
he's probably at D23
he's got a lot of breakfast
I think it's an instinct maybe
from
to a lesser extent
whether someone will show up at a comic con
but wrestling when
someone's a free agent or about to
be a free agent and you look at their
tour dates and it's like oh
well they're doing this show but
such and such promotion
is in town the next day
so they could show up there
well yes thank you for justifying
mild
stalkerish behavior
my joke
was like
that you weren't
that you actually don't have the full picture
of Mac Mcmally
I don't know for sure what he could be
doing that weekend perhaps Los
Angeles he has other business it's just
very coincidental that he's there
during that
unless he's added dates
well it's like you know we're going to be at
comic con doing the street sharks
panel and coincidentally
also nearby
is hall H and maybe we're getting announced
as
three of the fantastic
four in the
the next phase of the fantastic
once they reset this one
then we're three of the four
sometimes there have been three
the new fantastic
four
what is it hulk wolverine
spider-man and there's
another occasionally
versions I can't remember
we'll be in hall H yes
we'll just take care of that one
we won't be mysterious like Mac
maybe Mac will be in hall H too though
maybe he's doing music for fantastic four
ding-a-ding-a-ding-a-ding-a-ding-a-ding
so his involvement
that's again it's crazy you're like
yeah again what podcast
theme park podcast talks about Mack Mcenally at
length yeah and then for him
to be like a main figure on
this is pretty wild and the
potentially scary news of this ride
this attraction getting redone but it's
by somebody who you trust
yes I assume
I think so
I guess with that
We probably have to figure out, did they pull it off or not?
And I mean, here's the big, maybe the big thing to say is that it is mostly songs from
the Disney library and catalog, right?
Yes.
Songs from movies, done country-fied, done in very country bear style.
I definitely saw people just looking at the set list, having not watched the show and
saying that it feels boring to them.
Yeah.
So that's a sentiment that is out there.
Yes.
Did we feel this way?
How did you both feel?
I feel conflicted.
The bears look great.
You talked about this.
The fur is bright and vibrant.
Yes.
Looks nice.
The new outfits are great.
Their little outfits.
Everyone's little outfit is really good.
The show sounds cool.
It's great to see the bears, just feeling the love that was put into the bear robots
is nice to see on video.
I can appreciate all that.
It's a fun show.
I think kids will go in there.
They'll see funny bears.
They'll hear songs they like.
They will laugh.
They will applaud.
I'm scared by this tone.
They'll like it.
Their smiles will be formed on faces.
Now that said, there is a turn.
You interrupted whatever turn I was going to take.
But that's okay.
Maybe you blunted any sort of anger that was going to ... No, I'm not angry.
It feels a little bit like an ad for Disney.
It just feels a little bit like, yeah, they're doing the songs in a different style.
I would say my biggest complaint, and maybe this is wrong.
Maybe people will disagree.
It feels like the characters of the bears aren't there.
It almost feels like the main joke is just, can you believe this bear is singing that
song you know versus a bunch of hillbilly bears singing about being sad and horny, which
is what the old show was, which I agree maybe you don't need in a park in 2024.
So I understand why you would want to redo the show.
But now the main joke of the show is like, oh, they're doing the song from Aladdin.
Oh, okay.
Versus I can't believe that this bear is singing about ... Tears in a wine.
Tears, yes, which is like a sad song or going out and having women be upset with him because
he can't cheat on his wife or something.
It's a much simpler game, whatever you would call it.
It's a much simpler concept now, which again, I think people will like, and I like too,
it's just like, it feels kind of like an ad.
It feels a little bit like an ad for the other songs in the Disney catalog.
Well, it creates an insular world where only Disney songs and properties exist.
Yeah.
Doesn't it?
It's like a little bit of closing off of the bubble.
We found a place where there was a leak in the bubble and we patched it up.
Right, yes, yes.
There is ... Adam Resnick is the one who wrote Cabin Boy.
Yeah, yeah.
He has a book of essays and there's a pretty funny one where he talks about him and his
family going to Disney World with his sister-in-law's family and they are like die-hards and him
and his family don't really give a shit and they have a terrible time.
The weather is bad.
The parks are crowded.
They're staying at the wilderness lodge and his daughter is not enjoying any of that and
they walk back in the wilderness lodge and I think the big goofy bear from the wilderness
lodge from those old cartoons is there and she says something along the lines of like,
oh, God, they're here too and I think that's kind of, you know, was along the lines of
what Mike is saying like, oh, God, the songs are here too.
I see.
I know it's the middle of a Disney theme park but I think the thing that always appealed
to me since I was a little kid is like you can't get country bears, you can't see the
show anywhere else, you can't get Alien Encounter anywhere else, you can't get the people and
that's kind of what I locked in on.
Sure.
I think a big thing that's always appealed to me.
So by doing songs that exist in other forms, it feels a little less specific.
My other big thing is like it is fair, like it's not a bad thing because, you know, kids
only have so much patience but this show is fair, like they are doing snippets of these
songs and it's on to the next one.
Well that feels, the show feels shorter, definitely.
I feel like it was always snippets.
There were always some really short, you know.
Yeah, 30 second, 45 second little song.
Yes.
Yeah.
So that's not necessarily, but it definitely feels like they whip through it.
It feels like, I think like less characters, right?
I think some are out entirely.
A big gripe I have is they combine Trixie and the Sunbonnets into one musical number.
They don't get their own numbers now.
And Trixie does not come back at the end.
Oh, do they not?
Henry and the raccoon are in that spot.
So yes, that's like right away where you're like, well, they're all, they had to combine
the characters.
That bums me out.
They became backup singers instead of leaders of their own songs.
I mean the Sunbonnet Trio, that's the best song in the old show.
The guy to turn me on, turn me down.
If you haven't seen it before, watch it.
It's crazy.
They want you 24 to watch, but it's fun.
It's really funny.
And weird.
Now that is one of those, wait, okay.
Is that one, do we put that in the, in the category of cancel because they look little?
I mean, it's really strange to say turn me on in an old song.
So I think that used to be a little bit different.
I mean, it doesn't mean the same thing, but I think turning on didn't mean like, oh my
God, I've been turned on versus just like, oh, like I'm really, I like this guy.
You would use it meaning to like more.
I like this person and they don't like, yeah.
So I like that turn on tone also.
Oh my God.
Hey, that's what I do.
It's happening.
Baby, look at this.
Too much insight here.
It's in motion.
But that's what I go.
My voice gets gravelly.
I sound like Wolfman Jack.
Can you believe it?
You probably couldn't tell, but the blood is going haywire in my veins.
Look where it went.
My slightly below average testosterone level is getting slightly more average.
My heart is going wild and it's not just because of any sort of defects in there.
Well I will also, as I said before, I'm not against the idea that you can update all this
stuff.
I'm not saying that this needed to be still in the show.
I'm just saying that was such a funny, weird thing to have in a bear show with those three
characters and now they're sort of just backup singers and they don't get to do anything.
Okay, if they've lost any character's personalities, maybe it's them.
Three romantically aggressive bears is fine.
That has definitely gone away.
Yeah.
There's a way to do that like in sort of a soft.
And I also think, and I don't have a good example of what to do, I also think there
was a way to do some of it with Disney songs in clever ways and the one that they did,
the very least that they put a gag in is the supercalifragilisticexpialidocious number with
just the fiddler who his fiddle starts smoking because he's playing so fast.
At least you got a little joke in there.
That was a good gag, yeah.
In the lobby, there's new stuff in the lobby.
Well the lobby looks great too, we didn't even talk about that, but the lobby they put
a bunch of new stuff.
They put the classic little teddy bear from the original in a glass case.
There's like a lot of fun details that they put in there.
Reviews of the show outside from Grizzly Gazette and Hibernation magazine.
There is a picture that I think raises more questions than answers, but there is a picture
of Henry and the ladder.
He finds a ladder and goes up to swinging Teddy Barra and it appears they're eating
lunch.
Because the thing was like I'll be up there if I can find a ladder.
Yes, in the original show.
And now they've closed that loop.
As soon as I find a ladder I'll be right up.
Right, so all of that stuff makes me feel like okay people really cared is what you're
talking about, which confirms that they really wanted to put a bunch of references and stuff
too.
Okay, so here's something else I got out of this Q&A was the feeling, the guy's pretty
bald about the orders from above were the show is going to go away unless the music
can appeal to a broader audience.
Sure, that is what was said.
That's kind of the code for put songs people know and not like 1930s country songs.
And that's why I wanted to like give the props and credit to that Imagineer and everybody
who worked on this.
And I think this is the epitome of something we see a lot where there's like kind of a
maybe you call it an odd idea or a flawed idea or something that we don't necessarily
agree with but that is like being executed as lovingly and carefully as possible.
I think that we find this a lot that the Imagineers care about what the order like let's do that
order the best way we can do it, even if the order is a little weird.
Yes, and I do feel that because like, yeah, a Tiki Room Under New Manitoum or something
where you feel like, I don't know that the people who made that had disdain for the parks
or something, but sometimes you feel that in those old rides you're talking about or
the old overlays where you're like, they're like, they're like, ah, this old thing sucks,
huh?
Don't you hate it?
Yeah.
And you're like attitude.
And that's where it feels like it's coming from.
And there's no attitude in the right exactly.
So yes, of course, of course I can appreciate that.
I'm being a little bit like, I don't know what to call it.
Well, how do we feel about, you know, there's an introductory song, which is fine, called
Country Bear Musical Jamboree.
Yes.
That's original.
That's not from Other IP.
Right.
And that's you're like, all right, the stage slides out and the five bear rugs come out
and the hootenanny begins.
And it's like fine.
It's just like, I think it's fine.
I don't know why they couldn't have done the original one there.
I guess there's more like introducing the bears in that original one, which they maybe
didn't want to do.
They feel like we don't need to do that.
Yeah.
Don't worry about them.
And this one, this one definitely in the same way that Musical Jamboree underlines what
it is, says the title to like let people know this is what's happening more, I guess.
Yeah.
Even though you see a bunch of bears with instruments, I guess you should kind of know.
But maybe they felt like.
Now some bears are coming out and they have instruments.
Do you know that this is music?
This is musical.
Perhaps the premise was lost in the old way where people like, I don't know what this
is yet.
And you're like, well, let's call it Musical Jamboree in this, in the new song.
The song's fine.
I think it's fine.
It's fine.
Yeah.
Then we get into his first song up, Try Everything.
Yes, Try Everything.
And that sets the tone for what I think the whole show in me, because I've watched this
like six times, I think by now.
Wow.
And I do like it.
I do like it more and more.
At first I was like, oh, it grew on me.
Yeah, me too.
I put it on when I was kind of falling asleep one night and just listened to it.
I wasn't really watching.
I was like, and so then when I watched it and I could see all their jaunty little outfits,
I'm like.
The outfits are great.
The Sunbonnets new little outfits are great.
I'm a big fan of them.
And Trixies.
Let's be clear.
We like the bears little outfits.
But that set the tone for me seeing it, I think, is to seeing all the Sunbonnets and
Trixies are together.
And what is this?
Oh, there's pictures on the back wall, but they're not that funny.
Oh, the characters are lost.
What are we doing here?
That sort of set the first watch for me.
They ruined my childhood.
Yes.
It's complicated because they did preserve the slideshow, which I feel like was just a
technological thing of its time.
And I'm like, oh, I kind of like that.
That did come back.
I can't tell what's in it.
The videos I've watched are too far away.
Yeah.
I think that there's, I assume, I don't know what's happening, but OK, there's some pictures.
Trixie is like skiing and then she's trying, I think, pottery.
And then.
OK.
But yeah, they're like she's sailing here and they're Mark Davis concept art territory.
Bears looking silly.
It's not.
Trying things.
There's also, I think there's the effort made to make Trixie who was sad in previous iterations
to give her a happy arc as she stretches outside her comfort zone and tries everything.
Try everything.
The song that kind of opens Zootopia, the big like train ride that takes you through
all the different burrows and parts of Zootopia.
A song that I've I've ended up with a decently soft spot for due to my son liking the movie.
You know, I'm just in a place of I'm just glad he's not watching like evil YouTube garbage
made by A.I., like if we can get Zootopia on something like rendered nicely and with
a song made by a musician, I'm happy.
Daddy, it's a well thought out world.
If you think about the metaphor too hard, it starts to fall apart.
The depth that it prides itself on doesn't actually function.
Yeah, I think that the I don't I don't mind the song and I think that the shifting it
to country is kind of clever.
It's something you wouldn't think would work.
And I think it does lend itself decently.
It's not, you know, how about this to your point, Jason, about like it's songs that you
hear elsewhere in the park circuit here.
Yeah, try everything doesn't really exist in an American park anywhere.
You know what I mean?
Like, yeah, I don't think this is this.
I'm glad that it's not.
I mean, you get you've got a friend of me.
You get a whole new world.
But this is like a little bit less of an exploited song done in a revamped way, as I don't mind
it. Yeah, it's a little more it's it's crazy to say Shakira song is that's who sings it,
right? Yeah, that that's more of the beaten path.
But if I'm complimenting it, it does like start like high energy, like the top of the
show. So I think that works.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't mind. I will say I don't mind this.
I don't mind the version in like a vacuum.
But it also I think because it's very like uptempo, modern country sounding right away.
I was like, wait, wait, no, wait, what this because I want everything to sound recorded
in a little tin can still on some level, which some of the other arrangements are a
little more like that and some like because like I want everyone's voice to sound
like this. And I want like I want everything to sound a little bit more like you're on
the porch. You can see the calculation in these bears are a good vehicle for modern
country music. But that's not anything we're interested in, I don't think.
Yeah. And I like modern country music to some degree.
But it's like for that to be the first song out with with I'm just saying it set a bad
tone, even though I actually in a vacuum like this arrangement, I try everything.
Yeah. So I was like, oh, wait, what?
Oh, it's going to be because that was my fear.
It was like it was just going to sound like modern stuff.
Well, if it got more so from there, that would be the concern.
Yeah, it did it. It did more tin can music.
Yes. Yeah. They immediately were like hitting you with we don't talk about Bruno.
That would have been like, oh, here we go. Sure.
And later in the show, you get not let it go from Frozen.
But that's true. Frozen song, Fixer Upper.
I forgot that that was a Frozen song.
Frozen is one that hasn't made it to my child's viewing habits.
Yeah. And I've never seen the whole movie and I don't know this song, Fixer Upper.
I've seen the movie and I know most of the songs, but I was like, what is Fixer Upper?
The little trolls singing.
Is that right? Oh. The little ghoulies.
OK. They're a little scared.
The Frozen ghoulies. Yes, of course.
Yeah, I don't know. It's a fine song.
But I like that it's not let it go.
I like that we are. I agree.
You know, we got some obvious, but some, you know.
And Max sings on Fixer Upper because he is Shaker.
He's Shaker. Max plays Shaker.
Shaker, who is also who is Terrence.
Terrence is Shaker. Yes. Terrence is Shaker.
I think it's just like the that's his real name and Shaker is a nickname.
Well, right. Guitar strap that says Shaker is in the lobby display cases.
OK. And he's someone else to who is Mac. Mac.
Oh, yeah. I don't know. Is he one of the Bear Rugs?
He might be one of the Bear Rugs. Yeah, I think so.
Yeah. And he arranged it all.
Maybe we didn't say that in terms of his involvement.
He doesn't just say, but he arranged all of it, a lot of it.
It seems like a lot of it or all of it.
It does sound all like copacetic. Yeah, like it all makes sense,
which is a plus and a minus, because like
part of the weirdness was the variety of tones of the songs in the old one.
Yeah. And didn't the original Big Al saw that was just that was a recording of
that wasn't even something they made. Right.
Blood on the Tex Ritter, Tex Ritter. Yeah. Yeah.
The country bear, the vacation show and stuff like those,
those are more modern sounding recordings and they were more varied
in its like genre. But yeah, the original version. Yeah. Yeah.
And we don't have to go in order necessarily,
but just like strong feelings about any.
Well, as I said, the supercalifragilisticexpialidocious part, I like a lot.
Yeah. There's no singing on it.
It's just a fiddle. It's just earnest playing the fiddle.
You feel like they would have done that before.
And by the way, the original show had the Davy Crockett song.
It's not like they there wasn't stuff like this.
You know, I think the guy that that imaginary
even even pointed out the original plans were to have like
hi-ho and other Disney songs.
Yeah. And that happened like Tiki Room when you're leaving.
They're playing like a hi-ho. No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
The fiddle is also teased in the lobby.
There's a burned out fiddle in the display case. Oh, OK.
This is something he does all the time. I like that.
I like the whole new world.
And that is singer, songwriter and mandolin player Chris Thiele. Yes.
The man who replaced Garrison Keillor on a Prairie Own Companion.
And that's why Jason knows who it is, which was cancer.
Because he got the only job in show business Jason wants.
I yes, I applied two or three times to write on that show.
Prairie Own Companion.
And then they changed the name at some point.
And then it was canceled. OK. OK. Soon after that.
But like Mark Wahlberg talking about Blaine's on that fateful day.
Oh, you could have saved it.
It wouldn't have gone down that way if I had been there.
This is fascinating.
Have we said this on the show that you replied to write for Prairie Own Companion?
I wrote sketches.
They were just looking for like sample like radio sketch samples.
Yes. OK. So we need five long winded stories.
We need like three folksy anecdotes. Right.
If you have anything about pond deals or Sandy's, that'd be helpful.
We've been looking for Sandy's material.
I oh man, did I?
I might have put pond deals in on this.
You got to find that packet.
I wrote a lot of fake commercials.
I got to go through an old job box.
I also think you should just do like do your own Prairie Own Companion
and call it Prairie Own Companion.
Just like blatantly podcast.
Own Companion.
Yeah. Steal the whole premise.
Sure. Yeah, yeah.
But you could just update, you know, you could just take a format.
No updating. No update.
No, but I'm saying just do it.
But as a podcast now and then it'll be unrecognizable in our little
right scene of podcasts because nobody listens to that.
I think what you're saying makes a lot of sense.
And I think what I was pitching at the time, at least, was
inviting a lawsuit by doing the exact same show that Garrison
Keillor had been doing. Only Jason was hosting it.
So, yeah, what you're saying is correct.
But what's what's he going to do?
Yeah, he's on the ropes. Yeah.
He didn't die, did he? No, he's still alive.
But I did like this.
No, he kind of sings like in a very particular way that seems.
Yeah, he still sings it like a character.
You know what? That's what I like.
And they recorded his mandolin play is very talented instrumentally.
Yeah, this is him.
This is like musician and voice.
And he didn't even though he is somebody who does more like modern
country music a little bit.
He still did it in like a garsh kind of voice.
I've seen him in the Largo a bunch of times.
He'd pop into those John Bryant sets.
He's fantastic on the Nickle Creek.
He was in Punch Brothers.
And, you know, I'm no expert in a lot of that.
But, yeah, look up.
So there's a song I was happy with you.
The John Bryant song.
You know, we Mike and I both seen John Bryant a lot.
The film composer at Largo is an incredible songwriter.
Also, and he did all of these songs and all of these shows
that never came out in any form.
And some of them, I think, are like some of the best songs I've ever heard.
And there's one of him and Chris Thiele doing I was happy with you.
And it's great.
So if you want more of this, which character does he do?
He's Wendell.
If you want to see Wendell in real life,
doing a non Disney song, that's very good.
Yeah. And this is kind of a showstopper
set wise. Great.
And I think a fun use of the swing of Swing and Teddy
Barra's swing and the contextualizing it with flying.
And, you know, when you get a little like smoke machine situation,
I think this is a good for it.
For it being here's the country bears doing a song that's extremely overexposed.
Yeah. I think it's a pretty successful little number.
Yeah. Yes. I I.
I don't think the lines after like the come up.
She does say come up and see me sometime.
But then the jokes aren't as good as like when I find a ladder, I'll be right up.
I think it's great joke.
But the head say one of the head says,
I'm scared of heights, and there says, I'm scared of swings.
I'm like, there are a couple lines that I'm not so like.
Yeah. And by the way, we're watching videos of D23 preview.
Yeah. Where it's killing, where some of it's killing.
So, you know, if the jokes aren't landing there, we're in rough shape.
Yeah. Yeah.
But also, Jason, I feel like you're analyzing a come up and see me sometime
also. Well, that's one of the great references of all time.
Yes. Well, similarly, I think the joke of being a couple of the big
out moments don't quite work for me.
I think I think I am a fan.
I'm surprised how much I'm realizing that I that I like it.
I think, OK, it kills with this audience who is probably a lot of anticipation.
And it's not going to work like this everywhere where people are not in every
showing, where people are not like coming in as big fans of Big Al.
However, shows and going for a little bit.
Who's the who's the main character we're excited for who we haven't seen?
And then you hear pretty reminiscent of the old version.
Yeah. Out of key, Duong, and huge response to that.
Like he's here. It's like the Jaws music, like preceding the character.
All right. And then and then a lot of anticipation of what the song going to be.
And then it's Remember Me, one of the saddest songs in the Disney or Pixar
canon, and it is funny.
Maybe it requires like you're saying, Mike, maybe it requires the context of,
oh, I know this is a very sad character and that he's singing the very sad song.
It might be getting a laugh that's like
the weird laugh, you know, that requires context.
But I have the context that I liked it.
I think that works.
I think Al is more of a professional.
Like, I don't think it.
I don't think you should be breaking down crying.
Like, I get it's a sad song.
I think that it's Remember Me.
The part that doesn't work for me when is when he comes back
and he starts doing it again.
They try to do that bit from the old show.
He does it after the number is done.
He does it when the curtain of some bonnet
tree is lowering, the curtains closing.
And it's really not that big of an issue.
Like Henry comments on it.
But it's like, oh, he should have done that in the middle of this.
Well, but that's not the bit.
So the bit of the old show, one of the bits of the old show was
that the show was like going off the rails a little bit.
Or that Henry would be embarrassed because this is like the mama
don't whoop little Buford.
So he's like, well, we only have high class stuff.
And he's like nervous or whatever.
And then Big Al comes out with this song that's like blood,
like a really like violent song.
And they're like, they want that off stage.
So now and then he comes back later to try to interrupt the show.
But now it's just that Big Al is sad.
And the show has actually gone pretty well up until that point.
So it is a little different being a bummer, just bumming us out with the song.
Right. So he and he's too sad to even sing it.
So before Big Al was more like kind of this like goofy big bear
who's a little clueless to what he's singing.
And now it's that Big Al is depressed.
So they've actually given Big Al a different sort of character game
in this version.
That's a good point.
Big Al, though, is funny.
We were watching this last night.
My daughter didn't seem to care about some of it.
Again, this is video.
So she's, you know, playing with toys.
She saw Big Al. She goes, Big Bear.
OK. Big.
She kept saying Big Bear, Big Bear, like pointing at him, running up to the TV.
Big Bear. I go, well, that's that's the
design of Big Al is so funny.
They retained that.
Yes. You got that.
When does that matter?
Like, you know, does it matter that he's no longer doing blood in the saddle?
Well, once you hear that any gripe that I have, ultimately,
if kids love it and people like this version and maybe it's more filled up,
then I'm wrong.
Like I can I'm I might be wrong.
I'm more of like I will I will say that
my tastes are not the tastes of the average theme park goer.
Yeah. So I'm not happy to be wrong, but I'm accepting of being wrong.
If kids like this version better, which they probably do, they probably
I don't think the old version I think kids would like the old version
because they would see the funny robots in the songs.
You can clap along.
But now that they know the songs, is it going to be more fun for them?
Probably. And I'll say there's there's thought.
But it like I like Henry and the Raccoon, whose name I'm just blanking on.
I had to flip it up. Sammy. Sammy.
I like that they do. You've got a friend of me.
That's cute. And I like that the big closing number is bare necessity.
It's like, oh, that's the obvious.
I feel like Bear Bear, you know, that's the maybe the obvious song,
but they save it to the end. Yeah.
It's fun to see everyone sing it.
And then they do come again, which is which is the original,
original and from other versions of the show. Right.
And I like that. I like that they have a song when you're going out.
I feel like as we sit with it, because I think like, yeah,
we kind of hadn't gotten into it.
And the other night we were all like, we all had kind of a bug up our butt about it.
When you actually sit with it and watch it, you're like, what did we lose here?
And are we and I didn't want to be in the I was also starting to go like, OK,
what are these old things that we liked?
I did like all the guys that turned me on turned me down.
And they got big laughs out of that.
And those laughs are gone now.
I mean, people are laughing just that it's weird that it's there.
But then I'm like, what else went away?
And like, oh, yeah, mama, don't whip little Beaufort.
Like, I think we'd be on the wrong side of history to be saying they took away.
Well, right. I don't want to be those cranks going.
They took the song of that whooping away.
Well, as I said, even taking away the the guy that turned me on,
so I'm not saying that's wrong to take away.
It should have been a place by something equal.
If it needs to be softer in its weirdness, I understand that.
Yes, I think they OK, if we're good, if we had to note anything here,
I think it's that the Sunbonnet trio needs to sing a weird song still.
There's got to be something that would can raise the stock in my mind a lot.
Yes. But I think, yeah, like just stuff like the smoking fiddle
and things where I was like, I'm looking for a few more little joke things
in the actual show or it doesn't have to be weird.
It just has to be like little joke things versus sort of just going.
Isn't funny is I think as you say that, I think that's something that's missing.
Yeah, I think it's a little the show goes a little too cleanly.
Yes. This is like the Muppet show.
It's supposed to have a little disasters in it.
Also, I wonder, was rewriting lyrics on the table
because I think you could have gotten a lot in there that would have been fun
if you could have played with the lyrics a little bit.
Sure. And that like that that seems more interesting.
If I was writing the show, be like, could I like rewrite Gaston
or something with one of the characters?
Oh, yeah. And the same melody and some of the same lyrics.
But it's about Romeo McGraw or whatever.
There are other stuff in like the vacation show.
What's the number with the octopus in it?
There's stuff like that, even that I feel like could have been to.
Yes. Which is like one of the bears is singing a love song to an octopus.
And it's like, yeah, that that was such a little funny, simple thing
you could have done with like one of the Disney songs playing.
And now you've given it a context of like he's having this
like love affair with an octopus or something silly.
I just you know, I needed to conjure some.
I didn't have these ideas at the ready, and I just googled the phrase
the horniest Disney songs. Yeah.
And, you know, I think we got a great option here at number two.
Well, number one, just if you're curious, they put Gaston.
Oh, sure. You were right there.
Number two, Hellfire from Hunchback of Notre Dame.
That is the song of longing for Esmeralda.
Yeah, yeah. Hunchback.
I mean, we had Jane on and talked about that live show.
But rewatching that movie, I was like, I didn't remember this at all.
Like, it is a great movie, and it is so dark and strange.
And like to have the goofy gargoyles in the same movie.
Hey, don't get them, pal.
The the priest. I will burn her.
That was hilarious. He's going to burn.
But yeah, you know, there's got to be there's got to be a version of Hellfire
with some bonnet trio, right?
There is a bear who is so off limits to them that is so or different.
Maybe it's a member of a different species or it's a hunky skunk.
Henry, who has control over, you know, the the the back story
is that Henry like yay or nays who everybody dates.
He is kind of controlling and not a good way.
Maybe he's kind of the garrison keeler of the
he runs kind of a toxic ship.
Sure. Yeah.
Maybe like Teddy Bar has moved on from Henry, though,
although she's singing a duet and then the heads on the wall are commenting.
Yeah, it's not the connection there, really.
I guess, you know, it's just doesn't want to settle down, you know,
and that's that's not for people.
Some people want to play the field.
What? Maybe she's doing a Fleetwood Mac kind of thing.
You know, it's all crazy.
And it just feeds into the music.
Oh, well, that's then I want to then I want darker songs.
We need heavier songs to do as as Henry and Trixie stare at each other
or trig waiter or to Teddy Barra, I guess.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Like all of that tension, a la Stevie and Lindsay has to be clear.
Yeah. Here's one that they've used.
They used it in harmonious.
And then we will just be yelled.
This is so specific.
The Bastille Day fireworks, Disneyland, Paris.
So they go all out for that.
They're shooting off so many fire.
It is like even more than Fourth of July here in America.
But they use a bunch of hunchback stuff.
And I feel like they use out there pretty well in both those shows.
OK, so I that could be one.
I feel like that'd be fun to have, you know, someone saying
Teddy Barra on the swing or the Sunbonnet Trio, like pining for something out there.
Well, I I think that the I think that if Henry is specific, has outlawed
that the my bears are not allowed to date big, hunky skunks.
Yeah. And that is what.
And it is it is the Sunbonnets pining for.
Yeah. The sexiest skunk who is already sort of like priest habit in color.
You just you flip it. He's the man of faith.
We do take it the other way.
But then they're all singing about how they're going to burn
and then a skunk's face in flame.
It's a great question.
Who do we think of the bears as the most religious?
Hmm.
A very good question.
Do we think it's Wendell?
We're the fiddle player.
He channels God's power to smoke that fiddle.
Big Al kind of carries the most weight with him.
I know. I feel like I met a lot of like sad Catholics
and much who carry the guilt and carry the weight of the world.
And maybe that's the context of Big Al.
He doesn't allow himself joy due to all of the self-imposed rules.
Mm hmm.
That might be my guess, but I don't know.
It's up. That's another sound off in the comments.
Say hello to the comments.
Who do you think is the most faithful of all these bears?
And who do you think is an atheist?
I like to be prepared as number seven on this horny list of Disney songs.
Yeah, be prepared. Why? I don't know.
He's horny for power.
I think they were just running.
They couldn't do 10.
They couldn't find 10 that you could really classify as horny.
Yeah, yeah. You found the same article.
Can you feel the love tonight's also there?
Oh, that would have been great.
That's pretty clean. Yeah, that would have been. Yeah.
That is how they just they it's you know, it also doesn't have to be.
So we don't have to get it.
We don't have to say weird phrases.
We don't even have to like imply anything too odd.
You just I like the idea of all of them being like Miss Piggies
sort of like shoving a more diminutive character into their grip.
Yeah, a la Kermit. Sure.
Just like if the slideshow shows you
that each son bonnet has a different kind of like nervous boyfriend.
Yeah. And they are much more aggressive.
That's funny. I think that I think we're having fun with that. Uh huh.
How about sooner or later, you're going to be mine from Dick Tracy.
Oh, great. This song that Madonna sing.
I mean, if they did this, we'd be giving it a bad name.
The rest of the show could be worse and be like, well,
at least the fucking Dick Tracy songs in here, that's wild.
Yeah. Like I like Disney.
Just didn't he just buy Queens cattle like fully by Queens?
I thought it was the other way.
I thought it was that they I was thinking about this.
I think they maybe let Sony.
Oh, Sony got it. I think maybe.
Oh, they gave it away to Sony. OK.
This is a major deal.
Yeah, this is a that's what it was billion dollar deal more. Wow.
But yeah, any any songs like pop, regular rock or pop songs
that they could have thrown in here, too?
What's the horniest Queen song?
Oh, my goodness. Fat bottom bears.
Yeah, probably.
I'm like, they're out here putting that in the park.
Yeah, I don't think that's.
Oh, well, I'd love to see the sun, but I think don't stop me now.
Oh, my God.
That that and maybe in some ways, I'm really just like looking
for some more little surprises.
That's really what I want.
Like it doesn't have to be that everyone is sad and horny.
But like being surprised by don't stop me now.
A country version of Queen.
I've been like, well, that's unexpected.
That's weird.
Like just finding different oddities, different ways
to make things interesting or odd or funny.
Well, this is what we were talking about it in this argument of the feeling
that Disney stuff is kind of inherently like sanded off at the edges.
And I feel like as I thought about it more and as we talked about it more,
it doesn't feel so like the losses don't feel huge to me.
But it feels like like on Club 3,
I was complaining about the Beach Boys, Frank Marshall documentary
and how it's almost like a thing that's like and then and they like very Disney.
They lived happily ever after.
Oh, by the way, two of them died.
And don't worry about that.
And Brian and mental struggles enough that there was a full movie made about it.
And but don't and the struggles continue to this day.
OK, don't worry about it.
And that is that is a kind of a I think I think Disney,
Disney's modern stuff is definitely
I not to say it was ever edgier, but boy, is it not now.
And I don't need them to sing songs about whooping and being turned on.
But I but like a five percent more weird.
It's not about dirty, inappropriate.
And I think it's about weird.
I think so. That's where I think I align with you.
It doesn't take much. I think this is pretty successful.
But in this list, he's a tramp.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
A girl worth fighting for.
I mean, these are probably good to you for the great mouth.
The decisions of songs were based on what people know.
Yes. And the famous ones that are 25, 30 years old.
And then the newer things they could pick from new stuff
that will probably have sequels.
Yeah, I will say this all could have gone a lot.
Like the yes, 100 percent more unfortunate, like in this land choice
of like we're closing the shooting gallery to build a vacation club lounge.
Yeah, that sucks.
Like, that's weird.
And the room there was rumor for years that they were going to put
like a Toy Story Marionette show in here, which at least would have been a trick.
That might have been a planted rumor to find leakers.
Yeah. Or to see if people like it.
Some people have claimed, though, that there were at least plans for it.
Well, there's that one rumor that leaked also that it was going to be
kind of more remodeled on that very successful book that was made into a film
and that it was going to be turned into bear billy elegy.
And I think that's really smart that they didn't go.
I think now that would be that was a really divisive show.
If we could have gotten Glenn Close's Mimaw Bear in there.
Mimaw Bear would have been good.
That might have transcended the she's doing attractions.
She might have done Mimaw Bear.
The nice thing.
The nice thing is, is that the bears are refreshed.
They look good.
This is not going away anytime soon.
And there is a possibility for new shows.
I have not seen anyone say it.
Uh huh. But it could happen.
But it's possible.
And more set up for it to happen now.
Yes, because everything is refreshed and it's going to at least last for 10, 15 years.
Yeah. If they try to change the bears a little, there is not a chance
of workers getting blasted with hydraulic fluid by taking a jacket off.
Like taking that tag off of the clothes that a Coles that hits you with the ink.
If you try to steal a shirt, an expensive shirt.
Workers will not be blinded by out of date old fluid.
Right. So that's possible that they could do new stuff.
And I think the potential is there.
But yeah, yeah, I think chances are
there will the weirdness will never come back.
The weirdness can never come back.
In any part of the Disney company, I guess, in a way here.
Yeah, because like that's if there's any, you know,
Jason, I like a lot of Marvel stuff, Marvel movies, but that does feel like it's in a box.
There's a certain box you got to play in.
Obviously, no, Deadpool is going to blow this box wide open with this.
Our rating, I am looking forward to it.
I will say that.
But it feels very much like you got to stay in your lane and rides feel that way.
And movies and TV and stuff feel that way.
And I just I lament the lack of weirdness more than anything.
But it's good that they're it's good.
They're around the big bears still big bear like big bears still there.
And the big bear is funny.
Yeah. Yes. But yeah, I mean, if shouldn't we be taking
cues from Deadpool and if that's part of the company now and that's pointing
then should not some characters in this new country bear show do a song about pegging?
Yeah, I that's an important is apparently a big character trait.
Now I need to get caught up on Deadpool because I'm more behind on that.
The Breaking Bad.
So I got to watch those two movies fast so I can see the third.
Jason has a legal pad at home and it says get caught up on one
Deadpool to pegging to get prepared for this new movie.
Well, he just wants to read up to make sure he's caught up.
Either you put Deadpool on the ride.
But wouldn't it be funny if they made if the ride open, it was like way worse
and more aggressive and dirty.
And you're like, what?
How did they get away with this?
And then Deadpool showed up and you go, oh, I get it.
Oh, yeah. Deadpool's here.
Yeah. Chibi Changa's got it.
Henry pulls his mask off and you realize who it's been the whole time.
How is Deadpool going to be?
He's going to be in the parks.
There's no way Deadpool and I'm this is all speculation,
but Deadpool is going to be in another 10 movies.
Then when all is said and done, he's going to walk around
Avengers campus and roast it.
I'm sure Deadpool will be a walk around character soon.
Maybe next week or two weeks from now.
But there's like Deadpool ride, I bet, is like going to shoot up to the priority list.
And I wonder how that will look in a Disney park.
How long did you wait, idiots?
What? That's what he says.
Oh, in the line, I see.
Oh, how long did you wait, an hour or two?
I like that Deadpool impression.
How long did you wait, idiot?
I don't know what he sounds like.
I haven't watched the.
He sounds like everybody who's been in any commercial in the last 20 years.
Just kind of like a fast talking attitude guy.
So he sounds like the two of us.
Well, yeah, no, no, not those commercial actors.
He's talking about a different type.
Yeah, guys, you guys who kind of like shake their head around more.
Yeah, he's yeah.
But what does maybe this is a future up.
So we imagine what the Deadpool ride will be, you know, because we're thinking
we're going to we're going to fix Tomorrowland soon.
We're all going to do have different assignments.
Jason, of course, has budget tomorrow.
And I have reasonable, moderate sized budget.
Twenty twenty four Disney Tomorrowland.
Scott has blue sky, sky, unlimited sort of budget and imagination Tomorrowland.
But maybe in the future, we do this with Deadpool.
We each get different assignments and figure out what kind of a ride
Deadpool will have in the future.
I really don't know enough about Deadpool to begin to do it now again.
I'll have to catch up much as Jason does.
All I know is I from from what we've just been talking about about him.
I think I have a good idea of how the Deadpool ride could secure you in place.
Very true. All right.
I'm calling it. You survived the ride on that note.
Do do let us know like other series you want,
you know, the other things we can return to all our country.
We're jammer week for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast, the ride, the second gate or get one more bonus
episode on our VIP tier club three.
We'll find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
And there's nothing we don't have to say.
Chimichangas are what Deadpool would say.
I guess that's because it's kind of a non sequitur.
This is all I know.
When he's come up on the show, the word chimichanga is then immediately been said.
And now that I know, pegging is part of it.
And that's that's my Deadpool word.
We could we could add context to that and say that there was an article
that came out that Kevin Feige had to explain because Deadpool references
pegging, the sexual act.
And Kevin Feige, if you're wondering why in the world
the last 10 minutes of this pegging, Kevin Feige had to explain to coworkers,
which really sounds like an H.R.
nightmare. Yeah.
Boss, explain a sexual thing to you.
But anyway, so
Deadpool week coming soon.
You know, it sounds you know, it sounds like a much bigger nightmare
is our three dorky hosts of a podcast explaining who are relative
at low levels of sexual comfort, explaining what pegging is to you.
God, that sounds like the biggest nightmare of all.
No, thanks.
We can we get a hold of Deadpool co-creators,
Phoebe and Nisi and the Rob Liefeld and Joe Kelly.
You added the funny stuff.
Which of them, what do they think about all the pegging discourse around Deadpool?
Is it just in the movies or was it in the comics at some point?
Jason, I don't know the answer to that question.
I don't know when this entered.
How to boot up the Marvel Unlimited app.
And I'll try to get to the.
That's your assignment.
Put that on the number three as you find out the history of Deadpool and pegging.
OK.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.