Hey guys, before the episode starts,
we have a quick little announcement.
We wanted you on the second gate to be the first to know.
Mike, would you like to explain what's going on?
I guess so.
Folks, if you know what San Diego Comic-Con is,
it's the largest, what, Jason, what is it?
The pop culture convention?
What do they call it now?
The pop culture event?
Yeah, the pop culture event of the year.
It's a giant.
You've never heard of it.
100,000 people go to San Diego,
clog up the streets,
and they have fun going to different panels.
Get yelled at by people with religious signs.
You're all selling this so hard.
Here's the thing, I'm describing
what my favorite time of the year,
I'm so excited to go,
and I'm extra excited this year
because we are going down and doing something there
at the official convention.
Podcast The Ride is hosting a panel
in conjunction with Mattel, the real Mattel Company.
We're actually working with Mattel.
We are working with Mattel.
We went to Mattel for a meeting.
No joke, and we are going to be doing a show
with the topic of the street sharks.
They're back.
They're back, 30th anniversary street sharks.
Podcast The Ride, ex-street sharks, ex-Mattel.
It's happening at Comic-Con.
We can't say exactly the day and time yet,
but that will come out within a week or so.
So just keep it peeled,
so you'll catch it through our media.
We'll make sure you know about it.
But if you're already going to Comic-Con,
just know, be on the lookout,
because we might pop up as might Slammoo.
We will pop up.
Around every corner.
And Slammoo will pop up.
With our big action, our fast action fists.
Our jaws will be moving when we talk about it
on this live podcast, essentially, we're doing.
But yes, if you're going to Comic-Con,
Comic-Con is sold out, but there's still ways to go.
So if you're thinking about it,
let's get on it right now,
because you want to see us chat
about all the different sharks and all the mythology.
Mike, will you personally check your way,
check the listener's way in to get them in there?
I'm putting a lot on you,
That is hard to do.
What's the kind of thing you'd like to do?
It is a thing I'd like to do,
but yes, I don't think I can personally get you in,
is really, is the situation.
But I believe you, in your own personal life,
should look for shenanigans, how you could get in.
And I think that would be possible.
So if you're in San Diego.
But yeah, you need a badge.
You're going to the con already.
You do need a badge to attend whatever this is.
So just in case you think it's like a separate,
it's just like, you have to be going already.
Yes.
And don't go down there.
Get out and sanction our tomfoolery.
Yes, sanction our tomfoolery and come see us
at the official Street Sharks panel,
podcast the ride, X-Metal,
a Comic-Con exclusive presentation in just a few weeks.
We hope to see you down there.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to the second, second gate,
exclusive PTR post office here on podcast,
the ride, the second gate.
Like I said, second, just enough to make that confusing.
I'm Scott Gardner, it's Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am the second introduction on the show today.
My name is Mike Carlson and I am a second place in the,
let's see, treat race in general,
as far as having treats, I would say.
Okay, yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, the second of the treat loving boys.
I'm the silver medalist.
I'm a distant third.
Yeah.
Jason Sheridan's number one.
Thank you, yes.
Gold medal winner, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, gold medal winner.
Yeah, hey, we got a ton of great questions,
which makes me glad we're doing it in this way
and keeping everybody off of Twitter slash X
as much as possible, plus longer.
I mean, as much as I would love that,
like only the best of the best pay
for that extra space on X.
And I'd love to get questions from those people.
Yeah.
If we exclusively got questions from blue checkers,
I think we'd be in great shape.
Blue, yeah, blue checkers that don't know anything about us
but are hardcore Disney fans.
Yeah, yeah.
It would just be, you'd start to parse it,
the paragraphs and paragraphs that you unravel
and then like, wait, why are they, there's no question.
They're just telling us why AI is coming for us
and our jobs and why he's glad that it is.
Yeah, there'll be a lot of that.
There'll be a lot of guys named like Brer Brandon there
with like a cartoon of themselves dressed
in a song of the south clothes.
Briar Patch Bob has a lot of points he wants to get across.
Yeah, so we would be fielding those questions.
I don't know that we want to do that.
Do you think we can still turn it around?
I mean, it looks bad.
The Tiana sign is up and the tower is up
and they're starting to run it.
But I think if we put our minds to it,
we could still flip it back.
Yeah.
I really think we could.
Six months and it's back, you know, six months.
This is such a failure.
They'll realize the mistake they make
when they realize that they went woke
and then step two went broke.
They're keeping all those animatronics around.
Yeah.
They're still dressed themselves and I'm right back out.
Communicore Hall is actually for festivals.
That's why it looks like an empty hallway
at an abandoned school.
Okay.
You don't understand it.
I mean, for me, for me personally,
I think that a hectic park like Epcot,
you need like a break.
You need like some space to like take a breather.
But you know, if you just want it to be full of stuff to do
then that's fine, it's your prerogative.
Yeah, Epcot, it takes Disney like a year
to like finish the lawn of the Haunted Mansion.
But that's because they're putting every blade of grass
in one per day.
Okay, do you understand that?
They're taking the care and the time
on like Universal who just like built a whole park
in like two years.
Just kind of rushed job to just like spooged it out.
And is that what you want?
Do you want to just, do you want a company
that's just spraying its seed
or that's planting it carefully?
Like they want to get you pregnant.
And that's Disney.
Yeah.
Well, that'll be, that'll come soon.
That's not this episode though.
No, no.
This is a different vibe today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I feel like I should tell you guys at the top
that this is a real post office episode.
I had the thought.
I'm not launching any sort of prank or surprise attack
other than trying to hijack this
for just a couple of minutes to talk about my experience
seeing Kenny G live.
Oh, that's this over here.
Do you mind?
No, please.
Can I have a minute?
I don't want to like keep the listeners waiting.
Okay, yeah, go ahead.
I also wanted to bring it up
because it kind of closes the loop on something
that came up at the very end of the city walk
Orlando saga.
We were talking about the kind of cursed sub city walk
LA shopping, dining destination, LA live.
And you were defending it for some reason, Mike.
And Weiger said, when have you ever had a good time there?
Now I am happy to say.
Really?
The answer is seeing Kenny G at Club Novo.
This was a hell of a time.
And Club Novo is at LA live.
Club Novo, yes, Club Novo is at LA live.
Every concert venue there changes names every six months.
Microsoft Theater became Peacock Theater
and will be something else again in six months.
I wondered if it would be like boring.
I wondered if this would be sort of like a patience test
of a concert to get through.
Instead what I encountered was with the possible exception
of Corey Feldman and the Angels,
the most fascinating concert I've ever been to.
We didn't really know what to expect.
This was a birthday gift for Erin.
Because she, look, her Kenny G affection goes back to,
she was like a easy listening radio,
Coast 103.5, John Cicada, Peter Cetera.
So I knew this would be a big hit.
I've been dying on the hill that there is good Kenny G
in the early 80s, just like fun,
enjoyable little funk jams, right?
Even though I've said that,
I knew that this was not gonna be a concert of that.
I knew this was not gonna be like early 80s funk show.
And here's what I didn't expect was innovation.
And that's why I'm bringing it up.
Things that I've never expected to see in a concert
that break the concert form in ways
that completely caught me off guard.
Including very beginning, all the house lights are on,
I'm just talking to Erin, I was fielding a text
and then all of a sudden I look up and he's just there.
They didn't do an introduction, they didn't dim anything.
And not even on the stage,
he's on a little box down below the stage,
which was very close.
This is not that big of a venue
and for not too much expense, we were in the sixth row.
Yeah, we were doing it up for Kenny G
and suddenly just right there, it was crazy.
Like bigger than the Copperfield Theater in MGM Grand?
Ooh, that I'm not sure.
I don't have a good sense of-
Cause that's a pretty small room relatively.
It's got a second, like a balcony level.
Probably more seats then than that.
Which will factor into what happens in the store.
But yeah, just suddenly there,
just playing, no introduction, caught everybody off guard.
Stopping only to take a breath
and then sometimes look at us and make faces like,
yeah, it's me, no big deal, sorry.
I don't mean to put you out, hey, I'm just glad you're here.
And that's the vibe through the whole thing
is this very like, just casual like,
and he'll just like stop and just chat for a long time,
tell you about stuff on his mind,
music education he'll talk about for a while,
just to keep going with innovation though.
Here's the main, let me just drive right to it.
The main thing I wanted to talk about,
something I've never seen in a concert before,
he did a raffle.
It was a raffle as if like a high school fundraiser.
Church carnival.
Yes, yeah.
Just suddenly midway through the show,
all right, everybody, tickets out, let's do the drawing.
All right, who do we have?
30B and then everybody's gotta like go fishing
for the tickets.
Like, what is it, what do you mean?
And we'd never heard about the raffle.
We got in kind of right before it started.
So like raffle and for what?
Raffle, it goes to somebody up in the balcony
and he's like, okay, get down here quick.
And then they're like shuffling around
and taking their time.
And then he gets impatient with how long it's taking them
to come down from the balcony,
which is like, well then why did you do a raffle
if you knew it was possible for people up in the balcony
to get it and they don't know the venue,
they don't know where the exit doors are and everything.
So then he's got a vamp and he just complains
about how long it's taking.
And then it's the winner of the raffle
is a seven-year-old girl who clearly has no idea
who he is brought there by the dad,
who's also there, who's really enraptured,
but the girl is pretty bored, but trying to be polite
as she is sac serenaded by him two inches from her face.
And I'm like, was that the prize?
I guess that must be the prize,
is getting like a personal, like a little romantic moment,
even though it's going to a seven-year-old girl,
which made it very strange.
But then no, the prize is a saxophone.
You win a saxophone.
A normal saxophone or a straightened saxophone?
The straightened saxophone, his style of saxophone,
which then on the way out the door,
there is a sign that says Kenny G Saxophones for sale,
$1,000.
Wow.
So you could go to the merch booth and get a t-shirt
or you could pay $1,000 and get one of his saxophones
made by him, made to his specifications.
Did you look this up?
Is it like- Oh no, I don't know.
You have to assume there's an online component, right?
Well, I would think so,
because like many different musicians have a deal
with like Fender or they have a deal with Gibson
and they have their own signature instruments.
Okay, sure.
Jimmy Chamberlain, I forget which,
I was just watching a Long Rick Beato interview
with Jimmy Chamberlain and he has a deal
with some drum company and they have like signature stuff.
I watched a Long Rick Beato video yesterday.
The Jimmy Chamberlain video is awesome, honestly.
He's really like a smart guy about drums
and I've learned a lot is what I'm saying.
But yes, this is a common thing with famous musicians.
Are you starting a drum career then?
Are you gonna buy some Chamberlain drums?
I'm an amateur drummer for a long time.
So yeah, maybe I buy some Jimmy Chamberlain.
He's a guy with a lot of drums though.
I'm not a big, like having.
Yeah, you better master the three.
10 cymbals or anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can't do that.
I need like two.
Like a crash and a ride.
Okay, sure. That's all I really need.
You don't need all the trickery that Jimmy Chamberlain does.
Yeah, no. Yeah, it's just kind of for show.
He's too smart.
But Kenny, okay, KennyGSaxophones.com.
I'm finding this in.
Oh, thank you for filling this in.
I'm so curious.
Okay, this looks like a fake website.
This doesn't look real.
This looks.
Wait, wait, when you turned it around,
I was like, are you showing me Google?
Because it's just mostly white.
Well, this is KennyGSaxophones.com.
It's mostly white.
It looks like I'm Googling KennyGSaxophones.
Yeah, it looks like Google Translate.
Right.
Mixed with Google Images.
Why is this website so bad?
That when I, in the concert,
the sign was just like a, just black on white,
just a paper sign.
Why isn't he dressing this up more?
Wow, he must be just doing this out of his house.
Okay, wait.
The main office is in Muncie, Indiana.
Uh-huh.
KennyGSaxophones are owned and sold worldwide
by ANK Global Enterprises, Inc.,
a California corporation.
Owners are KennyG and Ruben Allen,
managing partners of ANK.
Okay.
This is $3,895.
Copper Tenor Demo.
That's the price you're seeing is.
Well, let me see if there's a regular.
I don't know what they were selling for 1,000,
but that's a steal.
Maybe he's like, well, you paid for the concert,
so I should cut you a deal.
Perhaps.
But there's probably a range, I would imagine.
I'm just so curious why this,
I feel like any of us could easily redesign his website
in a matter of minutes.
Yeah, of course, it would be 10 minutes.
The soprano sax is the type of sax he plays
that's the straight sax.
Okay, yeah.
This is too grand, though.
Geez.
I didn't know what a deal,
and especially to get it for free.
What I don't understand is,
is that girl an aspiring saxophone player?
Did people only enter if they want to be saxophone players?
Did they not know what the raffle was for?
Probably that.
Yeah, probably that.
I mean, it was all disorganized enough,
yeah, that would be my guess.
So then is it like an opportunity to flip it?
Now you can go on eBay and say there's a reel,
and there's a picture of me getting it from him
so you know that it's reputable.
What's the plan here?
Why is there this?
Why does he stop a concert to do this?
Well, it's a little convenient,
isn't it, that a little girl gets the saxophone
after he's talking about music in schools?
Well, it wasn't right after,
though it was a big component of the concert.
Right, if it's a big component,
though isn't that a little too coincidental?
You think this is a plant?
I'm just saying, I brought up Copperfield,
so maybe that's why I have plants on the brain,
but that's pretty wild that a little girl wins a saxophone
after he's made a big point about music in schools.
What are the chances that a little girl
had a Kenny G concert in 2024?
And why is there a little girl
at a Kenny G concert in 2024, huh?
I don't know, I'm just saying it's a little convenient.
You've cracked all this apart for me.
I don't know what to think anymore.
It's a little convenient.
Well, and do you think that Kenny G
might be the kind of performer
who relies on weird little tricks and plants
to make sure that he gets all of the audience pops
that he needs?
Maybe, you were there, though, I wasn't there.
My favorite innovation, though,
something, you know, Mike, you're a big concert goer,
I think you're used to the performer
pumping up the audience and trying to make that energy last
and like, do we want more?
Do you want more?
In this case, he maybe was sensing
an audience energy lag,
and he said, everybody doing good?
Do you wanna keep going?
If you're not into it, if you're feeling like you wanna be,
just go ahead and take off, I really don't care.
Not gonna make fun of you or anything.
Just like, feel free, door's right there.
Hope I gave you a good time,
but if you're, look, it's Sunday night,
everybody's got a lot to do.
Tomorrow's a work day, you got a lot to do, right?
Just feel, go ahead, it's fine.
Like, what is, have you ever seen that before in a concert?
The same thing as like, in the middle of like,
the third encore at a Springsteen show,
where he's like, do you wanna go home?
And people go, no, like, it's technically the same sentiment.
It's just delivered in a much different way.
It's definitely like, designed to make people go,
no, I don't wanna go home, let's keep going here.
In this case, he answered the question for us.
He kind of, he just assumed, gave us an out,
which was nice, and then he just kinda kept talking
for a while, and he's like, I'm excited to get home,
because, you know, I live here, I live in LA,
so I get to go sleep in my own bed.
And I'm like, boy, I can count the times
that I've done a show, and then gotten to go home
and sleep in my own bed.
How many times have I, what have I gotta do?
Like, one, two, three, four, five, six,
maybe like 12, not more than 12 times,
definitely not more than 12 times.
Anyway, so, feel free to go.
What is this monologue?
It just cuts.
He's really off the top of his head, it feels like.
Yeah, like close to just like, you know,
well, let me see, if I get back, then like, I can,
before I left, I got that fancy goat cheese.
That's probably still good, so I could get back
and have a little bit of that.
And I got those crostinis, that'll be,
I think I teavote 60 minutes, so I can pull 60 minutes.
Just like inner monologue.
Then all of it culminates in, like, where does all this go?
How do you close out a wide-ranging, bizarre set like that?
Well, only one place, obviously,
which is My Heart Will Go On.
That's the big showstopper, which he starts,
do, do, do, and in three notes,
everybody loses their fucking shit, screaming,
now it's Springsteen Energy.
All of a sudden, do, do, My Heart Will Go On,
except for the person in front of us,
who, keep in mind, this is the fifth row,
she is holding up her phone at her own face height,
typing on her phone, using a little pen.
I'll tell you this, watching her typing
with a little stylus on your phone,
slows everything down.
It's much more inconvenient to do it that way.
And then I'm like, the font's big enough,
I can see what she's doing, what is she doing?
Just a big text exchange that's saying, like,
do you have Zell?
You ever heard of Zell?
Well, Zell is this new thing that you can do
through your bank, and it's a lot like Venmo,
where I'm reading this giant paragraph,
just explaining the basics of what Zell is,
which she's just doing in front of her face,
ignoring the concert that she's presumably
paying this person back for.
This scene was just so bizarre.
All this just to say, there's a little bit of crossover
in that I know he does the Epcot thing,
the eat to the beat.
I gotta tell listeners, go see what he,
because you don't know what you're gonna get.
You don't know if you're gonna get 10 minutes
of hotel recommendations or credit cards
you might consider using.
You don't know what genres of music,
if he'll just suddenly play the Jaws theme on the saxophone.
There's no way to predict what is gonna happen.
Maybe at eat to the beat, he keeps it really local.
He's like, I'm staying at the Boardwalk this time.
Stayed at the Yacht Club last year.
Think I'd like them both equally.
Or you know what he would do is just fish for the,
what's the one that's kind of like old seaside style,
turn of the century?
No, not Yacht Club, no.
Oh, Beach, oh, Boardwalk.
Yeah, Boardwalk, no, it's the Beach Boardwalk Hotel.
It's called the Beach Boardwalk Hotel.
We have to look up,
I'm sure there's plenty of YouTube of him doing these.
I think he does them a lot.
And what I heard from a friend of the show, Kevin Tully,
was he went to see this and he's like,
I've never seen a performer use the space more.
Nobody's walked more in any concert I've ever seen.
Nobody's gotten more steps.
Which I actually thought that the step count
was kind of low.
It was my only disappointment from the LA Live show.
So anyways, check him out.
Go freak the fuck out when he does My Heart Will Go On.
Okay, now that you've done that,
let me reveal that I do have Madame with me
and this is secretly the, no, I'm just kidding.
You had me for a second.
Yeah, I thought.
But I was like, that's a casual way to bring that out.
No, I want you to think of it as Chekhov's Madame.
Where like, I could bring out Madame at any time.
So I want everyone to be nervous
every time we record an episode.
I mean, I am.
I'm nervous about the name being said.
But I also just occupied a bunch of time
to talk about Kenny G. Sure.
So I say, if you have an interest
that you want to wedge into the show,
just come to the show with your wedge.
Just start doing it.
Carve out the space.
Oh, well, I would probably say that.
Do you know about Zell?
It's like Venmo, but it's run by the bank.
Tell me more.
Type me more.
Get out as a stylist and explain the full history of Zell.
I've got a stylist pen right here,
magnetically attached to my iPad.
Did you guys know also that Kenny G. claims credit
for denting the Frappuccino?
No.
He was an early Starbucks investor.
Really?
And he, enough to where he can easily contact Howard Schultz
was like, yeah, I kept calling him and saying like,
hey, I got this place Coffee Bean near me
and they got lines out the door.
They do these things that are a little more like milkshakes.
You might want to consider doing something like that.
And you hear that and you're like,
well, that's bullshit.
That's gotta be bullshit.
But apparently somebody reached out to Starbucks for comment
and they were like, hey, we love Kenny, an early investor.
He really helped us out.
And guess what?
Kenny G. did consult on the Frappuccino.
Thanks for everything, Kenny.
Wow.
So that's not bullshit.
That sounds more like Coffee Bean invented the Frappuccino.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Kenny G. invented the idea of stealing from Coffee Bean
and giving it to Starbucks.
Wow.
An innovator.
As I said, that was the case that I made.
A concert innovator, a coffee innovator.
Thanks, Kenny.
Thanks for a good time.
Thank you, Kenny.
So questions?
I have one right here.
Blair asks, if Mike Scott and Jason animatronics
were added to an existing ride, Johnny Depp style,
which ride would it be and where in it
would you want your animatronic placed?
Yeah, that's a very good question.
So in this universe, is it our universe
where most of the guests will be confused
or is it a world where they know who we are?
Here's what I'll say.
My answer is going to be that I'm gonna be tastefully placed
in a ride, not as a show piece.
You don't want the focus on you?
Well, it'll be so confusing to the audience, I suppose.
If Jason is sitting in a rocking chair
at the end of a ride in such a prominent way
like the Johnny Depp pirates in Disneyland,
that would be so good, but who is this guy?
I don't understand why he's here.
Now, pirates is a good answer in general
because we could be a pirate, no problem.
You could sneak in there easily, yeah.
Yeah, but it's not the number one place
I think I would want it to be.
Even though I've had some maybe gripes
about Rise of the Resistance,
I think you could put me in Rise of the Resistance.
Well, I know that you want your friends to be in there.
I do, of course.
And who's a better friend than yourself?
That's exactly right.
So at the very least, I would then say,
at least I'm on Rise of the Resistance.
So I think it would be between,
Finn and I would be kind of behind that crate
that you can kind of not see it,
but I would be more prominent maybe.
You could see me a little bit closer.
Great, yeah.
And I'm yelling to Finn,
Finn, come here, come closer or whatever.
I can't, I don't have a full body.
Right.
Be like, no, no, it's okay, don't worry about it.
And I guess I would have a Stormtrooper outfit on as well
like I was in disguise before this.
Sure.
Or we could have it where I'm hanging out
up on that bridge with Kylo and General Hux.
Yeah.
So I could be at one of the consoles or something.
So I could be in the Chekhov or Mr. Sulu,
my jumping franchise is here,
but the Sulu or Mr. Chekhov,
or Lieutenant Commander Data position on the bridge.
And then we could just add something
where I would turn around and go,
they're here, just a quick little thing.
Get them.
Get them, or oh, watch out, something like that.
Again, I don't wanna draw focus.
It shouldn't be about me.
You guys can answer however you want, but.
You'd rather just blend in.
You'd just rather have it be an Easter egg.
Right.
You could help plot justify.
You could say, the cannons are down, sir.
Oh yeah, the cannons are down again, maybe forever.
Some people already have disputed my assertion
that those cannons are down forever,
but I hope I'm wrong.
But they're down certainly today.
They're not working.
They would be impressive if they were working.
Did that guy talk more than Kylo?
We really stopped for a while to listen to that guy.
You could hear him, he's still talking.
Like the ride vehicle seemed like it was about to leave,
but then it kept coming back, like, oh, he's still going.
Yeah.
You would jerk forward.
Wait, a tiny bit more.
Can we go into Dexter Jetsters after this?
Can we go out for a space shake, Kylo?
If we could add a couple of things there,
maybe as people are pulling away,
so it's a little bit of an Easter egg,
and I would say something about a prequel character I like,
but you'd have to be sort of like an eagle-eared listener,
a theme park goer to really notice
that I've slipped in some sort of a little prequel reference
or talking about Zabolba or Team Toppa Galeys,
one of my favorite podracers.
So, yeah, I like-
Oh, your favorite.
It's that hard to choose a favorite podracer.
Juan Sandage, Team Toppa Galeys,
any of the famous podracers that are famous to me.
So I think that's where I would choose.
If there was an Avengers or X-Men ride with robots,
I would probably go right there, but there's not.
So throw me in Rise of the Resistance.
Sure, yeah.
You got a thought, Jason?
I do.
Well, my original thought,
and this is probably recency bias,
and obviously I haven't written Tiana's in Florida yet,
but I like how much,
so I don't wanna give my full thoughts
because I haven't written it,
but I like how many scenes there are
of fun-loving animals playing instruments.
So I think I'd like to be placed
like next to one of those guys.
Oh, sure.
Next to a big frog
or mixed in with the band.
Wait, so there's a band of animals
and then there's just a guy next to them?
Yeah, exactly.
That is the reaction I wanna produce.
You want people to be whizzing by and go,
wait, is that a human?
Get off, go like, oh, that drop was so cool.
Did you see the animatron?
Yeah.
Hey, was there a guy just in the middle of that?
It's like, yeah, I kinda saw that.
There was just a guy in there.
Are you, do you wanna be,
did you say you wanna be playing an instrument
or do you wanna be more like that little baby bear
on Country Bears where he's just kinda sitting?
Oh, either would be great.
Okay.
You know, I'm just happy to be there.
But you don't wanna be a critter.
You wanna just be a person.
I'll let the professionals make that decision.
I think you should just be a person.
I think I should just be a person.
Yeah.
My other answer,
kinda inspired by Mike talking about pirates,
Disneyland Pirates starts,
you kinda go through the bayou
and there's a little shack.
Oh, oh.
With an old timer sitting there,
sitting in a rocking chair.
I would like to be next to him,
also in a rocking chair.
Same outfit?
Yeah, same outfit.
And again, like provoking the same reaction
of just like, hey, was there a guy?
Yeah, but that fits a lot.
When you get off.
That fits really well though.
Does he have a friend now?
I think people would go,
oh yeah, that guy's always been there.
That seems right to me.
Yeah, that's his friend.
That's his friend or that's his son.
Too normal, you're saying?
No, I'm not saying it's wrong.
I'm just saying, certainly on Tiana's,
they're gonna go, well, why was that guy there?
But this version, they're gonna go,
oh, there's two guys in rocking chairs.
Oh yeah, I think that's always been there.
I'm pretty sure.
It's copacetic, yeah.
Yeah, that guy looks like he belongs here on the shack.
All right, so there's a little more of a blend in.
That's a more of a blend in.
Stand out or blend in.
Scott?
I think I thought of it.
This is awesome.
Maybe in the blend in territory
or the has this always been their territory.
Hall of Presidents.
You could sneak somebody into Hall of Presidents real easy.
And I, in fact, did this video a long time ago
where I dubbed over the president's announcement
and with all of these fake names.
And I'm like, all right, you put me in there.
Maybe, I don't think I'm powdered wig.
I think I'm one of the,
I feel like that 1800s zone of like
Rutherford B. Hayes, James Garfields,
where like, who are all these guys?
So give me a beard, actually, but have it be me.
I can't really grow a beard.
Not a big, thick president beard, definitely.
But make me a beard president and just all of a sudden,
between numbers 18 and 19, whatever,
just suddenly in there like Russell Trunk.
And then it keeps going to a regular one.
And then you just see who knows the presidents
in history enough to know that there was,
there a Russell Trunk?
I don't remember President Russell Trunk.
Maybe impeached?
Maybe was he, was he the one who died
cause he got sick?
Cause he did, he did a speech in the cold.
Maybe Russell Trunk was only president
for four days or something.
And then he got like kicked by a mule.
Ended up in a permanent coma.
And then you can't really let a guy in a perma coma
be the president for, you know,
you probably want to slide somebody else in there.
So is your animatronic then,
are you dressed in a powdered wig?
And like, is it an old?
No, I was saying, I think I'm an 1800s guy.
Cause that's where you can blend in president wise.
People, if you try to name the presidents,
you might get like seven through
before you start forgetting.
Who we had to order.
But that middle, it's that reconstruction post Lincoln zone.
The names don't stand out as much.
They all look exactly the same.
They all look like the angriest men who've ever lived.
So I think you could really easily slip in Russell Trunk.
Okay, that's good.
Yeah, so then yeah, hopefully you would record the dialogue.
Like little talk.
Not all of them, some of them just nod.
Guys, the vast, vast majority of them just nod.
What are you talking about?
No, I know you're right.
Let's think about that.
All right, and now for a solo.
Okay.
Harry Truman.
They, none of them talk.
But yeah, if you, I would take, I'd do like a, hey, hi.
Just a quick interjection.
What up?
Russell Trunk.
How's it hanging?
All right, well here's a good real quick.
The last question then.
What is sort of the thing that your robot does
when it's announced?
Because you know, they do sort of like,
they'll do a nod or they'll do certain things.
Most of them don't do anything like so flashy,
but you could do anything.
Would you do a little salute?
Would you do a little like okay symbol?
I mean, I guess that's a white supremacist thing,
so don't do that.
But, you know.
I'd love to represent drinking in it for myself
and for many of our great drinker presidents.
And I may be like holding the martini glass
kinda with all the fingers out, with pinky out.
Just do, if I could like keep it down to my side,
like there's a chair in front of me so you can't see it,
then I'd bring it up and just do a little like hello.
Like yeah, I'm still standing, but not for long.
Uh huh.
People would love that.
That's a little fun injected into there.
Maybe Russell Trunk, President Russell Trunk
died of liver failure.
He was the first president to drink himself to death.
He was, yeah.
So you all have big like red cheeks.
I buried him on the south lawn.
You have like big red cheeks or something too.
Yeah, that's fine.
You'll look like Foster Brooks.
Sure, then you'd see me from all the way,
you could put me all the way in the back and I'd still pop.
Okay, well that's good.
Those are good robots.
I got one.
Jeremy Ayala, please do a best theme park toilets episode.
I need to know where the good boys
like to take the kids to the pool.
We've talked about, I feel like it's been a contender
for being a Final Four is some kind of,
and I think Disneyland's the only one
that we could speak to with expertise.
And something that we encountered with this though
in the planning is that our experience
of what is a good Disneyland bathroom is limited
because the women's restroom is an entire other area.
And I think that we would need a female perspective
in order to properly cover this area.
And now we've all got significant others
who've been on the show.
I think it's maybe, I've also encountered,
it's felt a little weird to me to go like,
hey, you're a girl, come do the girl toilets with us.
It is a weird request,
even though we have many friends do the show.
It's like, do you wanna come on and talk about pooping?
That's a hard question.
I guess-
There might be somebody who is like
trying for this. I'm sure there's somebody
who wants to, but you can't, it's not a thing you DM.
I'm not DMing that to somebody.
We have to do it in a way where someone
is gonna have to hear this or hear us say it
on a different episode and have to volunteer.
It has to be somebody who wants to volunteer.
There has to be a little bit of like pre-chat
in order to get this to happen.
And they have to hear it in a non,
like not, I was gonna say, it's not gonna be aggressive,
but they have to hear it in a non-pointed way
where they're being asked directly.
They have to offer up that they wanna talk about that.
Yeah, yeah.
But I hope that you appreciate our inclusive perspective,
that we need the female perspective.
Right.
And only then can we talk about
where we like to poop and pee.
We've certainly talked about this, by the way.
I haven't answered, we have answers
and we've said it on the show, so it's not like-
This is another reason that it's,
I've held back from really pushing this
as a competition, as a final four brackets sort of topic,
because I don't like something
where there's an easy, handy winner.
Yeah.
And I think that you got it,
because I know everybody,
we've talked about it plenty of times before.
It's that little hidden enchanted tiki room bathroom,
or the McCarthy Circle bathrooms
where the doors go all the way to the bottom.
Floor, yeah.
And that's not gonna be an interesting competition,
unless you pull those out. We know the winner.
Maybe you gotta put in some kind of rules
in order to like, it can only be this kind of bathroom,
or that kind of bathroom that's more regular.
Yeah.
Like single stalls don't count or something.
Yeah, we could add, yes,
we could add or subtract things from the contest,
but yeah, as far as we've said that,
but yeah, there's a couple easy answers.
Let's take easy ones out.
If you're just putting like, kind of like,
basics, like, you know,
because there's some that are like, always bedlam, right?
And then others where, actually,
I tend to find that one is a little quieter,
and maybe I'll go out of my way to do that one.
Well, you go to like, Grand Californian,
and you go to one of those sort of,
it's like kind of outdoor.
Let's talk parks, though.
Yeah, specifically parks. I think you're in the park.
You gotta go now. Okay, it has to be in the park.
You wanna go before you get in line.
Yeah, let's do that. It has to be in the park.
Okay, yeah.
Let's take a little bit of fancy out of it.
Okay, okay.
Because I think, you know what I find is not too bad,
even though it's near Fantasyland,
I think that the Alice in Wonderland bathrooms,
which are kind of adjacent to Matterhorn,
are usually a little okay,
because I think it's not in the,
if you're in the thick of a land,
if it's bathrooms between lots of rides,
those are all gonna be mobbed.
But if it's out of the way,
then people might not know about them,
or they need to step away from the activity
to go over there.
Yeah, that's an odd path to take.
And it's got a lot of ledges and planters outside.
It's good areas for if you're with a party,
like, oh, I don't have to go, I'll just wait out here.
They got somewhere to go, yes, yeah.
They won't be avoiding strollers and people all the time.
Yeah, that's just one knee jerk,
but do you guys have any others?
I do.
Okay, this is a thing I've noted.
There's two reasons for it.
Back by, okay, Paradise Gardens Park
in California Adventure by the Pizza and Pasta place,
there is still a bathroom there
with elaborate tile work of Route 66 scenes,
which is interesting going like,
oh, it's still like this from 2001.
It's still very California themed.
Sometimes bathrooms are a little like pocket
where they have not done a full renovation,
or an old theme might remain.
But the other thing about that,
and it's a thing I noticed a lot at Islands of Adventure,
the bathrooms that have been there since the beginning,
the 1999 to 2001 period had massive bathrooms,
like tons in bedrooms,
tons of urinals and stalls and everything.
Compare that to the Avengers campus bathrooms,
which are barely open.
There's barely any toilets in there.
I'm not super familiar, is that true?
Huh, I guess I don't know it off the top of my head.
I don't know that I've gone there.
It's just a thing I noticed, like normal,
I guess Galaxy's Edge has pretty large restrooms,
but it was just a thing I noticed at Islands,
and this popped into my head at California Adventures once,
like man, the bathrooms are really big
at the start of the new century.
But not as much anymore.
But not as much anymore,
because they want to use all the space for other things.
Yeah, I guess when California Adventures are open,
so we gotta kill as much of the square footage as we can.
All right, everybody gets like 10 square feet to yourself.
Every stall is 10 square feet wide.
You know what, I kinda like the Galaxy's Edge bathroom,
the one near the Savvy's Workshop or the Robot Place.
I kinda like that one.
That's kind of open, it kind of feels big,
because a lot of the bathrooms I don't like at Disneyland,
they also are small, and they're kind of dark.
That one feels like you got a lot of room in there,
especially by the sink area,
and I like the theming of it too.
I don't like the other bathroom as much,
it's closer to like the plush and the rise of resistance.
Yeah, it's more cramped.
It's more cramped, but you do kind of get,
it's kind of, yeah, you got breathing room
in that bathroom.
Sure, sure.
And you aren't mad at the bathroom
because your friends aren't in it?
I'm mad at everywhere in Galaxy's Edge
because my friends aren't in it.
Everywhere there should be my friends.
I wanna be able to take a shit next to Luke.
That's easy, you don't need any sort of
visual representation of him.
We know that they've AI'd his voice,
they've got every soundbite that Mark Hamill's ever said,
now take those samples and make,
let me hear what it sounds like
when he's struggling with his shit.
You want the Jar Jar to be saying,
like the toilet paper's out over here,
can you help me out?
Yes, if we could have dialogue from the movie,
I mean, with Luke, you could probably just use
the same dialogue when he's making the Death Star run,
and it would probably line up perfectly.
I want Leia to have run out of toilet paper
and that she needs some from me,
and she says, help me, you're my only hope.
Sure, yeah.
Yes.
Well, where are the,
look, that's an easy way they could get the friends
in the Galaxy's Edge.
That's just audio, that's just dialogue.
You don't have to build a robot necessarily.
So they can start there.
They can start there with Dexter Jutster.
I don't like that Luke and Leia aren't,
are you sure they aren't in there?
Have you been to the toilets?
You can have Jango Fett just say,
help me out over here.
That's easy enough.
Yeah, it should be a collection of Sam Clitz
from the movie that would make sense
being said in a bathroom.
So not changed at all, yeah.
Not changed at all, no.
Right.
So like you have, like Obi-Wan say,
you have the higher ground or something,
like just placed in there,
and then I don't know if that makes a lot of sense.
What's the big Yoda inspirational,
there is no try?
Do or do not, there is no try.
I mean that's applicable to making a difficult ship.
Can you cut it where it's a quicker,
so it goes doo doo or not?
There is no, and then like.
I'll allow it.
Okay, because that's.
I think technology would allow that to happen, yeah.
Yeah, doo doo.
And then you could have,
oh you could have Greedo saying McClunky.
Like you could have like a noise
that he went to the bathroom,
and then he goes.
You could have Greedo saying McClunky.
Yeah.
Also something sorely lacking in the parks, yes.
No representation of McClunky.
Dylan Lee, he says you're put in charge of parks
and told you have to level one land,
example, adventure land, on each coast,
but you can replace it with any theme of your choosing
as long as it's not a revamped aversion of the old land.
This is a big one.
What do you choose and why?
So you got it.
Jason looks concerned here,
because we've, this is recently.
Oh no, I'm thinking.
We've been talking.
Recently we've been talking.
I've, of course, brought the missile launcher out.
Yeah, people seem to like the missile launcher.
People like.
You really like, you corner us with that possibility.
So this is, you know, I think,
I assume this is talking Disney
because we would be here all day
if we were doing the Universal Parks,
but maybe not, I don't know.
Because like we've already,
I've already pointed that missile launcher at Toon Lagoon
and Marvel Super Hero Island too many times.
I don't want to make Jason upset anymore.
Do you want to though make this a missile launcher thing?
Just put that on top?
Because you got to level the land somehow, so.
Yeah, well luckily we can get the missile launcher out.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you could just, if you could nuke the lands for us,
that'd be great.
But we have to decide, don't we?
Yes, you have to decide.
I mean, look, there's the easy answer
in California Adventure is Hollywood Land goes away.
Hollywood Land is the easiest one to get rid of.
And could be almost anything, huh?
And then it could be almost anything.
And like the thing is, again,
it's like I know what modern Disney does,
so they're going to just want to make a land
based on one of the things they own.
But if I'm in charge,
if I have the keys,
like what do I want more than anything?
And that answer,
and we've talked a little bit about this,
is some kind of elaborate candy land.
I want a land full of candy.
It doesn't have to be the board game candy, candy land,
but it needs to be like you're walking
into a modern version of like a Willy Wonka's
chocolate factory,
or like a Willy Wonka's like terraformed island
where he's growing all of his candy.
So just because Hollywood Land
is like my least favorite part,
and I'm talking about where Monsters Inc. is,
and I'm talking about where,
I like Turtle Talk with Crush,
and I like Monsters Inc. fine,
but that stuff is all,
it all feels tired to me.
The theater feels tired to me now
because it's nothing going on there.
That's why it's tired.
So it might not blend so well,
but I would like to put a candy land of some kind in here
with, and it doesn't have to be a big E ticket,
but I want like a dark ride where you go through like,
let's say like,
I mean, it's hard not to get to the Willy Wonka comparison,
but if you're like, say like gum,
like you're going to the gumdrop fairy,
and you're like taking gumdrops and bringing them back
because you have to package gumdrops
and give them all to the children.
Like I want like big suckers.
I want sort of-
You have to package gumdrops?
You have to package them,
but like let's make them a fantastical thing
where like you go to the center of the earth
to get gumdrops.
One of the crusts in the center of the earth.
Those are like gems that you mine.
Exactly, like the seven dwarfs.
That's a perfect example, yes.
Okay, you don't realize that all candy is not,
candy isn't manufactured and just artificial ingredients.
Candy has to be harvested from the center of the earth.
So some sort of drill machine that takes you down.
Some sort of candy-
To grab gumdrops.
Exactly, and then there's like a bad guy there
and he's trying to stop you
because he's trying to use gumdrops for like evil gumdrops.
Let's say that gumdrops could like also be like
fossil fuels if you burn them and they're bad or something.
He's trying to use them for like evil,
but we just want to give candy to the kids.
So we're in a little vehicle.
I don't know, I didn't say flush out the ride,
but here we are flushing out the ride
where you have to take the gumdrops back.
And then like all the kids are there.
So now there's going to be a lot of fun candy
they sell in this land as well.
That's going to be a big thing too.
I would hope.
There's going to be a lot of selling of candy
and then there'll be a sort of,
we can leave the theater there even
and have some sort of a big sort of candy review
with like dancing suckers and like different,
like people dressed as Laffy Taffy
and they have like long arms and stuff
and mostly original songs,
but there will be like,
we will do a little Candy Man, of course.
You will do the song Sweet Gingerbread Man.
We'll do all the different like sort of sweets based songs.
Of course you will do Sweet Gingerbread Man.
No need to explain what Sweet Gingerbread Man is.
Well, it's another song that Sammy Davis Jr. sings.
God, I had a feeling.
He does a cover of Candy Man.
That's how I knew.
He does a cover of Sweet Gingerbread Man.
The reason I know the song is because my mom,
Bobby Sherman does a cover or does a version of it
and this is how it got on my radar first.
This is your mom's insistence on making sure
that you, her son, likes Bobby Sherman.
It comes up once a week.
She warped you permanently.
Yeah, so I think a fun candy land
in that area would be awesome
and I'm happy to elaborate on it more.
This says both coasts.
I don't think we have time to do both coasts,
but if you gentlemen wanna go here.
Geez.
Okay, no, but it can't be a redo
because I was gonna say blow up Pixar Pier,
build a new Pixar land from scratch.
That can't work.
Wasn't that different though?
If none of it's a place.
Well, what's the land then?
Is it specific to a Pixar movie
or are you saying general Pixar?
No, it's not to a specific movie.
Okay, that's the same thing then.
E-Ticket, Toy Story, E-Ticket, Upper Wally.
I guess I really like Turning Red,
but I was gonna say I think they hit their high mark
with Up and Wally.
Yeah.
Oh, show.
Okay, so it sounds like that's not,
we can't do that.
Yeah, no, I can't do that.
I don't know, can't you?
Because those aren't there.
You wanna blow up the lagoon.
That's a move is to not have a lagoon anymore
and to fill in that space with rides.
Well, no, I want the lagoon.
I just meant the.
It sounds like he wants the exact same land
except he wants like a Wally ride.
I want it better.
I want it.
I think that's acceptable.
No, I'm ruling it's not.
Oh, okay.
I'm saying it's not.
I would want to actually, you know what I would,
I would wanna blow up Toy Story land in Hollywood studios
and then build like a real like,
not Toy Story, but again, my other interest is toys.
So if like we really went hard on like a generic
like you've shrunk down land, it's an indoor land
and you're like on the floor of a bedroom
or in a toy store on a shelf.
I don't want the Toy Story IP.
I want it to be sort of generic, you've shrunk down
and now we're all toys in this land.
You've gone to like the Don Draper.
Like what is the idea of toys?
What is the idea of candy?
Exactly.
So Scott, do you have an answer for this?
Well, all right.
I was gonna say it feels obvious
to blow up part of Tomorrowland,
but we've talked about that a lot.
And both coasts makes me go to Main Street USA.
What if there was no more Main Street USA?
But I don't have any.
I just wanted to see what Jason would do if I said that.
Well, the Hollywood studios upset him.
You're pouting like you had a sour sucker.
Yeah, for Mike's candy land.
You can out all sorts of suckers in my candy land.
What would be better than Main Street USA?
If you replaced, yeah, that's a good question.
I mean, it's like Islands of Adventure
has a Main Street USA.
They all kind of have Main Street.
That is sort of just like the template now
if you're doing a big park is to have a Main Street.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, look, Springfield's gonna be up for grabs.
Let's Springfield, wait a minute.
Now let's use, all right,
we're gonna turn Main Street into,
how do you say out loud where Family Guy takes place?
Quahog?
Cohog?
Cohog, yeah.
Cohogger.
I think everybody.
And you know what, just paint it,
don't even blow it up, just paint it cartoon colors
and then all of our pals are poking out the windows.
Yeah, Quagmire Mayor Adam West
is welcoming you to Disneyland.
That's good.
What have you?
I think no complaints there.
I think everybody's happy if,
I mean, sure, people like Main Street USA,
but people love Family Guy.
That's true, that's true.
It is surprising Family Guy's not somewhere.
And then daily performances of the theme song
outside the castle. Oh yeah, sure.
I was gonna say just replace Main Street USA
with like a ride to get into the park.
Sure.
No Main Street.
Well, you could do like kind of Seven Seas Lagoon,
like you gotta get on a big boat
just to take you from here to there.
Yeah. Yeah.
There was also, you know, there was this weird promotion
where they did like an Olympic-sized pool
all the way down Main Street.
Just do that all the time.
If you wanna get into the park, you gotta swim for it.
Yeah, that's good.
That's, yeah.
Get in the pool.
No, it's not heated.
Go.
More effort, yes.
That's what I think.
I have one here.
Cody Holmes says,
this is a comedy podcast about theme parks.
We hear a lot about your favorite theme things,
but what's some comedy you're really digging right now
you could turn us all on to?
I, well, certainly the John Bellini show
that you worked on, Scott.
Oh, thanks.
Connor O'Malley has a new special on YouTube
that is really funny.
Joe Pera is on tour right now.
My college classmate, Joe Pera, he's always very funny.
Oh, I know that.
And then we were talking the other day,
guys you worked with on the Bellini show,
Jeremy and Rajat, Jeremy Levick and Rajat Suresh
are so funny.
They make these very funny, very weird videos.
Oh, and they've done so,
I don't even describe some of these
because some of them are so odd,
even just explaining the premise.
They're some of the best in the DIY game.
Yeah.
I was gonna say the show Family Guy,
just wanna give them a show.
I was gonna say Family Guy 2.
Wow, wow, okay.
Nice.
The same thing, yeah.
It's been going for a little while.
Also, not to beat up on Mike for all his,
you know, old-timey references.
I've been watching a lot of episodes of,
Scott, do you know the show The Mothers-in-Law?
No.
Okay.
This is available.
This is beating up on me and all.
On a lot of streaming services.
This was a two-season TV show
that would air between Bonanza
and the Wonderful World of Disney.
It is produced and mostly directed by Desi Arnaz.
Whoa.
And it stars Eve Arden and Kay Ballard.
Of course.
And they, they, they're adult children,
they are neighbors who are kind of friends,
but also kind at each other's throats.
And they're adult children get married to each other,
so they become the mother-in-laws.
And it is a very funny, I think it's very funny,
it is so cheap.
It is like the cheapest late 60s crapped-out TV show.
One of the husband's changes at season two,
because they said the only way we'll renew this,
we renew this, is if everyone takes the same money
and the one actor was like, no.
So they just replaced him.
No.
And the daughter on the show,
Debra Wally, was in a lot of those Bikini Beach movies.
She's in an Elvis movie as Elvis's love and trust,
one of his movies.
And it's just, I just think it's just such an oddball show.
Desi, of course, makes cameos in it.
Of course, yeah.
I think he better.
If he's on the set, just go to the other side,
go in front of the cameras.
My daughter seems to like the song Cuban Pete,
I'll say that when I play that for her.
Oh, that's fun.
Haven't you learned anything
from your Bobby Sherman upbringing?
You're starting the cycle again.
I'm not forcing her to learn about him.
It's just coming up on random sometimes,
because that's what my algorithm knows I want.
That's what it plays for her sometimes.
We're taking our time with these questions.
These are great questions.
We got so many great questions that, in fact,
we're gonna split this batch
into a whole other PTR Post Office episode.
So if we didn't get to your question in this one,
we will get to it in the next one.
And if we don't get to it in that one,
it's gone forever.
It's toast, de-atomized.
So a lot of pressure's on in that other episode.
Nick Cherry says,
"'What's the one unbuilt, rumored ride, theme parkland
"'that never happened that you most wish
"'would have come to fruition?''
I mean, there's so many of that.
Westcott is the easy answer, I think.
Because when I think of Disney World,
we've talked Disney World versus Disneyland,
and really what I miss from Disney World the most
is World Showcase and Epcot Center,
and then the hotels, Disney World hotels,
and the bubble itself.
But Westcott, really, you're like,
oh, God, Westcott, really?
I think if I had to pick anything,
that would be the thing.
And that's never coming back,
and there's no way they'll ever do that,
I don't think.
I don't know that, I can't imagine it having worked,
but boy, I think a lot about what is Los Angeles like
if Port Disney is in the beach.
Oh, that's fascinating, yeah.
Because if that was anywhere close to Disney Sea,
and I don't think it would have been,
because I think budget cuts would have made sure
it was not as cool, but that's such a strange area.
And I, you know, when I've been there for, you know,
Shacktoberfest, and I imagine, like, yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's right, yeah.
Not coming back.
Oh, the Shack branding.
It's back to Dark Harbor.
Wow, is this the first product?
Shack's over, yeah.
It's not Shack this year.
But he does have an immersive experience in Vegas.
Oh, yes, you told us this not in an episode, correct?
Right, yeah.
Yeah, and what's the deal with that?
I forget already.
But it looks like you could just have brunch,
and then you go into a room with colors, so.
Well, so my future answer, not unbuilt,
but for, you know, what attraction I miss the most
will be when that goes under.
Yeah, yeah.
And then it'll be, so that's the answer in five years.
Shack's fun house.
Okay, okay.
If Long Beach had an extra Disneyland that felt like 1990
and was full of crystals and stuff,
and there wasn't California Adventure potentially,
maybe it's all, probably everything's worse.
I'd say everything's worse and less convenient,
and we're all, like, now the 710 is jammed
as we go to this theme park that's rusted away
and smells bad, because it's by the sea.
Yeah.
But still, even that, I just want to know.
What would it be like?
I also, I know we already talked Star Wars.
That Star Wars coaster that seemed impossible to build
haunts me a little bit.
With the different storyline.
With the, like, three different paths,
and you move up in the swamp with Yoda,
like, that almost feels like I made it up in my head.
That's like a dream that I had or something.
That's an answer is blow up Main Street,
so you gotta have the space to put that in.
Oh, God, yeah.
Sure.
I was gonna say the, I don't know where exactly
it was gonna go, somewhere in the Middle East,
but there was all that concept art from Marvel.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
With, like, Spider-Man and Green Goblin,
like, actual buildings.
Yeah, like, there was a, like, one of the pieces of art,
we've talked about this before,
had, like, Times Square in chaos
with, like, Doc Ock's tentacles coming out
of one of the buildings, and that felt closer,
that felt more like a, not realistic,
but it was not necessarily comic book,
but it split the difference between being,
sort of, realism with the movies.
Pop party, yeah.
Right, versus, like, it's either one way
where it's, like, all, like, comic book stuff
in Islands of Adventure, or now it's, like,
it needs to feel like a college campus
or, like, a circuit city to be real.
It's a repurposed office park factory.
Yeah, where it's, like, that actually,
that's a good way to, like, make a very impressive-looking,
like, exterior for a land involving superheroes.
Like, that feels right to me, those pictures.
So that would have been a satisfying way
to, like, make a cool thing where you're like,
oh my god, I'm in Times Square and there's shit going down.
Yeah, yeah.
So I agree with that.
I'm gonna toss this in just so that a funny word
gets said at the end.
Please, yeah.
This is from Gina Boliega.
This one is from Mike.
Did you ever hear of a Chuck E. Cheese-esque place
in the Chicago suburb, Libertyville, called Chimpies?
It had a Rock of Fire explosion band and everything.
Oh, wow, Chimpies.
No, I don't know Chimpies.
Chimpies.
I looked it up.
Chimpies does seem to, yeah, it is just literally Rock of Fire.
Right.
It's just the same band.
Chimpies Pizza Safari.
Wow.
Again, this year, we have found so many,
the lineup of animatronic bands has just expanded
and expanded.
I'm reading how it, all right, closed in 2005.
The show was in poor condition with the deteriorating
cuss words and mechanical issues.
And they just put like Safari outfits on them.
All right, same band, but they're wearing camouflage
and they're falling apart.
And Billy Bob's jaw might snap off.
I really wish I could see Chimpies.
I wish I knew Chimpies.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
She also said also you guys should
do an Ed DeBevix episode.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
I mean, that's, you know Ed DeBevix?
I forget the deal with it.
It's like Dick's Last Resort.
Yeah, they're mean to you.
Oh, OK.
They're mean to you.
We haven't really done any of these.
We haven't done one of the mean to you chains.
Yeah.
Requires some traveling.
We don't have a lot of those in Los Angeles
because we're nice to each other here.
Los Angeles is a place of love.
Dick's closed in San Diego, but it is still in Las Vegas.
It's in the Excalibur.
And they'll still like.
Yes, that awful looking face is peering out of a castle town.
I'll have a dilapidated castle town.
It's very unpleasant, Dick's Last Resort.
And up until maybe still in Las Vegas, I don't know,
the joke would just be like, hey, you're gay.
The joke oftentimes when you would go into Dick's Last
Resort was like, the mean waiter would call you gay.
And you're like, oh, OK.
It's 2015.
OK.
This is interesting.
So not in the comedy recommendations
is the recent material of Dick's Last Resort.
Is the wait staff at Dick's Last Resort, yeah.
OK, good.
Well, hey, thank you for all these.
We'll do another batch.
But for now, you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
Thanks for your questions.
And if you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
Also one more plug, The Mother's in Law, Two Seasons
is available on 2B, the Roku channel, and Zumo Play.
Yeah, I've been watching it on Zumo,
because then you see all the weird ads
for what else is on Zumo.
What is Zumo Play?
Zumo is a streaming app that is co-owned by like two
of the cable giants.
And I don't quite understand why.
Well, they'll own Disneyland soon enough.
They're going to buy.
The theme parks have been splintered off, sold to Zumo.
It's Zumo land now.
Yeah, it's Zumo time.
Zumo time.