It's the podcast the ride show with Jay Leno's acting career.
Tonight, Jay acts with Pamela Anderson, Walter Cronkite, Pat
Morita with Jason Eubanks and the podcast the ride show band.
That's right, Scott.
That's cold, huh?
All right.
And now Jay Leno's acting career, the topic on the
pocket story of the second gate.
Hey, isn't that nice to start with that?
You have to feel what they felt in famous studio one, let's say on the Burbank lot.
That's not one that sometimes, you know, the studio, like 8H, you know, we don't
know, nobody remembered, they didn't write down what studio they did it in.
Yeah.
Right by a major freeway exit for Burbank, you're heading to the Disney studios.
Are you concerned about sound bleed or freeway?
Yeah, that's good point.
You want to be near a freeway, I think, just for, you know, helps audience, you
know, and it's not a big, a big deal for them.
Carson did it too.
So, you know, they were used to it.
Near the Wiener Schnitzel across the street.
You have to think that like, I mean, Jay's going to get recognized too much if he
goes to their Wiener Schnitzel himself, but you know that he sent out for Wiener
Schnitzels.
Yeah.
Every other day when he wasn't eating a big boy, he ate Wiener Schnitzel for
sure.
Hot dogs, hamburgers.
That was a pretty good, that was Ed Hall.
Right?
That was Ed Hall.
I don't know if I was even trying to do Ed Hall because Ed Hall was, Ed Hall was
kind of generic.
Ed Hall was his announcer, not for all of it.
Right?
Well, it was John Melendez, of course.
Suddering John.
Of course.
You remember.
That's another, it's one of those, those, those Jay Leno things that there's like
all, maybe not all talk shows, but a lot of long running talk shows have kind of
like, you remember this about the band or the sidekick or the, you know, of course,
you know, you can think of Carson's theme, you could think of Ed McMahon, but then
like, yeah, where did Jay do it?
Where did, who was his announcer?
What did he sound like?
Jay Leno.
This kind of nothing.
What was the song like even?
Like if you had to hum the Leno theme, I mean that, what, what, what I just played
was like not anything.
Yeah.
I guess I could have maybe gotten there, but I, yeah, it's not as memorable, but
like Letterman, do I know?
Is that it?
Yeah, yeah, that's, yeah, yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
And then also like, did Leno never made Ed a character as much on the show?
I feel like.
Not really.
Yeah.
That's where he didn't seem to have a lot going on.
Cause like Conan's announcers all became characters or were Andy
eventually was the announcer.
Yeah.
Yes.
And then Letterman too.
But Joel Goddard, yeah, that kind of odd.
I mean, maybe not everybody knows.
I'm assuming, and not everyone out there is a late night with Conan O'Brien fan.
That's true.
But like, yeah, if you watched it, you know, you know, Weinberg and his weird
looks and you know, Joel Goddard and his weird looks.
Do you think that's why I wasn't like dating more in high school?
Cause I could go on and on about Max Weinberg and Joel Goddard bits.
Uh, no.
And trying to do it.
No, I don't think that's why.
Oh, it was the unpleasant sarcasm.
Okay, fine.
That was a subtly mean joke from Mike.
Like, no, I think the problems might've been deeper.
My problems were deeper than knowing Joel Goddard.
Yeah.
And doing the Joel like smile, like that big smile.
That big toothy weird.
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, it's just, I was just like some, there's gotta be some eligible girl at
this high school who also knows who these people are, uh, who could recognize
Brian McCann on site.
I don't know that there was a single girl in high school that did know that.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm selling them short.
Maybe that is really offensive to say, but I don't know.
I don't, I never met them.
I was friends with a lot of people, uh, like girl wise.
I was, I was friends with, I was kind of friends with everyone.
Yeah, of course.
So I don't know.
I don't know.
And yet that didn't help with the dating ultimately.
Not really.
Or he just took you for, he's friends with everyone.
Well, my beyond friends with anyone.
I'm sure my type used to be people who are not interested in me.
Yeah.
But my charm will surely win them over my charm and humor.
And, uh, yeah, the damage of the Disney movies have done of like, I just
have to work very hard to win this person who doesn't know who I am over.
Surely won't make me come off like a extra big weirdo.
Yeah.
Well, there was one girl at my high school who I knew, and I knew that she
knew kids in the hall and the Christopher guest movies and things that were
important to me, and I just bided my time.
And after a while I married her.
So that did work.
It's already in the long run.
Yes.
We were not to be clear.
I don't know if the audience knows that Aaron and I went to high school together,
but we were not dating then, but.
Right.
It was like a 10 year plan.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It didn't even occur to me then admit it, but like, but I was like, wait,
whoa, there is a girl who knows these things.
So yeah, patience is the name of the game, I guess.
But we're not here to talk about the greatest comedy.
We're here to talk about Jay Leno and specifically his acting career.
Now we're using kind of that McGruff naming mechanism, but to say that he
had a full acting career is not necessarily accurate.
I mean, look, he's acted in more things than a lot of people.
Uh, uh, no offense to you guys, you know, professional actors.
He does have more credits acting.
He has so many more credits.
And that's just, that's after a long time.
And that's his celebrity, but this is an unfair comparison.
I don't know why I brought you in.
Now that now who's being mean.
Yeah, sure.
I don't act as much as the host of the tonight show and the Jay Leno show
with his green card challenge.
He's famous for the bits, the green card challenge.
Of course they're going to want him on other shows.
The acting comes from, from other things, obviously, and you want Jay
Leno cameos and things and all of that.
Most of the acting is concurrent to his standup work and his talk show work.
I have a broader theory to say as we sort of head into the Leno territory.
And that is this talk show hosts acting is generally very strange.
Oh yeah.
Someone who you mainly know as a talk show host being in a movie or a show as
themselves, it's a little weird as not themselves.
It's extremely weird.
It's sort of akin to seeing a polar bear in the rain forest.
You're like, it's an animal and animals are in the forest, right?
Well, not that kind of animal and not that kind of forest.
There's just something about it that doesn't square.
And that's, I think the broader, interesting area of this to me.
I see.
Well, for talk shows hosts specifically, I always think that when, like, there's a
different vibe about their fake talk show in the universe or in like, or the real
talk show, like if Jimmy Fallon's doing a tonight show in a movie or a TV show,
he's acting a little different than regular Jimmy Fallon in the same way with
all of them, because a movie, a TV show is different than late night.
And there's a, there's a uptightness about it.
It's hard to recreate like what your show is like, like, for example, something
that happened when I worked at Conan, it was a little off when Conan did a live
interview with the billionaire character that Michael Caine plays in Now You See
Me from the monologue spot.
I think what might've been weird, cause I, you know, look, I worked there.
I saw every episode of the show and I don't remember on the real show him ever
being at not the desk, but rather the monologue mark and doing a live interview
with a not terribly famous billionaire who is on a plane as the interview is
occurring. Look this up if you haven't seen.
Now I feel shame as in Now You See Me head that I have not seen this segment.
It's in the film.
You don't recall Conan O'Brien's appearance in Now You See Me?
Uh, it's coming to me.
And this, I'm more of a Now You See Me 2 guy, I think.
Yeah, maybe me too.
Uh, I think, well, that, that says less about you and more about kind of the
stickiness of Now You See Me.
And I believe, wait, Arthur Tressler is the name.
Uh, we go now to Arthur Tressler in his private plane.
Now, what do you have to say about the four horsemen and Conan not making any
jokes? It is often a very strange thing that is the people that talk show hosts
are called upon to do, but I'm even more thinking and what I want to focus on
with Leno is the rare bird, which is the appearance as a character, as not
yourself. And I think a lot of what we'll talk about is him as Jay, as Jay.
However, just if you think about, you compare this to other prominent talk
show hosts. Johnny Carson did not ever, as far as I know, Letterman pretty much
did not.
Other than the Simpsons.
Oh yeah, true.
Cabin Boy.
Yeah, Letterman did in Cabin Boy.
And in that, now see, I think that a lot of the reason you don't see a lot of
talk show hosts as characters in movies is because it takes you out of it.
Right.
And in Cabin Boy, I feel like that the point is to be taken way out of it.
Yeah.
I mean, he's playing like a mean weirdo.
Like he.
Yes.
Oh, you're a fancy boy, huh?
You're one of those fancy boys.
Like boy.
Oh boy.
Do I hate those fancy boys?
I really like that.
Yeah, it's funny, but it's such a weird movie.
It makes sense that there's like suddenly David Letterman being a big weirdo.
You want to buy a monkey.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
And it's, and that's like, he's doing it because he has, he trusts, he trusts his
old collaborator, Chris Elliott, that this will be a non-shame worthy movie that
people will talk about in glorious terms for, I mean, I know they do now, but it
was kind of a notorious bomb at the time.
Andy Richter talk show sidekick is in that film pre Conan.
Um, I think the talk show stigma in terms of crossover is so strange that when he
left Conan in the nineties to be an actor, him being a real actor, I think he
encountered a lot of people saying, what are you talking about?
Right.
That's like a monkey coming in and saying he wants to be an actor.
I think like everybody put like a sidekick is going to be in this.
Why?
As a novelty and he had to get over and like convince people, no, that is a
job that happened to me.
I didn't go to some sidekick school.
I am an actor and I, and then he was very good in a number of things.
Um, it's just, it's, it's a weird area in general.
Then you take like Conan and Kimmel into it and they will appear as themselves
in things, but mainly in a way of like, it's me, the talk show host in a suit.
And I have walked into a place that the talk show host is not supposed to be in.
And then that's kind of like, if the president or an astronaut comes into a
scene and the host gives you like, I'm sorry, the suit gives you like removal.
Like, okay, I've, this is happening because it's weird, right?
It's, it's just weird in general is what I'm saying.
Yeah, it's, it's weird in general.
I feel the same way about like, sort of when they do a newscast and it's like
generally fake newscasts are weird, but then when they have real people doing it,
like Wolf Blitz, I guess Wolf Blitz or Mission Impossible.
I kind of like, but
a lot of other things, but other things I don't, I'm like, it's weird that this is
Wolf, why is he even doing it?
Shouldn't he be busy with the news?
He doesn't have time to be in Mission Impossible.
And then if it's a fake newscast, I go, well, I've never seen this person before.
This is fake.
And then it's same sort of same thing with talk show hosts, where if it's a fake
talk show host, you go, well, this isn't how a talk show host is.
It doesn't feel like a talk show at all.
I know what talk shows feel like.
They didn't do it.
Right.
And then Jay is on and I go, well, this is weird too.
This is not how he is on his show.
Like, it's an oddness.
Sometimes I think they're able to create the vibe of like, because you got to,
I always wonder about the mechanics of it.
Like, how do they get these done?
Is it like, they got to slot it in between, like, we've just done the real
monologue and then like, hey, does everybody want to help us out?
We're doing a little bit of a movie.
I'm going to be an old part of wag the dog.
And then they kind of like keep the energy up.
And that's what you need.
If you can tell that the audience isn't there or the band isn't there, that kind
of thing is what makes it start to feel strange.
Right.
But there is some spontaneity on talk shows that is impossible almost to
recreate unless it's like, I guess Larry Sanders, but that's its own universe
they've created and established tones for both versions, like when they're on
air and when they're off.
Well, Larry Sanders and Curb, like a lot of these guys show up as
themselves on Curb Your Enthusiasm.
Oh, that's true.
Yes.
And I don't only like it.
I will say, because now you say that I'm flashing to Leno and Letterman and
anyone else appearing on Sanders and that works pretty well.
I think they knew how to because Sanders is so rooted in reality and, you know,
probably setting up a little situation where they don't get all hammy because
to bring it back to Leno, what I think is fascinating about this and this topic
that we've chosen is that for somebody who cannot act, he does a lot.
There's a lot more of this, I think, than anybody else that I just listed.
Did he ever say no to one of these?
God.
Well, there's no way to know.
I mean, I bet if it was like cake and you got to be naked, or you got to be
naked, I guess, but maybe if we do a body suit or something, that could be.
Um, he even like, he puts this, what I also find fascinating is he kind of
puts down his acting in general.
Uh, but yet he has been acting in things that aren't the tonight show.
Anytime anyone asks.
Yes.
Yeah.
So you always made the time.
I mean, this is a classic thing with Jay, which is it Jay?
Like, which, which actually is it?
I think he kind of likes doing it is my point.
Maybe.
I think he likes that because I think, you know, what you see him do is kind of
like, yeah, it's a lot of like, it's the jerky head and move kind of the, it's
almost like the stuff you do when you do a Jay Leno impression, he does
himself when he's at, he becomes like kind of a five to 10% plus up Leno.
So I think he likes, it's very like, it's like having a parent at it's like a dad
acting, he gets a little bit, I've directed my parents several times and I
know that the key is do less.
All right, dad do way less because you think like time to act and then you
like, do a little adjustment.
Yeah.
Well, now I have to flip a switch and I'm acting now.
That's still a thing.
Sometimes I have to say, like, you don't have to do very much if you're act
because it definitely feels like, okay, now I'm going to turn into a mutant and
I will act like, that's really what happened.
Like my eyebrows go weird.
I start to like, there was like, I just feel like you were like, I have to push
this, I have to push through the camera.
So people know I'm doing things.
It's like, that is not how it works.
Oh, yeah.
Well, acting training for like a live performance, like theatrical, often
you're playing to the back row.
So when you start doing it on camera, they're like, there is a microphone
above you, tamp it, tamp it down, you know, stop yelling.
Jay is yelling a lot.
Jay reminds me of Seinfeld acting just because it's like, oh, that's the
persona they honed on stage and he's just doing it on camera with his like,
whatever.
And it's like, he's a little bit removed from the situation with Jay more than
Jerry probably.
He got into the groove and also, and Jerry was constantly surrounded by three
fantastic actors, which helped, like he was, you know, couldn't help, but pick
up a certain amount, which he brings, which he, I think he really takes into
the smash hit feature film Unfrosted.
Sure.
Well, when I see it, I will, yes, I assume I'm going to agree.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I wish I was you with it still ahead of me.
I wish that I had this present to open.
You have Christmas ahead and I don't.
Okay, good, good.
Christmas is in my past.
I like Christmas.
One of the things I feel like with Leno is that in some of the stuff I saw, he's
delivering every line like it's like a standout punchline or setup.
And it's like, Jay, some lines in films just need to be lined, like some just
need to move things along.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, and you're right.
And that would be a great direction to give, but almost like if somebody told
him that would have any impact on anything that's going on, you know, I
don't think he wants more acting work.
I think the acting work just comes, even if he doesn't ask for it and he's
never terribly adjusted what he does.
And does he need to?
I don't know.
It's at least kept it to where it's all like interesting and dumb and funny
enough that we want to talk about it here, which I guess we're going to do.
I'm going to start going into some specific things.
Sure.
Yeah.
And maybe a good place to start is just that he, as I said, a lot of his acting
credits are him doing like monologue jokes in movies.
It's a good way to show that there are big stakes to the events of the film,
that what is happening has gotten famous enough that it can be
commented on by America's host.
Yes.
He did this in many things.
He did it on JAG.
He did it on DAG.
He did it in WAG, the dog, all sort of, all a variety of projects.
And then like, you know, anything about the president.
I feel like it, I think in Dave.
I was going to say, yeah, President Johnson's in hot water again.
This is what I wish I knew a little better.
I wish I could have, because I love fake movie presidents.
So I would love to like compile every time he talked about a fake movie president.
But sometimes the events of the, of the show or film require a little bit of
magical realism in order to get him in there.
And that's what I found in this clip, which I will play from the NBC soap
opera Passions, this one jumped out at me.
I remember that, you know, soap operas were on a lot of my house and my mom
watched days of our lives and that would, I think, run into Passions, which she had
no interest in, and I would just peripherally catch it and go like, so
there's like a witch and a doll boy.
The hell is this show?
Like it's that, that's a, that has some like weird shit in it, right?
Maybe we should watch Passions.
There's some supernatural stuff in Passions.
Cause my mom didn't care about Passions either.
I think there was, I think, but it was probably a certain mom, type of mom who
liked that supernatural stuff in the soap opera, but I wonder if Passions isn't
like good or at least interesting.
There's gotta be.
I know that, I assume that you could like to mention a talk show bit.
You could Walker, Texas Ranger, Lever, some out of context.
Yeah.
Or somebody out there just, there's a lot, there's all these out of context,
such and such accounts.
I'd love to see an out of context Passions.
If there is, I just haven't looked it up.
But anyway, this, this might be worth going in there.
I don't know what's going on with the Passions crew, but maybe
the scene will explain itself.
These so-called friends of mine are probably gloating over this, but
they're laughing at me right now.
The next thing you know, Jay Leno will be making fun of me on the tonight show.
Who wants to marry a multi-millionaire is back in the news.
Let's see, as socialized at Gwen Hoshkiss and social climate, Theresa
Lopez, Fitzgerald duke it out over rich boy, Ethan Crane of Harmony.
Boy, this sounds like a soap opera, doesn't it?
Anyway, when he's in shock, you see that Ethan called off their wedding.
After admitting he does have kind of the hots for, for Teresa, you see.
And Gwen, by the way, as you probably know, the winner of this year's, how
could you not see it coming award?
Hello.
I'm sorry, Gwen.
I'm not laughing at you.
I know you're hurting.
That was a little bit, that was a little bit like Chris Pratt trying to remember
the names of the Epcot center.
Things he loved as a kid on the guardians coaster.
Yeah.
Theresa Hawkins and the, uh, the veggie veggie fruit fruit.
Oh man.
It's so good.
So that was her imagining a little.
Yeah.
For the listener, this is kind of a fade.
You do a classic soap opera look, and then you fade into her imagining a
Jay Leno show that's talking about presumably her.
I would have to think that was a big complicated list of names.
You got to give them credit as a broadcaster.
Um, I think the only thing that's weird about it to your point, Mike, that these
things often feel weird is just like when in a talk show joke where there's
an economy of words, do you, is this, does the setup require three sentences
of soap opera style?
Who's who?
There's always something wrong in all these clips.
There's always something that you go, well, that's not right for this.
And you're right.
Yes.
The setup, why is Jay doing this long set up the events of passions?
I do really like that.
Then it shows, it does look, it does, it provides stakes within the world.
I think even the whole world is laughing at me or could be laughing
at me if this wasn't a fantasy.
Um, a lot of, I think there's a lot of this, I believe passions filmed like on
that, uh, Burbank lot next door near, uh, so, so that's pretty, you know, there's
a lot of like helping out the fellow NBC properties.
I'm in the family, you know, we all help each other out and that's how it works.
How did you, they're my family.
I can't anticipate them doing anything bad to me, uh, you know, way in the future.
Like, how did you get to Jay without the agent and manager to do a guest
spotting is calling the producer of the show?
Yeah, maybe.
Call tonight show probably.
Should we slot this in?
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, um, yes, or just like walk up to him in the parking lot.
Right.
Probably.
They know where he is.
Um, but so that's kind of an example of the norm, although that's a strange
set of things he's talking about, but I think where I started clocking that
it's funny when he's in things is, uh, the Flintstones movie from 94.
I don't have a clip of this.
It's not that worth playing, but Fred Flintstone is on the lamb for an
embezzling scandal and he is ducking around the streets of bedrock and there's
a TV in the store in a store window, um, that's playing the show bed rocks most
wanted and that's hosted by Jay Leno, who unfortunately I don't think gets
a rockified character name.
Uh, but you get to see him in a sleeveless caveman shirt, which is fun and
very natural because I think he has kind of a caveman sort of body and diet.
Maybe not diet because they ate a lot of like raw meat and he
eats the most processed meat.
It's possible that, yeah, no, I don't think Jay eats like big boy raw.
The big boy burger is raw.
Yeah, that is a great question though.
What does he, does he try to get them well done or does he go medium well?
He seems like a well done to me.
You think so?
Yeah.
Trump style.
Yeah, you might be right.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a good question though.
Maybe we could, we'll find the answer to that somewhere.
Whatever gives it the least taste.
I think he's not after taste.
I think he, he doesn't even want to be like, I don't, you know, eating's just
stuff that I do to give me energy to go do stand-up.
If I could, if I could take a pill, never eat again.
Um, that, so that's all interesting.
Also provokes the question of like, you know, they're, I think they're pretty
clever in the Flintstones of like, how do they, all right, the bird is the record
player in the phone or whatever the TV.
They're like, I don't know.
It's TV.
It's crystals.
Crystals make it so the cavemen have TVs.
Right.
Do you buy that?
Crystals.
They didn't have crystals.
Why didn't they use crystals for everything?
Why don't, why don't they have computers and internet?
I don't know, man.
We have to have to, story means we have to have to be, it is black and white though.
Let's be clear where this isn't crazy.
It's not sci-fi.
We don't cavemen didn't have color TV.
It's not as wild as passions.
There's logic to this.
Yeah.
We don't want to be some off the rails passions type production.
There's, there's a rhyme or reason.
Passions was on for nine seasons.
Geez.
Wow.
Which is, and that's an episode every day.
Daily show.
Yeah.
So that's a tall order to do.
We're going to have to, you know, a separate podcast.
Yeah, I think so.
A daily podcast, but a separate one.
Anyway, that is one of Jay's filmed products that have the participation of
Steven Spielberg, John Goodman and dinosaurs because the main one, and I
think what maybe spurred this episode idea a little while ago was his
participation in the film.
We're back and dinosaurs story, which I Jason style, uh, borrowed from the
library last night, very smart.
It's not really streaming besides rental.
It's a rent.
Yeah.
And do I want to, yeah, do I want to pay the three 99 to just flip through?
Uh, we're back.
And with, with apologies, look, this was down to the wire.
I had to do what I could.
I didn't, if you're a fan of this film in general, I didn't really breathe it all in.
I kind of focused on his character.
VORB.
Yeah.
Not a lot of VORB clips online.
I was looking for, if you just look up VORB, it doesn't come up.
Well, there is one though, uh, which I will play, which does give us a pretty
good sense of the, I've always been interested in this movie, not clearly
not enough to watch it, but I, you know, I remember it being an early clocking
of like, so there's non Disney movies.
Okay.
And it seems like there's cartoon movies that are less popular at school
than the ones that I think about all the time.
It doesn't seem like any kid is wearing a We're Back shirt.
Um, so this was in 93 and it was like a, not a fiasco, but it was not like, and
maybe like a little bit well regarded if you like kind of that era of, you know,
the post American tale kind of stuff, you know, great hand drawn animation in it,
but it also looks a little wonky, which maybe you can see the writing on the wall
of like needing to switch computer.
Right.
Um, so, uh, here's the context of this scene.
Um, we meet Rex, John Goodman's T-Rex character, and he, when we meet him, he
is golfing and talking, which establishes a reality in which dinosaurs golf and
talk, and you might wonder, how did we get to this point?
And the answer is, then you, then you flash back and you see a like feral
version of, you know, like a regular dinosaur version of Rex.
He looks scarier.
He's not talking.
He's roaring.
He's chasing after some prey until a steampunky airship arrives and it glows
with light and then out of it comes a weird little alien with a propeller on
his head who's after our hearts because he talks in a very familiar voice.
Um, so here's out of the airship and then maybe the rest of the
scene, uh, explains itself.
Here's Vorb.
That gives you an idea, uh, doing a voice and this, this is kind of the thing about
it for somebody who I think has what my guess would be that he doesn't have a
lot of range.
That's kind of a, it's pretty good.
Yeah.
He kind of gets there.
That's a, that's a little bit of a, hey, puts it on and like, I, you know what?
I've, if I think let's assess this all at the end and maybe pick a favorite
performance, but I think Vorb is going to be the one to beat because he sort of
does, but this might be his only true character, right?
Well, he, he does more voice acting.
He is, he does.
I mean, I have a little more about we're back, but we, but, but, uh,
the, the context here, by the way, is that he, uh, uh, he offers the, this
dinosaur brain grain cereal, which is something that, that I guess makes you
smart.
He lures him into the spaceship in a kind of grotesque scene, force feeds a
bunch of cereal into his mouth.
Uh, and then after which immediately he like pops a little bit and then becomes
a fun cartoon dinosaur.
Um, so now he can talk and stuff.
And then you meet some other smart dinosaurs and then you meet Vorb's boss,
professor new eyes.
Has anyone seen this movie?
No, this is all, it was pretty good.
Actually, I might encourage at least watching what, what I watched.
Uh, so you get to see a little interaction with his boss, uh, uh, I'm
sorry, captain, captain new eyes, uh, as voiced by Walter Cronkite.
And this is what I think we were noting when this came up before is that the
cast is all broadcasters.
Julia child also appears in this.
Um, so Leno works with Cronkite.
Uh, at some point he comes out and he's like a folksy guy and he said, like,
just a kindly grandpa fella.
And at some point he says, Hey, Vorb.
And he says, that's the truth.
Skipper classic, uh, new eyes.
Vorb interplay.
And then he explains his deal, which is, uh, you know, after all the
money I made on brain grain, uh, now I travel the world and through time to
make a few wishes come true.
And that's why I use this.
It's a wish radio.
This is a lot more complicated than what I knew about the movie.
Yeah.
When you heard the title, we're back.
Do you have any guesses as to why they're back?
Um, uh, it could be time travel or eggs hatching in central park and they're
just trying to figure out New York city.
That's what I thought the movie was.
Yeah.
I didn't know there was kind of like steampunk and inventor and he kind of,
you're getting passed a lot.
The main thing he tells you is that he made a lot of money on this smart guy
cereal, but then the fact that he invented time travel is just kind of
glossed over as just part of the new wise deal.
Don't worry about it.
We are on the way to wish radio.
That's the main thing.
Uh, so then he plays messages from his wish radio, which indicate that a lot
of kids wish that they could see dinosaurs.
Uh, Oh wait with it.
I can hear what young people are wishing for, especially young people
because they wish the loudest.
Oh, my kid, he learned how to wish.
He's keeping me up every night with his loud wishes.
I guess maybe audibly loud adults wish.
Maybe I would argue adults sometimes wish harder, but in a quiet way, silently
in your head.
Yeah.
And to prayers count as wishes.
Do you hear prayers or does this, does the wish radio filter it out?
You got prayers go to God, wishes go to professor new eyes.
Sorry, captain new wise.
I'll explain why I'm getting mixed up.
Uh, so that, that info dump happens and then like, so you're going to earth in
1993.
Here you go.
When you get there, there's two people to look for.
One is Dr.
Bleeve.
She's very nice.
That's Julia child.
The other is professor screw eyes.
He's my brother.
He is cruel and insane.
It's really sells out his own brother.
No love lost from the, who seems like a very kindly man.
He was, he will absolutely, he will tell the, the, uh, God honest, brutal
truth about his brother.
Wow.
Um, so this is, I mean, this is a
really intriguing.
I just honestly didn't have time.
I still have it, uh, from the library.
So do I finish it?
Uh, I've looked, probably still not, but, uh, if you're interested or, you
know, now, you know, check it out from the library, it did make the
DVD cut on like, uh, Boris and Natasha.
Oh, right, right, right.
No, I saw it to come.
I saw it to watch that.
You really, you really do.
This is your yellow stone.
It is, it is right under the TV next to my copy of the
La Nuba DVD I bought.
Oh, wait, you do.
Wow.
You have both of those.
I did.
Yeah.
I bought both of those.
They were both about, uh, $4, $4 or $5.
Well, obviously you have to prioritize.
La Nuba is the most important piece.
Well, that I watched a rip of.
There is a full rip of it, but I had to see those special features.
Uh, hi, Hey, Hey, uh, love the new, but check out La Nuba.
Um, uh, anyway, then they show up at the Macy's parade and they, uh, walk
around and stomp on a bunch of dinosaur balloons and they deflate them.
Which is ironic because ultimately, uh, Rex was a Macy's balloon that
did deflate, uh, during the parade.
Uh, so that's the story of VORB.
Uh, um, the, the, and you're right that this is like part of a very
fruitful, uh, voiceover career.
This is actually, that might almost be the most, there's a lot of Leno voiceover.
Yeah.
I, the main one I was thinking of, and I remember kind of watching it at the
time was fairly odd parents.
He is the crimson shin and the villain naked shin.
Uh, he's both, I think he's credited as both that I saw that required.
Now I'm not, I haven't watched any of this admittedly.
I, I'd be curious about the duality and whether he can pull off one of the most
difficult acting challenges there is, you know, there wasn't the same actor playing
captain new eyes and professor screw eyes.
So to put that all in one, one actor like Leno, that's a lot.
Mike, have you confronted Lindsay about is the crimson chin coming back?
Have we had discussions about that?
We had discussed discussions about it.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'm ready to say anything, you know, I will say Jim
Cummings though, did do dark wing duck and naked ducks voice.
You might say he's more accomplished voice actor than Jay, but yeah, yeah,
more, you know, a little more prominent ones, but you know, Leno was also busy.
This might've been his direction if he wasn't busy with a nightly show and
250 standup dates a year.
Yes.
Yeah.
And constant and like, and zero time between show taping and getting on a
private plane to go to Duluth.
Right.
So anyways, uh, the, yeah, uh, uh, now he's, he's in the Disney family enough
that there's a Disney, he's on Disney Wiki.
There's a lot of Disney stuff to, to, to bring up.
Uh, uh, he's Billy Beagle on Mickey and the roadster racers.
Um, so your child might love Billy Beagle and therefore the voice of Jay.
Um, I don't have a lot of, I don't really have anything on Billy B.
That's a lot to go through.
Yeah.
Um, but you know, they made him a car guy, which is a common thing.
I think here you'll see that a lot where he gets to mess around with cars on screen.
Seems to be a big way to get him.
That's how they got him on Titus.
Yes.
Sorry to disappoint everyone.
I don't have a clip of his appearance on Titus.
Well, Jason was telling me about his last man standing work.
Oh, yes.
And yeah, I have seen that last man standing the Tim Allen show.
I feel like I need to explain what it is, even though that was a nine season.
Right.
Unbelievably popular and successful show that actually, you know, it's
funny, uh, that he's like, he owns like a big old outdoor store.
And in the establishing shot, it's clearly a doctored Bass Pro shops.
Right.
Yeah.
So I like it.
I'm sure I would like it.
Uh, what does he do on, on the last man standing?
He's not playing Jay.
Oh, there you go.
But he's another car guy.
Tim Allen plays, uh, himself, himself, I think a lot.
He owns a giant outdoor store.
And he also vlogs where he complains about millennials.
Right.
Yes.
So in real life, he would be unbelievably popular, successful, uh, full
industry around him.
His endorsement could make or break the presidential election.
Um, yeah, no telling the power of the sky in reality.
And does he have a right, Jason, does he have a rivalry with Tim?
Oh, Jay, there's a rival.
So there's a rival, but it's a little winky of borrowing like Tim's tools.
If I know anything, I know that's not a, this sounds like, this sounds like a
good enough Tim rivalry to rival Toy Story.
The two, the two great boating of heads of Tim Allen characters.
Uh, he's a King Malbert and Igor, of course.
Uh, I don't know a lot about King Malbert.
I mean, mainly the, to me, the shiniest object in the voiceover world.
It's a very brief, but he does do a brief, uh, you know, kind of single
line or single joke cameo in cars as the indelible, maybe ultimately the part
he'll be known for the most given the popularity of cars, Jay limo, which is
a great car name.
It's really good.
It's so clean when they put that together, they must've been high fiving.
Um, and it's a really good world expander of the, of the cars of verse.
You know, you established early on with Bob Cutlass, that there are like
commenters, that there's play by play people and that makes sense because
we're in a world of car racing, but it's not a given that there would be monologue
jokes poking fun at the events of famous cars in the car world.
It's also very much like a new version of the Flintstones thing too.
Just name wise, it's like a fun way to be like, we have a version of this person
in our universe as well.
So that we can, yeah.
So we can have our, our equivalents, you know, our, our, the car version
of Mick Jagger or whatever.
Yeah.
And they're more clever.
No offense to the Flintstones.
There's more to work with.
Yeah, that's true.
You're dealing with rocks in the past.
I mean, they try to keep them all on the three yet it's rock or stone pretty much.
But with cars, yeah, that's true.
There's many, many options.
Even as I was saying that, I was like, well, it would be Mick Jaguar.
Oh yeah, that would be good.
Yeah.
That's pretty, yeah.
And cars four, which I assume is coming.
Uh, I, you can all, I mean, it's the one that like the other ones, they've had to
get their heads around, like, do we do sequels to these?
I mean, given the emotional punch of the previous ones, do we go back cars?
The one like, how, how many do you need?
Yeah, we can get up to cars 22 decade.
Yeah.
I don't know if I, I guess I really haven't heard them announce that.
I don't know.
Is there a problem because of John, big John not being there anymore?
Hmm.
Yeah.
I mean, that's his baby might've been the main fuel.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
Uh, if there are more, I'm hoping for more Jay limo.
And there's also, while that, while Jay limo himself kind of expands the world a
lot, I was doing my own world expansion, which is wondering, uh, did Jay limo get
his position presumably at 11 30 car time, uh, on that show due to, uh, the
backroom dealings of aggressive manager.
Helen Karshnik.
I'd like to think the answer.
I think the answer is yes.
Well, he really, what kind of car is Helen?
Um, who, huh?
I don't know if I know cars well enough.
Probably a station wagon, like a wood prison bus, prison bus is
better.
I just still aggressive vehicle.
Well, it's something that can hide the spikes, but then like, you know, unfurl
them all of a sudden, I just still feel so bad for a car.
No, no Buick.
Yeah.
I was going to say car, no, no Brian.
And then I was like, B car, B car.
I found it on the fly.
Yeah.
I found it.
Carnot.
No.
Wow.
Listen.
And then he fuckers don't have the lug nuts to keep that, that, that limited
popularity hack, Oh, Buick back at 12 30 where he belongs, then do I need to come
in and, uh, rip your carburetor out a late, so you want to like a late shift,
all cars in the cars verse full late shift only Pixar cars.
There is stuff in cars that like ask, you know, raises more questions
than answers because there's a one very quick shot, excuse me, in the first
movie where Bonnie hunts car, like goes to drive away and you see she has a
tramp stamp as if like, Oh, she had a wild phase in her younger years before
she was a lawyer who started running a desert motel.
Wow.
Um, and I, I was like, is that, I don't know if they still call them tramps.
They, that's what they used to call them when they were popular.
It might be an outdated term.
Uh, but she, she has like a tribal tattoo, like below her trunk, above her tail.
My barrier.
So above her trunk, it's a toilet trunk stamp.
Then we could say, uh, yeah.
Well, I mean, what does it call?
What does a wild time for a car and tail is the question?
Like, like, like, uh, huffing antifreeze.
Well, she went to sprocket break.
Yeah.
I've been writing this movie while we're sitting here doing a podcast.
Well, look, I'm already, I'm already doing a draft of blade.
So I may as well do a draft of cars while I'm there.
We're all doing a draft of blade.
We're trying to help out.
Everyone's doing a draft of blade.
Is it the blades in trouble and you're just throwing your head in the ring?
Yeah, they fired like five or six writers at this point.
They're onto their second director.
Somebody from a Mahershala Ali's camp who's playing blade and the new version
was just like, I've never seen anything like this.
I've never experienced anything like this where this has taken this long
to figure out what's going on with this movie.
They announced at Comic-Con 2019.
Wow.
So no, Jason, so simple then you put on a hat and it's like a done deal.
Now it turns out it's complicated to figure out the whole movie.
Apparently it is.
Wow.
Pitching in blade is cool.
Sprocket in this in the world, in the cars world, spring is called sprocket.
That's what the season is.
So when the winter is when window tour
because cars have windows, right?
That's true. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, that's that's the rules of summer is sputter.
And then fall is pretty hard.
Fall is hard.
Just to give you something more to auto, auto or just auto bond.
Auto bond. Yeah, that's probably fine.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What does this refreshing auto bond weather?
Yeah. Fall is good time for nice drive.
Oh, and the 90 mile an hour auto bond.
On the insane roads of Germany, when you're a race car, that is relaxing.
Yeah, that's actually that's going slow for you.
Yeah. Well, anyways, more Jaylen, more Jaylen, oh, please, more Helen Karshnik.
Late gear, late gear shift.
He competes for the for the slot with against David Jeddaman.
OK. Maybe he's got a big gap in his grill.
Oh, that's good. Yeah.
Let's see.
Bonnie Hunt's character is wild college or grad student.
I mean, it could be law school.
Is she going to cut loose in law school?
You write that spin off that wild spin off.
Sure. Bonnie Hunt's character, what is her name again?
Is she Holly?
Uh, no, that's the agent.
No, that's the spy one.
It's a pretty shift.
Is there Holly Shiftwell?
Well, that's a spy. That's the other spy.
It's something else.
Her name is something very plain, whatever it is.
That's what I. Yeah. Yeah.
Sally Carrera, Carrera, Carrera thing.
OK. The sky blue 2002 Porsche 911.
Hmm. Porsche 911.
And which we we are left to assume is the most beautiful kind of
because like there's light and checks her out when she spit.
Probably when she's revealing that snap that you're talking about.
Lightning's given her the up and down.
Like, yeah. Can you imagine?
Well, there's a porch in the desert in like this small desert town.
That's unusual.
There's a hot sports car here.
Yeah. Can you imagine how weird the meeting was when Lasseter
had to like explain to everybody exactly why this was the most attractive car
and what was attractive about it?
Like how creepy that must have been.
Everyone's like, really thought about this.
What's the car again? Like she's a Porsche.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Because when you're caught into the car gaze,
powder blue is the pretty you cannot resist.
Yeah. The most the shiniest powdery blue running around hugging everyone.
I you know, not to disagree with you.
But I feel like in a car's universe,
a sports car would be like the classically attractive.
Well, you're not disagreeing with me. You're disagreeing with John.
No, I'm unfortunately, I'm agreeing with John.
You are agreeing with John. Oh, you get it.
So you would have done the same speech if you ran Pixar.
Yeah, I mean, I guess.
I mean, do you have another standard for beauty for cars?
I've never thought about who the hottest car might be.
What kind of brand or type the hottest car?
Sports cars tend to have a lot of curves.
So if you're in the it's analogous, I guess, too.
Interesting. Yeah.
I never thought about it till Cybertruck came into my head.
Oh, well, yeah. Hello.
That's like you're going the other way.
You want an angular.
Scott likes a big boy.
You want the first first generation Laura Crawley.
Yeah. Tomb Raider.
Scott's got like Tomb Raider a lot.
Yes. Yes. It finally fulfills.
There's something in the real world that feels like a polygons.
Polygons, the sharpest.
Oh, don't poke me with the polygons.
Oh, I don't like when you poke me.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm going to have to take the whole episode here
not to think about what the hottest what I think the hottest car.
The hottest car.
If you're Mike, if you're going to be in a creative environment,
you need to be ready at all times to say what the hottest,
cutest car is.
I mean, I think about this all the time.
There's certain is that like we had a nineteen eight like Plymouth van.
But do you were attracted to that?
Like, well, I'm not saying I was attracted to the van.
You're putting words in my mouth.
That's what I'm saying.
It is aesthetically pleasing.
OK, what was the kind of a van was it?
It was a Plymouth.
We had a minivan.
I'm trying to remember even what it was that maybe that's my problem.
You're thinking on that.
I know that you're not saying you want to have sex with the van.
It was like a tan brown.
I don't know. I'm guessing late 80s.
It's just like a Plymouth van.
I mean, look at this.
Are we talking brown panel or is it like wood paneling?
It was wood paneling.
Yeah. OK.
What color the rest of it, you think?
Tan.
The rest is tan, but wood.
Oh, I see.
Well, I think we might be looking at a Grand Voyager then.
OK, let me take a look there.
What do we think?
OK, I don't know that I'm so attracted to it.
I like it for a retro kind of vibe.
I think it's an aesthetic I like.
It was very fun.
It was very sad when we got rid of it.
Do you want to touch its little Plymouth star?
Get all up on its Plymouth star?
I don't know that I've ever wanted to touch a car,
its little decorative brand logo.
You know, I guess the Batmobile from Batman Forever I like.
I don't know if I'm attracted.
I guess I'm attracted to it.
Again, that's a pretty notable aesthetic.
Batmobile is actually more phallic,
if I really think about it, than it is kind of male.
No, it's fine.
I'm just saying I'm trying to think of what these cars say
to me on an attraction level, which is a new territory,
I feel like.
So I'm just learning as I say the words here on the show.
So in Batman Forever XXX, Bruce Wayne admits his identity,
brings Dr. Chase Meridian home with him and says,
I just want to make you an offer, take it or leave it.
Would you like to have sex with my car?
It's like an indecent proposal or something, yeah.
Maybe that's why.
Her hair kind of blows back, it zooms way into her,
and she's kind of like, oh, maybe.
I hadn't thought about it, but I'm thinking about it now.
As a psychiatrist, I think I must do it,
just as a mind experiment.
Just an experiment.
Baby, I could bring you to a kiss from a car.
That can still make it into my Batman Forever II script,
so we'll see.
We'll see if that makes the cut.
When the most attractive female chase
and the most attractive male, the Batmobile, get together.
Yeah.
OK, real quick, what's the hottest Batmobile
of all the Batmobiles?
What do you think?
I think it's got to be the Bert.
Well, because I love the animated series Batmobile,
but it's kind of blocky.
It's almost full Cybertruck style,
but it is kind of blocky and angular.
But I mean, I think it's certainly not
the Tumbler from the Nolans.
No offense to the Tumbler.
Again, a cool vehicle, but not.
Original Burton has that big nub in the front,
which I think is like a missile that fires.
But you know, you could view that as phallic.
You could view it as akin to a nipple, if you wanted to.
I think it gives you something to caress.
So I'm going to lock in my vote for original Burton Batmobile.
We have Burton Batmobile.
I think that's good logic.
I think, you know what?
Batman and Robin has fun colors.
I might even say the Batman and Robin, the Clooney Batmobile.
I think I'm going to go iconoclastic
and go with the Batman forever.
The Tumbler?
No, no.
Oh, Batman Forever. I misheard it.
I'm so sorry. Not the Tumbler.
Yours, yours.
No, I don't like the Tumbler.
I don't know why it's on my mind.
No, I'm saying Batman Forever, your movie.
I'm saying I'm not obsessed with the Tumbler secretly,
and that's why I keep bringing it up.
I'm not attracted to it. That's what I'm saying.
I like when it flies.
Does it fly in the third one?
I think it flies in the third one,
because it flies the nuclear bomb out into the water.
Are we allowed to pick the plane?
Or just cars? Cars only.
The Batwing, I think so.
From Batman Returns as the plane, as the Batwing.
Well, the Batwing's in the first movie,
because he gets the, during the parade.
It is in the first movie.
Yeah, he gets all the balloons, and he shoots them up in the air
that have all the Joker gas in them.
Right. There's like one or two audience members
who have been fireworks factory-ing every other episode
and going, when are they going to talk about
which Batmobiles they want to fuck?
Well, finally, it's happened, and you can thank Jason for it.
Seven years.
Thank John Lasseter and Jason.
You're very welcome. Can I repay you with a hug?
Jason, could you say the same line now?
You're very welcome. Can I repay you?
No. No. I don't want to.
Don't incriminate him.
All right. All right.
Let's go back. Sorry. Sorry.
I, what, did you have more voice acting?
I, you know, no, if you want to close out the voice area,
I mean, I have a whole other zone that I can get into,
but, you know, don't let me dictate it.
If there are other, what I'm about to do
is move into his work in 90s syndicated television,
but if anybody else has another area,
they'd like to fit in there first.
Well, I think the area I focused on,
unfortunately, is his sole leading man role.
This is important. Do you want to end on that,
or do you want to end on the sitcoms?
I think we could do some, we could do the film right now.
And this is, you know, this is important, I think,
because this does offer up a alternate universe, Leno.
If this works better, maybe we get busy with a film career,
and not with The Tonight Show, because this is 89,
this comes out, you know, so this,
and this is definitely not, this is the opposite of him
just being a talk show host in a suit.
Would you like to tell us about the film, Jason?
This is the 1989 movie, Collision Course,
and I saw the AKA of this movie,
Kamikaze to Detroit.
Unfortunate, this is-
And I don't want to know the other AKAs.
I don't want to know the AKAs they didn't settle on.
And this might be the worst thing
I've ever watched for the podcast.
Did you watch the whole thing?
I watched the whole thing,
because I found a rip on YouTube.
Man, I've tried, I've like, it's been,
it's been on Macs, actually, for Here and There,
and survived all of the gluts, all of the wipeouts.
And as you could tell from this episode,
I'm very interested in Jay Leno and in Jay Leno acting.
I've never, I've always collapsed somewhere
in like minute eight of that movie.
I've just been seeing like the poster,
or like the VHS art box of him, like back to back,
with co-star Pat Morita,
who has some funny lines in this movie.
Pat Morita, I think, is funnier in this movie than Jay Leno.
Well, he's a movie star.
Yeah.
He's just been in some extremely popular movies,
and on Happy Days, and you know,
he's a professional comedic actor,
which is something that Jay Leno was not.
I think Jay might be miscast a little bit, too, here.
Yeah, well, you think he's like
a second or third choice, maybe?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I could see that being the case,
because like, where is, he's still a couple years away
from The Tonight Show, but he's doing the guest spot
on Carson at this point already,
so he's pretty well known.
But it still feels like a lead in a movie.
He hadn't, I mean, he's in other movies,
but yeah, I wonder if.
They wanted, they were going through,
it was probably all stand-ups,
and they're going through the list,
and just everybody's busy with touring,
so like Steven Wright, no, no, he won't do it.
Emo Phillips, no, no, Emo won't do it.
Michael Keaton, you're not gonna believe this,
but he's filming Batman right now?
Batman, what do you mean?
This would be way, Collision Course
would be way better for him.
He's gonna look like a fool in that suit.
This role is Detective Tony Costas.
Yes, he is a Detroit detective, works in robbery,
and Pat Morita is a Tokyo detective,
and he is sent to America to get,
to find a prototype that had been stolen,
stolen from another, from a car company.
Okay, so it's cars again.
We're back to cars. So it is cars.
And maybe they didn't think of him for it.
In the opening credits, Jay Leno is driving a Corvette,
which kind of comes back into play later in the movie,
but he's driving a big old car.
He was probably like,
Hey, can that come back into play a lot?
Actually, what if we can't, you know,
this scene I don't think we need,
I think all these lines we don't need,
can I just spitball him?
What if I'm just driving a Corvette again?
Actually, what if I'm fixing the Corvette?
Actually, what if you don't film it,
and I just fix the Corvette, and I don't do this movie,
and I go do some stand-up?
A lot of, I mean, there's so much about it.
This movie is very cheap, which comes into play.
There's a note on the Wikipedia, which is very funny.
When Merida guest starred on The Tonight Show in 1989
with Leno serving as guest host,
they recalled that the movie had run out of money
on the last day of filming,
with key scenes yet to be shot,
and no budget left for editing and post-production.
You need that.
Yeah, that's important.
It definitely, towards the end of the movie,
just kind of in, it just kind of wraps up.
It just freeze frames on something,
like this movie's in, what do you want?
They'll buy it, the suckers will buy it.
Some of the budget may have gone to
staging a fake car race going on in Detroit,
which does not play into the movie plot at all,
besides when Jay Leno and Pat Merida
ride a motorcycle through this car race.
Again, this is a J note.
It's a J thing.
I just had an idea.
What if there's a car race?
Well, that's a good boy.
We did have that money earmarked for editing and post.
That's boring stuff.
You go vroom, vroom.
Yeah, vroom, vroom is what we need.
A little vroom and then a little vroom, vroom, vroom.
We have all different kinds of engines.
I was, in the trailer, these clips are there,
which I watched, and it's like Jay's doing a stunt.
I was like, is Jay an action hero
kind of in this movie as well?
Yeah, kind of.
There is some action, other odd things about the movie.
Ernie Hudson is in the movie in about two or three scenes
and is behaving like he is an actor
playing a supporting role in a movie,
unlike Jay Leno, who is screaming most of his lines,
stand-up style.
You watched this movie from another room.
You watched it from the bathroom.
It's a little loud.
I'm gonna get some distance from this.
Jay is also like a creep in that movie.
He looks the female police officer up and down
in the first minute of the movie.
They really lean into that heart.
They're like a human version of a Porsche.
Yeah, he's asking every woman in the movie
for her home phone number for police business,
which is creepy.
There are a lot of jokes about Japan.
By when I say jokes, I mean saying the words
Godzilla or sushi.
I think the movie is rooted in anxiety
of Detroit falling apart and the rise
of affordable, reliable cars from Asia.
Honda, Toyota ostensibly is the theme in the movie,
but that just comes out in everyone hating Pat Morita.
Everyone being very racist to Pat Morita
in a way that some of Rush Hour holds up,
doesn't hold up in this movie,
there's jokes where you're like,
oh, I don't think you, you certainly can't say that now.
I don't think you should have been saying that in 1989.
Well, luckily no one saw it at the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no need to put the content warning before it
because that implies that anyone
is turning this movie on.
Whoever owns the movie, literally there was just
a little light bleeped at their headquarters yesterday.
Somebody watched the movie.
We haven't seen this in years and it was you.
No one's finished this movie.
Since the editor had to finish it.
Someone watched the illegal rip on YouTube.
The YouTubers, yeah.
Yeah, well, these things are known.
Seems fair to, I'm mad about foreign cars
and what that's doing to Detroit.
I'm gonna put all my anger on this police officer.
Yeah.
Seems fair.
There are, of course, a number of jokes about karate.
There's a funny gag where they're talking about Mickey Mouse
and Pat Morita says, we have Disneyland now in Tokyo.
And Jay Leno was like, no, you don't.
And Pat Morita was like, yes, we do.
Because, you know, it opened by then.
It did.
It's right here, if you wanna hear it.
What kind of Mickey Mouse system you got in Japan?
Mickey Mouse, American invention.
Right, you guys aren't clever enough to think about it.
Now, we have Disneyland now near Tokyo.
Do not.
All three of us are in the theater.
Ha!
In an otherwise silent screening of collision course,
three guys at one point just said ha, not even a big laugh.
I think the average person didn't know
that there was Disneyland there.
Yeah, I don't know.
So, like, how did that play in?
It was like six years later, yeah.
There's no internet, why would you know that?
How would that scene play to an American audience
who doesn't know that?
They stand up like, bullshit, there's no such thing.
Now we know that character's a liar.
Travel agents in the audience are like,
yes, no one believes me.
Finally, proof.
Thank you, collision course.
I otherwise don't like your politics and your stereotypes,
but in this case, you've been very helpful.
There's some massive, if you can believe it,
there's some massive logicals towards the end
where they track the leads to a garage
and it's really like, oh, that's in Duke's territory.
The gang, the Dukes, they're really dangerous.
Jay Leno leaves his car, his Corvette, by this garage.
It is never addressed again.
He also, Pat Morita drops the gun in this garage.
So a cop's gun is left in this garage
and it is never followed up on.
But probably the worst thing in the movie,
the big bad villain, the head of a luxury car company
who wants to use the stolen prototype,
is named Derek Jarrett.
And that is a bad movie name.
I don't know how names sound.
Derek Jarrett.
I kind of like it.
I kind of like it, actually.
There you go, bust this Derek Jarrett.
Derek Jarrett.
Jarrett also is spelled J-A-R-R-Y-D.
I've never encountered that in my life.
I've never seen that.
What is this, Elon Musk's son?
All right, we got a great show.
Melissa Etheridge is here.
Now that felt right.
That was right.
No, that was perfect, yeah.
I can't believe you inflicted this whole thing on yourself.
I did, because I was like, oh, well,
for the Pride Night episode,
I was going to try to watch all of Strange World
and I didn't get around to it.
I ran out of time.
And I already know that it's a much better movie.
You've been in the market for a great film.
Well, and I had watched Jay Leno's Cars Co-Star.
I watched an old Paul Newman movie called Harper
a few days ago where he plays an old.
Framing Paul Newman as Jay Leno's Cars Co-Star.
Whatever's on his tombstone, erase it and put that.
And I'm like, oh, I was reading about that.
And I'm like, oh, it's the adaptation
of the first Lou Archer novel, which I've read a few of.
And it's awesome.
And Lauren McCall is in it as the older client.
You mean that she's her old pal
or that it is an old film?
She's older from, it's the late 60s,
so she's older than the Key Largo or Hay Day.
What's the name of the character?
It's older than Kindergarten.
What's that?
What's the name of the character, Lou?
Lou Archer.
Archer, and that's who Paul Newman plays?
Well, they changed the name to Harper for whatever reason.
So he plays it in this movie
and then he plays it in a later movie called Drowning Pool.
Oh, like the band.
Like the band, yeah.
Let the body set the floor.
Wow, Peter Graves played Lou Archer as well.
How about that?
I don't think I knew that.
I didn't know.
Hmm.
So you, have you heard about this?
Have you heard about this?
Peter Graves is playing Lou Archer.
Jay Leno would probably love to talk about
Harper's beat up old convertible.
Well, Brian Keith also played Lou Archer.
Oh.
How about that?
Did you know that?
I didn't.
Sometimes I think if I wasn't here,
the podcast would be 100% the exchange that just happened.
Then like just have 45 seconds of silence
and then Jason and I both looking at Wikipedia going,
what else?
Okay, hmm.
I wondered, did a Carradine ever play?
Archer?
Oh, look at this.
Brian Keith was on an Alfred Hitchcock Presents.
Okay, yeah, this is his version.
This is just Jason and I alone.
I think a young Ed Asner could have worked as Archer.
Do you ever watch Family Affair?
When FX started, they started showing Batman 66
and they started showing this old show
called Family Affair that my mother loved.
Brian Keith, when you both start talking
about Quest Diagnostics for a while.
I've had a terrible time lately.
USPS informed delivery informs me
they're sending me something today.
I don't know what it is.
I checked my informed delivery as well this morning.
I love my informed delivery.
So, okay, but we are in a world where
I am one of the hosts of the show,
so we got anything else about collision cores?
I don't know.
I also turned it off because I went, oh my gosh.
It's rough.
It is really, yeah, it's really terrible.
I guess the only thing in my head is,
because this was the Kuznick era
and I am wondering about her negotiations
to lock him in as Costas.
And if there were any efforts to like,
what's this I hear about Merida
asking for the same that Jay's making?
Pat Merida is top-built because again,
he's a movie star.
Of course.
I know and it drives me crazy.
That's insane.
Merida's old news.
How long ago was Happy Days?
10 years ago, 15?
He's in the past.
Leno's the wave of the future.
I should go up to Merida's trailer
and rip his fucking sack off
for even attempting to get the same money
that the hottest comedian in America's making.
Come on.
This is the new Midnight Run
and Jay is Grodin and De Niro all in one.
You're lucky they're even pointing the camera
at your dogshit client, Merida.
She wrote the script probably.
You and me and Pat Merida are gonna be working
in this town for a long time.
Let me tell ya, I'm never looking him in the eyes again.
He's dead to me and so are you.
That's like your most effortless character, I think.
It really is.
That's how much the late shift is in me.
If you haven't seen it,
Ellen Kushnick has played by Kathy Bates
and if it is like, yeah, it's in there.
That's why you need to do that.
I said this when we did the late shift episode,
the full late shift series.
You show running a late shift show
which is really just about Jay and Helen.
And then you can make up most of it.
Well, look, you have to because she passed away.
Well, right.
So you would have to,
but you, I think, just have to include her in like,
Jay does joke after joke, night after night.
He has more jokes per minute than any other host on TV
and this guy comes out and fucks around
with a string dance and touching his nipples.
He belongs in a crazy house.
My first move will be to lock him up.
Forget him taking the Tonight Show.
I want him behind bars.
This is like, you would have to, again,
we're backed at a lot of explanation,
but maybe there's a Marvel universe type explanation
where alternate universe Helen Kushnick
comes through a portal in like 1997
and she just comes back to Jay
and then manages Jay for the rest of his career.
Well, that's the end of the first season.
Eight or 10 episodes.
It's a prestige TV.
It's called The Elite.
I think we said that.
I think we maybe said that on the episode, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just, yeah, make it nice and tidy.
I think it's seasons, though,
full of just pre-Tonight Show.
Then the actual Tonight Show debacle depicted
in The Late Shift is two seasons long.
Sure.
Then Helen passes away and then there's the portal
that opened, the Doctor Strange portal
and Helen walks through.
So you pricks thought you could bury me.
Well, you didn't count on me getting a heaping helping
of Forbes brain grain cereal.
It means it not only brought me back from the dead,
it also made me even better at deals than I used to be.
I would like another We're Back sequel
where it explains that brain grain,
if fed to corpses, brings them back to life.
Yeah, and that, too.
I also, now another thing you don't know about me
is that besides that I invented time travel,
I also have a new variety of brain grain
that reanimates corpses.
I heard so many wishes on my wish radio.
Every kid in the world is loudly wishing
that the dead could walk the earth again.
Some say I'm playing God.
I say I am God.
I have solved death.
Cronkite's voice would be good for God.
Does God have a cool airship?
Does God have a steampunk airship full of dinosaurs?
I think not.
That's a great theological question.
Does God have a cool airship full of dinosaurs?
Yeah, well the way people are like,
we should retire like I don't think of God
as being like a guy in a cloud with a beard.
I don't think of God as being like a guy
with a steampunk airship full of smart dinosaurs,
serial fed, of course.
Of course, yeah.
I mean, sometimes I'm open to the possibility
that God has a wish radio.
Yeah, I'm agnostic.
I'm not dogmatic about it.
I'm not saying either way, yes or no,
whether God has a magical wish radio,
you know, but I'm open to it.
You have to allow all systems of belief.
I would never hate my neighbor
because he doesn't think God has a wish radio.
As long as we acknowledge the reality of wish radios,
that's the belief I don't bend on.
Right, right, yeah, it makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, Zen meditation says come back to the breath
and it's okay, don't judge yourself if you get distracted.
Of course, distracted thinking of wish radios.
Listen, cocksucker, there's only two people
who've ever risen from the dead, Jesus Christ and me.
And if I see that prick around here anywhere,
I'll tell him to stop being so preachy.
The gospel of Helen rules this town.
Go back to Bethlehem.
That's some great character building
that Helen Kushnick is hoarding all the brain grain cereal.
That's why everybody's so like,
oh God, A, she's so mean on the phone
and B, she's got all the brain grain.
She gives Jay one bowl a year
so we can keep up with that shooting schedule
and all those stand-up dates.
How do you keep up that relentless pace, Jay?
I just love doing it.
I don't have intelligence increasing cereal
that my manager fed me.
It's based on the film that I was in where I played VORB.
How do you come up with all those Monica Lewinsky jokes, Jay?
Because eating it, that's not the cereal.
One sec, for no reason, let me just duck out of frame here.
I'll be right back.
Could you do a one-person show as Helen, maybe, even two?
God, I think I could, oh fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, just get me fitted for a pantsuit from there.
30 minutes, you could do,
well, you could do 90 if you want, I guess.
Kushnick the beginning, yeah.
You'd be exhausted by the end of each show.
Yeah, yeah, people would be like,
I've heard profanity in my time,
but when you started going into the audience
and me calling me a shit-eating little prick,
what did I do?
I gave you money for this show.
Why do I deserve that?
A lot of it's crowd work.
A lot of the one-man show will be crowd work.
You just insult the audience as Helen.
Listen, you pale, sweaty cuck.
You're the worst audience member I've ever seen.
Your eyes are darting every which way.
It's like you don't even know how to be in a fucking crowd.
Wow, the new queen of mean is here.
Scott Gardner is.
As, oh, and Kushnick.
And then everything comes back to.
A lot would have to happen to get me on a Snatch Game,
but if I had that opportunity,
I'd be the most obscure celebrity they've ever had,
besides Wayland Flowers and Madame.
Sure, of course.
Was not Madame, I think we've learned that,
that Madame was in a Snatch Game on Drag Race.
Yes, yes, Madame does pop up a lot, yes.
Of course, it's a very good transition as well.
Well, I saw something in that IMDB and I was wondering.
Yeah, Jay Leno was on Madame's place.
When I realized that I just backed this,
as excited as I've been to do this episode,
that I backed us into Madame actually sneaking in here.
Jay Leno was on Madame's place, which is insane.
Madame's Place just came up, what, two months ago?
It's pretty new as far as the podcast.
But, I mean, I don't know what you found
as far as clips and why's for Madame's Place.
I decided to leave it to you, Mike.
Well, I saved myself some work.
Here's the sad part about this,
is that there's really one YouTube channel called TavTV
that seems to have all of the Madame's Place,
or most of the Madame's Place episodes.
And Jay Leno appears on episode 14,
but they only have a partial part of the episode.
No!
And Madame's Place is not well archived in other places.
So.
I hate to talk about how the sausage is made,
but we're recording this the day after
the disastrous Biden debate.
Mood's a little grim.
Now you're telling me that they don't have
episode 14 on TavTV?
So really all it is, and we don't have to play it.
This country's fucked.
Jay appears on Madame's Place,
so the clip starts with Jay shaking Madame's hand.
Now, Madame again is a puppet who has a talk show.
And.
I think I forgot that part.
That's a big part of the premise,
is that Madame has a talk show.
And this clip just starts with Jay on the show.
He doesn't say anything,
and then he kind of disappears behind the curtain.
He does a little thing like he didn't know
where he was going.
And then he kind of does a little Jay dance,
like acroid running in Ghostbusters,
where he kind of is off kilter.
And then Madame just goes on with the episode,
and there's other guests.
So.
I was looking for the full episode,
and I hope it's not lost forever.
I hope this is not completely lost media.
Oh God.
But.
So at least we got to see Jay and Madame together.
They are in one frame together, yes.
But I was really hoping for a full thing
where like Madame was in love with Jay,
but maybe that is what happens early on in the episode.
But.
Yeah.
So you think because you've got some little
rinky dink talk show.
I saw your set.
It's nothing but lattices.
It looks cheap as hell.
We're talking about The Tonight Show.
The number one game in town.
First of all, look, I'm a lady,
and I know the audience is never gonna accept
a lady host of The Tonight Show.
So keep dreaming.
That's Jay's spot when that old fuck Carson croaks,
and you know it.
That's you as Helen on Madame's place, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
That's the first earlier scene.
And what does she sound like?
What would she say to that?
Oh, Madame.
I don't have my Madame impression down,
which again, that'll have to come here.
But I'll give you a little bit of just what she says to Jay
on the way out here,
and I'm gonna struggle with it for a second here.
Just watching the kind of montage,
I guess it's the credits.
Madame looks like a long snake
when she moves sometimes,
because she has a long pump. How dare you?
How dare you say that about Madame?
Oh, sure, America's gonna accept
some long-snaked old lady into their home every night.
Keep dreaming, you old bag.
She looks like a penis in balls, Jason.
That's what she looks like.
America wants a big, thick-chin man,
not a penis-faced woman.
We now join our show already in progress.
Thank you, Jay.
That was good.
We'll be right back.
Thank you, darling.
Well, wasn't that just terrific?
Now I've got a little question for my audience.
Have you ever wondered what those little ruffle things
they stick on the end of lamb chops are called?
They're called little panties.
I'll never forget the first time I pulled them off, either.
That was a bad joke, wasn't it?
This is what you are thirsting to talk about on this show.
Well, I will, like, you become Helen,
I will become Matt, as well.
That's what I'm thirsting to do.
Well, now I know what I can wield in this episode.
Whenever I get frustrated, I can become,
I think Helen is like, Helen's a way
to manifest the rage in me.
It's like a healthy way to let it come out, this other side.
People across the country could become Helen,
and it would really help get some anger and rage out.
And I'm just over here eating my show-recording lamb chops.
What was that joke?
Was that about panties?
What did she say?
Yeah, she said something called panties.
I think the little ruffles that you used to get on a chop,
like, they always draw it in loony tunes.
Is that what she's referring to?
This is a joke.
This is an early 80s joke about a now-defunct preparation
of lamb chops.
But it's really just an excuse for a madam to say panties.
Talk about taking them off.
And that didn't even get a laugh with the fake piped-in audience
of Madam's Place.
Well, they were, yeah.
I don't know if it was fake.
I don't know if maybe the audience had heard
the joke a few times.
Maybe the puppet had to reset.
There's no way there was a live audience.
I feel like I know how Alf was made.
There's no way you're making an audience sit
through all the puppet resets.
Scott, what if I were to tell you, at one point,
Madam is riding in the back of a Rolls-Royce?
And of course, it looks like she's standing up
because she's so stretched out.
It is kind of a grotesque image, even as I said.
Madam is scary.
I'm not denying.
I'm not going to argue Madam is cute.
Madam is scary.
I acknowledge that.
OK, all right.
Yeah, it has always.
I don't think that's the main thing.
I think my main complaint is that it sucks.
My secondary complaint is that she's scary.
She is scary.
But look, on the future.
I'm goddamn scary.
Madam's Place, other episodes have
William Shatner, Pee-wee Herman, Arsenio Hall.
I mean, we're in for a lot in the future of Madam discussion
on this podcast.
But not right now.
We already have.
Not right now.
Well, because some other often discussed kitschy celebrities
are right around the corner where I'm heading,
assuming that that closes out the Madam chapter.
Yeah, for now, yes.
I am going to bring up my beloved thing
that I ham-fistedly insert whenever I can, Baywatch.
Of course.
Very excited.
Jay Leno factors into one of my favorite episodes of Baywatch.
And it's an episode that really illustrates the kind of thing
that they started doing that I don't think the audience knows.
I think you picture a bunch of hokey ocean rescue hijinks.
And you don't know maybe that stuff like this
happens on Baywatch.
By this, I mean the season seven episode, episode 14 talk show.
OK, so it's talk show because of Jay Leno.
Well, kind of, but also because, much like Madam,
we are now dealing with a fictional talk show that
is only in the Baywatch reverse.
Mitch Buchanan, AKA David Hasselhoff, on the beach
rescues a woman's life.
But it's no ordinary woman.
I have a beloved, presumably non-Jay Leno talk show host,
Cassie Cole.
He rescues Cassie Cole's life.
That's a power player.
Cassie Cole is played by country singer and Branson Mainstay
Barbara Mandrell of the Mandrell Sisters.
Right, of course.
So she rescues.
She's rescued by Mitch Buchanan.
She says, well, you've got to come on my show
to talk about it.
That's an interesting thing to talk about.
You saved my life.
You've got to tell the story.
And he feels a little amiss about it
despite having incredible bravado.
I mean, how could you not if you're
an Adonis like Mitch Buchanan?
Yeah, this is the thing that kind of stresses me.
You just get a sense that maybe being on camera
is a whole other thing.
So then it goes to him on the show.
And he's set up to tell the story.
And he's immediately flop sweating.
He's very, very nervous.
And it starts to get a little amiss.
You start to wonder, is something up?
Are we maybe dealing with a little bit
of a dream sequence here?
And that is what I will play.
Despite it not having Jay Leno, I have to play this moment.
Mitch Buchanan on the Cassie Cole show.
Mitch, talk to me.
Oh, no.
Like airplane sweat.
I was in the water, and the waves came,
and I went over to the garden, and I was in that moon.
I can now just feel a Grammicon, feel a Grammicon,
feel a Grammicon, feel a Grammicon, feel a Grammicon.
And then he wakes up.
Then he wakes up sleeping in a tank top.
Yeah, as you do.
Well, if somebody broke into your house,
how else do you show off your bod?
To an intruder.
Yeah, you're right that it's, I think I said flop sweating,
but it's like just literal faucet coming to you.
You listener could hear there.
And then he starts babbling.
And then he starts saying, straight down the barrel
of the lens, feel a Grammicon, feel a Grammicon.
I cannot tell you why the fuck he is saying feel a Grammicon
over and over.
Is it like a reverse of some words?
Maybe, maybe.
Is it some, is this like, was he like one of the main German
investors in the successful syndication of Baywatch?
Is it a reference to something?
Is it just nonsense dream speak?
And they were like, oh, what's a funny thing?
Yes, that's my feeling.
Yeah, yeah, because he'd already done like blah, blah, blah.
But then feel a Grammicon.
I've been haunted by feeling a Grammicon for a long time.
Listener, if you can help, if you can explain
what feel a Grammicon is.
Really, if it's reversed, it doesn't really
look like anything.
Oh, you tried to flip it?
Yeah.
Thank you.
That was nice of you.
This is the real impetus for the episode.
Scott's trying to solve the mystery of feeling a Grammicon.
I've been, yes, the listeners should know that I don't sleep
and it has nothing to do with my young child.
This predates that.
I've been thinking about feel a Grammicon for eight years now.
And I need some help.
Tossing and turning in your sleep tank top.
Do you think it's weird to sleep in a tank top?
It's like a muscle shirt, I guess, more.
You mean it's too tight?
It's teal, that's something.
It's definitely what he would wear at work, too.
Right.
Yeah.
There's something, yeah, I think you're right.
There's something off about it.
Yeah, yeah.
But anyways, now actually I'm not
going to play a clip of, well, I don't know, maybe I should.
So there's two little scenes with Jay.
Jay is the lead guest that night on Cassie Cole.
There's a moment where he introduces himself
to a lifeguard who's not going to be on the show
and just kind of babbles and is very nervous.
He offers him a cookie.
This is an attribute that's given to Jay
in this version of Jay, which is that he's always
walking around with a basket of cookies
and offering them to people.
And then once you see him on the show,
Cassie Cole says, well, thank you so much for coming, Jay.
And thanks for bringing us some of your tonight show cookies.
And he's like, yeah, yeah, sure.
Tonight show cookies, huh, why?
You very quickly figure out, I'll
try to find a quick moment of it here.
Maybe worth, might not play the best for listeners.
But it keeps also to note, he keeps going back
to the cookies a lot.
Now that he's not the main guest,
he's still on the couch, he's eating cookies.
Then I'll let him tell the story.
See, I'm an extreme jock.
When I was a little girl, I used to take on any dare, even
a double dog dare.
Well, same goes today.
I mean, I pushed the envelope.
Live on the extreme.
So anyway, I was out surfing, right?
Not exactly.
I was out drowning.
Exactly.
Oh, Jay.
He's choking.
Thank you, I thought so too.
He needs help, he needs help.
Heimlich.
Heimlich, he's now saved two people's lives
in this episode.
Yeah, he's there to talk about the life that he saved,
and then he does it live on the show.
He saves America's tied favorite host
to Cassie Cole, Jay Leno.
You were just telling me about Heimlich being Heimlich.
Were you Heimlich, or were you Heimlich someone?
What were you talking about?
When I was three years old, we were at a diner,
and I started choking on a breakfast potato.
And I think I was Heimlich.
I know that's not funny, but breakfast potato.
Breakfast potato's a funny specific to say.
Like, not a tiny home fry,
like a, or not a tiny hash brown, like a...
Like a big wedge.
Like a chunk, or a wedge, yeah.
Did you see someone be Heimlich as well?
I learned how to Heimlich in the Cub Scouts.
Boy Scouts.
I was just, I actually had never, back on Wood,
I never had to be Heimlich.
You might have been talking about
if you have to Heimlich yourself, you get a chair.
Yeah, yeah.
I think I would start to do that,
and then realize I don't know the angle,
or, it's probably something I should learn.
In theory, I know how to do it.
In theory.
Yes, how will your theories play in reality, I don't know.
But anyway, well, we can all learn it from this scene.
It's a helpful scene in that way.
You get to see Jay with a bunch of regurgitated food
coming out of his mouth, which is interesting,
and then she says, how about I add,
he saved Jay, everybody,
and then Jay goes back to the cookies,
and he takes another bite.
That's funny.
Which is pretty funny.
That's funny, yeah.
And something tells me that was his choice,
because it's funnier than anything
that usually happens on Day Watch.
So, I've always loved this little sequence.
Fun to see him, he's in the suit,
but he's gotta do action and stuff.
That's good, yeah.
Really like this.
This is not the end of the Leno Baywatch connection,
because Leno also appears on a post-Baywatch show,
post-Pamela Anderson's departure from Baywatch,
her spinoff syndicated series, VIP.
Yes.
Now, in VIP, I feel like you might have pointed out
this naming mechanism.
Yes, Valerie Irons Protection.
See, Pamela Anderson is Valerie Irons.
Spelled in a weird way to spell Valerie,
and then, yeah, VIP is Valerie Irons Protection.
So, she's like kind of a bodyguard, but a little more.
She has a company, she has a whole team of bodyguards.
Okay, VIP looms large in my head,
and I've said this before,
and not just because Pamela Anderson was like,
you know, interesting to a young man at the time.
You know, if I had to guess,
I would say that wasn't any part of it.
Have anything to do with it.
There were attractive ladies on the show.
Certainly part of it, I'm not saying it's not nothing.
It's not nothing, but I was looking through some of it,
and I was like, there's an aesthetic to VIP I really like.
It's a very 90s colorful show that wouldn't,
you would find the same, let me find a good scene of it.
It would look right on maybe Nickelodeon or something
as well, certain scenes.
It's kind of like space cases style.
Kind of, yeah.
So, I'm like, oh yeah, that's definitely part
of my fascination with it,
and we were watching some of it over the pandemic,
and I was like, some of this is at least watchable
versus other ones of these hour-long syndicated shows.
Your Relic Hunters.
Yes, yeah, often shows like that have a really fun intro,
and then you really drag.
I'm sorry to say, that is kind of where I landed ultimately
with Sebastian Jackal.
Yes.
Ultimately, UPN's Deadly Games,
a little bit boring to watch.
These things come in hot
with a lot of very memorable opening sequence,
and that's my thing with Baywatch,
is that I find it so watchable,
especially with the beautiful remaster.
Of course, now you can finally see.
If VIP is in this area at all, I'm interested,
and now that I know VIP is on Tubi,
America's most successful streaming platform.
That's why I found Harper.
There's a shot I have.
I think it's all, it has the Netflix thing,
where like all the shit's actually there.
What's also funny.
Yeah, a lot of it, apparently, I think the end
of every month, a lot of it says it's expiring,
and then just doesn't.
Like, they get the contracts, they renew it anyway.
Nevermind, we got it.
And maybe, this is why maybe a larger VIP study
needs to be engaged in, is that I think,
because Jay's on two episodes of VIP,
and I think the intro just of the show in the second season,
they have to cram in more of the explanation
of what the show is, because people are maybe confused
by the premise, because the premise, I believe,
is that there's like mistaken identity or something,
and then these other like female assassins
get Pam Anderson to be like the figurehead
of their protection agency, and that she's not really
into like shooting and killing people.
I don't know if they actually kill anybody,
but like she's in a, she's just,
Like falls in a trash can or something.
She gets mixed up in all of this.
She does a lot of prep falls.
But it's like, it's kind of a confusing premise.
Yeah.
Like, why isn't she just on the,
like isn't she just on the team for some reason?
Yeah, sure, yeah.
But I bought, and I was like, oh, VIP,
oh, it's an acronym, Valerie Iron, like I bought that.
You understood it immediately, you're saying.
I understood it, and the fact that it would kick in
after Saturday morning cartoons.
Like their headquarters, it looks like it's a Barbie
dream house or something.
Sure. Like color-wise.
Yeah. Of course, this isn't loading,
but like their headquarters is very much the color here.
Yeah, well, it's kind of like where the Spice Girls
live in Spice World.
Yes, exactly, yes.
Mm-hmm, is that a bus?
That's like a giant bus.
I forget if they have a stationary home,
as well as the big bus.
Yeah.
I like things with big buses in general.
Sure.
There's a movie, in fact, called The Big Bus,
not to be confused with Super Train,
kind of in the same genre as Super Train.
Would you say you're attracted to buses more than cars?
Wait, that's my answer, big buses.
Big buses.
All right, the Spice Girls bus.
Probably, it's like a little feather boa
around the bumper.
They spiced up the bus.
The Spice Girls bus is Scott's answer.
Spiced up your life. Good answer, good answer, honestly.
But also another, and again,
I'm not fully declaring VIP,
like you gotta watch this, you gotta binge it,
but the first scene that Jay is in is great.
I'm gonna go in backwards order between the two.
I think that's smart, yes.
Because honestly, yeah, so you've seen it, so you know.
Yeah, I watched these, yeah, yeah.
That was my thought, is that she, you know,
he appeared on it twice, the second time in season two,
Valma and Louise.
And the, yeah, it's, in this one,
you'll notice a familiarity.
Like now they know each other,
and that's because of the events of the first one
and what she does for him.
But I'm gonna build to that.
Okay, so by now, Jay and Val are old pals.
They've worked together before,
but this is their second interaction.
Hey Jay, how you doing?
Hey Val, you look great.
How you doing?
Good, good.
You mentioned something about a transport, Mr. Leno.
Oh yeah, listen, I wanna hire VIP
to drive a Priscilla up to Cal State, Sacramento.
The lovely Priscilla, you are lovely.
Actually, that's Williams, that's you, sir.
Over here.
He tried to shake a woman's hand,
but they never explained who that woman was either.
You know.
Well, I'm gonna auction it off as I think.
Priscilla is a car, Priscilla is a car.
Yeah.
I mean, these VIP people, like, proclaim to be expert,
like they probably gotta find out a lot
about whoever they're protecting,
and they haven't figured out by now
that if Jay says positive things about a female name,
that it's a car.
It's gotta be, yeah.
You would think they would be pros by now,
but yeah, that's just an error in the writing.
Anyway, then there's a big thing.
He has a big list of rules for taking care of Priscilla,
but the car comes back all busted,
and that's kind of the crux of it.
But the other one is definitely more exciting.
This is the sixth episode of the show,
Diamonds Are Val's Best Friend, and this really is.
So Val is a guest on The Tonight Show.
Yes.
Much like how Cassie Cole has lifeguard Mitch Buchanan
to talk about, you know, saving lives,
and then he has a private security person.
The head of a private security.
The head of a, the non,
it was not technically not part of the company,
you said, or something.
Well, she was, I mean, at this point she is,
but I just, yeah.
It's complicated.
Well, that's why, you know,
you gotta dive into the show itself to tell you.
But, yeah, Valerie Irons is the guest tonight.
Presumably, you know, it was George Clooney before,
and now it's Val Irons, and the interview's in progress,
but it takes quite a turn.
Who guards your body from that guy?
Excuse me, this never happens.
What is that, a beeper?
Really important.
Push in dramatic, like, oh my God.
There's a bomb on the Leno set, it says in her beeper.
Yeah, and they are on the Leno set.
And Val gets up on the desk, and Jay's like,
oh, and then he's adjusting his tie,
like something racy is going on.
Something sexy is going on.
Jeez, what is this?
She's just, like, rushing around, though.
She's not doing anything.
The bomb's on the bottom of his microphone.
Listen, is it something I said?
So here she's running through the halls of the Tonight Show
with the bomb, the microphone bomb.
She throws it out, she goes out and exits.
And then she ducks, and there's an explosion.
An explosion so big it shakes Jay inside.
But they have not stopped the taping during any of this.
And Jay immediately knows what's happened and thanks her.
Thank you.
Did he suggest it, you think?
That feels like a Jay joke.
Even in the mid-90s, Tony Randall is a reference.
Like, I guess.
But it's an odd couple of years.
Yeah, yeah, another thing he could have done,
but you have to throw somebody under the bus,
but he might have, like, alt thing could be,
like, boy, I thought Louis Anderson
was the biggest bomb on our show.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, maybe he had alts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, you do if you're him.
You keep him handy.
Anyway, so it's this funny little action sequence,
and some of what the listener is missing
is just him making all these faces.
It's just, if Collision Course didn't prove
that he's not a viable action star,
this is definitely the biggest eyes, and oh, jeez, okay, yay.
But then a subtle thing that's funny about it
is that when there's that big push-in
and she realizes there's a bomb from the beeper,
it's done with the Tonight Show jib and camera.
Right.
And then running through the hallways and all
is shot with their cameras.
It actually switches back and forth
between four by three and 16 by nine.
So they're like, okay, we're filming here.
Well, I don't know, you know what?
Bringing our cameras isn't gonna be a hassle.
You think we could just use what they got?
Hey, the camera's a camera.
Look, hey, we got him.
Why would you not use our eyes?
We got him.
Mallory Irons, VIP filmed at Panavision.
You can only assume.
Yeah.
Did I look down for a second?
Was it the part with the coffee cup in there?
Oh, yeah, no, I skipped that.
Oh, you skipped it, got it, okay.
What was going on with that?
Because they find the other, the women in the agency
find on a boat evidence of this happening.
Oh, like they-
And they find a Tonight Show mug
that proves that's who the target
of whatever this plot is.
Whoa, a Tonight Show with Jay Leno mug?
So the kidnappers or the bombers or whatever
just couldn't help themselves?
So they're having a gunfight with this man,
which is just like an older character actor
who's got a pretty big, and then they finally,
they stop him and then they go inside the boat
to find the evidence and the evidence of,
or who they're gonna, who he's targeting
is this Tonight Show with Jay Leno mugs,
big blue mug, and they're trying to figure it out.
Oh no, there's dynamite, oh.
But what's the justification that Jay Leno needs to die?
I forget.
Well, I didn't watch the part.
But yeah, they pull up this Tonight Show
with Jay Leno mug.
That's like if there was a movie
where somebody planted a bomb on a roller coaster
at Magic Mountain and then like what's their target
and then they go in that bomber's boat
and they find a, I had a great time at Magic Mountain
and all I got was this lousy T-shirt.
A big XXL Taz sleep shirt.
Yeah.
Well, either they've been to Magic Mountain
or one of any mall, any of.
Yeah, any Warner Brothers store.
Yeah, yeah, one of any number of malls in the area.
And also just, I have a screenshot of Jay's face here
that I really like when Pam was on the desk.
Like, oh, look at it.
This is my favorite episode of the year.
This is our Emmy show.
Usually just the wildlife climb on the desk.
You thought he was having like a Drew Barrymore
Letterman moment.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Maybe that is the reference, I don't know.
Finally, I've been jealous ever since.
So.
Wow, wow.
That's some good Jay content.
And I think at this point we're winding it down,
but I'm happy to say that he has a little bit more
of a presence in hour long dramas.
Yeah.
Unless, are you?
I don't know, I just have,
I got bogged down in some like not so notable things.
Like Jay in the movie American Hot Wax.
Yeah, he plays Mookie in American Hot Wax.
Yes.
He's in a movie called America Thon as well,
which I've noted before because soundtrack feature,
actually Elvis Costello in the movie,
performing an original song in the movie.
Beach Boys not in it, but they performed the title song
and they have to convey all of the exposition in the movie
about how like it's a world where America has run out
of power and everybody has to bike down the freeway.
So there's a Beach Boys song where Al Jardine's
singing about no more power.
Everyone's using their bikes.
Doo-wop.
Sounds good.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good one.
Jay too, like 97, Jay is like in 89, I looked it up,
he's like 39 years old.
I always, yeah, I forget, he's like in his early 40s
when he gets to Tonight Show.
Oh wow.
So he's like 29 here in 1978,
but he almost looks like he's like got the Zemeckis de-aging.
It's almost like he looks, you know what I'm saying?
Like he's never looked young to me.
So it almost looks like they just smoothed out Jay now.
I know that's not fully the case,
but it's like he's just Jay now.
Are you showing us American Hot Wax?
This is American Hot Wax and it's not,
you can't really see it.
The story of DJ Alan Freed and Fran Drescher is in this.
Fran Drescher is in it, yes.
Which is probably helps it,
why he was on The Nanny at some point.
I'm missing that one.
Maybe.
I mean, it's not that important, but he just-
He always had that like shock of white hair,
so it was weird in Collision Course.
Oh, when he looked younger, yeah.
When he's got darker hair.
I think it's good for it.
He's a guy who Gray looks good on.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Maybe like present company included.
Well, I'm dying.
Thank you though.
There's also just stuff I've never heard of,
like a Jeremy Piven movie called Just Right.
Did you come up with this?
No, it's just-
I've never heard of this before.
Jay really only appears post credits on The Tonight Show
and he doesn't have a scene with Piven,
but this is a movie about Jeremy Piven
as a guy doing Hollywood tours
that lies to an actress about being a screenwriter
and he wears like a little outfit
when he's driving the bus.
You wear the 1930s like little bellhop uniform?
Uh-huh.
Wow.
And it's pre-Ari Gold Piven, so he's still bald.
He's in a little trolley,
but this is set in modern times?
Trolleywood tours, yeah.
And he's, it looks bad and I didn't watch all of it,
but I got bogged down like watching this bad movie
last night.
When I came to L.A. before I first came out here for school,
I really did like, I'm like,
it's probably not like the 90s version of Hollywood,
but there's probably a little bit,
and sure enough, you know.
There was one movie.
There was one movie about a man with a cap.
One disliked movie that no one knows
where it is like theme park Hollywood.
No one's ever heard of this movie
and Jay is in it at the end.
Wow.
What does he do?
He interviews a different,
it's not worth it to play it,
but he's just, it's almost like a little tag on the end
of what happens to this one actor in the movie.
Samuel L. Jackson of this movie.
Sure.
Stay, wait, what's it called?
Just Write?
Just Write W-
Don't leave the theater during the credits
for Just Write.
Assuming, actually, okay, let's be honest.
Leave the TV on while you're watching,
probably straight to TV movie Just Write.
Right.
I think accidentally straight to TV maybe.
Maybe they had ambitions.
Like, I think Collision Course.
I think Collision Course came out internationally.
Oh wow, I didn't know.
Maybe not in American theaters.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, they'll love it in Japan.
We make a lot of jokes about them.
Oh yeah, that'll be, yeah.
They'll think it's so funny.
Yeah, so I don't know.
Nothing else so notable,
but there's obviously a ton of Leno stuff still
and we couldn't go through all of it,
so I'm sure there's gems here and there we've missed.
Let's be clear about something
and if we've missed anything,
maybe we could pick it up in this episode.
Oh right.
Jay Leno's acting career is not
Jay Leno's wrestling career.
Right.
Entire other episode that is coming.
Yes.
This is the tidy way that we figured out
how to do more of what seemed to always be
our longest episodes, episodes involving Jay Leno.
So, and we're not quite out of the woods yet
because I'm really happy with this one.
Luckily, not a lot of set up for this.
I remember a kind of late 90s, early 2000s
NBC show called Providence.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, one of those like Saturday night,
like I don't know what it is.
Bunch of doctors in a little charming town.
I don't know.
Really doesn't matter.
I guess the only thing you need to know for this
is that we are going to watch a scene
involving a veterinarian
and this will be a better reveal for you guys
than the listener, but we'll clue you in.
Dr. Hanson, am I glad to see you.
Hey, you don't look so good.
Come on, let's get back upstairs.
Come on, follow me.
So, what is happening here is that
a woman has come in with her seeing eye dog.
There is a problem with the seeing eye dog.
It seems amiss and he's not doing his job.
And then I don't know if we're in fantasy land.
I don't know if the doctor, if the vet bumped his head
or whatever it is, but when he hears a voice,
like is there an intruder in my house?
And then he goes down into the kitchen
and he sees a dog and the dog talks to him
and the dog is voiced by Jay Leno.
There are some more moments of this.
He kind of ends up explaining his problem,
I think, in this clip.
You're still talking.
Yeah, we have a small window and we better take advantage.
I need you to tell me why this is happening to me.
Why, what's happening to you?
I'm in the middle of a guide dog's worst nightmare.
It's my eyes, doc.
I'm having trouble seeing.
A guide dog's.
He's a real guy's dog.
That's why he has that middle America feel.
Yeah, same to the regular guide dog.
He touched the bones from my one job.
Oh, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't eat any of the bones given to me by my first owner.
I go to a second owner that nobody knows about.
I go out on the road.
I go to other dog owners' doors and they give me bones
and that's what I survive on.
I do dog shows.
I live on my dog show money.
That's good, yeah.
I know, that's very good.
I don't touch my guide dog bones.
That's great.
Yeah, yeah.
And he owes all of those fucking guide dog bones to me.
I'm the one who got him the guide dog job.
Yeah, I'm a bitch.
I'm not afraid to say it.
A wolf rush is a dog in this scenario, right?
Yes, yeah.
What I should be called, woof woof, woof woof fucking woof.
One more little moment.
I think I'm going to have to do this again.
I'm going to have to do this again.
Woof.
One more little moment.
I think this kind of helps resolve it.
Dog Hanson, you're the best.
Lucky I couldn't have done it without a good guide dog.
You walked me right through it.
Listen, if you don't mind sticking around
for a little while,
there are about a million questions I'd like to ask you.
Okay, shoot.
Henry.
Then you don't get those questions.
He doesn't even get a question in?
No, he doesn't, which it was frustrating for me
because I don't know the show Providence,
so I don't know if there's magic in it typically.
I don't know if dogs, he seems a little surprised
but not that surprised.
Maybe dogs sometimes talk in Providence.
I don't know.
Maybe none of it had to do with dogs.
Maybe it was like, I got a lot of questions for you.
Okay, shoot.
In the Cars universe, why would there be talk shows
and tramp stamps?
Why are those things that Cars would need?
I don't know, a C&I dog.
I know what that...
What do I, yeah.
We've only, my owner can only listen to Cars.
What did Jay turn down?
This is my question.
Yeah, that I would like to know.
I think things with a lot of swearing or...
Oh yeah, maybe.
Maybe if something, yeah, it was like he had to play
against type or something and he was not,
I bet that is absolutely what it is, playing against type
where he's like a very mean guy.
He would never do it because he's so self-conscious
about being a nice guy and being an everyman.
Yeah, well now he's a little mean in Collision Course
but I think since he made the flip, yeah, yeah.
But that's when he was regular Jay, not Denim Jay
who has built a suit of denim to protect
from the harassment of his friends from back home.
The guys from back home were like,
oh, you make the big shot, which he talks about a lot.
I gave Jason a whole symposium on Jay's psychological profile
of why he does things in the car on the way over here
but yeah, it's because the denim
not touching the tights of money,
he's really worried about his buddies from back home
giving him grief about being rich and successful.
So that's why he's like, they'll go,
Jay, do you have a pool?
You've never swam in it.
Yeah, yeah, I can just imagine the guys back home going,
oh, Mr. Big Shot, there was this big pool
like in Beverly Hills.
And you're like, Jay, what's wrong with you?
Swim in your fucking pool.
There's a heat wave going on.
Yeah, so.
Jay, have you gone soft on us?
Do you, you don't eat sushi out there in Hollywood, do you?
No, no, nothing but hot dogs for me.
And I have not found a private caterer
who knows how to disguise sushi as hot dogs.
No, it's regular hot dogs.
It is what it is.
I think that's so much of the basis
for all of his odd behavior
is trying to appear normal to his old buddies.
Wow.
To the theory of old buddies.
And they might not exist, by the way, too.
He might just in his head be like,
no, you've gone, you're big time.
Well, if I didn't spend every second of my life
post-15 doing stand-up, then I might,
a guy like that might end up having a couple of friends.
So theoretically, I'm just hung up
on what my theoretical friends might think.
That's right.
You know, I'm friends with Adam Carolla.
I'm friends with some other good guys.
You don't want a friend.
Bill Maher, Adam Carolla, good guys, good guys.
Arnold Schwarzkopf, you know,
he's an ex-governor of California.
Yeah, he wouldn't have me do that
if he wasn't my friend.
We're friends.
Tim Allen.
Tim, of course, yeah, Tim.
Politically, you know, we don't see eye to eye,
necessarily, but like, his business is his business,
and what am I gonna do, you know, what am I saying?
You know, I got arrested for illicit substances
while in a car, and I don't like that,
because, you know, you could do damage to the car.
That could be hurt, yeah.
Drug driving, you know, it makes me crazy.
You could end up hitting the wrong button,
and then you do some damage to that thing.
Do you think it would be too weird to do an episode
just on Don't Blame Conan Letterman's monologue
from his show that Susser and I very often
will just text lines from this monologue,
because we're both obsessed with it,
and that's maybe what I would want to do
in an acting class, is when there's a part when Conan.
You've previously explained, it's also on the show,
for sure, I know that you've said,
you ever seen this clip, we both said yes,
then you said the whole clip anyway.
Well, now I'm doing it for the listener.
Now I'm not doing it to him.
Not on the show, too, I'm saying.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, but he's working on his piece for his acting class.
I'm working on the piece for my acting class.
I'm around the same age Jay was in Collision Course.
Well, that's a heady thing to do in an acting class.
This whole thing has been about talk show hosts
and their weird relationship to acting,
and that you are going to,
for you to get way more credits than Jay Leno has,
you're gonna use a monologue of acting
about talk show hosts to get there?
That might be the kind of ingenious meta thinking
that you need to light a fire.
I think that might be right.
So, coming soon, my one person show,
where I just recreate David Letterman's monologue.
Three minute monologue.
Or desk piece, I should say, not standing up.
Desk piece, yeah.
So, yeah, right next to each other, yes.
So, it's Mike Carlson is David Letterman.
Scott Gardner is Helen Kushnick.
Right.
Mine's called Don't Blame Conan,
which is what the clip is called.
And then to get in character,
yours is called, you do yours at a black box,
called The Player's Workshop,
and I, in character, am calling up The Player's Workshop.
You need to bump that tired old fuck Carlson.
He's already said this on a podcast twice.
Now you think people are gonna come in
and pay to hear the monologue?
I'm the hottest shit in town.
Me, this goddamn bitch with the biggest nards
you ever seen.
I just make a quick cameo in Mike's show.
It's Paul Schaefer.
I put a bald cap on and I go, no, Dave.
I hope you're not thinking about blaming Conan.
I wasn't.
You know what, Scott, you should do,
you should actually just become her
and become your own manager
and just be a phone manager.
Oh, like Trump?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, pretending you have a.
The voice is a little close.
I think if I could just run it through a filter or something.
On the phone, though, I think it wouldn't read.
Well, and you know what else I could do is like,
she's probably a speakerphone person.
Like, Marty, I'm putting you on speaker.
I got shit to do.
So if I go back here, maybe that kind of,
and if I establish, once you get me on the phone,
that I'm like deep voiced and friendly, wow.
Well, I'd love to do it.
I'd really love to be a part of your project.
I just really have to run it through my manager, Helen.
Listen, you.
Listen, you bald guzzler.
Scott Garner doesn't get out of bed
for less than 200K a day.
If you don't like it, I'll force feed you
of more brain grain cereal than you can eat.
Oh my God.
Although with the size of your mouth,
I bet you love having big loads in your mouth, don't you?
Helen.
Well, I guess we better give Scott.
What, you can't handle the heat?
Then get out of the goddamn kitchen.
I guess we better give Scott that 200K.
A day. A day.
That's an astounding day, right?
Yeah.
We don't want to be insulted by his manager again.
His manager, a real human woman who exists,
is gonna have my ass.
She keeps threatening to roast my nards on her stove.
Maybe that's what.
She says she's got a gas grill and an electric,
and she's not afraid to switch me back and forth.
Kill or be killed right now in the entertainment business.
And I think you need every leg up you can get.
I think this is the way.
Well, so apologies.
I'm gonna have to crush your show.
That's fine.
And then any other listeners out there, any other actor,
if you're doing any local theater productions,
you're dead to me.
Yeah.
And especially to Helen.
I don't want to.
I'm scared of Helen.
I'm afraid of her.
Listen, you little pussies
can't go any more minutes on this thing, can you?
You can't stand the heat.
You want to wrap up this episode, don't you?
Well, then I guess you survived podcast The Ride.
I could go another three hours.
I could do it in my sleep.
But look at you, quivering, falling to the ground,
sweating like Hasselhoff in that goddamn clip.
Oh yeah, you're right, Helen.
I bet everybody listening doesn't have the nards
to dig even deeper and join us
on our VIP Patreon tier, Club 3.
Bad news, you gotta have something bigger
than a tiny little prick if you want to make it in Club 3,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad-free, damn it.
I have tiny nards, Helen, I'm sorry.
You called me, you saw through me.
I see right through those teal shorts of yours.
Yeah.
Jason, I don't understand.
You make fun of Hasselhoff's teal body shirt,
but teal shorts on your buddy are just fine?
I don't want to bring up his nards.
I'm afraid you'll go in on my nards.
Jason, make fun of my nards
so Helen doesn't get extra mad.
Oh, nasty, nasty nards.
Was that good, Helen?
Helen likes it.
I can see you're smiling.
Very good, perhaps you could work in my office.
Oh, okay.
Salary starts at a buck an hour, 15 hours a day, damn it.
Take the job, take the job, Jason.
I don't think that's legal federally.
I don't care, keep it.
If you don't take this job right now,
I'll know you're the pussy I suspected you were
when you walked into this room.
I am, I've made no,
I've made no arguments that I am not.
You know what, you admitted you're a pussy
and I respect it.
You're hired.
Can I at least get $3 an hour?
Jason, no.
Hell fucking no.
Thought you would like it if I played a hard ball.