FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcasts may contain
photo op stress tests,
Mr. Spock's napkin,
Burbank statue rumors,
and a place to rent famous lamps.
All that plus Lamar Woods returns to chat about his time working at Warner Brothers Studio Tour
on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast
hosted by three men who are only interested in historical tours
if they include seeing clothes worn by dead actors
who have been dead at least 80 years.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always is Jason Sheridan.
Those clothes are hanging on.
Yes.
They are literally hanging on.
Oh, you mean in existence.
In existence, yeah.
You're not just hanging on like a hanger.
No, they're doing that too.
But if they are jostled too much,
like the trench coat from Casablanca will just fade.
Yeah, Scott Garner here as well.
Yeah, I don't disagree with that statement except for maybe the 80 years
because that implies that we're a level of film historian that we aren't
because 80 years takes us to 1944.
And like now let's all name people who we know died before 1944.
Jason, please, if you would.
It's got to be people who died in the war maybe.
It's got to be people who were drafted.
Well, either.
Either of the wars.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, probably a Barrymore.
There's a lot of them if you look back.
That's hanging on.
The first one without a specific name is really making us look bad.
I don't remember Lionel Barrymore was pretty old, like in the golden age of Hollywood.
Yeah.
Died in 1954.
Damn, I'm sorry.
I was so close.
In Van Nuys, California.
Should I re-edit the joke so I said 60 years at least?
Possibly.
OK.
Well, because what you're after are people who then were alive
and in old and bad shape just long enough to be on a bunch of hokey 70s variety shows.
Yeah, like on Death's Door on the 70s variety show.
Yes, that's optimal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Then barely, barely hanging on enough to tell three bad Bruce Belange jokes.
A young Bruce Belange.
To the actor who played Mr. Potter in It's a Wonderful Life.
Oh, great idea.
He looked pretty old by the time that movie was made.
He was probably one of those.
He was probably 54.
42 years old in that movie or something.
OK, the joke didn't work.
I hear there's going to be jokes that don't work when I do it at the top of episodes.
That is Lionel Barrymore.
Oh, that is Lionel Barrymore.
There you go.
Oh, Jason, you're making us look foolish again.
Wow.
Rosemary Clooney.
Oh, she was alive longer than 90s at least.
This is so humiliating.
Henry Potter is the name of that character.
Confusingly close to Harry Potter, the character who figures into the events of today's episode.
Yeah, a lot.
I think right before we get to the events of today's episode, let's get to events happening today as you're hearing this.
If you're hearing this the day that it drops, which is Friday, July 26th, 2024, unless you're hearing this many years from now, then you're totally shit out of luck.
80 years from now.
But if you are hearing this today and you're in San Diego and at Comic-Con and have a badge already, there's a lot of layers of access here.
But if you have all of those things, then certainly you need to come see us at our panel.
Street Sharks, 30 years of Jawsome done in tandem with Mattel.
We're celebrating Street Sharks and a new release of Street Sharks.
1 p.m. at the San Diego Central Library featuring special guest and completer Griffin Newman.
Yes.
If you want to complete all of your times having seen us with Griffin in the live setting, then you really got to get down there today.
It's today.
If you're in line for Hall H right now and tomorrow you're waiting to see Kevin Feige come out and announce that they've written their 17th draft of the movie Blade, get out of line and see us.
See Street Sharks.
Boring.
That's corporate.
This is well, it's corporate in that Mattel is involved.
However, we're we are at a table and we're not checking everything we say with them.
It can't be done.
Right.
That's technically it's from our mouths straight into the microphone.
I am doing a shift tapping badges when people get in.
You know, they have the RFI.
You need to tap in to get into things.
This is news to me.
This is how much of not a Comic-Con.
No, not in a long time.
So, yeah, this you watch me learn about badge tapping among other things.
Yeah, please make it down.
Don't take up a ton of time.
But it's happening today.
Yes, if you're there.
Come on out.
Yeah.
But that's that's separate from the guest who is sitting here.
Yes.
He's returning the returning guests.
He's a he's a writer, an actor, a musician.
He's a wax expert.
I would say we called him maybe the wax man last time.
We were wax guys.
We were wax guys last time, but you were the wax man.
We're waxing poetic about our days with the wax man.
Yeah.
And I'm glad that we're back in wax glory days again.
Yes.
Lamar Woods.
I don't know.
Some wax.
Hey.
I was about to say his name.
Oh, shoot.
OK.
No, do it.
Do it.
Lamar Woods is back.
Hey.
That intro.
The story of my life.
We're humiliating ourselves left and right today.
Oh, man.
What's up, y'all?
Hey.
What's up, Jason?
How you doing, man?
I'm good.
How are you doing?
I'm looking directly at Jason.
We're directly across from each other.
It's like, Jason, and then a guy with a chainsaw behind him.
Oh, old leather faces hanging out as you record most days.
Yeah.
Strange context of doing shows here.
It's so good to see y'all.
So good to be back.
I'm happy to be here.
Yeah.
Yeah, wax man in a full effect.
We're so happy to have you for a listener, any newer listeners, because it was a little
while ago.
But if you don't remember, Lamar was our guest for, and it's been long enough that I don't
remember the proper pronunciation of Madame Tussauds versus Madame Tussauds.
Was there a go-to for you?
I mean, I always said Madame Tussauds, but I think Tussauds might be the correct one.
But I feel like we didn't respect that.
We just said what we wanted.
No, yeah, Madame Tussauds, Madame Tussauds, Madame Tussauds.
Did I tell you?
I don't want to repeat stories I said in the last step, but I remember this guy, he called
her Madame Muzelle.
He was like, yo, so what's up with this Madame Muzelle?
He was like a guy from Brooklyn or something.
He was like, yo, tell me the story about Madame Muzelle.
I was like, sir, it's pronounced Madame Tussauds.
Please don't disrespect.
Is she available?
Yeah.
Is she?
I know she's a mademoiselle, not a mademoiselle.
I'm sorry, she's actually a mademoiselle.
Madame, we're on Hollywood Boulevard.
So yeah, is this, I don't know, is this some sort of lady of the night facility or no,
I'm sorry, it's a tour through Hollywood history.
Yeah.
It says someone walked in there thinking like, oh, there's a prostitute.
This is the nicest brothel I've ever seen.
I'm very disappointed.
And I say that having pounced on one of the characters.
Disappointed when they didn't move.
It is a lot like a cat house in HBO where you go through
and you choose the person you're going to be with.
Well, the lineup, that's why you have the lineup.
Oh, is that what it's called, the lineup on the cat house?
It's when it, yeah, the sex worker, you know, when everyone lines up in a lineup,
like lines up in a line.
Do they, wait.
And it's like, here is our stinky little theater that shows a weird CG Avengers movie.
Yes.
But going back, is the lineup something they say on the HBO show about the brothel
or is that something you just know in your head?
Because you really pounced on that.
I know it is a term.
I'm assuming they say it in the show.
Okay.
Right.
Got it.
I just wanted to make sure.
I just wanted the terminology to be correct.
I'm sure everything is booked online nowadays,
but I'm sure there's an in-person walk-in lineup.
I'm not sure that that's true.
I don't think everything's booked.
I don't think you want a record of that.
Everyone fill out this paperwork.
Send us an address and your ID.
Send your Venmo record.
I mean, obviously you could just write it for like a soup or something.
Roses.
Gifts.
Oh, sure.
Well, listeners, let us know by replying to this episode's tweet with your personal record.
Send us a screenshot of your online prostitution.
Yeah.
We've never.
The vans tell me Backpages is back.
Like that's what all the vans that are parked.
Backpages is back.
In LA.
Okay.
Got it.
Well, we'll review these things one day, I guess.
Backpages is back.
Is that a themed experience?
They're physical items in our city.
Maybe.
Kind of themed.
Yeah, yeah.
I can come back and talk about it.
Episode three.
Episode three, topless maids, the company.
That's a thing you'll see in Los Angeles, by the way.
There'll be like trucks driving around that say topless maids on them.
And it took me maybe 10 years to realize that's prostitution.
I was like, well, that's kind of a weird thing I have.
I knew it was ironic in some ways, but then I finally put two and two together when I was in my 30s where I was like, oh.
You were just concerned like they're going to spill caustic cleaning chemicals on their tops.
I was.
With under chests.
Yes.
Yeah.
My only association with that is the Broad City episode when they were like, they needed to make some money, I think, to get to a little wank.
Oh, yeah.
Something like that.
And they were like, we'll do this.
But they didn't want to take their clothes.
And then, what's his name?
Fred Armis.
It was just like creepily watching them.
But yeah, I didn't realize.
Yeah, I can't imagine.
I didn't realize.
I just thought it was like they just cleaned.
But I don't know.
I didn't realize they were like having sex or stuff.
I didn't put that together either.
I assume that's what's going on.
I could be wrong, but there has to be some elements.
I love that episode where it's like, it's the idea of like, you're just sitting there like you're naked.
Like, you're just watching the clean.
Like, woo, this is crazy.
Don't forget the dust on the ceiling.
That would be, Jason would do it and then BSBS be the most clean and concerned person.
I can't reach it.
The coffee mugs go in the second shelf.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to be a bother.
I've got a system.
You look beautiful by the way.
I should have written this down for you.
Do you want a drink?
Do you want a glass of water or some orange juice?
Have you scrubbed my lettuce crisper?
No one thinks about cleaning out the fruit and vegetable crispers, you know.
But so Madame T says you were here before because to refresh listeners memory, you not only, you were not on just as a fan of the organization,
but someone in the organization for many years running the show and with wild tales of dealing with the Hollywood Boulevard.
It was a big part of my life.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, we were, you know, I was telling my because I'm kind of helping this like a student like with writing and stuff.
And, you know, she was asking advice about balancing her career and her actual job and wanting to do comedy.
And I was like, yeah, like I was just talking about it today.
Like I've been that was like my career.
I mean, it was like there was no other version of like I wasn't sure if I was ever going to get into comedy stuff.
But it's like I was working every day.
Like the success of that museum was very important to me because it was like it was like a new place like in Hollywood.
I just don't understand.
I mean, that that Boulevard is still not really gotten ever back to glory.
I feel like.
But the person who does that, who actually does that, I think, well, I don't know.
Mayor Bass is up for it.
It's like not on her agenda, but someone's going to do something over there.
It's like it's still fun, but it doesn't fit.
I wish it was more like exciting, like that people really want to go there.
Well, have you checked out the redone Hollywood and Highland, which I believe is now called Ovation Hollywood?
Am I making that up?
The area where just listeners, if you haven't been, there's this whole zone on Hollywood Boulevard.
Manatee says is part of it kind of right next to the Chinese theater.
And then this pretty hellish shopping center kind of over to the right of all of that.
That is also where the Academy Awards take place.
And it's weird thinking about how all the biggest stars in Hollywood have to walk past the Hard Rock Cafe and Beard Papa on the way into the most important night of their lives.
But anyway, yeah, it's no, it's a whole other ballgame.
It's Ovation Hollywood now.
It's painted different.
Different establishments are closed instead of the ones that were closed before.
They have artificial grass.
They have grass there.
Really?
Yeah.
I gotta get back over there.
David Buster's still there?
Still David Buster's.
Sammy Hagar's Cabo Wabo's still there.
I think that's been closed for an extremely long time.
But it's not closed closed.
I think it's closed closed.
What?
Yeah.
And you know, and confusingly, there's another thing that I think is called Cabo Cantina.
Yeah, that's because my friend who works at Kimmel is always walking past and like, wait, is it the Sammy Hagar place?
And no one's ever in here.
And I'll go in and then sit there for 10 minutes and no one helps me.
And then I will just leave.
And then I look in the Yelp reviews are all like, I sat there for 10 minutes and no one helped me.
So I left.
And yet they have very desperate promotions outside like come in.
Really great drink deals.
Well, basically it's free.
Basically, just come in and then you try to and nothing happens.
It's a hell of a visit.
Listen, if you've ever been to Hollywood Boulevard in general, what a scene.
I don't know that I'd recommend it.
How do you feel at this point?
I mean, I don't I haven't been there in decades.
No, I still I mean, I still love the Chinese theater.
I mean, that's like when I would go see I want to see Dune there.
So yeah, that that's still my anchor into the Boulevard.
And what else?
I mean, the Roosevelt Hotel is like really dope.
I do like a lot of that classic Hollywood shit that's there, even like the gypsum theater.
But but the general like for entertainment for like just hanging out is tough.
Yeah, I haven't I haven't really got back to it.
I mean, my friend invited me to Dave and Busters.
My friend, my girlfriend, my girlfriend.
You should be.
We were friends.
And you still should be.
That's an important part of the relationship.
He was like, we're going to Dave and Busters.
You should meet us there.
But we have we have really good boundaries.
And I was like, and I was like, I don't think I feel comfortable.
I don't feel up to it today.
So that was my one opportunity.
But yeah, I love the Chinese theater.
I love, you know, I love the the theater.
What's the theater where they have the Kodak theater, right?
Is it Dolby currently or has it changed again?
I don't know.
So don't go there.
That's like aging.
I'm aging myself.
That's a way back.
They started holding the Oscars there.
Yeah.
I don't remember now.
There's something like a camera.
Where the slap happened.
That's really.
Oh, yeah.
They should call it the slap theater.
At the slap theater.
What about the slap theater?
It's like like how the Laugh Factory should just be called the Michael Richards place.
So should the whatever theater just be called the slap theater?
You want landmarks in Hollywood and Los Angeles at large to be named after the most infamous thing that happened?
Yeah, yeah.
That's why I want the Tello's to be just called Blake's.
Just call it Blake's.
Yeah.
Does Robert Blake own it?
No.
It's where he went to go get his gun.
Right.
I take him at his word.
It's his alibi.
Yeah.
Yes.
Proven not guilty.
So I believe it.
I believe in it.
Sure.
Wow.
Of all things, there's a Muji.
Do you know Muji?
The Japanese department store.
Right block pass like Hollywood and the Highland.
Really?
Like kind of attached to it.
And it's a lot.
They have clothes and home goods and stuff.
But I think got big in America for their like journals and pens and stuff.
Okay.
Like kind of high end stationery.
So you can get journals and pens at Hollywood and Highland now?
Yeah.
I was looking at the journals and pens once.
Let me get a quick journal real quick.
He's like, I have a thought.
I need to jot it down right now.
I was in there once and a man was kind of like, you know, picking up a box of pen and he had a sack of journals and stuff.
I was looking around.
I was like, oh, what is that smell?
And this man had very clearly shit his pants.
Oh, okay.
It was very, but he didn't look like just, you know, Hollywood.
He just seemed like a guy.
What if he had to shit his pants?
He's like, I'll just go where that happens a lot.
So no one knows.
Yeah, there.
It's time it doesn't.
So we went to the very like calm, like chill Japanese department store to do it.
And I went, I have enough pens and just put everything down and walked out.
I don't know what's going on here, but I don't want any part of it.
I want to go back to my car and go home.
I think it's important to remember anyone can shit their pants at any time.
Yes.
No.
And that is likely what the realization that horrified me of like this could be me at any moment.
But I think you would not just continue shopping.
Well, hold on.
If the pens or the notepads were very good.
If there's no one at the register, I might go ring up some, get some pens.
I might sign up for the loyalty program if no one's paying me any mind.
Sign up for a loyalty program with pants full of shit.
Well, it's already there.
I'm not coming back.
There's no coming back from this.
Oh my God.
It's an interesting spot, Hollywood and Highlands.
Yes.
But not to sidetrack too much.
I brought up that context of you and your history running the show with Madame Tussauds
because this led to this other chapter of your career besides your comedy career,
which has taken off since.
You also have kept a foot in the themed entertainment neck of the woods.
Brought your expertise from that into today's main topic, the Warner Brothers studio tour.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
That was a big deal because I was in it from the beginning.
I opened this, not the tour itself, but what they call Stage 48 is the script to screen experience.
And it was a new installment into the Warner Brothers tour.
And I got recruited over there to do it.
But it was directly related to my Wax Museum career.
This was basically just kind of like going from writing on one show to another.
It was not the same company, but people were talking.
They were hearing about me at Wax Place.
At the Wax Place I worked at, at Madame Tussauds.
And then I got recruited out of there.
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of fun.
If you're listening, audience, you should listen to this episode right after the other one
because it's basically like there was a continuation of my life after that.
After my experience at Madame Tussauds.
You were poached.
You were like headhunters.
Yeah.
Did I tell you all that?
Or do we talk about that?
You teased a little at the end of what had happened.
Yeah, basically I was doing very well.
So this is where it gets a little complicated, but I'm going to explain this only once.
And don't ask no questions.
It's like a very specific thing that companies do a lot.
But I think it makes it hard to talk about the Warner Brothers thing without explaining this part.
So basically I worked at Madame Tussauds, a company that's owned by Merlin Entertainment,
which has a bunch of theme parks in the UK and all over the world.
I was a manager there and for a long time I ran the photo department,
the people who would take your picture when you walk in.
But the people who provided that equipment is a company called Pixov, right?
So Pixov, they do them at Six Flags, at Legoland.
They're the ones who's basically operating the photos
and then sort of trying to sell you at the end.
Figuring out how to, do they give you a card with the codes that you can have the opportunity later
and storing and managing all that.
And is it green screen?
Yeah, they install the green screen.
And whenever we had tech issues, that's who we were calling.
So the person, Jessica, who was kind of like the liaison for Pixov,
we worked together for years while I was working at the Wax Museum.
So she's the one who basically, she knew me very well.
And she was like, we're opening up.
And this was like, had to be secret because they were literally poaching me like underneath Merlin's nose.
Merlin the wizard.
I'm a wizard, I should understand it.
You should have had a sense that it was happening.
Yeah, yeah, some wizard he is.
So she took me out to dinner up in the motherfucking, speak at Hollywood Boulevard
because she comes into town every quarter.
And she'll take me out because they kind of woo us, they want to keep us as clients.
And she's super cool.
And one of those girls who is always injured because she is always climbing mountains and doing crazy shit.
Like every time I see her, she has like a boot on her leg or like crutches, but she's awesome.
So she takes me to dinner at that Japanese restaurant that's on the hill up in.
Yeah.
Yamashiro.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
You can see the whole city from there.
Yeah, yeah.
I felt so cool.
Yeah, it was heavily, it was super immersive and yeah, just like transportive environment.
And they have like a giant Buddha like statue and you can walk around like the Zen Garden and all that.
Yeah, yeah.
Food is OK.
Yeah, that's probably what you're there for.
We've talked about it many times on the show.
The better the theming, probably the worse the food.
But yeah, cool place to be for sure.
So she was like, yo, I'm just between us, but we made a deal with Warner Brothers.
We're going to open up this new experience inside the tour.
So basically the tour will drop them off into this place and experience the script to screen thing.
And they're going to get to ride the Bat Bike and they'll ride Harry Potter.
And we have this really cool technology where you get to take the video home and it's awesome.
Right. I'm like, this is dope.
And but I was like really loyal to the way, you know, I'm the wax man.
I was like, I was like, Jessica, I can't believe you would try to take me away from them like that.
And she's like, I know, I know.
Look, we just love you a big fans.
I'm like, look, I don't know.
Let me think about it.
Also, I'm thinking like, I don't want to if I do this, I'm just forgetting my comedy career.
I was just like in this headspace of like, if I don't stop taking these jobs, I'm just going to do this forever.
What year are we talking about?
This is twenty twenty fourteen.
So this is like twenty fourteen and up to twenty fifteen.
Yeah. So I was like really conflicted and also like I'm such a I hate conflicts.
I was like, I don't even know how I would tell my my boss's stuff.
Who was, you know, he's I told you last, he's like a short British guy who cusses a lot.
Like I was like terrified of him.
So I was like, I don't know.
Well, I'll think about it.
So a couple of months go by, then she they make an offer and it was pretty good.
I mean, at the time, I was like, I was like, I've never seen any money like this.
I mean, I was making like fifteen dollars an hour running a whole museum.
So I'm like, I wouldn't get paid shit.
I mean, at the time, I just was more like just trying to survive.
Right. And then but the money they were offering was like, I mean, it didn't even compare.
It was just like, oh, this is like a career job.
So I went to my boss and went to his office and I was like, you know, like picks off.
They offer made me this offer.
But, you know, because I kind of looked down like a mentor a little bit to just like, what should I do really?
And he was like, he was like, how much they paying you?
And I showed him. He was like, you got to take that.
He was like, we're not going to match this.
And I was like, oh, shit.
So then I was like, so now I'm like, I got his blessing.
But now I'm like, man, I don't want to open up a whole.
I'm responsible for this site and I'm trying to do comedy.
I'm doing improv.
Like I was back when I was doing one love improv at like 11 p.m. on a Monday.
It's just like surely grinding on that shit.
And I was like, but but it's just I had no money.
I mean, I was like, I need to live like and like it was, you know, I'm getting older.
I'm like, we got to do something.
So I ended up taking it and and basically leaving.
That's when I had a whole little goodbye and all that to mount yourselves.
But it was like directly off of off of that job into this job, which was crazy.
But but yeah. And then we had it like really like I mean, you're talking from the ground up.
Like like they hadn't even built it yet.
So it was like, I don't think I have you ever done anything like that,
been in a company where something is fully opening, like doing like the ribbon cut in type of thing.
Not done. We don't really.
Yeah. Physical.
We don't do manual labor.
Well, we don't do manual labor. That's true.
We don't use our hands.
We use our voices.
Yeah. These are our tools, you see.
These are our hammers.
It's in a lot of ways harder than lifting and doing swinging things.
But is this the whole is this the zone that because I know that the tour leaves from a different like
it's there's like I don't even I don't know if I know the street,
but there's like a whole like dedicated parking garage facility, little like store, cafe, neck of the woods.
I that that's like a little like cul-de-sac near the studio.
Or is that what you're talking about? That like that was being built?
Or what is the or is it something within the were you mainly doing like the like a stop within the tour?
Yeah, it wasn't the whole the entire building hadn't exist yet.
It was like when I so there's there was like gift shops and stuff.
But this was like, OK, you're on the tour.
They take you, you know, because I had I remember writing and I take, you know,
to where I shoot all this stuff and and Batman and all that.
And then they just stop the tour and you go into this thing.
There is a gift shop in it and that but it's very specific to Harry Potter and the Dark Knight,
because those were the two sort of like experiences.
It's not where the tour begins and ends. That's not.
Yeah, it's like literally the middle of the OK.
Yeah, which is I'll tell you why that's a problem. Oh, big problem.
So OK, so they hire me. I mean, this is like crazy.
I mean, even as talking about it makes me so uncomfortable because it's like it's like it's just a lot of pressure.
It's like it's like because the company, it just felt like I got a job.
You know what I mean? It's like I got it's like I'm a I'm a corporate man.
Like I'm like, oh, doing this thing.
So they take they send me to Florida because that's where picks off is located.
The original the main headquarters.
And I had to go down there and meet the whole company and like train and stuff.
And they're like in Orlando. I bought this really like fancy.
I was like mad, man, like like it was like I had read like a red dress shirt and like a black suit.
I look fly as fuck. Like it was crazy.
But then I go to Florida and it's just I don't know.
It was just fucking so hot, like so humid and like no one is dressed like everyone's wearing like T-shirts and and shorts because they're like we know we live in Florida.
We would never dress like this to work.
And I felt so awkward because I was just in there just like I'm like, you know, like just like trying to, you know, trying to impress them.
But they're like, they're like, bro, you know, you don't need to dress like that here.
And then so what they did is they took me to Legoland and because there's a Legoland and where is it?
It's not in Orlando, but it's like outside.
It's like a winter garden.
Yes, it's like it was like an hour away from the old Cypress Garden.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because they took over it.
Yeah. And they changed it to Legoland, which is all part of they wanted their clients, but also another Merlin company.
So it was like still connected to the wax life because there were people.
The person who used to be my boss was running that Legoland at the time.
So I was trying to avoid him.
So but it was so like it was in the country.
But I was like there for like three months, just sort of like they're like training me how to do all the like all the tech stuff that I used to have to call them to do.
But now I'm learning that stuff.
You lived in. Wait, were you based in Orlando or Winter Haven?
Winter Haven. That's it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The company was in Orlando, like the heck where the CEO and stuff.
He was cool. Like his name is Don.
He was like he's like I'm like he had the slick back hair.
I was like this. I was like this is it.
It was such a different vibe from the British because Madison was such a British company.
This is like this is like a real American Florida company.
That's an hour south of Orlando.
OK, OK. Oh, weird. So did the trainer came back.
And then this guy Chris was cool guy.
He was like my kind of regional supervisor and he kind of we like just started higher.
Like we started doing the group hires and everything.
It was crazy. Like it was like I was like, man, I'm in charge.
I'm picking my staff, everything.
So I'm picking I'm doing like, you know, I'm putting it on.
This is what this will be important later when I tell you how crazy it got.
But like I'm putting on, you know, as on Craig, listen, you know, just trying to get people to come in.
And it's like very L.A., like local, like not actors or whatever, just like people who want a job.
And they were all really cool.
And like I was like really proud of the staff that I built.
It was like and I poached somebody from Man of Two Souls.
So I took one of one of our employees with me and they were mad about that.
And this was all L.A. and L.A. staff you put together.
Yeah. Yeah. You were done with Florida at that point.
Oh, yeah. I'm back in L.A. now. Yeah. After the train is over.
That was like, yeah, a couple of months, learn how to do the thing.
And now like we're all in Warner Brothers.
So then I go to Warner Brothers and also feel free to join.
I feel like I'm talking too much.
But yeah, like I go to Warner Brothers and the first thing.
Yeah. LeBron James is there doing the fucking back.
Like we have it. It's starting to get built up now.
And they gave him like a private like pre like experience of it.
So he got to like because, you know, I think at the time LeBron had a overall deal with Warner Brothers.
So he was there and he did the back bike and him and his kids and they did it.
And it was like, this is going to be fucking tight.
It's going to be awesome.
No, it wasn't.
It wasn't celebrities who topped LeBron James every day.
We start with LeBron.
It only gets better and better.
I'm like, no.
Can I ask what your height the hierarchy was and what your title was?
Yeah. OK.
So what do you call it?
So the guy, Chris, was like the regional manager.
So he was overseeing all the West Coast.
Yeah, like like there was like a theme park in Arizona and one in San Diego and then one in LA and then what we're doing in LA.
So he was above me.
And then my title was basically like what was it like?
I don't want to say store manager, but it was like I was basically like the head of operations.
I guess you are like, yeah, like something that I guess I don't remember.
But I think it was the most senior person in L.A.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Like when we do our we would do these conference calls and it would be so early because it had the people from you who worked in UK on it.
And I'm like the only I was the only West Coast person that was California, West Coast.
Right. And they would I'd be up at like six a.m.
Like on these calls. But I was literally representing.
Right. Like I was like representing this this establishment.
There was no one else speaking for it.
And that was like really intense.
But we were like they but they were all excited because I did such a good they heard about me through the man of two souls.
So they knew like I had a pretty good rep.
So they were like it was kind of like they they're like it's like Paul George going to the Sixers like we heard about you.
You know, is it going to work?
No.
Because there is a Warner Brothers studio tour in London.
You know what you mean?
I don't know that. Oh, there is.
There is a Harry Potter thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think they do something there.
And also they also work that like all the mountains all that because they have this huge partnership with Merlin.
So they're like the London Eye and the Whack Madame Tussauds in London.
They were also working on.
So I was still kind of weirdly in the world of Madame Tussauds even though I wasn't working for them anymore.
All through Pixar.
And Pixar was not previously part of the tour.
It was that like they were going to establish this new thing that is a way to get like photo opportunities.
Exactly.
With Bat-Bike and Harry Potter and others.
It's so strange.
So more of an American.
So that the tour is not just like hey look at that soundstay.
That's where they did Friends.
Can I go in?
No. Okay.
You keep going.
It's so that you get like something like physical and tactile.
Yeah.
You know, guaranteed when you take this tour.
And they do it like it's like in this way.
In this way that's like it's literally script to screen.
Like you're like it's script to screen.
It's an experience that's script to screen.
It starts with like the script process and there's like literally scripts that you can look at.
Like they have like memorialized.
And then you go into like casting.
A section about casting.
And then you get to sit on the Friends couch and like and they pretend to be like you're with your friends.
Pretend you have friends.
Yeah.
And then you go into the experience which is like the Harry Potter broom where you basically get on the broom and you're just riding it through quit.
What is it called?
Quit.
I should know this.
The Quidditch game.
Yeah.
You're right.
And then the bat bike is like you're riding through the dark night.
That truck scene basically.
So then.
But basically.
What they would do is like because they don't want it to be no separation.
So it was like we got we had to wear.
It's like everyone's wearing the uniform of a Warner Brothers tour guide.
So it's like you wouldn't as a customer wouldn't know that these people are working for another company.
It's like we're all kind of seamless.
Yeah.
Like the scripts to screen experience.
One seamless process.
The magic of the movie.
Probably with magic.
But let me tell you like that place Warner Brothers as a studio is like very when I say I am saying using the word conservative in a loose way like just like very strict like not like they don't mess around.
Like it's like very much like everything's got to be buttoned up.
It was just like a lot of rules and stuff.
So now I'm like coming in picks off guy and I got all these L.A. like people straight from like Crenshaw like you know like you know like real humans.
Yeah.
But it's like you know they got their hair dyed and they're like I mean they're like people that I would that are like OK this is this is real L.A.
And it's I mean it's so fast a fascinating and I think the people they've hired for the tours are more like attractive kind of not that my people I mean my people were attracted.
I shouldn't be talking about that.
I mean like they're like you know put together but they get like the clean cut.
Yeah like you know actor types like good posture white.
I'm trying to like I'm not trying to call them raises but but but it's like you know there was a clear difference like it would be like you go on a tour and it's all these like it's like these beautiful you know like crispy actor white actors.
And then you come into my area and it's like it's like it's like diverse and like cool like like hip street hip hop music starts playing out.
But it's like it's like it's like oh there's like a clear it's like if you were for the shirts it's like a clear shift right.
Right.
And it did feel like we were like if we felt like not a part of the thing it was like and they are so we was like in the beginning it was kind of like we were kind of I mean think of it like we were like the bad news.
Bears kind of thing like we were like they were like they weren't like you don't belong.
But it was like it did feel kind of like we was like just this like outcast a little bit like all of us me and the whole staff and everybody because one day had their own setup already and we're like coming in with this new thing.
Right.
And it was kind of like a Disney movie.
So then but no one had faith in like they just thought we were just ruining the you know the vibe.
But we were like cool like I mean you know we come in you know I'm like afraid to say I will go back and cut some stuff out if I have to.
Sure yeah.
Like one girl had it like you know it's just funny to me like as someone who like doesn't give a fuck anymore looking back.
But it's like you know one girl had she got the pants kind of low waist with this the thong showing you know how they do it when it's like it's like a little bit of that and it's kind of like you know my boss would cut the not my not my boss it picks off but the Warner Brothers boss would be like can you you know go talk to your employee.
But I'm like it's cool.
You have to have that conversation.
Yeah I'm like I don't know I'm like this is I'm like let them be I'm kind of I'm all like let everyone be who they are.
That's how I'm feeling.
Sure.
And but you know it's like we got one standard one rule like that.
So are you joining then this is like this new outpost and the rest of the tour is like Hollywood magic robots who've been doing it for 20 years.
Right.
Who are who are buttoned up and potland like because they're yeah there's a way that tour guides can be just like yeah super slick and kind of yeah like like cyborgs.
Yeah.
And you and you guys are not as.
Yeah we're like we're just more like you know just like chill like I don't know it was just a reflection of me basically.
It was just like I just hired what I thought who I want to hang out with you know not thinking about what they're doing over there.
And also I think I kind of was avoiding maybe I subconsciously avoiding hiring actors or not hiring people that wanted to be in Hollywood.
Right.
Because that was an issue for me at the Max Museum where they would always leave and go on audition.
So I was like I just want people who just need a job and want to work.
So it felt like more like the working class or whatever.
Right. But but no disrespect to either side.
Whatever you do is good.
I support it.
But so you know it was kind of like there was just this energy where they were like we ain't fucking with y'all kind of you know I mean and but we hadn't opened up yet.
So yeah so there was so much pressure on it and like it really felt like they had Mighty Ducks 3 where it's like because it's like it was like you know how to like they just want.
That's what I'm trying to think of.
We're like you know how they came into the school.
They weren't like it wasn't like it was like they were kind of like yeah we're like a ragtag group of people.
And it's like you're only at this school because they're trying to like make the school look cool or whatever.
But you guys don't really belong here.
I haven't actually seen D3.
Is that is it's like a kind of a stuffy boarding school kind of environment.
And then the yes but the but the ragtag Mighty Ducks have a different vibe.
I mean I'm going off of D2.
Is it called D3?
D2 where there's the evil Icelandic team who are a very very stiff shirt buttoned up and who don't appreciate the odd idiosyncrasies of the Mighty Ducks.
That's right.
It's a similar thing.
Yeah.
It was nothing like nothing that we need to like you know tweet tweet about or anything.
But like it was just like it was just like OK we got a different vibe coming in.
We're not we're not we're not cut from the same cloth.
It was like goodbye.
But this is the makings of a great story where you have the underdog story where you turn around and show them you had you always had it the whole time.
Man let's get into it.
Yes.
Did you have it.
Did the underdogs rule the day.
Triumph here at the end.
We just killed all of them.
Are we going to sneak in and fuck up the tour.
Because it did start to feel like the tour people versus the inside people.
The inside the studio.
The State 58 people.
But I don't know what I haven't worked there in like years.
I have no idea what's going on there.
Yeah.
This is yeah it's like 20.
Now it's we're in 2015 now.
A lot of turnover.
I bet.
Yeah.
I mean that those jobs turn over like crazy anyway.
Sure.
So we so now it's like all this pressure and people are like you know we got this big it was kind of like a friends and family kind of event where they're going to try it all out for the first time.
So I got everybody trained up you know I'm like feeling good.
We got the everything working and it's like all right.
Like this is like our big like our big showcase to show everybody who we are.
What why they brought us here because we ain't fucking around.
I mean fuck everybody gave everyone.
Yeah.
I was like man.
Fuck.
Like this is our shit.
Let's show them who we are.
You know what I'm saying.
So because it was just weird like I mean it's like but that's a weird thing anyway.
That's why I always explain that did that difference of like the company within a company.
Right.
Because you're like we don't work for them but it's like we work at the same place.
Like there's one like it's like they would even get mad.
Well I don't know.
OK.
But so then.
All right.
Here comes his friends and family night and I'll just take it as a friends and family night.
I invited all my homies from Madame Tussauds.
They came through my old boss came through.
He wanted to check it out.
So it was great.
It was great.
And then but what I didn't know it was like also supposed to be like a stress stress test
for that for the thing.
So we watched Bar Rescue.
We know about stress test.
Yeah.
That's where it can all fall apart.
Right.
Oh man.
It does.
Yeah.
It's like it's like you're stressing me out.
The bike back to the back bike tipped over.
He got crushed by the bike.
Shut it down.
Shut it all down.
Shut down.
I want it all shut down.
He flew off the broom.
He's flying around the whole building.
Custodial is using the broom to clean.
They stole the broom.
It's a broom.
It's getting real dirt on it.
Oh man.
It was great.
And so it started off great.
And it was like holy shit.
It's like it's got to be.
I mean I found out later it was like three thousand people.
Wow.
They sent through this thing.
Yeah.
I'm like why is there so many people here?
And it's also like in a matter of like a few hours.
And it's just our shit is not handled.
Our tech stuff is not handling it at all.
Right.
Because we never hadn't.
We stressed this I guess.
But we're like.
So now everyone's.
It's hype.
Like people are loving it.
So that was it's hype.
Like people are loving it like like emotionally loving this experience.
So I'm like happy about that.
But then now they can't get the video of it to take home and the pictures because it's
basically what happened is the way it was sending to the computer was all out of order.
So every time someone come up the arc my employee would have to go through the whole everything
that's taken.
Look at physically looking at them and trying to find their picture in the computer.
And it took out.
I mean it took forever.
So like I mean there was a point where there was I mean the entire tour was just stuff
right.
And it was because they kept driving people off like and it was the whole building was
packed and people were pissed like and complaining.
And it was just and I did is nothing I could do because it was it wasn't really anything
I could do because it was a tech issue.
Yeah.
And you know I'm calling them like they're all in Florida like and it's like nine o'clock
on East West Coast time.
So it's like midnight over there.
I'm like I'm like yo we need help man this is going crazy.
Why we brought you to Winter Haven so you wouldn't have to ask these questions.
We changed you in Winter Haven.
You learned nothing in Winter Haven.
I was like they don't respect women in Winter Haven.
So then I'm like yo what the fuck.
OK so now I'm like just trying to you know I'm like just telling you know just keep trying
to keep people happy and whatever.
I'm running around I'm like you know trying to help them out and jumping on registers
and stuff.
And then my boss who's like this like cool slick back guy not my picks off boss but
the guy who runs the whole tour.
He's like he's like he does the like Lamar come with me and I'm like oh man I'm like
this is bad.
He's like and he just man he let me have it.
I'm getting emotional now because I started crying like because he was like he was like
this is unacceptable.
Like you know just a full like I just you know just like I've never in my life seen
anything like this just like dressing me down.
And I was like I'm like I don't even want to be here.
I want to be a comedian.
And I'm just like in the cry ball the choke and I'm like I'm like a full failure right
here.
And then so and it was like also they all have now they really feel like you know we
really don't belong here now.
Because now all the tour guys people they're mad even though they're I don't know why they
care so much but they're like you're ruining the tour for all the people you know like
the tour has been going so well except for the stage 48 or whatever.
And I'm like yo man chill out.
Anyway so.
It's like a mean kids camp.
Yeah.
And they're shitting all over the meatballs.
Do they call themselves the meatballs in the movie meatballs?
I don't know.
Well let's just say they do.
You guys are the meatballs.
You mean well.
Yeah yeah you mean well but.
This is a test.
This is a test night.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
I know.
Maybe that's why you test.
You know it is you are right it is very strange to put that sort of thing in the middle of
the door.
Yeah.
Because I've been like on tours and stuff like the NBC one at Rockefeller Plaza.
The Rock.
In New York.
Thirty.
Seven seasons.
Do you know what it is?
I was tripped up on Plaza Center.
Both.
Sure.
And the green screen thing was right at the end.
Right.
So that if people didn't want to do it they're like all right I'm just going to leave.
I'm going to buy a t-shirt and then leave.
I'm going to buy a today shirt.
I'm going to buy my full length Matt Lauer tee.
And then leave.
It's a long tee.
Oh it's a tall tee.
So it's nearly his full size.
Get this your fired mug which I will cherish always.
This phrase will always mean a lot to me.
I'll never have different feelings about the host of this show.
But yeah right in the middle then it's holding up the back half.
And it was it did everyone get the pictures and video or was it like a money ad.
Oh yeah yeah.
Oh no wait.
Were things included?
It was free.
Yeah it was free.
Okay.
Yeah so nobody was spending money but also that also means everybody wants to do it.
Like nobody was skipping it.
So it was just like yeah we were giving them away but it was like it was like fuck like there's nothing we can do here.
And then then we just started having to eventually we got it fixed.
But it was by that point it had already died down the guest count and stuff.
And so we failed that test man.
I was like I'm about to get fired.
This is crazy.
And then and then we we know we we know the CEO the guy Don he had to come out like it was we were in trouble.
It was crazy like so he came out and had had it like you know calm everybody down and like we had this meeting where it was like you know like kind of what went wrong.
You know like the inquiry was that call when you when you go back like the mission and I love it.
It's like it was like what the hell happened.
It's like ultimately it was like also like it wasn't really on me.
You know it really was just like the equipment just couldn't handle all that people.
It was just like not made for that.
So like you know in a normal day you're not getting a thousand people coming in.
Right.
So but ultimately like we squashed it all got our shit together opened up and then we started making money money.
And like it was just like now we're like number one.
We end up becoming number one and out of all the picks off thing and everybody was doing it because we were like because I knew what I was.
I mean I knew what I was because I brought a lot of the what I did at the BACS exam over to it.
And it was like the price is everything was just perfect.
Like we were just like cashing out and everybody was like dang like nobody could say shit.
You know because we were like now we're fucking taking out on you.
And then and it was great.
And then that was like probably two months of doing that.
And then my friend Phil hit me up like yo are you still looking for a job?
And then like I was and then I met with this show runner for Survivors of Morris just thinking you know long shot like he read my pilot or whatever.
And then he's like hired me.
And then I like basically was like I got to start work next.
It was like the next week.
So I just left.
I was like oh and I was like yeah I was like I was like a real Hollywood situation where I was just saying I'm out of here.
I'm out of here y'all sorry.
My dreams just came true.
I was like literally script to screen like I was like I'm out of here.
So and so I left my they were all happy for me.
I mean the picks off we were happy because they knew I want they knew they knew that about me.
But I was like but it was like I had like I felt bad for the employees because we felt like we built a little community and I was like I got to go.
But so I haven't been back since so I don't know what it's like now.
Did you ever like fantasize that you would like be on the actual tour where you're on the tram and then you just step off with like a packet and you'd be like I'm in this building now.
I work here.
I'm a writer.
Yeah.
I do fantasize about.
I might I probably have more because I have less of a connection to that place but more.
But I have more of a fantasy of becoming a wax figure like famous enough one day.
That's where they like put me in my uniform.
I got the manager like with the walkie talkie and they could be like that's he used to work here or something like that.
That would be cool.
But that's if you write if you write the pilot and the smash hit show about working at the wax museum.
And then your character is so iconic the wax museum guy and then the character and you and characters put into the wax museum.
That would be in the spot where you worked and where it was all based on.
I mean it's funny because the possibility that is not that unlikely.
Yeah it's like very like I'm working on something when the wax man has nine successful seasons on Peacock.
I just I did this tour a couple of months ago.
We got invited to this or I got invited to this.
I don't know why actually.
Usually I have to beg to get invited to things and this just came into the into the inbox.
I think weirdly I thought this had come through Lamar like this episode was brewing and he hit up his contacts and he set us up with some sort of VIP.
You had nothing to do.
I have no news to you.
All right.
OK.
No thanks required.
Yeah.
Really. So I was just out of nowhere.
I don't know.
There's like a mysterious benefactor.
I think there's some listeners over there.
Maybe.
But no one like no one like DM to me like hey heads up I'm going to send you an invite to this because this was a big event.
Ben Menkowitz was there.
This was a whole thing.
I sat outside.
There were there were pastries.
I didn't know that all this I knew like there was going to be a little presentation of something but there was like food and stuff.
Yeah.
Is this because they have recently opened something with TCM components.
Yes.
Well I don't know.
That's why the thing happened.
That's not why we were invited because it's not.
It wasn't because that stuff is new that there's new like this videos that you watch that are TCM.
Yeah.
I'm just saying that is why people were invited but I still don't know our direct connection to why we got invited.
I don't know.
Is that maybe they list the you know.
We're the top dogs in the entertainment game and they got new TCM stuff.
Yeah.
They probably went out to talk about it.
We're doing it.
Geez.
Well now I feel pressure that we're fulfilling the other end of some kind of invited.
Well at the very least I didn't beg like I usually have to on the show.
I beg for I beg for press invites the things on this.
I'm pathetic on the show.
Please let us come for free.
We want a free drink please.
Your knees are unscuffed.
You haven't been on the ground groveling lately.
Your knees look fantastic.
Thank you.
I mean I'm also curious if the employee you know if there's anyone still working there that I use.
And I hired everybody.
Carl worked there.
Oh yeah.
For a little bit.
I don't know if you know.
Carl Turner?
Yeah Carl Turner.
Wow.
I had all the homies for a little bit.
Vlad and like yeah they were all it was it was fun for a bit.
What did Carl do?
He was he was taking the pictures like you know he was like you know like right go to the left go to you know.
Because let me not to get too far away from what Mike's talking about but like I as you've been talking I looked up like Warner Brothers Studio Batpod.
And what I found is that people have posted this on YouTube that it's you get like a minute long sequence where it's footage from the move from Dark Knight like you were saying intercut with like you know here's real footage.
And then there's it'll go to a kid and he's on the.
What do you call it?
Batpod?
Batpike?
Yeah.
Yeah there you go.
But like the cameras like the cameras moving and the bikes moving it actually blends really well.
And you can tell that the kid is getting direction like look up look down okay now make a face like whew like wipe sweat off like oh barely avoided that truck.
Oh and then he's shaking his fist like oh hey Joker get back here.
So that's just so Carl's doing that stuff.
Yeah.
Directions for kids.
That's something we came up we came up with the direct so I could take a little credit for that like.
Here's some of the things you can tell them to do.
Right.
But Carl in that you know these guys you know they're performers so they're they're having they're like killing it in there like because they're directing them to all types because if you don't tell them they'll just sit there.
And then they'll see the video and be like I don't want that.
This thing.
I don't want me listlessly riding a batbike.
Looking sick.
Also kids you probably get like they're excited to do it and then once they get there and there is a light on them.
They're terrifying and your entire family's watching you like I mean it's pretty well.
Things like that then terrified me so much more than like a full audience today.
You like things like that when you were a kid feel like I am now I am suddenly doing a recital at Carnegie Hall and everybody paid to come here but I forgot to have a talent to do.
Right.
And I'm going to I'm going to be laughed at and I'm going to pee my pants like anything like anything of that nature.
That's the video I did with my mom in Disney World the Gloria Stefan song and I'm sitting singing karaoke with my mom on this video you bought it at MGM Studios and I'm just grabbing my penis like I'm just like nervously touching myself.
I'm not like stimulating me.
Right.
I don't know what to do.
Like you're just like I don't.
Yeah.
That's terrifying.
So I was like I remember being like freaked out that like focuses on me and I don't know what to do.
I don't know the song.
I don't know what's going on.
Any memory of having to tell an awkward young boy please don't touch your crotch.
Did that happen for you?
Yeah.
It must have some at some point.
I don't think you were allowed to do that to you.
You can't have a Suicide Squad picture and doing that.
Yeah.
I feel like parents back then would just be like they had no respect for like you might not want it like it was just like stop being a little like just get out there.
It's like like as if like forcing you to do it.
You'll realize this was fun.
Right.
Thank you for making me do that.
But sometimes I mean I mean this was an interesting thing because it was people from all over the world were coming there.
So it was like a lot of people from different countries.
I'm not sure how much of them were like clocking like it was I'm not sure what they were clocking but it was very interesting seeing different cultures of stuff react to Batman.
Right.
I wonder if it's still the bad.
I mean that feels like almost dated at this point.
This is do we know what you did.
Is it.
Is this stuff going at all.
Yes.
OK.
It is still going.
I did not do it.
I guess I should have done it.
But they have.
Let me see.
I have a photo of it here.
Yeah.
This is the same.
That's kind of a bad photo.
But that's the bad bike.
OK.
That's green screen.
That looks the same.
It looks exactly like it.
Yeah.
This is also a good old demonstration of green screen at all.
So the children are at Hogwarts.
And typically, unless there's students who've been held over, there could be a 40-year-old
stuck at Hogwarts, being held back many, many years.
Actually, if you count the Christopher Nolan one, there's been three Batman's.
Right.
There's been an Affleck and a Patton.
Oh, since you mean?
Huh?
Since then?
Since then.
So there's actually a number of Batman.
And hundreds of children who've taken this tour.
Technically, the Batman number is 3,000.
Yeah, yeah.
That'd be still my favorite Batman,
the Dark Knight classic, I guess, at this point.
But I do wonder if they were to change it up
to something else.
Like, what's up, Warner Brothers?
They got all types of properties.
I mean, you could do anything.
Oh, Dr. Pimple Popper.
What's all the stuff they like now?
It's hard.
I mean, a lot of it's been thrown in the trash can,
I think, at this point.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Zazlov.
He's throwing it away.
Is Vanderpump in that umbrella?
Oh, maybe.
I don't remember the ownership of Vanderpump.
You're gonna be in the bar yelling at someone.
Everything is still Batman heavy,
like DC heavy, Batman heavy.
They have like models of the Batman Forever Batmobile,
which is cool.
They have the original, they have like the Keaton outfit,
the Christopher Reeve outfit, and then-
Oh, that's dope, yeah.
And they have, I got very excited,
they have Mr. Free, Arnold's Mr. Free's outfit.
Oh, yeah.
Which is really cool, and it was lit up.
I remember, I used to, some of my awareness of this area
and the tour zone in general is that I worked
in this building across the street from the lot.
Wasn't Warner affiliated, really.
But like, the nearest Starbucks, I think,
technically was the Starbucks in the tour.
Or was it like, there was, all right,
there's one a little bit closer,
or there's one that's a little bit further,
and if we all take a walk over there,
we can go see the Mr. Free's costume before we get our coffee,
and we would always choose that one,
despite it being further.
Yeah.
What a little boost to the,
that's better than a caffeine boost,
is seeing the real, the lit up Mr. Free's 100%.
Yeah, it's so cool.
It's actually a pretty dope costume, I mean.
Yeah.
That movie was insane.
It's fun, though.
It also looks a little shittier than you think
when you're really like up close.
You're like, oh, this is like,
oh, it's falling apart a little bit.
But like, when it's lit up and you take a picture,
you go, oh, it looks awesome.
Yeah.
But they've got like, they got a lot of new stuff.
They have the Pattinson Batman costume.
Oh, so they, yeah, I should take the tour again.
They have the Batmobile.
They have, they have, from Batman versus Superman,
they have Robin's costume that he was wearing
when he was killed by the Joker hanging up here,
if you remember this from Batman versus Superman.
I have never seen this film.
I don't think I knew Robin was in this stuff.
He's not.
His costume is hanging in the Batcave
that Batman has hanging there so he reminds himself
of when Robin was killed by the Joker,
but Robin is not in there.
Jesus.
Gotcha, gotcha.
That would make storyline in the 1980s in the comics
that they kind of use as background material in the movie.
Yes, that Batman wants to torture himself even more
by having his dead partner's outfit hanging.
Yeah, I'm just gonna physically put it up
in a way that's like, he's gone.
I don't want to bring us down,
but does he do it in a whimsical Joker way
or does he just shoot him in the face?
Well, it's unclear.
He has, he's spray painted on it.
It says, ha ha ha, jokes on you, Batman.
So I guess it's open to interpretation.
I don't think Affleck says exactly how it went down
in that movie.
Okay, so that's the Joker whimsy,
but the rest was just.
Yeah, and they got the big part of the plane in here,
the Batplane, from which one.
Did they take it to the Gilmore Girls set?
I feel like that was something I remember doing.
Is there a Batplane in the Pattinson?
Is there a plane?
I didn't actually identify, this is embarrassing.
I didn't identify.
I can't remember.
Because it's not the original Keaton.
This is like a newer thing.
I think it's maybe in Dawn of Justice or something
there's a Batwing, or one of the Snyder movies.
They do have the Keaton Batmobile.
That's my ship.
I remember the McDonald's commercials.
Oh yeah.
Weren't we recently having a conversation
about which Batmobile we would have sex with?
Yes, that was a topic on this show recently.
I don't want to make you get in on that,
but do you have a thought?
It doesn't have to have sex, just attracted to.
Oh yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like the sexiness of it.
You don't have to go near it.
Probably the Pattinson one, I think.
Oh really?
Can you pull it up?
I don't have a good photo of the Pattinson one.
I was reminded because I said the Keaton one
because it has that kind of big nub up front,
which I feel has.
It's very phallic.
Yeah, I think that has some.
But it could be a nipple as well.
Yes, you can interpret that.
You can interpret the nub however you want.
It's a single nipple on the front of the Batmobile.
Well of course the nipples come into play
in Batman and Robin.
Well that's true too, but we're not,
yes, that's a different point.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, that's a whole different sex act.
A pioneer of, yeah, before the Schumacher nipples,
the car had one giant nipple,
and that's why I think I have to declare it
the most attractive.
I mean that was my first thought,
but then I was like, I really like the one
in the Robert Pattinson one.
Or maybe I just like Robert Pattinson.
Maybe I just wanna have sex with Robert Pattinson.
You're inscribing Pattinson.
Sure, yeah.
It's cool, cool weird.
Just a couple, they have the Toon Squad jersey here
from the first Space Jam.
Nice, nice.
They have a big Selena.
Did they have Algie Rhythm's bomber jacket
from the second Space Jam?
Don Cheadle's Algie Rhythm bomber jacket.
I didn't see it there.
Hey wait a minute,
there was a problem on the server
when Lamar was trying to do his thing
and do the Friends and Family.
There was a big mysterious tech problem
on the Warner Brothers lot.
It was probably the nefarious Algie Rhythm
from Space Jam.
That's played by Don Cheadle,
who lives in the WB server verse
and messes everything up.
From Space Jam 2, a new legacy.
2015.
He was in there, that was.
Dude, are you implying he escaped
and in the current news site,
he is responsible for the worldwide computer.
Oh yes, the recent, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I think, I don't remember how.
They never stopped him, right?
See, I don't know because I fell asleep
the hardest you could possibly fall asleep
while watching Space Jam, a new legacy.
So I don't actually know what became of.
Me too, I fell asleep right before I found out
if they won or not.
I know the game, but I'm like.
They won, Bugs Bunny dies
and then comes back to life
and it's not really, it's like,
I don't know what happens. Oh yeah, he does die.
He comes back to life, like a camera cut later.
I think a computer deletes him, maybe?
Yeah, you were asked to feel emotion.
You were asked to, with all of your experiences
and feelings about Bugs Bunny,
now process Bugs Bunny's death
and then unprocess it approximately two minutes later.
Yeah, the next scene, he's just kind of standing
in a street corner talking to LeBron and his son.
Never mind, that was pretty crazy.
Yeah, did you see the old penguin
in the watching our basketball game?
Are you guys gonna play together one day?
Maybe. They'll get it right
with the third one, I think.
Yeah, who's gonna play,
who's gonna be the basketball player?
Oh, I don't know, it could be Brawny.
Yeah, that's true.
Let's bring Jordan back.
Yeah, yeah, it's so wild
when you think of how young basketball players are,
you're like, yeah, Jordan could totally do it.
He's very physically healthy.
He could totally just play.
It'd be a great way to follow up on Last Dance, too.
It's Last Dance Mania, just take it into Space Jam.
Today's Space Jam 3 is more of a documentary.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he's just doing an interview,
he's like, so then I had to go back to fight the Monstars.
Oh, yeah, wait, I wanna, yeah, yeah,
and the Monstars said they were gonna turn my friends
into theme park attractions, and I took that personally.
Yeah.
And if I see Isaiah Watt Thomas there,
I'm gonna fight him.
Oh, man.
That's a pretty good idea.
Talking trash on Bill Murray and.
Yeah.
I would totally watch that.
That sounds good.
Why didn't you even do that parody,
they're all about Space Jam.
Yeah, that sounds like a slam dunk.
That's the thing, actually, when I, yeah, well, hey.
What'd you say, Mike?
That's a good thing.
To bring up.
Actually, that is a thing that I think about
when we pass by,
because one of the studio in Burbank,
very close to where we all live,
that is a thing that I think about now when I pass by it,
is that the tidbit in The Last Dance
that when he was filming,
when Jordan was filming Space Jam that they,
that was one of his, he's like,
hey, I need to stay in shape,
like the movie, whatever, huh, fun,
but I have to be the best basketball player
in the world again.
Can you just build me a court?
And they go, yeah, sure.
And then this cut to this immaculate facility
where all the greatest players,
everybody traveled to make a point
of doing these cool private games.
And that's a thing,
I've watched that part of it a lot,
just like that's so crazy that on this studio,
there was just Michael Jordan's private basketball facility
where he'd go play four hours after filming all day.
That's a thing I'd like to know.
That's the thing I would ask about if I were on the tour,
is where was the private Jordan facility?
Oh yeah, that's a great,
because I'm sure they don't have it on the little plaque.
And is it somewhere that now official building
has been built, or is that a long-term question?
Yeah, I wonder,
because they must probably turn that stuff
into other things, I guess, at some point.
Yeah, yeah, a lot of like,
any lot has the situation,
I feel like I was recently talking about how like,
if any studio lot had a giant Western Sets area,
that got blown up a long time ago
to build a fancy new office building or something.
There's a thing I wanted to bring up
while we're talking about the tour.
There's only one,
I've only seen one source on this ever.
There's a YouTube channel I think
called Pardon or Dust or something,
that brought up how,
I don't know how far this got,
but in terms of like,
tourist attractions on the Warner Brothers Studio tour,
have you guys ever heard of this,
that there was talk of doing something called
Superhero City?
And what Superhero City was gonna be,
is that like,
I'll get hyper-specific and local.
If you're like on the Hollywood Way olive entrance,
basically like,
Hollywood Way is a big long street,
takes you all the way from the airport.
From very far away,
the street is such that for a while,
if you're driving south in Burbank,
you are facing the famous Warner Brothers water tower,
where the Animaniacs live.
Which is kind of cool that like,
that's like looming over the city.
Yeah, yeah, it's kind of fun,
because it's like icon from our childhoods.
But so on that side of the studio,
basically they were gonna like build around that
and make that kind of a centerpiece of it.
But that you would drive onto the studio that way,
because currently it's all private,
unless you're doing the tour.
But they were gonna take a big strip on that side of it
and make like sort of a city walk.
A little bit of a city walk,
like a tourist attraction,
with stores and restaurants and stuff.
And as part of this,
gigantic Batman and gigantic Superman,
as tall as the surrounding office buildings,
looming over the studio,
and a full Batcave that you would have gotten to hang out.
With like immersive attracts,
I don't know,
maybe some little experience like this too,
where they film you or whatever.
This is a thing that would change the fabric of the city,
because it's like a pretty stately kind of classic lot,
as it is now.
There's nothing as stupid as giant Batman and Superman,
like rewarding.
It's very much like how there were these Disney plans.
Michael Eisner wanted to build a hotel
that just looks like a gigantic Mickey Mouse,
that would have been straddling Riverside Drive.
And everybody was kind of like that.
What's that?
Oh yeah, yeah.
Everybody's staring,
yeah everybody's staring up while you're under Mickey's crotch.
Oh man.
I love to,
I feel like Burbank is just like no to all that stuff.
Maybe,
because I think,
yeah there's kind of,
I don't know,
there's a style,
I would like to think,
there's a style classiness to Burbank,
and that's all pretty stupid.
But that's all kind of of the nature of now,
that there's a big minion overlooking the 101.
That feels like a pre-minion situation.
Right, right.
But they did those,
a couple years ago,
they did like Halloween mazes on the studio tour.
Or I don't know if it was on the tour,
but it was a separate event.
But you would go,
like they made Arkham Asylum in one of the sound stages.
They only did this one year though.
2018, yeah.
So I don't know if it was a bust or what.
And it's like pre-haunt,
it's like right around the time
when I started going to these.
So I'm a little upset that I didn't get to do this,
because it feels like they didn't want to do it ever again.
Yeah,
what could have went wrong?
I mean,
it's a cool idea.
I know, it's pretty, yeah.
I don't understand that.
I mean, I guess like,
I just feel like people,
it's like the same thing that happens in Hollywood too.
It's just like,
they green light a show,
and then the people who did that got fired.
And now there's new people who are like,
I don't want to do that.
And then they kind of like kill an idea.
That was cool.
This is really the thing.
Can executives just keep their jobs for longer?
For God's sake.
It's the story of anybody,
we know all the biggest shows in the world and movies,
like then the executive got fired,
and then we couldn't do it anymore.
I know.
Garbage,
just keep these people in their jobs for longer,
so people can work,
God damn it.
I mean, Burbank,
they've been,
different superhero statues have been,
or at least the Batman one's been popping up,
and I heard tell that there's maybe a Green Lantern
going up at the Empire Center.
Like there's going to be more.
Really?
Yes, I think Green Lantern and Wonder Woman.
I can't remember.
I think it's Green Lantern outside the tour.
Outside of the new episode where you,
that's like the entrance, exit point
for the Warner Brothers story.
The visitors,
and that's where the Starbucks you would go to.
No, it moved, actually.
No, it moved.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
There's like a commissary building.
It used to be over there,
and then they moved it kind of across the street,
which that's a little pro tip hack.
If you don't want to pay for the tour,
but you just want to kill a little bit of time
and see some themed bullshit,
it is free to go into the visitor's center,
where you don't even have to go in
to see the Wonder Woman statue,
and then you can go in and get
the most expensive Starbucks you could imagine,
like a big brass Bugs and Daffy,
and the store you can just walk around.
Like, we were killing time before dinner one time.
Like, you want to go see what's in there?
And then like, I don't know,
there's like a big Harry Potter bell or something.
If you like Harry Potter, do you know what,
oh no, it's a big cup.
It says Wiz.
Anyone know what that's about?
No.
All right.
Like the Wiz?
Not like the Michael Jackson's Wiz?
No, it's not.
I don't think it's that,
unless I'm vastly misinterpreting.
No, I think this is a Harry Potter thing.
It's probably the cup.
The cup.
Is it the god blade of fire?
Could be.
This really shows you.
Well, yeah, that coffee shop thing is true,
because when we were doing interviews,
like we would, I couldn't get into the lot
because I didn't have access yet.
That was like the one place we would go and meet,
because I would do stuff there,
and that's in that Starbucks,
and it was like, yeah, you can just walk.
It wasn't like...
It's a little bit of free stuff to see, yeah.
You just gotta do the security screening.
That's why it's a hassle.
The current thing, and the one I used to go to at work,
is that having to get a security screening
in order to get a cup of coffee is very silly.
But worth it, if you get to see Mr. Freeze.
I do see that one pop up on the app every now and then,
but years ago, I knew someone who lived over there,
because there were apartment buildings
kind of around the Weir brothers' lot,
and they would talk about walking
to get Starbucks in the morning.
I was just like, where the fuck is there a Starbucks
in that part of Burbank?
And it turns out, I think they were walking to the visitors
that they were walking to that Starbucks.
It seemed like you were very suspicious, or angry,
or wondering if they were lying.
I was feeling this.
Why are people lying to me about this?
It's a good thing the desks were built,
counter built into the wall, or would have flipped it.
Jason, would you be excited to know in the gift shop
you can buy a Wonka's jacket from the new Wonka movie?
Which, the Chalamet Wonka?
The Chalamet Wonka, yeah.
You can buy his jacket.
It looks a little big.
Yeah.
It does look a little big.
It was on sale.
It was marked down from, I think it was $119.
It is now $19.99.
Wow.
That's so cheap.
That was a few months ago at this point.
That's an ambitious ask, I would say.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Oh yeah, I forgot, sorry, a couple things real quick.
They have, in the tour, they have Leonard Nimoy's
cloth napkin from a Big Bang Theory episode.
Cool.
Where he says, live long and prosper,
and he says it's done.
It's on one of those mobile vacuum things.
Yeah, it looks like that, yeah.
To Sheldon, live long and prosper, Leonard Nimoy.
It's a napkin.
Oh, it's a napkin on the Roomba, the famous episode.
Did you ever, did anyone ever go,
anyone ever go into the prop-like soundstage,
not soundstage, but whatever, the area,
they keep all the props that are rented out
for commercials and TV and movies.
Yeah, I went in there when I did the first time.
I don't remember it too well.
Yeah, because it's interesting if you've ever gone
in anything like this, it's just,
there'll be a room of chandeliers.
There'll be a room of lamps.
There'll be a room of just weird stuff
that just get rented out, like old telephones.
There's just a row of them.
People come in for an old movie, and they go,
I want this, and they sign it out,
or whatever the money is, and I'm like,
I'm keeping my eye out for exciting stuff for me,
and the most exciting thing I saw,
and they didn't mention it, the person didn't mention it,
but the big skeleton-like skull head from Batman Returns
that the goons wear at the start of the movie,
that they're on the motorbike,
do you guys know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was with my friend Luke, and I think he goes like,
oh my God, look over there, it's the skull head.
And I was like, yeah, it is,
but it was like hanging out in the corner,
and I'm like, does anybody,
why do they even have that in here?
Is somebody gonna come in and rent that?
Like, why is it here?
But that is a cool part of the tour,
because they do have some things with,
I think we could take photos in there,
but they have some things that'll be like,
ah, this is the telephone from My Fair Lady, or whatever.
Yeah, no, the telephone from My Fair Lady.
I don't remember.
Maybe like an early one.
They don't know what to do with it.
Yeah, yeah.
So wait, did you take the full tour?
I took the full tour.
I listened to a full presentation
about the magic of the movies with Bang Mankiewicz.
Wow.
I was eating pastries,
I was having like a little orange juice or something.
We're gonna end up with a very jealous Jason.
105 degrees out, it was just the sun,
they didn't have any covering over us.
Oh really?
Oh my God.
And then we got, then we stood up and we're like,
okay, because we're not sure what was happening.
I think we were taken there on a tram
into this area of the back lot,
and then we were like,
oh, I guess we're gonna do the rest of the tour or whatever,
and then a tram pulled up with Bang Mankiewicz
and everybody on it,
and a whole marching band playing like 76 trombones
in the big parade.
What?
Yes, my dream.
They did a full like little song and dance.
The dream.
I do trust that Jason has long referred to this
as the dream.
And a full marching band.
Yeah, I know.
Jason wasn't there, my God.
He was invited to go.
I didn't know there was gonna be a marching band.
Wow.
I couldn't even go.
He invited you?
I invited him.
I'm not keeping that to, I forget why.
But that's the, you know, when you hear about it,
like Warner Brother, okay, okay.
If the headline had been a 76 trombone parade
playing 76 trombones in the place where the music man
was filmed, apparently, I have learned
from looking at Wikipedia's today.
Uh-huh.
So, we got a little show.
That's what's happening right now.
And then, yes, we got in the tram
and then they did the whole thing.
They, you know, pointed out sound stages
where things filmed.
And then we drove by the Conan Studio that's empty.
Oh, yeah.
Is it just empty?
It's all been over there.
I don't know, it just seemed kind of empty.
I don't know, I didn't go in, but.
Weird.
But the like prop area, or whatever you'd call it,
the prop house is not so far from there.
By the way, Mike, the place you and I met.
That's right, yeah.
We started this whole, that's the biggest
Hollywood history.
It really is.
It really is, yeah, shooting a bit for Conan
that's not directed.
Goat, yeah, wait, if we've never said this on the show,
that it was like, yeah, when I worked,
because I worked on the lot for the Conan Show,
and I got a call for a bit like,
hey, the writer is gonna do this, he's busy,
so you need to go downstairs, there's a guy,
and he's like jumping onto a big futon made of ramen, go.
And I didn't know what it was,
or what was considered to be the successful version of that,
but that was Mike.
I was there, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was a really thrust together,
and me having to pretend that I knew what was doing,
or what I was doing, or what to tell you to do.
Yeah, it was fun, you worked there,
but I was like, I actually was here a couple,
like a good amount of times.
Was that your first time there,
or did you, they called you?
The thing you directed, yes, that was the first time.
Wow.
But then I was there for a couple meetings,
there were other things that happened in that building,
so I was like, oh, it's that building,
and no one's there, I don't think.
Did it seem like I knew what I was doing,
and that I'd carefully crafted the ramen bit?
Did I present a professional front,
as opposed to I had no idea it was happening
until 60 seconds before?
No, I think I was probably like,
ooh, I have to really impress everyone
with my jumping onto this thing here,
and I was not paying attention
to if everybody else was comfortable.
I remember I was worried that I was gonna hurt my teeth
biting into the ramen, which is crazy,
because ramen is so brittle, it's not a big deal,
and then, yeah.
I remember referencing that I kinda made a meal
out of putting my hands above my head,
and I said it was like a Mike Hanford move,
that's what I remember saying.
Yes, which did get my attention.
You were like, oh, I know who that is.
You know Mike Hanford, all right.
The beginning of the connection.
This guy's on the level of friend of Hanford.
So that was sad, seeing that.
It's like driving by your...
Let's get coffee sometime,
because we have to go through a security check, though.
Yeah.
So yeah, the prop place was right by there,
and we got out of the tram at that point
and walked through it, which is fun.
So yeah, I don't know, the tour was cool.
How long was it overall?
I know it was shortened.
We were not being given the full tour,
but we were probably done.
Once the marching band came out,
it was probably 45 minutes.
Where did the marching band?
Was that on the back lot?
Was that in a music man type environment?
Kinda, it was on the fake streets and stuff.
So we were all set up in this sort of section.
I don't even know if I have a good photo of it.
We were all set up in this section
of like one of the back lot areas,
and then around the corner,
we all kinda walked and waited for the tram,
and that's when the marching band came down.
This is amazing, my God.
Yeah, that's like a Beyonce concert.
Yeah, yeah, it was fun.
Again, on the tram, and I forget,
I should really know his name.
They had like one old actor there,
one guy who was at least in his 80s,
who was like a cowboy.
He's like good blazing saddles and a few other things,
and he was there,
and they didn't have much for him to do.
They were just like, here's an old guy
who's just seen things.
He had like his boots on,
and oh, well, very nice to be here, or whatever.
But then he's on the tram at the front.
So I swear they were all waving something
in their hands or something
as they turned the corner in the tram.
So like, Pam Mankiewicz, this guy,
this old actor guy, and I was like,
oh, this is really good, this is really funny.
Wow.
What a strange little show you got.
I gotta, yeah, it was really, it was really good.
What was Ben doing while the marching band was playing?
Was he just tapping his toes?
He was in the tram, like waving something around.
Like he was trying to like be part of it.
Streamers, banners.
Streamers, something like that, yeah.
I should remember.
They really put him to work.
They really did.
Yeah, they made him do physical effort,
something that we've said we try to avoid.
Exactly, yeah, so.
And this aligns right with the time
when like Steven Spielberg and a bunch of other directors
had to call David Zaslav at Warner Brothers
and go like, please do not shut down Turner Classic movies.
Oh, that's right.
Maybe, yeah, yeah, so.
Is this whole thing in response to,
like let's give it a presence on the tour,
let's show the work committed in a public way to.
Showed like David, like pictures of my face
being like excited when I saw the marching band or something.
And he's like, well, I will keep around the classic films.
I love that pocket.
Oh yeah, I love it.
Maybe David invited us.
He listened, he zapped off.
Hey, well, if you're listening, David, we love you.
We approve of everything you've done.
Please don't look at any old tweets.
Yeah, yeah.
We like that you deleted Batgirl.
We heard that it wasn't releasable.
And we're sure you're right.
Bold decision making.
It's just like, he just hit delete.
Wait, he deleted our show.
He didn't believe us and he deleted Podcast the Right.
How could he even do that?
He doesn't know.
Yeah, people seem to love this new Bad Boys
and that's the same directors,
but I'm sure the other Batgirl was unreleased.
Must have been, yeah.
There's no way they could have sold a Batman property of any kind.
Who would ever see that?
They put the tour, they have all the stuff they didn't release.
The deleted room.
Yeah, that's called the deleted room.
Yeah.
Would you come out of retirement
to put together the photo op for the deleted room?
I would totally do that.
Yeah, in fact, I would love to.
Oh, it's the Western digital hard drive with Coyote versus Acme.
It's like, we've got to do a stress test.
No, I can't do it.
I can't do it no more.
Oh, it's USB 2.0, not 3.0.
It's not going to be able to handle the strain.
Yeah, you're going to have war flashbacks
if we keep this bit going.
I'm going to have to take a nap after this.
Yeah.
Yeah, geez.
But yeah, yeah.
So you wouldn't necessarily choose to go take a spin
on the studio tour for fun, given your legacy of history.
I don't know.
It's hard.
Like I said, it's such a weird time in my life.
But I don't know.
I would have to like people who have someone
have to come in town and really want to do it.
Yeah.
And I'd be like, all right, let's do it.
But you do it in disguise or something, to be sure.
Yeah.
Just like, hmm.
I mean.
Dressed like Wonka.
I would love to.
I mean, definitely.
Just a quick 1999 jacket.
It's like, this is a great tour.
But yeah, I think I would do it just to see that I can't believe it's still.
I would actually just care who still works there.
Yeah.
I would love to see the employees because I did like them a lot.
They were like really cool people.
But there's no way they all still work there.
People are quitting left and right.
It was crazy.
Like even within that time, I hired like so many different people.
But yeah, man, it was long.
I remember feeling long just when I did it, when I had to do it just for fun,
for just to experience it.
Too long?
Because this is like, I don't know, for anybody who might visit or consider
taking this kind of thing, you've got the Universal Tram Tour, which I did.
And that's a very like theme parkified.
That's a 50 minute.
That's a very different beast.
That's like kind of a ride.
And it's not at all what a like studio tour is where you're on a smaller vehicle
and you're getting out and you're looking at stuff.
But that's going to be a longer experience.
Something you got to commit to for more time.
And there's not like a ton of these either.
Disney has never offered one, which I've always found odd,
because I think a lot of people would be interested in seeing the Disneyland.
Yeah.
Paramount does it, which I don't know anything about.
Paramount seems like maybe sort of a dry one, a little bit.
I don't think they have anything that compares to the back.
That's my favorite lot.
The Paramount lot is my favorite lot.
It's a cool lot.
Yeah.
I like that lot.
That big like sea they can fill up.
You probably park in what can be turned into that you can fill it with water.
And they've got like a backdrop, like a blue sky.
That's cool.
It's the coolest gate to drive in.
Yeah.
It feels like a very Sunset Boulevard, like really in Hollywood.
You're in the 40s.
Yeah.
I like the Disney.
I mean, we were all doing a strike.
It was like a lot of like, what lot do you like?
What lot did you like?
I was at Disney.
I mean, it's close to me, but also a lot of shade.
And like I am mad at Disney, but also I kind of like looking at the architecture,
like seeing the Robert Graves building with the dwarves holding it up and seeing the big Mickey hat.
I mean, I'm mad at them, but I'll see the Sorcerer's hat, though, too.
I think Disney was my favorite, too.
Yeah.
And then just the sort of the time it takes to go around.
You would go around once and you would like, it would.
That's a healthy walk.
Yeah.
I feel like I was getting exercise.
I think a lot of other lots like Netflix had very little,
I don't think I ever went to Netflix and there was very little like space to.
Yeah.
You can march here.
You can march in this like one block little, it's like a little dog run.
But Disney, you got to, yeah, that's like, that's a big story.
Yeah, it was just like good exercise.
Then I used to go to the CBS Raffer because that's where I was like really,
that's where all the old white dudes were because it was like they would like not,
they would be, it was like no talking.
Just everyone would have fun.
There's more like of a, I guess I was like, I want to interact with people.
That's when I like hold my, like hold my sign and do my laps.
And then this shit ain't fun.
Yeah.
You weren't there to party.
If you go to Netflix at Paramount, it was like lit.
It was like a party over there.
Yeah, yeah.
It was crack killing karaoke and shit.
It's crazy.
Okay, what's happening?
Which one did Imagine Dragons play in front of?
That was Netflix, I think.
Weezer did Paramount, right?
Oh, Weezer was Paramount.
Weezer was Paramount?
I forget where.
Wow.
Yeah, I wasn't there.
Boy, strike nostalgia, huh?
Those were the days.
I know.
I feel like I was making some other, what point was I heading for?
I don't know.
It's just a very different thing that you're getting.
Like a two to three hour really getting to explore studio grounds as opposed to the
Universal one where it's a very crank it out kind of like theme park version of it.
What do you think, Mike?
Do you think you'd recommend the experience to listeners who might
want to take a look around a studio?
I, yeah, I think so.
I mean, if you're in Burbank already, if you're going to be here especially,
I mean, I guess if you're making a trip, there's enough stuff
if you're like into that Burbank, I would recommend in general.
You don't have to go to the Empire Center, which is a strip mall.
Basically, this is what we talk about on the show.
I would say absolutely do not go to Empire Center.
Yeah, don't go to that.
That's where we go to Target, but it's not a place you should visit as a tourist.
But then also there's another school of thought.
I love it.
I like the airplane thing too of all the airplanes on the highway.
Well, I think that's why the Green Lantern is going there because he's like a pilot.
He's a pilot?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know anything about Green Lantern.
It's a tribute to Burbank's legacy of aviation.
Perhaps that's the thinking.
I like the Batman in the AMC that batmastache is awesome.
He's cool.
That is good.
Yeah, it's silly, but it's good.
I mean, there's a school of thought that is like you come to Burbank
and you tour podcast the rides Burbank.
Oh, 100%.
You see the marquee of what's the club?
Laffer's, Chuckler's.
Flapper's?
Flapper's, yes, where Jay Leno plays every week, seemingly.
You see the hallowed Burbank Sears,
which has come up on seemingly every episode for the last few months.
I mean, that's just a choose-your-own-adventure kind of tour.
So that's what this show can do.
You've got Raising Canes over there.
But this is a...
Yeah, how is that Raising Canes?
I was so over-hyped initially, but then I find myself craving it constantly.
Yeah, it really grew on me.
Yeah, does it live up to the...
Because I feel like it shows up in places and then giant lines, the clogged streets.
Well, I was Mr...
Because I had been Mr. Hot Chicken out here for so many years,
and I was like, well, it's okay or whatever.
But then I more and more would drive by and be like, maybe I'm going...
No, I did eat it and I was like, this is just chicken tenders.
But every time I see it, I'm like, turn in there.
I think the secret of Raising Canes is sort of the same in and out secret of consistency.
I think that you get a very consistently good fast food meal every time you go there,
and because of that consistency, it makes your brain go,
I know exactly what I'm getting.
Because Taco Bell, McDonald's, you can get bad ones of those.
You can get the B team working one night.
Raising Canes seems like they always have the A team.
Yeah, they're always on their shit.
Yeah, limited menu.
They only have one thing in different ways.
Like in and out as well.
All right, there's a chicken tender place at the crypto.com.
Yeah.
That shit is awful.
I was like, I was going to get a hot dog, but the line was long.
And then I look, I don't know why I didn't take the note that nobody was in line over there.
But it was like a Raising Cane, but it was like, it wasn't Raising Canes,
but it was just like chicken tenders.
And they had, that's all they had.
I was like, all right, chicken tenders fries.
And they immediately gave it to me, which is like, I'm like, this ain't going to be good.
Yeah, it was dry as hell.
It was crazy.
They've got a really good promotion going with iced tea right now at Raising Cane.
So they have pictures of him in the drive-through.
He's like saying hello to you.
And I'm like, this is great.
Wait, iced tea, the wrapper?
Yeah.
That was very confusing to me because I was like, oh yeah, drinking iced tea.
I really did not think, when you said him, I was like, Cain, who is Cain?
No, Cain is the dog.
Cain's the dog?
Cain is native to the owner's old dog.
They've got like cardboard cutouts of him in the drive-through if you drive by,
like going all along now.
So that's extra.
I'm like, oh, this is fun.
I think I love Raising Cane's.
If iced tea likes it, I like it.
Can we justify Raising Cane's as a themed experience too?
Is there enough there because we don't want to step in on the Doughboys area?
We'd have to get an episode that's almost not about the food at all.
Is there enough?
That's really how, in terms of jurisdiction, that seems like enough.
It's like a living drive-through haunt where iced tea jumpscares you.
He's like, there's only one sauce, you got to get that sauce.
Because if you don't get that sauce, there ain't no barbecue sauce, no honey mustard.
The sauce is a big part of it for me.
Yeah, I've been working on it.
I had no idea this would be the first place I would do it.
Yeah, wow, what a debut.
You got to test it out before Edinburgh.
I just sent this to my friend.
He's like poking out at it.
Yeah, wait, so Lamar, what's he saying there?
He's like, yeah, I got a little slushy for you.
If you don't move this line along, I'm going to throw it in the window.
It's just the kind of life we live at Raising Cane's.
Burbank, it wasn't always at airports out here.
I just like him going into facts about Burbank.
Yeah, so far in across the street, it's in the end of true romance.
Iconic scene for movies and TV.
I'll pay tribute to Burbank's legacy of aviation.
If you don't move this car along, I'll kick you so hard you go flying through the air.
That Sears has been hollowed out for some time.
But yeah, man, I was going to say I totally lost my thought.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
I think for sure, if you're coming out here, do it.
Because it's also like it's a crowd pleaser with like the family.
Yeah, we're talking about the tour, Raising Cane's.
Both, both Raising Cane's.
Yeah, they're in the same area.
The tour, yeah.
I know what I was going to say.
But grandma and grandpa love the tour.
They love the movies.
It's enough big stuff.
And then there's like the friends stuff that everybody likes.
Oh wait, was that part of your experience too?
The friends, this was like, it's not, you aren't in the place where
the show was filmed.
Oh, that's something you can see is the friends stage.
Right.
But like, yeah, it seems like they've tried to maintain
that there's some central perk replication.
Yeah, they got the real one and then they have, they recreated it.
And I was part of that.
I mean, I didn't help build it or anything, but that was like just the cameras.
And you can kind of like, there's like a fake camera.
I don't know if it's fake, but you can go in there and see yourself on TV or whatever.
Oh, gotcha.
Okay, okay.
But yeah, that was really dope.
Because I love friends.
I mean, I love, I guess I would go on the tour because I do like a lot of Warner Brothers shit.
Yeah.
It's weird when you realize like you're a fan of a corporate brand.
Like it's like, oh, I like what they do.
Like Disney, all that shit.
Well, they, you know, from the Warner Brothers studio store,
I don't know if you grew up with any of those around,
like when they had a mall store, like the Disney store,
I think that did something to me of like, maybe I like the brand.
Wait, Batman and Superman and Sylvester the cat.
This all lives as one thing to me.
I understand.
I like Animaniacs, which kind of ties it all together.
They meet those characters and parody those characters.
So I have enough of that fondness, I'd say, for like 90s Warner Brothers vibe.
And then you add Big Bang Theory on top of that
and you can go in the gift store and buy a notepad that says Bazinga on it.
Now we're talking.
Sheldon, both middle aged man and young version.
I was going to say, were you ever at Disney when they,
when Danny Trejo was out there handing out water bottles and stuff?
No.
That was cool thing about Disney.
I just remember that.
Oh, yeah.
Ice tea, maybe it was from ice tea.
Trejo was around.
No, Mr. Trejo.
He would pull up in like a dope ass like lowrider
and like just chill on the road and just hand out water to everybody.
Wow.
But I said, well, I did, though, see, I couldn't believe that I was at the place
at the time to see on day one where a classic car pulls up and who should get out.
But Mr. Classic Car, J. Leno.
Oh, wow.
Two boxes of donuts for 500 striking raiders.
Get a guy out of the car left really quick.
But then I'm like, how did I manage to be at the spot where I assumed the only J.
Leno appearance of the strike happened?
I mean, that felt very special.
That's very special.
Not to pit Leno against Trejo.
Yeah, I mean, look, I mean, you have no shot.
I mean, yours is way better.
It depends on who you ask, I think.
I know, yeah.
I mean, it was cool.
Not everybody's life revolves around Leno the way mine seems to.
No, I was excited to see Danny.
That was cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Hollywood history, it's still all around us.
You can experience it in these places.
Well, I am curious how much of what you set up is still around,
or if at least that your spirit of being a little more casual,
if the ragtag vibes that you tried to set up there, does that remain?
I think Pixar in general probably kind of has that energy anyway,
even if I wasn't there.
So I can't imagine it just fully flipped over and changed.
But it's got to be, I feel like if I went back, I feel like I would know.
I wonder if I, because you probably didn't,
before I told you that difference, you probably,
they looked like all just Warner Brothers employees, right?
You didn't, you weren't like, this feels like a different company.
Yeah, I didn't know.
Yeah, like I want to, I'm curious how seamless it is,
or if it's like, if I would actually see the like,
there's a, okay, there's a company shift here, right?
When I walk into this building.
But, but, you know, man, that was a, that was a beautiful time.
Thank you for making me relive it.
Yeah, thanks for, absolutely.
Yeah, I know.
Besides the stress test, it seems stressful to remember your own stress test
and having to relive the stress test.
But besides that, it's a stress test for me to talk about it.
I mean, yeah.
You did it.
You made it.
You survived podcast, The Ride.
Lamar, what do you say?
The Ride of this ride.
This is my favorite ride.
Okay, we're so glad.
Well, your friends asked it, so we'll go the heavy again.
Let's exit through the gift shop past the now marked down in 1999 Wonka jacket.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, just check out my album, Highly Sensitive Person.
It's on Spotify, Apple, all the streaming platforms.
But if you want to buy it from me and support the kid,
just go to www.lamar-wiz.com and you can buy the album directly.
Either way, I'll be happy.
But just listen to it, though.
That's the vibe.
And then follow me at Profmatic on IG.
Yeah, Profmatic.
And if anybody wants to get in touch with you
to set up any different photo opportunity things,
are you open to that or is that done?
Absolutely not.
Do not talk to me about any of that stuff.
It's a past chapter, a past chapter.
You relived with us.
Thank you.
But in the past.
Yeah, I'm still excited about Wax.
I think that was a bigger part of my life.
Because that was like my first seven years in LA.
So I'm always going to have love for a man of two souls, for sure.
Sure.
And yet you didn't go with, as your musical name, The Wax Man.
Yeah.
I might do a tape, like a theme tape called The Wax Man.
And yeah, it's all wax themed.
Put it on wax.
Different persona.
Yeah, literally.
Wax on wax.
Chris Gaines.
Chris Gaines or Garth Brooks's alter ego, Chris Gaines.
You could have an alter ego.
Yeah, The Wax Man.
I play the harper or something.
But check that out, it's dope.
It's about being sensitive and anxiety and stuff like that.
Wow. I can't promise that the same topics
will be the core of our panel about street sharks.
It'll be a little bit more aggressive than that,
what with all of the slamming and such.
But nonetheless, come check that out again today,
possibly Friday, July 26th, 1 p.m.
at the San Diego Central Library Comic-Con Badge Required.
And besides that, for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
That'll do it, I guess.
Well, let's take a picture or something
and you should give us some guidance as to how to do it well.
Wipe the sweat off.
Lean left, lean right.
Yeah, I'll help you out with that.
Thank you, appreciate it.
Good to have a pro.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram at foreverdogteam
and liking our page on Facebook.