Hey, Club 3 subscribers.
If every word I said could make you laugh, I'd talk forever, especially because you voted
for my topic, the Beach Boys episodes of Full House in this month's Club 3 poll.
Mike Jason, how you feeling?
Hi, fine.
I feel fine.
The Weirdos made it farther than I thought.
That's really the victory.
Yeah.
I don't remember where we left this.
Mike threw a last-minute candidate in, which is a puppet band that's been playing with
Coldplay in recent, but you just caught in an unrelated, the video was about somebody
falling off, they're trying to invade their stage and falling, but you're like, wait,
there's puppets.
Right.
And they are called the Weirdos, maybe this is something to throw into the poll.
This was a much better faring than Madam, than your previous puppet campaign.
Yeah.
Yes.
My theory is that the Henson connection made a lot of people interested.
You say Henson, and I think a bunch of people go, their ears perk up.
If Madam was Henson, I feel like maybe I could have gotten another 10%.
But this is all, this is in hindsight.
If Hillary went to Wisconsin, what would have happened?
These are all hypotheticals and we don't know what if Madam was a Henson, would it have
made a difference?
I don't know.
Would Henson make a version of Madam?
Maybe they did.
Maybe if I say now we're only going to talk about Madam, who was a Henson created Madam
that was in a specific kind of show and we put it back up on the poll, maybe Madam runs
away with it.
I don't know.
Are you proposing that we lie about the source and history of Madam just to prop up, to
lie about Madam's background?
But I'm saying there's been, what I should have said, there's multiple Madams, I think
after Wayland Flowers passed away, there were different people doing Madam.
Perhaps one of these times, Henson company made a Madam for someone.
Perhaps, perhaps.
Well they have a puppet workshop.
We can perhaps all day.
They could make anything, they could probably make anything if you pay them.
Well, they could make Puppets of the Beach Boys, therefore keep doing more Beach Boys
episodes.
I'm saying hypothetically, this is my theory of why the Weirdos did better than most of
my choices do.
That's what I'm saying.
I think the world of puppeteering is pretty specialized and pretty small, so the likelihood
of a person who worked for Henson working on a Madam at some point is very high.
Well, I'm not saying we're going to do it, I'm just saying perhaps.
We are trying everything we can to get Madam on.
It's possible that one of Madam's finger flaps was brushed by somebody who elsewhere had
their hand up a Ralph.
I may know a guy who did a post-Wayland Flowers, Madam.
I do know, well yes, I have the same source, there's a source.
These are the saddest humble brags in history.
Your source also contacted me about this situation as well.
I may know a latter-day unknown operator of Madam.
A later Madam, a later operator of Madam.
Post-Madam, post-Wayland, P.W. post-Wayland.
I know somebody who disposed of a moth-eaten, unwanted old Charlie horse from Mallory Lewis,
Sherry Lewis' daughter, who has a strange Instagram now.
Well, that's a brag I would be interested in at least.
I will say this about me, most of my name drops in real life, not on microphone, do sound like that.
That is true, because the amount of times that I've said on the show and then seen you in reality say,
well, you know, I used to work for, and I already don't remember the name, I used to work for so-and-so, Crosby.
Catherine Crosby, I was going to go Mary's Widow.
And then I wait for the moment where people are like, OK, I know Crosby, but Catherine, I don't know.
Is this a daughter? Is this an ex-wife? Who are we dealing with here?
Second wife, yeah. Yeah.
So my name drops are like this.
This is what I'm most proud to name drop in my life.
Are you almost, do you know that people are not going to know these things,
which gives you the in to do the second sentence, which like pulls them in deeper?
Because, you know, if you say it all in the first sentence, then maybe the story is done.
That's a good question. If you want to psychoanalyze me why I do it.
I think it's funny that in particular, I think that's funny and I do want to talk about it.
That's probably the blanket way is like I do want to tell that story because I can't really believe that it happened.
I can't believe that I had many days spent with Bing Crosby's widow working on her like live show
that she performed to the Magic Castle and other places.
By the way, potential future Club 3. Yes.
Hear Mike's Catherine Crosby stories.
That will be better than my high school story.
Well, it's not amazing or anything.
But not as good as the Crosby nights, you know.
What? What?
What do you know?
You spent many days, you know, but one of the many nights.
I don't know.
30 seconds ago.
I appreciate it now.
I thought if flying Mike had an illicit affair with Hollywood royalty, I thought it would be fun.
One of my favorite.
I thought it would be funny.
We don't get enough credit for like we're not just idiots.
We're craftsmen, you know.
Us?
Yeah, all of us, you know.
We shred these boards, you know.
What boards are we shredding?
Well, we are technically on a stage right now, you know.
This is an elevator.
You keep introducing.
Jason keeps introducing new words into the sentence that makes it harder to tie it all together.
Yeah, what did the joke refer to?
We shred these boards.
We shred these boards like so many before us.
A joke was a little disconnected.
Then he got to the point where he was saying we don't get enough credit for being craftsmen.
Then he also said that what we're doing, we're technically on a stage, which I guess that's true too.
If they're listening, they get it.
Now, yes, you know, we're part of the tradition of Tin Pan Alley, you see.
We who have done 10 live shows in seven years.
This is like that is like something like Bono would say on stage or something, you know.
That's my main association.
I stay.
Yeah, well, you know, Tin Pan Alley, Andrew Lloyd Webber.
Anyway, here's what we've been working on.
Well, if you're looking for another, sorry, I made you turn down the levels due to my.
Yeah, well, it might happen later if I start.
We don't get enough credit for.
You know, I'm glad you turned the levels down because at some point I will be doing
an impression of Brian Wilson's acting, which is loud.
So I'm glad that you've adjusted.
And I'm but look, I'm heading in that direction.
But I want to just before we close out talking about the poll,
the runner up Olympics opening and closing ceremonies, fun area.
I like that.
But there's something bigger going on here.
And this wasn't everybody, but I definitely saw some comments to the effect of
I don't like any of these choices.
I was going to bring this up to you.
This is the worst group that we've had.
And Mike, I'm sorry.
I've been hitting you already in this episode.
Mixed with a lot of hitting and other ways.
This isn't my fault from this choice.
No.
But well, look, I saw the list of what you could have chosen.
There were arts related things or a number of things that you could have picked
because you sort of got a second choice the way we do it.
There was the weirdos and then you got another one and you're like,
I guess I'll go with the Beverly Hillbillies album from 1965.
I knew it wasn't going to win.
But not only did it not win, it is now and I've crunched numbers on this.
It is the lowest performing topic in the history of the club three poll.
It is a three point one percent down from like a three point two eight percent.
I guess.
But this these comments about hating all these choices were all the choices, not just this.
I agree.
I'm just saying I'm just giving context that in addition to this overall thought
that also we did have this month the lowest performing topic ever in the world.
Do we know what the actual voter turnout was for this time?
Because perhaps were that there was a depression of voting because of the poor topic.
So that's why my obscure choice didn't fare so well.
This is what happens during presidential races that have low voter turnout.
That is that's a good point.
That is something that happened except here where there was very good turnout
and a lot of people.
OK, well, OK, that's information I needed to have to know.
Now, actually, if we're getting really granular here, there was a lower turnout.
OK, and literal people, 44 people voted for the Beverly Hillbillies album.
OK, if we're going now, this is not this is percentage wise out of the whole did better.
The literal people, Ford's Garage, the Ford themed restaurant was 32 people.
So if we're lining them up, literally, that is the lowest in terms of turnout.
OK.
They were in the if we saw 32 people in the room.
OK, so 44.
So I guess you have that to tout that.
But you only lost percent.
I will not pander to the audience.
I will not with things that go right up to things that an actual like 80 to 90 percent
of the audience would be interested in hearing.
I want in a world where it's already niche, where already the winner is the Beach Boys
on full house.
I went I will not be niche in general.
I will be niche within a niche within a niche.
I will pick next time if somebody proposes a less known TV show, a more obscure TV show
that has an album, I will choose that.
OK, then my mother, the car album actually comes out.
Is there such a thing?
I don't think so.
But if there is, I would choose it.
Yeah, I think now the challenge is for Mike to go see if you can go further.
We're building our T levels on the opposite end.
Can you get lower than three percent of the vote with still
within within the listener has picked?
Yeah, I believe I can.
Yeah. OK.
Well, this is a new other.
If you're this is like kind of like playing.
All right.
I'm playing, you know, just the zeros on the roulette.
But, you know, you can do different kind of tax here.
I'm doing just odds, whatever.
Right.
You know, if listener, if you don't think you can win the club three poll,
see if you can give Mike fuel for the lowest, the new lowest performing topic ever.
I believe I can get.
Let me let me call my shot here.
Well, see, the problem is now people are maybe going to do this to ruin my fun.
I believe I could get zero.
I believe I could find a topic that is so unappealing to the vast majority of listeners
or every listener that they would not vote for it.
And we can't even start brainstorming because then they'll know.
Yeah, exactly.
We can't.
And it can't be next month.
I don't think we can.
No, they'll forget about a very fun challenge.
I believe I can get a zero.
Wow.
I believe I can do it.
And listener, if you have a suspicion that you think that might be Mike's zero attempt,
I mean, it's up to you.
You can ruin the zero attempts if you're mad at Mike.
But if you want to really support Mike, don't vote for his topic.
Right.
Unless you do want to hear it legitimate.
I think everybody needs to be honest.
That really is what it is.
Everybody now listening has to be honest.
Do you want to hear this or not?
So just don't vote for it if you don't want to hear it.
They still have to propose it, too, which is so great.
I guess, OK, OK, OK.
I have to amend this now.
It has to be one.
It has to be a vote of one because the person who proposed it likely will vote for it.
You're right.
Yeah, we can't put zero expectation on it.
One, zero would be impossible unless they just did it for fun, which is fine.
But one is what I'm going to call a shot.
I have no objection to this.
I picked the Donkey Kong Country cartoon because I thought it was nice.
And that didn't dance with third and fourth for a while.
It was going back.
It had the edge on Weirdos for a little while.
One percent, the Weirdos squeaked it out to third.
Well, and look, and I have to commend you because that is a thing for merely,
what, 25 years ago, 27 years ago, as opposed to look, I'm putting it all on you, Mike,
but mine, which did win, is still a topic that's about old men appearing on an old sitcom.
So I think that's where the overage came, maybe, is a lot of sitcom.
I don't think any of them were theme park related.
And what I'm driving to is a solution to the problem.
If there was the general feeling that this group was amiss and we need fresh blood,
I think it's time to put our fingers on the scale.
And I reached out to a potential guest, and I have his permission to say,
and it still requires parliamentary procedure.
Somebody has to submit this.
But we are open in August next month to Disney Lorcona with Nick Weiger.
Wow.
He is game.
You give a good Weiger wow to this.
So if that is something that we want, that's a way that we can shake things up.
Weiger Lorcona, presumably, will be in the next.
Right.
So some but still a listener has to propose it.
Yes, I think so.
And then there will be a formal vote as well.
Yeah, yeah.
So feel free to, if you want to hear your name read on the show,
get to it first.
Throw it in there first.
I would love a professional polling company to do some polls for our listeners,
because sometimes I feel like there's three different warring factions of listeners.
There probably is one faction that's just like whatever you lunatics want to do is fine.
Yeah.
But then there's people that are like befuddled by like,
why are we talking about full house?
What?
And then there's other people that are like, why?
Like, I do think maybe it's actually more than three.
Maybe there's like 10 different factions that are like,
well, I love theme parks in Jay Leno.
So this is my podcast.
But I do not understand why we're talking about some of this other stuff.
Yeah.
So maybe there's going to be some overlap on the Venn diagram.
I think what I think is fascinating about the polls is it's where all of the factions
kind of like get to fight jockey for control.
We get a sense of how many of what faction are out there.
Yeah.
You know, now we get it.
All right.
So like roughly, it's not the whole audience that just
who subscribes and who subscribes to Club 3.
But of that, only 3% want to hear about the Beverly O'Billy album.
Yes, 3%.
I should do a podcast solo just for the 3% for 50 people.
That's the show they want.
And the show I want to do, perhaps.
Maybe that's what I should be doing, just a show for 50 people.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it would be those 50 people.
And again, you didn't quite get the 50 on the numbers.
So that would be that's in success.
You get to 50.
A couple people maybe forgot to vote.
There's always that.
That's true.
Anyway, we still need other topics, though.
Hey, you might be vying for second place because Weiger Lorcan might be the one to beat.
As for this month, Augustine Macias, Club 3 suggestion.
In honor of the Beach Boys documentary on Disney Plus next month, this is back in April,
the boys should discuss all the episodes of Full House with the Beach Boys.
And I was thrilled to see this, I think.
I mean, not for obvious reasons, but also I think this is a very good way to section off.
We've talked to some TGIF stuff.
I did a Beach Boys episode.
I think this is probably the smartest way to kind of corral a bunch of Beach Boys stuff.
It's definitely its own thing and plenty to talk about right here.
I'm also really happy that you said, due to the documentary, talk about this other thing,
because in referring to the Frank Marshall directed Disney Plus documentary,
which came out in May, which I have watched, and it stinks.
It's fucking awful.
And I feel bad doing this because I've already gone at you a bunch, Mike.
However, your boy fucked up.
Mr. Marshall fucked up.
I think this guy should stick to not giving speeches because this was the dullest,
most corporate AI produced.
Yeah.
I hated the Frank Marshall.
Did you guys watch it for any reason?
A little bit of it.
My dad watched it and he said you were right about it.
Yay.
Thanks, Mike's dad.
I did.
Would you say that if you went in, you maybe were an alien that just landed in your flying saucer
and you put Disney Plus on and you watched this,
would at least give you like a basic explainer or was even like not suitable for that scenario?
I think it is acceptable as that only.
Okay.
You'd want just like a general, I don't know why this would happen,
but if some teacher in your school who's as out of touch as me,
assigned you a report about the Beach Boys,
and you needed to process a bunch of information really quickly,
maybe the documentary would be a good way to soak it all up.
But if you want any level of, I think it's so bizarre because post Get Back,
I feel like there was a boom in like retro music documentaries,
but Get Back is all about like granular and nitty gritty and like,
wow, this goes so deep and we're seeing these things just at their origin.
And it's like flipping the story we thought we knew on its head.
And then this is just like, well, you know, Dennis was the only surfer.
You know, I said, why don't we try a song about surfing?
And Brian said, all right.
It's like there's nothing in this you haven't heard a hundred times.
It's almost like reheated leftovers of a documentary.
Yeah.
I saw some like a film critic complaining about like Disney Plus
keeps doing these like A-list documentaries, either subject matter
or behind the person like Ron Howard did the Henshin one.
And it's just like they're not nailing it.
I have no idea.
I'm not the person to assess the Henshin documentary.
When I was complaining about this on our group chat with Griffin,
where Frank Marshall is the topic frequently,
he said, well, I'm worried about this with the I don't know where he landed.
We haven't talked to him about that, about the Ron Howard.
I'm like, I'm not the person because I'm not a Henshin encyclopedist.
I watched him was fine with it, but I could see maybe somebody who's
super Henshin obsessed is like, no, they completely brushed over this and that.
And it didn't the same thing I'm doing because I'm a super fan.
Sure.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's fine for me, though.
I don't know of all the things.
But you're right, Jason, that that is a big area.
Or these like it's I feel like all the streamers are doing documentaries
where the participants or the subjects are participants.
And that's a great way to make it a warts and no warts.
No warts whatsoever, a no warts documentary.
If there's new footage of the subject in the documentary talking,
generally speaking, you're not getting a full story.
Yeah, usually, usually.
Unless that's part of like they really like the idea or the pitch of like,
I'm really going to tell this crazy story or this crazy period of my life.
The thing that drove me crazy about this documentary, it all builds up to well,
for the first time in years, because the boys don't get together a lot.
And it's like not everybody's in great shape.
And so what if we reunite them at the spot where they took the first album cover
in Paradise Cove and Malibu?
And what if we got them together, put guitars in their hands and just
see what happens, see what they talk about, see what they do.
After all these years in this shared history, I wonder what they'll say and do.
And keep wondering because they don't show you any of it.
Like the cameras like jibs away.
Really?
Yes, that is how it ends.
And not only that, I found a press junket interview where Al Jardine,
one of the Beach Boys, is sitting with Frank Marshall and that comes up.
And he turns to Frank and says, yeah, why didn't you show any of the stuff we shot?
That was some great stuff.
We did a lot of good.
He yells at Frank promoting the movie about why would you end it that way?
Oh, because you had to walk down a lot of stairs to get to Paradise Cove.
And all these old men were just wheezing for an hour.
That's very possible.
It's very possible.
These are old.
Hold some items now that you've climbed.
Could be it.
Well, I don't know.
It doesn't seem like the world is particularly opposed to showing
ghastly footage of 80-year-olds on a giant stage.
Maybe now that's been normalized.
That's entertainment.
Now release the footage.
Actually now, Mike Love is running for president.
In 40 years, like Get Back, maybe that footage will come out and we'll get to see what that
beach day was like.
Maybe I can do it.
And you can do it.
And then make the narrative like enterprising by then 68-year-old filmmaker usurps
a deceased hack Frank Marshall.
I'm going to get it back.
It's my Get Back.
This young whippersnapper who probably spends all his money on freaking avocado toast.
That's what they're still saying.
They're still thinking about it.
In the year 2052.
Stop buying coffee.
Yeah, in 2052.
Stop buying coffee out.
Stop eating avocado toast.
That does seem accurate.
I also think we're probably heading for a world where the boomers are still alive somehow.
Where Gen X are starting to die off.
But only boomers are alive.
They're 132 years old and they are mad at us about everything still.
And they have the biggest phones with the largest font possible.
And they are tapping so slowly.
Did you know Frank is almost 80 years old?
Wow.
Frank's 78 years old.
I looked this up because Andrew Grissom and I went to see a magic show that he directed
a week ago.
We can't talk about another thing.
Another possible thing.
There were good magic tricks in the show, though.
He was not there.
He's producing the new Jurassic Park.
He's on location in Thailand.
Right, right.
So he was not there.
Because I was really hoping he'd be there.
Yeah, popping up, giving notes, whispering stuff.
Whispering stuff.
And then I could say some of the most confusing sentences he's ever heard in his life to him
after the show.
I have a podcast.
I don't know how I'd ever be able to explain to him that he comes up so often.
Honey, a man's attacking me.
Yeah, exactly.
Yes.
So I would have cried.
This is actually a running argument because we went to the Jurassic World premiere and
we talked about how you gave a speech but it turned out you didn't give a speech.
But I still argued that you did give a speech.
There's no way to have done it.
But I was fantasizing about it.
But then I saw that day he was in Thailand for Jurassic Park 5 or 7, whatever it is.
For him.
So yeah.
God, they're starting that, really?
That's up and running.
Scarlett Johansson's in.
Wow.
It's like David Kep is back.
He's writing.
He wrote the script.
It's going to be great.
Mm-hmm.
Everything's going to be good.
We're not here to talk about those dinosaurs.
We're here to talk about the Beach Boys.
And they're episodes of Full House.
And again, thrilled about this topic.
And I think in terms of where this sits in their story, in general, I just look.
I love Full House and I love the Beach Boys separately.
And these things are tied together.
The collision of these two is just this ultimate mix-up of pop culture kitch.
I feel like these episodes, which happened all from like 88 to 92, I think they genuinely
did expose the Beach Boys to a new generation that has kept the Beach Boys in their mind.
But perhaps as a kind of out of it oldies band who can't act and wear terrible clothes
and say hokey punch lines on a show.
And I've found this to be, with people I know and with my own wife, the biggest hurdle
to saying the Beach Boys made a lot of really remarkable music.
And maybe you've heard of Fett Sounds, but it's this late 60s, early 70s stuff I think
is so special.
And they just didn't get attention at the time.
And it matters so much to me.
And there are people who are like, the Beach Boys did?
From Full House?
The guys in the hats?
So I think while this was important that they do this, it also solidified a certain kind
of Beach Boys to people forever.
Right.
Yes, because watching it back, it was like, how old could they be in these clips?
They're not that old.
But as a kid, you were like, these old guys come into the house.
And they were hanging out with Uncle Jesse, who's a cool young guy.
I think Dave Coulier is way cooler than these old men.
Yeah, by my scale, man.
I'm like, Dave Coulier is funny.
These guys aren't funny.
I know these songs.
I like the songs.
But they very much felt like they were all 70 years old then.
Yeah, I think also in an era where eras and decades, I think everything moved more rapidly.
So they seemed like relics.
They seemed like, here's some time travelers from another era.
And they were never particularly charismatic in that way.
So that doesn't help either.
Because you would see other old rock stars, at least had personality.
None of them have personality on Full House, really.
No.
Think about a McCartney who does cameos on things.
And he just doesn't even try to act.
I remember him coming out on a live 30 Rock.
And he just doesn't really do anything.
He just finger points and soaks up, it's me and I'm here.
And that's how he is in an SNL sketch or whatever.
Yes.
This is much more sedate because you're still making Mike.
Well, as long as I get some of Becky's famous homey cooking.
It's really...
It's lascivious.
I don't want to jump too far ahead.
But I got to say, a lot of Mike's lines sound like threats.
That's what he's like all the time.
When he says, I wasn't paying close attention at first,
but I was watching with Jane.
And I had to rewind because she went, which one is that?
When he goes, let's order a vegetarian pizza.
It sounds like he pulled out a gun.
And I'm like, oh.
He has the family hostage.
His demand is just a pizza, but still a demand.
Don't know how many weapons.
They're guns hiding under his hat.
I think Michelle says, play Kokomo.
And he went, oh, great, a request.
Mike Hale's just like, oh, no.
Yeah.
It's just that he just squints those eyes in a real...
He does squint.
I don't know if it's how it's...
It's not how it's meant to read.
I don't know if it reads this way to everybody, but I'm just like...
You're Clint Eastwood and you're angry at somebody.
Yeah.
That is a great comparison.
He's just 24-7 unpleasant.
That's the only way he is.
He can exist.
You feel the chip on the shoulder in every action he does.
Even when good vibrations surf in sand.
Like, why are you saying it like that?
I'm totally with you.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really strange.
And I'm not trying to get off on an Aerosmith tangent,
but Aerosmith on rock and roller coaster, I knew they weren't young.
But I was like, this guy's kind of fun.
This main guy's kind of fun.
They're goofing.
There were bands that were old that you would see in the various media
that I think in your kid brain, you'd be like, oh, this is fun.
This guy seems cool or whatever.
The Beach Boys did not at the time to me seem cool.
They don't seem cool watching it at this age.
I can see what you're saying about that defining them for a bunch of people.
I saw this stuff at the time that it aired.
Probably not the first one, but I definitely caught up
and probably watched it live, the last one from 92.
And just the way I was raised, I did think they were cool.
I thought the way they dressed was cool.
And then I would kind of dress like that.
I just found a neon orange hat with a little rope,
like the kind Mike wears, which I remember wearing.
And that and a Hawaiian shirt ties into this episode.
I saw Jack Murphy Stadium in San Diego after a Padres game.
This is the thing they would do for a long time, was like,
come see a baseball game and stick around for the Beach Boys.
And I was dancing in the rows.
I was the dorkiest little boy.
Just loving it.
I did.
I think Mike loves cool.
I want to dress like him.
Wow.
Stamos was at that, I remember.
I remember he ran all the way out and did a guitar solo up on top of the dugout.
Cherished memories.
This is who I am.
This is where I came from.
That's so funny.
Even The Beatles, who I liked, when The Beatles Anthology aired on ABC,
and you watch those clips now,
I think they seem like such dorky older guys in those anthology clips.
Their style.
None of them were styling.
None of them had any sort of style.
Cardi actually got more timeless the way he dresses.
Cardi looks great now at 80.
And Ringo kind of, too, versus back then when you're just like,
these are just some dorky 50-year-olds who don't know how to dress.
Yeah, he's got a mullet and a denim shirt.
They are wearing just the goofiest looking clothes,
and they're not that old, obviously.
But at the time, even watching that, you go, oh, they're uncool.
I'm not thinking that actively, but I had that feeling about them
where, oh, they're just sort of old, uncool.
Beatles are cooler now, maybe, than they were.
100%, I think.
They were not doing themselves any favors in the 90s.
What were you saying, Jason?
I interrupted you.
Oh, I was going to say the concert after a baseball game is still a thing,
and I just remember last year watching the Phillies,
and they're like, hey, stick around.
If you come out in two weeks,
there's a free concert after the game, a free concert by DJ Diesel.
DJ Diesel?
Yes, that's Shaquille O'Neal's DJ days.
Wow, it worked on me.
His Sergeant Pepper-esque thin disguise.
I'd love to know more about DJ Diesel and what those sets are like.
I feel strongly that there's a lot of Shaq in our future.
I hope so.
Yes, I would love for there to be plenty.
He's left Dark Harbor in a...
Yeah, yeah, unfortunately.
So we're going to have to get our Shaq fixed elsewhere.
Thankfully, there are dozens and dozens of other places.
Let's get to these episodes.
A Beach Boy, at least, appears in three different episodes of Full House,
though their music is present in many more,
a constant thread through John Stamos and his character Jesse
and his band, The Rippers, who seem to primarily do covers of Beach Boys
and of songs like Hippie Hippie Shake.
In these episodes, they're referred to as a cool new Bay Area band,
and you almost never hear them do anything that isn't like,
I don't know, Monster Mash.
I don't know if they did the Monster Mash, but it seems like...
That seems like something they would do.
I think in Fuller House at some point, they perform What I Like About You,
and I think that's a cool song in the spectrum of Jesse and the Rippers.
I'm surprised they wouldn't have them covering Rick Springfield or something.
That feels like the vibe,
and it would have been more era-appropriate for somebody Stamos' age.
But I think he...
Well, look, like us, we have things in common with this man.
My own Beach Boys fandom, big Disney fan, as we know.
Yeah, that's true.
And I think like him, and we all together want to live in our childhoods
in a bigger way than most.
And I think he's like, I'm a star on a show that is working.
I want to sing the songs I loved growing up.
I want to dress up like Elvis.
Did it ever occur to you that I might be a little dorky?
No.
It's cool to me.
I was just thinking about watching him in the 90s.
I think it is cool.
There's a real sincerity to all of his Beach Boys and his old music,
which I think is cringy.
I get embarrassment goosebumps a lot while watching moments from these episodes,
from a lot of any Jesse and the Rippers.
My hair stands up on its arm.
It's definitely very cringy, but so much fun.
And I think that's what makes it...
Again, we're pretty thin and our theme park tie together,
but it's silly and embarrassing in the way a theme park show is sometimes.
You know what I mean?
Yes, there's a lack of true coolness.
He's kind of handsome and cool in ways.
Sort of.
To a child.
He was passionately cool to a child.
But if you knew Nirvana then or whatever, then no.
I think that's a through line in a lot of the non-theme parkie topics
is that this shares a DNA with a theme park stunt show.
I hope it doesn't sound like we're just falsifying,
but to me, it's the same part of my brain that's lit up for sure.
It's like cheesiness, but they mean it and I don't know.
They're working really hard and everything.
So episode one, Beach Boy Bingo is their first appearance.
This is season two, episode six, November 18th, 1988.
88 is a really big year for the Beach Boys.
I think I talked about it in my Big Beach Boys episode last year.
This is when the infamous Rock and Roll Hall of Fame speech occurred.
Brian did his first solo record that year.
A few weeks before this airs, Kokomo goes to number one.
So we're getting the Beach Boys on Full House at the ultimate moment of Mike Love's control.
He's never been further from having to go back to the sheet metal factory.
Brian's literally doing other things.
Kokomo, he was not even invited to the session and he's like,
we got the number one record and my buddy, a guy I've been associating with for years,
is now not just on a TV show.
He's on the biggest TV, a massive TV show.
Everything is lined up, Mike Love, in 1988.
And now that's what he's in.
He used to be like, let's get back to the 60s.
And now he's like, let's get back to 1988.
In terms of my life and politically as well.
So I want to focus on the boys.
I don't want to say too much about the entire stories of these things.
So just like Cliff Note's version, the Beach Boys are in town.
They're going to do a concert.
Their helicopter doesn't arrive in time to be on Wake Up San Francisco.
But the Beach Boys are in San Francisco, right?
There's a radio contest or something.
DJ is the seventh caller, oldest daughter DJ, Candice Cameron.
And she wins the contest.
And the prize is not just going to a Beach Boys concert
and two tickets to a Beach Boys concert, but a limousine ride.
The Beach Boys themselves are going to go pick up the winner
and another person and go take them to their concert.
Now, the winner and their guests will have to ride up front with the driver.
The Beach Boys don't even want to look at them.
Well, they're trying to focus before the stage.
Yeah, but yeah.
And also, yeah, they don't want that regular people stink on them.
It's like a similar rock and roller coaster plot.
Oh, yeah, it kind of is.
Yeah, the show is starting.
Hey, you know how we feel about our fans?
I wish we could pick up every one of them and stretch limo.
Really not how this happens.
You also, there's the realism question maybe of like,
they're taking a limo to the concert.
Wouldn't they want to get there a lot earlier?
And then I actually just found, I found, you know,
as I do a bunch of just raw footage of the Beach Boys on a tour,
unedited from 1993.
Yeah.
And they do literally just drive up and walk onto the stage.
There's no sound check.
They just.
Oh, really?
This is how little they were.
Well, you say, oh, really, but if you watch and soon,
I will play you what they sounded like live at the time.
I think you wouldn't say, oh, really, once you hear the results of that.
OK.
Do you know they sound check these days?
I couldn't tell you that.
Somebody sound checks, probably.
They, you know, yeah, you know what?
I think actually the touring Beach Boys have musicians who care a little bit more.
I think at the time they were doing these episodes,
I think they hated each other.
I think they didn't speak to each other until they were getting onto the stage.
I think it's the little Beach Boy downtime as there could be.
That's funny.
Keep that tension in your mind as you watch these scenes where they all pretend to be buddies.
It's like I follow like I think I think the account's name is Spring Nuts,
Bruce Springsteen fans, and they will report what they've played at sound check.
Yeah, so people will hang out outside the arena and they will list
the songs they've heard the band sound check like, oh,
maybe there'll be these new songs they'll play tonight.
Sometimes it doesn't happen.
But obviously Bruce is there.
He's old, but he's had some health issues in the last few years.
But obviously he's still showing up at whatever two in the afternoon sound checking.
But he is a musician who cares about the music being good.
That's fair.
The way it breaks down is Mike just wants to like do his little schtick
and like point to the girls and here's the cheerleaders.
Carl Wilson, my favorite Beach Boy, heart of the band,
was the only one who cared about how they sound.
But by the 90s he kind of thrown in the towel because we're playing in state fair venues.
Right.
And that's not a knock.
That's not saying like they're only doing they're playing state fair venues with
in front of 20,000 people where you can't even hear how they sit.
Nobody's going to notice the clock and the glockenspiel part.
Right.
So like he just was like, I'm not going to be I'm not going to be a micromanager here.
I'm going to show up.
I'm just going to.
Yeah.
They'll be more mad at me if I try to make this good.
Right.
So that's where we're at.
That's the Beach Boys.
Got it.
Anyway, DJ only gets one ticket.
So she's got to pick which of the tanners she's going to take.
She ends up choosing Jesse because he's a musician.
Wouldn't he want to?
And she betrays her own dad.
And then there's a heart to heart between Danny and Jesse
who Danny at some point says, I guess I just can't compete with Uncle Rock and Roll.
I like that line a lot.
That is I as a kid thought all these people were a million years old.
At some point in one of these episodes or maybe a later one, it said that Uncle Jesse is 29.
He's supposed to be 29.
I think he has the twins and he's married and he's 29 in the show.
That is why especially I was like thinking about the music choices.
Yeah.
He literally is picking the stuff he heard when he was little.
Yes, yeah.
I think I mentioned once I looked in his book and he discovered the Beach Boys in the 70s
at Disneyland from the cover band that is in the rising Tomorrowland stage.
It's not like he grew up with them.
He's like us.
He's kind of nostalgic for an era that wasn't even a unit.
And he wasn't alive for Elvis or barely.
I forget how that lines up.
Sure.
As a child, they did Kokomo on some of the Disney parades or an opening special or something.
So the presence of them on Full House, the music video on TV, the presence on Disney specials,
I was like, oh, these guys are big rock and rollers.
With all that put together, it was almost like the play is let's be for kids.
We're a band for kids now.
I think that's what they were kind of aiming for and sort of successfully.
Because that's where the money is if we could get the new generation.
It's all about generations and good vibrations.
Speaking of Hanson, Muppets and Kokomo go together.
And I do think that's also responsible for a bunch of people liking
Kokomo and then Beach Boys when they were kids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It just all, yeah, I don't know.
It was like kid safe music in an era where there wasn't maybe a lot of that.
You know, Motley Crue, all this, you know, and Twisted Sister and Tipper Gore and the
putting the labels that Mike Love incidentally was on the other side of that.
Mike Love was a person who fought for the labels to be on records.
Mike Love fought for the Confederacy.
He would have.
I mean, you just got to get back to those good old days.
What days are you talking about?
I don't know.
1840 or something.
That's the day.
You know, it's pure evil.
Mike Love.
Southern gentry.
Plantation Dixieland.
He's at Mar-a-Lago all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's some there's some scary photos, just like red eye flash bad.
He is.
Yeah, he is.
So you think he's scarier now than he is?
I feel like the opposite sometimes happens.
Joe Biden to me actually seems friendlier now than he did in these like old hearings.
Mike Love actually seems like he's getting even scarier in some ways.
It's hard to say.
Scariest era of Mike.
What's the scariest era?
Well, some of these lines will help him compete here in this era.
Anyway, there's so much fighting that DJ is like,
I don't even want to go to the concert anymore.
And they're like, no, that's great.
Somebody's got to go.
Don't say that, DJ.
And then all of a sudden, before they're in a big fight,
before you know it, the Beach Boys are at their door.
They made good on their prom.
This is what the contest was.
And they're in no rush.
They're like, we're going to hang out here for a little bit.
And I mean, the full band is at the door.
Mike Love, Carl Wilson, Al Jardine, the strange sprite one,
Bruce Johnston, who's a little hard to quantify.
I'll explain Bruce better later.
And then mainly, Brian Wilson.
Brian Wilson acting.
Yeah.
Brian Wilson acting performance.
When they all say hello at the door, I think he's blocked.
Yeah, you can't see him.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I noted that as well.
You're like, is he in the back?
Yeah, yeah, which makes you go, was Brian ever on the show?
OK, and then they all enter.
And you're like, I guess he was.
That said, Brian did a Reddit AMA a number of years ago,
which almost every answer of which is very quotable.
And he, at some point, got the question,
how was it filming with the cast of Full House?
His response, I've never been on Full House.
Oh, man.
Poor Brian.
Yeah, yeah.
Because he was, if you know the movie Love and Mercy,
if you know his real story, you know he was under the control
and microscope of this corrupt doctor who inserted himself
in his life and his every move was.
And what I find so interesting about movies like that is that,
like, yes, that's all true.
And that's what you should focus on.
But I'm like, but also, he was on Full House.
He was not.
He was, like, in a trap.
But also, then he'd go do this.
It's really weird.
Really weird.
And I don't know how you put that in the movie.
It doesn't really go along with the narrative.
But I always think that about things.
Like, there was this David Bowie, IMAX documentary,
tone poem kind of thing.
I don't know if you saw it.
The Moon Age Daydream?
Moon Age Daydream.
Yeah, I actually watched only a part of it.
Well, it's a good presentation of the music,
but it's very pretentious.
It's definitely very weighty and kind of about the legend
and the alien that he even walked among us
is impossible to comprehend.
And you're like, he was the man who fell to Earth.
Yes, he was literally the man who fell to Earth.
And then you're like, yeah, but also, wasn't he on Extras once?
Like, he was pretty, he was funny on talk shows around.
These things kind of build these people up,
and then you forget.
Kind of like, and also, they were around.
They're like, cool guys.
He did a Conan confession.
Yeah, he did, right?
Yeah, very funny.
Those are always very funny.
Anyways, something you realize at the door
is that they all dress like psychopaths.
Yeah, I wanted to bring this up.
This immediately struck me to the point where I was like,
are they all wearing their own clothes?
And I looked again, and I'm like,
no, this has to be Costumer because they're all perfectly different.
Or that's just all what they like to wear
and showed up in their own clothes.
Well, I think possibly that.
Yeah, maybe they took, all right,
let's take inspiration for what you guys wear.
Here's the thing, though.
It's an interesting question of whether they chose them or not.
But I know a lot of concerts.
It's definitely how Mike Love would wear a lot of full American flag jumpers and stuff.
Weird thing is, Al and Mike are wearing the same hat.
They both are wearing a hat.
It's a black hat with purple stripes, and it says,
the Beach Boys high surf, which is not a song of theirs.
So now they did. I don't know what it means.
So that's a weird thing.
It took me a minute to go like, wait, they're wearing the same hat.
And then Al is wearing, he's wearing pants that are full of letters.
R, A, F, all decanted.
And then like this huge blue, like a Michael Jackson jacket,
except that's like three sizes too big for him.
And I was watching with Erin, and she's like,
this is like if you let a toddler dress himself.
This is an insane way.
You'd think it was cute if an 18-month-old was in clothes way too big for them.
So that's, that's, Al Jardine may be the least cool person to be in any big popular band.
All the Rolling Stones are a little cool.
Yeah.
Even Ringo's a little cool.
It's on some level.
Al Jardine, who's a ponytail a lot of the time with a bald spot.
You can't do a bald spot on a ponytail.
I feel like Max Weinberg is a big dork,
but the Conan Association gives him some cool, I think it's both.
I think it's like part why you kind of think of him as uptight kind of guy.
But also I think that being on Conan makes him a little cooler.
I think just due to how they cast him in dozens and dozens of sketches,
I think of him as a sex freak.
Yeah.
I think they took something, not that he's a sex freak,
they took things, they took an uptight guy and they decided to make him a joke often.
Yeah.
Did you know Max Weinberg's son is the drummer for Slipknot?
Jay, yeah.
But I believe he was fired or left Slipknot the other day.
He was just playing with Slipknot.
He was just playing with East Street Band.
Hot off the presses.
He filled in for Max when The Tonight Show started, I believe.
Oh, really?
For a few weeks, I think.
Yeah, Jay.
Jay Weinberg, now a character on the show.
So this is the speed we're going to go at because they haven't even entered the door
and this is where we're at.
But then they enter, they're all introduced, Jesse shakes all their hands,
and he says to Mike Love, hey, Dr. Love.
That was confusing to me.
This happens every single time Mike Love shows up.
I, as you know, am an Encyclopedic Beach Boys fan.
There is no other media in which Mike Love is referred to as Dr. Love.
This is a John Stamos exclusive that is consistent in every episode, every time it happens.
I'm like, why?
No one has agreed to this.
Feel good kind of thing, like a nickname.
I don't know, it's something about just how esteemed he is, you know?
How long he's been around and how wise.
Calling somebody like Dr. Cosby, you know?
Only the best of the wisest.
Yeah, that's like a cute little nickname, I feel.
Dr. So-and-so, I guess.
Unless there's some other thing we don't know.
Dr. Love.
I guess that's just like a cool, like, oh, that's a cool thing I do with my friend here.
It's a nickname I have with my friend.
He has to be a little cagey here, right?
He has to act as if Jesse is meeting Mike for the first time,
rather than that they are good buddies.
Imagine him having to stifle what good buddies he is
with this guy who he thinks everyone will be very impressed that he's good buddies.
Uh, then the acting begins, and here I go to my first clip.
Here is the Beach Boys doing the action.
What was your phrase about the boards being, like, here they are.
Ah, treading the boards.
Here's the Beach Boys treading the boards, not the surf boards this time.
Brian, you're Carl, you're Mike.
Hi.
Bruce, how are you?
How are you, Carl?
Love you so much.
Love you, Bruce.
How are you, Mike?
Is there a DJ Tanner here?
Yeah, that's me.
Hi.
We hear you're not coming to the concert.
Bon Jovian Town?
No, it's a long story.
Well, we've got time.
They never start the show without us.
Let's order a vegetarian pizza.
That was Mike.
Why, yes, why the malice.
Bon Jovian Town.
Boy, I love.
Also, if you're a fan of this stuff,
if you're trying to now collect all of the Beach Boys acting,
don't sleep on Al Jardine on Decker.
That Heidegger got him to be a villain in an episode,
and he has, I think, not learned anything about acting.
No, but also it's not his deal.
Why should he?
I'm so delighted by all of it.
I love these strange men.
How could they be so uncharismatic for being performers their whole life?
There's a good bit in there, I think,
where they all introduce themselves to the tanners,
and then the camera cuts,
and they all introduce themselves to each other.
That's a funny bit.
That's a solid sitcom gag.
Monkey-style way to put it.
In my head, I was like, what is it?
It's kind of like Hard Day's Night.
It's like the way that, yeah, the musicians are all kind of our-
Kooky eyes.
Yeah, a little kooky plays on, yeah, we flip it on you.
We see things in a different way.
Yeah, if you've ever watched the old monkey show,
it feels very much like that to me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which all is sort of like-
Head-warpy, I can't pin these guys down.
They say something weird, everything you say to them.
Yeah, but they're not like that.
But they're so clever.
Mickey Dolan's just try to kind of be like that still,
I feel like, where he's got to quip a minute,
and they're not always so funny, but-
Something tells me if you let him talk for a while,
he might start talking about some unsavory things.
Perhaps, but-
Knowing nothing except looking at him.
I have my guesses about Mickey Dolan.
Possible.
I haven't heard anything like that, especially,
I've heard some funny stories about him being ridiculous.
But my point just is that there's something in
the monkey's actual as human beings and the Beatles,
where you can see they like to have some fun.
I don't get that sense from the Beach Boys.
No, well, now it's on these writers to figure out
what the Beach Boys are like.
And I do like where they land.
I like that they're like quippy 60s people,
and I like that Mike is, that he likes food,
he likes to eat, he's like shaggy.
Why not?
I gotta add, they're gonna land somewhere,
I gotta give them characters.
Anyway, then they sing Kokomo all in the living room,
and the kids clap along, and it's cute,
and it's for everybody.
And Stamos is playing guitar with them.
I know he played guitar on the show,
but that's kind of presumptuous for a guy
who doesn't know the Beach Boys.
Because if the Beach Boys were in my living room,
and they didn't know who I was,
and they decided to play Kokomo,
I would not say, can I play guitar with you?
Unless maybe they offered, I suppose,
or said, hey, you play?
Maybe that's the drive that a Stamos has.
Well, he does like to be seen with them.
That is part of what he loves.
Extremely.
And he jumps around, and he still runs around.
I don't know if he's bragging that he can run around on stage,
and these old men can't.
Yeah, that's got to help in these shows, you think,
that at least one guy is being physical.
He's a youthful 60 years old now at this point.
He is, though.
Boy, if you compare current Stamos to...
He's got to be older now than the Beach Boys were in that clip.
Yeah.
Oh, he must be.
For sure.
Yeah, yeah.
And he looks like a different species.
But I guess if you've been in actor mode,
then you'll be...
Because he's probably particularly with it for his age.
Probably.
I don't know what the excuses of these Beach Boys...
At least, look, Brian has lost hundreds of pounds, literally.
But that is less of a fitness and more of a you're going to die.
So that's the thing.
That's the strange thing.
I don't know how much I explained the doctor,
but that's what's weird.
The doctor saved his life, Dr. Eugene Landy,
but then he went too far.
Another strange thing is that he also worked with Maureen McCormick,
Marcia Brady.
Yeah.
This is just a strange lineup of folks who...
Yeah, really.
I forget what her issues were, but yeah, he was like...
If you want on Club 3 to dive into Maureen McCormick's,
Dr. Landy experience, go ahead and vote for it.
I will do as much Brady as humanly possible.
I even earlier this week...
I had the frazzled day for whatever reason,
and the way I calmed down at the end of the day
was watching the full TV movie,
Dawn Portrait of a Teenage Runaway,
Eve Plum's Serious Turn,
which kept her out of the Brady Bunch variety hour.
I really liked Dawn Portrait of a Teenage Runaway.
I recommend it.
I recommend it more than another movie by the same director,
Boy in the Plastic Bubble.
I got a little more of the Travolta movie.
You've probably heard of that one.
Yeah, of course.
I got a little more bored during that one.
Dawn, I feel like had it.
Really?
I was with it, and here's what's really weird.
The director of both of those movies,
also the director of Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
Wow.
Yeah.
And Grease.
And Grease as well.
All the same Disney's white thing, I think.
That's funny.
Randall Kleiser is the guy.
It's the strangest filmography.
Interesting.
Anyways, that's the top...
Hey, that could be a losing topic in the future,
but then you'll know it's mine and you don't have to vote.
Right.
You could vote for it.
The Christopher Knight VH1 reality show.
You could vote for it with Adrian Curry.
Admittedly, I've watched a lot of Brady stuff.
I've drawn the line at the reality shows,
but maybe the home renovation show's good.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't seen that.
Jason used to live right by their house.
That's right.
I lived by the original Brady house.
Yeah, they renovated it inside to make it look like a real house.
I was walking through the neighborhood once,
and there was a bunch of bleachers and a fake marching band,
a fake audience, because they were filming an HGTV spot.
I haven't seen it.
So yeah, anyway...
Yeah, they saw with your own eyes that they didn't have a window.
Well, we haven't done Barry's Branson show yet.
We teased that years ago.
Man, there's a lot of good Brady out there.
It's just to be clear, if you see Brady in a poll,
that's not you trying to get zero votes or one vote?
At this point, it doesn't.
It seems like there's actually too much enthusiasm for Brady stuff,
even though we haven't seen it.
But...
Well, there's more group enthusiasm.
Yeah, I think it has to literally be you two are turned off.
Jason's usually on board for most things,
but I would have to try to turn Jason off, I think.
It'd have to be so repellent that Jason has no interest.
It'd be hard, though, because he's usually on board.
Yeah, I usually try to be a sport, even if I'm not interested.
Jesus, Jason is a sport.
I try to be a sport.
My end of the day wind down movie the other day was the...
I think it was the late 60s, early 70s adaptation of The Big Sleep
with a older Robert Mitchum and a very old Jimmy Stewart.
Really, it's Mitchum mania for you right now.
I love Mitchum and Burt Lancaster as I've gotten older
are the actors that I appreciate.
For me, it's Eve Plumb.
For me, it's YouTube toy reviewer Pixel Dan.
Actually, I think you turned Jason off with toy YouTubers, maybe,
and then political stuff you shouldn't be paying attention to also.
Well, maybe.
It would have to be so unpleasant.
He likes some of the toy-Tuber talk, though.
So you'd be like, I was watching Mickey Dolenz's nephew
who's very right-wing neo-Nazi.
I'm making this person.
Yeah, I'm not saying I don't know if there is this.
He might have a wonderful nephew or no nephews at all.
Anyways, they're having fun.
They even like, whoa, look at this.
Hanging out with the Beach Boys, eating pizza.
The pizza's a big part of it.
But ultimately, things come to a head.
OK, DJ, who's coming with you?
And somehow, they make the decision that it's everybody.
And then smash cut to a big stadium show.
Beach Boys playing Kokomo there.
And the Tanner family just off to the side
with the best seats in the house.
No seats.
They're just right off to the side of the stage.
The kind of setup I saw where they're in the center of the field.
And then mostly, it's just empty field around them,
except for so many cheerleaders.
We were trying to figure out, is this the Rose Bowl?
It is not the Rose Bowl.
It's the LA Coliseum.
It's the Coliseum.
The then home of the Raiders, I believe.
Yes, not San Francisco.
I think this was after a USC Trojans game,
which if eagle-eyed viewers might notice,
whenever they cut to the crowd, there are 60 USC shirts
in every single crowd shot.
That makes sense.
Sort of takes away the San Francisco of it all.
I mentioned the fact before, which is that Brian Wilson
had nothing to do with Kokomo.
And this was such a shot in the arm for Mike
that finally the genius wasn't even here,
and I abandoned one.
I just needed that guy, that sex creep from the mamas
and the papas, and the guy who Manson was trying to kill.
The strangest group of ne'er-do-wells who made Kokomo.
Is it three credited?
Four.
There's another guy.
Scott McKenzie, I think, is the name.
I'm not sure his deal, but it was like an old demo
by the guy from mamas and the papas.
So they get kind of bought by Mike Love and the Melcher,
Terry Melcher.
But anyway, Brian not part of Kokomo,
yet here he is on stage singing it with him.
Can you tell from this performance?
Just listen for a voice that maybe
seems a little bit lost as to the melody or the lyrics.
Did you catch that?
Like the kind of high pitch?
Yeah.
Yeah, we got a little more here.
Actually, they cut to him too.
See you later.
Brian.
OK, so was Brian playing live with them in this year?
It was a weird thing where you just wouldn't know.
For a long time, it's like, is he going to be there or not?
Open door question of, I don't know,
technically open door if he wants.
So sometimes you would see him with them this year.
Once in a while.
Mostly not.
The vast majority not.
And you'd hear that they hate each other.
There were lawsuits.
And then we'd still be on stage.
It's like you really couldn't predict it.
Brian for many, many years has just stood behind a keyboard
that isn't plugged in, doesn't do anything,
but it makes him comfortable.
I believe in fashion check, I think he's maybe wearing a shirt
for Mike Tukakis.
Post-election, I guess.
Or an aired post.
No, wait.
No.
Right.
What year was it again?
It aired post-election November night.
But maybe they filmed it when Tukakis was Bush's opponent.
So all right.
That dates it.
Scott, you real quick slipped in the name Terry Melcher in there
without mentioning the fact, Dwight,
that that is Doris Day's son.
Yes.
Yeah.
I likely probably would have gotten too excited
if you said that.
So I know why you didn't.
I would have gotten rambunctious.
I would have gotten Ramey.
You know, it's not a bad thing, Jason, getting Ramey.
It might have been the intended Manson family,
intended victim.
I learned from doing the oh, hello piece with Mulaney.
I learned from a Mulaney riff that he was dating
Candice Bergen at the time.
Oh, right.
That she was maybe the possible target.
If you don't know that, that the Mansons were after the people
who Manson sent were after Terry Melcher, this music guy,
because he wasn't helping him out with the music.
And he like, all right, well, you're the Hollywood pig.
And that's why.
And then they got confused about the house.
And it was other people.
They had moved out.
So that's why it was Tate and the others.
Right.
But they were after the guy who ended up writing and producing
Kokomo, who is also Doris Day's son.
Yeah.
And also a weird thing I just learned.
My grandfather was an entertainment reporter.
He wrote for Modern Screen magazine.
And I did a search for him somewhere, Carl Schrader.
I did a search for him in some form that I'd never checked.
And I found a big profile he wrote about Doris Day.
And who is Doris Day married to?
I think the name was Al Jordan.
OK.
Wow.
He's a good pull.
No, I just saw it on Google.
Family tree.
But yeah, he followed Doris Day on a vacation.
He took a vacation with them and wrote about it.
And there's a part where, like, I went to their lovely home
and saw their little son Terry running around.
Holy shit.
My grandfather was around Melcher.
This guy was in this strange pocket in history.
So what year is that around?
60?
I don't know.
60s?
Well, no.
No.
No, earlier.
Earlier.
Yeah.
Maybe like later 50s.
Yeah, because 60s.
Right.
By the end of the 60s, Manson's looking for him.
Yeah.
I think that's what Terry Melchrom was renting the house
that Sharon Tate and Roman Polanski took over.
He still owned it.
And then they.
OK.
And then Polanski was out of town.
Yeah, he was out of town.
Was he filming something?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Yeah, wild.
The Beach Boys Association has a whole other thing
that we barely touched on.
You could vote for it for Club 3 if you want more Beach Boys.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, a lot of sub times here.
What if the Manson Beach Boys connection outvotes a Weiger
Lorcan episode?
Yeah.
Weiger.
Yeah, I did ask if the school.
A different psychopath has been beaten.
Scarier.
In a lot of ways, scarier than Manson.
Not every way, but a lot of ways.
My teacher gave me a lot of notes early.
Positive notes.
Weiger, not Manson.
Very encouraging.
Not Manson.
Well, Manson inspired me in other ways.
Manson did your 201.
Yeah.
Tell a lesson from UCB.
They were so hard up for teachers.
They let Charles Manson do it from prison.
Yeah, of course.
Jason, pretty good.
My note for you.
Just one quick note would be like.
Jack.
Sorry, I'm writing that down.
Could you say it again?
Got it.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jack.
Anyway, I don't have a ton to say about this.
They invite the Tanner's up on stage with them.
And it's all in the character of the show.
So like, please welcome some new friends of ours, the Tanner family.
And then the audience for this concert narratively
just watches a random family up on stage swimming with them, which is weird.
We were recently talking about just stuff feeling a little wrong
about when talk shows have a segment in a movie or a TV show.
This is something as a kid I kind of clocked that.
This isn't really what happens.
But it is.
Of all the things, they definitely did send them out at a real concert.
Yes, they did.
That's the old ad.
That's true.
Oh, but you're saying that, yeah, that a random family would not suddenly be up.
Yeah, usually not.
That's true, except I think Barbara Ann, which is what they perform, is the.
Is it?
Yeah.
No, it's Barbara Ann and Fun Fun Fall in the Credits.
The credits, yeah, Barbara Ann.
OK, OK.
But I think this is the zone where like,
if we know somebody, just send them up because it's just bedlam by this point.
Just give them a tambourine.
Right.
Because I just saw in the period of time where I got to work with Rob Lowe,
somehow the Beach Boys came up and he's like,
I remember singing Barbara Ann with them on stage back in 88.
Whoa, what?
I was like, what, did Stamos get you up there?
And I think he said, it might have been Glenn Fry.
What the fuck?
I can't believe I'm talking to you.
You know these people.
So possibly this is just the arrow and they were just like,
whoever's backstage, come on up.
Yeah, I think so.
I think it's possible.
Yeah, trot out this well again.
Mike's quest for relevance.
And if there's a young, hot star there.
And I did, today I found footage of that.
I didn't know there was footage of that.
That there's Rob Lowe in a sleeveless shirt and sunglasses.
Wow.
Singing Barbara Ann with them.
And then Dave Coulier takes over on the drums.
Really?
He drums?
Wow.
Yeah.
OK.
The hottest stars, Coulier.
Does he play drums on the show?
Because there's a plot, one of the part of the,
there's a joke I should say, that they want to pass Mike
their demo tape.
Stamos and Coulier.
And then Mike makes a comment of like,
I'm so glad that no one tried to make me listen
to one of their songs or something.
He says something like that.
And they back up.
And they back away.
Which I actually, then I was kind of impressed
that they followed up on the plot in the concert.
They had to track that.
And Joey sneaks a tape into his shirt pocket.
And then Mike makes a face while still singing.
It was pretty good.
That is, yeah.
This is a pro.
You're doing your business of doing the concert
and the sitcom plot.
I'm just trying to remember, did he play,
he was not in Jesse and the Rippers.
No.
They were DJs together.
This might have been an off series.
I don't know if they ever did.
Yeah.
Because that's overkill.
They have two characters who play the drums, right?
They were trying to sell jingles.
They were.
Yes, they did work together musically.
I thought of Joey as more the lyricist.
They also were the rush hour renegades.
They were DJs.
They were a lot of jobs.
They were like Homer Simpson.
Yeah, they all get involved in local regional media
at a certain point.
Which is my big thing for a long time, Gro,
is the people in San Francisco ever clocked
that all of the titans of media in this city
all live in the same home?
Right.
Everyone who could.
All the airwaves.
Doesn't it seem like a monopoly is afoot over in this one?
Yeah, that's pretty weird.
I mean, that happens, though.
UCB, New York, and it's late 2000.
All these people ended up being on TV.
All the people that lived in the full house house
ended up having big careers.
That's what happens.
Sometimes Laurel Canyon.
Frank Marshall makes a documentary about Laurel Canyon,
and you can learn all about it there.
It's similar to other ones.
I forget if I've seen that one.
I liked his Bee Gees documentary.
Well, what happened to that?
Was he just so handcuffed by the boys?
But did you know as much about the Bee Gees?
Yeah, I liked that one, too.
No.
Maybe if I was more of a.
Maybe.
But I also feel like they got real.
I feel like they actually had, there were teary moments.
Well, Barry, is it the one where Barry
says that he would give all the success up
if his brothers were alive?
And you just fucking fall out of your chair with sadness
when you hear that?
That's crazy.
I think if it's that one, then yes.
That's a heavy fucking line, if that's what it is.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's like the Beach Boys, actually.
And only one of the brothers, kind of a leader brother
in a way, is the only one still remaining.
Yeah.
Boy.
So I don't know.
Maybe he just got lucky.
I can't remember if it's that one.
They were more vulnerable.
I don't know.
Maybe you got to deal with Beach Boys, Inc. so much.
The Laurel Canyon one he did was just
sort of like the other Laurel Canyon ones you've ever seen.
That's another.
Yes.
It's all the same sanitized sort of story.
Everyone's agreed on that narrative.
Yeah, and it's all just sort of fun.
Maybe they'll talk about somebody streaking once,
and that's about as raunchy as it gets or something,
when you know it was fucking nuts.
Like theme park rides, needing to get to them early
so that when they stop doing certain tricks,
you could say that you saw it, or they just
settle into what the ride's really going to be.
It's like how documentaries, you need
to catch real stuff early, or maybe where they don't even
know there's a documentary that's going to get used.
Is it called Endless Harmony?
There's one from like 98 that's vastly superior to the Frank
Marshall one, just a made for TV.
And then they talk about Kokomo and glorify it for a while,
and then we were back on top, and the boys
and the generations, you see, they loved it.
And then it just cuts to Brian, and it's silent for a second.
And he's like, don't get to be part of that one.
Cut, next thing.
That's more raw than anything that happened in the Marshall
one.
It's like giving Brian the iPad from The Last Dance
or something, where you get an honest reaction from a thing
they just told him.
That's the vibe.
Knowing all of the drama of The Beach Boys,
I think that if The Last Dance was only an hour and a half,
it was like, so was Michael ever hard to work with?
Nope, it was just good vibrations.
The mic and The Last Dance.
For The Beach Bulls, it was nothing but good vibrations.
At the very least, though, The Last Dance
is a documentary totally from the point of view
of Michael Jordan.
So at least you've got that going for it,
because The Last Dance is fantastic.
Obviously, a lot of the players are upset with it,
because it's completely Jordan's point of view.
Oh, sure, sure.
And he has the cigar and the glass of whiskey,
and you can see the levels changing
as they're cutting the different clips.
So when he's trying to settle scores,
he's trying to change narratives.
And I took that personally.
Right, and there's so many meme-able things from it,
so many memorable.
And the bulls themselves were so cool at that time.
So at the very least, it's not just a here's what happened,
and that's the sanitized version.
You're getting one of the most fascinating men of all time's
point of view.
So that's what makes that compelling,
even though it might not be the whole truth of the situation.
He's willing to showcase his own villainy in it.
Yes, and it's so good.
It's so compelling.
That's why if there was a raw Mike Love documentary,
I think it'd be one of the greatest things.
Exactly.
If you could get that from him, at the very least,
it would be some of the most compelling television.
It does exist.
You just have to piecemeal it yourself, as I have done.
It's a documentary that exists in 200 YouTube clips,
basically, one of which I think I'll play.
You have to hear that I took it personally in your own head.
He's not going to say it.
Other than at the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame when he did say it.
You said it in many more words.
Michael Jordan, also kind of a weird, vindictive Hall
of Fame speech, right?
This is the.
Yeah, certainly.
And yeah, and certainly still carrying grudges in Last Dance.
Yeah.
Mike Love should not grow a mustache
like Michael Jordan had for a while there.
Jordan still, I'd rather hang out with him
100 times than Mike Love.
This is a strange statement to say as a surprise.
I know, it's not.
I'm just saying.
You'd rather hang out.
You'd like to hang out with the greatest basketball
player of all time.
And somebody who is like, how many times richer?
10,000?
Well, that rich, whatever.
But I'm just saying, it seems like you
could have a fun time with Jordan.
I can't see a scenario where you would ever
have any fun with Mike Love.
Well, I would.
I know I would.
Well, I would choose to hang out with him.
If somebody said, do you want to hang out with Mike Love tonight,
I would say 100% I do.
But I can't imagine it going well in any scenario.
Jordan, I can imagine it like we go in like a bender
and play like 48 holes of golf or something.
Either way, you're starting at a steakhouse.
You're starting at minimum like a Ruth's Chris steakhouse.
I think you and Mike Love are hanging out
at the Lake Tahoe Sizzler.
Yeah, and he's not paying for you.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Yeah, you got this.
Separate checks.
I mean, I gave you a lot of music for free.
Decades of music for the whole generation.
You actually owe me.
In the story of Full House, the Tanners
definitely paid for that pizza.
Oh, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
Then they were kind of like, let us get this.
And he's like, yeah.
Jordan would like bet.
You would be Jordan would pay, but you'd
have to like beat him in like a betting scenario or something.
Like there's a sports game on or something in the room,
and you have to bet that like he has to lose a bet for him
to pay for your whole meal.
And he's a little upset.
And then he wants to go double or nothing
on something else afterward.
Then you end up paying for 20 pizzas.
Yeah, probably.
But it's more fun.
It's a lot more energy, a lot more fun.
You know, this is kind of like the clean episode, right?
The whole baby's in it, and they do a concert,
and there's the Tanners.
Imagine being in that crowd if you liked Full House.
Wow, the Full House cast is up there with the Beach Boys.
And it's a little less hokey, and they kind of just
get to do what they do, and it all works out for them.
So you're like pretty good clean, right?
Let me just, let me back this up a tiny bit to,
because this, you know, as I've said,
this all comes from the deep Stamos love friendship.
They truly are best friends,
love performed Stamos' wedding ceremony.
It's really, I think it's a matter of,
it's what kind of,
what's your tropical musician best friendship?
Is it Marshall Buffett, or is it Stamos' love?
And I'm sorry.
I know what sounds much more attractive,
hanging out-wise.
Yes.
Well, one, not more.
Musically you can, well, look.
Musically you can debate it, I think.
But as far as fun times, I don't think there's any debate.
I suppose, yeah, well, yeah, one of them flew a plane.
But anyways, because this friendship goes way back,
so do their sitcom appearances.
This did not begin on Full House.
There was a kind of less popular show that Stamos was on.
He was a soap opera star, which is why it all happened.
He showed up at a Beach Boys show.
Girls are screaming, who's that guy?
Why are all the girls screaming for him?
Get him on stage.
And then he rode that relevant,
and boy did he put money on the right horse with Stamos,
because he made it out of soap.
But he was already, that's a big enough star for me.
Then he made it to prime time,
and then to a much bigger prime time show.
And then perennial TV star, he's always on something.
But it started on prime time TV
with a show called You Again with Jack Klugman.
And this is where the onscreen collaboration
between the Beach Boys and Stamos begin.
Really quick context here.
Stamos' character in that show, if you can believe it,
is a drummer, and he is asked to fill in
for Beach Boys' gig.
He's nervous about it, but it ends up,
he prepares, and it ends up going great,
and he knows all the songs by heart,
and they kill a whole act of the show
just letting the Beach Boys do a concert together.
Great, let's write, wonderful, wrap that up.
But then, here's the sitcom lesson,
that he's cocky, went great,
it's gonna keep going great for me.
Shows up in the morning to get ready for the next show,
and they come in with new shit they wanna do.
And that does not go nearly as well.
So that's the context of this moment.
And this is everybody again,
this is full band lineup, including Brian Wilson,
and see if you can guess which voice is Brian Wilson's.
You were some hit last night.
Thanks, Bruce.
That's great.
Glad I didn't make a fool out of myself, you know?
You knew all the tunes, that's for sure.
Sorry I'm late, try these, Matt.
What are they?
Some new arrangements.
Oh, really?
I like the old arrangements.
So do we, gotta keep it fresh.
Oh.
All right.
And then he fumbles with the song.
Has that ever happened?
We have to do a new arrangement.
I love what they're painting,
but live perfection is, yeah.
I just, I'm always perfect, I gotta try new ways.
Never satisfied.
Gotta keep it fresh.
I'm every bit of the guy who wasn't doing pet sounds.
Try these, Matt.
Sorry I'm late.
He's not as bad as he could be though.
I will say this,
cause I was watching some of this and I was like,
he's okay.
Well, let me keep making the argument here.
Let's see if you remain at he's okay.
As I show you another clip from the same era.
This is without Stamos.
This is Brian Wilson solo on a show from earlier,
in 1988, the biggest year for them.
A show called The New Leave It To Beaver.
The context here, these are,
I think it's like the kids of the original
Leave It To Beaver characters.
Of course.
And they're passing notes in class.
And then their teacher catches wind of what's going on.
Uh oh.
What seems to be the problem, Mr. Haskell?
Well, Mr. Hawthorne,
I was just explaining to our new classmate how
you really brought history to life for me.
Cut the ballparky and give me the note, huh?
I'm not the culprit here.
As you know, I only use a number two and a half pencil.
Who wrote this?
Very well.
I'll see you all here after school,
and we can just sit until somebody comes forward.
Cut the ballparky and show me who.
He could be worse.
I'm not sure.
I mean, for a person who's having like,
one of the most severe decades long traumatic episodes
anybody's ever had.
I mean, he's holding it together.
The New Leave It To Beaver,
did it go for like seven seasons or something?
It was a hundred episodes.
What's it that many?
Made it to a hundred episodes.
So what is that?
Five seasons or six seasons?
Four long ones, I think.
Yeah, I know.
You're like, there was a New Leave It To Beaver?
Yeah, a hundred episodes.
That's like that newer Munsters from the 90s
going longer than the original show.
No one's ever seen that.
That's only 14 episodes less than the odd couple
that Jack Klugman was on.
I'm learning.
I immediately was Googling.
You mentioned Jack Klugman,
and I was just like, Quincy.
You got Rammy.
Quincy himself.
I got Rammy.
Quincy.
Rammy for Quincy.
A long dead.
It only passed in 2012.
It lived very long.
He did?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was born in 1922.
We haven't said Klugman's name on this show enough.
Wow, that was the first utterance of Klugman.
I don't think it's the first.
I don't think so.
But it has been a while.
Odd couple, 12 angry men, Quincy.
It's just a killer.
Guys, cut the bullpucky and let's move on.
If you don't stop saying names to Jack Klugman's shows,
then we're going to have to end this podcast early.
Very well.
Let's continue.
Was he a one-off on this show?
Yes, I believe the character of Mr. Hawthorne.
Mr. Hawthorne only appeared once.
It's a musical episode.
What ends up happening is that it turns in,
then the character starts singing,
and then he gets into it,
and he pulls a keyboard out of his stiff teacher desk
and is playing along.
Oh, so they almost like they cool,
or they thaw his icy heart in a way?
I think so, yeah.
Well, yeah, once a magical rhythm kicks through the room,
then even he can't get up and tap a toe.
I know you brought this up before.
I think you have.
It was on Disney Channel or TBS?
Was it?
It says Networks, Disney Channel, and TBS,
so I don't know if it, like, re-arranged.
Yeah.
Wow, that's so wild.
For you.
And everybody got rich off of working on it.
Not me, that scared me to sandwich.
Everybody finds, somebody finds a way
to screw old Brian Wilson,
whatever ends, no matter what.
Wow.
Anyway, yeah, the kids, well.
Wait a minute, why'd I end up paying
all my Labor to Beaver day rate to my manager dad?
He's dead.
I had to join the guilt.
I've got a cut of all of it, Brian, goddammit.
I had to join the guilt, join the guilt for this?
I don't want to pay those dues, man.
Wait, this is new Labor to Beaver?
I thought it was the original.
I thought it was still on TV.
Brian, that has been on TV for decades.
Oh, man.
We gotta meet Tony Dow.
This kid, I gotta do a scene with Tony Dow's kid?
What do you mean?
Since when are sag dudes $100,000 a year?
I think somebody's trying,
new sag president, Mike Love, what?
All right, fine, I'll fork it over.
Poor Brian.
Let's, well, anyway, that's the last Brian
that we'll be hearing,
because he never appears on it again.
In fact, it starts becoming slim pickings
in terms of which Beach Boys are willing to return.
We get to the second episode, our very first telethon,
season three, episode 24.
This is the finale of season three of Full House.
Context here, Danny Tanner is hosting a telethon
for kids or something,
but he's very sleep deprived, putting the show together,
so he ends up dozing through most of the show,
doesn't really have control over what's happening,
so it just becomes a big talent show
for everybody in the family.
He's gotta fill in and do their stuff,
which I love at this point.
Look, I liked all of the kids.
As a kid, in this era, I loved all of the daughters.
Like, Erin attested to this.
She's like, Stephanie Tanner, aspirational for me.
We watched the part of the episode.
In that episode, she does a dance to what is called
Love Shack Baby, and she does this dance
to a bad sound-alike of Love Shack,
where they make Fridg-Snyder British
at the side of the road and well.
But the dance is so good.
She's in a cool sweater and rules,
and then she introduces another one.
I'd be remiss not to play just a quick clip
of the song that DJ sings to Michelle.
I'll let Stephanie introduce it with her big,
her sweater, which has five colors,
and then it says friends in yarn.
That's cool.
Oh man, all right, here's this.
Everybody give it up for DJ Tanner!
Here's a shopping cart with Michelle in it.
I'm riding down the aisle in a shopping cart.
I ask my dad, please, can we get some of these?
He says you're going to the dentist
to get your teeth cleaned
so you can't have any of those sweets.
So we're headed for the check-in and I think...
I'm going to go to the dentist.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d!
Just every once in a while,
send in the loudest, just an ear-shattering drum machine.
They also just ripped off.
It's like Jingle Bell Rock.
Oh yeah!
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d.
Yeah, it ends the same.
Happy as I can be, lollipops and gummy bears
are my favorite treat.
This is such a funny, dopey song.
I've always liked this a lot.
Yeah.
But they saved the big guns
for where they got to get over the hump.
They got to hit their million dollar goal
and the producer of the station comes in and like,
guess what, guess what?
One of the Beach Boys is here.
Mike Love!
And he, what's the Mike Love business?
Well, earlier in the show,
there was a performance by some cheerleaders.
So when he comes out and they're like,
would you be willing to do a,
well, maybe if we can get those cheerleaders back here.
Always about the cheerleaders.
Nothing strange about the way that's said.
He, in this one, is wearing a big jacket with a,
he's wearing the same hat as the other episode
and he's wearing a jacket
with like a big treasure map on the back.
It's amazing fashion.
And at this point, they can no longer pretend,
Stamos can't stifle the friendship anymore.
He has to, Jesse, in addition to John himself,
has to show that he is best of friends with Mike Love.
I don't know when it happened
because he was just a contest winner,
but his niece was a contest winner before.
But it's clearly they've gotten to be very chummy
in the time stamp, but they are because of,
Dr. Love, hey, Dr. Love.
And then it's like, they're razzin' each other,
of course I'll jump in on drums.
There's this schtick that happens
where they do the song, Be True to Your School,
and Mike tells him,
all right, when I sing this line,
then you just gotta do a little,
just a little light drum fill, okay?
And then he does like a massive drum solo,
and then Mike has to throw a towel at him
to get him to stop.
And I think the joke is,
ever since Ringo started touring,
we've had this problem with drummers.
What is that?
That really doesn't really work as a joke.
I guess the idea that a drummer is front and center
in a concert means, I don't know.
Yeah, it's a hard one to track.
This is schtick that remains in Beach Boys shows
to this day.
That's what we are watching.
Is little, they put into the sitcom
the little bit of business that these guys do,
but they get a little raunchier
than they would be willing to do on Full House.
Oh, wow.
And I'll let it explain for itself,
but this is the same thing.
This is Stamos playing with them.
This is from 13 years ago,
and yeah, they did this bit a lot.
So they're setting up for Be True to Your School
and to do a little drum thing.
I forget if that matters for the clip, but here it is.
So, John, because you are part-time,
I want to refresh your memory
on something we'd like to do.
It's a patriotic song.
It's inspired by people in uniform,
in particular cheerleading uniforms.
She's still, yeah.
Something more fundamentally patriotic
than Friday Night Football in the United States.
Okay, as long as they're cheerleaders,
or Saturday or Sunday.
John, we're gonna do this song
recorded quite some time ago,
actually, we recorded it in 1963.
That was the year I was born.
The year I was born.
John says, 63 was the year he was born.
John, you really don't have to remind me of that
because your mother Loretta and I
had some great times back then.
It wasn't my fault, John, it was the 60s.
Come on.
Pshh.
Wow, Mike.
And Loretta's here tonight, too.
It's like deja vu all over him.
Aw.
Okay, John, we're gonna begin the song.
Would they do these jokes the same way?
Then he says, yes, daddy.
Oh, sorry, sorry, I missed.
So we have a run of bits here implying
that Mike Love is the secret biological father
of John Stamos, which kind of drags.
November 22nd, 1963, America Moores
for the young president,
killed in mysterious circumstances.
You know, they say everybody remembers where they were
when they heard Kennedy was shot.
I was fucking John Stamos' mom.
I want you to give birth to our new drummer.
I know, to keep, it's a family band,
but brothers, what do you know,
is eventually they're gonna start dying off.
How do we get the new generation?
I guess I gotta make them myself.
It is funny to see Mike a little more alive.
Yeah, yeah.
There.
He's got it there, yeah.
Holding court, raunchy jokes.
And they do the same,
he's playing too much of a drum solo bit.
Yeah, exact same thing.
And also, there's a crazy thing he does
where he, when he sings,
I've said before that Beecher Your School
is not one of my Beach Boys' favorites,
I don't know if I can get this out.
This might explain why, the note that he hits.
Here we go, maestro, my note, my note, please.
Jeez.
I'm afraid of that.
Sorry, big lead up.
Sorry, daddy.
This is too honest.
A lot of feedback, a lot of feedback.
Do I make fun of your hairdo on the poor house?
Oh.
Wow.
This is just minutes, you go to see them live
and he just gives them the business.
Is he still, like, if we go see him,
you refuse to see this lineup of the Beach Boys.
Yeah, yeah, I don't think I'm gonna enjoy that.
I think we should make a pact,
or not a pact, whatever, you should agree
that if they're still touring in 10 years,
you will go see them.
Yeah, that sounds good, yes.
Yeah, yeah, I'm with you on that.
The tour in 10 years, we should make a date,
we should date it.
It should be Friday, July 5th.
Well, 4th of July is always a big show for them.
Oh, right, that's what we'll do then.
Yeah, so 2034.
2034, if the Beach Boys, whoever is in the band still,
if it's just Stamos and a bunch of other people
and all the originals are dead, you have to go see them.
I mean, that sounds great, yeah, yeah.
So yeah, he's just in a hospital bed
that they put, like, Lays and stuff on.
Lays and an American flag.
We're accustomed to this point that he lies down
while doing it, they just put a microphone on top of him
and then just even more, hey, happy 4th of July.
He zooms in from a hospital.
Just put a screen up.
Hey, and just a big, you know,
God just wanna say God bless America
and God bless President Trump
now in his third consecutive term.
Oh, God.
I'll try to avoid those jokes.
We're all a little edgy.
But yeah, okay, 10 years from now.
Yeah, yeah, I'm in.
I'm excited for you to see, and it has to be, yeah,
any version of it, as long as the official,
even if it's just whoever they sold the name to,
is running an official Beach Boys show
and Stamos is there and they're pretending
it's the original members, you have to see it too.
Imagine Dragons presents the Beach Boys.
If that's what it is.
Yeah, that's great.
I think by then, Mark McGrath is a full-time member.
I think they're gonna draft him.
I think he's gonna do the math and like,
all right, here's what I'll do.
I'll get, all right, the one Sugar Ray guy
I still get along with, he's just coming with me.
He'll be in the Beach Boys.
I only, it's all about the, isn't he already,
it's like, it's all about those three songs.
The three mother songs for me.
Isn't that something that Mark talks about?
Oh yeah, that's familiar.
These songs, they give me life.
They gave us all this.
They gave us this lifestyle and I honored these songs.
So as long as he gets to do the Sugar Ray songs mid-set,
then he'll just be, he'll be the new singer
of the Beach Boys forever.
I think that's, yeah, like a 70-year-old Stamos
will still be in the band.
Yeah, McGrath, Stamos, the last surviving member
of the Wrecking Crew.
What, at the end, 10 years from now?
Yeah, they were real young in the Wrecking Crew.
Luckily, it's the Triangle player.
He just has to bash his head into it every once in a while.
But yeah, if Podcast the Ride's still happening,
that's gonna be an episode in 10 years.
Sure.
10 years from now.
Yeah, yeah.
Siri, Siri set a reminder for 10 years from now
that Scott has to go see the Beach Boys.
Is she gonna talk?
Is this the first appearance of Siri on the show?
If you have Do Not Disturb, I want you to line up.
Oh yeah, it doesn't, but it did set it.
It did set the date.
All right, new rule, always have,
all of us always have Do Not Disturb off
when we record episodes. Yeah, that's a good point.
So that we can talk to Siri.
I should've turned it on.
The main time I turned it on, okay.
Anyway, performance at Be True to Your School,
the cheerleader, the cheerleaders come out,
John manages to play drums at the start
and then guitar for the bulk of it.
He goes back to back with Mike, and as I've said,
nobody plays instruments more than John Stamos.
I don't mean amount of time that he plays them,
I mean amount of playing.
Like Dick Van Dyke and Mary Poppins.
Yes.
Like a one-man band.
Well, I mean, not only that, but also just that he like,
he doesn't just play the guitar regularly.
Right, right.
He puts it all the way above his head.
He stands while drumming.
He's very- He lifts his arms so high.
He shows you, I am playing instruments right now.
Do you see?
He very much wants you to know he's playing instruments.
He's, and that bit, that joke, quote unquote,
is also like, look at me.
Yeah, he's like standing up on the stool.
He's making a big- It's a joke made
so he can drum solo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Mike doing that joke over the course of two minutes,
10 years from now.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, boy.
And I remember.
Because.
It's a-
He'll have a neural link from Elon Musk's company
and he'll just think his thoughts and they'll,
AI will then use his voice and he'll come
through the speaker.
Oh, the first.
He'll just like kind of make like a grimace
and he'll go, ugh.
That's the grimace that means he's telling the joke.
And then you'll, but you'll hear it.
The AI will speak his voice via his thoughts,
via the technology.
So he won't actually have to use his decaying vocal cords.
You will hear Mike Love's voice via AI
straight from his decaying brain.
It's kind of beautiful.
We'll get more, this is why AI helps us.
We all get more life out of it.
The only problem is sometimes his brain wanders
and he'll have like a dark thought that you will hear.
You will hear a dark thought once in a while on stage.
It was me who told the Mansons to kill.
I pinned it on Dennis, but it was always me.
It was always me.
That's right in the middle of good vibrations.
They were peaceful up at Spahn Ranch.
They just played with flowers.
Mike, and then you see somebody like.
I told them to kill dirty hippies.
Backstage.
They're threatening our way of life.
At the booth, like somebody's like, kill us.
Kill us, slash him up.
Kill us, Neuralink.
I went back.
Passes out on the stage.
I tried to get Dakota Fanning and Lena Dunham
and Austin Butler.
I tried to get them to do it.
And then everyone told me they were actors and I left.
Tarantino's gonna want you to go method.
You gotta kill him for real.
Gotta kill him.
Margaret Qualley, I know you can do it.
Vibrations.
I don't like Leo and Brad Pitt
because everybody says they're more handsome than me.
I'll show them who's handsome.
Neuralink Mike Lowe.
You can't be handsome when Austin Butler slashed up
your face.
So anyways, I mean, that sums that up.
Let's move on to the third episode,
which is a two-parter captain video,
season five, episode 25.
At this point, the Beach Boys are finale only.
That's how big of a deal it is to have them on the show.
This is May 5th, 1992, and by this point, much has changed.
The Beach Boys being on Full House is no mere lark.
It's part of the business model.
Mike has realized, look what happened separately
with Kokomo and us being on Full House.
Now I look in the audience, there's seven-year-olds
with the 70-year-olds.
We gotta keep that train flowing.
So they've got a new album coming out,
and this is their attempt to triangulate everything
with the big Full House appearance.
And look, I know people liked, our song was in Cocktail
and everybody likes Tom Cruise,
but it wasn't Tom Cruise singing the song.
What if we could get our heartthrob pal
to sing our new song?
It's got primetime placement, 20 million people watching it.
That will make our new album, Summer in Paradise,
the biggest success we've ever had.
This is the first album they've ever made
with zero participation from Brian Wilson.
I'll show you who's the genius.
I go, oh, watch me, watch me do without him.
I'll run circles around that old psycho.
So he is real cocky heading into this one.
Episode story doesn't particularly matter.
I think there's, I think Jesse,
now Jesse and the Rippers are fully a part of it,
and they're trying to get signed.
They're struggling to get signed by a label.
Well, because Jesse gets fired from the kids' show that...
That happened in this one?
Oh, really? Yes.
Oh, okay.
Dave Goullier, he fires him.
He fires him from Ranger Rick?
Whoa, I didn't realize that.
And he says, why can't you fire the puppet?
It's like, because he's a puppet, we don't pay him.
Boy, I feel you.
I got a lot of rage towards puppets myself.
I can relate to this episode.
Sure, and then he was like, you know what?
I'm gonna put my mind to it.
I'm really gonna work on my music.
And he gets a record contract, then like two days later.
In 20 minutes.
He gets an offer very quickly.
All right, I'm glad you...
I go to these episodes, I go right to the boys.
This is all on Macs, by the way,
if you wanna watch any of it.
And Hulu.
And Hulu too, oh really?
Yeah.
Okay, so at this point,
they just kind of randomly show up
at the kitchen door or the other door.
This time it's just Mike and Bruce Johnston,
who if you see them today, those are the only two left.
Bruce is the only one with allegiance to Mike.
There's not much to say about him.
I always liked him a lot musically.
He wrote great songs.
A song called Deedra is really loved.
Deedri, I guess you'd say.
A song called Disney Girls actually is quite lovely.
Personally, he's kind of a strange guy.
Two weird facts about him.
He was on a Weekend song on the last record.
Oh yeah, you mentioned this.
Called Here We Go Again.
Him and Mike Love's son sing together.
Even though apparently he never met the Weekend during,
he was like over, I was in Malibu
when I laid down some vocals at Skrillex's house.
What, okay.
That's why he's on there.
Kenny G's on a Weekend song too.
Is he really?
I believe.
Kenny, all right.
My guys, he knows, Weekend knows.
I like Jim Carrey on that album too,
doing the interstitials.
He also is a weird guy who at one point,
he was just signing autographs for people
and started saying,
Obama's a socialist asshole.
Don't vote for him if you want to keep any of your money.
So weirdness to Bruce either way.
But here he's all smiles, big quaffed hair.
He's wearing a, maybe the craziest shirt any of them wear.
Yeah, I hooded on this too.
This massive bright blue big dog shirt.
It's a big dog woven sweater, isn't it?
So funny.
It's a sweater or a sweatshirt.
I couldn't tell, but I was like,
he immediately walks in the Tanner door
and I'm like, big dog.
Big dog, yeah, I kind of remember these shirts being around.
Did you have a big dog shirt ever?
Sure, of course.
You think so?
I didn't, not that I was against it,
I'm just saying I didn't have one.
We had a lot of the,
I think we had travel coffee mugs of the Star Wars ones,
the dog bites back, I think it was.
There was a big dog outlets
at some of the Pennsylvania outlet mugs.
So we would always like to look at all the parody mugs.
Big dog's still going.
It was an all big dog store?
Yo, yeah.
Whoa.
Yeah.
You could still get, this is big dogs.
Is that the same big dog or big dogs?
There's a website called big dogs
and this has different big dog shirts.
Big Bow Wow Wow Ski with a Big Lebowski parody.
But it's, yeah, big dogs trademark.
Is that the same as big dog or is this a rip off?
That's a good question.
I'm not sure.
Big dog, oh, it is dogs plural.
Oh, I've been saying dog singular this whole time.
I think I've just been going back and forth
with whatever I say when I think of it.
There's some good shirts here.
I feel like I wanted to buy a couple new shirts
for the summer.
I'd like to buy the one Bruce is wearing.
Oh yeah, there's one where a dog is in a hammock.
It says Department of Relaxation and it's a tank top.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
Jason, you would wear that.
Oh yeah, I love that.
That's what Rob Lowe wears on stage
when we think of that old concert.
Big dogs, that could be a club three.
I think big dogs.
Mike revealed that not,
like big dogs was always a little bawdy,
but not that often.
They were?
You and Gio would always talk about the Big Johnson shirts.
Oh, you want to talk about bawdy, Jason.
The Big Johnson was dirty.
Those were dirt.
They sold those at the Wisconsin Dells.
You would see those in a Spencer's Gifts
and that was like a Leisure Suit Larry style humor.
That was like a-
It was nastier.
Nastier than any big dogs.
That was a bosomy cartoon woman
and then like a lewd remark perhaps.
I did not own any of that.
A lewd remark on ties.
If the bosoms weren't enough,
a lewd remark would come into play.
But no, I did not have any of those.
Oh my goodness.
I would never have one of those.
You would turn your back.
You would leave the town you were in
if you saw one of those.
I'm not a good guy like me, isn't wanted here.
Oh, they've got, I'm on the Big Johnson website now,
which still is around.
They have Hawk Tua shirts, of course.
Oh, that was fast.
Hawk Tua girl.
Was it fast?
Fast for a t-shirt production designing?
They're not so-
It's not fast for like a guy to make,
but for a company to mobilize.
They have to, the Big Johnson brain trust has to meet
and go, so there's a girl.
She has described the act of oral sex
in a very colorful way.
So like Big Johnson fishing gear
and there's these cartoon characters,
the Big Johnson characters, of course.
And it says, she'll be ready to bite
as soon as your fly drops.
So that's the type of thing you would wear on your shirt.
And then they're still doing it decades later.
That's still the brand.
Yeah, because the Wisconsin Dells
and Myrtle Beach are still cities.
Yeah, so I, yeah, I did not,
you had Big Dog, but not Big Johnson.
You never heard of Big Johnson.
I'm sure I saw it on the beach,
but like sold at the boardwalk.
I think it was much more-
Would you wear this Big Johnson shirt
that just says, I love hot moms?
Well, does Jason really wanna broadcast
his inner thoughts like that?
Like Mike loves Neuralink?
Would you rather do that one
or wear like Big Johnson bass boats
that says, cause nothing beats landing a large mouth
on your Big Johnson.
Would you wear that shirt?
I don't think I'd wear any of these.
I'm gonna find one you're gonna wear by the end of this.
And I will-
Can you find me, like the Big Dog shirts
are a lot more cute and marvelous.
You brought up Big Johnson.
You opened up this Pandora's box.
It had, there was no other way
than going through every single shirt
you're seeing on a website.
Exactly.
So I'll find one.
This is on you, Jason.
I'll find one.
Well, if you start adding to eBay and Depop,
you're gonna be here all night.
Well, if we have to, we have to.
If you need to tune out, Mike,
while I say things and to find Jason
a tasteful Big Johnson shirt.
I mean, it's not gonna be fully tasteful, but-
No.
Well, look, this, the Big Dog shirt
that Bruce is wearing is just a big,
it's just the biggest dog head
that could possibly fit onto a shirt.
There's nothing wrong with that.
And now that we're back to food with this,
it's a lot of like, yeah, we're picky.
We heard about your famous home cooking.
And then she can't cook is the-
Yeah, yeah.
So they have to fake that the-
Right.
She has to keep lying about that.
The site crashed.
The Big Johnson site crashed on me.
It just-
Someone's on it.
Oh, Jason's on it looking for shirts for himself.
You guys are crazy.
You're crazy.
The traffic is so high.
Wait, they're giving me two people.
No, they can't.
They didn't pay.
In the same city?
Big Johnson isn't that wealthy.
Now that's no Big Johnson shirts
for anybody for the next month.
We used up the bandwidth.
Right in the time where they were trying to strike.
It's hoctuamania.
Yeah.
I saw someone post a picture from a Trump rally
and two people had a shirt that said,
Trump 2024 and then a cartoon drawing of him.
And then on top it said, spit on that thing.
And it seemed like the gist was like,
they didn't fully learn what the meme was
before making these shirts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like him because he's gonna spit on Biden.
Yeah.
I don't know what this hoctua is about,
but I would love to see Trump do some of this hoctua
to Biden.
Presidential debates just devolved
into octogenarian spitting on each other.
We're not far.
You know what?
You know who took a photo with this hoctua girl?
Shaq.
Wow.
Two days ago.
Oh, DJ Diesel.
DJ Diesel took a photo.
Yeah, they were together.
Wow, wow.
How about it?
A gigantic star and Shaq.
That's right.
So once again, Dr. Love, what are you doing here?
And his hair looks weird.
He's tending to his hair, him, a man.
So it was just very embarrassing.
Yeah.
And this is the wrong time for the Beach Boys
to come over and say that they heard,
you have a home studio now and they wanna jam.
The Beach Boys are here to jam.
So he calls the Rippers over.
We're gonna jam down there and enter Forever.
Now we are dealing with Forever.
They are mid song of this song Forever.
It's being performed by Jesse in this very moany.
That's the sky.
He could not be, that's his angle on the singing.
It's so breathy.
It's so hoctuey.
And he really spits on the vocals, you see.
Yeah, of course.
This finishes, he says, God, man.
Ah, that is such a cool song.
Boy, I tell ya, if I had a song like Forever,
Fatfish Records would sign us like that.
Bruce says, you want it?
You got it.
Wait, what do you mean?
Really, you'd let me record Forever?
Sure, as long as Becky keeps cooking up food like this.
Now, so what has just happened?
If you didn't know, they don't really explain it
to the viewer necessarily.
Forever is a lesser known Beach Boys song
from the early 70s.
They were just jamming together.
Now the Beach Boys have given permission
to Jesse and the Rippers to record their own version of it.
Here's what's strange.
This has bugged me for a very long time.
This song's from maybe my favorite album
besides Pet Sand, Sunflower.
Maybe one of the only Beach Boys albums
that's like perfect front to back.
Just like, oh, what a, that's exactly where the good,
just mellow, beautiful, gentle Beach Boys music lives.
And a big part of it is Forever, the original version.
If you've never heard it, I encourage you to look it up.
And this is one of the more prominent songs
by Dennis Wilson, drummer of the Beach Boys,
who was not putting himself out there as a songwriter
too much up until this point.
And then he starts contributing songs to the albums
because Brian started checked out.
So like, who's gonna be writing?
He starts giving songs like this and they're wonderful.
Everyone's like, who knew he had this in him?
It's like, it's his primary song at this point.
And when this episode is made,
he's the only member who has passed away.
He's the only dead Beach Boy.
Cut to, boy, I wish we could do that.
You want it?
You got it.
Yeah, as long as they get more cooking.
How are all of the songs in the catalog,
how is the one that they give over to be done
in this schlocky sitcom way, the one by the dead guy?
Does this not seem somewhat disrespectful?
Yeah, it seems, well, what is your opinion?
Cause I really don't have one.
Like, is your opinion that they were like,
well, he's the one who did it,
that's why we're giving it away.
Or did they think that this would have the best chances
as a hit with Stamos?
I think, according to his book,
I think that he had,
maybe it comes from a more innocent place.
Maybe he had a fascination with this song,
loved the song as do I.
John, you mean?
Yeah, Stamos, yeah.
And maybe he proposed it all himself.
This might not have been some nefarious,
oh, I know what we could do.
Cause it seems weird.
If we're gonna trash one of these songs,
we could give him, you know,
Dennis's pile of shit.
Dennis, fuck with me, and I don't have to fuck with him.
Because this wasn't a song in the vernacular.
They wouldn't have played this live.
This was sort of, with Dennis's passing,
this was not a song that they really talked about.
Well, maybe John also strategically,
was there any strategy involved?
Or was it just literally a song he really liked
that they maybe didn't pay so much attention to?
That is how he friends him, certainly.
Now, it certainly ends up lending itself
to this sort of power ballad arrangement.
But I'm really, my Beach Boys episodes
have been about celebrating the bad,
the recognizing the good.
And if you've never heard the original forever,
what a lovely song.
It's so much malware and just like,
it's just introspective.
It's so like what's in Dennis's heart.
It's wonderful.
And that it becomes that most people think, I think,
that's that stupid song from Full House.
Yeah.
Well, we've talked a little bit about it,
Dennis's solo album, which like,
the Dennis songs like, almost in the same way
that like some big star hits me,
or like Chris Bell solo, where you're like,
this is even beyond like,
this is truly transferring like a feeling,
like what's in your brain or your heart is being like,
just, it hurts you, yeah.
And forever is such a funny,
for the version that Stamos does is so cheesy.
It's really funny.
It is just, boy, did they cheese it up.
And this is where, I'm glad, it's funny,
this is the end of it because like,
it does really culminate in almost like,
the Beach Boys have collaborated with a sitcom
to make up a new pop hit.
If you're Stamos though.
On the corpse of the one dead member.
Cause if you're Stamos though,
and you've been playing with the Beach Boys now
for a couple of years, you're kind of in the band.
What is then the next step?
The next step is that,
why am I not singing one of the songs?
So I don't want to make him seem so nefarious,
but I bet there was some strategy
cause he certainly likes people to know
he's in the Beach Boys.
Even if you've gone to the concert,
he's making you know,
hey, hey, everybody notice this,
I'm in the Beach Boys.
He's also, let's think about what else he is.
This whole episode we've been talking about
kind of the lack of charisma of these gentlemen.
There's nothing cool about Al Jardine.
Brian Wilson was always an uncomfortable,
even younger days, even before his troubles.
He was not at ease as,
he was not a John or a Paul, right?
Dennis was always the comfortable one,
the hot one, the only hot one, the only one.
Aaron said that he's the only one
who could be construed as attractive.
And especially, and he looked great in the 70s too.
Like, you know, once he grew the hair out
and he's a little more rugged,
he's the rugged long-haired drummer of the Beach Boys.
Who does that become?
John Stamos.
So it's almost like his way of like,
I'm gonna do Dennis's,
I'm officially taking the mantle.
Yeah, and I'm doing his song too.
And for such a big Beach Boys fan,
I could see that being like premeditated.
I could see him thinking that too.
Cause Mike has even said like,
you're the young stud in the band.
He's a scholar of Beach Boys history.
He knows Dennis.
I mean, following that thread of like,
what if I sang the song?
Do you think he cushioned that?
Cause the events of the episode
make Uncle Jesse look very foolish.
Yes, indeed.
Yeah. Sure.
Yeah, things end up very silly.
Yeah, they really piss on the song
even further as it goes.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, if I were jockeying to get in there,
I wouldn't be so bold as to be the new Dennis.
I'd fish for being the new Al Jardine.
Right.
Where I just kind of do like long rambles
about like Robert Frost between songs.
And then like,
hey, here's a song about the Santa Ana winds.
Fire wind.
It's a real one if you don't know.
I don't know that.
He expires, at the top of the song,
he's like, there's a condition.
He expires like a doctor.
There's a condition in California
called the Santa Ana winds.
Fire wind.
What's the environmental song
where like there's a video with like Paul McCartney
at the end walking out of some Grammy ceremony.
Don't Fight the Sea.
Don't Fight the Sea, thank you.
Yes, yeah.
He got a half interest, like,
hey Paul, I made this video,
it's called Don't Fight the Sea.
You just really quickly look down the barrel of the lens
and say, don't fight the sea.
And then he does with as much Paul,
as much of like Paul Panache as a tired Paul can do.
He's like, don't fight the sea.
And he by the halfway through that four word sentence,
he's looking the other way.
Yeah, he's leaving.
He's clearly like, can we do one more?
Nope, nope, good, peace and love.
Hey, all right, love you buddy.
Anyway, so a really, really quick clip as they,
I don't know, I don't think it needs any,
so the jam session continues.
I mean, this is cool.
That would be great if we did that.
I mean, you know, normally record stuff would be right,
but quite frankly, who's buying it?
You know what, Elvis never recorded anything he wrote.
I wonder what it would have been like
if Elvis had done a Beach Boys song.
If everybody had an ocean across the USA.
That's scary.
How about a like this, though?
If everybody had an ocean.
Your Mike Love voice and Boogmane voice are very similar.
Well, yeah, yeah, there's some crossover in energy.
Yeah.
Sometimes I think he and I have a light
Mike and Brian dynamic.
Yes, yes.
So anyways, also later in this song,
he sings the line in Surfing USA,
a bushy, bushy blonde hairdo,
and he picks up some of DJ Tanner's hair.
No!
And then kind of drop, lets it go.
Evil.
She is 16 years old.
When this is occurring.
It's terrifying.
This has always creeped me out.
Thank you for voting for this topic
so I could get that off my chest.
I had crushes on other girls, too, growing up.
They were my age.
Yes, yes.
I am like two months older than the Olsen twins.
Do you have a crush on?
Not then, you didn't.
Not as much, not Michelle.
No, I am like DJ. You're this two months
older than the Olsen twins?
They are about my age.
Maybe it's six months.
They're right around.
But that's more that you're waiting for.
DJ and Stephanie.
Yeah, yeah.
I definitely had crushes on them.
Olsen's is later.
Olsen's is when they're doing like Island in the Sun
and all these movies.
So old time.
They're 86.
They're 86, okay.
So anyway, he does record forever.
He takes it to Fatfish Music.
They say we're in.
Fatfish Music signs him.
David Janellori, in fact.
Hey guys, David Janellori from Fatfish Records
is coming over.
This actor comes out like,
yeah, oh Jesse, you love it.
Duh, you're just gonna do gangbusters.
I'm like, this guy, why does he look so familiar?
Who is this actor?
I look it up.
The record executive is played by Brian Robbins,
who is currently the CEO of Paramount Pictures
and the president of Nickelodeon.
Wow.
And in a recent power shift after Bob Bakish left,
all of Paramount is controlled by three people
and he's one of them.
Whoa.
Yeah, so he's a real life David Janellori
of Fatfish Music now.
He also, his directorial filmography
on the way to being an executive is pretty amazing.
Good Burger, Ready to Rumble, Hardfall,
Disney Shaggy Dog, Meet Dave,
and Brian Wilson's favorite movie, Norbit.
Right, yes.
Geez, wait a minute.
You guys are in an episode with a director in Norbit?
Man, that's out of sight.
Isn't there a thing recently on Twitter
where people are talking about how much Brian Wilson
thinks the song Shorten and Bread
is the greatest song of all time?
Yeah, there's Shorten and Bread.
I think that's from a book,
His Obsession with Shorten and Bread.
There is a story and this might have been,
this might have been with Elton John.
It might have been with Elton John
and even Brian Toppin, perhaps.
I could be wrong, but it's big people like that
who are like, hey, do you wanna come hang out
at Brian Wilson's house?
Yes, I do, that's great.
Hey, come to the piano, you guys are great.
You're out of sight.
You're piano man, just like me.
All right, here, let's,
why don't we do a little bit of Shorten and Bread?
And then, mama's little bit, and then they start
and it's a song kind of like,
it's like in a round, right, a little bit.
So it keeps going and going and going
and it does not end.
And like maybe hours in, Elton John backs out of the room.
All right, I think I've had my fill of Shorten and Bread.
There are multiple Shorten and Bread anecdotes.
Yeah, somebody's posting them.
Are you recording it?
And then.
Yeah, I was trying to find it.
There's a recorded version of it.
I know that.
Trying to get people to jam on it or.
This is only just because I literally just saw it,
a picture of Elton, Bernie, Alice Cooper, and Paul Linde
all hanging out, completely drunk and smoking.
Damn.
Pretty good picture.
Geez, these are the days.
Put that on a big Johnson shirt.
Well, let me know any further
Shorten and Bread information you find.
Anyway, David Janellori is, you know,
he signs him, that's the dream,
but he's a little bit of a sleaze
and he just kind of runs some game on Jesse
and says, yeah, we're gonna film
the hottest dance video you ever seen.
And he's like, dance video?
I don't dance.
Oh, by the time we're through with you,
everybody's gonna be doing the Jess Man.
And then that's the story of part two
is that he's manipulated into doing a hammer type,
baggy pants, Arabian Nights themed number.
And when I play this,
I understand that it's supposed to be bad.
What they're showing us is
that he's being asked to do a song
that's very out of character
and so that then later on, he can do it my way.
That said, again, Dead Beach Boys song,
and this is being done to it on television.
More people are seeing this
than anybody who heard the original song.
This is unforgivable.
Ooh.
["Dead Beach Boys"]
It's really bad.
This is a meaningful song to this man who has died.
He's gone.
Yeah.
Drowned.
He was just looking for memories,
just getting a framed photo
from off his Marina Del Rey boat.
And he went down just because he was on a lot of cocaine
and alcohol and we lost him.
And now this is happening.
He's dressed like Aladdin and we're doing a wrap.
Oh boy.
Rough, rough, rough stuff.
So anyway, this is proof, ultimately.
Fat Fish is gonna drop him,
but then he pretends he has another offer,
even though that's just Michelle from her piggy bank.
But they start telling the Fat Fish guy,
hey, you know what?
If you don't sign him, you're gonna be the biggest fool.
You'll be like the guy who didn't sign the Beatles.
I mean, you're looking at a number one record here.
Just file that away,
that they keep saying this is a number one record.
And then we get to Forever, the music video.
You guys remembered that.
You have like strong memories of Forever.
Of course.
What do you remember thinking about it at the time?
That I didn't like it.
That I didn't like any part of it.
That I'm like, when will this part of the show be over?
Yeah, because we leave the style of the show.
It just becomes like kind of a big
post-November rain music video.
Yeah, a lot of candles.
So many candles.
I was likely nervous by all the lit candles everywhere.
How old is that church?
That thing could go in a second.
Tinder box.
Yes, yes.
Just a powder gag.
A lot of arbitrary sepia and black and white.
And then him, he's naked in a bed outside the church
and just so just brooding
and the most overproduced drums ever.
And a lot of him holding up babies
to where you see their little ball sacks from behind.
And you're like, I don't know.
I'm not inherently bothered by a naked baby.
I don't post a lot of, even the green circle.
I'm not posting naked pictures of my son.
But anyway, even if that is your deal,
it's like, that's not his babies though.
These are actor babies.
This is a guy, this is like a weird shirtless guy,
unshaven, holding up not his own babies.
I'm looking at their butts.
It's very uncomfortable.
This, does he talk about this video in his book at all?
I don't know if they really go into the video.
Okay, cause like this is a sincere attempt
at something cool.
Yeah.
Like on his part.
Which I feel like these things always try to avoid.
How can we not get back into a corner
where we have to actually convey that?
And then the thing works and it's good.
Yeah.
They do it here, they go for it.
They go for it.
And it's just, yes, it's for a kid swinging a huge mess.
Cause like the audience is kids and families.
So what were you think,
what was the thought process behind this type of a video?
I never want to see this video again
is I'm sure what I thought as a kid,
I wasn't not in like that mean a term.
I think I was probably like,
oh, he's in a grownup rock star
and this is what music videos.
But you didn't like it, did you?
I don't really remember it.
You probably just didn't process it.
This is a thing for adults.
You blacked it out.
Yeah.
I don't know when you're told,
like I could see that actually.
I'll take their word for it.
The John Stamos, big adult contemporary star.
I definitely more remembered the sleazy record producer
cause that was such a go-to in like 90s sitcoms.
It's like, oh, yeah, hey, we really liked this song
you recorded with your friends at the mall.
I'm John sleaze bag.
I'd like to give you a deal.
And like there's a creepiest character
which looking back on now, it's like,
oh, this is sitcom writer is going like,
I've met a lot of fucking scumbags in this town.
So I'm gonna make, put all of them into this one guy.
The creator of the show, full house.
Oh, right, right, right, I forgot.
Take a look, Google that.
Real life David Janeler.
Google that.
But like, I'm just like as a kid, even a five-year-old,
I would watch the monkeys in Nickelodeon.
I would see, you see the, you can call me Al video
or something and you're like, this is, I like this.
This is fun.
This is not fun for a kid.
I mean, look, I love it now.
Well, sure, I'm not saying it's bad now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm just saying it's a, what a weird choice for a kid's,
I'd say the song would be different, I suppose.
Song choice would be different.
Would you not, I mean, I think,
would you not think of it as a success for full house?
Because I feel like it's like a very memorable part
of the show.
I guess that's true.
And then the show comes back in fuller house
and we're still, you know, like, we,
But do you think forever is the reason?
Not the reason, but do you, just like,
as far as memorable episodes,
even if some of the memorable memorableness is cheesiness,
it's still like, if you had, all right,
flash to 10 full house episodes.
It was, it was an interesting choice.
Yeah.
That sticks out.
That's true.
I think it's more of a success for full house
than it is for the Beach Boys.
Yeah.
Who did include it on their album.
The album ends with, so the 92 album Summer in Paradise
ends with this.
Is this a backdoor pilot for Stamos's music career?
Probably, yeah.
Sneaking on to a, he must have occurred to him,
like, I could get a full album out, oh, totally.
I never thought about that, but yeah, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, that's what it is.
Because if this was a hit, then there absolutely would be.
Right.
Because look, he is a good musician.
Sure.
And he sings it fine.
It's just all, it's all steeped in cheesiness
and the fact that he's like usually performing
in like a black leather vest and the hair,
like he's, I don't know.
He's in this, is Brian Adams the only thing
that's like kind of, like what else is in the genre
of forever?
That's a good question.
That's all I can think of.
Well, like, do you count like air supply in this show?
I mean, sort of?
No, that's a different thing.
That's like 80s easy listening.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm like 90s where it's, that's all,
because he feels, because he's got that
like open-shirt lethario thing.
It's like that song, like,
have you ever really, really, really, really, really,
or it's kind of like, not how he looks,
but it's kind of like 90s Don Henley.
Yes.
It's a little like divorce rock.
I like the version of like a hammer,
like what the record labels were looking for at the time.
This is still, this made such an impact
on the popular consciousness.
There is still a generation or two who thinks this what,
this is what rap music is.
You're saying the hammer did?
The hammer like kind of dance,
like the full house version of hip hop.
Oh, that that's what hip hop was in a certain time.
Yeah, yeah, right, right.
Anyway, it's like, yeah, it's just,
or I'm making, do we got all the details?
Okay, yeah, Naked Babies, Icky, great, said it.
Drumming on Gems said it.
Last Piano Note, he blows out the candle on it.
It's just, oh, what a big pile of cheese.
It's incredible.
But yeah, you're right.
It just, it's weird.
It's weird.
And I don't think, and I don't think like if you actually,
he shows up on a fake MTV show
hosted by Martha Quinn to get on the air.
Martha Quinn appearance, yeah.
Martha Quinn's on it.
The guy who tries to cheat Jesse out of dance,
it's like the coolest character who's ever on full,
like he's a legitimately like cool guy.
I like his jacket and hat.
I'm jealous of that.
Oh, all right.
I never had a big Letterman's jacket,
fake money jacket like that.
They did convey genuine cool with somebody.
But anyway, also a quick note about the music video.
Carl Wilson didn't return to be on the sitcom,
but he does sing in the song.
And it's why I like him.
Is it even in this cheesy song?
He's giving his all.
He sounds fantastic.
He's in the music video.
Al Jardine is not in it because at the time,
and this is per an article that Doug Jones wrote
about this album, Summer in Paradise,
Al Jardine was suspended
due to having a severe attitude problem.
So he's not on the show or on the thing.
So again, they keep saying this could be big number one.
And then later on,
they convey that the song is number one in Japan.
At least in the world of Full House,
this song is a gigantic hit in real life.
Forever on the Beach Boys album, Summer in Paradise,
as a single makes it to number 100 in Australia.
And that is the end of the charting of Forever.
Also, the album that it came from, Summer in Paradise,
which again, we're putting our eggs into this basket.
We're using the mechanism of this show.
We're gonna launch a full album
with all the might of Full House.
And the album comes out,
supposedly sold less than a thousand copies.
Whoa.
Wow.
Back then.
Yes, in peak CD sales.
Also per Doug,
he said that they shifted to another number at some point.
They're like, no, it's 125,000.
That's crazy.
It's not a thousand.
And he claims that people were saying that like,
no, that's how many you shipped.
That's not how many it sold.
Oh.
So all that, and it, I think,
bankrupted the independent label that it was released on.
Whoa.
So this blew up in Mike's face in a massive way.
Brian Wilson vindicated this album.
The album received nightmarish reviews.
People still are like,
is this one of the worst albums ever recorded?
Forever is part of the conversation of why it's so bad.
The Beach Boys do not record a mostly original album
for 20 years after this.
This thing was a huge fail.
Now Wondry wanted some of Aunt Becky's cooking.
He's nearly penniless.
He's like, who have I ever,
all right, let me think about anybody
who ever won one of our contests.
Maybe I can impress my way into the door
and eat some of their home cooking.
He's so filled with rage of being broke.
He didn't even notice that he was essentially eating
California Chicken Cafe on China platters.
He wouldn't know.
He doesn't go to, he can't go to restaurants anymore.
I don't know what Cuckoo Roos is.
It's been out of business for 10 years.
It's out of cover and reference in it.
Yeah.
Yeah, Cuckoo Roos feels like,
well everybody knows a little place like Cuckoo Roos.
It's where you wanna go, get away from it all.
Anyway, this is the last Beach Boys appearance
forever returns because they have to convey
that it's number one in Japan
in an episode called Road to Tokyo
where there's a big produced performance of it
with a rabid crowd.
This taping was attended by Doug Jones as a child
who in a DJ fashion won a raffle
to get to go to the taping.
Wow.
But I think with that, that closes out really
the Beach Boys full house involvement.
Stamos later appeared in a music video,
a cover of Crocodile Rock,
one of the most embarrassing things I've ever seen.
The Beach Boys all wear the worst suits
ever worn by 50 year old men.
They dance around the golfing stuff in Ventura.
It's really something worth checking out.
That's quite a statement,
the worst suits 50 year olds have ever worn.
That's doing a lot.
I guess I'd have to see a full, I mean, I don't know.
If you're in, maybe like,
if you're a white guy wearing like a Steve Harvey
like brick pattern type suit.
Oh yeah, like a Roger Stone kind of.
Oh yes, all right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, you know what?
They do all look like Roger Stone.
That's who I can only assume is a pal of mine.
Who they is at Mar-a-Lago a lot.
Yeah, in his part time Roger Stone manages the band.
He works his men at Stone Magic.
Anyway, that's sort of the story of that
from the dream of the first one
to the record sale collapse of the last one.
But thank you Augustine for setting this one up.
I mean, clearly a ton to say.
And once again, one of the longest episodes.
I do feel like I talked forever as Dennis
and then Stamos threaten to in the song.
Oh wait, one more little postscript.
I love stiff acting on a family sitcom of a band
so much that I got an incredible opportunity
to reproduce my love of these episodes
with the resources of Funny or Die
because we heard that the band Chicago
wanted to make a video with Funny or Die.
And somebody ran down the hall and said,
didn't you write a sketch about Chicago?
Yes I did, get down there right now.
I just had written it for fun.
I was maybe gonna put like whoever be in it
because nobody knows what Chicago looks like
for the most part.
And then I got to make this.
I got on a set.
I made what was essentially my tribute.
It's called Chicago and Me.
It's on YouTube, look it up.
The premise is that the whole band Chicago
adopts a kid together.
They all signed the adoption form together
and they're all in it
but they didn't get the rights to Chicago's music.
So they act but don't perform any of their songs
which is the only reason why you'd ever want
to have Chicago do a sitcom.
So that's on YouTube, check that out.
And I got to like live the fantasy of directing
a Beach Boys Full House episode with like their peers.
I fucking love Chicago.
This is crazy to do.
It was the real horn section.
I got to direct Jimmy Pankow.
I got to direct Robert Lamb.
I got to direct Jason Scheff
who was then the singer of this band.
Now has gone solo and he often performs
at Epcot's Eat to the Beat.
Of course he does.
Yeah so imagine me shoulder to shoulder
with a real Eat to the Beat performer.
Eat to the Beat lineup just came out I believe
a day or two ago.
Oh whoa.
That should be, it's too late now to,
this is a long episode.
We should have live streamed.
I want to figure out a way to on microphone reveal that.
But anyway, check that out.
My love letter to these episodes as was this.
Thanks for Augustine for letting us do it.
Just telling us to do it.
Thank you for voting for it.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done freedom fighters.
And I hope you enjoyed that
but I guess apologies for the poll otherwise.
Yeah sorry.
We'll try to rectify that
with a cool cat named Nick Weinger.
Yeah.
What are you heading for Mike?
Well I have a shirt here I'd like Jason to wear.
It's $70 on eBay but it says big Johnson revolvers
and then there's like sort of a busty lady cop
and then sort of like a smaller like meek man
who's holding a big gun.
It says you never shoot blanks
when you're packing a big Johnson.
So I think I'll be getting that for you.
Would you wear it?
A lot of upsetting elements of that shirt.
Which part is upsetting other than the slogan?
I think the casual gun use, the cop,
that sexy lady cop.
Well it sounds like a no
but maybe if you want an episode of Club 3 vote for,
ask Jason if he would wear this shirt as a topic.
Pitch shirts for Jason to wear yeah.
I don't know I think that's cool.
I think you put that on and now you're getting
some attention from a couple of cheerleaders.