Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate, today a therapy session about the ultimate
toys we were deprived of as kids.
I'm Scott Gardner, I've got a lot to work through today, Mike Carlson.
Yeah, me too.
So I'm preemptively sad, usually I'm sad by the end of every Podcast The Ride episode
just for various reasons, but today I'm sad ahead of time.
Everyone?
Yeah, I'm just very sensitive and I hide it well.
Gee, well except the ones where you announce it, Jason Sheridan has to leave that for too
long.
Yeah, there's so much already to deconstruct.
Already?
Already, Mike.
Oh, with what I just said you mean?
The toys we didn't get, I've got stories about that, Mike's hidden sadness, like this
is...
Well, I mean, this came up recently because you just came out of the gate like, look,
I don't want to complain, but I don't want to be dark, but, and then it was that you
don't get to go to something called Quacky Duck City because it's only in Tokyo.
It was still mildly baffling energy to me, although I guess I started with something
similar here.
But you know, at least I take comfort in that no one gets to do any of what we're talking
about today.
It's all unbuilt stuff.
That's a good point, because if other people were having fun, then I would be jealous and
sad, but I'm just sad now.
Yeah, no one got to meet the light keepers.
Imagine who we would be if we got to spend time with the light keepers.
Oh boy, I wish.
We would have retained their light, it would have carried us into adulthood instead of
the pure black dark that is in us instead.
Yeah, which in Mike's case is why half of the music of Olivia Rodrigo resonates so much
because it taps into that that darkness and that angst.
You know, there's a Taylor Swift song she has on her new album called So High School
that I really like.
It's really good, but it's about being like in high school again.
So it's like really doing a couple of things, making me feel young because of the lyrics,
but also because Taylor Swift is a popular music artist.
I feel young in that way as well.
Let me ask, are you a light keeper in disguise?
Maybe.
Because that sounded like a very quote unquote human sense.
Yeah, there was a lot.
Yeah, very normal things that a human being, a flesh human being would say.
It makes me feel young because Taylor Swift is a pop star singer person.
Yeah, it's like an AI.
It's like I'm hosting a show, but I'm not here.
It's an AI of me hosting.
It makes you feel young because it's about high school.
Yeah, well, right.
Because it says the words high school in it.
Well, no, but it's about, there's specifics in it about like American Pie and Grand Theft
Auto.
She says, touch me while your bros play Grand Theft Auto, I believe, in the thing, in the
song.
It's not a scenario I've ever been in or wanted to be in.
Neither have I.
It was a little inappropriate for young, I guess, I guess for some people, it was normal.
It takes you back.
So it takes you back to high school memories that you don't have because they didn't happen
because you wouldn't have been in that position.
A common thing on the show is me having nostalgia for things I didn't do, like the Pleasure
Island episode and then this perhaps because it never existed, but still I have nostalgia
for something that didn't happen.
I think this is common as well.
I like I'm a big Hold Steady fan and there's just constant like people overdosing in those
songs and having like really messy breakups.
I've had none of that.
These are all like fantasies, but like for some reason I'm nostalgia for the characters
from the Craig Finns song.
You fantasize about overdosing?
No, I don't.
I'm just saying, though, like this feels like, oh yeah, I remember when I was hanging out
like back in these days with these characters and like, I'm like, you didn't hang out.
You were not partying like these people were partying.
This is not your life.
I hate to say, I think both of you, I think all of us would be the ones playing Grand
Theft Auto and yet none of us would be referred to as bros.
We're not in the other room with Taylor.
That's true.
And probably going, hey, keep it down back there.
Are you touching her?
Would you stop it?
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
I hear moaning.
Go in another room, allow some privacy, some decorum.
I'm on a heist.
I'm doing a heist over here.
I've got three stars.
The police are after me.
I stole a cop car.
And you're doing your hanky panky over there.
Can we stick to the missions when we go off the rails, it just gets a little foul.
I just want to, I want to achieve things and we get out of the car and start beating people
up.
I want a low body count on this mission.
All right.
I don't want any shenanigans.
That's the sign of a success.
Yeah.
Was anyone
Not a body count, not a body count in regards to like a high school sex haver.
You are, you've already got the low body count in one way.
I want it the other way.
Now you've gone from AI to serial killer.
You think stacking up how many people, how many bodies you've had sexual encounters with
is a body count?
No, that's a young person.
Jason, help me out here.
That's what young people call the monosexual partners.
Young people in videos say, what's your body count?
Listener, you have to know this is one of those times that Mike is pointing and pointing
and pointing.
I'm not crazy for this.
When he's fired up, we point and point.
This is real.
A body count can refer to sexual partners, romantic partners, or the number of people
you've killed in Grand Theft Auto.
Yes.
And this will come.
This is not obscure.
Or IST's band.
Mike, I want to say, you are essentially pining.
It's like the Hollywood that never was and always will be.
The plaque that's in MGM Studio, that's kind of like back in high school.
That feels like that to me.
The high school
That never was.
The high school that never was.
And will always haunt you.
It could have been so perfect, if only.
This doesn't make sense to me.
Is not your life better now than it was in high school?
Well, sure, of course.
So why do you still want high school to have been good?
Well, the movies and TV tell me it's going to be a wild, fun time, and it was not.
I think that's what I'm saying.
I think it's probably not for most people.
The idea of still that you wish that high school was great.
I think that's still in there.
I think this is most popular culture.
I think so, too.
I think most people in their mind wish high school was better.
I think it fuels a lot of people in their adult lives up until they die.
They're trying to fix mistakes from high school.
Some people use it in a destructive way.
But I think that's a common thing where your brain is trying to kind of like...
The people who like to spend their time trying to prank deans.
Schools they don't even go to.
And that's just...
There's a thin line between pranking and assault.
Yes, that's true.
That is one way this can manifest.
Yeah, you unleash three pigs in the school and you paint on their backs one, two, four.
But there is no pig three.
But they're looking.
They think there's a pig three.
So that adds to the prank.
OK, that is a good prank.
From something?
Or is that a prank you just came up with?
I'm sure it's shown up in TV.
I feel like I was just heard it as an urban legend.
You didn't commit this prank because you would never...
No, no.
Yeah.
Would you prank us in that way?
No, probably not.
Seems an elaborate prank, I suppose.
So a bunch of pigs have burst into the recording and said, well, this is a podcast.
Well, now we know who's responsible if a bunch of pigs burst in here.
So I guess you can't do it now.
Well, if you can...
Jason just looked at me like, oh, can't I paint with pig bloods on my hands?
I was using a dramatic pause.
That was purposeful dead air.
Well, if...
It was for a reason.
I was milking, you see.
No.
OK, well, if we can get our heads in the present and out of a high school that never was and
never can be in order to make this episode happen, and if us, the human podcaster stars
can get through this episode and we can talk about, well, this, I guess, that's all confusing
because now we're talking about a future that never was and never can be unless they go
back and do these plans again, because we're talking about Tomorrowland 2055, the unofficial,
perhaps official, well, official enough because they use this logo, I guess they were going
to call it this.
But this is the unbuilt Tomorrowland redo for Disneyland in the early 90s.
We talked recently about the rocket rods and as part of that, the Tomorrowland redo that
did happen in 1998, which was meant to fix Tomorrowland forever so that we would never
have to go back and redo it again.
And instead, it's almost immediately after was in a permanent state of always needing
a redo, perhaps more than ever.
A heartbreaking thing, especially given that this was potentially in the cards.
I know.
It's just, it feels tragic.
As we've said over and over and over again on the show, this thing could have at least
given us what we want.
It would have fulfilled the promise of Tomorrowland and made it our favorite place in the park,
potentially.
That's all they said for me.
I'm sure if they carried out these plans, I think I would still, Tomorrowland would
be my zone in Disneyland.
I feel like visually, this might be pretty timeless.
If all these lighting effects worked, because I think what they were pitching is kind of
proto version of stuff they have done elsewhere and that has been very successful elsewhere.
So there was an opportunity here, much like High School Us, that was blown.
I know.
There are similar levels of tragic, I think, for having not gone the right way in my mind.
Now, if we have time or want to, there is also the talk of talking about another unbuilt
Tomorrowland in Tokyo, Sci-Fi City.
Did you guys look into Sci-Fi City at all?
We could touch on that.
I'm not pining for that one as much, although there are incredibly cool ideas.
As we head towards an episode where we try to crack the Tomorrowland problem, I think
it's good to touch on these unbuilt ideas and maybe they end up influencing what we
end up proposing, either at mega budget or micro budget levels.
So Tomorrowland 2055, have you guys, has it been similar, basically we're working with
three pieces of concept art here.
There's not a lot.
Yeah, it's not.
I was like, oh yeah, well now I'll dig in and find, but it is basically the big ones
I've seen.
Yes.
There's a lot out there, but they are, what is out there is intriguing enough to haunt
you for sure.
Oh yeah.
For sure.
Yes.
Did you guys, I guess we should start, this is like the overview of the land, this kind
of glowing gems.
Yes.
And this was, who knows how far this got.
That looks like heaven to me.
It looks like-
It does.
It kind of does.
Yes.
If you told me that there definitively is a heaven and it looks like the concept art
you just showed, I'd say that's fine.
I'm ready to die.
As long as it's bigger, I'm like, cause that doesn't seem like enough to fit, you know,
every soul that's ever, well not every soul, cause some go to hell.
Yeah, yeah, but I completely agree.
I mean, it feels like a really cool mall or heaven.
Which I guess is the same thing.
Same thing to me.
So basics here.
In terms of that, yeah, that overall vibe, which seems so much more coherent and consistent
and forward thinking than obviously what we ended up getting.
But even like, I mean, one big question I have is, would this have been better than
any of what we got?
Would this have been better than Discovery Land, which remains kind of successful in
Paris?
Is it maybe better than Tomorrowland 94?
The redo that happened in Disney World, if it was the ultimately achieved version of
that concept art?
I feel like maybe.
I think this could have been best Tomorrowland.
I think very possibly, yes, I think you're probably right.
I would be interested to know what it looked like during the day, cause what we see here
looks like everything's illuminated and they're sparkly and things, there's different colors
on the sides of buildings that kind of pop and almost make it look like they're stars.
But I wonder, I just wonder what that would look like during the day.
Would it look a little cheap, especially in this year?
Like I could see a version where this is just an amazing like a blue sky version and ultimately
what we got still looks cool, but it looks a little cheaper.
It looks a little less inviting, less heaven-like, I guess.
A lot.
Yeah, a lot.
There's this piece of art of the Carousel Theater building that they were going to kind
of turn into Flying Saucer, again, drawn at night to emphasize all the lighting rigs.
But it could have.
I mean, it definitely could have.
I think it was definitely, it would have been in the mix for best one.
Well, you still got amazing architecture either way and like, you know, and we're looking
at cool rock work and cool spires, you know, I mean, that stuff stays.
And I think if the inherent colors are neat, then they are.
Yes, yes.
I think what's cool about this is that, well, like some of the other, you know, there's
like mildly a story, I would say, to some of the Tomorrowland re-dos that did end up
happening and this would have had a general buy-in in sort of a galaxy's edge way before
you even enter the land.
And the buy-in is crystals.
The story is crystals.
Yeah.
It's the story of crystals.
They, like in digging up and trying to redo Tomorrowland, they happened upon ancient supernatural
crystals, beacons buried beneath the earth long ago.
Great.
Yeah.
Just like kind of at the sewer line of what ended up getting turned into Disneyland.
It's lucky how that worked out.
So in this, like, where should we put all these crystals?
Orange groves?
Those orange groves right there.
It seems like nobody's touching those for a while.
So aliens planted crystals and now they are uncovered and exposed to earth's sun and the
glowing crystals are transmitting messages deep into space, drawing aliens who had long
forgotten about earth.
Yeah.
Neat.
That is cool.
Yeah.
Big communication crystals.
A lot to read into if you are a crystals kind of person.
Yeah.
It's one of my favorite theme park conceits of like, we were building a ride or we were
shooting a movie and then it turns out, I thinking of the mummy ride in Florida.
It's like, oh, we were filming a movie and we accidentally unleashed the mummy.
Yeah.
It's funny how this ends up working out.
It's like certain themes are just inherently imbued in certain plots of land and the future
part of this park, like it, you know, it's that way because it had crystals and this
sound stage is this way because there really were mummies under there.
It's kind of magical.
If you think about it.
Yeah, very magical.
Yes.
And as a kid, especially that would actually make, if you're in that right age where you're
like a little bit logical, but you still believe in things like that's the perfect narrative
for that, where you're like, I'm a kid, I know mummies aren't real, but I am a little
afraid still.
I'm still kind of a kid.
And then you go on that ride and it really walks your brain into a reality where maybe
the mummy is real, by the way, like there's a perfect, like, I don't know what the everyone's
different, but like, you know, 11 to say 30 for some of us, but like 11 to like 15 or
something where you're like, I'm, I'm an adult now basically, but I'm kind of afraid of mummies.
Like it's a really good way to bridge that.
You've taken the PSAT, but you're still a little scared of those mummies.
You're still a little scared of mummies.
I would say if we're looking for reasons why your ultimate Taylor Swift, make out with
your bros, what make out while bros play grand theft, if you're looking for why your high
school experience wasn't like this, perhaps fear of mummies as a teenager might factor
into.
Yeah, of course that was part of it.
Yes, of course.
The big thing holding you back was being, that even at any house party, I can't trust
this.
I don't know.
I don't know who half of these people are.
One might be a mummy.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, I, but if you just give me a little chance, I'm going to razzle dazzle you and
told you about the magic of storytelling.
Well, you, that's what was waiting.
That was what your problem.
Why won't a pretty girl come talk to me so I can convey the power of storytelling?
You wanted to talk about the power of stories.
Yeah.
And old actors.
Say, baby, do you know stories bind us all?
Never thought about it, huh?
Watch me while your friends talk about the power of stories.
I think that could be a good lyric too.
She wanted to change it.
Or there's a remix, you know.
Hey, pretty lady.
Did you know Norman Desmond is still a star?
It's the pictures that got small.
I could rewrite the whole so high school where like Taylor and the boyfriend are hanging
out and then you're in the background doing all your stuff.
Like you're singing to to tootsie and stuff in the background.
Surprise verse four.
Yeah.
Taylor picks Jason.
He's done a full remix before of certain songs.
So you know, you've probably heard the phrase, I'm ready for my close up, Mr. DeMille.
And now what that's referring to is Cecil B. DeMille.
You're like a tour guide and you're 12.
I very much wanted to be a 12 year old giving tours.
Taylor, let me whisk you to a world, a world comprised of the three most famous quotes
from movies before 19.
Oh, yeah, I have heard those before from a movie, right?
Yes, they are.
But you're two more obvious ones.
She grew up in Pennsylvania.
She wasn't that far away, you know, could have happened, could have happened at one
of those school meetings, you know, at one of those, you know, competitions or something.
Would that have overlapped?
How old is she?
36?
I guess that could have worked.
Yeah, that would have worked.
That's all.
You do an age check and yes, all right, could have worked, could have worked.
No other factors need to be considered.
Well, it could have been totally impossible if that age was different.
We were both on field trips to Amish country.
You know, we toured a pretzel factory, we went to a smorgasbord.
Yes, this could have happened.
It is possible that it happened.
It didn't.
I mean, it's possible that it could have happened.
Looking at the giant smorgasbord Good and Plenty and saying, like, you know, this inspired
the Imagineers for Ohana.
Did you know that?
Wait, the place was called Good and Plenty?
It's called Good and Plenty.
But not related to the candy.
No, it's not related to the candy.
Okay.
The story is that an Imagineer saw buses of people, like giant tour buses being dropped
off and others coming and going.
Plenty is like, well, if they can feed this many people per hour, we can do it.
So they ripped off the Good and Plenty.
Because it serves family style.
Right.
I know what that is.
That's family style is what I had at the Liberty Tree Tavern or whatever it's called.
Sure.
Family style for one.
Can you just plop Taylor into this and just see where her mind goes?
Family style.
Tell me more.
Okay, so I had a flight late at five o'clock.
Jason could have been hanging out with Taylor Swift.
Yeah.
He could have been in the entourage by now.
Or they fled to Nashville.
You should quit writing those songs.
That's never going to get you anywhere.
Get a summer job with me at the Jersey Shore at the Taffy's factory.
Now that's a path forward.
And would you turn off that rock and roll music?
Why don't you listen to something a little bit more classy?
A little bit higher brow.
Hey, give me down back there.
I'm trying to play Grand Theft Auto.
You could have been, yeah, you could be on the vacation with her and Phoebe Bridgers
and Haim and Jason.
All on vacation together.
Hi everyone.
Are we going to make our itinerary times?
So y'all do music, huh?
Any of it big band?
Glenn Miller?
Anything?
Dorsey Brothers?
How many trumpets you've got in the lineup?
Alto sax?
All right.
Well, I guess it sounds interesting.
I could see my toes tapping to that.
You're in Boy Genius now.
You're the male member of Boy Genius.
I'm the boy.
Jason is the boy in Boy Genius.
They named it after you.
Yeah.
Because you were so knowledgeable about the old big band music.
Anyone want a moon pie?
It's inexplicable that they came to that name despite not knowing the boy genius himself.
Yeah, that is weird.
Now that couldn't, they are younger.
That couldn't have happened in high school.
They are younger.
They are young.
Boy Genius is younger.
So that we can eliminate.
We can eliminate that.
This is the least ratio of episode topic to being talked about.
Which is funny because there's certainly plenty here.
And I like this topic.
I'm not trying to avoid it at all.
Yeah, I like a lot.
We've waited for it for years.
We just keep landing there.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So it's just always a funny switch to make.
So imagine a Tomorrowland that is a melting pot of humans.
I don't know.
It is cool.
Because at this point you've got to work with, as I said in the Rock Rods episode, you have
to work with the locks.
The rides that aren't going anywhere.
We've got Space Mountain.
We've got Star Tours.
Any premise has to include those as well.
And those are interstellar travel situations.
Those are ways to get to space and back.
So the rest of the land has to involve that kind of stuff too.
So it's a land that's a port.
It's a transport hub.
And there's ways for humans to get here and there into space.
And there's ways for aliens to get here and there.
So it would have been this bustling metropolis of some human wares, some alien wares.
Sort of a proto version of what Galaxy's Edge became.
Yes.
It's a neat, tidy explanation for many lands, I feel like.
They're sort of ports.
This is where everybody gets together.
I feel like that comes back in a lot of, obviously, port Disney, just even the idea of it.
Port of entry.
A port where you can enter.
It's easy.
It makes sense.
Okay, everything is gathering here.
It's an exciting place.
Good catch-all.
You need a lot of stuff at a port or a port city.
And then it also makes sense, too, because it's like, okay, the Star Wars characters
are here as well.
But then also, original Disney aliens that we're going to create are here as well.
You can fold in different universes into this premise.
Yeah.
And other ones are versions of this.
But I'd say they fully bailed in order to do what they did in 98.
But so, you know, also this notion of, like, okay, that it's crystals and things that
are, like, all the lighting is coming from within the big physical pieces that we build.
That's a little bit Pandora, right?
I even see that the word bioluminescence is used in reference to some of what they were
going to do.
Yeah, yeah.
So this, and this is what makes me think it could have been a big success, is that we've
that become Galaxy's Edge and Pandora are used in a big way in those, like, giant hit
lands.
We might have gotten to them here.
Yeah.
No, that's a good point, too.
I think, yeah, there are a lot of things in here that sound very promising.
One of them?
A second floor.
I know.
And this is, you almost, like, forget, it sort of doesn't sound like a big idea on
its face.
But as you start going through it, you're like, yeah, wait, theme parks are pretty much
one story, right?
Yes.
It's really not a lot where you go up on a second floor, other than to, like, wait in
a line and the line is up there.
But stuff to do up on a second level, like, this would have been, you would have been
able to walk through all of it in theory.
It's shops and restaurants and stuff that's just up there, and then you get views of stuff
from up there.
Bridges, escalators, catwalks, you know, that kind of thing.
Yes.
That all sounds great.
And I spoke very highly of Tokyo's Tomorrowland, which, like, look, half of it is very locked
in 1983.
And therefore, because they're kind of doing the Tomorrowland of Magic Kingdom,
therefore it feels kind of 70s, which I love.
But I could understand why it's not a big thing for a lot of people.
But, all right, you know, the main drag is OK.
But then that zone that I love so much with the Pangalactic Pizza Port and a star
tours that takes you upstairs at the end and then you've got to exit through a catwalk
and then you and then you can deal with different vantage points of that restaurant,
whether you're on the second floor or the first floor.
It does so much to the vibe, even though it's not much.
It's just one little bridge and then like cool satellite dishes and stuff up there.
But it like this nook is, I think, maybe at least to me and my particular
interests, like the most successful zone of any Tomorrowland, because it's doing all
these kinds of things, these characters you can only meet if you go up into those catwalks.
It's so cool.
And to think about a version that we have here and it's all like that is it's overwhelming.
I'm pining. Yeah, I know we're specific that specifically when exiting star tours,
you get that vantage point. Yeah, they have they have like kind of like a main drag
from the hub that's very similar to the ones we know.
We're like, there's a right over here and right over here.
And none of that's a lot to write.
I don't even remember what they are.
It was one of them Buzz Lightyear and one of them's some stitch thing.
It's not the same stitch thing. Right.
It seems fine. You know, I don't know.
That they could change.
And then they are blowing up Space Mountain and starting over.
Yeah, cool. And which looks kind of like this.
I was going to say, yeah, the the saucer building looks very similar to what they're
ended ending up like the concept are for the new Space Mountain there.
And yeah, that's so like fun and playful.
And like, it's it's very like it's rounded edges and swoops and squiggles.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
As opposed to the very like kind of stiff uptight version of most Tomorrowland,
which even this would would fall into. Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I mean, we've talked many times on the show about like looking at things
from different angles that we really like when you're on the train,
the old people mover and then out and the people mover in Florida.
It's like just getting to see your favorite ride from a different vantage point.
The line of your favorite ride from a different vantage point.
So the idea that you could like, like see Tomorrowland from up and down.
Yeah. Well, the second floor of the old interventions, carousel building
in Disneyland, they have set up couches like they have set up couches.
So they get it. They know people like being up high.
Yeah, to a certain extent, cosmic rays that you get your food
kind of on one level and then the seating is all kind of down the level.
Sort of. That's like a ramp.
That's like a foot down, though.
I'm saying you see a sunny eclipse for a little elevated.
And then you can go.
I'm never going to be mad about seeing them from a different angle.
But we're talking about at least three to six feet.
I it's a stretch, I admit.
I like seeing sunny from lots of angles.
You're just saying that's how much you like elevation.
That's how much of a hype miser you are is that even three feet counts as height.
You can maybe see a bald spot on Sunny Eclipse.
Right. Yes. Yeah.
I'm probably elevating it because the second level has the toppings bar.
And I find the finest area and dining as we've established.
You have defended that place a few times on the show.
And I think, yes, we figured out it's because of the toppings bar.
Yes. But it's at least the last time I had it.
It's bad. It was bad.
Do you get like a feeling in your heart?
Like when you're about to say it, does your heart kind of swell
like you're as if you're going to like, you know, like discuss a true love?
I mean, I used to like Cosmic Graze a lot better
because they had pretty good cheesesteaks.
And it was very and we were so far from Philadelphia.
But then to get the good cheesesteak and then go to the topping bar
and get extra onions and mushrooms.
That's OK. Here's another thing.
You're on like you're on an early vacation and you like
you're about to pine for like, oh, these mother.
These cheesecakes will be fine.
They'll satiate me for now.
But oh, the cheesesteaks back at home.
And then you hear and then you see a statuesque blonde girl
saying the same thing to her parents.
And you and you lock eyes from across the few years younger.
But she's still close and she would go to high school with you.
Well, this is a lovely scenario.
My eyes are fully locked on sunny eclipse.
I don't care about anything going on around the biggest obstacle.
Yes, to a chance Taylor Swift.
We have girls back home.
We don't have sunny eclipse.
Oh, you're a singer, huh?
You'll never reach the heights of the space angels. Yeah.
I also like the idea that you're gone for like five to seven days
and you're just like, oh, those Philly cheesesteaks.
How I miss them.
Mom, I'm having a good time, but I can't help but be a little wistful.
It's not quite wistful from home, but anything that wasn't slices
of pizza or cheeseburgers was interesting in the 90s at Disney World.
You're saying, OK, so you're saying the novelty of the sunny eclipse.
The novelty, you know, the novelty of cheesesteaks period
in the Magic Kingdom is kind of terrible food. Right.
But I'm just saying like you were missing the home cheesesteaks,
but you were intrigued by what the Disney World cheesesteaks were.
Well, I certainly was intrigued to try them.
But I'm just saying the food offerings in the 90s were so bad.
Oh, of course.
I'm just saying it sounds like you were like missing that,
like you would miss like your dog was at home or something.
You were missing the cheesesteak for five days.
I suppose a little.
You're writing like a letter to the cheesesteak.
A dearest cheesesteak.
You're correct.
Yeah, the food offerings have gotten better,
except at the place we're talking about.
The food remains garbage.
A bad place.
I didn't have it last time we were there, but the time before was bad.
I had some good chicken fingers and fries.
What do you want?
You're there for the entertainment and the ambiance, not the food.
Well, that's true.
You bring your own food and sit in there.
Yeah, that's true.
Twenty twenty one.
We were happy to be out of the house, you know.
What else do you want?
That was the oldest man thing ever said about one of the most recent years.
Twenty twenty one are happy to be out of the house.
Your chicken figure going to complain about chicken fingers?
OK, those were the days about three years ago.
All right.
I guess it helps that we are recording this with you on a plaid couch.
That's a set from another show that records here.
Yeah, I said like a fake basement.
So I am you are giving me like very Archie Bunker and
shit my dad and shit my dad, William Shatner.
Bleep, my dad says, you know, even regardless of what you're saying.
OK, so so there wouldn't have been a cosmic race here.
I don't I don't believe so.
I don't even know exactly what's going on restaurant wise,
except that maybe there's up there's some up on the intriguing second floor.
Yes. Attractions, I'd say, are the main thing.
And maybe the thing that would have set this apart is because, like, for example,
in one of the places that is now a pizza
cafeteria type restaurant, there would have been an attraction instead,
which is one of the great losses.
Like any you know how sad the Imagineers were to go.
We have lost a ride or an attraction, at least.
And it's going to become just a pizza place instead.
I don't know. As I say this, maybe Jason doesn't feel.
No, no, I honestly didn't know for years that that
that exactly was where Mission to Mars and Flight to the Moon were.
But like, it does make sense because it is a huge plot of land. Yes.
And Mission to Mars and Rugged to the Moon, that space, which is these
it was we talked about it a couple of months ago or longer.
That that was like retundas essentially all in the round,
you know, with like stadium style seating.
And all eyes are drawn to the center of the room for what was then
like a little simulator thing.
And to replace this and which these attractions were getting very outdated
and to do something cooler and edgier and scarier.
That is why Alien Encounter was developed.
It was meant to fit into that space.
And that's the space that it fit into in the Magic Kingdom and Disney world.
And this is what it was.
It was supposed to be here first.
So this if this at all gone according to plan,
Disneyland would have had the first alien encounter.
I wonder if Disneyland would have like received it better.
Like, I wonder if it would have stuck around longer.
Well, that's what a lot of the blogs I was reading said.
Like, oh, they already have PG-13 kind of thrills.
They have Star Tours, they have Indiana Jones.
So it might have been received better.
And then it might have stuck around later.
Yeah, that there's less like, yeah, I mean, I guess
you still think of Disneyland as like the storybook park.
But I guess by virtue of that, you know, more goes.
I guess like everything is tamer, I guess, in the Magic Kingdom.
Magic Kingdom, yeah, that time didn't have anything at the level of Star Tours even.
Right. So, yeah, maybe, maybe.
And just like the California guests are tougher than the Florida guests.
They could they could hang.
That's interesting.
That's a big proposition.
Well, the locals, the locals, they go on more rides more often.
More, you know, you don't think everybody in SoCal is a soft Hollywood.
Well, I am. We are, but not not the average
like annual pass holder.
Plus, a lot of teens, teens used to hang out in Tomorrowland a lot.
That Jason's right.
There are more teens, I bet, in California in general,
and teens would like to go and scream on Alien Counter.
There's more teens in California going to Disneyland.
They would be hanging out there.
More teens going to California than going to Disney World in Florida.
Well, the locals park, so it would stand to reason
there would be more teens hanging out often together with themselves
just as teens and not on a vacation, like a family vacation.
I think back when annual passes were very cheap and bands.
One video I saw, it was like, well, bands would play the Tomorrowland stage.
So that's where people would congregate.
They would just treat it like a mall if they lived close by, you know.
But you think the way less of this in Florida?
This is a sweeping general about teens.
All right. I know.
And then, Mike, I know that you remain a teen expert, however.
Yeah. Well, let's unpack what.
OK, so Disneyland is much more of a locals park. OK.
So I do think there's some logic in it, in that there would be more
just teens hanging around because there's more people with annual
passes in general.
So I think it would stand to reason that there would be more just teens
roaming in the Disneyland and I guess now California Adventure.
Versus families all going on vacation together.
And yes, certainly teens can break off from them.
And I would do that with my family and I would go do stuff entirely alone.
I would just ride the same rides, but in the order I want it.
And then and loiter in the stores for as long as I pleased.
Free from the tyrannical rule of your parents.
Of my very low key parents.
Of your low key parents who wanted to go on the same things,
but not in the precise order that you were just striking out my own.
I just want a little time to myself.
All right. We'll see. I guess so.
To keep in mind, the teens that it's Florida, the teens aren't roaming.
It's a theory that maybe Alina kind of would have done better
because there are more teens hanging around and people were a little more used
to like a mature experience at Disneyland.
And they would have learned to appreciate this art deco concept art
if it actually got made.
This, by the way, the roaming SoCal teens A are tough and B appreciate art deco.
Do you guys know Jason's point? I'm not going to argue that point.
I think if they built this building, if they did all like metalwork
statue kind of carvings and stuff in this might have ended up
being the most expensive building at Disneyland.
That is insane. Yeah.
That's right. That's really cool.
It's so weird and scary.
You get a creepy feeling just looking at it because it's like,
yeah, it's it's art deco and we're somewhere.
It's even in I don't know.
It's reminiscent of like whatever murals and statues and Rockefeller Center
or whatever.
But it's like in this kind of scary, brutalist
you know, German kind of way.
It's like it's a bunch of like toiling laborers.
Like this is what they were trying to imply is that, OK, if you look close,
the pillars of the building are all like people being really put upon
and having to like carry the building on their shoulders.
Yeah. Which is meant to subtly imply that you're going to get in here.
And what is built is kind of a friendly demonstration of what if aliens
could teleport to us that it's being done by people
who kind of have other plans for humanity?
Yeah. Yeah.
Who maybe are going to dominate us and whip us and keep us in cages.
Which kind of mirrors the art at Rockefeller Center
that the artist feuded with Rockefeller a lot about that art.
Really? Yeah, you can see it in
oh, the Frida Kahlo movie, I think, that Salma Hayek was in.
Ed Norton is Rockefeller.
Oh, and Molina is is it Rivera was the artist?
I don't know.
I'm blank on his first name.
But that was a historical fact.
You really had to fight to get those murals and statues and stuff in there.
OK. It would have been similar.
Well, this feels like like that building and even just the explanation
of alien kind of it does feel like it's like two two letter grades
more intense for anything at Disneyland.
Three letter like it.
Yeah. Like if Indiana like, let's use movie writing like Indiana Jones is PG.
This does feel like an R rated ride in some ways.
Yeah. And especially your swearing.
The roots being they were trying to get like the 20th century Fox.
Sure. There was discussions about like,
can it can the alien the to be the xenomorph?
Yeah. Yeah.
And George Lucas was involved in the early like, like,
it'd be interesting to see, does this does this early version?
Does it work?
Do they somehow by using the real alien and having George Lucas's involvement,
does it somehow succeed more?
Because it is undeniably like I think a lot of people are very fond of it,
but it undeniably like was a troubled production
that they had to keep retooling.
And does it sail through better or is that initial version so
hard are scary that it has all the same issues?
Is it a flawed concept regardless of its Lucas or its xenomorph?
That's a good question.
It's it's interesting because I think like years now of like just, OK,
Epic Universe were doing the Monster's Land.
They just revealed this in a video. It looks amazing.
The ride looks scary as shit.
Yes. Yes. I think I was hearing that.
But like that, I'm like, oh, I think they're really going to go for it.
I do think years of Halloween horror nights and different Halloween events
have prepared your average theme park goer for something this scary.
Yes. So I think maybe you're what you might be getting at
or what it might have just ended up being too early
for your average theme park guest to be that scared on a ride.
But I don't know that in this day and age, if it was placed
in the right spot in a Disney park, people would understand it
and would be like willing to be that scared because they like that now.
And Disney owns that alien.
Yes, that's true.
What is what has Disney done that is scary?
They have they gone in this direction at all?
And I don't mean like the thrill of the ride.
I mean, like thematically scary.
I mean, what is that?
It's a good question.
What's the scariest moment on a Disney attraction or like
is Tower of Terror scary?
I mean, it was scary to me when I was a kid.
But is that just is it part of what happens in it?
Is it like is the story scary or no?
Because it's like, but it's not like you're about to get killed
by an alien in the like complete pitch black wrapped in.
Yeah, but it is scary.
I mean, that's that's up there.
And then Everest Yeti sort of scary.
Yeah, but that's one where you're like going so fast.
Yeah, to me, at least when I'm going fast, I'm not quite as scared
that like when I'm going slow, there's not a lot of the domestic parks,
but they Hong Kong did have houses when you're one year.
They did it is they are.
They are grotesque in a way that was in a Club Three poll.
Yeah, yeah, but that's worth looking at.
Yeah, but then they don't do those anymore.
Yes.
So they just never they haven't really gone this direction.
They have not gone really much this direct since, especially since.
But I do think years now of horror nights in different haunted houses,
I think more people really love this because everything is expanded so much.
But under the universal.
Certainly under the universal.
But I'm sure there's plenty of Disney people that go to both
and there would be an appetite for it.
So I think it was ahead of its time in some ways that they are.
But we needed all of the 90s Halloween events to to desensitize you a little.
But that's how it happened to me.
And to get the floor to get the Florida people
tough to the degree of the socal teens famously tough socal team.
Well, they have been going to scary farm.
So they had sort of worked themselves into a spot
where they now were a little bit tougher than the Florida goers
who didn't have a scary farm seeing the sliders.
Right. They're calloused from the sliders.
Yes. So I I'm sure there's some imagine
you're somewhere that's like we could sneak an alien ride in here.
And I don't think it's going to I would bet no money that will happen.
Yeah. Yeah. I would bet zero money that they're thinking about it.
It's land or something.
Maybe. Yeah. But even villains land like the xenomorph doesn't fit tonally with.
It would be funny if they're like the villains.
Jafar, the queen of hearts, the xenomorph.
Yes, that would be awesome.
But I don't see that bandits from home alone with bandits.
The top villains and the predator and the predator predator.
If we have room predator.
Oh, that would be so great.
But there's no way. Yeah.
There's no unless it's a fifth park that's all Fox properties,
which we talked about for nemesis from American Dad.
Yes. This is from American.
Dad is in there.
The one Mr. Burns, Mr.
Burns and the one eyebrow baby from Simpsons, Maggie's nemesis.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And then which were the planet of the apes would be in there, I guess, as well.
Yeah. But they're not. Yeah.
But the nemesis is man. Right.
So that's a tough ride.
That's a ride that makes you think, yep, I'm the I'm the villain in villain land.
Anyway, it did like cool building.
Oh, I also saw the term techno deco.
How cool is that? That's a cool name. Yeah.
Right. There's a guy named a designer named Rob Yeo who created
what he thought this land might be like in 3D.
And I encourage you to look up those designs.
Those are really cool. He took some leaps.
He was going off of like the several pieces of concept art that exist.
But in doing so, kind of like extrapolated from, OK,
if there's if we're doing this techno deco thing, you know,
maybe this would look like this or this would look like this.
And I especially really love how he rendered the people mover
in this cool where it's like, I yeah, I don't know.
I don't know how to describe it.
It just it looks like it's a weird 40s version of the people mover,
which is really neat.
It's not anything the Imagineers actually thought of, but they should have.
It's cool. And boy, if it was if this place is going to be anything
like his concept art would have been even cooler at night than you think.
Yeah. Then even just the logo on cast member,
like crew gifts and stuff that they they is very cool.
This logo is awesome. It's out there.
You're showing an eBay listing is a picture, I guess,
for something that they're selling on eBay.
These things would come up at some of these van Eten auctions
where they sold the park stuff like crew jackets they've sold.
Here's the jacket.
The asking price for one button is 79.95.
Wow. And the jacket they won
one thousand four hundred ninety five.
Geez. Wow. Wow.
I wonder what's the last one that sold.
I wonder if that's like it sold for that or that's just like one of a kind
almost on eBay at this point.
I don't know. It is such a neat logo that really like
just alludes to the promise of what this place would have been.
This tomorrow would have been like aesthetically.
You see it sometimes with like pink on black teal on black
or the version you just showed both.
This is a superior color scheme. I love it very much.
And it's the outlines of big rocks like what would have been in the front.
We got kind of a lesser version of the big
jagged rocks in the final land.
And then also the moon liner, the big rocket was going to be a part of this.
Now, the rocket did end up existing.
It is a Coke booth where I mean, it's OK.
This is a thing that was in Disneyland in the 50s and 60s.
It was maybe one of the icons.
If you went to the park back then, then it went away for a long time.
They were they did bring it back, though it's kind of small.
And as we addressed, just that's where I think you get the Coke bottles
that shoot up out a little cannon that I'd never heard about until now.
In this version of the land, it would have been three times bigger.
The symbol of the land, I think, like, you know, the big pinnacle piece in the center.
Yeah, sounds really cool. Looks really cool.
Yeah, I just think those I wonder what like would be around now.
I guess I guess now because I was impressed that they even had like 3D
rendering stuff back then.
But it's you know, that stuff was all available, maybe not commercially,
but was available to designers and things.
But I just I would I want somebody now to make like a 3D model of this,
like with modern technology, too, just so you can like I want to like go VR.
I guess what I'm saying. Oh, sure.
Well, Rob, you might have like had to add it to that.
I don't know. Yeah, maybe you might have had a walk around version.
And I remember so other stuff.
I mean, like big central attractions would have been just, you know,
imagine the Tomorrowland doesn't have pizza port.
It has alien encounter that somehow makes it to this day.
The Timekeeper, I believe, would have been in the Circle Vision Theater,
which will address more fully down the road, but like pretty cool,
unique, very memorable attraction.
There was a Disney World for a long time.
But I feel like the central piece is what ends up in that carousel theater.
This is what really haunts you because they had already started
bailing on America sings those robots are going to Splash Mountain.
We aren't going to run this thing anymore, but we didn't rip out the mechanism.
It still turns. We didn't rip out the seats.
We could get something new in here.
And this if it's not the primary.
OK, you know what?
Sometimes we get the question in a mailbag or whatever.
Like, what's the unbuilt thing that you find for the most?
And if you go, if you want to say like a full park, right?
You want to say Westcott, you want to say Port Disney or even this,
this full land in general.
If we're going specific attractions could be my number one.
This is because we don't know much, but the phrase will always haunt me.
And the phrase is Plectu's fantastic intergalactic review.
Yeah, really happy we've arrived at the point in this podcast
where we can talk about Plectu.
I mean, just the name alone just implies the funnest, silliest.
It's a sci fi country bears that would have it.
And if it's in the revolving theater, that means we get five stages.
Right. Of instead of, you know, Storks, Whistle and Dixie,
all this shit that was in there before.
We just not like it to one bit.
Instead, you get like five stages of weird sci fi robots.
Wouldn't have been as educational as the carousel of progress,
but it might have been a lot more fun.
This is this sounds so great.
Yes, it is. It is.
This is something that they'll never do again.
It'll never something like this will never happen again.
It's something that requires like a minimum.
What's a minimum is like 70 animatronics, right?
Yes, right.
And these are seemingly original characters.
And obviously, if we're explaining why, I mean, if you listen to the podcast,
you don't need to know why.
But this is like, you know, the hyper Chuck E.
Cheese with new original Disney created sci fi characters.
And especially with my kid brain, I was all about space.
I did not care about the old west.
I did not care about a lot of these other things.
And I said this, I've admitted this before on the show.
I liked the country bears as a kid, but I was not enamored with them
like I am as an adult.
So especially with my kid brain, this is what I wanted from a robot show.
This is the ultimate thing.
This is a alien based space based robot show with, I assume, original songs.
Yes. I don't know.
Some covers, whatever.
But this is my kid brain is all I wanted.
There's a pretty I'm going to call this an unvetted fact
because it only appeared in comment sections.
And, you know, now I'm looking at things through Eisner Golf for brain.
Yeah. And I can't report this like it's a real thing
because I just don't think the proof is there.
But there were people saying that the music for this attraction
was being worked on by Danny Elfman.
Take that as you would.
That seems too crazy that he's making time for that in early 90s
when he's the most in demand.
Well, he's done stuff for the parks.
He's what he did something for a Mystic Manor, correct?
Yes. And he did. He's doing Epic Universe.
He's doing the Monsters Land.
He is. Yeah.
I didn't know that part. He said it.
He announced it too on his Instagram. Oh, I've never heard that.
I'm hearing this for the first time.
That's crazy. Wow.
So, yeah, and he's he I don't know, he wrote enough things
in that post to make me think he like, oh, he's interested in theme park.
So I don't know if he's doing Nightmare Before Christmas around this time,
then he's at Disney and he's doing songs with vocals.
So maybe, maybe.
So, yeah, possible, very possible.
But I don't know.
That's maybe something for a gym to look up, somebody to look up,
somebody to find out. Yeah, we need a little bit.
We need some official, we need to see some pace.
I'm talking about, but maybe then maybe it just didn't happen.
Maybe it didn't get to the point where somebody was actually writing songs.
Yeah. OK.
What to say about this premise wise, and we're not we're going off of not a lot here.
There's a couple of blog posts. Yeah.
But the basics are in the carousel theater would be transformed
into a flying saucer that is crash landed at that spot in Tomorrowland.
And and they happen to have a dinner show going.
I don't know. I was doing a wind up as if I had a lot more to say, and I don't.
I don't know. Flying saucer landed and they put on a show for you and spins. Great.
Yeah, it's great.
It wasn't like they're not eating in there.
But it was. Oh, thanks.
Yeah. But they're doing a little review.
There's a lot more lights and neon on the outside of the building.
Yes. Yeah. Neon squiggles.
Love it. Great squiggle.
Big light fixture that looks like a big drum kit.
Awesome. One question I have is like, would this have been outdated by the time?
Like maybe now Plectu would not be looking.
Plectu might be the ultimate thing that we talk about.
You know, Plectu is a two part, three part episode for us.
Yeah. But other people are like, what's this boring Plectu thing?
But we know we know how much this would be in our wheelhouse.
If this got 100 percent, I do think it would be closed down by now.
Probably. It might have been closed down in 2000.
Very possible, because we've also this is the problem with the country bears out here.
The locals are blamed because the locals don't go to shows like that as much as a tourist.
Obviously, also part of the country was we built two theaters,
which is too much real estate out here because they're like, it's so popular in Florida.
We need two of them out here. And they did not.
Yeah. Expanded too quickly, like Planet Hollywood, which just like Planet Hollywood.
But I do think also I've heard people blame the fact that locals
don't necessarily go and fill up theaters for longer shows.
We've seen that. We'll see that next time or we'll see that next year.
And they're so tough. Also, they're too tough.
And they're too tough to enjoy a cutesy bear show.
Cutesy shows. The teens would rather go Rome.
They don't want to sit in one place for 20 minutes.
I think that's right. They get antsy. Teens get antsy.
They would have loved hearing me explain, you know, this original character, P.T.
Quantum is kind of a run down to P.T. Barnum.
Is that so? They would have loved that.
They wouldn't do it in that room.
Yeah, Pete. Yes, P.T. Quantum.
Now, here's where things show me that photo again. Sorry, Jason.
Sure. He is. Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's a little space hub. Yeah, he's great.
He's well, and he's got a big staff.
We're in botanicals land. Yeah.
This might have been maybe this might have superseded.
We maybe we wouldn't have even made it to Botanicus. Right.
Until way later in the show, because we would have been so fixated on P.T. Quantum.
So T-shirts had just said pot quantum.
You're already there. You're like one letter away.
Most of the letters you need.
I mean, he's so great.
What if you had to if you're staring at him,
what is a sci fi property that exists that seems the closest
to something that P.T. Quantum would exist in?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Like he's in a he's in a very complicated robe.
There is so much design going on on the road and the staff is so complicated.
And his art, his hands look like they have barnacles.
And he sort of has the proportion.
We're almost like, couldn't you see like this is the concept art
of a Ninja Turtle action figure?
Well, I was about to say he looks almost like more of a Mirage Comics
Eastman and Laird character.
Even even the drawing style.
He certainly looks like he could just have been a figure, a playmates figure.
But he specifically does look like he was from maybe like the original comics.
Yeah, art style wise, too.
I'm trying to think of a good obviously splinter is a very like
yeah, character that you would think is similar to this guy.
But even other characters, I'm trying to think.
This is not a futuristic property,
but I feel like he would not be out of place in the world of Dark Crystal.
Oh, yeah, for sure. Yeah, Dark Crystal.
There's a French comic artist, like long, long time acclaimed guy named Mobius.
Is it Mobius? Yeah. Yeah.
And and he's worked with every big company under the sun.
He did a lot of movie concept art.
I think he worked on some Blade Runner stuff.
But it's very much in his wheelhouse, I feel like. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it's like an expanded unit, like an old Star Wars comic specifically.
Sure. Yeah. Marvel Comics.
Star Wars. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You could slide into a lot of different places, probably.
Did you guys find the other characters?
This is a very last minute find for me.
Yeah, I did.
And there's there's a thing I want to talk about one of them.
But go ahead.
Well, we got some other characters.
And I don't know if you ran into harmony and melody.
Listeners just put up space after Harmo Harmo.
First name, last name, the Mel space.
Oh, D. Irish.
And these are also they're kind of like big Fraggles.
Yes. Right. Big Fraggles.
Bucky O'Hare. They look like they do look like Bucky O'Hare characters.
Bucky O'Hare. Yes.
Oh, wow. It even says Irish Micronauts.
They did think this through.
Harmony is like the painting, the blue boy,
except a weird little like space gopher.
Yeah. And he's got like tassels and I don't know.
I like him.
And then and I'd love to see a robot of him.
And then Melody is kind of like a boy.
I mean, she's like a marching band sort of.
She's described as fun and feisty, like Marion Ravenwood.
She plays the raucous stuff.
He the softer, prettier passages.
Yeah. And there's a lot of notes on the art.
Lambskin Collar like this.
We're looking at like some deep Imagineer art here with all of the details.
But then there's something very strange that I will leave it to Jason.
Yeah, there's a phrase that is probably the correct phrase to use
in like trying to design creatures or a species
right atop the drawing of Melody.
It says sexual dimorphism and micronauts.
And that is very interesting to me.
That is just such an oddball note.
I'm assuming it is.
They just mean like, here's a boy one.
Here's a girl one.
What is it? Male, female.
What does it mean to say it?
It's just it's almost I mean, you're looking.
You look at that phrase and it looks like the name of an essay.
Right. It's a strange like if you put that on a piece of art
because otherwise it says like her jacket is red.
He has freckles.
Sexual dimorphism in micronauts.
It's a very strange.
What is that? What does it literally mean?
Dymorphic refers to occurring in or representing two distinct forms.
OK. But then OK, sexual dimorphism is the condition where sexes
of the same species exhibit different morphological characteristics.
So just, you know, and then there's a picture of two ducks
and the male and the female look very different
than the species Mandarin ducks.
That's what I'm seeing.
I mean, I this always seems to happen.
Like in like sometimes in science fiction where it's like,
there are these creatures and they're not like you and I.
They speak through thoughts or light that there's a boy one and a girl one.
For sure, there is.
I mean, it's also it's I guess sexual dimorphism is it's
just telling us that the male and the female even have the same species
like look extremely different.
Like another example here on Wikipedia is Mississippi map turtles.
And the male turtle is kind of small.
And the female turtle is like three times.
Yeah. Wow. Look at that. That's wild.
Wow. Interesting.
It looks normal to me.
Just the way I see the world.
Everyone's bigger than Jason.
You're just a tiny turtle in this world.
So there's some there's some sexual dimorphism
in the difference between you and Taylor Swift.
Wild. OK.
So important one of the strangest things written in an
imaginary document as far as I've seen. Yeah.
I have some questions.
We've seen Melody in Harmony and we've seen PT Quantum.
But who is the titular Plectu?
There's no concept art of Plectu.
Is he is that what the P stands for in PT Quantum?
Probably not. That's a little confusing.
I want to know who Plectu is.
It's somebody that we meet.
Is it someone that we have to rescue through the power of rock music?
Good question.
Is Plectu in any of this art, the other art things I'm assuming you saw?
There's one that kind of looks like under the sea.
Yes, for sure. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe Plectu is in there.
Is that Plectu?
I don't know. I don't know.
And then for this one, I haven't seen what you're showing.
What's happening in that one?
This one, this is just sort of a sketch of like it kind of shows you
like the type of like with the old man in the Muppet sit
up in this part of the theater.
There's a big, there's a long haired, there's a long neck creature there.
There's like kind of a long neck creature with two eyes that are kind of
like also on long necks and then a sort of a more round creature sitting up there.
And they look like they're in like the little little box,
like the Muppets guy, like Statler and Waldorf.
And then on stage, there is a kind of long necked alien
pulling a head out of a hat, like he's doing a magic trick.
Wow. There would have been magic in this show.
And then what looks like there's a alien behind him
playing maybe a guitar, but also smoking a cigarette or a cigar.
Like there's there's definitely smoke lines coming off of this stick
that this alien with a guitar is holding.
So there was some alien smoking a cigar or a cigarette there, too.
So that's very exciting.
Well, you know, with all due respect to the Carousel Progress,
which I like and I do every time.
But then you're in there and it's like, you know, we got the Ed Sol running
and then America Sings is a collection
of some of the most unpleasant songs ever created.
And that we're going to get this, that we're going to get cigar
smoking aliens doing magic tricks and melody and sexual dimorphism.
This is a wild show.
There is another piece of concept art.
Did you see this of the building?
It's a little less detailed than the other drawings of the building.
But it looks like they gave the building like legs.
Well, that's cool.
It looks a little more crooked, like it didn't land so straight.
Yeah. Yeah. It's sort of a canted thing.
Yeah. Cool. I don't know.
We're just left to speculate.
Yeah. I mean, well, like music musically, though,
Danny Elfman doesn't even feel right for for that for when my dream
scenario of what this show was.
And I guess I'm picturing more of like 80s synth pop
more than Danny Elfman, the genre that he did.
Well, yeah, but not the kind I'm thinking of.
OK. You know, not not necessarily dead man's party or anything.
Or I'm just thinking of like I'm trying.
I'm talking out loud here, like what I would want from it.
And I think I don't know.
I don't know. Maybe maybe in the mid 90s, he would have done
like I don't want it to sound like Nightmare Before Christmas.
I don't want it to sound like Beetlejuice.
I want it to be kind of like Halyx.
I get Halyx a little too rockin, but I don't know.
I want something more in that vein, I guess.
I don't know. It's a customer.
If you worked there. Yeah.
There are some music tracks
labeled Tomorrowland 2055.
Yes, but that's like area music.
Apparently leaked because they were playing it just in a bathroom.
Oh, yeah, I saw that music in the bathroom at Disneyland.
So and somehow this has been saved from that form.
But this music idea, I don't know.
I mean, is how do we arrive at an artist that satisfies what you want?
It's a good question.
I mean, the Tomorrowland loop in Florida is close.
Like, I think that's great.
It's like technically versions of a lot of the Tomorrowland songs
throughout the years.
I'm just trying to think of like what the ultimate artist I want to
would have wanted to be contracted in the mid 90s to do early 90s to do this.
Yeah, that's closer, I think.
I'm trying to think like early Madonna.
Could would Madonna have done the music for this?
Could you have gotten in the early 90s photo of old man P.T.
Quantum? Something tells me that Madonna in 1982, her absolute zenith.
What about you would have had a hard time
looping her in to make up the songs for P.T. Quantum?
But she kind of likes.
I mean, she was like material girl era.
She did, you know, the Sondheim music.
She said it's a major motion picture, though.
And this is a ride with an alien smoking a cigar with an ancient.
Just I mean, you can imagine with this guy.
We've come from across the galaxy.
All right now, everyone. Vogue.
Tiffany or Cyndi Lauper, maybe you're firing Danny Elfman
and you're giving it to Tiffany.
Tiffany can even write.
She may not have written any of those songs, and she didn't write.
I'm sorry. I'm having trouble here.
Devo, yes, Oingo Boingo, no.
Is this this cold hearted nature where Elfman is out?
Elfman, you're looking at looking at Giffords in the mouth.
I'm not just doing it because of the allegations recently.
I'm just that's I'm just trying to think of what I would picture this being.
I'm just OK. I'm not saying this is all definitively.
I'm just again, I'm thinking out loud here.
I mean, I look at Melody and I hear her singing like that.
What is the song like? Do you hear me?
What is that song?
Uh, wait, what is it?
Not Papa. Can you hear me?
No, no, no. That's a different song.
Am I? What am I thinking?
I'm not sure since. Oh, maybe you hear me.
I don't know what that is. Is it Kate Bush or something? No.
Kate Bush could do the music for this.
Now we're talking.
OK. Hounds of Love era, Kate Bush.
Yeah, that would be awesome.
That might be the ultimate.
Yeah, that would be good. I could see that.
Well, because and it's also I don't know.
They're like they're like a like fantasy.
They're very fantasy in their design, too, which I see her
what I'm with as well.
What about Electric Light Orchestra?
Not then. Oh, not in the early 90s, no.
Well, what if they got contracted years prior, though?
It's been a work.
They've been working on this for a long time.
History here. OK.
Well, that's part of the fun of this.
Changing history.
What if they were still good?
I guess. OK.
I mean, yes, a bunch of aliens putting on a show that sounds like DLO
still in likes, but we got to go, you know, they start to get bad.
You know, we're going to go back to 78.
OK, that's fair enough. They might be giants.
It's a little kooky and it's a little good.
I know you like them, but I love that.
I revisit them.
I have no problem with them.
But for this, we're talking about a harmony and melody.
We're going to do this.
Think college music for that.
I'm going to veto that.
They've been. They've been.
I know the songs I like.
I like some songs.
They've been on letter.
They were just they were doing Birdhouse in your song Letterman.
You could say that about any artist, though.
Been on Letterman. So funny.
You know, you know who could do it? Ronnie Spector.
She's been on Letterman.
That's true. She has.
I mean, she would be good.
She would be. That would be cool.
Well, what if this was more of a Phil Spector sound show?
Well, yeah, Phil Spector kind of sound a little bit, you know, in his wig mode.
He looks a little bit like PT Quantum. Yeah.
Yeah. If his if the trial had gone one more day,
he would have come out in a big robe and a crystal staff and a beard.
Phil Spector pulling a gun on PT Quantum.
PT Quantum pulls out a ray gun.
Oh, very good. It's a standoff.
Yeah, I could think of more modern things, I guess.
But yeah, I'm trying to think of actual era appropriate.
I didn't even know her. I swear I didn't even know her.
I didn't blow her brains out, OK?
Their brains were blown out when I got here.
I don't even know her name.
It's Melody, sir.
And I think you know that you are very interested in the sexual dimorphism at foot.
When does when does a love and when is Brian Wilson put out Love and Mercy?
What year? Eighty eight.
Hey, OK, it's a little early, I guess.
This era of Brian.
I thought I thought you were going to say Brian Sensor.
Oh, Brian Sensor. Yeah, straight cats.
I'm going to veto it, sadly.
I'm going to veto it.
It's not what I want for this.
This this also I would like to make.
I would like to make the music.
I just like to do it.
I just like to do it now for fun.
That's what's happened.
You're in the you're in Imagineering in this year and like, Danny, I don't know.
Elfman, I mean, is he to blend?
You're there. Like, what does that mean?
I don't know. He's like a little bump.
What does that mean?
Mike, are you trying to say that you just want to do?
All right. Fine. I've done it already.
We dance around it.
Why just started? Just do it then.
I've done it already.
Here's the CD.
I've been working on it for the last two weeks, nonstop.
No sleep here.
If we are trying to figure out what was going to be happening musically here,
there's one little clue.
And this these seem to be official Imagineering documents
that indicate that maybe an element of this would have been
cyborg versions of actual rock stars.
And I will now show you two photos.
One is some sort of very bendy.
Yeah, first of all, somebody with a version,
a robotic Mick Jagger with very bad posture.
Yeah. Which I guess is fine if you're a robot.
So we got a would have had a robot Mick Jagger.
And then just below that, we have what seems to be a robot Tina Turner.
Now, I start to doubt the show a bit here.
These I don't know about original characters.
Sure. But I think we might have might have started to feel a little bit dated,
even though those are still relevant.
Yeah. You know, like you you go to I was about to say,
you know, you go to see a Legends in Concert and that's he'd see that
the ultimate test of relevancy, that weird guy in his show Legends in Concert.
But, you know, I mean, like legendary. Right. Figures.
I think they would have gotten in trouble if it was like,
and now the new bots on the block.
Yeah. Well, the new chips off the block.
Also considering Mick Jagger's like like eight days away
from playing SoFi Stadium in Los Angeles, like he's still doing it.
So that at least wouldn't have been so far fetched.
You would have known maybe who that is.
But you but I guess besides that, there's the issue of does this suck?
Oh, it's it's the chances of it sucking are very high.
Yeah, because it's not you know, it's not going to be them.
Like, look, we're this is now where we end up in Food Rocks territory.
Yes. Now, I'm you know, would I if they brought back Food Rocks,
would I be there as soon as possible? Absolutely.
Do I think this is the highest caliber of show?
Not necessarily, you know, if we're because I mean,
I think some people voiced themselves in Food Rocks,
but I don't think Mick Jagger was going to be one of these people.
Probably not. And like I, you know, him like just so so an impersonator like,
hey, you get off of my shit.
I don't get no stratosphere action.
Uh huh. Yeah, yeah, no, it's bad.
That that version of it is bad.
I guess if it's just sort of like, you know, they resemble those people,
but their original songs.
But no, I don't need a Rolling Stone parody in this show.
I don't want that.
I don't think that I don't think that's good.
I can't imagine a version of it where that's good.
And still like I would still like like it as much.
She just does. She just uses alien nonsense.
Like, what's Blurg got to do with it?
I mean, it would be fun to talk about that show for a few hours
and see once or twice, but it's not last.
It doesn't last in our hearts that way.
I came up with a few ideas for like songs about nuclear reactors.
And they're like, no, Three Mile Island is still fresh in everyone's mind.
Chernobyl has just occurred.
And now a musical salute to nuclear reactors.
I feel like the power system could power the flying saucer.
Jason's hanging out with Taylor Swift and the bros.
And he's like, Three Mile Island, have you fellas heard of this?
You know about this? Pennsylvania.
You know, this was his before he had 9-11 to go to.
This is what it was.
Because you have to remember that three days earlier,
there had been a little incident called Three Mile Island.
Everything is centered around a tragedy or a disaster.
Well, the boy genius is at it again.
Oh, boy.
And what's the thing that started where you referenced it recently?
Like, keep in mind what had just occurred.
The assassination of Archduke.
The Archduke transferred it in.
Like the cool band.
If somebody, I know Van Art,
if someone wants to draw Jason telling the the ladies from Boy Genius
about Three Mile Island, I would like to see that.
You don't waste your time, though.
I don't. A lot of people to draw. Yeah, yeah.
So anyways, I mean, I still think overall from what we've seen
and from how the the exterior would have looked, this would have been
superior to what ended up going in here.
Nothing for six years.
And then a giant ad for Compaq.
Yeah. I mean, it is so insulting that that's what it ended up being.
I even ended up at literature that was saying how the people in charge.
This is what's heartbreaking is that, like, OK, Tony Baxter,
who we love, obviously, and another great imagineer.
Oh, what's the name?
Bruce Gordon. Oh, yeah.
These were the people who, you know, they stayed on the part.
They had to oversee the weird cheapo overlay of tomorrow. Right.
Because they were on the Tomorrowland project from this when it was blue sky
and crazy, you know, and sort of wild and experimental.
But and then cut to them years later.
And apparently, I think it was Bruce Gordon, who was apparently saying, like,
like that, like in a quiet way, like you're just internal people
that, OK, we've announced that it is in inventions.
We don't actually know what's going in there.
And it opens in a year that they they they were so scrambling to figure out.
They just said interventions as a placeholder.
And then, like, I don't know.
And there were models.
You can look at models from imagineering showing like, well,
it is the kind of thing we could do.
And they had like six months to go from then.
So and, you know, you could feel it, I would say.
Feel that they were just like, I don't know, maybe.
Yeah. Did a good job for the time when they had.
But they did it with what did not happen is Plectu's
fantastic intergalactic review.
I really wish we could have seen some version of this.
And then here's the real heartbreaker is that apparently
this idea ultimately did not.
They didn't sell it all the way through to Michael Eisner.
And that he said, this just seems too cutesy and like something you'd see
at Chuck E.
Cheese restaurants around the country, to which I say, yeah, fucking right.
Yeah, exactly.
But it's you guys doing it.
Yeah, it's going to be even better with the best damn Chuck E.
Cheese that ever happened.
Plectu is going to blow Chuck E.
Cheese out of water. Michael, this is the one time that you messed up.
The one time was the the were the robots at the Malibu Chuck E.
Cheese and disarray and disrepair.
Like, why did he have such a negative connotation with Chuck E.
Cheese? Like it's the sea air.
It's getting in the circuits, Michael.
There is there a mall.
What's the closest of Chuck E.
Cheese to the to Malibu?
I were probably I don't know, we're probably in Ventura,
but this would even blow that way.
Yeah, true. Maybe there was a thousand oaks.
I'm not sure.
But or this one I don't know about the current Nobu in Malibu.
What's the story? That was a Chuck E.
Cheese. Yeah.
So, yeah, I don't know.
He and maybe this is where unfortunately, maybe Michael Eisner
didn't really get to Marlin.
I think he because he it was his like overnoting and over worry
that made Alien Encounter kind of a problem.
And then he pulled the tree.
He he caused the cheap version of Tomorrowland.
He didn't get Plectu. Right.
And he wanted something faster than people movers.
So we get dumb rocket rods.
So maybe this is where Rubber Meets the Road kind of with Eisner.
Like Eisner, right.
Eisner and Tomorrowland, maybe.
Wait, I'm saying that.
But then he caused Star Tours and Captain EO.
So I don't know.
He just lost it in the older.
It was younger back then.
Yeah. So maybe he lost his passion for space.
Maybe he lost his vision for what a fun,
futurey show or ride would be something we can never do.
And especially as we dive into soon, our depictions of Tomorrowland.
And Scott, you're the only one who can bring Plectu back in a real way.
No spoilers. But would you believe I would?
I would maybe there's a yeah.
Yes, this may be a key part of my plan.
Jason, you can paint Plectu on a sign somewhere.
That's the budget you have.
Paint costs a lot of money, brother.
I was going to say, thinking about them not having
interventions like vendors set up and it's just like, all right,
we're working the weekend, put a pot of coffee on.
We just lost the fucking Dippin' Dots people.
They went with Six Flags.
The ice cream of the future is not ours anymore.
We're not going to be able to demonstrate what the ice cream of the future will be.
If we're trying to convince people that the ice cream of the future
is the ice cream of the present, that's going to bomb them out.
What kind of future is that?
Jason does your proposal.
Can I ask for a spoiler? Does it involve Dippin' Dots?
Well, it's food.
Food may come into play.
Good. I better. I better. Yeah.
OK. Yeah. That's one of the main things you have to work with, I think. Yeah.
So I think that the lack of enthusiasm for Plectu might have, you know,
along with all the other stuff going on, you do well, blah.
So it all goes away.
And that was going to be one of the centerpieces.
So when that goes, the whole thing went and we had to figure out the cheaper version.
There's one more element of this that would have been cool.
I think we've referred to this in the past when talking about light magic,
the weird, very much disliked replacement for Main Street Electrical Parade.
But as part of like whatever.
All right. It's the the summer of New Tomorrowland.
We're launching this thing.
And as part of that, we're going to celebrate Tomorrowland parkwide
with our new high tech replacement for the Main Street Electrical Parade.
Light keepers.
Jason, I know you learned about light keepers.
I yeah, I saw this mentioned.
It's mentioned on the fandom page for this.
And then some blogs had picked it up.
Like you said earlier, like, oh, there's a lot of comments.
I saw people like quoting the press release for this.
But I'll just read this chunk from the park lore post.
Um, here we go.
Now, when it was time for Disney's nice time parade,
an announcement throughout the park, which is weird,
would suggest that a strange flying object had been spotted
flying toward Disneyland.
Then fireworks projection and sound effects would signal
that a spacecraft was indeed hovering above the park.
That's so, you know, Copperfield, Copperfield,
as blue 32 as after a few moments of anticipation,
the gates to that backstage area would swing open as brilliant
white light flooded out this nighttime parade called light keepers
would feature a tall, elegant, ethereal alien race.
So giant six or eight feet tall, like
glowing creatures that were walking around.
I'm going to say this. It sounds scary to me.
Yeah, it sounds like the Spectremen. Yes.
And they used to you used to be able to get away from there on top of the big balls.
But what if the Spectremen hopped down and started following you?
But what if their faces were beautiful?
What if the aliens had beautiful faces and they were eight feet tall?
What if the faces were just pure light?
Maybe that's the only way to get around it.
You can't even see their face.
That's creepy, though, too.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
A lack of face has never been used for warmth or comfort. Right.
What if they're just their faces are just all tens?
It's beautiful faces.
They can have kind of weird bodies, but like their faces to a human eye
are attractive. Would that be OK?
I think you put an attractive real woman's face on a big beam of light.
I think it's going to be scary.
You're describing like cosmic sirens.
They don't have to be sirens.
Like luring you to the rocks, to the crystals.
You can choose to be lured by them, but they're not actively trying to lure you
like a siren would.
I guess that there's ropes and stanchions that wouldn't get very far.
Yeah, I'm just saying that like, you know, I'm trying to appease Scott in this.
We're in this brainstorming session on how to make this a little bit more appealing,
because like we all think of like the gray, you know, your gray alien face
when you think of just sort of aliens or weird.
I'm trying to think of a like, I guess, Wookiees are like eight feet tall.
So but that's not what this is.
That's not what they're describing here.
Yeah. So I feel like we're in the territory of those,
the like crazy advanced robots at the end of A.I., which are scary.
Yeah. Yeah. All doesn't help.
Spinley doesn't help.
OK, these are these are we're describing space groups.
This is going to be a race of space groups.
Here's OK. They would never do this.
And this is a reverse of what I'm saying.
But in concept, does the idea of an alien invasion
at Disneyland sound awesome for a Halloween event or something?
Yeah, definitely. That sounds awesome.
A gate opens and a bunch of aliens come. Yes.
Or they're hiding in different spots and like the whole thing is scary.
I don't they would never do it because I don't think they want to like
have you leave a castle park having a creepy feeling.
But with like the right lights and soundtrack, I think it would be really awesome.
What if they're friendly?
Hoo hoo. You found me.
It's like the Mr. Burns.
Now, can you define friendly?
What if they're hot and friendly?
Combine the two.
Please touch me while your bros play Grand Theft Auto.
Yeah, and they're funny and they're topical to play no modern music.
So it's very they're very inviting.
You you understand these people, you relate to them, these aliens, excuse me.
So it's an ethereal, glowing light life.
But you need like you're doing the bar stool like sports like,
oh, and then it's perfect ten in the face. Yeah.
I'm grading them on the bar stool scale. Yeah, for sure.
It's not something I do in my real life.
I'm just again, I'm trying to make this seem more fun or inviting
and make the aliens less scary.
No, none of the light keepers are fours.
You need them to be. You need them to be ten.
Yeah, I like this. Yeah, I am.
I am made of pure light and energy.
In through me flows all information and images throughout all of time.
Yeah. Looking at your face, though, kind of an eight.
Well, you got any people that looked like they'd be hanging out
with Spud's Mackenzie, the dog.
Any bikini beads back there?
Well, when you thought of like what a lady was a ten,
you think of like Spud's Mackenzie.
I think beer commercials. I see what you're saying.
I think in like a bikini clad tenders to Spud's Mackenzie. Yes.
I'm thinking of like Fabio face to like a Fabio type of a guy
who's just like a romance novel cover. Yeah, a class.
Your idea of a ten is Fabio.
Well, he's technically I mean, I guess you would more consider a Brad Pitt
a ten, I suppose.
But in my mind, you know, I'm a pro wrestling fan.
So I think more of the the bulkier man is being a ten, I suppose.
Didn't impress Janiah Twain much.
It's true. So there'll be a variety of tens.
OK, so you're a light keeper.
That don't impress me.
There's different flavors of tens in my pitch.
OK, it doesn't have to be the specific.
There's a beer commercial ten.
It's a pro wrestling ten.
It's all a variety of tens in this scenario.
You know, to make you I hate to make you grade
Melo Melo D. Oh, yeah.
Oh, D Melo, I got to pull her up.
I had her before. Right here you go.
Sorry, you got to get Melody.
This is trickier because she's not a human woman.
There would be a light keeper.
But I'm let me compare her to Jenny from Bucky O'Hare.
Who I can only imagine is a ten.
Jenny, I guess is a ten.
Yeah, probably.
So I'm this is the only this is the most sexist thing I've ever done on the show.
I just want to be clear that I know what I'm doing here.
I'm going to say she's like an eight.
I'm going to give her an eight.
OK. All right.
Well, you know, still in the top, still in the top five.
Let me see. That's a B.
It's a B minus.
Jenny from Bucky O'Hare.
Here she is.
Obvious. Obviously.
Very serious. I'm very serious.
Yeah. So that's even even ascribing a score to this character
who has weird notes all over her, as mentioned before,
including like female fingers are more delicate.
Oh, God, it says sexy pelvic tilt.
This is the weirdest part I've ever seen.
It has the word sexual on it.
And there's lots of weird notes.
And we're given a number.
I think we're in a strange area here.
Maybe maybe this is all you think.
Why should we?
We're like to is canceled because the series Bible was just like,
oh, no, that's too creepy.
We're not building this right.
Jason, what would you I hate to hate to ask you the question now.
One to ten.
How would you rank Bucky O'Hare character Mimi LaFleur?
I those pictures are so small.
Oh, I saw you want me to bring her over here.
Yeah, bring her up.
Yeah, bring her over this way.
So maybe to send me me right this day.
Maybe it's very pretty.
She's in her like work uniform, though.
Well, yeah, she's got her like general stuff.
Yes, her army space army is I can't even I can't process Mimi LaFleur
on a scale of one to ten.
Well, that was my problem, too.
That was my problem, too.
When you quiz me, I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah.
But I think you got there more easily than me because I think maybe you have
thought about a number for Bucky O'Hare character.
Do you want to see Mimi in her prison outfit?
Because this is her in her like orange prison suit.
That doesn't change much.
All right.
It covers everything.
Yeah, these are all very modest outfits you're showing.
Yeah, OK.
Let's let's let's wind this down.
I mean, so, yeah, we didn't get to meet Melody and the light keepers
and we didn't get to ascribe numbers to them.
And it's all said, I really quickly just want to say
sci fi city in Tokyo, which maybe we can't get into a ton.
But I wanted to shout out that really cool sounding ride called UFO Encounter.
And the idea of this, this would have been a tower of terror.
But that going up, the up and down nature of it is getting abducted.
That's a beam.
Oh, track that.
Isn't that a good idea?
A tower of terror.
But you're in a tractor beam.
Awesome. That is really good.
That's really it is that ride system like you would like.
There's what?
Only two versions of it, really, now at this point.
But there's there's the Geyser Mountain, too, which is the tower of terror.
That was just like you were going down to see like robots doing like mining.
And then Geyser bursts and shoots you up.
That's another great version of that, too, that never got built.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it might have also had something called a version of the rock and roller
coaster, but where you're launched into an alien computer system.
And it is called the place that you're launched into is called the cyber mid.
Perfect.
Which is it's tough to unhear the current use of mid, but you know, it's pyramid.
It's not right. Right. Right.
It's a cyber mid.
Great. The opposite of Pira.
That's that's really good.
Cyber mid. So anyway, and like and this would have had something cooler
than rocker rods, rocket bikes.
They would have cracked the issue of a fast ride system moving all around.
And this looks very much the concept are in this look very much like the
like by way of fifties Dexter Jester future.
Yeah. So just another cool unbuilt.
I would have taken either
is the thing that we're pining for the most Plectu.
Is that the saddest loss?
I believe so. Yeah, that for sure is my biggest regret.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, let's see if any of these ideas end up factoring into
that episode or do we just do we could cancel it and instead do
a fixing our high school years.
And we draw straw, we pick numbers again and we go, OK, so you have
the same amount of sexual drive and libido that you did in high school.
And then you have a middle amount.
And then one of somebody gets a blue sky amount of self.
And I guess confidence you would need as well. Of tea.
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
So there's a there's a supply of straw.
You only get a little bit.
OK. Yeah. Yeah.
And we'll see. But, you know, ultimately, the blue sky does end up with you
making out while bros big grand theft auto in the other room.
This much we know. OK.
Yeah, we could do that.
At least went to another room that's much more polite for everyone.
Well, I would say I was going to say at the very least, reading a Bucky O'Hare
comic with this photo of Mimi LaFleur.
It's a full body shot of Mimi LaFleur.
Revised lyric.
Read me a Mimi LaFleur comic while your bros play Grand Theft Auto.
Yeah, no, no activity, no body activity, no body count is occurring.
No, we are not adding to my body.
Every room in this house is all the dorky shit's happening.
OK, well, I think we did it.
I think you survived podcast the ride, the second gate.
Thank you for subscribing.
And if you want to go even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon
to your club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
The song I was trying to place was missing persons.
No one is thinking about it now, but I just wanted to declare that I got there.
OK, I did think of it.
And P.T. Quantum does sound like P.T. Barnum.