FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following special podcast report may include Disney property that resembles
the film Children of Men, freakish mashups of fish and waffles, and an emotionally draining
bathroom visit.
Jacquees Neal regales us with travel tales from Shanghai Disney and so much more on today's
podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast which is making an extremely wise
decision by not attempting an opening joke in Chinese.
I'm Scott Gertner, I executed that decision, and Mike Carlson probably agrees.
Thank God, yeah.
Can you imagine it?
Because you might think, like, that'd be a cute thing to do.
We'd do a little welcome, too, but then we translate it and then, like, knowing how we
pronounce things, I think in one syllable, we are not only mocked but canceled.
Oh, but yeah, that's probably, yeah, there could be, it could be any version of just
embarrassment to just, we're not allowed to broadcast somehow.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, that hasn't stopped other people.
Or pulled off the airs, the air that no body governs whatsoever.
It'd be kind of weird because there are other people that are doing much more offensive
things, but somehow maybe that would happen to us, I don't know.
We would pronounce things so offensively, Jason, Jared, and Helen.
Look, you do it in Mandarin, the Cantonese speakers are mad, you do it in Cantonese,
the Mandarin speakers are mad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And probably both sides are like, which one were they doing?
Didn't sound like either.
Yeah.
Well, we're going to stay away from that.
We will focus on English here.
Smart.
Yeah, I believe so.
It's the language I know the best, and only.
So today, here's what's happening.
Since pandemic and babies, since that era, I would say international theme park travel
has not been our forte, any of us.
And that is why we lean so heavily on the Foreign Correspondent Program.
We have guests who are on the beat meeting and greeting the world.
Griffin Newman started this program and we're passing the baton today to a great returning
guest, a very well-traveled guest who's here to talk about things we've almost never talked
about on the show, so I'm very excited.
From Grand Cru and the live show Comedian Feud here in LA, it's Jaquice Neal, hello.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I am going to attempt Chinese.
I'm not.
Did you learn it?
No, not at all.
I tried to.
Well, I went to Japan and I was doing Duolingo and then I stopped doing it for like three
or four days and then it started to roast me.
It was like, well, I guess you're ignoring me.
And I was like, yeah, fuck you.
I'm going to ignore you now.
And then it changed my icon to like the saddest green monster.
Really?
Yes.
On my phone, it was the happy Duolingo, whatever that thing is.
And then after I didn't go for like a week, I looked at my phone, I was like, why does
it look like that?
It was like so sad.
It had folds in his face.
What?
I was like.
He was dying.
You were making him sick.
Like ET.
He's suffering.
I was like, this is not the way to get me to engage in this at all.
I don't want to engage with this.
Wow.
Are you making it sick or is that like, this is you.
You're a sickly loser who's not learning.
I think it's both because it was like, you know, it would be great for you today.
If you practiced, it would like neg me, like straight up neg me.
So I gave up learning any type of language on my way to Japan, which probably was a mistake
because man, those pronunciations were whooping my ass.
It was, it was hard.
You just have to start.
What I remember from Tokyo is just like, you just kind of like, maybe you, you talk into
a translate program and then like sadly hold out the phone and play it or just show them
what's on the screen or you just kind of like the worst case scenario is you just kind
of put your hands up like help, help, help me, which they do because everybody's nice
and helpful.
Thank God.
Yeah.
A lot of people do speaking when I was in Shanghai, that was half the case.
It was less the case or they were just, you know, like whatever, like leaf, which is very
much the vibe, but was signage helping you out?
Was there at least like English sign?
Okay.
I mean, that's what you need.
I mean, the Chinese system, you guys know.
Yeah.
It's fucking great.
It's great.
Yeah.
A lot of, sorry.
A lot of stuff is in a lot of, a lot of things are in English that you, it's easy to go.
I did not struggle.
I was there for three and a half weeks and I was like, I'm, this is fine.
It's not, they aren't, it's not different arrows there.
Right.
You know, it's not different arrows.
And then like, they still do use like our, or the alphabet that we use for a lot of things,
like the symbols.
I'm like, yeah, that's cool.
That's the most intimidating.
That's what you wonder the most is like, if I'm in a, if I'm in a land of all symbols,
some screw, but yeah, I can't learn all this for 10 days because you know, the thing is
not even that is hard to like, cause I don't know what the other, I don't know what the
things that are using the alphabet are saying either, but if I learned it once, then I could
be like, oh, I know what that says.
Oh yeah.
If I see the symbols and somebody like, that means this, I'm not going to remember that
shit the next time I see it.
Like it's like harder for me to actually like pick up that in a, as quick as I can pick
up like anything that uses the alphabet that we use.
Yeah.
I'm very impressed.
Anybody learns, who successfully learns languages now when they are more of an adult.
Yes.
Yeah.
When your brain is not the sponge it used to be.
You have like, I was so excited when we started talking about what to do, it was a matter
of narrowing it down because you've done, since you've, and you weren't with us that
long ago, but since then you've done like everything.
You've been everywhere theme park speaking.
I, it wasn't that long ago, but I'm almost sure it was still before I went to Europe.
I think I'm way over two years actually.
Yeah.
I think so.
I went to Europe in August, September of 2022.
So I'm pretty sure it was before that.
I think so.
Yeah.
Were you about to go on a cruise?
Disney cruise?
I also went on, I also went on a Disney cruise.
So that's, and that's probably, that's ancient at this point.
Which one?
I went on in December of 22.
Okay.
That was, I just did the one off of, it was like a five day cruise.
I truly can't even remember where we went because I went on two cruises that month.
It was insane.
Wow.
But it was beautiful.
I loved it.
It was great.
We, it was just like going to a couple of places in Mexico, which I feel like, I mean,
now I sound like just a couple of places in Mexico, just a little dilly dally in Mexico.
But I think the cruises that leave like Los Angeles or Southern California are all great,
but like you, they're, they're a lot more like hangout cruises.
Right.
It was like three days, go to Ensenada, come home, but it's mostly about just hanging out
with your friends and eating and drinking.
Okay.
Destiny.
It's not all about the destination.
It's not always about the destination.
Yeah.
So this Disney cruise was similar to that.
It wasn't about the destinations.
It was more about just being on the boat.
Do you remember the name of the boat?
Because they always name these wish or dream.
This is the biggest area of like, yeah, it's destiny.
I'm almost sure it was Inspire.
Which is the name of one of the passes.
That's where the other place they use all the words.
No, no, no.
That's a lie.
It was Wonder.
The Wonder.
Disney Wonder.
I don't think you could feel the specific theme of Wonder as opposed to, I'm sure the
wish is an entirely other situation.
You know what I did when they made it snow on the boat, because it was a holiday cruise.
Oh, wow.
It was a holiday cruise.
I was like, this is wondrous.
Wow.
This is wondrous.
It is a wonder.
Holiday wonder.
Was Santa there?
It was a holiday wonder.
Santa was there.
He was all over the boat.
It was great.
Did he like jump in the pool or anything?
No, I did that on another cruise though, and it was slightly more sexual.
That cruise.
It was a Virgin cruise.
So I don't think that was the Disney cruise vibe.
Wait, did you jump in the pool or Santa did?
No, no.
It was a party.
Santa was not on that boat.
Santa was on that boat actually.
He did not jump in the pool.
Not in his Santa gear at least.
Not in his Santa gear.
It was crazy.
I can't conjure the name now to officially recommend it, but I found this YouTube channel
that is dozens and dozens of videos deep, that's like the 20-minute video they would
send you if you were going to go on the cruise or to convince you to go on the cruise, and
it's all from late 80s, early 90s, exactly the pocket I'm looking for.
These are so great.
Every shot they show you, these incredible atriums with incredible elevators on the boat,
original songs.
There's people who are represented as like cruise ship celebrities, you know who Martin
Starling is.
Wow, you got to be deep, I get to know Martin Starling.
And my other takeaway from all these videos, Kathie Lee Gifford is in a lot of them, and
I did not realize until watching these how attracted I am to Kathie Lee Gifford.
It never occurred to me, if you watch these videos, I don't think anyone would disagree
with me.
I will say I've had this thought in the last year.
Kathie Lee Gifford is attractive.
I'm not obsessing about it, but watching her in cruise mode, you're like, jeez, there's
something about her.
But is it kid you're like, it's like my mom's on TV or something like that, you didn't think
of her in that way at all.
She was no one way at all.
And Cody and Howard Stern makes fun of her and all that, but you remove her from all
that.
When you see her in vacation mode, it's a whole other vibe.
It's a whole different vibe.
See, I'm struggling to even remember what she looks like because I haven't seen her
face in probably 20 years.
Carnival cruise.
I mean, I think she was like, you know, part of an, there was an official one that she
was in spokes for.
It could have been Carnival.
But that's, that's, that's there to look up.
I'll try to figure out what the channel is because we were not, there was not a miss.
We were putting on one of these a night for a while and not a single one of them.
Let me down.
I love it.
And this, and this was from the eighties and stuff you said, right?
Yeah.
Did they send you a video?
Did you get like, here's what to expect on the cruise?
Yeah.
It was very, it was very much like, thank you for your money.
We'll see you on December 2nd.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's a lack of, that's the, they're missing wonder.
They're missing wonder.
They could have got the wonder going from the very beginning, but instead they saved
it for the boat.
Yeah.
No, they don't, they didn't send much.
They send like the little luggage tags and stuff like that, but you know, they didn't
send much.
So let me ask you this question because I believe Kevin Perjurer from Defunct Land was
on our show maybe three years ago.
And he said that the cruise is the only place that the Disney difference still exists.
Meaning that's where you actually feel like, oh, this is a different level of, I don't
know, service or theming or.
Yeah.
So do you feel that?
Maybe.
I actually just talked about this with somebody about the difference in service between Disneyland
and world.
And it's all kind of tanking, but land is a whole different level of tanking right now.
But like, I would say yes, but I don't know, like I've been on, it was definitely, I've
been on nine cruises.
Oh wow.
10.
I've been on 10 cruises in my life and it was definitely a different cruise.
It was like, this is a Disney cruise, right?
Other cruises have similarities.
And the only reason that I probably am not as enthralled with that idea is because later
that month I went on that Virgin cruise, which was like 21 and over.
And that was truly like the craziest, most different cruise I've ever been on in my life.
So it was like, so like the Disney cruise, while it was different from like your Royal
Caribbean's, your carnivals, it still had cruise elements to it.
Whereas that Virgin cruise was like, nah, bro, this is going to be different.
Should we throw out what we were going to do and just talk about this Virgin cruise?
Just talk about the Virgin cruise.
Do we just review that?
How much you can tell us?
Seeming on it?
Listen.
Trip report.
Listen, it was crazy.
It was crazy.
Out of Miami too.
It was a beautiful time.
But yes, I did the Disney cruise.
I've also been to Disney Paris now.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I've been to Disney Tokyo, both of them, Universal Japan.
A week before I went to Japan, I had been before, but I was at Universal Orlando.
Wow.
I sent that in too?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
And it's been, it's been, I went with my partner and she was like, I have not been in as many
parks in my life, let alone in a five week period.
How did she, did she wear out?
Did she wear out?
Yeah.
Was it too much?
To a degree.
Yeah.
By the time we got to Shanghai, Disney, we went to it, but then we also had another day
to chill and she was like, I'm staying in.
You go do whatever you got to do.
I'm sleeping.
It's important.
Know your limits.
We've all been partnered in there.
We've all just communicated.
I like, like where the, the partner has to communicate.
You understand, you understand, I still like this more than 80% of people, but that doesn't
match you.
Right.
You're in the top 0.05%.
Seriously.
Do what you got to do.
You've offered us so many options.
I'm not even sure where to go.
I'm interested to just hear about your Disneyland tanking thoughts, but I'm going to leave it
to you.
Just like, where, where do you want to take us?
Where are you the most excited to talk about?
You know, like, here's the thing.
We got to talk about Shanghai because it was truly one of the most wildest experiences
of my life for any park that I've ever been to.
I will say this though, like a lot of people have asked me, because now I only have one
left.
I only have Disney Hong Kong.
Yeah.
Right.
So I've been to, and I've been to, Alani, I've been on the cruises.
I've been to every Disney thing that you can fucking do and like, which is crazy to me,
but like at this point I'm doing it so I can check them.
I mean, I'm doing it because I love it, but I'm also like, I got to check it off now.
At this point, I'm close enough, but people always ask, all right, so what's your favorite
Disney park now?
And I will say my favorite Disney vacation will always be Disney World.
Sure.
Best Disney parks are Tokyo.
That's a good distinction.
Best Disney parks were Tokyo.
My favorite Disney vacation was Disney World.
Shanghai, my Lord.
Now let me say this.
Okay.
It's a great park.
The crowd culture at Disney Shanghai was the worst crowd culture I have ever experienced
out of any park.
Like worse than Six Flags.
Whoa.
Interesting.
Why?
What's happening?
They literally have signs around Shanghai asking guests to not pee and poop out of the
bathroom.
What?
And I saw it, like I saw butt naked children pissing in the middle of the goddamn road,
like in bags.
On Main Street?
Yes.
Wow.
Really?
Crazy.
I mean, all right.
So here's the thing.
Like Disney Shanghai was beautiful.
It's a beautiful park.
It's chill.
It's only one park.
Yeah.
And we went for one and a half day, essentially.
So we did everything.
Everything was fun.
The parades were cute.
The firework show, best firework show out of any Disney park that I've been to.
Really?
There were great things about the park.
Zootopia Land is new.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you saw that.
Oh, you knew that.
Yeah, yeah.
I did.
It just opened last year or this year?
Recently.
Last few months.
It was like, you know, it was a line to get in the land that can take up to an hour type
thing.
Yeah, yeah.
But the land is very cool.
Like super dope.
It feels like you're dropped in the middle of like Zootopia.
Does it feel small?
That's a question I have about it.
Is it like, is there a lot jam packed or is it sort of a spacious land?
It is a lot jam packed, but it's not as small as like Super Nintendo World.
Super Nintendo World.
Yeah.
It's not as big as like, you know, Star Wars land or Cars Land.
Sure.
It's somewhere like in the middle of the two, where it didn't feel, it was a type of place
that you could be like, all right, you know, I can stand in this spot and see 70% of the
park or 70% of the land.
And then if I go over there, I'll see the rest.
Like if I'm just, you know, standing and looking around type thing, which I guess Cars Land
is kind of like that too.
But it has, you know.
There's like a corner you turn.
Here's a whole other section.
Yeah.
Nothing's going to be as impressive as like Star Wars land.
Like as far as the scope, size, stuff like that.
You cannot see it all.
Like yeah, it's radically different.
Nothing's going to be like that.
But Zootopia was dope.
And it was like, it was like really cool because it also makes you feel like you're an animal.
So like, and it's like a city.
So they have like a news ticker and like, you know, newscast for like the animals and
like people, the animals getting off the subway station and like there was a big giraffe
working out on the treadmill and stuff like that.
Do they have puppets in the window or something too?
They have puppets in the window, animatronics.
And they have yeah, like animatronics like in the windows, on the, on the streets and
stuff like that.
Just kind of moving and talking and stuff like that.
Did you get any of the food there?
I did get the food.
The food there was.
Like the big food.
There's like a big popsicle in Zootopia land.
There's like the big popsicle.
There's also like, their food combinations were a little weird.
Like they had tuna and waffle, which I was like, I don't need to try that at all.
That sounds good to me.
I'm okay.
Horrible to me.
You would eat that.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, it's just a tuna sandwich in a slightly different form.
Mixed with sweet, that's a little rough.
I didn't try it.
Neither one of us tried it.
All right.
They had like little Paul food, you know, like food that's in Paul shape.
Also by that time, you know, we had just, we were in Japan for like three and a half
weeks.
I was a little over trying new shit.
Sure.
I was like, I, you know, just, I just want to eat McDonald's for a taste of home.
Not even, not even going to McDonald's was just like, I don't need to try anything that
I'm like, I may not like this.
I just like, just give me food that I want.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat it.
And then like, you know, cause they had a couple of things there that was like, okay,
maybe, you know, a week ago, I would have tried this to see how it was, but right now
I'm like, I'm good.
I'm okay.
I think that zone that like, cause when Tokyo Disney opens, I think there's the feeling
of they want the American experience and they want just like burgers, hot dogs, pizza.
If you wanted to go that route, is that, can you do that in Shanghai?
Yeah.
Just basic basics.
Not, kind of, kind of, it's not, it's, it's very, the one thing I liked about the Tokyo
Disney's, the Disney's in Asia, obviously I haven't gone to Hong Kong yet, as opposed
to like Disney Paris, which I've been to, was like, they very much don't give a shit
about Americans.
Like most of the shows are not, have no English in them.
Right.
There's a couple that did, but like every show in Disney Paris was like, it's half English,
half French.
Right.
Whereas this one, which like was really cool cause it's like, yeah, no, you're here.
Like, this is ours, right?
There was some where I was like, hey, you know, maybe just play, you know, never had
a friend from Robin Williams instead of whatever version this is, but like other than that,
Even the crowd was just like, we don't care about this.
You'd rather it be the voice you know and the syllables you know, even if it's not your
language.
Yeah.
Cause they, you know, a lot of people all over the world know those versions too.
But yeah, it was, it was, it was definitely just very un-American, which was like refreshing
in a way.
Yeah.
It's just fully theirs.
And then in that land and in that ride, assuming you did the ride.
Zootopia ride.
I did do the Zootopia ride, which was very fun.
Okay.
Very fun.
Are you dealing, is it like Jason Bateman and people, did they, or is it sound-alikes
because it's all in other?
It's all in, it's all in, that one was all in, man, y'all about to make me, whatever
language they speak in, Shanghai, Mandarin or I'm not sure.
Yeah.
I'm not sure the division of Mandarin and Cantonese and the breakdown.
It was not, it was not in English.
So I would assume that it was not like-
Probably not Bateman.
Bateman.
Unless-
He didn't teach him Chinese.
Unless he has some hidden skills that we haven't seen yet on camera.
I don't know.
Well, John Cena, I don't know if you've seen John Cena speak Mandarin.
He's fluent.
Yeah, yeah.
When he had to do, it's an amazing video where he had to do an apology for something
which he executes in perfect Mandarin and it looks like a hostage video.
It's the scariest thing you ever see.
Is that, did he use a slightly wrong distinction of Taiwan, Taipei?
And he wanted to apologize.
Oh, yeah, I don't remember.
I don't even remember what it was about.
You might be right.
He had to apologize because it was-
It was the Taiwan is a country issue.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
He, I believe if I'm, hopefully I'm not getting my John Cena history wrong is that there was
an interview where maybe Steve Austin asked him like, well, what do you do for fun?
What are you doing for fun?
He goes, well, I'm learning Chinese so I can help expand the brand, the WWE brand over
to China.
And he's like, you could tell he was like a little confused, like for fun, like, well,
I just, you know, I just want to help the WWE grow more and more.
And you're like, oh, okay.
That was John Cena's whole thing.
He just announced his retirement yesterday.
Yes, he did.
Yeah.
Next year.
It was his last year doing anything, well, wrestling at least.
Or he comes back in two years and it's like none of it happened.
Like they all do.
They all do.
They all do, yeah.
They never retire.
Never retire.
Oh yeah.
No, I didn't, I didn't, I forgot what the, I know what we were talking about.
I was actually talking about Voices in the Rite.
Voices in the Rite, yeah.
But the Rite itself.
Rite itself was great.
Looks cool.
Yeah, the Rite itself was great.
It's very similar to, I mean, it's trackless.
Uh-huh.
You know, like.
With like some of the same tricks where like, now I don't remember the names of the kid
that hasn't been on in my house in a while, the fox and the rabbit that they pull up in
a car and almost the same way as Mickey and Minnie and yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
It's very similar to that.
Uh, it's way better than like, people get mad at me when I say this, but like the Mario
Kart shit is so trash to me.
That's been the take on this show.
That's what we feel.
Yeah.
It's so trash.
We talked around it for a while and ultimately let, no, I think there's no other way to land
than this.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
It's sad.
It makes us so sad to say it too.
It is.
It should be very fun.
Yeah.
It's the ultimate slam dunk of a ride.
And yet they figured out a way.
And they just biffed it.
Yeah.
Uh, but Zootopia was fun.
Like it was a fun ride.
It was cool.
It was dope.
Yeah.
Do you end up like, uh, I should know this.
I should have watched her ride through, but like, do they, and in the land in general,
do they, they take advantage of that?
Like now we're in a small world and now we're in a big world, like big size differences.
Yeah.
So like, it's like half screen, half like actual sets and stuff like that, but they
also do like, uh, take advantage of like, if you're in a place where it's windy, you
feels like there's a place where it was supposed to be cold and it got super cold and hot and
stuff like that.
So they take advantage of like all the, the feelings around you and stuff like that.
Um, but it is, it is utilizing like screens, but also like animatronics and it was very
well done.
It was like super, super cool.
Um, you'd be happy if this, if this showed up in animal kingdom, which is a possibility
I guess where it should go.
Right?
Yeah.
I think people will love it.
I've not done Ratatouille yet.
We did.
We've all done it now.
Yeah.
You know what?
I think I was kind of underrating it.
I got to do it in Paris kind of right when it opened and was maybe like with all the
build up, maybe built it up too much.
And then the way we did it end of the day, end of a long day, uh, tiring day, a wine
filled day.
It was like a really nice little like, ah, of a, yeah, if you do it under that, like,
because trackless rides is often you build up that like they're supposed to be, uh, you
know, the thrilling breakneck kind of, but if you view that as like a tourism ride, like
a Soren or something, I think it's a pleasant little ride.
Yeah.
It's a chance to do it.
I mean, it was closed when I went to Paris, which was very, it was the only ride closed
when I went to Paris.
What do they have in that park?
What do they have if not Ratatouille?
It was, I was very disappointed.
I was like, and it was when I always laugh at people when they come here, like to Disneyland
because we're local, so we can go anytime, but I always like, man, I came in this ride
was closed.
And I was like, Hey man, I'm big breaks.
And then it happened to me and I was like, this was bullshit on the other side of the
earth.
I traveled all the way here and it's closed my money back.
Well, that's what we're, and we'll talk about it soon a little bit, but like it's come up
before, but I didn't get to do Pooh's honey hunt, which still itches at me and isn't that's
a good one, right?
In Tokyo.
Tokyo.
I did not do it actually.
I didn't think I did it either.
Oh, okay.
I think it was closed.
Oh, also closed.
Wow.
We are not.
Mike, you're the only one with any luck.
It's much better than the ones here.
Yeah.
It's trackless.
First trackless, I believe, right?
In Disney.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
When I saw it was closed, I was like, ah, that's okay.
Cause I was comparing it to the one here.
I was like, that's fine.
No.
It's not fine.
Dang.
Gotta go back.
You should be upset.
Did you get something?
I don't know if anybody's really been on our show and talked about Beauty and the Beast.
Did you get that one?
Man.
Uh, top, top three, top three rides that I've ever been on at Disney for sure.
That's the Magic Kingdom, it's not called that, but that's the Magic Kingdom Park in
Tokyo.
Yeah.
That's, that's Tokyo Disneyland.
Um, and I didn't know anything about it.
Like I, I didn't, I, I, I purposefully.
Cause like, you know, I'm such a Disney park person.
I purposefully like, didn't like look at what rides are there, you know, and stuff like
that.
Cause I wanted to have some surprise.
Yeah.
You rarely have that opportunity to like just bump into things and I literally don't know
what I'm getting on right now.
Exactly.
It's the greatest.
And I don't have that opportunity in many parks.
Even at, even at Universal Japan, like.
You know what Spider-Man is.
You know what, yeah.
That's what the rides are.
Right?
So I was like, I didn't look too much.
So when we got, when we were looking, it was like, Oh, this Beauty and the Beast ride is
like, you know, the wait times are pretty high.
Like it must be popular.
Yeah.
And we were able to get like the priority pass forward or something like that.
And we rode it and like this, you know, the big teacups, I'm like, huh, this is interesting.
But I still didn't know what was about to happen.
And then when you get on it and you're in it and like, I'm looking around, I'm like,
this is phenomenal.
This is fucking phenomenal.
Like it was so.
Like some of the nicest rooms they've ever made.
It seems like.
Man.
I got a lot.
I have a lot to say about Shanghai, but I will say this about Tokyo.
Best technology out of any park I've ever been to.
Yeah.
Like the technology at, I mean, there was fucking, I mean, the statues, like this little
statue, this might, who's this?
Leatherface?
Leatherface.
Space where another, where the show movies baby happens on forever dog.
So it's often, you listeners might not know, we're often recording next to a life sized
leather face with a chainsaw that could come on if we plugged it in.
It could, which would be dope.
Oh yeah.
You got some.
Okay.
That's dope.
Well, at Tokyo Disney, they would sprinkle a little magic and then it would just come
to life.
Fully articulated, bending and moving.
It was really, really cool.
Like I loved the technology at Tokyo Disney.
So the technology in that room was dope.
We're jumping all around a little, but do you flash to any, uh, any attractions or,
or just, or, or just buildings or whatever, where you're like, I know this, I know this
from the American parks and then you did the Tokyo version and like, Oh, I don't know that
like they did it so much better.
Yeah.
Uh, not, not so much in Tokyo for some of the things that were the same.
Like there were some differences, but I had that experience more actually in Paris with
Haunted Manor.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I was on that ride and I was like, this is kind of terrifying.
That is a moody ride.
Yes.
Yeah.
There is a vibe to that.
It sticks.
I like feel something in my chest.
Yeah.
Even remembering it.
And I was not expecting that.
Yeah.
Even though some of the things are the same, it's still the busts and it's still like the
stretch.
Like so many of the things are the same, but it's just the way it's painted in the score
and everything.
Yeah.
It's even the regular stuff scarier.
It is more horror-based.
It also feels like, wait, cause I've only watched a video of it.
It's like you do the cemetery and then you leave through the town, which I assume gives
you like just a, there's a final feeling of leaving through the town and seeing the, whatever
that guy's name is.
What is it?
Phantom Manor?
The Phantom?
Yeah.
There's a thing that like lingers with you that way because the last thing you see is
that stuff.
Yeah.
It was really wild.
And it's not just a fun party with the ghosts following you.
What was going on in that town?
I don't even remember specifically, but it's a mood.
It's definitely a mood.
I was surprised by that.
And then Space Mountain in Paris too, like it was pretty much the same, but then all
of a sudden I felt myself going upside down and I was like, what the fuck is going on?
Oh yeah.
Oh, you didn't know it, did you?
I didn't know that.
Oh, this is great.
I love how you experienced it.
Like we've ruined too many things for ourselves.
I know.
I didn't ruin Journey to the Center of the Earth.
That was the one where I was like, I don't think it's scary enough that I need to like
know that it does, but that was like the rare time.
Like I'm going to make myself not know what the hell is right.
Yeah.
And I'm so glad I did it though.
It was cool.
I like, I really like Journey.
Tokyo Disney was great.
Did you see any of the Fantasy Springs expansion?
It was, I think it was slated to open in June.
Okay.
So it's open now, I think.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
I was there late April.
So it was pretty, I don't even think I saw where it was.
It's like way back too.
Yeah.
It was pretty well hidden and pretty like, nobody come near here.
That's not like Vasa Coasters getting built in the middle of the park.
They can like fully close that off and still conduct regular business.
It's a huge walk from Disney Seas entrance, I think too, to completely opposite side,
I think.
It's like, cause Disney Seas, huge, like it is so big.
Cannot believe.
Yeah.
It was truly one of the most, and just like we went for two days and like toward the end
of the second day, we were still coming up on parts of Disney Seas.
We were like, oh shit, we didn't even know this was over here.
Yeah.
It was so big.
So yeah, no, I didn't see any of Fantasy Springs, but I'm sure it would be dope.
I mean, they were getting ready for it, they were passing out stickers and like when we
turned the sticker down, cause we had already gotten three, they were like, what?
They start laughing at us like, they don't want a sticker?
I was like, damn.
Aren't you also like knowing that there's this huge, there's this big expansion with
like three mini zones and big new rides.
And you were at Tokyo Disney Sea before that, it's like, it doesn't need that.
It doesn't need it.
I mean, it's great that it has it, but like of all, it's so insane that that of all parks
gets an expansion while here we wait.
There's just full dead zones in the Disneyland resort.
Yeah.
It needs something to happen.
I kind of almost wish like they would start franchising the Disney's out here, like they
do at the ones in Asia.
Cause it's like.
Well, it's just budget.
Yeah.
Budget wise, they'll spend the money.
They spend the money.
Yeah.
They have so much money for the ones that like, I was reading like how much money they
have just for those parks and it's in the millions of dollars.
Yeah.
Well, Shanghai, the full Shanghai resort, there's land to build two more theme parks.
Wow.
It's huge and it's kind of too big.
Right.
Like to start the day at Disney Shanghai, like, cause we took a Uber or taxi or something
from our hotel and to get to the, from that to get to the park was almost like a 20 minute
walk.
But like, which is, you know, kind of can be the same here, but it was like a 20 minute
straightaway walk.
It was not like going through different, you know, got to turn these blocks and go through
a town and shit.
It was like, no, straight to like the park gate is like a 20 minute walk.
That's harder.
Yeah.
You can get tricked if there's like, you're winding and strolling, but oh my God.
But the one, all right, so man, when we got out the car, I will say this about Walt Disney.
He had, he had it right when he was like, I want to move to places where I can regulate
who's around my park.
Like, because that was needed at Shanghai.
As soon as we got out the car, there are hundreds of people trying to sell you bootleg Disney
stuff.
Oh really?
Yes.
To the point where like somebody put their hands on me, like they are opening your car
door.
They're following you.
They're in your space.
And this is on Disney's property.
Oh shit.
It's not like, it's not in the town next to Disney.
You have passed the gate of Disney and like, they are there.
And so, and like, and it's the whole 20 minute walk, trying to in your face, selling you
stuff.
This, I've not even gotten to, we'll talk about nighttime because it's crazy, but like
the whole 20 minute walk.
And so I, like, I just did not expect that.
Like, you know, you don't expect that at Disney.
I noticed it in Paris and it's not the full, but like right outside the train station.
I was shocked that it's just like people like doing like glowing things that fly up in the
air, like in regular Paris.
I was so surprised to see that anywhere close.
It was, it was, it was crazy.
It was truly like, the only thing I could equate it to was like when I go to the Caribbean
and everybody's trying to sell you shit, times 20 and throw in time square vibes of
like, just aggressiveness.
Yeah.
Like it was like, it was, it was really crazy.
And, and also at this point, like I'm at the end of the trip, my patience is low and the
dude touched me.
Like my, my girlfriend had to like, come on, man, don't get arrested in China because he
literally like grabbed me and turned me around.
Whoa.
And it's nine in the morning.
I'm like, please take your hands off of me.
Like you're dialed in for a Disney day.
You are not expecting to get into a street fight.
It was, it was so insane.
So about it.
So by the time we do that, I'm like, all right.
Can I ask what are they like t-shirts, t-shirts, ears, teddy stuffed animals, like sunscreen,
like everything.
Yeah.
Some of it is knockoff merchandise that you can find in the park.
Others are things that you may need for the day.
Right.
Like there's kids selling shit and adults.
It was, it was truly, and it's not even that it was like, I've been around that before,
right?
You know, like, but not at Disney.
So like, that was the jarring part.
Like I was not ready for that in particular.
Yeah.
And are you, you're like on the, you're like on like landscaped grounds and like faint.
It's a small world.
I can see.
Yeah.
I can see the castle.
Weird.
I can see the castle dude.
I've never heard this.
It is.
This is why.
It was, it was so wild.
And like we're walking to the park, we're like, all right.
Like, you know, by the time when you get a little closer to the park, it's not as like
aggressive.
So that was like chill.
But when we got in the line and this set us up for the whole day, like there's people
smoking in line.
And like, when I say it set us up for the whole day, you will get people smoking in
the lines and the rides and the bathrooms, like walking through the park, like it, and
it was so crazy.
And it's just like, I get if, if you'd let people get away with this, they will try,
but like, they don't let you get away with this at other Disney's like, right.
That was the crazy part.
Like.
Is it tech?
It's no technically not supposed to be smoking, right?
Yeah.
I looked it up as we were starting.
It's not supposed to be.
Yeah.
And it is like smoking only in certain areas.
Okay.
No.
But they just don't enforce it.
No, they don't.
That's the thing.
They don't enforce anything.
Like they have the sign saying don't piss on the street, but they don't enforce it.
People are actually like not doing it.
Right.
Wait.
I think we also plowed past that.
I knew you said piss and poop percent.
Did you see people peeing?
That's what he said.
Yeah.
I didn't see anybody shitting, thankfully.
Okay.
But I saw two people.
I saw two people.
I saw a preteen.
Where?
Both children.
So not adults.
Okay.
But I saw a preteen, but their families were with them.
I saw a preteen just pissing in a bush.
And then I saw this kid was maybe like six, seven, butt naked.
And his parents were holding a like grocery store bag for him to pee in.
But a bag to pee in seems impractical.
Pooping at least makes more sense.
It makes, I guess, you know, the bathroom 30 yards away.
It makes the most sense.
Regardless of that, I'm just saying.
Pooping in a bag makes more sense.
It makes more sense to me.
The whole urine is just pure liquid.
You can scoop up a poop.
You can scoop up the poop once it's on the ground, but pee you know it's going to spread.
I understand the thought.
I'm just saying.
It's like a diaper that they aren't wearing.
Yeah.
A diaper that you hold out.
You're like a target.
This is, I mean, she won't care if I say this, but like me and my partner were like having
a disagreement.
Like, in this hour, you know, 24, 25 days, 25 days together, yeah, we were having a disagreement.
So, we weren't like, you know, we were just like, you know, arguing about something.
I can't even remember what, and like, and we saw this little kid, that was the first
one we saw, the kid like butt naked, and it like snapped us out of our argument.
We were both just like, you saw that, right?
Like we were fine after that.
Because it was just so jarring, it's so jarring to see that.
Sure, yeah.
I wonder what was nearby, do you remember like, this line, this riot, or this sort of
Yeah, it was, like imagine you are walking down the road where like Indiana Jones and
like all, it was like that, it was like food places, and it's not even like seeing the
kid pee, because kids will do crazy shit.
The parents were assisting this child, and that was the crazy part to me.
They came with a bag, they knew this was their plan, this is how they do it.
And I'm like, take them to the bathroom, like, it's, I mean like, the Disney's don't not
have bathrooms there, and they're pretty nice, they're clean.
Sure, but you know, privacy you find to be a good thing, I think so.
It's a good thing for everybody, for you and the people around you, there's a reason we
do this.
And so, you know, after we see this little naked boy, we're just like, all right, we're
in for a day.
And like, but the biggest pet peeve outside of the smoking, the peeing and pooping, in
the park, was like, you have to stand your ground, or people will cut you.
Oh man.
And not even like, people will just literally like, brush past you, and be like, no, you're
not here.
And like, and it's weird because it's not confrontational, like, if you say something
they'll be like, oh, oh, okay, like, they'll back up and be like, oh yeah, yeah.
But like, it's almost like you don't exist, it's like you don't exist.
So there's no gate, because like, oftentimes in the American parks, or a Six Flags or something,
I feel like people will do a trick.
They'll pretend they're on the phone, they'll pretend, excuse me, they'll pretend somebody's
ahead.
I've seen this a lot.
They go, oh, hey, and they wave to the person, then they go by you, and you're like, I'm
pretty sure they just.
Yeah, they just cut.
So there's a little game that generally is played, I feel like, when I see this.
There's no games.
They were like, no, we're just going, we don't want to be here, we're going to go to where
we want to be.
Yeah, sure.
And like, so it was almost to a point where like, and it wasn't every ride, but it was
like two or three, where you almost have to kind of like stand side by side.
So people like don't rush past you, like, to be your own bodyguards.
It was, it was so wild.
It was just such all this crazy, and it is the example, and it made me appreciate the
Disney's here more.
And it made me appreciate, I guess, American decorum, because it's not even because a lot
of the things that people were doing, I would say would happen.
Maybe not the peeing and the pooping, but like the smoking, the cutting in line, a lot
of that type of stuff would happen if consequence wasn't a thing.
Right?
Like, if somebody, if somebody would say like, Hey, you can't do that.
Like I, you know, people would cut everybody, you know, people try it even, but like, it
would be more rampant.
Sure.
It was just like, they did, the Disney workers didn't care.
Like they did not care.
Like people were smoking in front of cast members, like, and I don't know if it's just
like, Oh, well, we can't do anything about it.
Too many people at once doing it.
Like, I don't know.
I don't know, dude.
It would be, it would be unenforceable by cast members not making very much money.
I guess maybe that's it.
Because so many people are doing things.
It would just be, they would be spending their whole day.
It feels okay.
If somebody was doing it, like if somebody was smoking, it wouldn't be like 12 people
smoking in a line.
It would be like one or two.
So it was easy enough to be like, you put your cigarette out, you can pinpoint who's
doing the things.
Can I ask this question?
Was the, with this, as far as the smoking, was there ever a time when somebody was smoking
on a ride where you were like, that's actually cool looking?
Never on the rides.
It was always in lines and in bathrooms.
Because that's what my dream is, to smoke a cigarette on Pirates of the Caribbean.
That would be tight.
Yeah.
Did you and your partner go buy cigarettes after witnessing the naked child roaming around?
We bought crack.
Oh.
Cause like, look, if they're going to let us do it, we might as well go all out.
Sure.
We might as well do it all.
Yeah, man, it was, I was just, it was, it was, it was a really weird day.
It was a really weird day because like in the middle of like all this beautiful stuff
and it's still Disney-fied in a way, you just have like, I can't tell you how many times
I got shoulder-checked, like somebody shoulder-checked like my partner, which like, it was just,
people were rude.
And they don't care.
Like that was the crazy part.
It was just like, there's no, and, and, you know, I know I'm saying all this and like,
if we're talking percentages, 98% of the people were fine.
Sure, sure.
But still 2% of like people doing all that is still jarring for Disney.
I think you, one person does some of this stuff in a regular park day and you remember
it and you clock it and it's a story later, as opposed to you, you're lost and it's happening
so much you can't even pick them up and pick them out.
Yeah, because we were together when we saw the person vape during the Barbossa scene
on Pirates of the Caribbean and it blew smoke up and I'll never forget it, so it stuck with
me forever.
Yeah.
Because it's not something you see very often.
It's not something you see very often.
And because you were jealous.
You wanted it to be you.
And because I said that looks fucking cool.
Yeah.
I wish I could do it.
Which you should, look, go to Shanghai.
You will, you can do it.
I will say this, you, I completely forgot about this, to your point like from earlier,
was there any like ride that was just like way, Pirates.
Oh yeah, right.
In Shanghai.
You've done that.
That's what my question is.
Oh my God.
Nuts.
That's one that I've watched the video just because I'm like, I'll spoil this.
I don't know, when am I going to get to Shanghai?
That's bonkers.
It is, that, that, yeah, that Beauty and the Beast Pirates, definitely like top like five.
Wow.
Like any ride I've ever been on.
Yeah.
Like as far as like besides like roller coasters, but like that Pirates ride, I, because they
did the Disney Plus did the Behind the Attraction and one of the episodes was, I think Shanghai
or something.
I can't remember what, but like I did see on the documentary or something, like it was
different.
So I knew it was different going in, right?
Yeah.
Even knowing it's different going in, it's still like, this is one of the best things.
You are, you are on a boat that is like going through an entire world.
You're turning, you're like, I mean, like you're going backwards.
You're doing is.
Does it, does it fake you out?
Like you sort of, it resembles the Pirates, you know, and then starts doing things that
the real boat never could.
Is there sort of a fake out like that?
There's a couple, like there's, there's, they really utilize the space really dope.
Not to spoil, I mean, at this point, if you listen to this, you probably spoiled a lot
of shit.
But like, there was a part where like you're on the ride.
They do really good with like keeping your attention over here while some other shit
is happening.
So like you're looking at some great stuff and it's another thing they use, utilize the
screens and sets and animatronics and things like that.
Yeah.
So you're looking at like this animatronic in the screen and you're on a boat and it's
just immersive is all you can see then all of a sudden you're like boat turns to the
left and it's a huge boat with the pirate fight going on, like that.
You're just like, where the hell did this come from?
Like, and it's just like a lot of that, like as you're going through it and you go like
these big screens, like simulate going under the water and then going back up above the
water.
Yeah.
And this is the one like, you know, there's talk of maybe depth comes out of some of the
ones here, but not this one.
Depth's part.
He's in it.
Sparrow is the, you can't extract sparrow from that version of the ride.
No, he is, he is, he is in it, in it.
Like he, if you were to do it, you would have to like change the entire ride.
You think everything.
Look at a different theme entirely.
Tron.
It's Tron now.
Yeah.
Well, that's the Shanghai Bedlam is you can drink, you can piss outside and they're never
getting rid of sparrow.
Not even, right.
This is the wild culture.
Listen, for that one, I don't think, I think sparrow would be like a saint for them.
Sure.
They're all emulating it.
I'm just acting like sparrow.
Can I tell you guys the end of the day?
Oh yeah, go ahead.
So we, I am a fan of the Disney fireworks.
Yeah.
I love a fireworks show at Disney.
It's a beautiful thing.
The fireworks show at Tokyo was complete ass.
Really?
It was so bad.
It was like five minutes or less.
It's not a theme to it.
It's like not even over the cat.
They put it in a place where you could see the fireworks show from both Disneyland and
Disney Sea.
So it's not really over anything.
It's just kind of randomly in the middle of the sky.
Yeah.
Music playing.
It's just like, it's like a, it's like a Burbank 4th of July fireworks show.
And so I was like, that was terrible.
So like I had heard the Shanghai fireworks show was beautiful.
I purchased like a thing where we can get like good seats for it.
It was like $20.
So it wasn't that expensive, but it was like, you're right in the middle.
It was gorgeous.
One of the best fireworks shows I'd ever seen.
We're riding this beautiful high flag.
It's the end of the day, even after all this crazy shit, we're like, ah, that was a Disney
day.
Like it feels great.
And we walk out the park and all those people that were there in the beginning of the day
are also there at the end of the day.
However, also there at the end of the day, where at least one to 200 security guards
on bullhorns.
Oh my God.
Just repeatedly, like, like, like at full volume, repeatedly, it's in another language,
but like just, and it's like that nonstop.
When I tell you it was like, I, I, you know, if you went, if you've been to some protests,
if you were going to those protests in 2020, when the cops were like aggressive toward
like the, it was like that and it was like, yes, this is a problem.
Like the people selling things, cause that's what they're doing it to.
They're doing it to like push all those people away.
So they're like, so like there would be 20 people like chasing one person selling something
to push them out and the bullhorns are basically yelling at them.
So I'm like, is that a problem?
Is it annoying?
Yes.
But you guys are making it much worse.
It was the most aggressive, like it truly, I truly felt like I was in like, in like a
police state, like it was crazy.
And it was like, my, my partner was like this, like I'm stressed.
I was stressed.
Yeah.
It was the craziest.
I wish I would have got like a video of it, but I was just so like, what the hell is going
on?
And I didn't even like think to do it, but I was like, after this beautiful, magical
like end of the day, we walk out to the most aggressive energy that I could possibly.
And it's like this on that entire 20 minute walk back to where we need to go.
It was, it was the craziest shit I've ever experienced in my life.
And that must happen every night.
It must.
Like the second day we went, we were only there for a half day.
So we left in the middle of the day.
So it was like, it was like a peaceful exit.
Like, I was like, this is great.
But like, it must be like that every night.
At least it was like that the night I went.
Yeah.
And this is in third downtown Disney, Disney Springs, which is called Disney town.
Disney town.
Yeah.
It's in Disney town.
It is in like the way back to like where it, you know, if you took a bus, a shuttle parked
taxi is on the way back to that stuff as well.
But it is literally like, as soon as you exit the park.
I'm trying to figure out, I just don't want to see this on street view.
Like what is this route that I want to know like the official name of it.
The route.
I don't even know what it's got.
You walk over a huge bridge and then like there is you walk through parts before you
can like go off to like Disney town because there's a huge lake.
Okay.
Yeah.
There's so much property there.
That's the crazy thing.
It's a lot of property there.
You also go up this long escalate, this long escalator, similar to like a universal escalator
to get up.
Starway.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
It like, it was just a cheesecake factory, eating cheesecake, just hear screaming bullhorns
outside.
Bro.
It was, it was the wildest shit I've ever experienced in my life.
And like, I grew up on the south side of Chicago and I was just like, I have been around police
officers.
I've been around gunshots.
I've been around all types of shit.
And at the end of this Disney day at Shanghai, I was like, this is the most aggressive energy
that I've ever felt like leaving a place in my life.
This felt like watching Disney fall.
This is like, this is the state overtaking.
It was wild.
Disney town.
And it's just like, again, I know those Disney's are franchised.
So Disney itself doesn't have a say, but I'm like, if this were to happen at Disneyland
or Disney World, like the way they stop that is just don't allow those people on the property.
You don't bring like a tank.
Disney Springs rolling it around like, if you don't leave, we gonna fuck y'all up.
Like, they're not doing that.
Like, they just don't, you just don't get on the property.
Right.
Yes.
Warnay, please vacate, but also come back tomorrow and just be nicer tomorrow.
That's the thing.
You can come back tomorrow, but leave now.
We know you'll be back tomorrow, but today you should leave.
Leaving Tokyo, Disney, I was like, man, you know, we just suck in America.
And then after Shanghai, I was like, I can't wait to get the fuck back to like, like some
American decorum.
Some Florida decorum.
Yeah.
Where shit makes sense, you know, they may not like me cause I'm black, but they won't
put a bullhorn on my face.
It's just dirty looks.
A man is trying to sell me a fucked up looking Cluedo, 10 police officers are chasing him.
It was, it was, it was so funny, man.
It was, it was just so crazy.
It was, it was the wildest thing and it was like the last park out of the whole trip.
So it was just like the final image.
That was the end of the trip.
Way to go out.
It was the end of the trip.
Oh my God.
My wife and I both cried when we left Tokyo.
We're on the plane tearing up because we didn't want to leave.
This is the opposite.
You're like, I was like, yeah, we can go.
I don't have to come back to Shanghai.
You're blowing noisemakers.
All right.
America.
Like Disney Tokyo.
I'll go back any day.
I cannot wait to be in LAX.
Seriously.
A place with clarity and order.
And order.
Law and order.
I do love like, I copy, just to remember wherever you've been, I copy pasted your
DMs into my notes and I am looking at the phrase, you know, crowd culture differences.
I'm like, well, you really underplayed.
I didn't think piss bags would be part of that.
It was, it was really wild, man.
Like I, cause you know, look, again, I've been to so many, I've been to every, at this
point until next year, when the new universal opens up, I've been to every universal gate.
I've only not been to one like Disney gate.
I've been to like Cedar point.
I've been to bush gardens.
I've been to all the shit here.
Like I've been to so many theme parks.
I was a teenager at Six Flags.
Like I've been to parks where like, you know, people are wild, right?
And so like, you know, it is, I'm 37, it is very rare where you can have experiences where
like I just truly was not expecting like that.
And I walked out of that was like, and the weird part about it is it would even make
a little bit more sense if it was just a full trash day, if it was just like that Disney
just sucked everything about it.
But it was like, it still had the Disney world in it.
Your favorite fireworks.
Yeah, it was, it was like my least favorite hellish mile where I was screamed at by bull
horns.
It's like the most, it's the juxtaposition that was the problem or it was the like whiplash.
It was the whiplash.
Yeah.
I hate to keep bringing up a pro, but if I'm at a protest and this shit has happened, I'm
like, yeah, this makes sense.
Yeah.
It's a little stranger next to a giant Lego store.
You're at a protest, but then like you go on a boat ride to like see Johnny Depp and
then it's like the most magical thing.
It's the most magical thing and then you walk out and you know, somebody's pooping in a
bush.
It was crazy, man.
It was crazy.
It's a very unique experience.
I had never heard that.
Okay.
So, you know, just, just spoilers, I guess, if you, if you don't want the parks, if you
go to Shanghai, you don't want to rune for you, Zootopia is a trackless ride system.
And when you leave, you are accosted and scared for, you're part of an, you're part of an
unwilling haunt experience.
That is real.
That is so real.
And look, man, you, you know, you can get some Disney ears for maybe a half a price
if you want.
It's probably some deals though.
You can get some deals.
There's some deals.
You can probably get some deals.
Yeah.
Honestly, you can probably get some deals.
A piss bag with Huey on it.
Yeah.
Get your piss bags here.
An off model Huey.
Yeah.
But he still is Huey.
He looks like Huey.
He's Huey.
But he's still.
Man.
This is crazy.
Yeah, dude.
I, if, if I got to go for free, I would go back to Disney Shanghai, uh, because the park
is fun.
The park is cool.
There was some rides there that were like really great.
Um, I'm almost sure Tron was, yeah, Tron is there.
Did you do the Buzz Lightyear ride?
Looks crazy.
Yeah.
I did do that.
It was fun.
It was, it was super fun.
Was it different?
What's up with that one?
It's just like very built up and there's a lot of animatronics and robots.
There's more animatronics.
It's like a bigger budget version of it.
Yeah.
It's still the same type of ride.
Sure.
Um, as far as like what you're doing, but like, it's just bad.
Better.
Yeah.
Um, in that aspect.
There's something called, there looks like this very pleasant boat ride that kind of
goes around the castle and it's lots of little like fairy tale scenes.
Did you do that?
Does that sound familiar?
Yeah, that sounds familiar.
I can't.
Voyage to the Crystal Grotto.
Do you remember, did you voyage to the Crystal Grotto?
Did I voyage to the Crystal Grotto?
Like I'm sure I did.
It seems like a very like slight ride, but like very pleasant and that kind of like uses
castle environment in a way you don't always see.
It seems like a kind of like updated storybook land and like here's just like pastoral grounds
and gentle.
Okay.
That's the thing.
I did, we, I did so much that like so much stuff blends together.
So I did do that and it, and it kind of lets you off in like a Alice in Wonderland or near
Alice in Wonderland type like land or area or something like that.
Okay.
Um, but it's right around a castle and this really is really cute.
You see like what I'm looking at now, there's like Beers Beauty and the Beast, right?
Like they'd dance for a second and then like Aladdin and then Genie on a carpet and, and
it's all fountains and just looks nice.
That's of all the ride throughs I've watched.
This one seems like it'd be kind of a quiet leave.
It was very much like storybook canal or whatever they call it here.
Storybook land or whatever, the bold ride, but just, you know, better.
They got more money for their stuff there, which is, you know, so a lot of the things
are much better.
Yeah.
As far as like just the experience of the ride or how much money they have.
The castle is the castle, the biggest castle, right?
Or did the new Hong Kong, did that make it bigger when they just, they expanded the castle
in Hong Kong and made it bigger.
But this is the biggest.
This is the one where the castle is like, if you look at it and if you like divide it
into fifths, it's kind of like, they all nod to the different castles.
Are you talking about the one in Shanghai?
Yeah.
So that sliver of it is kind of a nod to Cinderella Castle and this part is Sleeping
Beauty.
Or is that the Shanghai one?
Or is that Hong Kong?
No, that's Hong Kong.
I think that's Hong Kong.
Now I'm looking to see like what the...
So the castle at, the castle at Shanghai is pretty basic.
I think the castle at Disney, Tokyo Disneyland was probably more impressive to me, I think.
I think, if I'm remembering.
This is, it is the Shanghai is the biggest one.
The Shanghai is the biggest one?
Okay.
So maybe that's the one.
Maybe that's the one I'm thinking of.
They also have a, on the attraction list, on the English language website, there is
in Disney town one attraction just labeled Giant Donald Duck.
Yep.
Wow.
There's a big, by the lake, there is a big inflatable Donald Duck, which is also funny
imagining like bull horns next to big Donald Duck.
And it was.
There's bull horns next to it.
Oh yeah.
That's just like pavement.
That's really not dressed or...
No, it's just in the middle of the water and you just walk up to it and it's cool, it's
very big.
I know, I'm a big fan of that.
Does it feel fair to call it an attraction or does that feel like overseeing it?
No.
No, it's a photo spot.
It's just listed under.
It's definitely a photo spot, but you know, because like I said, we, the second day we
left midday and before we went out and it was so peaceful, we went to go sit by the
water and sit right in front of it because we was like, we didn't get this experience
last night.
Let's just have a peaceful last 10 minutes as we say goodbye to get the hell out of here.
This is crazy.
Wow.
Do you remember anything else about Disney town?
Disney town was pretty basic.
I didn't go to that much.
It was just a few restaurants.
Nothing is as impressive as Disney Springs.
Did you have any, did you stop anywhere, let me switch to Universal Osaka because you're
probably one of the only people who's at least walked through City Walk Japan.
Did you do anything?
Did you notice anything?
Is there anything to, would it be?
I guess what I'm asking is would City Walk Japan have the fuel for a 19 parts or more
daily series that a podcast like this might do?
Probably not.
Okay.
I would say it's probably a mix between, it's probably a mix between Hollywood and Orlando.
So like the one in Orlando is huge and the one here is very cool, but it's a lot smaller
and the one there is probably a mix between the two.
So it's not as big, but it's bigger than the one here.
Okay.
I like that.
That's good.
So it's definitely more space, but it has a vibe to the one here as opposed to the one
in Orlando.
Scott, what if I were to tell you City Walk Osaka, because I looked this up last night
to compare it to Disney town, City Walk Osaka has a TGI Fridays and a Red Lobster.
They do.
All right.
They're going to get factory stores so you can get some great deals.
Well, City Walk Japan Saga next year then, I guess.
There you go.
Why next year?
Why not in a couple of months?
I mean, listen, there's still six months left in this year, you know?
That's true.
A lot to go.
I think we've all got another saga in us, right?
It only takes 13 hours to get over there, you know?
You can find that time in six months.
Jason, you ready?
Let's go to Japan.
Yeah.
You would definitely have some good times.
You can get like a five-part saga.
At least a five.
Okay, okay.
Well, five in your numbers equals what, 25 to us?
Okay.
Sure.
That's about it.
Yeah.
25.
Great, great.
Osaka, Japan was cool though.
Osaka, Japan.
Universal Osaka was cool.
I had a good time there.
I was only there for one day.
It was really chill.
It was the Nintendo World.
I mean, I really want to like Nintendo World.
I will say this.
I'm not a huge Nintendo.
I was always a Sega Genesis fan.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Nintendo, I played a lot as I've grown up.
So I don't have as much, so I will say this.
I don't have as much nostalgia for Nintendo as somebody who would.
I hate to tell you this, I don't think that's helping anything.
It doesn't.
I think why I was more of a Nintendo kid doesn't mean I don't find this one not super crowded
and irritating.
It's so, and so like I went to the one in Universal Japan because like the one here
to me is just bad.
It's so, it's too small, it's too crowded, and there's nothing to do for how crowded
it gets.
There's just nothing to do in there.
So I was like, all right, maybe the one in Japan will be bigger, which it is.
It's two stories.
You know, they have two levels, still just as crowded though, and still really nothing
to do.
Like they got the one ride where like we got, because we went during Golden Week, so it
was very busy in Japan when we went.
Oh, right, right.
And so we got express tickets.
Okay.
And so we were able to get express into the Mario Kart and whatever the Ouija ride or
whatever it was.
So we did the Ouija ride or whatever.
The Yoshi ride?
The Yoshi ride, yes.
And see, that's how much I'm not a Disney or a Nintendo.
The Yoshi ride and like, we were like, all right, this looks cool, it looks cute.
And we went on it and I was like, I would rather stand in line for an hour and a half
to go on that like 30 second Harry Potter ride.
That like the flight of the hitter, yeah, which is the most annoying thing to stand
in line for.
You just can't, if there's any line, it's too much line.
And I would rather stand in line for that than go on this Yoshi ride.
It was...
Wow, really?
Wow.
It was, it moves three miles an hour and there's nothing to do.
Like you press, you're supposed to press buttons and you're pressing it and nothing
is happening.
I'm like, this is, and by the end we were like, oh, okay, maybe the ride is about to
pick up now.
And it was like, oh no, it's time to get off.
Oh man.
See, we're looking at it like the key mistake was not doing the Yoshi ride, which seems
so charming and brings so much life to the, and you're telling us like, no, the Yoshi
ride is not...
It was bad.
Again, you know, maybe I don't have the nostalgia, the nostalgia for Mario world, but I really
wanted...
I like Yoshi, but I can look at a picture of Yoshi.
You can look at a picture.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do I want to wait in that line?
And you might see, that's the part.
If it was a 33 second line to get on a ride, by all means, but like that line, we did express,
so we got right on, but that line was up to like two hours.
And I was like, if I would have waited two hours to ride this, I would be an international
news story because I would have flipped my fucking lid, like I would have been so mad.
Man melts down, caught on 100 cell phones, fake Yoshi eggs smashed, American diplomats
sent to embassy to retrieve American man riding diplomatic relations.
An American started hopping on tourists' heads as if he is Mario.
Real life Mario incident.
Did you go to universal Beijing or just Shanghai?
There's a universal Beijing?
Okay, so now...
This is where we're going to start.
Oh shit, so I have not been to every universal.
You do have more universals to go, I think.
Damn.
Okay.
Is there also Singapore?
Singapore?
Yes.
Do you have any universals, is it?
More coming.
Sorry.
There's going to be assignments.
Right.
You're going to have, with your foreign correspond duties now on our show, I think you're going
to have to go back and report.
My plan is to go to Disney, Hong Kong in the next two-ish years.
Okay.
Which one of those is closest to Beijing, I think?
Beijing, I think, is probably the closest to that.
I'll throw that in.
I forget what's special about it.
That's the one that we've discovered has an entire, even though it was built in the last
couple of years, they have a new Waterworld land, not just the show, it's an entire land
that is Waterworld.
That's fun.
The relevant film in 2024.
Listen, I love Waterworld.
They have Waterworld in Osaka.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I got to be a part of it a little bit.
Oh really?
Whoa.
Because I was the only black person there.
So I stood out, and I had on a little Dragon Ball Z shirt, and they were just loving me.
They was like, yeah, come here.
They brought me up to pour water in one of the people's faces, and then my little stick
didn't have water in it, and then they just doused me with water.
Oh, classic bit.
Really?
The classic bit.
Wow.
So that was fun, and after we were leaving, people was like, yeah!
So that was super fun.
Wow.
I love the Waterworld show, and my girlfriend had never seen the one here, so that was her
first one.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
Which was very funny, too, because the dude who plays the main hero, I think, didn't know
any Japanese, so he literally was mute the entire time, and I was trying to remember,
he talks in the show here, right?
Yeah.
Mute.
Didn't say a single word.
Wow.
Not a single word.
That's one way to play after what he's seen.
After what he's seen.
Yeah.
Waterworlds.
Yeah, yeah.
After the piss he's drunk.
Yeah, the Mariner does drink piss at one point in the movie.
So funny.
I don't think I've ever seen the movie, and I don't think I have to.
I've seen the show.
The show is more of the thing now.
That's really the main thing you've got to see.
Potentially the plan in Shanghai with those guests, by the way, possibly, you need a little
refresher later.
You need a refresher.
You got your piss bag.
Maybe that's why they do it.
Classic bag, yeah.
The drinks are expensive there.
They've got those straws now, like life straws, where if you're stranded or something, you
could potentially, I think, drink pee with the straw, and it'll filter out the bad stuff.
Life straws.
Really?
I don't know that the life straw says you should drink pee.
I think it's more for just like if you're in the middle of somewhere and you had to
drink water, you're not sure if it's filtered or not.
But I bet it might work on pee.
Okay, I'm sure it would.
But you could just try using a light.
You have life straws?
Yeah.
That was my next question.
Have you purchased life straws?
I have a few, sure.
I think you have an assignment.
To pee in the ...
Well, I could just ...
The Mariner Challenge.
Should I just put the straw in the toilet?
I just put the straw in the toilet after I go.
Don't be disgusting.
Yeah.
Have some decorum.
Use a coffee mug or something.
It's hard to pee in a coffee mug though.
Have some American decorum.
Yeah.
Okay.
Pee in a mug and drink that.
I think if you could do it ... All right.
So we are going to make you drink piss for the show, but if we have you do it in a Trader
Sam's Tiki mug that looks like a robot or something and you can line the room with sugar,
we will let you prepare the best glass possible out of which to drink your own pee, which
I think it might make you enjoy the experience, right?
It might.
If there was a sugar rim.
Yeah.
And it's a fun character.
Wow.
So I have the Hat Box Goes Tiki Mug from Trader Sam's and I'll just put sugar on his rim.
On his hat rim.
On his hat.
Not his ...
I'm not rimming the Hat Box Goes asshole.
Here's a tip.
Put sugar on a rim for a delightful experience.
His hat rim, folks.
And then I'll pee in it.
Okay.
And drink it.
Wait, is it the word brim?
Is that the ... Is that a hat?
It is.
That is a part of a hat.
It's not a rim.
It's a brim.
Well, the brim is here.
You're pointing to your eye, but you're pointing ... Oh, but you would have to drink it out
of the top so that it would be a rim.
Yeah, it would have to be at the top.
More of the rim of his hat.
Got it.
All right.
Never mind.
Okay.
Little top of hat.
Can you ... Do you think the LifeStraw ... Can you put a silly straw on top of a LifeStraw?
Or does LifeStraw make a silly version of their straw?
That's the way it is.
Why not have fun in a survival situation?
Why not have fun?
Let me Google to see if they have that.
Why not make the water take longer to get to you?
Or filter it.
While filtering.
Yeah.
It's got a long way to go.
Well, let's you psych yourself up.
I'm drinking straight out of a sewer, or I'm drinking my own piss.
Why not just ... Let me adjust to this while I watch it, go like, oh, it's lightening up.
All right.
I have Googled, can you drink pee with LifeStraw?
And it says they don't recommend drinking urine with any LifeStraw product.
It's not going to make it not pee.
But they didn't say no.
Yeah.
Didn't say ... They just don't suggest it.
This ... Okay, wait.
There's an editorial that says a LifeStraw does not make urine remotely safe to drink.
But that's like, they have to say ... Remember how they used to have to say bongs are for
tobacco?
They had to pretend and play the game.
They know the people ... If you're buying a LifeStraw, you're doing it because you want
to drink piss.
Yeah.
They got to save themselves.
Quote, unquote, caution.
Don't drink your own piss.
Oh, Rhett and Link actually did this, apparently, on YouTube.
They drunk pee?
Five years ago.
Wow.
Was Jordan Morton here?
Did you hear that one?
It's possible.
Did Jordan have to drink his own pee?
Maybe.
We should ask him.
Wow.
They're still kicking.
They still got a show.
I guess so.
Well, with innovations, like drinking piss out of LifeStraws.
They need to make a more of a piss-based LifeStraw that will actually help filter it.
Look, Costner's out there.
Costner's never been more around.
This is a great thing to put his name on.
He is.
Make a little extra stretch.
He's directing stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
He could close out the dream of owning literally all of Montana.
Yeah.
I'm sure there's a couple acres he doesn't have yet.
You get that LifeStraw money.
He sunk all that money into these movies, so I wonder if he's going to be hurting.
That's how these happen?
He's not making any of it back.
This is a Megalopolis situation?
I believe so.
Yeah, I believe he hundreds of millions of dollars.
This movie has to make, which it's doing okay, right?
Disappointing now, but it's going to like ...
Megalopolis?
That's not Costner.
Oh, it's Francis Ford Cobalt.
No, no, no.
It's the same city.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gotcha, gotcha.
I was like, Costner doing that?
Selling his winery.
Yeah, yeah.
He's doing a Megalopolis 2.
He's also doing a Megalopolis.
Same titles.
Yeah, yeah.
What is the Costner one called?
Horizon.
It's a place.
Part chapter one and two.
Okay.
Well, there could be a Megalopolis on the horizon.
Chapter three could be ... Horizon chapter three Megalopolis and the franchises merge.
I have not seen that movie, but somebody on Twitter said something along the lines of
that there's a sex scene in this Kevin Costner movie that could fit into an early 90s Steven
Seagal movie.
Oh, cool.
I was like, whoa, really?
What a wild specific.
Yeah, yeah.
We have to see this.
He's the sexiest man.
Yeah.
And we all want to see simulated thrust.
70-year-old Costner.
I assume it's Costner.
I don't know who else is in the movie.
Oh, good point.
I assume it is, too.
Yeah.
I mean, if I direct it, I would put myself in the sex scene.
I wouldn't let anybody else have that.
Right.
You might as well.
That's a part of you get ... Yeah.
The Tommy Wiseau rule.
The room rule.
Put yourself in ...
You don't think he's giving it to a co-star of Horizon, Michael Rooker, because they got
Rooker in there.
That's a way.
That's an interesting weathered man.
Yeah, he could be.
That's a cool sex scene.
Yeah.
It's got a crazy beard in it.
We don't know if it's not the two of them, although I have my guesses.
It might be.
Yeah, I don't know.
No, I haven't seen Horizon.
Isn't Rooker's butt in Mallrats?
Don't you see him naked?
Rooker's butt is ... Yeah, he is partially naked in Mallrats.
So?
Man.
He's already done it.
He's comfortable.
So, 30 years ago ...
Yes.
He was naked.
He's held it up.
The butt only gets better with age.
That's right.
Yeah.
Just know what they always say.
Yeah, that's right.
Crack, don't crack.
Crack, stay the same.
I'm not finding any results for Michael Rooker's butt, but maybe I've got a safe search on
that I don't know about.
That could be possible.
Isn't there somebody whose butt is in Mallrats, and I thought it was his?
I haven't seen Mallrats in ...
30 years?
Probably 20-plus years.
Yeah.
I'm sure it also similarly hasn't aged a bit.
The Jaws Squad ride is preserved in Mallrats.
I think that's ... Is that the Jaws in Florida?
No, I think it's California.
I think it's Studio Tour.
It's California.
Okay.
Yeah, I believe so, but don't quote me on that.
Oh, did you do the Jaws ride at Universal?
I did.
It was the first ride I did.
Great.
Wow.
Yeah.
That would be my first.
Wow, what a nostalgia blast.
That's great.
Yeah.
It was fun.
It was cool.
Definitely, there's a Baskin Robbins right next to that with no flavors that I was used
to besides vanilla.
Tuna and waffle.
Yeah, tuna waffle.
Tuna waffle.
Tuna waffle flavor.
A fish.
Yeah, that was the first ride we did, was the Jaws ride in Osaka.
That's the way to do it.
Yeah, it was cool.
All the nostalgia ones are sort of ... They had no more T2 now and no more Backdraft now?
No.
Okay.
Because that was what was luring me.
I was on my way to Kyoto and like, what if we dropped off our bags, bought one more bullet
train ticket, kept going, just hit up a real quick, but then Kyoto as you went to ... Kyoto
is such a lovely place.
Kyoto is my favorite spot.
I was so at peace there.
Tokyo was great.
Osaka, I'm happy I was only there for like three, four days.
It was really close.
But Kyoto, I was there for like seven, eight days and I was like, I couldn't come back
here.
Geez, really.
I mean, me too.
I'm really jealous.
I wish I'd done so much more.
I mean, we did a couple day trips and overnights from Kyoto, so we weren't there the full time.
That was like a base.
Okay, yeah.
We were there for like four full days at last.
Wow.
It was beautiful.
I'm so jealous of that.
Geez.
What a mega travel.
Saw some geishas.
Oh, wow.
Which was really cool.
Yeah, man.
Kyoto was great.
I really loved Kyoto.
Man, man.
Anything else you want to shout out that's not like a main theme party?
Was there anything else like, not that it has to be like a silly, kitschy thing, but
I'm sure there's, I mean, there's plenty of that in Japan.
There was a lot, man.
I really loved Akihabara.
I think that's how you say it.
What is that?
It's like the electric city, they call it, it was in Japan, but it was very much like
just a bunch of like lights and screens and like just, it just felt like a video game
world.
Sure, sure.
Like jumping into a video game world or an electronic world, which was really cool.
And that night is beautiful because it's all lit up and stuff like that.
Oh, okay.
There was like multiple, like seven story, like arcades.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which was like really cool.
I didn't make it here.
Yeah, this is nuts.
Did you go in any of the like video game stores, like the, cause I went in those stores like
where you could buy old video game consoles and stuff.
Yeah.
And that blew my mind.
I went to, yeah, we did walk in a couple.
I didn't buy anything, but like just to like see what it was like.
So that was, that was really, really dope.
I'm like, cause they, like stuff that didn't come out here and different covers for games
that you had when you were a little kid.
Yeah.
I didn't come back with anything either.
And I like kind of regret it.
I don't.
Yeah.
I kind of the same.
Like I was like, Oh, I could have bought something, but I would have bought it.
I would have bought it and it would have just collected dust, which is fine.
Like that's cool.
But like, but like the Nintendo, they released a heart, like a different drive for the Nintendo
64.
Really?
64 DD or whatever it was called.
And it would put it, you would put it on top of it and it was like, like hard disks you
would put in, not even cartridges.
And they only released it in Japan and never came out here and I was obsessed with it and
they had it.
I could have bought it.
Yeah.
But yeah, I'm not going to be playing it a lot.
I remember like when I had my PlayStation and PS2 and stuff like that, like, um, there
were a couple, I think it was my PlayStation or Xbox, one of them, I can't remember, uh,
that I sent to Japan to get modded.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And like, you know, so I could play bootleg games and stuff like that.
Um, but yeah, I had forgot about that until a little bit.
Literally this moment.
Uh, so yeah, like I bet they have a bunch of stuff over there that never released here.
That would have been cool.
I can't wait to go back.
I will say one of the more fun things I did to, that's not like ride or video again.
I did go to like a, a new Japan pro wrestling show.
Yeah.
Great.
Was it at Corgan hall?
Yes.
Yeah.
Corgan hall.
It's like going back in time.
Yeah.
It was truly like, Oh, this is most, this must be what it feels like when like wrestling
was in like territories.
Yeah.
And then like the popcorn and the beer are both like stale there.
But like that's kind of part of it.
I had a cold pork sandwich.
Yeah.
We had standing room, we saw a show too there and we saw it was standing room in the back.
We got, but.
It was dope.
I, it was, it was really cool, man.
I enjoyed it.
What was the main event?
Can I ask?
Um, the main event.
Do you remember?
I can't remember, but it was a couple of people.
It was one person who's now in a WWE, um, a part of the bloodline, if anybody watches
WWE.
Uh, so that was cool.
I can't remember any of their names, but, um, the crowd was like destiny, Tamatanga
and Tonga Loa.
Yeah.
Uh, it was, uh, the crowd was into it, man.
Like the crowd got into it.
The, the Jeff, Jeff, I will say this about Japan is just so polite, just so polite to
the point where it's like, are you guys bored?
Um, cause it was kind of like, but you can get them hot.
Even at Disney, like they're like, if like never had a friend like me came on here, like
everybody would be, but they were just like, I think part of it was like, it's not in English,
even though like, I don't know, but like, there's no, the generalization at some point
in time, maybe this isn't true anymore, but the concerts would, I'd hear about like American
going to Japan and then finishing a song and like nothing happening.
They're like, what's up with this?
Well, no, they're just waiting for it to be fully done.
They are just taking it in.
They're taking it in.
Yeah.
Really respectful of them.
Cause it's not, they're not, there's not like a boredom thing, but I do think it's just
like a very respectful, like, cause like there was like a, at the New Japan show, there was
like a, one of the matches that started with almost a four minute grappling, like it was
truly one of the most boring things I've ever watched in my life.
And like the crowd was dead silent for the entire four minutes.
And then when they finally started, I was like, yeah, I get it.
This is boring.
And then when they finally stopped everybody in the crowd, start clapping, it was so funny.
It was like, even, even if they were bored, they still respected what they did.
It's enough to like show appreciation, which I thought was really cool.
I thought that was really cool.
Did you, cause Crookin Hall is right by Tokyo Dome and Tokyo Dome city.
Did you do any of the rides at Tokyo Dome city?
I didn't.
Cause it was, it was, we were going to Disney, we were going to Tokyo Disney the next day
and like the show ended at like nine or 10 o'clock or something.
So we were like, we gotta go home.
But it was dope.
I didn't expect to see Tokyo Dome.
I didn't know it was right next to it.
So it was really cool.
It's like his own little city.
Yeah.
Around there.
With a Bubba Gump.
With a TJ Fridays.
With a Shake Shack.
With a Taco Bell that I ate at.
I was very excited about it.
Cause you could change the heat level of your meal.
Oh, the taco of the meal.
Yeah.
So you could pick like whatever a number seven with the two Chalupas, but then you could say
I want it medium spice.
That's awesome.
Wow.
Yeah.
All right.
I gotta go back.
And I don't remember what it was.
Can I ask this?
Because I don't eat, I eat McDonald's breakfast, but I don't, I haven't had McDonald's like
lunch menu burger since 2012 until Tokyo.
Because everybody was like, Oh man, the international McDonald's blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I was like, I guess I got to have a burger.
And I ate it and I was like, yeah, that was still bad.
Still bad.
You're going to offend some people in this room by suggesting that McDonald's might be
anything less than top tier.
It was like, yeah, like this tastes exactly how I remember.
Are the like Taco Bells, are they like a little bit, are they better?
Are they?
I would say all the fast food is better.
Yeah.
But we're still in the zone.
You're still in the zone.
So it's going to have the similar taste.
It's going to be the similar taste.
Okay.
Zone being the best zone, the highest quality of zone there could ever be.
Fantastic stuff that I love.
Okay.
And that I eat a lot.
Did you go to convenience store, the 7-Eleven is supposed to be very good.
Oh yeah, the 7-Eleven Family Marts.
That stuff's true.
Yeah.
Any 7-Eleven random snack.
I got some great spaghetti.
I wanted the convenience store.
Oh wow.
It was like delicious.
It was late at night.
I was hungry.
I was on my way back to my hotel and I was like, this, and my girlfriend's vegan, so
she wanted something.
She got us both something.
And I was like, this is delicious.
This is good spaghetti.
Those are the little things in Japan where you're like, why, if we all just decided together
as a society to make, why do we all decide that this area has to be like bad and shitty
food-wise, cleanliness-wise, like they all just, they all just together collectively
said 7-Elevens will be great.
I went to a bathroom.
I had, I had, you know, I'm a bidet king.
I love a bidet.
I have a bidet on every toilet in my apartment and like, I, you know, so some of the, I had
some of the best experiences of my life, like in the public bathrooms in Japan.
Yeah.
I was like, this makes me want to cry how great this is.
And I also had one of the worst experiences.
Seats, lights, music, all the like these little things.
Just, just heated toilet seats, nice little lights.
There was a spray that you press the button and it sprays the toilet so you can disinfect
it on like a couple of the public bathrooms I went to.
I was like, this is nice.
Beautiful.
I remember, I remember it in my hotel room.
I remember a toilet in DisneySea that was wonderful.
I remember a toilet in the Hello Kitty Sanrio Puroland or just, there was just like a full-on
like lights and music show.
Yeah.
There is a like delightful little thing that you only can do in the bathroom, right?
Where, there's nowhere else on earth I have bathroom memories.
The bathrooms at Disney like play like things so you can have privacy.
They have like, where if you're taking a monster shit, nobody will hear you take a shit.
It'll just sound like, oh, like it's just like noises, just like masks.
It's like Thumper from Thumper's dialogue from Bambi.
Did you encounter any of the toilets in the floor when you were traveling?
That was the worst experience I've had.
The worst toilet experience I've ever had was also Tokyo.
I went to, we were going to the garden, the lab, something where it was like installments
in a park, like lights and shit like that.
I can't remember exactly what it was called.
And on the way there, like once we got off the train, we had like a little 10-minute
walk to get to it.
And on the way there, your boy's stomach started hurting and I was like, I gots to go.
And like it was, it was a bad, it was a bad one too.
And like, I'm like finding a bathroom, I find a bathroom and I'm like, you know what,
like all I got to do is reach a bathroom, I'll get a bidet, I'll sit on a nice seat.
I'll like, you know, go to work and like I'll come out and I'll be feeling refreshed.
Take a good 20 minutes in there as much time as you need.
And I opened the door and there's a fucking hole in the ground.
And like, and it was one, and it was one of those shits where I had to take off all my clothes.
And like, and like, I am squatting, I don't squat, and I'm like squatting.
And it was just, and like, I like, I think I teared up a couple of times because I was
just like, this is the worst.
Like I walked out to my, I walked out to my girlfriend and just like, was like, can you give me a hug?
And, and the goddamn sink didn't have no soap.
So like, I couldn't even, so like, so I was just like, this was the worst 20 minutes of my life.
Was there, let me ask, because I learned about this from the YouTube channel Ordinary Adventures.
Yeah.
Who, they, they traveled through Asia and they were like, also some of the bathrooms don't have toilet paper.
You have to bring your own.
Thank the Lord that was not the case.
Okay.
But I did have to like, like open up the new toilet roll.
It was almost out and like, but luckily it was there, but like, it was no bidet.
It was, it was just a hole in the ground with not even like shit that I could hold on to.
So I'm like, and it's nighttime.
So I've been walking all day.
I'm like squatting and it was, it was the worst.
And then no soap.
And then to make it worse, like I found out that if I just want to went around like the building
corner, there was a Western bathroom that I couldn't, it sat on the toilet.
And, but like, you know, at this point, several steps make a big difference.
You probably didn't have that in you.
Yeah, I did not move.
I like, but you know how your brains work.
By the time my brain saw a bathroom door, it was like, it's coming in a hole in the ground.
If I have to, Oh, that is what I'm doing.
We'll be doing that.
That is exactly correct.
Who can I ask how big the hole is?
It is, it is, it is not circular.
At least the one I use wasn't circular.
It was more like oblong shaped.
Like, cause it's, is it like hard to get it in there?
It wasn't easy to get it in.
It wasn't golf or putting this is very precise.
I know people are listening.
It was like, this is the worst conversation, but like, I will say, like, I will say this.
If it was a normal bathroom experience, it would have been fine.
A bathroom experience where like is messy.
Because it was not, it wasn't booty shaped.
It wasn't, it wasn't booty shaped.
I see.
It just seems hard.
It seems hard for a number of reasons.
And you know, you, you know, when we were growing up, you know, we got to,
we had to learn how to, you know, you know, aim for the Cheerios, whatever.
Nobody teaches you how to aim your shit.
So it was not possible, right?
You don't even think you have.
Yes. You don't have to.
It's general enough that I will never have to worry.
I would never have to worry about this.
And then my, my girlfriend who is a Southeast Asian or South Southeast, South Asian was like,
yeah, you're going to have a terrible time in India.
She was like, cause she was like, yeah, this is, this is normal.
Like she was like, yeah, that happens.
And my American ass was like, what the fuck is this?
Wow.
Can I run you through the thought experiment of if,
as suggested, there had been no toilet paper.
Oh my God.
Do you think what, what might you have knowing what was, had been in that room?
I'm going to run you through a survival scenario.
Man, if there was no toilet, I would have,
I would have, I would have had to go home immediately afterwards.
Yeah.
And maybe close.
Whatever happens to the clothes.
Yeah, I kind of, I guess so.
Cause it was, but there was people all out in there.
So I would have had to walk.
I would have, yeah, here's the thing.
This has happened to me before.
Oh no.
Where I was on a hike and like, you know, nature called and I didn't have no toilet paper.
And, you know, you use, you use your underwear.
That layer goes.
That layer, that's the first layer.
You start using underclothes.
If you have anything extra on socks.
Oh, socks.
Yeah.
Then you just barefoot.
If you've got some gloves on, if you're wearing hiking gloves.
You use it, anything extra.
And then sleeves, you just rip sleeves off.
This is a sleeveless shirt now.
And if I would have had to, I would have, I would have, I would have just called an Uber
and just knew that this is going to be a story for this Uber driver.
It was like, I had a person get in my car who smelled like shit.
But I would have went directly home.
He said, he said, take me to the closest combini so I can buy rubbing alcohol.
I think you stumped me and Mike yet again.
That's a slang term for Japanese convenience stores.
Oh, okay.
How'd you know that?
I heard that.
Convenience.
Yeah.
I figured that's what you meant.
I didn't know.
Yeah.
Geez, good work.
And you've not even been there.
Man, it was a, it was, it was a terrible experience.
So yeah, but still I had the decorum to do it in the toilet and not on the side of the road.
That was good.
So you can rank yourself higher than certain six-year-olds at Shanghai Disney.
That's something to be proud of.
Dodging another international incident.
Taking your clothes off to use the floor toilet.
And you got away scot-free, did not have to call the embassy.
Yeah, those 15, 20 minutes after that experience were some of the lowest.
I felt bad.
Body trauma you've been through.
Oh my God.
Like I felt bad.
I was like, yeah, this is terrible.
Is there a culprit?
Can you name like what, do you have a, do you have a sense of what the food?
It wasn't McDonald's, was it?
It wasn't.
Wait a minute.
And I mean, I think this is Tokyo we're talking about, but this, this would really
confirm a lot of my feelings if this had been City Walk Osaka.
We know there's something in the air.
There's something in the air.
We all had a lot of gastrointestinal issues when we were dealing with City Walk.
All the City Walks.
I think it's the thing that binds all of the City Walks together, no matter where they are.
You're going to have some stomach issues.
You're going to have the bubbles.
I can't remember what I ate.
I can't remember what I ate before.
And we had like very pressed time.
Like it was like, you have to be here at nine and we got, and it was a 10 minute walk.
And we got off the train at like 8 49.
So like, we were like, kind of like we weren't running, but we were briskly walking.
Yeah.
And like, and I, and like sometimes if I play sports, like after the game, I'll be like, all
right, time to go to the bathroom.
Like just jostle or running.
Like the runners tell you, like sometimes like after you run, like your stomach is like,
all right, you've jostled us enough.
Like, let's, let's get this over with.
This is news to the three of us.
I'm saying I know hypothetically what he's saying.
Hypothetically.
And I, I, and like, so because we were briskly walking, I think my stomach was like, oh,
you're moving.
And like, eventually I had to tell that like, we need to slow down.
Yeah.
Right now.
Yes.
And so like, but again, like my brain was still telling me like, this is like, calm yourself
down, you know, like every adult, like we have IBS or something like that.
So like, you learn, calm yourself down, you know, cause like I've learned this.
Like when you, when that's happening, your body goes into fight or flight.
Yeah.
And so that's what makes it really like, I need to go now.
So it's just like, I was talking to myself.
I'm like, you're good.
You've got to go get a bidet.
You've got to go like, and then that has, so it was just like a, it was crazy.
Wow.
At least you're generally in the land of, I'm sure, I'm sure a bidet at some point helped
rectify.
Oh, I took a shower.
Once I took a full body, get to a park with the art installations.
Like, Hey, do you have a shower?
It's really sour hose.
I don't know the word for hose.
I'm so sorry.
I need some butt water.
Is there any, let's, as we sort of head to the exit here is you've taken us to so many
places.
It's great.
Is there, is there some, is there a more pleasant note to go out on somewhere from
your travels?
Do we miss anything?
Cause you, I mean, boy, you've, you've whisked us on an international tour.
It's been wonderful.
Did you buy any merch?
Did you get any character pictures or any of that stuff?
Yeah, I got a couple.
I did go to, I'm a fan of chef Mickey's, which is at the contemporary at Disney world.
And I was able, they had a chef Mickey's.
I was, I stayed at the ambassador hotel at Tokyo Disney.
Okay.
And recommended good hotel?
Huh?
Was it, was it good?
It was great.
Yeah, it was really great.
It was a really great hotel.
Yeah.
It's not, it's one of the partner hotels.
Okay.
Yeah.
Nope.
That's a lie.
It's one of the main hotels.
But it's not like the fanciest and like, like what's right outside of Disney.
So yeah, yeah, it's right.
Yeah.
It's right along the track.
And shit, what was I?
We're chef Mickey.
Oh, chef Mickey's and I was pleasantly surprised.
I had a chef Mickey's there.
So that was cool.
So I got some character pictures there.
I'm not a huge character picture taker anymore.
Yeah.
Like the first couple of times I went to Disney, I was like, yeah, let's get these.
And now I'm like, all right, I got a couple.
Is there a character you would be like, oh, I do need to get a photo because they're not always out.
There was, they had Scrooge McDuck.
Oh, well that's, yeah.
Which was, yeah.
You don't really see a lot of Scrooge McDuck.
You don't see Scrooge McDuck.
So that was cool.
I didn't get a picture of him because he was like walking away.
But like with him, I mean, I got a picture of him.
So that was cool.
If I would have saw him again, I would have did that for sure.
And who else?
There was like one more and I was like, you rarely see that character like at the parks,
but I can't, it was probably, maybe it was Scrooge McDuck.
Yeah.
We had like really transcendent moments with the Cinderella mice.
That is my wife's favorite thing is those.
I forget their names now, but that was such a dream.
And when we got our Cinderella mice moment in their nice little like plain girls outfits,
she just loves them.
And then which are the Aristocats.
Oh yeah.
I also don't know their name, but like Jacques and whatever.
Like we had so much fun with one of those Aristocats.
Just really did it up and was flirting with her and making me mad.
We had a bunch of business.
You don't see those.
Yeah, you don't see those too often.
Yeah, there was a few.
One thing you mentioned I was curious about.
You said your girlfriend is vegan.
How did she do eating in Tokyo and Shanghai?
Like was it reasonable accommodations or reasonable vegetable dishes or?
Yeah, she actually, so that was her second time in Japan.
She had gone like nine years previous.
And when she went that time, she was like,
I basically only had to eat in like convenience stores.
This time, there is no shortage of vegan restaurants all over Tokyo.
Not so much in Shanghai, but she most, we were in Disney and
when we weren't at Disney, she was at the hotel.
So it was, but in Japan, if you're listening to this and you're vegan,
if you ever go there, download the Happy Cow app.
Okay.
The Happy Cow app is basically an app that lets you know every vegan
restaurant, food stand, like snack you can get no matter where you are.
It's like a Google's map type thing.
So that was tight.
She ate well.
Like she ate, there were some places where we were able to eat together,
which was really cool.
And then, you know, I'm a meat eater.
So in some places where there wasn't much for her to eat,
what we would do is like, I would go to a place.
I would have my like meal.
She would maybe have like an appetizer or something.
And then we would find like a place for her to go.
And then she would have her main meal and I would eat something.
I would have a drink or something like that.
Yeah.
So like we were able to, so that way we wouldn't have to be like, you know,
well, I can't go here because you can't eat here.
We just was like, all right, dinner is going to be an hour and a half today or two hours.
Like we're going to go to two places, which was cool.
So yeah, now at Tokyo Disney, this was my only gripe about Tokyo Disney.
It was, it was so hard to get them to do anything they weren't supposed to.
Oh, right, right, right.
Like it was, it was almost to like, it was almost to a fault where it was like,
we're not allowed to do that.
And like, where it's like, that's very not Disney.
Disney will very much bend over backwards to try to, not always, but like, you know,
and it was simple things.
Like we went to a show and like, there's a whole menu of stuff, some vegan options,
but like the show only gave us two options.
And we're like, well, can we just get this?
It was like, nope, it's not a part of the show.
It was like, but it's actually cheaper than what this costs to like, just like, no,
like, can we substitute bread?
Nope, you can't do that.
It was just, and like, we had one moment where she just wanted no mushrooms and something
and like two managers had to come over.
It was like a 20 minute talk.
The recommendations we got were like, well, how about you order it and he eats it.
And it was like, no, I don't want it either.
So that was the hard, it was, it was very funny.
But that was the hardest part about being there.
It was just like, if it was something that they couldn't do, they would be very nice
about it, but they would not do it.
So like, so it was a little harder for her to eat in the parks.
But they still had some vegan options, but it wasn't as easy,
but everywhere else was super easy, right?
Super easy.
But yeah, that, that the, I was talking to my friend because like I'm a sneaker head
and I was about to buy some custom Jordans, which were only going to be 120.
And I don't know if this is as crazy to anybody else as it is to me, but like I wear a size 11
and I was like, all right, can you give me a size 11?
And they went to the back and they finally came out and they was like,
Hey, I'm so sorry.
We don't have a size 11, but we brought you a size nine.
And I was like, what the, what I can't fit that.
Thank you.
But it was more just like they want to, he was saying, cause he lives there.
He was like, a lot of it was, you know, even if they can't do it,
they don't want the perception to be that they didn't try.
I see.
It was very much like that at Tokyo where it was like,
you know, we'll bring this person over.
We'll bring this person over.
We'll go through the list.
We'll give you all the options.
Right, right, right.
But we can't do what you want.
The effort was made.
Okay.
Let's compromise.
She can pick the mushrooms out.
How about that?
Yeah, that was, that was one option too, where we were like, yeah, but no.
There's a Jordan store in Tokyo, right?
I would be able to stand right around the corner from it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
In Shibuya.
It was really dope.
Yeah.
I really wish I could fit a size nine.
They tried, they tried.
You can build your own size 11 out of mushrooms.
Would that work for you?
Draw his shape.
In the mushrooms.
I would say this, man, if anybody wants to ever, I mean, to end on a happier note with Tokyo,
like, cause you know, for us, we get going, right?
But there are some people, and I'm sure everybody who listens to this gets going too,
but we get, there are going to be some people's like, why don't you go
all the way over there to like go to Disney, right?
We have Disney here is something a regular person might say and has said to me.
Yeah, you get that all the time.
Yeah.
And truly, like, unless you just hate theme parks, like, which is fair.
If you hate theme parks, don't go.
But if you enjoy a day where a theme park is an option, like just take the day.
You don't even have to do both.
Like take a day, go check it out.
It's like truly the best park.
It's one of the best park experiences I've had, like in a very long time, if not ever.
Yeah.
I think it'd be really strange to get for somebody to just not like Disney Sea,
especially to not be impressed by it, find something to like about.
I think food's good.
That I think like there's great.
I don't know.
It just has, it's the full package.
Everything was great.
For sure.
It was Disney Sea was beautiful.
Disney Tokyo, Disneyland Tokyo was also great.
And, you know, there was some similarities between the, all the Disneyland's, right?
You know, it was different enough where I went in Kaki.
I was like, this is Disneyland.
I'm going to know where it is.
And I went in like, all right, let me look at this map real quick.
Sorry, the train doesn't go around the park.
The train's one little thing over here.
Haunted Mansion is in fantasy land.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
It's wild.
So it's really, it's worth it.
It was worth it.
It was the perfect way to end our portion in Tokyo.
Yes.
Yeah.
It was a great end to the trip.
And then you had a much worse end to the trip.
And then I had to work.
Which still was nice too a little bit.
Still was nice.
Look, it's a story.
I have a story forever.
Which made it perfect for us.
And we're so glad you brought all, that brought us all of this.
I really appreciate it.
Jikki Sneel, you survived podcast, The Ride.
What a time.
Boy, oh boy.
So glad you could do it.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
We brought it up at the beginning.
If you're ever in town, Comedian Feud is always a good time.
We're live streaming it now as well.
Maybe come into a town near you at some point.
Always have some.
It's pretty much just Celebrity Family Feud.
That's all it is.
Which I was able to do last year, which was fun.
So-
Really?
They know about the show too.
Oh.
My lawyer was like, don't bring it up.
They brought it up to me.
Oh.
I was like, you want Steve to mention it?
And I was like, no.
Confusing or something.
Yeah.
You were on the show, really?
I was on the show last year.
How'd it go?
We lost.
I was on the Lauren Lapkus's team.
Oh.
Did this air?
I don't remember.
It aired last summer or last fall or something like that.
I can't remember exactly.
Oh, congrats.
It was super fun.
But yeah, come to that Comedian Feud and then on social media,
I post everything else I'm doing that gets announced.
This was a debate on our show a little bit,
or a debate we closed off and answered,
but I think this was on a Club 3 episode about an old Family Feud episode.
Do you have a choice of best Family Feud host for Besides Yourself?
Yes.
That's a good question.
Is it Steve?
I still think Richard Dawson is the best host.
Wow, really?
I still think he is.
The classic host, I think out of-
This is a very good question.
I think Richard Dawson is the best host.
I think one of my favorite hosts was Ray Combs,
but I can understand how people-
But I just thought he was like-
He reminded me of like a Mark Summers.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like genial, nice-
He was the first one I ever saw.
Yeah, it's probably the one I watched in the end.
But out of all the hosts that they've had since Richard Dawson,
Steve Harvey has made it his own the most.
Where they had the Louis Anderson's, the John O'Hurley's,
all the people that's done it.
Karn.
Family Feud will forever be synonymous with Richard Dawson and Steve Harvey.
Those are the two hosts of Family Feud.
And everybody else in between is just everybody else in between.
Well, we sort of landed on we like Harvey the most,
and we all sort of agreed.
And then Mike Scollins wrote us angry.
He was mad about that opinion.
Well, that, yeah.
You're insane, too.
That's not a bad opinion.
Thanks for backing us up.
I felt not strong enough about it to not-
I did not like double down.
Fuck off, Scollins.
I didn't feel that way at all.
He didn't say that either, yeah.
But he certainly felt strongly enough.
He did feel strongly enough.
I think also on the episode rewatching some old Dawson,
which I am, my brain wants to love an old boozed up actor hosting a game show.
And I was disappointed because I was like, this guy's kind of like tired and like-
Yeah, he's drunk.
Actually not as fun.
It's not as fun as I want it to be.
I almost like Gene Rayburn on Match Game Better now.
Gene Rayburn was great.
Because he at least had some energy.
Dawson, I'm like, the kissing and like that's like a funny thing, but it's like kind of gross.
Yeah.
I think Harvey takes it easily.
If you're really just, if they're all on equal footing, you're like,
I think Harvey's the best one of all time.
I think for me, what makes Richard Dawson good is, yes, he was very 70s, right?
Very suave, boozy, all that stuff.
And the suits, the suits are so puffy and crazy.
Yeah.
Most 70s.
But he is like, out of any game show that I've seen,
he is like, oh, this dude created the model for how this show is supposed to be hosted, right?
Yes.
And like, you know, because even Drew Carey changes it up from like, but like everybody's
following that Richard Dawson model of just like how to navigate the families and stuff like that.
He was a boozy one, but he was like a host.
Whereas everybody else kind of feels like they're playing host, except for Ray Combe.
I liked Ray Combe a lot.
But Steve Harvey is just Steve Harvey.
Truly, it is celebrity for you.
So it's 10 celebrities, quote unquote, on stage.
And when Steve walks out, he's the biggest star on that stage, right?
Of course, yeah, right.
He didn't speak to us before.
But wouldn't you be the most fascinated to see?
Yeah.
Wow, like he talked to you.
Steve Harvey talked to you.
I'd be very starstruck.
He smelled great.
Yeah, dude, it was fucking Steve Harvey.
That's great.
If we had to guess, I'm not so sure Richard Dawson would have smelled great.
I'm sure.
He would have smelled like cigarette smells.
Cigarettes probably are.
Some cologne that by our standards today would be disgusting.
Your eyes would just start tearing up smelling cigarettes in the perfume.
Cigarettes and a couple 7-in-7s, you know.
Yeah.
He certainly got booze on his breath.
At least that, yeah, yeah.
100%.
All right.
Well, yeah, check the show out if you're in town.
And as for us, extra plug here, we brought this up on the second gate,
but let's tell the main feed, we are going to be at Comic-Con.
We can't say every detail about this, but we are doing a panel
that is a collaboration with Mattel, actually with Mattel.
Mike, can you say the deal here?
We're going to talk about the Street Sharks.
We're doing the Street Sharks panel, and we can't say much beyond that,
and we can't officially say date or anything,
but just keep your eyes on our social media.
It might be out by the time this airs, but I'm not sure.
Maybe.
It's possible.
But come check it out.
If you're already going to Comic-Con, if you got the badges and everything,
just look out for us and come see us.
It's an official panel during the convention.
Yeah, we aren't just taking over a Taco Bell cantina and talking to potentially no one.
This is a real thing.
It's real.
We are insane.
For three bonus episodes every month, check out Podcast the Ride, the second gate,
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
We talked about Family Feud.
That was a fun one.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Good stuff.
Michael Rooker's butt.
Here it is.
It's that scene where he's like, he's like watching TV
and he's like trying to like pretending he's fighting and his towel falls off
and you see his butt.
Wow.
Okay.
You remember?
I remember.
I was the one who confirmed.
Jason, look at his butt.
In Jason's face.
I wish you could have saw Jason's face.
Look, look it.
And Jason's like, why are you showing this to me?
Are you looking at yours?
It is so close to me.
I broke my phone holding it.
If you need to see it.
If you need to chase that out of your eyes,
Cruise Nostalgia is the channel I mentioned forever ago.
Look at some nice cruise ship images and hey,
Cathy Lee Gifford.
Hey.
You can't complain about that either.
Not bad.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team
and liking our page on Facebook.