FOREVER!
DOG!
The year, 2024.
Disneyland's Tomorrowland is in shambles.
People mover tracks its unused, clogging up an already narrow walkway.
An arcade once vibrant and full of beeps and boops is now a space where you can sometimes get a free button.
Toward the back is an old rotating theater that rotates no longer,
where a man named John once told us about his new oven.
Can this land be salvaged?
Can the future be saved?
We roll up our sleeves and get to work.
Fixing Tomorrowland on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, where today we roll up our sleeves
and do what the Disney Corporation hasn't for over 30 years.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Mike Carlson.
I'm here.
It's the burden we've got.
I feel the weight of what we're doing today.
Yes, and you know, besides the weight of literal shovels and dirt and construction equipment,
there's no real weight, but the mental weight.
The weight in trying to figure out how to fix this problem,
which I'm sure nobody in the building has even attempted.
Never.
Jason, Sharon, and I.
You know, it was a land that we've encountered and talked a lot about.
Like, a lot of essays, a lot of writing videos talk about Tomorrowland,
almost forgotten about, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, and Disneyland first opened.
Like, very underpowered, and it took a long time to add some real meaty attractions.
Oh, that's, yes.
Well, yes.
Well, as we've covered this, you know, slowly, sporadically,
barely over the course of the last two years, the Tomorrowland problem,
we have discovered it is a problem from the root, from the get-go.
They just jammed a bunch of stuff in there because they didn't know what else to do.
Things that were exciting at the time got out of date very fast.
There have been successful redo's, overlays, successful entire other Tomorrowlands
and other parks, but we, of course, are focused on the Disneyland Tomorrowland,
which has pretty much sucked shit since the failed redo in 1998,
the redo that made everything worse.
And it now takes us to this point where we try to figure out how to do it ourselves,
how to fix Tomorrowland, at Disneyland specifically.
Yeah, and we've decided to do it in a unique way.
This was a thing I've concocted a while ago,
and hopefully it turns out that this was the best way to do it,
but we're going to take different approaches.
Each of us has a different assignment.
We've been, we've randomly chosen these assignments on a previous episode,
and basically what the deal is is we're going to try to cover all the different ways
Disneyland could fix Tomorrowland with no budget at all
or barely a budget with sort of a good, healthy budget
and in their normal, synergistic corporate thinking.
And then we're also going to give one of us, or Scott, of course,
is going to get a blue sky, heavy, big budget to do cool stuff.
Who knows what he's concocted? We don't know anything.
We don't know anything. We haven't told each other what we're doing yet.
So each of us are coming at it from a different budget and a different philosophy.
And different, these are very like different thought exercises, I would say.
You know, like there's these varying degrees of realism versus science fiction,
much like Tomorrowland itself.
Yes, so yeah, so when we're all done here,
I mean, I'm not saying we have to combine these three ideas at the end or anything,
but there will be, we can probably get good stuff from all these pitches
and we can really assess in all the different ways
you could possibly assess how to fix Tomorrowland.
We will now have a full picture of it.
And this is, look, will Disney listen
and will they take any of the things we say and apply them?
I don't think so, but we'll see.
Maybe they don't say anything about Tomorrowland at the upcoming D23 conference.
Yes.
And they do learn from us. I don't know.
Well, that's, you know, and we are kind of in the middle of a block of episodes
related to the upcoming, I think tomorrow as of the day this is released,
the D23 Horizons Disney Experiences Showcase.
Yes.
Which rolls off the tongue, which we all have been saying
as naturally as the names of our partners and children.
Yes.
So, you know, here on Horizons Disney Experiences Showcase Eve,
this is an interesting juncture point, I think, to determine, you know,
what if some of the stuff we say gets done?
Then we'll know that they didn't steal it from us
because a day is frankly too much time, too little time to turn that around.
Probably, yeah.
Or will they say nothing at all,
which is something that I literally bet money on
if you didn't hear the episode about betting on D23,
which just happened on the second gate.
I recommend that one.
You can see if you agree with our assessments,
if you think our money place was foolish.
And then once again on Sunday,
we're going to do an early episode for that week on the main feed
where we go through all of the news we actually do get
and see if it is exciting.
Is it as exciting as a blue sky version,
or does it have the hollow ring of a low budget version?
Well, it's going to be very interesting.
We're doing two episodes essentially where we are making predictions
or like casting our hopes and dreams onto the Disney company.
So we're really going to get to see if anything we said comes true.
And that's exciting for me personally.
Yeah.
That's coming. We don't usually have something like this.
This scenario is sort of unique.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, when an event as unique as D23 Horizon's Disney Experience
Showcase comes up, you have to be as unique along with it.
Yes.
It's going to, boy, I hope it blows the rafters,
blows the roof off the Honda Center.
Yeah.
I mean, hopefully they retire Josh Demaro's suit or casual shirt,
casual tie-less shirt.
In the rafters.
In the rafters, yeah, yeah.
Is that a way usually reserved for athletes or for Billy Joel
in Madison Square Garden?
So anyways, yes, as you said, via a randomized order,
we figured out who was going to do low, mid, and big.
Actually, let me also say really quickly that we are recording this
on a day where earlier today I set foot on Disney property
for the first time in a little over six months.
Wow.
I have not been down there nearly at all,
and I ended up down there for a, I mean,
it was a day of fun in Anaheim, not Disneyland,
but that ended up with a delightful father-son lunch
with my four-year-old boy at Trader Sam's.
Wow.
This was, like, he'd never been there before.
This was such a success and such a delight.
Like, not inside, we were out on the patio,
but getting some island vibes just, like,
put me in a good place to ideate here.
It reminded me of how crucial it is
that we pass these places down to the next generation,
that we and Disney and all of us together make it so
that we have a vibrant Disneyland,
and that depends on a vibrant Tomorrowland.
I think so.
And it was very, this was just resonating in my head.
Another thing this reminded me of is how much I like hazy IPAs.
Oh, wow.
Well, one single one.
Wow, you're loose for this episode.
No, no, that was hours ago.
There was a nap in the intervening time.
Oh, wow, Jason, you can appreciate that.
I know, I'm living it up.
Beer, nap, podcasting with the boys on a Sunday.
Wow, what a chilled-out day.
I napped because the heat was making me lightheaded,
so I chugged some ice water.
I think that was probably in there for me, too.
It's been crazy in LA recently.
But anyways, so that said, when we kind of digitally drew straws,
Jason had the assignment of coming up with the lowest budget version.
That's still, it's an interesting thing because that does,
it's still called fixing Tomorrowland.
There still is the burden of like, you have to consider it somehow.
Something has to be fixed despite,
and I don't know how low you mentally put your budget,
and I'm excited to hear.
Oh, jeez, oh, jeez.
Well, I tried my best.
We're going to try.
Somehow I started getting emails that the budget was being,
the imaginary budget was being slashed.
It kept happening.
I think you put yourself through the right mental exercise, absolutely.
Do you want me to get started?
I suppose so, let's do it.
Jason, fix Tomorrowland.
I should just real quick say before,
part of our job will be sort of saying,
okay, what you just proposed maybe that seems like out of budget
or that seems out of character maybe for the Disney.
So we'll be doing a little of sort of judging as we go or toward the end,
and then we'll have a discussion about it.
That's what I was going to say is that I think the role of the others
in the individual presentations I think should be to push it further
in the direction that it's supposed to be in.
If we feel like the low budget broke the rules a little bit,
we can nudge it.
Mike, yours as the realism I think probably needs the most curtailing,
and if mine doesn't use enough imagination,
I need your help with that.
So it'll be sort of, and I think it's up to all of us individually.
Do we want to just monologue for a while?
Do we want feedback from the Peanut Gallery?
It's really up to you.
Yeah, we'll feel it out.
Jason seems stressed.
Oh, jeez.
You do, I know.
I'm trying my best.
All right.
Well, I'm going to go ahead and go start.
Okay.
All right.
Budget Tomorrowland.
Yes, Budget Tomorrowland.
And just fair warning, I'm going low to high.
So if it seems a little not up to your speed, just bear with me, okay?
All right, go ahead.
All right.
First things first, you know all those planters in Tomorrowland?
The ones, where are they located?
They're all around.
They've got like cabbages and they've got different bushes.
The idea in 98 at some point was that it's all edible stuff.
And I don't remember how much they committed to that anyway.
Is it over by Star Tours and stuff?
All around, you're saying.
All around.
Everywhere, okay.
Okay, planners.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, yes.
Good news, those planners are all getting new sod.
Wow.
Okay, great.
Yay.
All right.
The crowd's freaking.
If you're Tomorrow right now, the audience is about to faint.
AG Sod Farms is coming through.
They're giving us a sponsorship.
No money.
Oh, great.
No money, but up to 14 bags of sod.
So that's coming through.
Very good, yes.
Star Tours, unchanged.
That's right.
Wait, no, I'm so sorry.
The Stanchions outside.
You know that really brutal extended queue in the sunlight?
Right, yeah.
That area's getting new ropes on the Stanchions.
Good, good.
Okay, what kind of ropes?
The same nylon, but it's just a little less, you know.
Just new.
Clawed at by like heat-stroked children.
Yeah, kids will wear that down.
That's smart, that's good.
You need that.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay, really good news.
We're turning the Orbitron back on.
The kinetic sculpture that used to go off every few minutes.
Right.
It's coming back.
Is it the Observatron?
Oh, jeez.
We're thinking of Orbiton from E.T. Adventure, the character.
We're always thinking of Orbiton.
Is that his name, Orbiton?
No, look, I'm asking that to myself too because it said in my presentation as well, so I'm
not totally, but the point is...
It's back.
Wow.
It's coming back.
They're flipping the on switch.
Soon you'll be able to stand there and go like, what is that?
Interesting.
And people around you will go, sir, this is the middle of a wall.
Could you keep moving?
Wow.
Please.
It'll confuse new generations.
Yeah.
That's right.
And that will cost a little money.
So just want to keep it in mind.
I'm not saying it's out of bounds, but I think it will cost a little money to turn that back
on.
It needs some work.
Yeah.
And we got to switch out the CD player for like a Pono or something, like an MP3 player.
Neil Young's Pono is what you're saying.
High quality audio.
Right.
It costs $500 per player, I believe.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So that's going to be powering that.
That's the highest ticket item, I think, the whole time.
So far, yeah.
So far.
Okay.
How about this?
Space Mountain.
The giant crosshairs outside of Space Mountain are getting a fresh coat of paint.
Wow.
This is kind of a throwback to Tomorrowland 98 where much of the budget went to paint.
Yes.
Got it.
Still crosshairs.
Yeah.
It's still unsettling crosshairs that you can't get anywhere near and it's taking up a lot
of room.
Some might say it's supposed to be like, oh, this is for a rocket.
That's where a rocket would land.
Got it.
Yeah.
But it does look like crosshairs.
But a rocket has never, nothing interesting has ever happened.
No, the rocket was removed.
So maybe one day it'll come back.
Not for this budget.
Not this.
No, no.
Got it.
Okay.
Very good news.
Star Wars Launch Bay is glowing away forever.
Wow.
It's glowing away.
And that building has a brand new sponsor.
And this is a big one.
Google.
Okay.
The old interventions.
They got a lot of money.
Is now becoming the Chromebook Clubhouse.
You know Chromebooks, the computers that are made so cheaply.
They just give them away to schools.
Well, they're here.
And you'll be able to test out Chromebooks from any number of manufacturers.
But that's not all.
You'll be able to meet new original characters.
The Chrome Critters.
Ooh.
Now this is good.
And this is paid for by Google.
Google's covering it.
So Disney doesn't have to spend any money.
Google.
No more money than Pono.
They are saving.
What's it called?
Pono, yeah.
They're saving our ass.
Okay.
You get to meet Google Chrome characters.
Like we see you're using a different browser.
Google recommends using Chrome.
Switch now.
And your Google Drive is filling up.
Buy more space.
And everyone's favorite character.
Green Text Balloon.
Hey, it's Green Text Balloon.
He's walking around.
He's got arms and legs.
Okay.
Can I ask a couple questions?
Yeah.
How will you meet them?
Are they in animatronic form?
Are they like a mascot type character?
They have a costume.
They walk around.
They're like little bubbles.
They look like the little pop-ups we all love.
Right.
Got it.
And you see all the time if you're using Safari or Firefox on a laptop.
Right, right.
But the other good thing about this carousel building,
if you're looking for a place to warm up on those chilly Southern California evenings.
Of course.
Oh, yeah.
Famously, yes.
Southern California does get a little chilly much of the year.
You've got to bring a light sweater.
You really do.
Especially in winter.
Well, you're going to want to head for Chromebook Clubhouse
because just like using Chrome browser on a laptop,
this building gets very hot.
And that's for accuracy's sake.
Google demanded that.
So that will be, Google will pay for it,
but you're going to have to change the building to make it hot.
There will be some technological upgrades.
It's going to naturally get hot.
All those Chromebooks in there,
and then people are going to be trying the Chromebook browser,
checking their email, presumably.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, okay.
That's going to be hot.
All right, so you've got to think about air conditioning here.
You're going to need a solid system.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so keep going around the horn.
Finding Nemo subs, unchanged.
Autopia, unchanged.
Electric versions on hold for now,
but hopefully getting back on track soon.
Your version put them on hold.
Yeah, your version is not.
It's not me.
I'm doing my best.
This is a blue sky situation.
So the thing they said that was canceled in your world.
Yeah.
I mean, I get, yeah.
I'm just clarifying.
I agree with you.
I'm just, you know,
I'm being loyal to the spirit of Tomorrowland 98.
For better or worse.
But hey, how about something more optimistic?
Let's talk food in Tomorrowland.
Okay?
Okay, great, yes.
Okay.
Tomorrowland Terrace is about to become
the dining destination of Disneyland.
All right?
Get ready for the food of tomorrow.
And by tomorrow, I mean roughly 10 years ago, like 2014.
So we're talking cronuts.
We're talking the Kroy Sparkling Water.
Whoa.
And you better believe we're talking Sriracha mayo.
Wow.
Okay.
That sounds good.
The most Sriracha mayo you can add for a dollar
to your burgers and fries, your dipping cups.
Oh, yeah.
And you might get a lot,
because often if that's an ingredient in something
and it shows up,
it's been squirted out in a very uncareful manner.
Scott, you might get a lot.
You might get like an eyedropper's worth.
Okay?
It's part of the unpredictability.
We don't really know what the future's gonna hold.
You know, the story, and we thought a lot about story.
Yeah.
The story is that the future is untold.
The future is unwritten.
Yeah, that's true.
So it could really be anything.
I'm so glad you focused on story,
because I've been worried about all of our,
that we would all lose sight of that it's all about story.
It is all about story.
And hey, speaking of story,
for all you Easter egg fans out there, keep an eye out.
Can I, real quick,
because I just remember this is something
that really makes me laugh,
is that I was listening to a Tony Baxter interview recently
where he was a little grumpy,
but he was talking about Mark Davis talking about,
he goes,
people keep talking about these rides are stories.
They're not stories.
Really?
That's what he says.
Whoa.
He's like, Mark Davis is just like,
why do they keep saying they're stories?
They're not stories.
Wow.
He's on a ride and you look at,
he really simplified it.
Like you're on a ride,
you look at fun stuff or whatever,
but his whole philosophy was not.
I love that.
I did too.
I thought it was great.
Oh man.
I love that cut through the clutter.
That's funny.
Wow.
Cool.
Maybe it's not a direct quote,
but it seemed,
I'm pretty sure I'm like 90% right.
Sorry, sorry.
But today,
Disney Company is about story.
I thought that was good to interrupt.
I apologize.
It's about story and Easter eggs.
Great, great, great.
So keep an eye out
because you might have a chance to see
Milo from Treasure Planet's silhouette
on one of the ordering windows.
Whoa.
Wow.
Huh?
How about that?
He's got presumably zigzaggy hair.
His hair,
he's got kind of the big,
he's got the middle part
that I always had growing up.
Wow.
And the glasses,
we've got glasses in there.
And by the way,
don't think we've forgotten
about Alien Pizza Planet.
Alien Pizza Planet
is gonna have flatbreads
instead of slices.
Damn, damn.
How about that?
In the future,
that does sound good.
We'll all get to eat
our own little pizza.
Yeah.
We'll all get to eat
our own little pizza.
A flatbread pizza.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, that certainly brings the spirit
of some of the rest of the resort,
which all,
I think every location
at California Adventure
particularly has flatbreads.
Right.
So,
I'm glad Tomorrowland
is finally caught up
to, yeah, again,
to the food of 10 years ago.
Yeah.
Tomorrow is today.
Wow.
Okay.
So,
I'm glad Tomorrowland
is finally caught up
to, yeah, again,
to the food of 10 years ago.
Yeah.
Tomorrow is today.
Wow.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Jason's perspiring.
Yeah, yeah.
You're literally wiping your fit.
You brought a towel.
I don't know why he's out of breath.
Jason's sort of embodied.
When he was writing this up,
he was imagining like an executive
of like breathing down his neck
or something, I think.
It was stressing him out.
He's really lived it.
Yeah.
He's gone method for this.
This was supposed to be
a fun exercise,
but it's really taken a toll on him.
We got word,
even in this imaginary version.
Who's we?
What do you mean,
we got word?
We.
The crew, the gang.
The team, the storytellers,
the dreamers.
A lot of this is dependent
on the success of ESPN bets,
and we're moving somebody around.
This would be great.
If they don't announce anything
at D23 that we like,
if there was just like
a very like tired guy on stage,
I guess tomorrow would have to be them.
If he was just like,
kind of his suit was rumpled
and hair was messy,
and he's like,
look, this is all dependent
on ESPN bets,
and we can't do any of this
if we don't announce anything
at D23.
I mean,
we don't know.
We know,
we know about it.
We know about these bets,
and we can't do any of this
if this betting app
doesn't work out.
Oh, God.
I'm really sorry,
you guys.
Someone made a crazy
multi-parlay bet
on Simone Bile's
Olympic performance
and she killed it.
We owe that person
a lot of money.
Let's.
Oh, go ahead, yeah.
I want to get to the big,
the big, like.
The big stuff.
Great.
Right.
This is kind of where
25% of the budget went, okay?
Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters will be glowing away forever.
Wow, really?
Yes.
You know, but this is where we spent a lot of the budget,
like I said, Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters
is becoming Ant-Man and the Wasp Nano Battle.
Oh, wow.
You know Ant-Man and the Wasp Nano Battle,
the Hong Kong Disneyland attraction that opened in 2019
and none of us ever talk about.
I've never even been curious enough to watch a ride.
Right, right, right.
Now get curious.
Wow.
Because it's coming to Anaheim right at the front
and you're gonna thrill to all the original footage
featuring Paul Rudd himself
and the finest Robert Downey Jr. impersonator
Fiverr has to offer.
This is not a joke.
Look up this ride.
The joke is, yeah.
Oh, they're gonna tell us to look up this guy on Fiverr
who's really good.
Are there impressionists on Fiverr?
That is a good, yeah.
Oh, there's voice people, yeah.
There's definitely voice people,
but oh man, like specifically, like yeah,
do you need a Scarlett Johansson?
Gotcha covered, five bucks.
Don't worry, by the way,
the original manufacturer, Sansei Technologies,
formerly Sansei Yusoki is on board.
Great.
Okay, so we got Sansei.
A surely not nefarious Chinese company.
It's actually a Japanese manufacturing firm.
I double checked that.
Okay, okay, all right, all right, got it.
So you're gonna be able to go on this ride.
Well, see, I don't love that
because I would like more nefariousness, honestly.
Okay, yeah, you would like the nefariousness
of like Arnim Zola, the computer presence
who shows up as the adversary in the ride.
Oh, is that true?
You know Arnim Zola.
Yes, Zola shows up.
I am a big Zola guy.
You and I are both big Zola guys.
Big Zola guys.
No, but I guess I'm gonna learn to be.
Yeah, you guys are.
Arnim Yusoki.
Yeah, Arnim Zola.
And going on this ride, you're gonna get to experience
shades of yellow in gray
that you've never seen or thought of before
because this ride is mostly gray and yellow.
And I do have to say,
this ride was going to be an original story.
Unfortunately, Ant-Man and the Wasp,
Kangalanga Ding Dong has Jonathan Majors all over it.
So it's going straight to the vault.
So we just cloned the great ride from Hong Kong
and it's the same ride as Hong Kong.
The same ride.
Same ride.
Same money, I guess they shot some of it, you're saying.
Yeah, it's mostly in English
and we're gonna try to get the part that's not translated.
Sure, sure.
We're trying.
And so that's my presentation.
We've gone all the way around back to the entrance.
Great.
So that's budget tomorrow, Lance.
So we got some marveling there.
We got a new ride.
We got a new corporate.
Debuting in the United States for the first time.
That's how you dress that up.
For the first time for American visitors.
For the first time.
Can enjoy a nano battle.
We've got a huge sponsor.
We've got a slightly smaller, solid sponsor.
The ropes and paint, we do have to pay out of pocket.
Don't love that.
They got word it was Disney buying it.
So they kind of got us over a barrel.
So that's budget Tomorrowland redo.
Well, you have questions?
Well, I have thought my first thoughts, you know,
and is that this, what all this stuff Jason said
would make Tomorrowland better.
Like the better, like if there was better food
in Tomorrowland, which is one of my biggest gripes
about Tomorrowland is it's just like very boring pizza
and bad hamburgers.
Those are bad food locations.
That's the worst place for food in the park.
Just improving the food would give me a little bit
of a better feeling about going to Tomorrowland.
We thought we were gonna get that back in like 2015
when they're like Star Wars, Seasons of the Force.
I think that was the first one.
And they had Star Wars themed food and it was not it.
It was not it, right.
So what I'm saying is all of the things I think you said
are a net positive for Tomorrowland.
Ultimately.
Wait, when you put it that way, I know.
It's like the beleaguered tone and the apologetic tone
does kind of like belied that you're right.
These are all like achievable improvements that are right.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, the biggest question is if you can,
yeah, they are all a net positive.
The biggest question is if they could actually call that
a fully new Tomorrowland.
Right, does that fix the problem?
I think they would.
But you feel comfortable fully calling that
a new Tomorrowland?
I think so, yeah.
Do you think, how much paint?
Because clearly if we're going 98 style,
at the very least you gotta paint.
Right.
I think so.
I think like one U-Haul cargo,
like however much we fit in there, you know.
Tony's talked about like doing a lot of this himself
and there's gonna be a real hands-on,
everyone on board kind of endeavor.
Don't make him do it again.
They admire him as a painter,
not really pay him because it's like,
well look, you wouldn't, look, the money,
don't you have enough money that we gave you before?
Yeah, right.
I mean, would you have any of that if not for us?
So, get painted.
We might need to borrow some of those Mary Poppins
two lights and props he has in his backyard.
He made a Mary Poppins two backyard.
Yeah, yeah, that was in the paper, I think.
Yeah, that's not, I think he said that in public,
so that's not like.
I think there was a photo spread.
That's not something we know from looking at
his house on Google Maps.
Or through binoculars.
That's not from that.
We didn't do that, by the way, either.
We've not looked at his house.
Did not.
No.
Either of those things.
Nope.
You know what, not, do you get like a,
you know what else would be a good trick is just like,
new, just like the logo,
because logos don't really cost money.
Yeah, logo would be good.
Oh, logo would be great.
That doesn't, you could throw that on
and I think, I think people buy that.
Right.
You just like reveal the name at D23 and that's a lot.
Sure.
You put it at enough places in the land,
you put it on t-shirts and coffee mugs,
and just kind of cement it in people's minds.
You've done like half the work.
What's really funny about everything you said
and in the manner in which you said it,
well it was obviously funny in the way you said it,
but I can imagine the way that Josh Demaro
would say all of that to like thunderous applause.
And then end with like, there's an Ant-Man ride coming
and you'd be like, yeah, okay, Paul Rudd's a funny guy.
Yeah, Paul Rudd's great.
You can see just the way in which you deliver the message.
He's like.
They kind of like, oh, and I did forget one thing.
Then the iconic Ant-Man score plays
that the people in that room know and I don't.
I just hear like.
Like it's not anything to me,
but like I think just that would get a big pop and.
Right.
It's not known enough that Nano Battle
is sort of nothing to write home about.
So like they might not know.
Sure.
And then like if he does,
if he frames it as kind of like,
we have revitalized the plant life all around.
Yes, right.
To build to a sustainable future.
I would say you don't use the word sod public facing.
God, I wish I would have thought of this.
I should have called you guys.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Look, your honesty was the,
like this, but what you have done is exactly
how it's presented to tomorrow.
And then he has to like take a deep breath,
psych himself up in the mirror.
You can do this.
You can do this, you handsome devil.
You can sell a fast one on him again.
You've done it before.
You'll do it again.
Like some sort of Boogie Nights-esque movie monologue.
Oh yeah, of course.
And then he steams the bomber jacket
and then he goes out there.
We use a hand steamer.
Yeah, a hand steamer.
We have one at home.
It's great.
So convenient.
Depends on the material, but yeah, they work pretty well.
Yeah, so if you have mixed materials,
you don't want to use a steamer
because they dry at different rates.
So you don't want to use a steamer on like a men's suit coat.
There's too many layers.
I got it.
That's, you got to dry clean.
But DiMauro knows that.
Of course.
You get that in executive school.
That's like 70% of his job, yeah.
Yeah, that's executive school 101.
Any executive's job is just, yeah, yeah.
You can deliver any message while looking sharp
and it'll sail.
Right.
So get your steam around Josh
and get people excited about that sod.
I think that was pretty good.
That was pretty good.
It was very funny and also like,
that God, it kind of is just enough, isn't it?
It's kind of just enough.
It really is just enough.
Yeah, yeah.
You got some Easter eggs.
You got new food alone.
I feel like people come out for it.
That's what I'm saying.
I would feel like, oh cool,
I would go try like the better Tomorrowland food.
I'd be interested in that.
You just call it like, it's just,
now it's Tomorrowland bistro.
And now we're, that's all you got to do.
Yeah, it'd be like, we got to go down to the bistro,
the Tomorrowland bistro.
Let's make a trip to Anaheim.
They really want it to be risky
and get a little futuristic.
The S could be a two and the O could be a zero.
And now like, ooh, futuristic.
I guess it'd probably be,
I was trying to figure out like,
what would a digital bistro be?
And then that would be distro.
I think that'd be too confusing.
Distro.
But distro, it seems like it's popping for you.
Wait a minute.
I do like the sound of that.
That's not bad.
It's not the, what's the character?
Is Destro the character?
DC character?
That's a G.I. Joe villain?
Well, I'll check it.
I'll check it and see which villain I'm trying to think of.
Look, I got a lot of villains running around in my head
for my youth, so I don't, I can't keep them straight.
Okay.
That was excellent.
Yeah, I think perfectly, yeah.
Followed the rules, great.
Got the job done.
Thank you so much.
Oh, thank God.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank God.
Take off.
It's over.
Yeah, it's over.
Get that towel on you.
Towel off for a couple days.
Oh, Jason, wait.
And it's Josh's problem now.
Wait, it didn't, we're not recording, Jason.
Oh, no.
Oh, jeez.
You gotta do the whole thing again.
By memory.
All right, just let me hit the urgent care
and then I'll come back around.
Oh, okay, all right.
It takes you an hour or two to boot that thing up, right?
Yeah, it takes a couple hours.
Okay.
All right, just kidding, J.K.
All right, so I really tried my best
to imagine what realistically would happen
in this year of Our Lord 2024.
There's a couple things I think, it's a gray area,
and there's one big thing
that I'll probably talk about at the end
that I struggled with.
Okay.
That I was like, this doesn't feel right happening,
but maybe it does happen.
So check me.
Everybody check me.
You're allowed to have a little dessert.
Sure, I try, yes.
Not one drop of whipped cream for Jason,
but you get to, so it might very well be.
Oh, yeah, please don't make me deal
with the dairy distributors,
because they are cut through.
They're worse than the sod people.
So, yeah, so I really,
so just to give you my philosophy before I start here,
and this, I guess, yeah, tomorrow wouldn't do this,
but this is how I'm choosing to present this,
is I was trying to keep most of the existing infrastructure
because that would save a lot of money.
I would have loved to demolish everything and start fresh,
but that's not probably what I think they would do in 2024.
So we gotta kinda keep the bones of Tomorrowland.
So I've tried to find fun stuff
that I don't think is gonna break the bank
for my proposal here.
So I think Tomorrowland needs some sort of a new tagline,
a new thing,
because that's the way Disney does everything now.
They add more words.
So I would call it Tomorrowland Spaceport Infinity.
That would be, and you could call it SPI, I guess,
for short, SPI, called SPI or whatever.
And the loose premise,
which we've talked about this before,
is it's sort of a port of entry.
It's a place where, you know, spaceships land
and they take off and aliens congregate
and all the different IP congregate as well.
So I was thinking, I want stuff that feels like
nods to Disney history and sort of original stuff,
but that's not gonna happen in the modern company.
So let's see if we can cram it somewhere else.
So I thought, well, why not go with Buzz Lightyear
and change the name
and change a little bit of what's inside.
Call it Buzz Lightyear Adventures Alien Encounter.
With an exclamation mark.
So we talked about this a while ago,
the whole hype of Guardians of the Galaxy,
oh, they're gonna reference Epcot stuff,
is loosely referenced.
But I feel like in this Buzz Lightyear Adventures
Alien Encounter, you keep the ride system,
you keep it to shoot a ride,
but you change sort of the narrative of the ride
and you change every room to maybe be a different reference
to old Tomorrowland stuff.
So you shrink down in one, like, inner space
and you do, you know, you can have your references
to Alien Encounter itself with the excess tech and stuff.
Zerg can still be involved, he's still kind of the bad guy,
but maybe he's the one who kind of is torturing
the alien from Alien Encounter.
Then you kind of end up having to save that alien
by the end.
Which then there's that heart,
then you're rooting for that character.
Because like that character was sort of mistreated,
the alien from Alien Encounter,
but you can still have it be a little lightly scary.
Everything's still gonna be kind of cartoonish
to keep kind of in the same theme,
Buzz Lightyear, the way it is now.
Whatever, Space Rangers spin,
is that what it's called in Disneyland?
No, it's Astro Blaster,
it's Disneyland, Space Rangers spin in Florida.
I had to look this up yesterday too,
and I did remember we went through this on the episode.
But yeah, you can do like, if you had Wing's room,
you can do Captain EO Evil Queen room here,
and you can do it in like a cartoon Buzz Lightyear style.
Oh, her rendered as the-
Which would be fun.
So you can give,
because this is what they've been doing lately,
I feel like, and this is what Country Bear BBQ Jamboree,
the people in Imagineering do want to give us what we want,
but they have to sneak it in.
So this is my attempt to sneak it in here
with an overlay, or not overlay,
a redo that wouldn't be so expensive
and would keep the ride system there.
And would improve Buzz Lightyear,
which I think is a good, it has room for improvement.
I'm curious what an if you had Wing's room means.
I don't really know,
I should have fleshed that out a little more.
It could just be a little like one of the hallways
that take you from one room to the other.
Like kind of like a burnt,
maybe a burnt, like crumbling Eastern Airways sign.
Sure, that could be a short little reference.
That doesn't necessarily have to have its own room.
They're just watching Buzz Lightyear
take a comfortable flight.
Sure, that's fine too.
Seven and seven, please.
Right, so yeah.
He deserves a break.
You can shoot Chairman Clench at the end of the ride,
maybe a cartoon Chairman Clench.
Zerg and Clench teaming up makes sense.
That's fun. I like that.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
You could do like some like,
you could kind of like America,
you could have a little like America Sings references
with like the characters in like little space outfits
or something flying around.
Like the eagle, the burlives eagle.
Can I with lasers blow the head off that eagle?
Only if you, there's a secret target.
Okay, okay, you gotta be good.
I was gonna say no out of goes to get it.
Yeah, you have to be such a precise shot
to actually have the head fly off,
which they don't want normal park goers to see.
It's a little violent.
But like there's a techno version
of like way down upon the Swanee River.
The songs of that attraction.
You already have one of those on your iPhone, right?
Yeah, well, my Bandcamp app, my Bandcamp creator app.
You could just load that right in.
That's announced at Honda Center
and there's just one shriek from Jason.
Right. Yeah.
Baffled audience.
Let's go.
Yes.
So that is, yes,
that is not the most expensive thing in the world,
but it is a nice little refresh.
That's cool.
With the references that we like.
Great.
And we will feel take,
because we, us Disneyland weirdos,
wanna feel taken care of.
And this is the type of thing
that makes us feel taken care of.
I don't think I even need to say this
because they're gonna do it.
Yeah.
But if it's a ride full of Easter eggs,
you gotta get an A113 in there.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, so that we can,
and that's code on some spaceship or something.
But that way you can get,
every hundredth car is a car with nerds going,
A113, that's the classroom that's a college
where a lot of the animators, Tim Burton is,
so it's kind of a message to each other
that they put in the movies.
Yeah.
So yeah, that'll be in there.
And there'll be maybe a target
that will illuminate it or something too
to really make sure nerds point it out.
So it gets bigger when,
if you know the right target to make it bigger and appear,
then you can even loudly or even more loudly say
to the person next to you.
It kind of gives you implicit permission
to stop whispering that.
I think that stuff's important to point out,
especially if you're on a date or something at Disneyland
because pointing it out can help facilitate
the end of a relationship that's not meant to be.
Right.
Which is nice, yeah.
It really gives the girl an out.
I'm saying girl, it's probably gonna be a girl,
probably, more likely.
Yeah.
Probably, yeah.
Yeah, it's a good test.
Probably.
And A113 is a CalArts classroom
for an Imagineering.
Well, now I have to just say the real,
no, that's a CalArts thing, yeah.
Okay.
Because a lot of the, now I don't remember.
It's like, it's Brad Bird and it's Lasseter
and it's Tim Burton.
Tim Burton.
It's a room they all would have known.
Like a studio.
It's wild.
Yeah, so every 10th car.
It is actually interesting.
I'm just, I said it facetiously.
Every 10th car is into it,
but every 9th car is complaining about the prevalence
of the CalArts style,
which I've seen online before
and I don't understand what they're talking about.
No, yeah, I don't know.
That's lost on me.
I think it's something about animation,
specifically animation, television animation style.
Hmm.
Okay, well, we'll look into that.
No, I don't know.
No, it's not.
You don't think we should look into it?
I'd say let's not.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's not look into it.
Yeah, I'm sorry all these guys made a bunch
of good movies and shows.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, well, yeah.
Star Tours, the adventures continue.
The adventures continue.
That's what it is.
I can't think of any of the names of these rides.
The ride that names no one calls it?
Yeah.
Right, basically the same,
but we're adding BB-8 to the queue.
BB-8's gonna be with R2-3PO.
That's gonna get a big cheer in the room.
Doesn't seem the most expensive thing.
And then we're gonna just get a couple new scenes.
Canto Bight from Last Jedi.
We're gonna do.
Oh, Canto Bight's good for a, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that would work in a Star Tours.
And more of like a Bespin-like scene too,
a Cloud City scene.
Yeah.
A big Cloud City guy.
And let's even flirt with the idea
that it's like more of a calm scene.
It's a pleasant scene,
because I always talk about.
That it's a what?
It's like a calming.
Oh, more of a calm.
It's a calm scene.
It would have to be the first one
because you want to end on a big climax.
I thought you said like Morpha Calm.
I'm like, I don't know that planet.
That's cool.
We can make up our own planets too.
And you go to Morpha Calm.
Morpha Calm.
And then just more characters that can
like send their transmission.
Max Rebo.
Give us a Max Rebo.
Give us, I guess, Figuring Dan and the Modal Nodes.
Three of them, or how many?
There's six of them.
There's a lot to fit in there,
but you can do it. Yeah, but.
Just really like, let's open it up
as far as like all the different characters.
All the pod racers could contact you.
And again, this isn't the most expensive thing
in the world, and it's a nice thing
that Star Tours already does this stuff.
And I think if you just give us,
throw us a couple more things,
we'll feel like, okay, yes,
Star Tours is a little refreshed.
I like the idea enough to give you permission
to say one of the names of the pod racers
I know you want to say.
No, I don't want to, no.
No, really.
I don't need to.
I want you to.
Can I say it?
All right, let's Jason do it.
Jason can say it, yeah.
Okay.
Team Toppa Gaileys.
All right, thank you.
Very good.
Team Toppa Gaileys.
All right, everybody earned that
with their good effort. I don't want to say
Juan Sandage or
Odie Randrell.
I don't want to say any of the names.
I don't like it anymore.
And I shouldn't make you.
I shouldn't make you say.
I don't like to say the names.
Astral Orbiter, gone.
Taking that thing.
It's almost like that.
It's like if they only did that.
Yes, that would be a big step.
That thing is gone.
Right now, if you don't know,
it's right at the front of Tomorrowland
and it is so inconvenient.
You got to walk around it.
There's always bottlenecks happening.
We've talked about it before.
Great idea in theory,
but with how crowded Disneyland is,
it just, it's not worth it being there.
It would only work
if everything had like 20% more,
if you were building a Tomorrowland from the ground up
and that was your entry point, great.
But it's a pretty narrow,
the main avenue, whatever you want to call it,
Tomorrow Avenue.
Right.
Just, yeah, it's tough.
And we're ripping out people mover track
that goes down the walkway there.
Okay, okay.
Because that also is in the way
and just inconvenient
and obviously they haven't done anything within a while,
but that's got to go for traffic reasons.
And you think about other Tomorrow Avenues
in other parks and they don't have that overhang
and it feels more open and free.
Yes.
And then the, now that we've questioned what it's called,
I'm just thinking Orvidon.
That thing's gone.
I'm pulling that thing out too.
Orvidon's out.
I'm pulling that whole stretch of stuff out
to open that walkway up
because that's just, it's all inconvenient at this point
and it's got to go.
And there's nothing in there.
This is somewhat expensive,
but okay, it's got to go, I think.
And I do that,
feels like they would do that
with a modern day, decent budget.
But it's just nothing.
That's not even replaced by, there's no tower.
No.
No, I don't want to put anything there.
I don't want to put anything there.
Some more planters?
With fresh sod?
Keep in mind, yeah, if you had 12 bags,
Mike's getting at least 15.
Yeah, that's, hmm, okay.
Matt, we'll think about the planters.
I'm not sure.
I'm iffy on the planters.
Okay, fair enough.
Space Mountain basically stays the same, I think,
with this, Space Mountain's still a great ride.
Would I like them to do what Tokyo's doing
is rip it out and put in the coolest thing ever?
Yes, doesn't seem likely.
They're not even doing that in Florida.
So there's no way they're gonna do it here.
Well, if you had to, look, if you had to rocket launch
or blow one up, you would choose Florida.
Yeah, of course.
It's pretty rough.
It doesn't have the fun score and smoothness of Anaheim.
It doesn't have any music, right?
Huh?
It doesn't have any music?
It's just eerily.
It's like kind of quiet.
I think it's a lot of click-clacking.
And someone out there is listening and saying,
but all that stuff you said is what's good about that.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I understand.
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I really like the Christmas party version
where they blast you with really loud Christmas music
and yellow and green lights.
Right.
That is fun.
I wish they would do that out here.
Well, let's put that in yours.
That's part of mine too.
Good, yeah, yeah.
Nice, nice.
But I think they can, I swear they've done this
and I've seen no one confirm this online,
but when Space Mountain had a redo a couple months ago,
a year ago or something,
it did feel like the effects with the stars were brighter
and I don't know if that any,
I don't know what the technology is behind
making the stars brighter but not showing the track.
And somebody, I'm probably sounding like an idiot,
but there's probably little stuff like that they could do
or whatever tricks they've learned on Guardians
to make that thing feel so bright but still not feel like.
It's a very high contrast experience, isn't it?
Yeah.
The whites are very white and the blacks are very black.
And that's trickier because the track is, I think,
a lot closer together on Space Mountain.
It's like this big cylinder in my mind.
And really, yeah, you've probably got room to project
and separate in that new Guardians building.
So I know you can't do something so incredible,
but I don't know, I kinda like the Star Wars overlay they do
so more of that stuff.
So you could announce little things like that.
There's some improvements coming to the Star Wars
Space Mountain overlay or whatever, but.
I'm mostly not a fan of the Star Wars overlay
but there's a move in it where you kind of,
there is a real surprise jump scare of a blast.
Some ship blows up. Yes, yeah.
And you kinda duck under, you're heading right for it
and then you duck under it with barely any time.
And I would say some equivalent move that's always there
in a non-Star Wars version.
Oh yeah, that would be cool.
Like a meteor shower or blast or like a meteor.
Or just some, I don't know, supernova.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, two comets collide.
Oh yeah, that's cool.
Yeah, something like that would be cool.
Because yeah, the way they have it, it feels like.
Or just an astronaut's head explodes without it.
Which is what happens when an astronaut
doesn't have his helmet on.
His head gradually expands and then bursts like a balloon.
Like that Simpsons joke.
It feels like a lot of the Star Wars effects on that overlay
is just they've put like a long neon strip
of like green and red to simulate the fire
from the X-Wing or the TIE Fighters.
And then they just play the noise and then do it.
And it kinda works.
Very effective.
It does.
Well, some of that shit's simple in the first movie.
So it's like that, it's very, yeah, just basic.
The opening score, going up the hill and stuff,
that really.
I like that, yeah.
I guess as we add it up, I don't know, yeah.
There's value to it.
But I'm saying like that's what we're gonna do
with this overlay.
There's gonna be light little effects changes,
but it's not gonna be, we're not putting a lot of money
into a new space mountain in this pitch.
It's not, I don't think a required piece of.
No, it's not, again, I wish they were,
I said this before, if they would replace it with Guardians,
I would actually be fine with it, like in Florida.
No space mountain.
Oh, in Florida, oh, okay.
Like the Guardians' coaster, I'm saying, in Florida.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like, oh, that's, that's.
I thought you were saying replace space mountain
in Florida with Guardians,
which I would also be fine with, second Guardians.
Sure, yeah, too.
In two parks, that's great.
Oh, yeah, that would be great.
It's cheaper, yeah, you don't have to build
a new space mountain.
But what I am excited about in regards to space mountain
is next to space mountain, the Star Wars launch,
current Star Wars launch bay.
What are we gonna do with this thing?
This thing has been sitting,
this is maybe the most offensive part of Tomorrowland
in a lot of ways.
Yeah, I've said it for a long time.
Yeah, I am.
And it's just sitting there, it's had the house
of the future, or whatever they called it.
Was it called the house of the future
when it was just the weird, like.
Oh, the intervention.
It was just a part of intervention.
Sorry, yes.
Yeah.
Nobody liked that, and then it's,
now it's like meet and greets for Star Wars characters,
which there's fun stuff in there,
but it's just, it's so much space and whatever.
I think what you gotta do with this
is turn it into a big restaurant.
Yeah.
I think that. Oh, good.
Now, you can do it a couple ways.
You could keep the building as it is.
I mean, it rotates, but you don't have to do that.
Or you could just demolish it
and build a new two-story restaurant.
Yeah.
And have the top part be a bar lounge
with a nice terrace out there.
Yeah.
And this thing is gonna be packed every night.
There's no one who wouldn't wanna do it.
Make it Blue Bayou level, make,
I mean, that's for Disney, that's high level,
but it's, you know, be a be, depending on what you get.
But you can have a cocktail up there.
You can have a nice meal.
You can have different rooms
because there's a lot of real estate.
So you can do some of the space restaurant
and up-cott stuff in here, too.
So you could have different, like, be our guest.
You could have different rooms that are, you know,
simulating different parts of a spaceship.
One thing is you're actually in space.
One, you're, I don't know, dining in the capsule.
It's a smaller room or whatever.
Sure.
Or, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, like a big round table
and kind of a centrifugal room, yeah, yeah.
So, like, I just think this makes a lot of sense
because there's, like, Blue Bayou, I guess,
is technically the best restaurant in Disneyland
other than Club 33.
Yeah.
Right?
It feels like I'm wondering why they haven't done more
of this is what I'm saying.
And they've never done, Disneyland has never done
a be our guest, not that I have no idea
of the actual quality of that place.
I think it's gone down since it opened.
Okay, okay.
If it became a pre-fixed menu, it used to be like,
oh, go with breakfast, it's counter-serve,
and it's like, you can see it all for really cheap,
and they're like, pre-fixed lunch and dinner.
Yeah.
I think it might be still okay, but I think it was,
I went pretty, no, I guess not soon, a couple years after,
and I thought it was really good,
and the next time I went, it was fine.
It was okay to find.
Yeah, we definitely don't have, like,
there's not like a skipper's canteen or anything.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, Disneyland is pretty weak
with the sit-down restaurants.
Right.
What I like about this is you're sneaking in original ideas,
original stuff in here, but it's covered by like,
oh, the food and beverage offerings
will pay it off in a year.
Right, this is something we would be excited about,
but this is just a money-generating thing.
That will be cool and be like, attraction-adjacent.
Yes.
You know, it's okay that it's not a revolving
theatrical show.
Now, if they're getting very ambitious,
you demolish the building, and you build
a new two-story building, and you put the Astro Orbiter
on top of it.
Oh.
Oh, jeez.
Which now they can, now it can't support it.
Yes, because you would have to destroy it.
I'm sure it can't hold it as it is.
That's cool.
But then, yeah, so then you could be like,
you could really even bring out the terraces,
and you could have it so you can kind of see
the Astro Orbiter above you.
You could do it in a different, cool way,
where there were a lot of just opportunities
for interesting seating and interesting vantage points.
I guess you could load people.
They would have to take an elevator up to get it,
but it would be kind of like, I guess,
you could do it like the PeopleMover in Florida,
where there's a moving.
That's how rocket jets work in Florida.
Yes.
And you could say you could have a queue
within that big new structure,
which could kind of come out a little bit.
It could sort of go west because you've demolished
the waste of space of the Orbidon Tower.
Right, and then there could be a little VIP entrance
up to the Astro Orbiters.
After you go to a drink at the bar,
you go up and you get a little rocket ride
around Tomorrowland.
And then that sounds like heaven to me.
Yeah.
Are you saying you get a special entrance
because you're?
Maybe there's a special entrance, yeah.
A little perk, a little fast pass perk.
A little fast pass perk, yes.
Because you ate at the new, at one of the, at the grill.
And there's like a special little entrance
or elevator that you take.
That's like the elevator at the restaurant in Epcot.
It's nothing like eating a full-size lamb chop
and then going on the Astro Orbiter immediately.
Yes, being around for a while.
Just a quick seven and seven and pork chop
and then get right on the Astro Orbiter.
Hey, if you can't handle that,
you should not be in space, you know?
That's a good point.
If you can't, being with a big pork chop in your stomach.
It's kind of a test.
Get to Adventureland, pal.
Get to Frontierland.
You can't cut it in space with the rest of us.
I got some pitches for the name.
Oh, great.
Space Mountain Station.
It would have to be called Space Mountain Station Restaurant.
Spaceship Eat is another one of my pitches.
Oh, that's really good.
So you get your Disney reference there.
Somewhere in mine, this isn't better than that,
but I was toying with an idea in mind
with the phrase Space Mountain Summit.
Okay.
Like that.
Or Base Camp or something.
Something that uses the mountain aspect of it.
But I think Spaceship Eat's probably the one.
Spaceship Eat is funny.
Yeah.
I have some other ones down where I would Google it
and I'd be like, is anything called that?
I was like, call the bar Bar Orbit.
I don't know if it's just a name
or there's actually a restaurant or something called that.
What was the name of, you know how Disney did have
a restaurant in the theme building at LAX,
which is the big 60s mod.
No, the Encounter?
The Z-Structure.
Is that what it was called?
I think it was called The Encounter.
Oh, okay, okay.
Yeah.
Bring it on back.
That's what we gotta look into.
There's a lot of interesting stuff.
Closed now, but a lot of interesting history.
I felt like it was only barely open.
Yeah, and really sporadically.
All right.
So yeah, we could name it different things.
Some little things, Magic Eye Theater,
which just is usually like a preview of a movie.
I feel like what you could do is turn it
into a meet and greet walkthrough,
like the way they do Chewbacca,
where you kind of go through a tiny little section
of a rebel base or something,
and then you meet Chewbacca and it's in a themed room
and the photographer's obviously already there,
but we could do a full retro Mickey and Friends
spaceship outfit, kind of space station meet and greet,
and then it would be a pretty good people eater
because you would line up the same way
you would line up for Captain EO or Honey,
I Shrunk, the audience, and then they would go in
and they just kind of go in,
because you could, it's a couple hundred seats theater
or something, you could probably change that
into just a little bit of like a windy maze
that looks kind of Space Mountain Q-ish,
and then you get to the end and it's like a little like,
you could use this, probably use the same screen,
it's just like a screen that has,
I guess you couldn't, it would have to be a video screen,
not a projection screen like it is in there,
so that doesn't make sense,
but it would be like a big space window or whatever,
and Mickey, Minnie, everybody,
but wearing the retro outfits,
which is another thing that's gonna get a big pop
if you go, oh, we're bringing back the Disney characters
in those old space outfits.
Which I don't think I've ever heard
officially acknowledged by the company,
but I feel like everybody would know,
at least if you're at that. I think so.
Yeah, yeah, the little space outfits.
The little space outfits. We want the little space outfits.
They're in that photo spread of like,
was it Vogue from 91 or something,
or it was a high fashion magazine photo spread
of people in different outfits around Disney World,
and they were with the space Mickey and Minnie in Epcot.
Wow. Yeah.
Good enough for Vogue.
Yeah, so they can show that at the presentation
if they're doing my ideas,
but yeah, that's, you basically keep the building the same,
and then that's just- And now they've gained
a committed meet and greet of characters,
but in this different new way.
And then flexible,
so you can do different characters in there,
depending, to keep it fresh,
if everybody has already had their pictures
with the little space suit Disney characters.
Perhaps, perhaps.
A Disneyland place and presence for Figment.
Well, that's an interesting idea.
Very interesting. I never thought of that.
That sounded like I have it coming up.
There's no reason to not have Figment also.
That's an interesting-
In some small way here.
I kind of don't know if I agree with it.
You like making- I've never thought about it before.
Figment a special, only Epcot.
Truly, I've never thought about that before.
Jason, have you ever thought about that before?
I haven't thought about it before,
but I think enough time has passed
of him being an original Epcot.
It's been like 50 years now, or 40 years.
I can be sold on that.
Yeah.
But it is interesting,
because it's almost like it felt shocking to me.
I didn't consider it.
Wow, you just said.
So strange that he went,
well, as strange as Mickey Mouse appearing
at the end of a show of Star Wars characters at-
Well, that's just exciting.
Disney, at a Disney park.
Curious to see if anyone's doing that.
Oh, man.
In our, oh, a permanent hyperspace hoopla.
I unfortunately picked stuff that I think they would do.
But I'd love to see that.
Figment could-
Time to rewrite, then.
What about Figment having like a brother or something?
A West Coast brother?
A West Coast brother.
Eric.
Figment.
He doesn't have a whimsical name.
Right, right.
It's Figment's brother, Eric.
Parents got tired at number two.
Ironically ran out of imagination.
Your grandfather is Eric, right?
Right.
Let's come with that.
Family name.
He's a great guy.
Okay, little stuff.
Autopia stays the same.
We're doing the electric cars in whatever, four years.
It's a lot of real estate.
I'd love to demolish it.
Doesn't seem like it's gonna happen.
Maybe within your, you can't.
That's what I felt.
That's how I felt.
Especially now I'm trying to keep them,
I know they're going to do electric cars,
they say they are, but we'll see.
Sub's staying the same.
And with Tomorrowland Terrace and stuff for the food there,
I just have, make the food better.
Just make the food better.
Yeah.
Just like have it 25% better.
It doesn't even have to be different items.
No.
It's done better.
And I love the stage it comes out from underground.
That stays the same.
I just want more live entertainment.
And it doesn't have to be like a rockabilly band
playing in Tomorrowland at night, but it wouldn't hurt.
I wouldn't mind it.
Because I always like when you go over to Tomorrowland
and there's a band playing at night.
Even if you don't stop and watch it,
it just feels like something's happening here tonight.
So yeah, more of that.
We had fun talking about Pride Night with Henry,
and I'm like leather stitched all the time.
Why not?
Let's just deploy all of that.
I mean, the biggest risk is that some right-wing crank
talks about it for nine days,
and then it never is thought about or controversial again.
Right.
It's gonna ride out exactly one cycle of Libs of TikTok,
and then they can do whatever.
Then Stitch could dance for years to come.
That is, I would love to go back,
teach a media literacy class at Ithaca,
and go like, okay, first things first, no comment.
Second thing, wait it out.
Those nine days are gonna fly by
if you focus on other things.
This is you teaching kids,
well, you're teaching kids how to ride out a scandal
that's a class you're gonna do at Ithaca.
Not an actual scandal.
No, I don't encourage like Logan Paul's in this forest.
I don't want something like that.
So he's Logan Paul's on a talk show,
and they're like, well,
how did you get over that scandal last year?
And he goes, well, my teacher Jason Sheridan,
when I took his class at Ithaca,
he taught me how to ride out anything bad
that I've ever done.
Now, I don't know that I'm ready to be the scapegoat.
That might be lesson number three.
Pick a well-placed scapegoat
that if you get caught in something, you can blame them.
Well, this seems like a different philosophy
than what you said in the first two bits.
No, no, no, well, the first one is for manufactured
bullshit right-wing outrage.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
But this is, now you're,
but you are getting into the territory, I assume,
of the show Scandal.
You are kind of, and I don't, I can't,
I have no further details about the show Scandal.
I have only seen like one or two of Scandal.
I like Kerry Washington a lot.
Jason, you're turning into a regular Olivia Pope.
Oh yeah.
I did know the name Olivia Pope.
I didn't, I haven't had to look up.
You were all nervous when you were presenting,
but now you're very confident when you're telling people
just to ride out a scandal.
To the pressures off, I did my project,
and now I just chilling.
Just saying you're very comfortable
with this part of presenting and teaching.
Because you're in the hot seat now.
I am in the hot seat, yeah.
You're in the tank.
Because the sod concern is off his back.
The sod people don't have sniper's dots on his.
I've blocked all those numbers.
We have delivery date and payment date, okay?
It's accounts, payable, and receivables problem now.
So there's one final question mark on my presentation,
because I do think what I just presented,
if presented in the sexy, demoral way,
would be pretty popular, and people would be excited.
I think Carousel is like an amended space.
Yeah.
That's great, I think that's huge.
Just that.
Just that would work.
Now, on our Patreon, on our second gate episode,
I predicted that Tomorrowland is gonna close D23.
That there's going to be an announcement
about New Tomorrowland.
And I also made an even riskier prediction
about some kind of people mover coming back.
Okay.
And this has been weighing on me now for days,
because I start, I'm really doubting myself now.
If it fits in your budget range.
Because, yes, and part of it is because I was just like,
to me it feels like they don't have anything big
for Disneyland, and they always wanna close
on a hometown announcement.
Now, I was thinking about how you said that
in that episode, and then I was like,
has that ever actually happened?
I feel like it has.
Just not in a while.
But not in a while.
Because lately it's just like.
You know, it's like beyond big,
the last two years ago it was just, there was nothing.
It was like, we're thinking about what would happen
in Florida, whatever.
If your hometown likes the word maybe.
We could, I know you like that, Anaheim.
Destination D23 maybe has a more localized conclusion.
Also, sometimes what I might be thinking of too
is that they'll be like, and we're giving everybody
a free something fast pass to go,
if you're in the park today, you can go.
Whatever.
If you have a reservation on your ticket, you can use this.
Also, my logic was, there just doesn't feel like
a lot of stuff they're gonna fully announce
where it's going for Disneyland that's gonna open
in the next five to six years.
And to me, it's like, there's a couple things,
and then Tomorrowland has to happen now
before Disneyland, Florida, or else it's not happening.
So that's sort of part of my logic for like,
I feel like it's gonna close with Tomorrowland.
That's a guess, I don't know,
I don't have any insider information, but I said.
You've programmed a great show.
I just don't know if it's realistic.
And I understand, I understand.
We'll see how accurate I am.
But I said, I think this is gonna be maybe
like a new people mover.
And I am starting to doubt my prediction.
I'll keep my bet, I'm not gonna go back on my bet.
A man of your word and your money.
But I'm looking at this Google map.
I'm studying this Google map overhead view.
I did a lot of this too, yeah.
Trying to figure out where we could comfortably
make a new Tomorrowland, not Trans,
that's the Florida version,
but just people mover track in general
that wouldn't cost a bunch of money
because you'd have to demolish existing buildings.
And boy does it seem tough.
I don't know other than really changing some stuff
around there where you're going to get the space.
You can kind of go around the back,
like you could kind of maybe go around
the back of Space Mountain and go around
sort of toward Launch Bay.
I just don't know what's happening over there.
I don't know the state of any of those tunnels.
You would have to think that if they were gonna shut down,
if they were gonna like, if Autopia's gonna be down
for a while, can we just, can we like fix those tracks
over there while as part of that,
that's just part of the same project.
Right, so I'm looking at this and I'm just,
I'm stressing out, I'm not an engineer of any kind.
I don't know what I'm doing other than I'm just eyeballing
what looks like there's room to expand
and expand in a way that won't interfere
with the existing infrastructure there.
And it seems pretty impossible to do it.
So I start to really doubt my prediction
about there being a people mover.
But maybe Disney gives a little more money
for this presentation or this redo of Tomorrowland.
And they rebuild, they don't put,
I think they should not put the people mover track
in the middle anymore.
I still think that's a bad idea there.
But maybe.
I watched somebody kinda ideate on some of this stuff.
I think offhand Disney is the YouTube.
Yes, he's really excited about.
Yeah, yeah, I like some of his ideas.
And I, he had the proposal of doing it like Disney World
where there's no middle track and it goes
along the sides of the show buildings down Tomorrow Avenue.
Yes, I think that's basically what I came
to the conclusion that it would have to be.
It still feels like they're gonna have to do
some adjusting existing building to existing buildings.
And it's not the easiest thing in the world.
But what I would do then in keeping with modern Disney
is theme the people mover to Tron.
Great, great.
And it's not gonna go fast,
but it's gonna have neon when you're in the tunnels.
It's gonna go around and you can call it,
there's two names.
Tronple movers.
Well, that's good too.
Call it the transportation center.
Cool, yeah.
You could also call it the Tron Transit Authority,
but that's not as fun, I don't think.
Transit.
But the, yeah, transportation center.
You could call it the Ticket and Transportation Center,
I guess if you really wanted to be the complete
accurate reference to Disney World.
But yes, it would have to go sort of around
the outskirts of Tomorrowland.
It gets tricky, and this is where I really should have
really done my homework and figured out
how it can loop around the area by Autopia and the subs.
Because that's tricky,
because you got Monorail track there,
you got the cars, obviously we got the streets for Autopia.
But there's gotta be some way to kind of loop it around there
and have it come back.
You could just do less, it just doesn't do as much.
Which would be unfortunate, but that's the way it gets done
in your mid-budget version.
I think you'd also have to just close attractions in phases.
You close Star Tours for three months,
Space Pound for three months, Autopia for three months.
And you just, the track gets built,
like people know, like, oh, it's coming,
it's getting closer, they started here, now they're here.
And I think the pitch then for where you load,
if you're gonna build a new restaurant from the ground up,
I think it loads sort of in that general area.
It's like that, because that sort of feels like
it's got the most space, and then especially
if you're gonna demolish that building anyway,
you can add, you're, excuse me,
I'm getting indigestion from talking so much.
You could add your, like whatever, moving walkway
or your elevator, and sort of have that whole restaurant
just be like a big transportation hub, a big port,
a big spaceport for all the different places
you wanna go in the galaxy.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, it's maybe a, somewhere some of that stuff
could happen is like Starcade,
Starcades like becomes loading for something.
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
I'm trying to think of the geography of that.
Star Traders goes or something.
If it's not there, I also would pitch,
just fill that up with arcades, please.
Like, fill that up like the old days.
It was very fun when it was like,
I guess it was on Flynn's arcade
that was in California Adventure,
but Wreck-It Ralph around that time,
before that it was just Generic Arcade,
then it was Wreck-It Ralph kinda themed,
and then it just shut down.
I was remembering they had the short-lived
Magic Key Holder Lounge,
which was mostly tiny digital advertisements
for West Side Story, and one photo opportunity
step and repeat, and then after I checked that out,
we went to Tomorrowland Terrace,
and I got food that was so bad, and it was my birthday.
It was my birthday, that lounge was terrible,
the food was off, it was something like
waffle fries with pulled pork on it,
two of my favorite foods, and it was so bad,
and every wait was like over an hour, like 90 minutes,
and tears were kinda welling up in my eyes,
because I was like, this day sucks so much.
And on my birthday, that food sounds terrible.
How many times have you been back since?
Ah, even I have my limits.
That was how crowded it was.
I usually avoid Tomorrowland Terrace,
but I was like, that's got a reasonable line.
I think it's cool, I think you kinda got a way
to attack PeopleMover, and the Tron thing maybe
gives it the extra money it needs.
That's my thought.
New movie coming, synergy.
They seem to keep wanting to try.
Yeah, great, new bad movie coming,
new disappointing, turgid, boring movie coming.
But again, I don't care, I do not care
about the quality of these films,
I just want some, if it finances some lights
in these theme parks.
Some blue glowing lights, you'll put up with,
I'm guessing a reunion of Jared Leto and Skrillex
back together again, not since Suicide Squad,
the first one.
Are they in it together?
No, I'm just guessing, it's like the downgrade
from the original Daft Punk album,
the soundtrack for the second one
that everyone liked so much, and it's like,
Skrillex is back, 10 years after his prime.
Because Daft Punk broke up.
Is that right?
I didn't hear that.
Helmets finally cracked?
Yeah, they only had one set of helmets.
Fuck.
Yeah, it's over.
That was all it took.
Well, once there was a crack in the helmets,
then that allowed oxygen in, and they're aliens,
so their heads expanded and blew up,
like Jared described earlier.
They're robots.
Okay.
Well, robots who also can't be exposed.
They could be like humanoid robots.
But they're wearing helmets,
it's gotta be for some reason.
Vacuum is being sucked out of the circuits and wires.
The only reason I, I really like watching interviews
with Nile Rodgers talking about
when he worked on that last Daft Punk album,
and he calls them the robots and stuff very casually.
I guess Paul Williams in the speech.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
The robots.
I'm here with a bunch of robots.
I liked the original cartoon,
anime footage from the one album,
like the music videos,
where they were animated as blue aliens,
and that aired on Adult Swim once
at one or two in the morning,
and it was summer in high school,
and I was like, I don't know what the hell is going on,
but I like that.
I had no idea.
I didn't know about the mythology.
I didn't know about the albums.
Sure.
And you were in the window of time
where you were noting new music.
It was still in that zone.
Oh yeah.
Soon to conclude.
I was trying to note.
I was trying to note,
but Adult Swim in the local TV guide,
it wasn't explaining it enough.
Right.
Before you wrapped it up
and stuck to the soundtrack of Mame.
Mame, where Mike was driving us home the other night
from Jane's birthday,
he was making fun of me,
because December's song came on a shuffle.
Oh, I had shuffle on.
He had shuffle on December's,
and I go, hey, something for Jason.
Jason likes his nerd shit.
I was like, these guys are so smart.
You hear these lyrics?
And I'm like, yeah.
But it was on your shuffle.
They sing sea shanties.
I like them.
Me being able to make fun of Jason
doesn't mean I'm not being a hypocrite.
You're not all say, sure, sure.
You were right.
Yeah.
Well, same goes for me.
Listen to the queen wife a lot.
Of course.
I like them.
Well, I dig it.
I don't think either of these
have needed a lot of course correction
in terms of understanding the assignment.
I think you're on to something.
And that whole, well, look, here's the thing.
I think you will find some crossover with mine.
Sure.
And this was some of the,
if we all go off and think separately,
maybe it really illuminates some areas
that are, I don't know, key areas, I guess,
that they could and should do.
Right.
So I guess with that, we can get into mine.
I'm trying to think any caveats.
I mean, I feel like maybe this assignment
gives you the most, at least I took it to be,
there's the most room for putting
your own narrative voice and opinions and taste into.
Right.
So I think you'll find that.
There are some things that are very much
the things I want, but I don't think entirely.
I think it's a crowd pleaser too.
And I, you know, feel free to interrupt
because I think I am gonna try to go a little bit tomorrow.
Oh, please, yeah.
Let's, not that I'm even in the same league,
but let's see what I can,
if I can get steaming and make everybody else get steamy.
Okay, yeah.
Let me, I'll try to, okay, okay.
Remember when we dreamed of a better tomorrow?
A tomorrow without limits.
A tomorrow that acknowledges and celebrates yesterday,
but isn't stuck in it.
A tomorrow that doesn't merely imagine the near future,
but rather millennia beyond.
Welcome to Tomorrowland 3055.
Oh, wow.
That clears it, that's fine, 30 Tomorrowland 3055.
A visionary hub of innovation,
transportation, and imagination.
Tomorrowland 35, in an unprecedented decision,
certainly not said half an hour ago,
will deliver on the promise of an intergalactic port
where mind-blowing vehicles and astounding technology
let you rocket to the stars and beyond
and unforgettable visits to our planet
by astounding beings from across the cosmos.
The experience begins before you even set foot
on an attraction where, during the day,
a refurbished, repainted, white-chrome,
and crystal-color scheme has finally unified
the land aesthetically, and at night,
eye-popping LED screens turn the land aquamarine,
purple, blue, and magenta in a light show
that rivals New Spaceship Earth's sphere
or the streets of Tokyo.
I mean, isn't that the way, like, just brighten it up,
you know? Of course.
They can at least get to L.A. Live.
Can we not get to L.A. Live?
Of course. Can we not get to L.A. Live?
Mike, just imagine this is the Aaron Sorkin,
Danny Boyle movie, Steve Jobs,
and you and I are standing on the side of the stage,
and he's Steve Jobs, and we're just there going, like,
he's doing it, he's really doing it.
Wow. That's what I felt.
I was wrong.
You put it into a movie reference, yeah.
The structure of this has been split into three,
much like that film.
Nice.
That's, by the way, that's,
what you said is expensive.
Yeah, sure.
I guess that's the reason it hasn't been done,
but let's fuck it.
Yeah, let's go.
If some fucking crappy mall can do it.
I and they. They can do it.
Okay.
Guests will immediately note the wide open space,
thanks to the absence of the Astro Orbiter
in the entryway. Of course, of course.
Did it go back atop the central tower,
replacing the observatron, not,
or I'm sorry, the orb-a-don.
Orb-a-don. Not quite.
The highest point in Tomorrowland
now belongs to a brand new attraction concept,
Abduction Point.
Wow.
Inspired by a never-built Tokyo attraction,
this high-in-the-sky drop tower
beams guests up toward a hovering alien craft,
only to plummet back towards Earth,
offering stunning views of the entire park along the way
and a dazzling light show from the UFO's beams.
We touched on this,
but this was not fleshed out to that extent.
I mentioned it really quick at the end
of the Tomorrowland 2055.
I thought that's such a fucking cool,
like a tower of terror.
And this would be kind of like a mini version,
like more of like a, not carnival-ish,
but closer to whatever that California Adventure One
was called.
But like elevate, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
We don't need a circular, we don't need another Dumbo.
Let's do something new.
Well, in a way, yeah, you're also looking at something
that actually then becomes a decoration
in the way that other things in Tomorrowland would be.
So it is a ride, but primarily it's for kinetic energy.
It's primarily for the lights
and to really add to the atmosphere.
A thousand percent, absolutely.
If these, and I think you'll find that throughout,
if the rides as light shows
and depictions of transportation technology.
It's a weenie.
Yes.
It's like the way.
You know what, I think this is,
I think there's like more centerpiece attractions,
but this is the weenie.
This is the weenie in the way that MGM Studios,
then Hollywood Studios kept changing.
Like, oh, the Earful Tower is the weenie.
The Big Sorcerer's Hat.
No, it's actually Terror Tower.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And much like Disney Studios,
I am keeping Star Wars Launch Bay.
I'm the only one who's. Wow, really?
No, no, I'm not doing that.
Absolutely not.
That would have been a bold choice.
It would have been good, yeah.
I'll find a way to make it work.
We're blowing up Galaxy's Edge
and keeping only the Launch Bay,
boiling it down to its essential.
Wow, yeah.
Okay, perhaps while caught in that UFO beam,
you looked over and noticed the nearby lagoon.
The water seems cleaner and also more active.
That's because the submarines have made way
for a Tokyo Disney Sea audience favorite, Aquatopia.
Oh, wow. No more
slow-loading claustrophobic tubes.
Now guests will travel open air
in personal trackless hovercraft,
whizzing and splashing above the water.
Jason, you're aware of this.
Mike, you've seen this attraction.
Doesn't that seem like. I did, yeah.
Let's keep it, let's keep water,
but that's a futuristic water attraction
that's more fun than any of the stuff around here.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Is there a thin amount of water,
like a shallow amount of water at Aquatopia?
There's a TikTok of a cast member
walking out onto the water
that the ground is very close.
So you're gonna have to develop new technology, perhaps,
to have full Wi-Fi boats.
Well, I think it's like you redo the lagoon.
Oh, okay, fill up the lagoon.
Yeah, yeah, you just keep the lagoon atmosphere and vibe
because as I think you'll find throughout,
I'm not necessarily blowing it all up and starting over
because I do love Tomorrowland.
There's a lot that I love about the bones of Tomorrowland.
So that's another version,
and I might be curious to hear when all's said and done,
what would be good ideas if we were blowing it all up,
but I'm not the person to do that
because I love Tomorrowland.
I think there was a lot that was great about Tomorrowland.
The first time I ever went to the place in 1988,
and I think it's a matter of restoring and building back.
Because if I had your assignment,
I think I would have said,
first things first, we're leveling all of it to the ground.
Well, this is what, let's play that out after I'm done.
Of course, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because that's probably the one thing, yeah,
that is different between how you and I would have done it.
Okay, so, Aquatopia will delight guests
with its showcase of clean energy so thoroughly
that they aren't upset that we have eliminated Autopia,
don't care if it's electric, it's going away, land canceled.
A lot of real estate.
It is a lot of real estate,
and I have been very gracious
despite this being a Tomorrowland project.
I have donated the top half of the Autopia property
to Fantasyland in order to build,
and this was a tough choice,
but I ended up landing on Beauty and the Beast Tokyo ride.
That's what we're getting.
So you've added to Fantasyland.
I have taken, yes.
I mean, if you consider all of Autopia to be Tomorrowland,
yeah, I think this is worth an annex.
I think it makes, there's not room
for full new Fantasyland up there.
So I was like, let me pick the best of the best
and something that I don't think needs
the full real estate of Disneyland forward,
because I like the frozen stuff aesthetically.
There's another fairy tale.
I mean, there's Tangled, all that Fantasy Springs stuff,
but I'd rather just take all that new land,
do all of Fantasy Springs over there,
and let's just take the best of the best
that could work in Fantasyland.
I think that's Beauty and the Beast.
The Beast's castle will blend perfectly into Aquatopia
with a new backdrop of forests and waterfalls.
I think that'll all blend and look nice next to Matterhorn.
Elsewhere, cherished classics remain,
but with fan favorite enhancements.
Star Tours is still bustling,
but one cabin has been permanently converted
to a restored, enhanced version
of the original Star Tours journey,
complete with our old pal Captain Rex.
Yeah, good, very good.
Just one, and then the rest are still interactive,
and you don't know if you're gonna end up in that,
even though certain guests, you might be looking at one,
will demand to always go on the Rex one.
They'll have to figure out how they'll handle
the amount of requests to go on the old one.
Well, I think the biggest thing in their corner
will be that everybody who, like,
excuse me, could I do, all of the Rex demanders
will be such pushovers that they'll wait wherever
they have to wait as long as they need to wait.
And you'll be able to spot them.
You'll be able to spot them in line.
Well, it will become a contest between cast members of like,
all right, whichever one of them
is crying the hardest gets to go.
Mm-hmm.
You know, you know what actually would be good,
is every car had a different person piloting it.
Like, C-3PO's in one.
Ooh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
And then there's a different Forlom,
the bounty hunter is in one or something.
Forlom, the bounty hunter.
Forlom, yeah.
I mean, seems like a fun place for Grogu.
Sure.
Let's figure out how to make him pilot.
Right, great.
If he's gotta sit on a couple of crates.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Sit on some crates and go to a crate.
Yeah, if he's a little clumsy piloting,
but he keeps moving stuff out of the way with force
so it works, you know.
If you sorta go, like, it's original trilogy,
one cabin is original, one is prequel,
one is new, one is, or TV, whatever.
Like post 2015, essentially,
and then one is old school Disneyland with race.
That's a good, and now we're covering everything.
Babu Frick in one of them.
Cool.
Yes.
Oh, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very good pilot.
Hell yeah.
Or just give him a seat.
Just like, he just gets to sit and enjoy it like us
and you just gotta really make sure
people don't squish him.
Can I say real quick about this D23 Starspeeder toy
that's coming out that's exclusive,
they're linking 3,000 of them,
that actually plays the original Star Tours movie
and the little LED screen inside of it.
It's a toy that plays the ride film.
Do we know how much, do we know with what technology?
Oh, oh, how much it costs?
No, how much of the-
I think it's all of the ride.
It plays the entire- I believe.
It's like a toy re-release of a restored ride film.
Yes.
It's an LCD, it's got little seat belts.
It's got, you can click the seat belts.
I don't know if it's each one or it just might be a row.
You can just click the seatbelt in the row.
I don't know if there's a tiny dirty little yellow strap.
I don't know about that either,
but I know it's an original,
it's not like a redo of one of the old Starspeeder toys.
And I think this is, of all the toy chats I have,
this is the one that almost is universally being purchased
by all these toy people I know.
They say it will be on sale in person,
but also online Monday,
but who knows how many will be left.
That's gotta go so fast.
That's $300, but-
That's $300?
That's actually not so-
It's not so, I know, I know.
It's not.
This is one of those purchases where I go,
and I go, I'll buy it and keep it in the box,
and if I need to pay for a medical bill,
I guess I'll just sell it, but I need-
If the dog gets sick.
Yes, I need to have it.
That'll do, that'll go a third of the way.
Yeah, that's basically, that's maybe my philosophy going in.
That's smart, that's smart.
Okay, Space Mountain.
I am not blowing it up.
I like the current Space Mountain.
There's plenty, I think, even in a blue sky version,
there's a lot that I'm too addicted to,
but I have made a crucial change.
If a visitor named Mike Carlson asks a cast member nicely,
they will turn on the goddamn Red Hot Chili Peppers.
Thank you, wow, that's really nice.
It's back, only if you ask for it,
much like the robots at Chuck E. Cheese in Northridge,
and mostly it will not be asked for.
Any song, can I choose a song, too,
or does it have to be one of the old ones that played?
Don't push your luck, it's whatever it was before.
It's, yeah, it was the higher ground cover, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, all right, so that.
Okay.
So here already, we now have a thriving land of UFOs,
hovercraft, rockets, star speeders,
and of course, monorails.
Hey, let's redo that, I didn't think about it,
let's redo that station, that signage is dumb,
it's like a little bit steampunky, don't make it.
It's all, everything's, look, it's white, it's white,
it's silver, it's chrome, we're going simple here.
Right.
With a lot of LED, of course.
But, we have missed one big vehicle,
probably the centerpiece of the whole thing, light cycles.
An entire mini land within Tomorrowland 3055
will be the Tron game grid.
The centerpiece of this, of course,
will be Tron light cycle run 2.0, that's right.
It is elevated, it is lifted up,
it is no mere carbon copy of Magic Kingdom
and Shanghai's Tron light cycle run.
This is a brand new experience tailor made
for the Tomorrowland Disneyland space.
So, the former Carousel Theater will be raised to the ground,
much like Mike's version, in order to build
a new towering Q building and launch site,
combining the neon aesthetics of Tron
and the never built crystal cubism of Lucasport.
Oh, wow.
A little bit of flavor of that cool Lucasport concept.
Talked about it on the second gate,
if you haven't heard it, look it up.
Slash Ventureport, I had a couple names,
but like big cool crystal building,
almost like journey into imagination building, but better.
Yeah, you know what, I completely,
I had that thought for the restaurant in my pitch,
with that aesthetic, but I completely forgot
to write it down.
We were, I think we're thinking,
this is where the parallel thinking I think is great.
I hadn't even, I felt like you maybe keep that,
because I like aesthetically the Carousel building.
I think there's a way to, but also,
just the land it sits on, and like,
as they found with parking structures,
when you don't have a lot of space,
what do you do, you build up.
And I think Tomorrowland is a great place
to build up, for sure.
I think there's been a lot of advances, too,
in compact roller, like getting a lot of thrill
out of a compact coaster.
Sure, sure.
Well, that is my question,
unless you're about to go there.
Yeah, yeah, I'll explain, I'll take it there.
But poke holes in this,
because this one might have the biggest logic holes.
So, on the top floor of the Tron Game Grid building,
a permanent end-of-line club,
straight out of the Electronica event,
where you can dance to electronic beats,
drink Glohitos, as well as actual drinks for grownups,
and take in the highest in-park view
of fireworks available.
The end-of-line club will be amazing,
and open, and available to all guests,
not some DVC bullshit.
That's for everybody.
Nice, amen.
Yeah, great.
For the people.
Oh, and also part of this, in this new land,
the little UFO booth that's kind of, as you get it,
like next to the unused people mover tower,
there's a UFO, and like an umbrella,
where you learn about DVC pricing,
and this will be personally put
into a shredding machine by me.
I will insist on myself getting rid
of this stupid fucking tacky booth.
You know, that is the first mention
of umbrellas, or awnings, or shade,
that I'm hoping any one of these Tomorrowlands
might address down the line, is like,
oh, this is a little too brutalist heat-wise,
you know, it's a lot of cement.
I guess so. And metal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean, you lose that
with the people mover track.
Yeah. But I don't know,
maybe some of the other,
maybe the other track I'm talking about.
Okay, before I get to the light cycles,
another part of the game grid is Alien Pizza Planet
becomes Flynn's Barcade,
an amended concept, like Jason referred to earlier.
This is an indoor-outdoor space
where the whole family can eat, drink,
well, not the whole family can drink,
you know what I'm saying,
and play both modern and old-school video games,
often, hopefully, customized games
from within the Disney universe.
Tron, Fix-It Felix, a Toy Story alien claw game,
acknowledging the Toy Story history of that space.
You can do the Zerg game from the cold open
of Toy Story 2. Oh, yeah.
Maybe you always lose, you always get blasted,
and then your little legs drop to the ground,
and Zerg laughs, there's no way to win the game.
But putting all the Disney video games in one place,
and this is the thing,
I'm not trying to just please myself
with some of these things,
I'm trying to think country bear style,
and how do we fold Disney IP into itself.
So, oh, and also, they do still serve pizza,
but it is no longer trash.
Oh, okay, so it's good.
They do good pizza, yes. That's an upgrade, yeah.
Yes, by reaching out to Acclaimed Chef Anyone,
we can finally get some good pizza.
By Acclaimed Chef, your stepmom got a pizza stone
for Christmas, and wants to try it out
with some Trader Joe's dough,
and there's a bottle of Francesca Rinaldi in the pantry.
Absolutely, done, your stepmom, she's in.
So, now let's talk light cycles.
Inspired by the original route of the people mover,
Tron light cycles will take a winding path
that traverses all of Tomorrowland.
Once aboard, your light cycle will launch
past Space Mountain, out of Disneyland,
out of the park, into a glowing canopy,
much like what is in Shanghai in Magic Kingdom,
but this is built in the former
bus and transportation zone off Harbor.
That sequence, that big launch and loop,
and the glowing light show all happens in the,
not the hub, the Esplanade.
It takes over part of the Esplanade,
which I think frankly makes more sense for this zone,
and is cooler than a Pandora expansion.
I want Pandora over in Disneyland Forward.
I don't want Pandora to be cramped at all.
I don't really get that coming out of that part of the park.
Now, this portion of the ride
doubles as a stunning free light show
for guests arriving from Harbor Boulevard,
and even non-paying guests on their way to downtown Disney.
You are using some of your blue sky to make public art.
That's right.
Civic engaging.
Giving back, yes.
What does that do to a zone that is kind of like,
look, we haven't done the Harbor Hoedown yet.
We may never do the Harbor Hoedown.
Is one possibility.
That's one blue sky.
But aesthetics are not always the best around that place.
And especially now, in a way, I'm sad to see the bus zone.
I do think that bus zone's gonna go,
and I've had nice memories there
because that's why I've been doing it.
I've been doing a hotel that's a little ways away,
and I take a shuttle, but the shuttle drops you right there.
And I kinda don't like that the bus is going across.
It's gonna add to hassle a little bit,
but I do want it for park,
and the idea of a light show that the public gets
that also lures you in,
that's a weenie that's outside Disneyland.
It's like, well, what's the rest of this thing do?
That's interesting.
Yeah, I wonder what the vibe of that area,
like, is it gonna be like when you're in different parts
of Tokyo or Vegas or something,
where it's like a neon sign, essentially,
for Disneyland, I guess?
I think so.
Well, you know what it is,
is it's a big advertisement
that Tomorrowland is back in business.
I mean, it's definitely like, well, here's the thing.
I think there'd be enough separation between that
and then where you have to get train station Mickey Mouse
to get, there's space between those.
So it's not like, if it's kind of a different vibe
than the rest of Esplanade, I think it's okay.
I think it's cool.
Well, the way that the parking situation is described
is that there's gonna be a big parking garage,
and this is the thing, the Eastern Gateway Project,
that was called?
Yeah.
It was gonna be on the other side of Harbor,
and they were gonna build a big parking garage there,
and then you were gonna have all your security over there,
and then you were gonna walk across a bridge
just right into the Esplanade, no security,
so you can make that walkway a lot more narrow
all of a sudden. Yeah, yeah.
So you have more room.
It doesn't need like a row after row
of metal detectors, right?
Right, it needs nothing.
So it obviously needs to be big enough
for people to walk to and fro,
but you can have a lot of room on both sides to do stuff.
I think maybe with this plan,
you still get a little room for California Adventure
to expand, too.
So you could get a little, yeah,
but it could be 75, 25, even.
Yeah, yeah, yes, I like that,
and maybe some, you know, like I think we talked about
if Zootopia is a rumor over there, that's cool,
you get a little extra Zootopia.
What if they did something we neglected
in the bedding episode?
There's people who think and want
that maybe we get a Monsters, Inc. door coaster.
That's been for, I think it's been 20 years
we've not heard about that door coaster.
I don't see any reason other than it'd be fun
to think about that it would be now,
but like imagine if you sort of,
what if you did a better, bigger Monstropolis
over there in DCA?
That's fine.
I just want, I don't want Avatar,
I don't want Pandora to be stifled.
We already said this. We need room to breathe.
Why would that go there?
That doesn't make any sense.
We might find out tomorrow that it is there.
I will be shocked if that happens.
It doesn't feel right.
That feels very online rumor that it's not really.
Jason liked it, but I thought that was wild.
No, I don't like it.
It's the fact that he kept calling it an experience
and not an attraction.
Well, there is an attraction.
But we're getting, no, we've got concept.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
A boat ride.
I want a lot of room for that thing.
That needs to be where it has room to breathe.
Well, it's gotta be the sea, not the, you know.
Yes, they need room to splash and swim free
and experience all the wonders of life
with the great mighty Tolkien.
We need some Tolkien animatronics.
Oh, if we get a physical, a real Pyacon.
I'll be happy to visit any Pyacon,
but the ability to hug Pyacon would certainly.
Oh.
Well, this isn't blue-skying Avatar, sadly.
I know, I know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I could change plans.
No more Beauty and the Beast.
It goes over there.
That's technically in my confines.
You could go like a nod to Disneyland,
like the storybook boats.
Storybook canal boats.
You could go into a Tolkien's mouth, Pyacon's mouth,
or you could take inspiration from Islands of Adventure
when you used to be able to meet the Triceratops
and you could pet.
Like, ah, Pyacon is coming for his daily hello.
He's coming for his little pets.
That relaxes me so much,
thinking about being able to go and love Pyacon.
To do a Pyacon encounter.
Tell him my darkest secrets.
I can trust you with this.
Isn't that right, boy?
It's like you're the little girl in Once Upon a Time
in Hollywood and you like whisper,
you're the best Pyacon I've ever seen.
Pyacon starts sobbing like DiCaprio.
Okay, so where was I?
Oh, okay, so yeah, that's that big initial.
That's the big exciting start.
It gets you, we get extra space.
It takes you out of the park,
but from there, the ride turns back into Tomorrowland
speeds all through Disneyland's eastern half
over the two main show buildings in Tomorrowland,
on Tomorrow Avenue.
A dramatic curve across the hub
that serves as the entry arch for Tomorrowland 3055.
Show scene tunnels that revitalize long unused spaces
like the second floor of the Starcade.
You'll crisscross around the monorail tracks
and even take in a dizzying loop
all the way around the Matterhorn.
Wow.
Yeah, imagine that big loop.
You feel like inches away from it.
How about that?
So you'll see that from Main Street, obviously.
Oh, I guess you could.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, why not?
You could see the Astro Orbiter from Main Street
and it stinks.
True.
Let's get something cool.
It doesn't make any sense to see,
that's the spirit to me is like,
doesn't make any sense to see a mountain from Main Street,
but why not?
Hey, doesn't make any sense to see a castle from Main Street,
but we're making it all happen.
Is there any way you could theme the outside of it
to look more Matterhorn, like it belongs,
when you're seeing the Matterhorn from a certain angle.
Like a slalom tunnel of some kind.
Yes, a tunnel of some kind.
Like, you're worried about a clash.
I am worried about a clash.
Over there, that's a fair note.
Well, then I'm glad I didn't take it all the way.
I was thinking, here's, you wanna get a really blue sky?
Yeah.
Matterhorn rebuilt from the ground up.
I was thinking about it.
I don't know if that counts, it's kind of fantasy land,
but yeah, you've mentioned it,
it's one of those structural things.
What if we do it now?
What if it's the sturdiest building ever built?
It's got room for a properly working Yeti.
We get the Yeti in there.
And, you know, abominable-ified, whatever.
But I was thinking,
Lufthron light cycles go through the Matterhorn.
Yeah, it'd be awesome.
Yeah, okay, well, if you're in favor of it,
let's do it. Well, with this version
where it's been rebuilt,
then you can really kind of hide it
in the way I'm thinking.
So it won't be so, like, why is there a space motorcycle
going in front of the Matterhorn
when I'm looking at it from Main Street?
I agree with you, except that's another,
as I was starting to say, I think that's, you know,
why is there a train going through a dinosaur world?
Why was there, I mean, Skyway is kind of like Swiss chalet.
I think, actually, the spirit of light cycles
go through the Matterhorn is what's missing.
I think that is, like, original Disneyland thinking
and your wedding, flashy things.
Yeah, Skyway went through it, yeah.
You know what you're saying.
And if you're really that concerned,
you put, like, a video wall,
you make it look like a video wall
for, like, a Grand Budapest hotel-style funicular
going up the Matterhorn,
but it's really the light cycles going inside the tunnel,
you know? Oh, okay.
Yeah, I don't know the pitch on, like, how to mask it at all,
but the more I think about it,
the more I'm like, I just wanna proudly have things
that don't quite match,
because I think there's great moments
in Disneyland attraction combining
that don't quite line up, and I think it's great.
It's like a child's imagination
when the X-Men meet the G.I. Joe and they meet the turtles.
That's right.
When a cowboy plays with a spaceman
and a Mr. Potato Head and a dinosaur.
Well, there we are.
And it's the most magical combining
of all these universes altogether.
I'm trying to think what light you would expect,
like a red flare light.
So it's almost like when the bike goes around
and hits into the Matterhorn, it almost turns red.
So it's almost like you see a flare
coming off the mountain in the distance.
Oh, sure.
Like somebody is seeking rescue?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
Something like that.
Because I guess when you first described it,
I was almost like, okay, it just kinda goes in front of it.
But yeah, if you could do something that from the distance
looks like it's kind of themed to the Matterhorn more,
and it gives it some energy,
and then obviously when you're riding it
and you're seeing it, it's just you're going through,
you're on a space motorcycle, you're on an internet motorcycle.
I mean, I hear you.
There's something weird about it,
but maybe it's a good kind of weird.
I just think, for whatever reason,
I'm hung up on far away seeing it
and it not looking right.
Blue sky, no bad ideas.
I'm not saying it's a bad idea.
There's also, I guess, a version where,
but it also does not, maybe not from the hub,
but do we not get already monorail right now?
Monorail doesn't make sense next to Matterhorn, technically.
That's true, yeah.
Yeah.
That's true.
I don't know.
I think it's worth an adjust.
You're not wrong, but my argument,
just to try to fight for it, might be fuck it,
let's do it and be legends.
I think the electric flow is very kind of besetic
with the weight of the snow is often, snow and ice,
often portrayed as blue and white.
The new building of Matterhorn,
going in and out of it, though I'm on board for,
I was just sort of thinking of other ways to make it look.
To bring that back, that a ride goes through.
For whatever reason, I was hung up on the old Matterhorn
just sort of having a Tron thing in front of it,
whatever reason.
Okay, so somehow through does it.
I'm almost surprised that that,
okay, well then we're doing that.
All right, new Matterhorn, yetis in there
and light cycles go through it.
Sure, yeah, yeah, great.
Hell yeah.
They'll blend it, they'll do something good.
That's for them to do, the engineers.
Anyway, this is an e-ticket and visual spectacle
that pumps life through all of Tomorrowland and beyond.
But by making the light cycles kind of the,
now that's the track that weaves through all of Tomorrowland.
Are we now ignoring the need for a mellow,
slow-moving, family-friendly experience?
I say hardly because Buzz Lightyear's Astro Blasters
will say goodbye, what was the phrase?
Glowing away.
I'm gonna use that.
Like the parade.
Astro Blasters is glowing away forever
to make way for a brand new journey
through the world of WALL-E.
WALL-E is coming to My Tomorrowland
in WALL-E's Cosmic Directive.
Feel free to, we'll workshop this.
I couldn't quite land on one,
but the word directive's part of the movie.
Guests will follow WALL-E and Eve's journey
from Earth to space and back aboard the Axiom
and the returning pet,
and even go past the events of the film
to see how WALL-E and his robot pals
revive Earth with plant life.
Imagine a pleasant, slow-moving dark ride
that takes you to space
where an adorable, creaky-voiced pal
uses his healing touch to turn a planet green.
Oh, interesting.
The merchandising makes itself,
like WALL-E or Eve holding a little plant.
And if you, Jason, I know that you like to bring,
or want to bring little plants home from theme parks.
If you could do it in a boot,
in a WALL-E boot, that's, you know what?
That's a good little merchandise opportunity.
That's a really good one.
I think this lived entirely in Club 3,
the notion presented by Griffin, not me,
that people liked, they liked it.
The notion that living with the land
gets a nice, subtle WALL-E overlay
that uses this, because WALL-E is the bridge
between technology and future and plants.
He ties it all together.
It could be subtle, it could be nice,
it could be additive,
and then you go home with your boot
with a little simple plant in it.
Cool, cool.
I didn't even think about that aspect of it.
That is great, and that is not just like,
with apologies to the star speeder,
which sounds great, and everything like it,
that's not just a piece of plastic.
Now you go home and you're making nature happen
where you live.
This is beautiful, is what I think of it.
Okay, okay, well, then I'm, oh yeah, go ahead.
Does WALL-E have any new character you've created
that's like a teacher of his or anything?
Oh, shoot.
Eric.
WALL-E needs your help.
Not Eric.
Eric's on mine.
Oh, okay.
Or Eric's Figment's brother.
He's not WALL-E's teacher.
It's a different character.
Okay.
I would like a very stiff Andrew Stanton
to do a pre-show video.
We don't have much time, we have to be quick.
WALL-E needs your help.
Only you can help WALL-E.
He would love that.
He's a Parks guy, isn't he?
Did he write the Mark Davis giant coffee table book,
I think?
Oh, really?
Something like that.
One of the Pixar guys worked on it.
I think he's got it in him to be as charismatic
as Steven Spielberg.
I believe so.
Which is to say, limited,
but that's what I love is the limited.
Yeah.
Okay, so the ride's exit could perfectly transition
into a stacked hydroponic garden.
I'm going a little living with the land here
that forms a lush environment
for a re-imagined galactic grill,
I think, to Marlin Terrace, whatever you're calling it.
Still quick service,
but now serving entirely sustainably grown food.
We're eating healthy there now.
It's fast, but it's healthy,
and they have to commit to it.
They can't say they're doing that
and then make the food get worse as it goes.
But it's like good, fresh, farm-grown ingredients.
Let's turn that into a good restaurant
that is the aftermath.
And in the, you know what?
It's not consumerist.
That's the message of WALL-E, right?
It can't be a gift shop other than getting the plant
in the boot.
It has to take you into,
I mean, it's consumerist because you're in Disneyland
and you're buying food at a restaurant,
but it's not a gift shop.
It's a place where you go eat from the earth, you see,
which WALL-E has made possible for you.
Beautiful.
You should make available the boot a la carte,
the boot with seeds,
just in case people don't want to lug soil home.
Oh, sure.
But the boot a la carte,
especially for international travelers,
might have restrictions on bringing plant life
into their country.
This is a very, very good thing that you thought of.
A good logistical issue,
and I really like the phrase boot a la carte.
A lot of good stuff happening over there.
Well, it's what I end up catching down at the pond
when I'm not catching the ailes.
I wish they'd throw in French fries and coleslaw,
but it just don't happen.
Now, I've missed one aspect of this attraction,
the ride vehicle.
The ride vehicle is an updated and restored people mover.
The people mover is the ride vehicle in the WALL-E ride,
allowing a high capacity relaxing experience
for the whole family.
This is a ride with heart,
the dreams of a better future for our planet.
But it's not the only heart in Tomorrowland 3055,
and for that we turn to the long ignored,
but not destroyed Magic Eye Theater.
The fact is I can't do, I can't blow it up.
I can't make a new Space Mountain
because I love that area of that Space Mountain atrium
with the big metal bars that feels like an 80s airport.
I love it too much.
It's too much core memory for me.
I wanna make it work.
That's why we got some of Barcade in there.
And then what we have is a world class venue
that will no longer be limited to previews of movies
that have been out for years.
In fact, it will no longer be limited to movies at all
because it will now be home to a little attraction
called Plekdu's Fantastic Intergalactic Review.
I'm getting a lot of Tomorrowland 2055 in here
and it's not just due to nostalgia,
nostalgia for what never was.
I think it can work now today.
And I don't think that has to be carousel theater.
I think, honestly, you have to build
less animatronics this way,
but you are still building animatronics.
God damn it, of course you are.
This is a new country bear, jamboree type
animatronic and film show.
You could still screen it,
but let's update those screens,
teeming with aliens and robots
from across the Disney universe.
One thing we have to figure out is who is Plekdu?
What is Plekdu?
And I've decided that Plekdu is the ringleader
of this whole thing and he is part of the same species
as Skippy from Alien and Counter.
Here we go.
Yes, he is a Skippy.
His, apparently, his species,
here's what's happening.
My phone, or sorry, my laptop has autocorrected
so much of the, in doing this,
I had to teach my computer what Autopia is
and what Plekdu is.
It's trying to tell me that these aren't words,
but they are words.
I'm teaching my computer a lot.
My phone tried to correct Chu Chu to Chop Chop.
And I'm like, I must have typed Chu Chu before.
I need to know the context in which you were trying
to send a message to someone with Chu Chu.
Great question.
Jane was sending me a tweet about how there's
a tiny, big Thunder Mountain playset
you can buy at Tokyo Disney now.
Oh, I saw that.
And I wrote back Chu Chu.
Very good.
This is a text for the ages.
Anyway, I was, this thing was trying to autocorrect
the species that Skippy is, which is,
I can say proudly, Fluthmagoon cliffhugger.
That is the species now we know.
Somehow it didn't come up when we talked
about alien encounter years ago.
So, this cliffhugger, despite his small stature,
is the most revered musical mind in this or any galaxy.
And using the power of teleportation,
Plekdu has prepared an incredible show featuring
all the greatest musicians and performers
across the known universe.
This is now a show, a review, that features Sonny Eclipse.
Whoa!
He's in it.
You said him before, Max Rebo.
Max Rebo's in it, they own it, he's in it.
The Cantina Band is in it, why not?
Figuring Dan, they own it.
Why was there not a show that puts all this stuff together?
I hear you.
Here's where, let me take a deep breath
and say that the main backing band,
the wrecking crew of this show, will be Hooter,
Heidi and Odie, Major and Minor Domo, Fuzzball,
Captain Eo's pals, who all play music
and turn into instruments at the end of Captain Eo.
It's the theater where Captain Eo happened.
This will be a great band, we know that they can bring it,
and they will finally be freed from the tyrannical clutches
of their problematic captain, free to do their own thing.
This was a thing I thought about too.
Oh man, they don't work for him anymore.
It's like, I guess we could just make a new movie
with a different Captain Eo in there.
That was a pitch I was thinking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but it's, I don't know.
Let's just take these characters, they're just,
they're drums, they're living keyboards now.
Unless you think that this is only for dorks
and nostalgic for the 80s, this can also be a vessel
to tie together all kinds of Disney IP.
The Toy Story aliens could be in it, Zerg can be in it,
Zerg can do a song, let's let Zerg do a song.
Baymax, Stitch can do an Elvis song.
They own the Muppets, they could have the Yip-Yip aliens.
Put the Yip-Yips in it, they'd do some Yip-Yip song.
Pigs in Space?
Yeah, yeah, sure, yes, yes, and you know what,
and it doesn't all have to be, they don't all have
to have a song associated with them.
I think we can draw from the Disney library.
Well, hey, why not do original stuff too?
I mean, there's lots of possibilities musically here.
Hey, you know who's an alien?
The Navi Shaman song.
What if the Navi Shaman song showed up in her own thing?
Oh my God.
Yeah, yeah.
She could do a duet with Zerg.
I would love to see Zerg in a full tuxedo,
pulling a Seth MacFarlane and singing some,
like singing Beyond the Sea or something.
Yeah, yeah, well, what's like a good, you know,
I mean, Randy Newman is the soundtrack of the Toy Story
world, you know, like a really heavy, I don't know,
Living Without You or something sung by Zerg.
Who had to go without his son for so many years.
It's so hard.
Musically, I mean, this could be a way,
I wanna tie together the whole sci-fi Disney space averse.
You could do like the Universe of Energy song.
Oh yeah.
Epcot music could be part of this.
You know what could be part of this?
Also paying tribute to the legacy of this very spot,
Halix, we could do Halix songs.
They own the Halix songs.
It's amazing, like to finally use,
it's such a like fucking movie previews for years
in the place where Halix and Captain EO happened.
We're fixing this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
I thought about Halix too,
but I was like, they wouldn't do it.
I know they would, but I don't know,
they pay attention to stuff.
The documentary is a huge hit.
That was a, that's a massive YouTube thing.
People bring that up to me.
That's been a way to like reconnect with people
who I haven't seen in years.
I saw you in that Halix documentary.
That's wild that that is a thing that's getting around.
And I'm so happy, rightfully so.
Matthew, Kevin did such a great job.
But anyway, Halix can be here.
Where else could it build but Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow?
Now we're revitalizing all of these things that they own
and they could be doing something with.
Like a Skrillex version of Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow.
That's of course.
Yes, let Skrillex go to town on that baby.
Finally make it a good song, right Jason?
Yeah.
We're trying to needle you in failing.
We could really, not in the history,
you could get Devo 3.0 in here.
Even younger children singing the hits of Devo.
Animatronic Devo 3.0.
And yet somehow, and this is not an alien thing,
but does this not feel like a,
if we're gonna have lots of alien races
and different types of robots all working together
and singing together in harmony,
would not a great way to sum this all up be,
if we listen to each other.
Let's do that, let's do that.
Eye to Eye is the finale.
I think they need a permanent spot
for Eye to Eye somewhere in the parks.
They've got a Muzak version of Eye to Eye
playing in Toontown.
Really? Yeah.
Great, great.
And there's others, some like Muzak version of like.
Is that in the queue or is that like out in the.
Out in the.
That's out in the grass.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
They have like DuckTales and Chip and Dale Muzak themes.
Oh cool.
And Mickey Mouse Clubhouse songs,
which now I'm very aware of.
Oh, okay.
Hot Diggity Dog, Bye, They Might Be Giants.
Oh. Hey.
Which plays on the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Wow, wow, wow.
Okay, okay.
Anyway, this is gonna of course also be installed
at Epcot's Magic Eye Theater.
We don't have to limit ourselves to,
I mean space wise, who fucking knows,
but we'll figure it out, they'll figure it out.
It also, some of it could be screens.
If we go really good screens.
Sure.
If we go born-stuntacular screens, maybe now we,
I don't know, if we're limited in space,
it could be a mix of animatronics
and just really good screen technology.
Also, here's a thought too.
If we're, of course we all love this.
It's very 80s, 90s.
If ultimately, somehow this is not seized upon by the world,
I have another idea.
Because to do this right,
you'd have to do a full refresh of the seating
and the sound for this theater.
You'd put immersive speakers next to every seat.
During the day, this would create incredible quality
for the music for Plectu's Intergalactic Review.
But at night, it could enable an entire second show.
Imagine a Monsters After Dark night only,
perhaps Halloween only, or maybe it expands.
But imagine if the same space passed a certain hour
transformed into an experience meant only for adults
and the bravest of children.
A re-imagined alien encounter.
Oh wow, this theater.
In the same theater, in this theater.
I guess that had harnesses before, but whatever.
I think you'd re, I don't know,
you could discombobulate it.
Just do something new with it.
But sort of that idea,
and I haven't fleshed this out thoroughly,
but imagine if now it finally is featuring the true alien,
now the property of Disney,
as it was meant to be in this neck of the park.
The xenomorph is actually in
a new re-imagined alien encounter.
Wow.
Yeah, that would be very cool.
I also thought a little bit about some of that alien stuff,
but then I was,
I guess really like you could've put like a mind,
Buzz Lightyear could've done like a cartoon xenomorph.
Oh sure.
But then, a cute-ish xenomorph.
Are we aware real quick of the Haunted Mansion
Krusty reference that's been removed?
No.
In Haunted Mansion Holiday, on one of the boxes
where like the Jack in the Box pops out,
there's a kind of haunted-looking Krusty the Clown
on the box, and people pointed it out right away.
Oh, this is a Simpsons reference in a Disney park.
In the Haunted Mansion, people pointed it out right away,
three or four days later, gone.
Wow.
Jeez, I wonder what does that mean.
I don't know.
Wait a minute, is the Tim Burton Batman Returns duck in there?
The tiny toy duck.
Is it weird?
Do you know about this?
In the Haunted Mansion?
In Haunted Mansion Holiday,
there's a small duck that looks like
the Penguin's giant duck.
I did not see that.
It's been there for years.
Oh.
What?
Yeah.
But is it just a duck-looking thing?
It looks like the duck.
Okay.
It looks like the vehicle that the Penguin.
So it's a little reference,
it's because Tim Burton produced the movie.
It's a little nod, because Tim Burton, yeah.
Oh.
Produced the movie.
Oh wait, I get a second comment.
But it's sort of like the Mr. Limpet Fish.
Right, it's not official, yeah, yeah.
It's not official enough, and it's,
I see.
You know what I mean?
Mr. Limpet yet, the character is on the Snow White,
or Snow White, it's been a long record, I guess.
A Little Mermaid ride.
A Little Mermaid.
Yeah.
Oh, they don't, and they don't own Limpet.
That's a brazen cut.
Wow, wow.
Yeah, so he's just, he's not lit up,
Mr. Limpet, on the Little Mermaid ride,
and you have to know where to look.
And that's definitely one of my top.
Grab the person next to me by the arm,
and shake the arm, and tell them,
look, it's Mr. Limpet, the character of Mr. Limpet.
The time-out's played.
And they're like, what is that?
Yeah, of course.
Let go of me.
I was born in the 1980s, what is that?
What's wrong with you?
Are you a time traveler?
Your daughter just responds with, eh.
So, brand new attractions, revitalized favorites
from Tomorrowland's past and never built,
light speed and slow speed, thrills and heart,
it's all waiting in Tomorrowland 3055,
my blue sky presentation.
That felt, I felt emotional writing this.
I bet.
Even just imagining that any of the,
I wanted to go so deep in thinking about this
that maybe it like, lands in my dreams.
I wanna dream about some of this stuff so bad.
I want to too.
I mean, there's a lot of marquee attractions.
It's like, it's kinda like that moment at the movies
in the middle of summer, kind of about now,
where like, all the blockbusters
and some big indie surprise hits are playing at once.
And you're like, look at all these movies.
Yeah, well, that's how it should feel.
That's how it could feel.
I don't, you know, it's like some ideas they've sort of done.
It's some blue sky stuff.
And like, as I said, there's enough that I love
about what's there and what's been there
that I don't wanna fully blow it up.
I do ask you, and I mean, maybe just really quick,
if you were gonna fully blow it up,
if you had my assignment, what's the,
is there like, do you flash to this thing's out entirely?
I'm not joking when I say I level the whole,
everything goes.
Wow.
You rebuild space, I mean, the only thing is like,
keeping something that looks sort of space mountainish,
but I think I would rebuild the whole thing.
Yeah.
Because I would want whatever that Tokyo space mountain is.
Yeah, yeah, and maybe I should have,
but again, I love my atrium, it's weird,
and I love Star Tours, and I don't, you know.
I think there's a really good version
that's a full blow up, but it's not my version.
Yeah.
I wouldn't be honest.
Definitely, I would have blown the whole thing up,
it would have been like two stories,
like Tomorrowland 2055.
Yeah, well, you know what I thought about is that like,
at least the WALL-E side of things,
the former Buzz Lightyear side of things,
that that could be room for like a Tron tunnel or something,
like the show scene happens in there.
So you could, maybe you raise, like that one's gone,
Star Tours, I'm capin' though.
Right, and then, yeah, and then just,
yeah, I don't think, I think the Lagoon goes,
I think Autopia goes for me.
Yeah, yeah.
And then I think another full, PeopleMover is there,
it's New Space Mountain, I think there's,
I would add one more e-ticket
that would be like in a completely original e-ticket.
Yeah.
That's like, this is off the top of my head,
like some sort of like planetary exploration ride.
Okay.
Where you're like goin' through like, I don't know,
maybe like a crater, like an asteroid or something.
More of an on the ground sort of.
You're running into aliens and stuff,
and it could be kinda scary, depending.
Could you be like in an astronaut training
and Gary Sinise is there?
Gary Sinise could be there, yes.
And you're in a G-Force, like?
We call it Mission Space, but it could be good,
and it could be more of a dark ride
where you come upon aliens
and like you're now exploring the surface of a planet.
What about like Journey to the Center of the Earth,
but it's in space?
Sure.
The way, like those cool caves that you.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know what, God, that's really good.
That is a future aesthetic that isn't mined anywhere,
is like craters underground.
Here's an interesting, this is again,
I haven't thought this through to where,
but if you could have it where it was almost like
a Tower of Terror ride system,
and you could kind of float almost
and make it feel like you were zero gravity.
If there was a way, I guess maybe Kuka Arm
is the way to do it, but a Kuka Arm
that wouldn't so kind of aggressively move you around,
if it could almost like,
a Kuka Arm that was really gentle,
that could kind of float you.
Serene feeling.
Yeah, so it could kind of float you in front of things
and you could get jump scares that way,
but then you could get like cool,
like feeling like you're zero gravity
where you're kind of jumping.
That feeling that you would always,
when you see like the footage of the people on the moon,
where you're like, oh, that would be so cool to be jumping
and you'd have like 10 seconds of hang time,
something like that.
Like I would have gone with another, yeah,
like a completely original.
The gravity, representing the gravity
like on the ground on the moon.
Something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Because I'm obsessed with that patent for that spider,
probably a Spider-Man ride that was suspending you
from the ceiling on kind of like a row of chairs
that would have simulated swinging like Spider-Man,
because it's when we talk about like,
well, what would you want from the property
with Spider-Man?
It's like swinging is the coolest thing
if you could actually feel like you were swinging
in a practical city,
which is what it looked like that ride would have been.
And I guess it gets like.
Well, getting a good upper body workout
is also a very cool thing.
Well, that's true too.
Yeah, having really warm down shoulders.
It's pretty fun.
Sure.
But yeah, even though I do love the stuff
you're talking about in Tomorrowland,
I'm like, I'm envisioning like crazy new Tomorrowland.
Well, I almost like, you know,
I almost feel like I landed at not fully,
but I had a lot of like logic in mind
and in keeping infrastructure.
So I almost feel like mine,
if there was any failing in what I did,
it was that the, like,
it was like maybe somewhere between mid and blue sky.
I do like the dreaming of,
no, yeah, it's just, you know,
to personal taste, I suppose.
But yeah, something fully new.
I think I am so hung up on what they've wanted to do.
I do, I love all of the never built Tomorrowland stuff,
almost like more than what I think
I could come up with myself.
Well, I love so much of these ideas.
I think reusing that UFO abduction drop tower is like,
I think yours were a lot of e-tech kids
and honored Disney history
and then no idea ever abandoned, you know.
What we both were doing
was trying to like,
cause there's so much stuff that's gone
that we miss or miss cause it didn't exist
and trying to like encapsulate that sign,
trying to like forge that in iron
so it can't go away.
It has a presence like there forever
or like just like embalm it.
So like we can still get little tastes
of all the stuff we like from the history of Disney.
Cause it feels like so much of that weird stuff is gone.
So just trying to sneak it in here and there.
Yeah, we're still very IP brand.
We like we need,
we know even in a blue sky version, you like want that.
But I do love some of this IP.
That's the thing,
Metron, I love the aesthetic of at least.
I do love Wally, like of all the areas,
I think there are a lot
and some Toy Story Buzz representation, you know.
I don't need it to be free of IP.
That said, I love your crater.
It's just off the top of my head or whatever.
I know, you don't even have notes out.
Can you put the guitar down?
We don't have it hooked up to the audio.
You can't sing.
I'm just strumming G, A minor, D minor.
I'm just feeling it.
I feel like we should wind it down,
but I mean, I don't think there's any winning or losing here.
No.
The only losers will be all of us
when they don't stay anything close
to any of what was said, not even the sod.
I actually, trying to be faithful to current company,
I have been laid off.
I've been kicked out of the Slack channels.
You got fired from your fictional job?
I was only 10.99 anyway, so.
It's not like an official firing.
Yeah.
Oh man, so you didn't get insurance anyway.
It's just freelance.
Covered California actually got worse
because of the increased revenue, increased income.
Boy, oh boy, I am so sorry for your fake struggles.
Sorry, so many thoughts in my head at once.
What is the most logical thing
that they'll announce of all three of these pitches?
Is there one thing that one of us has said
where you go, well, that is gonna happen?
Is there a single thing?
I think some, I don't think they will.
The fact that we both landed there,
I think something with Carousel and Space Restaurant
or something, or it's a bar up there,
you build higher or you make that building cooler,
they should, I don't know if they will,
but I think if they actually are gonna redo all of Tomorrowland,
now I'm like, that we both landed there means
maybe they will too.
Maybe, yeah.
But, yeah, you're right.
Of what was said, what do we think actually will?
Ant-Man could be the answer.
This ride is, now I've watched it, it's nonsense.
It took me a while to realize,
oh, Ant-Man, you're shrunk down.
They still have the rule
that Marvel's in California Adventure, but.
I guess.
That's like an easy thing they've got designed
that would fit and it would be an announcement
of something somewhat exciting to.
I don't know.
I think it's gotta be from yours, right?
What do you think from yours, Mike?
Well, from mine, I mean, I don't,
I don't think they're gonna do my Buzz Lightyear idea,
but I think they could potentially announce
just other Star Tours levels.
They could, it's possible they could just throw those in.
I think it's funny we all got rid of Buzz,
which I don't know that they're guaranteed to.
Well, I kept Buzz the character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I just changed it.
But we all agreed something there,
which I don't think we've like.
Yeah, that's true.
It's not that I dislike the ride,
it's just like there's still possibilities.
It needs something, it needs a refreshing.
There's little juice, something.
It needs some juice.
Yeah.
Some fresh juice.
It's hard, I cannot come up with what,
I mean, it's something to carousel building,
but I'm not sure what it is.
Maybe.
Yes, yes, it is something,
if you're right, it's something there.
Is there any possibility that Tron is there
and not in the new?
This is the whole thing,
I'm looking at Google Maps and I'm looking
at the footprint of Tron in Magic Kingdom,
and I'm like, it's so big.
That's why I went with a deconstructed.
I like Tron as people movers.
Kind of both of our ideas in different ways.
I really love that idea.
I think they should do it.
And again, I want as much,
I'm just like, let's do shit here,
so then it's all free over in Disneyland Forest.
It still feels like if they do a rear,
like a bridged Tron or a different Tron,
it still feels like they're gonna have to build a lot.
It doesn't feel like there's an easy plot of land
for them to build this new Tron
because it still needs long stretches for it to go fast.
So, I mean, your idea into the Esplanade,
it makes a lot of sense if they're gonna,
if it's gonna coincide with the expansion of that area.
So, yeah, I guess it's possible,
but I was just looking at it going,
ah, it feels like that's a lot of work for them
to figure out where to put Tron here.
I don't think you can just do regular light cycle run.
You can't, I don't think it's possible.
That's right, I want them to do something bold.
But yes, then it's an expensive thing, I think,
because then they gotta build
either on top of infrastructure there
or they gotta go behind into different areas,
and I don't know which buildings are necessary.
And then the train stuff is right there.
There's like a road, there's like a service road,
and then the train stuff is right there.
And you're at Harbor pretty fast, too.
It's a tough gambit.
Listeners, we had to think so hard about all these things.
It's tricky.
Oh, the maps, all of us.
It wasn't, yeah, you know what?
It was a struggle for all of us.
Jason's the only one who got fired, but otherwise.
I try my best, I mean, I'll still put it on my resume.
You should, yeah, you should.
It's a bad time to look for work
in Southern California entertainment industry, but.
Cissier, you personally redesigned and painted
all of New Tomorrowland at Disneyland.
Yep, yep, I'm willing to start from the bottom
and I'm hard, my, you know, my greatest weakness
is actually that I'm too hard of a worker.
That's smart, that's a good tip.
I care too much.
That's a good thing to say when you're in an interview.
It's a tip, good tip.
All right, well, that's good because
we got a lot of sod to sew.
Well, you are hired as a sodsman.
Okay, well, at least that has benefits
in the Landscaper's Union, right?
Of course, yeah.
Okay.
We've undermined the union a little bit,
don't worry about it. Oh, no.
Well, we will see, we will see tomorrow,
if tomorrow, if there is anything close
to what we have discussed for Tomorrowland.
Yes, and real quick, I'd like to say,
why not do this concept with other lands?
Ooh, you're right, you're right.
May as well.
I enjoyed it, I hope the listener did too.
I absolute well, that's, hey, listeners,
what do you want us to,
you know what, yeah, because any,
even the best land could use it, you know?
I'll demolish almost any land.
Yeah, yeah.
It's interesting, like, make it better,
I'll try to make it better,
that's the whole goal, I think,
if you get the, if you draw,
I think we'll keep this structure,
and if you draw the special blue sky
where you could demolish everything,
just try to make it better.
Yeah, I'm helping, I'm just here to help.
Just here to help.
And you know what, building our dream
Disneyland four words is also probably,
I think we should do that too.
Yeah, yeah, I think we should.
All right, well, hey, new ideas opened up.
I hope you enjoyed this mental exercise.
I hope that you're sad that none of what we said will happen.
I hope that there is,
I hope that there is, like, the Avatar onboarding.
I don't get to actually live on Pandora,
and I hope that all of you are upset
that some of these cool things will never happen.
I know I am.
I have to say goodbye now to Plectu
and a show with all my friends,
and Wally is ET.
So anyway, hope you're sad,
but otherwise you survived Podcast The Ride.
For three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast The Ride The Second Gate,
where we recently bet on D23.
See if any of it came true.
Or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three,
Lorcona with Nick Weiger, coming soon.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Boy, oh boy.
Imagine, like, truly if they say nothing now.
Wow.
Imagine.
I hope not.
Everyone wished so hard.
Imagine if you will.
They said nothing.
You know, the story is no story
because what is better story than a blank piece of paper?
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at foreverdogteam and liking our page on Facebook.