Alright, finally we're gonna talk about something I like on the show.
Oh wow, finally.
It's unprecedented for Scott Gertner to get his way, Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
I'm here, I'm happy for you, finally it's been three years or so.
Oh I know, it really, that's how it feels, it's been three years of suffering through
arduous materials like Jay Leno and the Beach Boys and a Kenny G trip report and the just
very taxing task of getting to Blue Sky, Tomorrowland.
It's been a rough run for old Scotty and I've finally caught a break here on my birthday
shot episode.
Well, happy birthday, finally.
Yeah, it's about time some recognition comes my way.
You guys are in the dark currently on what I have chosen, which is a fun way to do it,
I don't think we always have to do it this way, but I figured why not, and let you guys
chill out, you know, like this is, you know, birthday is a time to give back, too.
That's right, yeah.
And there's no reason to say this, but boy was there a heated political conversation
going on right before we started, and I love that I get to take you guys on a trip to something
that has nothing to do with any of that, although it is about, it is a topic that is about America,
but in a way that I think is easier to get behind.
That celebrates two American art forms mashed together, maybe that gives you a guess or
a preview.
Sure, hopefully a lot less freaks, or at least the freaks that are like fun and pitchy.
The Houdini freaks that come out at night is kind of the sort of the area that I'm going
for.
That's what I didn't go for in considering an especially indulgent birthday episode.
Because Club 3 voted for a Beach Boys topic recently, I'm not doing Beach Boys 2, so thank
you for taking care of that for me and pairing it with Full House, an excellent pair.
The best, ah, the best wine and cheese pairing there could have been.
I really thought about, and I would plan a flag in the future for an episode about a
big passion of mine, which is legendary music producer and cockiest man on earth, David
Foster.
I feel like there's an episode there, but it's harder to wrap my head around than today's,
which came very naturally.
I've also, there's one more that I want to shout out, and maybe you put it in the category
of threaten, but the biggest swing I could have taken is something that I've had an obsession
with for a long time, which is a 1980s deep south soul singer named Marvin Sees.
You ever come across Marvin Sees or have I referenced Marvin Sees before?
I don't think so.
Kevin Tully knew what Marvin Sees was.
I think he was encouraging me off the ledge on this one, but I think the time's not now.
What's interesting about Marvin Sees is that his entire discography is all music that is
really blatantly about Cunnilingus.
Really?
Just like the most, not even, none of it, it's not double entendre, it's just straight to
the heart of the matter.
He has a song called I Ate You For My Breakfast.
Whoa.
Wow.
He has a song called Put Your Condom On Your Tongue.
Nice.
Yeah.
That's how you gotta be safe.
It's the same thing with my discography.
I'm gonna have to fucking sue this guy.
We hit you with this Jason Sings The Old Ones thing, but really the music you've been cooking
up all these years is blatant oral sex music.
Yeah.
Right.
I didn't want to start-
Go down with Jason.
You know, on the Bears, the new Bears episode, you said something about like three hosts
uncongerable with their sexuality, and I'm like, well, we're about to rock, but I want
to sidetrack it and go, well, two hosts.
Wow.
One of these big Jason brags.
I do read, and I am very comfortable.
All right, wait.
All right.
I'm changing it.
Well, one of us recognized our sexual beingness, you know.
All right.
Because it's my birthday and I can do what I want, I'm putting, I'm pushing some of this
to the side.
I would like, Jason, you would take one minute of what you would have said about sexual comfort.
Yeah, yeah.
You have one minute of space to talk about anything you want to say involving you in
sex.
Just that it's awesome, and I have a lot of fun, and it's a great way to communicate
and connect with your partner.
To be clear, Jason, Mike and I have both made children.
If that indicates anything about our feelings about sex.
We could have gotten it thrown across the room and somebody had, like, it could have
been artificial, I suppose.
Yeah, that's true.
We haven't actually, we haven't disclosed, yes.
The common artificial insemination technique of throwing it across the room will slap.
Well, that was, yeah, that was a colloquial way to refer to artificial insemination.
I interrupted, though.
You were saying that sex, this is news to me.
Oh, yeah, no, it just rolls.
I was a late bloomer, so, you know, still probably playing catch up.
Are you telling me, just to be clear, are you telling me that sex is a great way to
connect with my partner?
Because I've been looking for one of those.
Yeah.
This is news to me.
I've heard this for the first time.
I accidentally set the timer for an hour, so I guess you're going to have to finish.
Oh, no, you put it next to my head.
There's no way to fix it.
Would you, Jason, would you say you're a jealous, or not jealous, excuse me, upset that Kevin
Smith usurped your sort of feelings about this type of thing with his tweet, with his
famous tweet?
Oh, the famous tweet?
Yeah.
Was that something that you had tweeted before and you feel like he's just more famous than
you at the time?
Oh, yeah, it was stolen word for word.
Okay, all right.
Oh, jeez.
He just didn't want to threaten legal action, you know, he's more, he's got to be more
lawyered up than you.
I was already selling t-shirts that say clit brown t-teria.
Oh, I remember that now, yeah.
They weren't selling so well.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's your birthday.
I don't mean to usurp.
Also, you're probably, you're probably getting horned up talking about it, too.
Yeah, that's true.
We can't see, we can't see his leg is blocking his tent area.
We can't see how much of a pitch is happening.
Well, no, this is-
Happy birthday.
Oh, I'm very happy, but this is a birthday thing.
Anyway, well, Marvin sees is somebody for you.
Maybe that'll come up in the future.
But here's what, here's why I chose what I chose today is because somebody once asked
or somebody had an idea for a party where a bunch of people like, you act like it's
a conference.
It's like, you know, it's a bachelor party where everybody goes to a hotel or something.
But then the fake business of the party is that everyone has to do a presentation about
something and something that's fun enough that you feel like you could sort of, you
know, wouldn't be arduous to do it.
And I was like, you know what?
I know exactly what that would be if that, and that party hasn't happened.
So the party's happening now.
But something that's like a Ted talk that I could essentially do in my sleep.
And it is this.
And I think I've sort of alluded to wanting to do this on the show before.
And it is football wraps.
That is what we're doing today.
Right, right, right.
You recall football wraps being addressed in the past.
Great, great.
As I said, a mashup of two great American art forms.
Football's an art, but whatever.
I think you could say it's an art.
It's an American form of something.
And what I mean is that there was a trend in the late 80s with the rapid popularity
of rap music and of MTV of entire football teams putting out songs that are braggadocious
about their football skills.
I would venture a guess that everybody can think of one of these.
And for a long time, I was under the impression that there was one of these.
I didn't realize that it was an entire genre.
And that is where the obsession began is realizing that just the sheer volume of full
football team braggie rap music that's out there.
Kind of a cousin, I feel like, of what you did, Mike, for your birthday shot.
Oh, yeah.
And actors doing music kind of thing.
I think this is a fascination with everybody's, you know, people trying a form that is not
their inherently trained form and the fun that can come from that.
I would like to see Jason do a braggie rap about cunnilingus.
A really filthy Jason rap, yes.
I would be, I mean, I also don't want to just, I think that it'd be in my birthday power
to say, Jason, excuse yourself, go to the lobby and write that rap for an hour.
You put one hour on the clock and come back and do the going down rap.
Hey, he's done musical improv before.
He could do it right now off the top of his head.
I love doing musical improv.
You know that I'm very comfortable.
Yeah, something you're less comfortable with.
All right.
Well, it's really easy.
Just do it here.
Quick freestyle or rhyme of cunnilingus.
Oh, hmm.
When you're flying air lingus.
Don't go so fast and we'll all have a blast.
The joy it brings.
No, no, no, it has to rhyme with cunnilingus.
The joy it brings us.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Wow.
Yeah, that is good.
Oh, geez.
Well, even with your, you put a wholesome Mike-esque spin on a dirty Jason thought.
Boy, I like cunnilingus.
Boy, it's great to do it.
It's the joy that we get from it.
How far can this pleasure bring us?
These are.
You two are the music guy, you know.
With RBS.
This is what we bring to the show.
Two music guys and one fucking guy.
Freak.
Nasty little freak.
One fucking freak who thinks partners can connect via sexual activity.
You gotta get your testosterone tested.
We have to find out.
I, you know, I have had a lot of tests done.
I will have to ask the doctor.
Yeah, we gotta get it done.
We gotta get it done.
Are my T levels in there?
Oh, yeah.
In there?
In the results.
You have them already, you're wondering?
Because they give you, you can read so much in like the mind chart apps and stuff.
You send me a link to your mind chart.
I'll take a look.
My biggest birthday wish is to not hear about charts and quest diagnostics.
All right, fine.
But you want to hear about T.
So it's in the family.
I do.
But that's, I want to cut to the end result.
I don't even know how we got it.
Fine.
Well, we'll find out.
I'll go to the doctor's office and I'll look.
The U.S.C. medical system has a whole other similar variation of it.
Give me your doctor's phone number.
Give me your doctor's phone number and I will call after this and we will find out.
Here now, on the air.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'll just log in to the private messaging.
That's the most efficient way to get a hold of them.
Yeah, but it's less fun.
Okay.
I want to talk turkey with this guy.
All right.
Well, I got a whole page of phone numbers.
Look, I've been working with this guy for a long time.
Level with me.
What is the size of this guy's sack?
Yeah, I have some questions.
I have some other questions, yeah.
Sack size, I don't think necessarily, you know, figuratively maybe associates with T
levels, but.
It's about the motion of the ocean, not the flapping of the.
Of the sack.
Of the sacking.
How many, have you tested how many darts per minute his tongue can do, doctor?
I just want to know how, how athletic is his tongue?
Please.
My God, his tongue could be used to mix up medicines.
What's that, Mr. C?
Oh, yeah.
Like a centrifuge.
It's like a collider can destroy atoms.
Okay.
Look, well, not to distract from the macho men here in the room, but we're here to talk
about some incredible athletes doing a different kind of athleticism, and that's artistic and
musical.
So, you know, when I bring this up, what probably everybody goes to is the most famous
example of this by far, which is the Super Bowl shuffle, the song done by the 1985
Chicago Bears, who seemingly, and maybe you can speak to this, Mike.
I mean, this is right as you're born, but I don't know if there was still kind of like
crater a little bit in Chicago of the, like just the like overly sized pop culture impact
of this team, because it seems like kind of a couple years before the Bulls, who are bigger
than the city they're in, it's like people know Dick and Walter Payton and William the
Refrigerator Perry.
And so a lot of it's from the song, but I don't think they would have done the song
if there wasn't already.
Could you feel like still would you go into restaurants and like, all right, here's pictures
of Super Bowl shuffle.
Here's these guys.
Here's Dick.
I will say that I don't know that I knew the Super Bowl shuffle until later.
I knew who Dick was.
I knew Walter Payton.
I knew Refrigerator Perry, but it was not on my radar like the Bulls was.
I was very much stuck in my own world of anthropomorphic characters at this point.
And the real world was not so interesting, but they were around.
I remember them being around.
Sure.
Yeah.
I feel like in a VH1, I love the eighties kind of way.
Something like kind of like weird color that exemplifies the time.
Teddy Ruxpin, Rubik's Cube, that kind of thing.
Where's the beef?
Just eighties oddities.
It is very possible that you see the Super Bowl shuffle in there.
Yeah.
And it exemplifies the kind of song that I'm talking.
It sets the standard for what becomes a genre, certainly in the wake of this,
which is this kind of rap that's very, my name's this and I like to this.
Introductory rap, the kind of rap that is still what my dad thinks that it is,
which I find very charming because in this case, I need to be introduced to all of these people.
I don't know who they are.
Football is the sport that I follow the least by far.
And that's saying a lot.
So all of the names in this song, you know, Richard Dent and Mike Singletary,
people who are, they're icons to me entirely from their being in this song,
which I think I always knew about, but sometime in high school, I'm like,
I really need to meditate on this, on the Super Bowl shuffle.
This is such a funny, odd thing.
Also something in this song, it's in a lot of what is to come, saxophone.
There's definitely sax solos in a lot of them, as in all the best rap songs.
Yeah.
If we all just conjure all of what we think of the best hip hop songs ever made, probably sax solo.
Yeah, and the artier, maybe the artier ones these days have a sax in there.
They're probably, yeah, but I bet occasionally.
In the classic ones though, yes, you're correct.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, always.
Go through them all in your head.
Be a sax guy.
Yeah.
And also probably, you know, the toughest thing with these songs is like cutting it down, right?
There's so many, there's dozens of players on the team.
They can't all get a rap, even if they're all pretty short.
So probably you're getting eight to ten who get kind of like spotlight verses,
and then everybody else is on the back line pretending to play instruments in sunglasses
and having a ball back there.
Jason, just to be clear, Jason, have you ever like, you certainly know this thing or not?
I don't know.
Have you ever watched the Super Bowl shuffle?
Oh, yeah, a number of times.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
So, you know, I don't need to go into a lot of detail about this.
The Chicago Bears shuffling crew being fairly iconic, I feel.
But let me do, I'm also not going to play a clip of it for reasons that I will soon explain.
Okay, what I'd like to do, and I think I can do it, but maybe I'll fall on my face,
is I'm going to text you guys a list of everybody who does a verse in the Super Bowl shuffle.
All of the vocalists in the Chicago Bears shuffling crew.
Well, one of you pick a name, and I'm going to close my laptop so you know that I'm not cheating,
just to show you how deep-seated this is.
This is like a magic trick.
And I don't know if I can guarantee getting the whole thing, but I'm certainly going to try.
Just pick a name.
Steve Fuller.
Okay, wait.
I always forget how this one starts.
Okay, okay.
But then you picked one of my favorites, and you picked a white guy, which is very helpful.
Oh, good.
They say Jimbo is our man.
If Jimmy can't do it, I sure can.
This is Steve, and it's no wonder.
I drive like lightning.
It sounds like thunder.
So bring on Atlanta.
Bring on Dallas.
This is for Mike and Papa Bear Hallis, but I'm not here to feathers ruffle.
I'm just here to do a Super Bowl shuffle.
There you go.
Pretty good.
Got it.
I got it.
That's one of my favorites to do, I would say, because he has kind of the...
I believe what he...
And again, I'm just taking context from the song, because I don't know anything about the team.
I know that they won the Super Bowl, and they were a very good team.
Besides that, I don't know much.
I believe that...
I don't know.
I'm not even...
I think Jimbo is main quarterback, punky QB, Jim McMahon, and Steve is the backup quarterback, I believe.
It's kind of odd that a backup quarterback gets a verse in a team song.
That's a good point.
But I can see why.
This guy's got a...
He's got a Kenneth the Page charisma.
Kenneth the Page as a football player is a funny pitch.
That's a funny...
He's swimming in those shoulder pads.
Can I pick one?
Yeah, yeah, please.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Shut your laptop.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, thanks.
Mike Singletary.
I was a little bit worried about a mic coming up because I get confused in these and there's
two mics.
There's LA Mike, but this is Samurai Mike.
I'm Samurai Mike.
I stop them cold.
Part of the defense, big and bold.
I've been jamming for quite a while, doing what's right and setting the style.
Give me a chance, I'll rock you good.
Nobody's messing in our neighborhood.
We didn't come here looking for trouble.
We just came to do the Super Bowl shuffle.
Wow.
I mean, very impressive, regardless of what you might...
I had to think about it.
When I had this idea, I was like, the mics are what's going to trip me up, but I also
wanted to do it without literally running flashcards because that'd be an insane way
to spend my life and spend my birthday.
Nobody needs me to prove this that much, but okay, thank you for...
And excellent choices, too.
I think those are some of the...
The one that I...
Because I was going to just do...
Is it Gary Fencek?
Yeah.
Because I like his a lot.
He's got probably the voice most similar to mine with kind of like a twang and a little
bit...
He's just like hard diction.
It's Gary here and I'm Mr. Clean.
They call me Hitman.
Don't know what they mean.
I'm on my man.
One-on-one.
Buddies, guys, cover it down to the bone.
That's why they call us the 46 Zone.
Don't know what that is.
Don't know what it means, but I don't care.
This is like...
It's such a dip into...
I might as well just be hearing about what life is like on the other side of the world.
It doesn't matter to me.
It's like people singing English songs in Tokyo.
So, if that shows you my fondness for the song, and I've just loved any and all references
to it.
I remember there was an Onion article, like early Onion, that like fleshed out an entire
behind the music, like what was up...
A full musical ecosystem of the Chicago Bear Shuffling crew and solo careers that never
took place.
And my favorite part of that is that there's a guy...
One of them is named Willie Galt and he does a line, I'm as smooth as a chocolate swirl.
And Onion made up that he had a minor R&B hit with the song Chocolate Swirl.
That's what I'm smooth as.
The show got me obsessed with.
And I don't think I knew the song when I read it.
I'm just like, ah, all of these little phrases.
I love it.
I love that these guys did this.
I love that then you start looking into the history of it and that they did this months
before they were even going to be in the Super Bowl.
This is not a victory lap for winning the Super Bowl.
This was a cockiest call of a shot that we will be in it, we will win it, and we will
then do the Super Bowl shuffle.
Could you imagine if they had recorded this and then lost?
Oh my God, the humiliation.
Yeah.
Then, well, it's not quite the same because it's not the person who did it, but it would
be a similar feeling to when you watch the Lin-Manuel Miranda rap about Tim Kaine in
the membrane.
Oh yeah, yeah.
He's at some function.
What is the rest of that?
I mean, that's the one you remember the most.
Yeah.
Tim Kaine in the membrane.
Jason Chenoweth.
Tim Kaine in the brain.
And it was days before the election.
Yeah.
He also, he was doing a lot of election rapping because he went on SNL and passed by a framed
photo of recent host Trump and did a little rap about, never going to be president, never
going to be president.
No.
Weeks later.
So yeah, it's a dangerous game to call your shot via rap.
No, it's not anybody do any, I mean, I don't think anybody is going to do any cocky raps
at least not on the Democrat side.
This year, I don't think anybody's feeling too cocky.
He should rap for Trump this year to reverse, to reverse the like mojo.
Yeah, reverse the curse.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think get everybody, that it seems like probably the best way is to get everybody
who did Super Hillary's raps like Lin-Manuel and Lena Dunham.
Right, right.
That seems like the best way to insure Trump loss.
That's right.
Democratic raps, the most cursed genre.
Yeah.
Much, much more so than football.
That's Jason's birthday shot.
Democratic, yeah.
Democratic raps.
Ironically, the most sexless choice from who I guess we've determined is the most sexual
man.
I think I've settled on mine.
I had a few in my head, but I think I've decided.
Really?
It is unfortunately very wholesome.
It is not freaky at all.
It's not like porno or some porno with Jason Jordan.
No, it's not porno, no.
Tongue flicking.
That's just for me.
Okay.
All right.
Well, in that episode, we will acknowledge you as a non-sexual being.
Okay.
Also a non-sexual being.
A wholesome being.
So anyways, some things that you might not know about the Chicago Bears Shufflin' Crew.
One is the, I mean this song was such a massive hit.
This is like a million seller.
It was so huge, just far beyond the Chicago bubble to the point where it was nominated
for a Grammy in 1987 for best R&B performance by a duo or group.
That's crazy.
The Chicago Bears were all, I don't think they were there.
I don't think all of the Bears were at the Grammys in Texas rubbing shoulders with Quincy Jones.
That award incidentally was won ultimately by the song Kiss by Prince and the Revolution.
Okay.
Perhaps a superior song.
Maybe.
Even to equate top five groups of the year.
Well, you'd have to say Prince and the Revolution and you'd have to say a bunch of football players
wearing fedoras and sunglasses pretending to play the bass.
That's good.
They all should have gone to the Grammys and they all should have been wearing their jerseys.
And like pads.
Oh yeah, oh with, yes, and then tuxes over that.
That's great.
Yeah, yeah.
I would have said pads over the tuxes, almost like the Road Warriors, the wrestling tag team.
They had the big shoulder but they had spikes on them over their singlet or whatever.
Well yeah, that's, I really like it.
My only note is to how to get it fancier and my suggestion would be bow ties on every spike.
Yeah, okay, great.
Yeah.
That's the sharpest style I could possibly imagine.
The other thing that is interesting about this song is the long history of litigiousness surrounding it.
So this song, to quote Walter Payton in the first verse,
we're not doing this because we're greedy, the bears are doing it to feed the needy.
This was a charity song.
Right.
I think while the understanding was always that some percentage would go to the people putting it together
and to the bears themselves that the majority of it would go to charity.
Years go by and I don't think the money has gone to charity
and it becomes an issue for the Illinois Attorney General.
He has to get involved.
Wow.
And there's a discussion of, well we were thinking 50-50 split, how does that sound?
The Illinois Attorney General says, well the state standard is 75%.
Anything that's going to charity minimum is 75.
Meanwhile, the company that put it together had been thinking 15.
So nobody had any clue and then it was just settled.
They just gave like one big lump sum to what charity?
I'm not entirely sure.
But that was that and that closed it out and no more money was given to charity.
Meanwhile, the song continues to rake in a lot of dough.
It's oddly a big money generator.
And at some point six of the Shufflin crew had to get together and do the litigation shuffle and sue.
We are here to feather your ruffle.
They had to sue the company that put it together for like going back on their promise
and not continuing to give money and royalties to charity.
Wow.
Which was also a sticking point because individually they all got $6,000.
Every player in the song got $6,000.
Which was fine if the rest of the money is going to charity, but it wasn't.
So they're like either more to charity or pay us because this is neither here nor there.
Wow.
Also, litigiousness has come over the years from the song by the...
So the wife of the woman who put it together now controls the rights.
She appears in the video as a referee who blows the whistle when the characters...
The characters.
When the football characters are about to curse.
That's why some end up on their poop and it cuts to like she's doing a penalty.
So the female referee who is in the music video is now literally a whistleblower
for illegal use of the song that her husband put together.
This has left this strange world where the song is really hard to find.
It's out of print as a piece of music and as a video.
If it goes up on YouTube, it is probably pulled down very quickly with the announcement.
This video has received a copyright strike from female referee.
And I don't really want to say the name and I'll say why.
Because why do I know about any of this and the copyright strike situation?
Because she went after me.
Wow.
I had a run in with female referee.
Again, I don't...
Even behind a paywall, I want to be careful here because I've run afoul of this person.
You guys know and the listener might know that I did a video a while back called the Sex Offender Shuffle.
It is inspired by this area of video and music.
The idea is that it is a bunch of people who are not the best at rapping introducing themselves via rap.
But it is because they are registered sex offenders moving into a neighborhood.
And therefore, this video will reduce the need to have to do the awkward door to door.
We can just send the video to everybody so that they know what sex offenders are moving into their neighborhood.
This was a big hit for me and continues to be.
It's got kind of this odd wave of views.
It just like belongs to the internet now.
It's so far outside of anything I can do with it or it even being attributed to me.
But if the listener knows it or if you haven't seen it, a lot of familiar faces.
I'm in it. Aaron's in it. Nick Mundy is in it.
Playing a bad man before he became a bad man.
In real life, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
On this show.
With his sector shuffle.
So anyways, I mean, you know, the Super Bowl shuffle was an influence, you would say, on my video, The Sex Offender Shuffle.
But it is not the music.
There is nothing copyright about this that this person could go after.
So when I just suddenly and this is how YouTube works, it's kind of terrible that you just get you're seeing with Disney a lot lately.
You just get a strike and there's no chance.
Sometimes there's no chance to even fight back.
Right.
Because nobody's on the receiving end of that.
You know, it's all bots answering all the responses.
Luckily, when I logged in and saw that my video had been pulled, there was a chance for me to make my case.
And I was like, this is not I know that I don't know much about the law, but I know that this is a it's it's parody.
Very clearly a parody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's not even like, you know, compositionally, you'd have nothing to hit me for.
It's just like, you know, if you if you can copyright the word shuffle, then we then the English language uses a great loses a great word word that's open to everyone.
So, yeah, I and then I'm so then I'm like Googling and like, oh, my God, there's been articles about ESPN wrote an article about this person.
And she described herself as like, you know, when you get a rock in your shoe and you can't shake it out and you just got to do everything you can.
And that rock is going to be so annoying.
That's me. That's me with the copyright to like, OK, so clearly this is a she sued Viacom four times.
It's a whole thing. But I just knew I was in the clear here.
So I made my big case and I pointed to like counter examples.
And thankfully, I thank YouTube for this, that they did restore it.
No questions asked. And there was never any other, you know, problem there.
But the thing that really frustrated me about the situation, if it had gone the other way, is that not only do I know that it's parody and it's a style thing, but I also knew that the Super Bowl shuffle was not even the main basis of that video.
There's an entire other thing that was way more what I was going for.
It's the best of the genre by far.
And I'm going to close with that because there's no way to top it.
Right. One of the best videos I've ever seen anywhere for any reason.
I'm excited to share it with you guys and the listeners.
But with that, I'm going to keep going to other football songs.
And here's one where I'm a little less concerned about playing clips because the OK, so I believe that.
Oh, wait. Well, first of all, in response to the Super Bowl shuffle, the New England Patriots had to scramble and put out their own song.
It is clearly we need to show strength and shit like where we are definitely going to lose this thing if we don't get a song out real quick.
They put out a song as quickly as they could to counter the Super Bowl shuffle.
And that song is called New England, the Patriots and we.
Here's a clip.
It's terrible. It's dog shit.
It's not good. And I think it's why they lost.
I think, you know, I mean, OK, if you're preparing for the Super Bowl, I guess one school of thought is that you should prepare for the Super Bowl, you know, get in shape and such.
But, you know, run drills. Yes.
But whatever. Yeah, whatever. Well, that's for Jason to tell us as a team manager.
Oh, yeah. What's the sort of thing that a football team should be doing?
Well, the fundamentals. Ah, yes.
You can't lose sight of the fundamentals. Never.
Even if you're in the Super Bowl. That's right.
Fundamentals are more important than ever.
But I would say you're trying to come up with even like a goofy competitive song.
You shouldn't make it sound like a tourism ad jingle.
Yes. Yeah, that one does feel like come visit our city.
Mm hmm. Yeah, this was one where they like they thank the mayor for like, you know, the mayors like do bets and stuff.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. One of those like thanks for thanks for the peaches.
Mayor Bradley, sort of from a previous something with an Atlanta mayor that went their way.
It's a little too friendly.
I guess that's maybe a component of the football rap is that there has to be something a little bit tough and challenging about it.
Yeah, these are extremely friendly songs overall.
However, that one is really friendly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Much. Yeah, they seem like pushovers. Right.
Yeah, that's not winning you any games. Yeah, no, no.
And if and sure they put like, you know, for the listener, it's like a bunch of like, you know, like locals with a lot of spirit all singing.
That's not what it's about. Right about the we have to be building up the players. Right.
They're the stars. Yeah. You can't do a football rap without the players and without rap.
That's really the big mistake. Rap is the correct genre. That was the genre at the time.
They were bucking the trend. Yeah, maybe they thought they were being creative there, changing it up.
But it was a mistake. I think so. Yeah.
Yeah. Why mess with the good thing?
But it had been less than that. Again, this is only the second one of these.
So we're still figuring it out. Now, I think the next year, the genre was perfected.
And I don't think I'm just saying that due to local allegiance.
But I do think that the genre was perfected in Los Angeles by the L.A.
Rams. And sexual being Jason over there will be excited to hear that the song is called Ram It.
What does it sound like?
It was that kind of what's we're sort of near Rockwell.
Somebody's watching me. Yeah, yeah. A little bit.
But then that didn't didn't didn't didn't. I don't know.
I guess it's a little pointer sisters or something.
I mean, this is this is jazzy. This is catchy. Yeah, that's good.
It's good uniform. They are also they're just in the stadium and they're all packed together so tight with their vibrant blue and gold.
And they are the dance, I think, is really good.
They do they kind of like go backwards and do sort of a like arm pump.
That's they don't know. They look like proud pirates or something.
They smell like smooth operator or something. What am I thinking of?
I'm trying to think a little a little bit. A little bit.
It also sounds like we could fit out of our smart kids.
It could be on smart kids. You know what?
Well, that's well, that's you just my highest praise.
Yeah, you would put it in the. Yeah, I would have loved an L.A.
Rams. Come on and ram it.
Say no to drugs collaboration.
That'd be awesome. Or him or a response song.
The L.A. Rams abused their position in the city by taking their name and putting it into a double entendre.
Double entendres are no good.
If you're going to say sex thing, say it in private, not over the airwaves.
And the song should have been a more clear cut phrase like the Rams are here and they want to win.
It's less catchy, but it's also less filthy.
Double entendres confuse the brain. It makes it work too hard.
Don't wear out your brain trying to figure out what a double entendre means.
Ask your parents to vote against double entendres in any legislation intended to make them illegal.
Thank you, Mr. Dan Quayle, for signing on to this new bill.
This important initiative.
Also, entendre is French, I think.
So it should be illegal in America on those grounds alone.
Call an entendre a meaning.
That's what it is. A meaning.
Use an American word.
The sexual the sexually charged French language seeks to seduce our children.
A country of perverts and cigarette smokers.
Parents, take the pledge to never allow your children to go to France.
Put up a wall.
I don't know how it'll work, but put up a French wall that prevents Americans from going in.
They should have moved the Berlin Wall.
Move the Berlin Wall to France.
That's the idea. We want that down.
Reagan says tear down that wall.
McGruff says put it back up around filthy France.
Launch a satellite into orbit that will suck all the horny energy from the French people into space.
We don't need it. We don't need that energy around here.
Maybe some alien freaks have some use for it.
It has no place here on Earth.
Also, support making Ronald Reagan the king of Earth forever.
Grow him new organs in a lab somewhere so we can replace his dying old organs with new fresh ones.
So this man may reign for 300 years.
Octopus tentacles could be cool too.
If we're blue-skying what cool amending to Reagans could be.
Add animal parts to him. Doesn't matter where.
It should be kind of a random shuffling. That's the most fun probably.
Give him the xenomorph tongue from Alien.
Human-animal mutant hyrids are okay.
Double-entronters are not.
Take it from me. I am one.
My life is pain.
Give him ram-orns. Just don't make any double-entronters about him.
Anyway, I think these are great. It's the best dance.
I'm sorry the listener can't see the dance.
Let's get a taste of some of their...
Yeah, yeah, definitely. We can because we're not going to get sued by that whistleblower referee.
Okay, here's a little of the rapping.
Well, maybe it's not. Maybe it's just them making strong arms and doing fist pumps.
But let's see. I mean, you're going off of my imitations of the bears and not the real deal.
All right. Well, let's not even compare. Just compare the rams to all hip-hop artists you've ever heard.
Okay.
Don't worry that the rams are rapping. When game time comes, we'll get back to...
Jabbing?
I don't know. I don't know. What did they say?
He's rapping very fast. He's rapping at sort of an Eminem pace there when Eminem goes real fast.
Yeah.
Or Twista is another guy.
I think if you cut the beat like Forgot About Dre, I think this guy's plowing through.
I think he's got a natural rhythm. It's a lot faster than the Super Bowl shuffle.
So it's a more vocally dexterous piece that they're trying to pull off here.
But what is he... All right. Don't worry that the rams are...
This is important to address. They need to focus on the games. But what do they say?
In my head, it's jappin?
I don't want to even speculate.
It's a football term that I don't... Is it jabbing? Like ram horns?
Maybe, yeah. Let's say it to that.
Okay. Yeah. I guess so. For now. I need some peace with this.
There's so many things there. This is Limousine Willie. My moves are like dreams.
Also, I know they used to use chalkboards when drawing on football plays and stuff.
But seeing a wrapping in front of just like a green chalkboard with nothing on it.
Yeah. Unless the VHS... I mean, I see some writing. Maybe it's just some... It's really hard to see through the...
Well, and then the next one just walks out of like the, you know, closet and locker room.
He's fully in a locker and then steps out of it. Yeah. I also like this one a lot because of the staging.
I think the Super Bowl shuffle looks great. I like the soundstage that they filmed on.
However, I think there's some clever use of the environment. I don't know where they were playing at this point.
This might be at what is now Angel Stadium because that's where they were for a long time.
It was a weird hybrid stadium that was kind of awkwardly sized until it became baseball only.
So we might be in Anaheim here. I'm not totally sure. I feel like there's one more good bit of staging.
Let me see. There's some saxophone, of course. Let me see what we have here.
That's it. Okay. This guy's on a motorcycle. That's great. In the dressing room. It's parked.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. He's no, he's not doing donuts. That would ruin it permanently, I would think.
I like that one though, a lot where he says, and stopping me is like stopping a train. Really pleasant. Stopping a train.
None of them are doing it. None of them are like acting tough. No, really.
Yeah. It's definitely a different vibe than you would get.
Because you think it would be like pro-wrestler style.
Like you could feel the grating of their teeth. No, everyone's like, hello there. I'm a man. Nice to see you. Yes, I can.
I think that's something I love about it is the smiley-ness. I mean, they aren't all the, and we'll get to ones that are, I guess, a little bit tougher.
Yeah. But I don't know. Yeah, this Rams one is just so, so goofy, so upbeat. Yeah. You got like the female singers in it.
We're gonna ram it. Let's ram it. It might, however, have worked against them because not only did the Rams not go on to win the Super Bowl,
I don't think any other team that did a song ever won a Super Bowl. I think there was this, like the Bears got in there.
They rode the song cockiness all the way to the trophy. I think from here on out, it's a curse. I think the song never did anything for you.
I also like when they, later they're all like in an office park, which is also very adorable.
I think that's, you know, adorable is not a word I would usually apply to a bunch of football players.
And that's some of what I like about this is that, here, you'll see what I mean here. They're all hung up in an office park lawn.
It's cute. It's like everyone's being cute. Yeah.
Because everyone's like a high school assembly or some like energy of just like, Oh, can you believe these silly guys are doing this?
Did you guys like rallies that high school where like the football players are doing skits and stuff?
Well, I certainly had a little bit of a chip on my shoulder about like other people doing like skits and stuff.
That's exactly where I was. Yes. But as I've explained on the show, then in senior year, we did our Batman stuff, which is a high point to my life.
Glory days. Yeah, yeah. No athletic glory days except for tennis. But taking over two rallies. Yes. Especially one big rally.
Uh huh. Uh huh. Yeah, I didn't. I didn't. I never crossed into rally. I just didn't ever feel like stuff was going to play in the arena setting.
It's tough. You had to go big. It remains tough to this day. Only the Maniscalcos of the world can handle it.
Yeah, that's why you had to put on like a live Batman stunt show like we did. Well, you did. You did it right.
Yours was not about, you know, verbal and clever. It was. It was big. It was. You used your theme park brain. Yeah, action.
What's going to play. It was all action. Yes. Yeah. Did you ever play in the band at any of these? All of them.
Okay. Did you guys have like a casual ensemble? Because I just remember the band sitting in one set of bleachers, all of them in black t-shirts and khakis.
We just had a band shirt. A band t-shirt. Okay. And pants. Yeah. You were asking about the look. We weren't wearing marching band outfits at a pep rally.
The casual black tee and khaki, like you're going to fix their cable kind of look.
That would scarcely be appropriate for a marching band, I wouldn't think. I just think it was like a maroon band shirt. Okay.
I want at least a little bit of, I want mild tassel. You don't need tassels on all your shoulders and elbows and you don't need 12 sets of tassels, but I'd say at least two.
There might have been a tassel hanging from the little, the thing that held the little sheet music I would play that you could stick on top of your trumpet.
There might have been a tassel hanging off that. Okay. Then at least, yeah. So something would flow.
Tassel care I feel is a very difficult area. Those things get sticky. Yeah. They bunch.
I think there's a reason why people don't casually wear tassels day to day very often.
Well, marching band I worked, I had tassels. I was tasseling. Did your mom have to clean tassel clothes or was this a special job?
Dry clean. Okay. Yeah. So they would clean the tassels. No, best leave it to the experts. Yeah.
Those things, yeah. They were, we did not buy them. They were used many years. Yeah. You think still, you think anybody, maybe even a podcast,
The Ride fan is unknowingly putting on Mike Carlson's superhero cape equivalent. If they're still using that 20 years later,
I hope the school is having funding issues. Wow. I hope. They're playing like, hey, Mike Carlson's marching band. Yeah, it's possible.
Tassels. I would love to know what the set list is as far as pep rallies now. Yeah.
Well, what's the most recent song that has made it to marching band?
You know, it feels like a very theme park area where you're probably not getting a hit from this year in the marching band.
But maybe, maybe, you know, it's the Bruno Mars kind of level. We want it to become a wedding song so that it can become a Bruno Mars.
When I See You Again from the Fast and the Furious after the Fall Walker.
Is that a marching band? For marching? You know, you never know.
Well, that's if you're a band. We would have killed for a song that was 10 years old at these pep rallies.
We were playing Give Me Some Lovin' and the Peter Gunn theme. That's what we were doing. I'm not saying they were bad. It was fun to play.
Jason would have killed for a song that's 150 years old. Well, right. And he usually got them.
Oh, let's have another cup of coffee. Let's have another piece of pie. What's that one?
It's like an old song. Let's have another cup of coffee. Let's have another piece of pie. Hang on. What's that? Yeah. What's this?
Can you say any other details about it or is it just from the world? Let's have another piece. Let's see. How old do we think it is?
What if we figure out, though, that it's a Jason original? Oh, my God, I hope.
Let's have another cup of coffee song by Fred Waring. OK, let's see. OK.
Let's have another cup of coffee song by Irving Berlin appearing in the musical comedy Face the Music, which opened in 1932.
So it's almost 100 years. Wow. Wow. Just around the corner, there's a rainbow in the sky.
Let's have another cup of coffee and let's have another piece of pie.
The hit version was released in 1932 on the RCA Victor label by Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians with vocals by Chick Bullock with the Three Waring Girls.
So how about it? Chick Bullock. There are beauties and I'm not just saying that because they're my daughters.
Charles Chick Bullock. September 6, 1898 to September 15, 1981. Lived pretty good. Lived a long life.
I had definitely heard the name Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians before.
You know about his Three Waring Girls? I didn't know about the Waring Girls.
Well, if you're in Pennsylvania, they occupy the cultural space that the Chicago Shufflin crew does in Chicago.
They were a supreme court for a long time.
Burl Ives included the song in his album Burl Ives Sings Irving Berlin. Oh, so how about that? That sounds like a corker.
1960. Do you think we are at least the only comedy podcast that probably once a year references Burl Ives?
Probably. I don't know.
Paul of Tompkins I feel like might say Burl Ives once in a while. Yeah, that's a good guess.
I'm guessing. Yeah, I don't think it's frequent. I don't think it's happening often.
Yeah, it's up to all of us to keep his name alive. Yeah, he's got a great voice.
Any future child I have will be named Burl. It hasn't been a Burl in a while.
Has Burl had his voice in a theme park ever? Do we know? Burl Ives was America Sings. America Sings, yeah.
Of course. That's why I kept him in my head. God, I'm going to edit that out so I don't look foolish.
Of course it is. That's why I thought that.
Okay, where were we? I think that was all the Rammet clips. Rammet is my favorite.
That's where I got excited. It's not just this. People actually took the baton and went further with it, deeper with it.
Unfortunately, Rammet I think is the only other superior song.
There's moments that I like in other ones, including, actually, Jason, we're going to take it over to Philly.
We're going to the Philadelphia Eagles. They did one in 1988 called Buddy's Watching You.
Do you have any new Buddies? Is he somehow a local character enough? I can't really place it.
I think he was the coach at the time, Buddy Ryan potentially.
It's a little exclusionary to put him in the title. They're not getting on MTV with this. That's a little too specific.
I am a fan of the individual personalities in this thing. I feel like this one's a little tougher in general,
maybe save for the guy who looks exactly like Will Arnett with sunglasses and a fake mustache.
I think the Eagles do go harder. I'm going to play a little of the chorus and then it goes into the verse from The Kicker,
which I've never forgotten about in many years.
They couldn't have fixed that in post.
He got through it before the spacing. Yeah, that wasn't easy to do.
He admitted he was nervous. Am I nervous?
Yeah, I suppose. A lot of these things inspired individual moves in my video, The Sex Offender Shuffle.
That happens in that for that reason. Somebody gets through it too quickly and then doesn't know what to do and coughs with the extra face.
This is like when you see Quentin Tarantino talking about Kill Bill and he's like,
I took this from this movie and I took this from this samurai movie and I took this from this kung fu movie.
You're doing that with the different shuffles.
If I had his film knowledge, maybe I'd be further in the film world.
I think I really did corner the market on tributing football raps. I found a way to acknowledge all of them.
More than you'll know because you'll hear at the end where really the basis was graphically and everything.
I'm excited to give it some love. As for other rap pieces, it starts to get a little inessential.
Besides Rammet, I think it gets a little sloppy. The San Francisco 49ers did one.
I think it's just called We Are the Niners. I don't think it's much to write home about.
Notable though that Sheila E.'s dad and brother put the song together.
Sheila E. was around. She's in the video, I believe.
I think they brought her in like, hey, can you just teach these guys how to be good on camera and dance and move and not look mad?
Which I think she tried to do to mild success to no success.
There's an oral. A lot of these songs are like, at least there's a local pride to them.
A lot of them have had articles written about them and this one did in some San Francisco press.
I like the detail of it. Weird coincidence, Joe Montana is not available for the video shoot.
Joe Montana is going to be busy, I'm afraid. Jerry Rice did it.
There's not always huge names in them for the Bears.
Yeah, but ooh, no, Joe would love to do this rap. He's got sick kids to meet and stuff.
But you can't ask him to say no to the sick kids.
I wonder how high you had to be on the food chain on a team to be able to turn something like this down.
Ooh, yeah.
You know what? That's also some Super Bowl shuffle behind the scenes.
Walter Payton originally said no and Punky QB Jim McMahon originally said no.
Then they got talked into doing it because I think it turned out pretty well and all the players were like, come on.
And I think they thought they'd sorted out the charity thing more and they're like, all right, fine.
So they did it on green screen later, which is why they're on green screen.
If you've ever been wondering why the Walter Payton shots and the Jim McMahon shots look different, well, I'm at the hot scoop.
This is like the MCU stuff where you go, oh yeah, a lot of it's green screen. I didn't realize that.
Even if you have a united team like the Avengers or the Guardians of the Galaxy, sometimes you have to resort to green screen tactics.
Like Quentin Tarantino, you should now, after you retire from making content of any kind, making TV or movies, you should just write criticism books about shuffles.
You should just write thousands and thousands of words on each shuffle and what the shuffle is, what's good about it and how it was made.
Yeah, yeah, and how it moved the shuffle art form forward.
And you're right to say that. I do consider them all shuffles, whether or not they say the phrase shuffle.
Technically, yeah, they're not necessarily shuffles, but they fit into the genre.
I also don't know musically if it's correct to call any of it a shuffle.
What is a shuffle technically?
Well, I feel like there is a type of music that you would call a shuffle, but I don't know enough about percussion and meter to say that.
I feel like they define it as the dance that they're going to do when they are at the Super Bowl.
Right. The shuffle rhythm is a specific eighth note rhythmic feel.
I always think of it as like we're shuffling.
Sure. Oh, I think that's right. Maybe you're using brushes on the drums.
You could do, yeah, I think that's possible too.
Well, that's, I mean, that's a whole chapter there is how the Super Bowl shuffle turned the genre on its head by not being a shuffle, but at the same time redefined what everybody, everyone's notions of what a shuffle is or could be.
I'm really excited to write these books and I'm really excited for three people to read them.
Not my own family, even out of politeness.
Can you get a 33 in the third book on just the Super Bowl shuffle?
I think it's deserving of it, but I'm going to have to make peace with the family in order to have any official.
Right, right.
Because that's the whole, like, you know, like also why I didn't play any clips is that she's also said we licensed the song.
We will do it. Right.
And, you know, it's we just price it out to be fair.
You know, it's like a thousand dollars a second.
And then if you do that math, you're like, wait, so it's like, I mean, wait, I might be wrong, but it is it gets some somehow it gets into being four hundred thousand dollars to use the full Super Bowl shuffle.
There is one or two that survived on YouTube.
Yes. So you want to see it.
I know. I don't know how those have made.
Yeah. But there was a long time where it would just suddenly be a black screen.
And I'm sympathetic to her.
I've had to do this a number of times every once in a while, like once every quarter, I go on YouTube and eliminate versions of my video.
I don't eliminate it if it does something like, you know, putting I don't know.
There's one where they they deep fake like Nancy Pelosi and Chuck Schumer and do it.
That's fine. It's something to it.
But if you're just going to repost it and say that you found it, I actually had to kick it off of Spotify.
It is now up on Spotify.
My own official version remastered by the composer, Alfred Montejano, did a great job and he played the saxophone on it.
But yeah, I've had to look, I am in the shoes of this referee.
I am sympathetic to her plight.
Just in that case, I did not agree with her ruling and neither did YouTube in general.
You should team up with her.
Maybe you can become an ambassador or something for the song.
Oh, yeah.
Well, as a I don't I don't want to say this, but the numbers don't lie.
I think I have one of the more popular shuffles out there as a later day entry into the genre.
So, yeah, are not the the two, you know, bastions of the shuffle genre and not.
Uh huh.
Don't we need to get together?
You should stop being stubborn and she should much in the same way the U.S.
government.
If they catch a hacker, they will sometimes say, hey, you know what?
Actually, let's just get the hacker on our team.
Yeah.
Let's just recruit the hacker for our purposes.
So she should do that to you.
You can partner with the surviving member of LM FAO because they have that part of party rock anthem where they go every day I'm shuffling.
Wow.
Every day I'm shuffling.
Gosh, that's right.
Yeah.
Well, they thank you for alerting me to some of the other great shufflers out there.
Every day.
Even I can't say that every day I'm shuffling.
That's that's impossible to compete with.
Did you say there's one of them dead?
What did you just say?
Yeah, one of them passed.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
I think we never acknowledged it on the show.
We didn't do a full LM FAO.
I don't think that's true.
I swore.
Red Fu and Sky Blue, they both appear to be alive.
I swore one of them passed away.
What a thing to throw out.
No, I swear to God.
That one of them is dead.
Is it because the Wikipedia says past members?
I think that's just because the group seems to be not together.
Actually, well, it's the group that's dead.
I don't think I knew that.
I didn't know.
I'm not an LM FAO expert.
I just I feel like I would have heard if one of them died.
I think the band is they like they're defunct right now or they're not doing new LM FAO music.
I didn't know that Red Fu is the youngest son of Barry Gordy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Barry Gordy's son was the aforementioned Rockwell who did the song Somebody's Watching Me that I referred to earlier.
Here's what.
Okay, Jason, I think this is what you're thinking.
Are you thinking of the band LFO who did the song Summer Girls?
Oh, that would be fitting if I was.
But no, I swore a member because two of those people are dead.
Rich Cronin from LFO is dead.
I think somebody else powered Stern clip.
Yes.
Describing Lou Pearlman trying to trick them.
Right. Yes.
Doing untoward acts in his thick Boston accent.
I won't go into it now, but oh, my God.
Disturbing.
So, yes.
Are you sure LM FAO and LFO were not mixed up?
I think that feels right.
I think that's what you're thinking about.
I mean, Jason, you don't seem sure about that.
No.
But yeah.
I mean.
You're not going to.
They're alive.
I don't know if you're still looking to see if they're dead.
They are alive.
They are both alive.
But I swore there was something where it was a duo and one of them passed.
And now I can't remember what I'm thinking.
You're thinking of the Dorsey brothers.
They're all passed.
You're thinking of Burr Alives?
Are you thinking of Burr Alives?
He's dead, too.
Burr Alives Jr. is still going strong.
He's also an LM FAO.
Yeah.
Very Gordy.
It's a future Jason or future Mike thing.
And for a while, I was working for Burr Alives Jr.
Cricket.
89 year old Burr Alives Jr.
I wish.
Oh, God.
All right.
What have I not gotten to?
Oh, I mean, there's so many of these that are just coming in.
I was like, I need to scan.
OK.
Raiders did one.
Silver and Black.
I don't think there's anything terribly notable about it.
But if you're a big fan of that, I apologize.
There's ones I didn't know about until this morning.
The Dallas Cowboys did one called Living the American Dream.
Whoa.
But it's a little too singy.
I don't think it's.
I think I do think these have to be hip hop.
I think a fairly successful one is one outside of the NFL.
This is by the Florida State Seminoles.
It's called Simply Seminole Rap.
It's a little unfortunate in that there's a lot of white guys in this one.
There's a lot of guys.
It's kind of in the zone.
You know, the Lonely Island Just Two Guys?
Yeah, yeah.
The especially awkward rap, Akiva and Yorma.
I think the two quarterbacks are kind of a proto Just Two Guys.
He says, eat steel for lunch.
And then there's a shot of him taking a bite out of a barbell.
That's good.
Yeah, that's really good.
That guy also, the second guy, it's like two like oddly kind of slight guys.
I feel like this is the slight whites.
And then I mean, I'm sure they're vastly stronger than me still.
But then the other guy is such a bull that they cut.
Yeah, yeah.
It's very fun seeing him.
That's that's what I want is like the ideal to me is kind of good music, kind of clever.
Writing, if possible.
And then like just an enthusiasm cap on who's doing the performing.
That's the best recipe.
If all they give, the highest they can get to is, hey, I'm Gus and I do this.
Throw it long and I'll run fast.
It's just there's a sweet spot between somebody who, whether it's like acting,
whether it's like Walnut Show, Paul T. Goldman, where Paul acts in his own movie.
There's a sweet spot between somebody who completely doesn't know how to do the thing they're doing
and is really good at it for some reason.
There's a middle spot that I love.
And I think you're describing the same thing where it's like they're OK at it.
And there's things that will happen in the performance that are just surprising and funny.
Choices that a regular actor would not make.
Right. And that's like for certain brains, I think our brains, that is really enjoyable depending on who it is.
Yes. It's basically just what you're saying, choices.
It's just choices and maybe a little bit of nervousness or hesitancy that does something to the performance.
So whenever it's like this or whether it's the room, whether it's something,
it's like that is sometimes just really fun to watch somebody who is not polished do something creative.
Just take their best shot at it.
You played a lot of the Batman music in your birthday episode.
And I just like not that this is the ultimate version of one of these, but that Bert,
it's like it's a romantic song to one of your biggest fans.
OK, got it. Hi, it's me.
The boy wonder.
Why are you shouting?
Was that the choice?
Yeah.
You don't want to be.
But I'm so glad he did it.
Yeah. Yeah. It's surprising.
It's fun.
Now, there's a guy in the Seminoles who has it clearly.
I mean, not what we're talking about.
He just has it for real.
He's a star because this is a young Deon Sanders.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't even check to that one.
That's really good.
All right. Here's a guy.
Here's a future star, obviously.
Yeah, yeah.
A little less enthusiastic.
A little more nervous.
Yellow poles.
I was like, I just want to like lay back and do this rap.
You're like, you're like, isn't that's not the I want to get out there
and I want to dominate the football field.
It's like, no, I want to chill out.
The rap is a chill out part of the rap.
The rap is the chance for them to have some fun and they deserve it.
A hard season.
Deon Sanders, incidentally, full rap album,
which he made them let him do on Saturday Night Live.
I didn't realize that.
He hosted it in one of those horrible seasons,
the one where there was afterwards,
there was the full reset with Will Ferrell and everybody.
Deon Sanders was the host and Bon Jovi was the musical guest,
but he still carved out towards the end of the show
where maybe they're going like, well, maybe we'll have to cut.
Maybe we'll run short on time, but they did not.
He's on the musical guest stage doing a song called Must Be the Money
in a bright pink suit, the craziest suit.
What year is that?
Ninety-five.
Yeah, yeah.
In the same episode where there's a just unwatchable,
homophobic, alien probing sketch
where Chris Farley's pants come fully off.
Oh, I've seen that.
I've seen this episode.
I don't remember the Deon Sanders musical performance.
That's the deepest.
Well, I don't think this clip is going to be shown
at the 50th anniversary.
No, but I vividly remember that sketch.
Yeah.
From watching it live or soon after, yeah.
It's a rough one.
But anyways, so he did rap for real.
You could see the start there.
But what you start to see is sort of like a going through the motions,
kind of a lack of innovation in this area.
We're going to do raps and it's all going to end with,
we're going to do the such and such rap, seeing it done.
There's only one team that tried to do something vastly different,
and that is the 1986 Cleveland Browns.
They made a piece that does involve music,
but it is not a music video per se, and it is not a rap.
It is, in fact, a 17-minute short film.
It is called Masters of the Gridiron.
Whoa.
It is inspired by films such as Conan the Barbarian.
Wow.
And properties like He-Man.
What happened here is there's a guy,
I think this guy was a fan of Conan the Barbarian,
Mike Babb was a player on the Browns,
and he thought, what if we made this all?
Let's just do something way different.
Let's make a little Barbarian movie,
and we'll say that the team are the Babbarians,
and we got to go, let's just go find a castle,
and we'll run around, we'll storm the castle,
and we'll tell a whole little story.
Wow.
And this happened, this was made,
and again, whenever I found out about all of this,
this is really where I got excited,
because holy shit, Masters of the Gridiron,
here's a taste of Masters of the Gridiron.
Your quest to bring the ring to the great city
will be hard and filled with many dangers.
You will have to do battle with the mysterious Lord's Beasts,
beasts such as bears, rams, and falcons.
But once you are victorious, the ring will be yours,
and the city by the lake called Erie will be home
to the Masters of the Gridiron.
I, ruler of our great city,
I shall undertake this quest to bring back with me
the ring worthy of the Masters of the Gridiron.
Wow, I've never heard of this.
This is, oh.
I've wanted a place to talk about
Masters of the Gridiron for so long.
The camera quality is like, I don't know,
it'd be like polished for a porno.
It'd be like, here's a really good looking 1986 porno.
But they try their best.
It's like shots of just a guy's mouth.
And then Bab puts on war paint, and he's in a good,
he's got a big sword on his back.
Yeah, he looks good.
Yeah, he looks like Schwarzenegger.
It's great.
They tried so hard on this.
This one I don't think had any Joe Montanas.
They were like, no thanks.
I think everybody did it.
Apparently they all asked, do I get a line,
and am I going to look stupid?
And all but two of them did it.
And then the next day everybody was so raved.
Wow, that's so great.
That was awesome.
And the two didn't do it really mad and continue to be mad.
They didn't get to be part of it.
So they have to go storm a castle.
And somehow Cleveland has a castle.
There's something called Squire's Castle.
Wow.
And they went and filmed there.
And then there's a lot of, basically he gets hit on the head
during a game, kind of a dark acknowledgement
of the senior underbelly of the NFL.
But in this case, rather than, oh well,
maybe accompanying permanent brain damage,
he gets to have a fun little medieval adventure
when he bumps his noggin.
And he, oh sorry.
So he gets a fantasy basically that he's having or no?
Yeah, yeah.
He's playing and then he gets hurt.
And then like, Mike, wake up.
Mike, Mike, Mike.
And then he's zooming to his head and he imagines
that all of his teammates are his barbarians
and they got to go fight for the ring.
There's a guy named the Lord of the League
who they have to watch out for.
And then you watch all of them.
The Lord of the League.
Oh, get ready for.
The Lord of the League is a celebrity cameo.
Whoa.
I don't think there's any way you could guess.
But I'm really happy to say it is a 1960s weird talk show relic.
So excited that this is around the corner.
My first guess was because it was like Bronson Pinchot.
Earlier, 60s.
Yeah, 60s talk show guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Anyway.
Jason, do you know 60s talk show guy?
You have a guess?
Can you guess?
Musical weirdo oddity man.
Musical weirdo.
Something I don't think we really talk about, though.
But you had a famous talk show moment in the 60s.
Interesting.
Not Tennessee Ernie Ford was before that.
Not Tennessee Ernie Ford.
Darn.
It's more mainstream.
Odd energy, odd hair.
What year is the Gong Show?
Frank Zappa?
No, but kind of a Zappa look.
It's not Chuck Barris, is it?
Not Chuck Barris, no.
Okay.
Well, basically, we were going over maps of like in here.
From the mines of Offensia comes so-and-so and the Hamlet of Interceptus.
It's so good.
Wow, that is really good.
It's really good.
I really like that.
And then it becomes, so it's kind of a Lord of the Rings thing where it's a quest for
the ring, but it's Super Bowl.
Super Bowl.
And then we get to, all right, here's the Lord of the League.
I'm curious if you recognize the Lord of the League on site or for the listeners by voice.
Is this too obscure of a person to even know?
Interesting.
Oh, great warriors, please do speak.
I know you've traveled far.
What is it that you seek?
We mean to have the ring of the masters of the great eye.
Is that Tiny Tim?
Tiny Tim.
Yeah.
Tiny Tim who I, like, what are the basics of Tiny Tim?
I don't even really know.
Oh, he sang Tiptoe Through the Tulips and kind of a high tip toe through the tulips.
Yeah.
He got married on the Johnny Carson show.
Right.
That was the highest ratings they ever got.
I think he got remarried on the Leno Tonight show, you know, which no, but that may have
happened on the night that I was on it on Halloween.
Oh, really?
I think that also maybe was occurring.
Big episode.
Tiny Tim still alive, Jason?
What do you think?
No, I don't think so.
You think he died?
I don't think so.
I feel like I know him as like a reference.
Yeah.
Like as I started seeking out comedy when I was very young.
I would hear people reference Tiny Tim and I would know it was not like Christmas Carol
Sick Boy Tiny Tim.
Yeah.
There are references I learned pretty early on between old movies and like Looney Tunes
moments parodying stuff.
Yeah.
You know him as a ref through the filter of reference.
Anyway, yeah, he's in like a cape and he looks scary and he's got like big eye makeup on
and then it becomes like you, you must go, you must fight for your, you know, to rule
the league.
And then like, okay, so who are they going to fight?
Another football team?
No.
When it gets to who they are fighting, it is again, this is like a warrior movie, a barbarian
kind of movie.
And then it cuts to a field of ninjas.
And that is the context of this.
And I also a little bit of music kicks in.
Here we go.
Your enemies await you.
This could be coming out of our shells.
Yeah.
Yes.
Also, I like that little, uh, that part is really nice.
This is apparent.
This was like a very popular band in Cleveland called the Michael Stanley band.
Wow.
This guy, like a very much like singer of his time, kind of like serious guy in a suit
with beard, sort of Michael McDonnelly.
And it's, it, he's playing in an empty stadium and it's a lot of shots of him like turning
around, back turned to camera and then singing the line or they'll do like the journey separate
ways shot or all this, all the band members are lined up kind of staggered.
Right.
Uh, this is just a definition thing.
Are those samurai as opposed to ninjas?
I've saw, I've seen it listed as ninjas.
I'm not sure.
Oh, okay.
I don't know if they knew.
I mean, they're doing, it's like hand to hand combat with sticks.
Right.
Is what we're, what we're dealing with here.
Uh, let me, let me play a little more taste.
Really?
The song has nothing to do with anything that's going on.
It's not about football.
It's not about fighting.
I, it's like, it's very like Trey Parker rock.
It's very America.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's a little less aggro though than that.
Cause it's still a little moody.
A little more soft.
We get, well, it's, I think he comes out of the gate with such a, this is the kind of
shit I like, like in our, in the, uh, sky dome episode, this kind of like stupid anonymous
grunt rock, like glass tiger.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Michael Stanley band.
But yeah, you're right.
It gets a little moodier than that.
And then I just, okay, this is the moment that I really love and it's a little softened
by not being able to see it, but when it gets to the chorus, which is about like lovers
and clearly not about fighting, and then there is a moment, this is just, this is genuinely
one of my favorite moments in media I've ever seen.
If, if like, we weren't cooking enough with this dumb band and a football player gladiators
fighting ninjas, they're like, how can they top it while they find a way?
There's a bear in there, a real bear.
A shirtless football player in a loin cloth is fighting a real bear.
Oh my God.
Does not, there's no distance between them.
The bear's mouth is on his arm.
They're hugging each other.
Yeah, they're kind of slow dancing.
It's really slow.
Yes.
Yeah.
So it's not like they actually, I, it's supposed to look like they're fighting, but I think
it looks like they're just hugging and the bear is like sucking a honey off of his shoulder.
It's very, yeah, they're playing.
It's very tender, especially given the, the song.
There won't be another lover.
It's still dangerous.
Yeah, but the bear looks like it's having fun.
Yeah.
Well, the bear might be like sort of aroused.
I don't know.
There's possibility there that the bear is feeling amorous.
Well, they do kind of a turn in their little slow dance and the turn does not reveal a
big erect bear penis, but also there's not such fidelity to this footage and you know,
he's just black down there.
I don't know what, I don't know the color of a black bear's penis.
I don't know if it's also black.
Also though, animals sometimes get aroused in different ways.
So it's, I don't know if a bear has a traditional human looking correction.
Doesn't it?
I don't know.
Of all the species.
It might.
Is man not an animal?
Yes, that is true.
I agree with that.
I just don't think I've ever heard that a bear is one that has like a weird little spiral.
Yeah, but a horse, a horse, I've seen it.
I know what it looks like on a horse.
I know what it looks like on a dog.
I just, I haven't seen it with a bear.
That's all I'm saying.
I'm sure.
You don't doubt that.
Yeah.
I'm just saying that maybe it looks different than I think it does.
That's why you failed the animal husbandry elective you took at your college.
I'm just being curious.
Have you ever seen a bear's erection?
No, I can't say that I have.
Of course.
Okay, Scott.
Have you ever seen a bear's erection?
Well, now I have.
Okay.
But not up until this moment.
I think we're pretty standard.
I think yeah, we're pretty standard here.
Also, when you Google erect bear penis, you get headlines like
penis bones of ancient bears suggest they had long lasting sex sessions.
Okay.
Nice.
The bears and Jason both.
Jason's carrying out the tradition of the bears.
That's nice.
Really, it's not even about, you know, about sex.
Let's not think of it as tawdry.
I'm just, I am being as the bears were.
I like to think of it as a long conversation.
That's the way I think of it.
Connection with a partner through hard ramming for hours and hours.
Speaking through ramming.
Speaking through gyration.
Gyration.
That's sort of the way I.
I got, when I searched bear erection, I got a.
Erection.
No, I got a pill called boner bears for sale at the Hustler Hollywood online store.
Male enhancement and it's.
Boner bears.
Two of the grateful dead bears kind of entwined.
You think it's licensed?
No, I don't.
Okay.
But it's easiest way to communicate it in an audio medium.
All right.
Wait, what's the name of it again?
It's called Boner Bears Male Enhancement.
And why are they not a sponsor of this show?
Should we do a practice ad right now?
We would be happy to do it.
Yeah.
Hey there.
You know, we're not always comfortable talking about sexuality on the show.
Luckily, one of the hosts definitely is.
He taught us earlier today that sex is a way to connect with a partner.
And ever since he said that, I've been wanting to connect with mine more.
That's why I turned to Boner Bears Male Enhancement.
If you're looking for a session that's as long as the film or August 14th, 1976, you want boner bears.
That's a thing, right?
Grateful Dead fans are always talking about specific things.
Well, yeah, they showed it at Sphere.
I don't feel like they're so ripping off the Grateful Dead bears.
I mean, I guess it's of the same style family.
Okay, now I need to eat boner bears.
Oh, Mike, they're gummies.
Okay.
You like that shit.
You know, you love gummies.
You love gummies, too.
Yeah, wait a minute.
I did.
I ate a few handfuls.
I finished off a Haribo bag last night.
Hey, freak, you love that gummy shit.
Cut to Jason with an entire giant rainbow bag in his house.
On my nightstand, like, I just got to finish this.
It's been sitting here for a few days.
I've just been picking at it.
There's different style of boner bear cartoon mascots, too.
And there is, I see what you're saying.
It's a little bit more like that.
I'm comparing two of them.
I guess Jason's not wrong about the, yeah, we're in the design area, I guess.
The female enhancement one's much more generic.
But of course, the male one looked like the Grateful Dead.
You got to appeal to Dude's favorite music, the Grateful Dead.
Yeah, Dead and Co.
That's Sphere.
Sphere just announced an EDM show by an artist I've never heard of because I'm not a big EDM guy.
But it's got like, it's apparently an EDM show with all these original weird looking CGI characters.
And they promoted it by showing a character on the outside of Sphere that bursts through.
And for a second, it looked like Aura.
I really should show you guys a video of this and probably not on the end of this episode.
Aura the Sphere.
It's not Aura, but it looks like Aura.
And I was like, oh my god, are they doing something where Aura breaks out of Sphere?
But it's not. It's a different character.
Breaks out of her Sphere jail.
Yes, I should.
Take that, Dolan.
Doesn't this look like Aura at first glance?
Yeah.
And she breaks out?
It's not her, though.
It's a different character from an EDM artist.
Oh.
Oh, that they brought to the table.
Right.
And then there's a New Year's EDM show with these original scary looking CGI characters.
This is so insane that people look out their windows and watch a big full animation of a robot climbing out of a building.
Yes.
It's like Anya is the name?
Is it Anya?
Anyama.
I don't know how to pronounce it.
I should have done it before.
And then they break out of it.
But apparently there's just a ton of scary looking characters that play during this EDM show.
Which is something I would want to go to if I was young and had more free time.
I could see doing that.
You'd get an apartment overlooking Sphere.
You'd want Sphere proximity.
Yes.
The kind of places that people have moved out of because it's too bright to be there now.
You'd be in there because you'd essentially, you know, you can't literally live at Sphere, but you do the next best thing.
Yes, I would do that.
I think when the Horror Nights attraction opens in Vegas, they should have all of the Horror Nights icons on the Sphere.
They should have Jack the Clown.
Sure.
The director, the caretaker.
They should have a scary version of Woody Woodpecker.
Chilly Willy on the Sphere.
Little Moon.
I've been saying for years, Chilly Willy on the Sphere.
I agree with you.
Chilly Willy on the Sphere.
That's something I've been protesting.
Hot Stuff the Little Devil.
He's already a devil.
Hot Stuff on the Sphere.
I agree.
There needs to be more Harvey characters being promoted on Sphere, not this EDM dance music.
Maybe Baby Huey.
You guys don't actually like Baby Huey, do you?
Baby Huey sucks.
I kind of like Baby Huey.
Baby Huey's a fucking creep.
He's a scamp.
I kind of like Baby Huey.
He's an adult diaper fetishist.
He's not a baby.
Scott, you would hate that.
These are some of the creepiest looking gross CGI characters.
Yeah.
No, I'm not a fan.
It feels very, yeah, it's in the AI zone.
These are the EDM original characters.
Yeah, but I mean, I'll look in to see if they all have names and stuff.
Yeah.
And if it's worth doing an episode of EDM original characters.
A-N-Y-M-A.
Enema?
I have to find out the pronunciation of it.
Well, I know the artists that I would like to play Sphere the most.
I don't think it's going to be possible because I am sure they have all passed away.
But let me get to the end that I built up here.
And again, I've already played one of my favorite pieces of media with the bear
fighting the football player, but it does get better in the shuffle genre.
And it is this.
And this is truly where I pulled all my inspiration from.
So there was something called the Southern Food Brokerage Corporation.
We probably not talked about the Southern Food Brokerage Corporation yet.
I know.
It's got a name dull enough that it's asking for attention from us.
Sponsored a buffet at Disney World for the first month it opened or something.
Wait, this is your way.
That's really the...
You actually know about the Southern Food Brokerage?
No, no, I'm making something up.
That seemed confident.
Jason's a fan.
No, those first five years of Disney World, like the first few years of Disneyland,
it's a little strange.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, I was not previously a fan, but I certainly am now.
The video just throws you into it.
And you're just forced to assume from context clues that this is some kind of a group
that is a middleman between products, food companies like Planters and Ortega,
and empty supermarket shelves needing products to carry.
And it's seemingly this group is a lot of like very earnest older Midwesterners.
Oh, my.
And I don't know if they were doing some kind of an event, a trade show,
a company-wide meetup, or if this was just some like morale building tape
to send around through the company.
But this group got together, and God bless them,
made something that I can never unsee that inspired me so much.
And that is a piece called the Super Broker Shuffle.
Whoa.
I'm Laura Moser.
I'm Patsy Hughes.
I'm Jan Bradshaw.
And we're all in clues.
We're the Ortega Build Back office crew bringing the Super Broker team to you.
We are the best sales rep crew doing the Super Broker Shuffle for you.
We're so bad, but know we're good.
Nobody messes with our neighborhood.
We didn't come here looking for trouble.
We came here to win the Super Broker Shuffle.
Before I get to the verses, I mean, this thing is incredible in general.
Big sign that says Southern Food Broker Corporation,
shot in a real sound stage that's so dull, that's so beige.
They're all wearing beige.
They're all wearing this like really boring,
but kind of like old Epcotty logo in a way where it says SFB,
and then there's like kind of burnt orange, very 80s orange,
and the outline of a supermarket cart is in it.
And then they're all in white shirts with the same logo and khakis,
just a wall of khakis.
And they're also in front of a bunch of like jars, except for the girls.
The girls are up front, and they got pom poms, and they got little skirts,
and they do the fun little rah rah intro.
I'm Laura Moser.
I'm Patsy Hughes.
Jan Bradshaw.
I love these people.
I love this vibe.
There's something kind of King of the Hill about it.
It's so earnest.
And I enjoy this long rap of them not really syncing up as they clap back and forth.
But where this thing really gets great is where you get to meet the individual brokers.
I love all of these people.
I want action figures of all of them.
This is great.
Layer Channel, I'm here to say.
If you listen to me, I'll talk all day.
Have a lot of bread rabbit on your cakes.
The best thing you'll eat, for goodness sake.
I didn't come here to pop my bubble.
I came here to win a Super Broker Shuffle.
Hello, everybody, I'm Charlie Carson.
When the time will sell, I freak like a Parson.
Where my swedish, she can be.
Find me sir from a maple tree.
I didn't come here to stand in a huddle.
I came here to win a Super Broker Shuffle.
What's the line about Parson?
Preach like a little everybody.
I'm Charlie Carson.
Time to sell.
I preach like a person.
The finest serve for the maple tree.
Yeah.
That guy's the winner.
Hello everybody.
I, and they all like this differing levels of comfort.
Larry Tanner at the top has a little bit of swagger to him.
Charlie Carson looks so scared.
Yeah.
So unhappy to be there.
And this is what inspired my video because the idea of, I just said, like,
it looks like they're doing this at gunpoint.
It looks like some entity is forcing them to do this rap.
I'm like, wait, well, that's a whole, okay, wait, if you're being made to do
something, what do people have to do?
Well, I have to go door to door and say their sex spenders.
So that's where the whole thing came from.
Yeah.
If, if anybody should do a copyright strike and please don't, but if you
somehow are involved in this, in the Southern fruit brokerage corporation,
Hey, you got me.
What can I say?
Uh, I, but it's so funny, like in what other circumstance are you going to see
a 70 year old man rapping and scared?
He is so, they feel, and there's, there's others.
I feel like there's one more who seems mildly humiliated.
The next guy, similar to the kicker from, but he's watching you is he
just kind of wants to get through it.
So he's going, sometimes when you're nervous, you just go a little too fast.
I came here to win the super broker shop, call me Niles land and say, I'm married.
I've touched when it comes to selling.
Call me Mr.
Clutch.
Great.
Poop con is full of spice.
Spread it on a sandwich.
It tastes so nice.
I didn't come here to drop my duffel.
I came here to win the super broker shuffle.
Uh, come, come.
Are we done?
Uh, drop my duffel.
No, no, not here to try my dough.
It's like he's, it's almost like they told him, like you got to get it
in before the beat is over.
Yeah.
Like a big glove is going to punch you.
Jackass style.
If you don't get this done on time by my duffel.
Terror.
He's just filled with terror.
It's like a slight, it's like a slow down, but only a little bit of boom.
How are.
Yeah.
If you could understand boom, how are a little bit better.
Dang old.
All right.
I didn't come here by my dang old duffel.
It also definitely also something I took from this and the super bowl
shuffle does it too, but these kind of, they mostly just end with like, I
didn't come here to looking for trouble.
That's usually what it is.
But I was like, no, I'm going to think of a different tortured shuffle
ride to pop your bubble.
I'm going to think of one every fucking time.
I'm going to change it up.
It's cheating to just do trouble.
Cause I didn't come here to huffle or buffle.
That's good.
Yeah.
It's almost as hard as thinking of rhymes for cuddling.
We'll get to that for God.
They should have done.
I love the show Friday night lights and they should have really done a
Friday night lights shuffle the perfect thing.
What great viral marketing would have been damn.
Yeah.
There's been comedy shot.
I mean, besides mine, I like all of the super bowl shuffle guys all did a
reunion for a super bowl ad at some point.
And we made that made up for the lack of money they made doing the original thing.
Um, here's okay.
There's more.
All right.
Here's my, here's my other.
And you know what?
And we sent it.
Well, it comes up every once in a while.
What do you want action figures of?
Truly.
If I could somehow, if I had a hookup to get an action figure of everybody
in the super broker shuffle, uh, here's, here's another good one.
Cecil Bozeman is my name supervising sales is the way to fame blue
bonnet margin's hard to stop.
If it's up to us, we'll put it on top.
I didn't come here to try to muffle.
I came here to win the super broker shop.
I'm Jesse Frank from the Delta land.
I put your heads where it stands.
That guy's like bald.
They all look like old Disney CEO.
They look like who ran the company in the seventies.
That guy looks like, uh, uh, Dick Van Dyke show character, Mel Cooley.
He looks like Mel.
Yes.
Big, big, crazy glasses like that.
Cecil Bozeman is my name supervising sales.
It makes me laugh as hard now as it did the names are great years ago.
Those two are probably the best salesman because they just have
a quiet confidence about them.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
There's none of that sweatiness.
They're not rushing Cecil Bozeman might be the guy.
If any, if we're judging them as salesmen, he's, he's lit.
It's like we're, we got plenty of time.
Cecil's worried about glasses guy.
No, Cecil's the one.
He's the guy before.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just solid.
They all remind me of my long ago, ex-girlfriend's father who
sold medical equipment in Ohio.
It was just the most like nicest guy, sharp shooter, you know, he's not a
guy who like, you know, we're not doing a bunch of jokes and bits together.
Just like Scott, how's it going to, well, I'm so glad to hear it.
You deserve it.
It's been a long school year and you have just like, if, if my ex's
dad was in this, it would make all the sense in the world.
They're all very likable.
I, and it's just, it's so funny.
They have to do this thing.
They, this guy has a hard time mustering the confidence, not the confidence.
He, you just, he just can't fake that he does not want to be rapping.
To cool and cuddle, I came here to win the super broker shuffle.
Call me Gary Ballard, I'm solid as a rock.
Big jockeys better buy my brand.
It's how Wallions hunt.
When it comes to other drinks, I'll eat your lunch.
I didn't come here to huff or buffle.
Look at that hair.
I came here to win the super broker shuffle.
Ronnie Acker from the Cajun State.
Wow.
I like Tim because he had like a rhythm I've never heard before.
That's an innovative rhythm.
Yeah.
That's like a...
Call me Mr.
Clutch.
Like when you hear little Wayne for the first time and you go, wow, he's really
doing something like different, I've never heard anyone do hip hop like this.
Yeah.
What does he like?
He's like, mm hmm.
He's like sling blade a little bit, French fried potato.
I was selling French fried potatoes.
Is he got a toupee on or is that a dye?
Is that dyed hair?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, it is kind of like thick black, isn't it?
Yeah, that's, he is too old for having that darker hair.
Just kind of got kind of like a wide froggy face and kind of like puffs the
head back to call me Gary Ballard.
You don't want to, he's the one I want to fuck with the least.
Yes.
I hope he doesn't own the rights.
The, the other guy, if they, if they don't like it, they can go to hail.
I also love hearing about all of these brands.
Like you're left to imply like, okay, I guess there was a rare rabbit syrup.
That was, yeah.
My question.
Weishman's merge, like kind of not all the brands are around.
That's the whole part of the mystery of this.
Um, and then just one more shout out to the girls.
I mean, they already got their time, but I love the girls.
I want to give them some shine.
I'm Laura Mosley.
I'm Patsy Hughes.
I'm Jan Bradshaw.
And we're all enthused with Gina wine and planter snacks and
royal desserts to eat grocery sacks.
We didn't come here asking for trouble.
We came here to win the super broker show.
I'm Bob Berman and I'm mighty proud to be a member of this super proud.
There's something, let me just, all right, to go a little Jason's direction.
I think I can admit, I think I there's some, there's, for
some reason I'm attracted to the, like the sedateness of these women.
Just the like, the kind of just like, so they're just so down here.
I don't know what it is.
I, I don't know, like so like they're hard to get, you know, like what does
they're playing it cool ultimately.
Yeah.
I particular, I would, I would say Laura Mosley primarily.
You want, oh, I'd have to see them full.
I, but I, the vibe wise vibe wise here, let me, if they laughed at your
joke with that vibe, you would feel like maybe you accomplished some, like.
Yeah.
Like if I could get them out of the vibe, if they're, you know, they're sort of,
you know what, actually, you know who I was similarly attracted to because she
seemed so like dead inside.
I don't know.
It's hard to explain why I felt this way, but, uh, uh, Dakota Johnson in, uh,
Madam Webb is so like, she's got that vibe in general.
Yeah.
Like, what is it?
It's so like flipping.
I was like, I don't know why, I don't know why that's appealing somehow.
Yeah.
Well, that would take a second for me to psychoanalyze.
She's so odd and standoffish and doesn't want to be in the movie.
There's an energy.
I can't tell like this is deep psychology here, I guess.
Yeah.
Well, you felt a lot of sympathy for her after you learned about what happened
when her mom was studying spiders in the Amazon.
That's part of it too, for sure.
So there's some empathy, there's like, oh, she's being so vulnerable telling
us about their mother's spider.
Did you guys ever watch it?
Not yet.
Recommended, highly recommended.
That is almost like a new room type.
Like the villain of the movie has that, like, oh my God, the spiders.
I'm going to get my spiders back.
Oh good.
They have my spiders and I need to regain my spiders.
He never says spiders in a normal way.
She's so, she hates being there.
Sydney Sweeney hates being there.
Yeah.
I don't know what it is, but here, one more time.
Okay.
So tell me if I'm wrong.
I'm Laura Mosley.
I'm Patsy Hughes.
I'm Jan Branchoff.
And we're all in through Regina.
Pick your fighter.
They're all, first of all, they're all probably 25 years old.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
In this clip, just cause people look different in the old days.
People styled themselves in an older fashion.
Yes.
I was watching a clip, of course, of Matlock, which, because I, of course,
recently discovered Don Knotts had a recurring role on later seasons of
Matlock and they're goofing around.
And I looked it up and I'm like, these motherfuckers look like they're 80 years
old and they're both in their sixties.
They're like a couple of years away from Tom Cruise right now.
And Andy, and Don Knotts just looks like he's a skeleton man about to
like go right into the ground.
You showed me one of it.
Oh, I showed you the other day.
It's the worst stage fighting I've ever seen.
He accidentally, Andy accidentally punches Don Knotts in this scene.
I think, Mike, your dream would be that years from now, there's a podcast
that talks about old kitschy things.
And one of the things that they talk about is podcast the ride.
We have podcast the ride guy growing up.
I was, yeah.
You know, what's crazy to look back on is that Mike, Mike, you always thought,
didn't, how old do you think he was?
17, I'd say 17.
That's what I thought too.
I always thought that was a 17 year old with two 45 year olds, but it turns out
actually, if you look up their age, they were all the same age.
Yeah.
But that's crazy to me.
Cause I always thought he was so young, youthful.
This is my dream.
I would be so happy about this.
I would be, what's the opposite of rolling in your grave?
What's the up clapping in your grave or shuffling in your grave?
That's what I would be shuffling in your grave.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, but I want to be frozen.
So I wouldn't be able to move so well.
Um, but yeah, those, those, the, uh, that like unaffected thing.
I mean, Jimmy, Jimmy Garofalo had that.
I was of course, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
So there's something about that.
I think, yeah.
Said droll, maybe maybe it's funny.
And yeah, I mean, I don't know that these women are funny.
Jimmy Garofalo is funny.
I don't know all these women in the work in this food supply company.
Yeah.
There may be only one piece of media with Laura Mosley.
Uh, um, but any, but there's obviously there's some, something weird that
Erin was the, was in sex benefit shuffle and that she has that energy that I'm
like, you cast her in the role.
Yeah.
I didn't know what you did.
Vertigo.
Wait, wait, refresh my, what is it?
Vertigo is like Jimmy Stewart, like remakes Kim Novak to look, I mean, it is
her, but he like remakes her to look like the woman that he actually loves.
So you really love the woman in this video and you remade Erin to look like
the woman that you actually love pulled a vertigo because of the show, this,
this, uh, food service shuffle.
You had a vibe of kind of a more, uh, I don't know, kind of low on enthusiasm.
So crazy Southern food.
Jimmy Stewart so creepy.
So I want your hair to look like this.
And he's like making sure her hair is right.
And he buys her the clothes and like, he's obsessed.
He needs to recreate this woman.
Like this is his complete, like he's, he's been, well, I mean, this isn't the
same thing, but I guess it's related that, uh, just in, in this era of early
Scott Garner videos that there's that.
And then also I, I made a couple of videos where I play Michael McDonald and I made
these partially because the first one was a birthday video for Erin and she had
remarks, she was looking at footage of old Michael McDonald's early seventies,
Michael McDonald and like, like, boy, he was attracted.
Boy, he was a sharp looker back then.
And I was like, hmm, go to store by beard image of Michael.
Yeah.
Associate myself.
You have announced one person you were attracted to.
Then I'm dressing up like him.
Oddly threatened by the former mode of a singer from long ago.
Uh, so weird psychology abounds, but I shouldn't open myself up to
this analysis on my, my birthday.
Uh, this would be a little, little simpler.
Don't pick me apart.
It's my birthday.
I've had a beard and mustache for over a decade.
Cause Lindsay told me to do it.
Oh, I like it.
I prefer it now.
I would.
Yeah.
I want to, I want to look like Michael McDonald.
I want to look like Carl Wilson, favorite beach boy, heart of the band.
I want to so much revealing a lot here.
Yeah, really.
They ended this really ended up in an interesting spot.
It started at an interesting spot.
I would say.
Yes indeed.
Yeah.
A spot I would like to explore more.
Uh, but that's for another episode.
I think for now, thank you for letting me do the full lineage of shuffles as I see
it, um, uh, you know, from the one that everybody knew to what I think is the,
the absolutely superior one of the genre, uh, a lot of fun, right?
A lot of fun characters, great ways for people to, um, and the only thing is,
uh, you know, we're on our way.
Let me, I'll say you survived podcast, the ride second gate, uh, you know,
keep it tuned here.
More birthday shots coming.
Uh, you can upgrade to our VIP tier, uh, club three, uh, for even deeper nonsense.
I would see if we could really quick, at least think of a couplet to acknowledge
Jason's time as a football team manager.
Is there something that you could tell us that you thought you were good at or
that was part of the duty that you think could be if you had to do, if you had to
think of a braggadocious rap about being a football manager?
Um, okay.
Uh, one thing I remember in particular was filling up the water cooler, not
with water, but with ice from the one like teacher's lounge and you can't,
uh, a grown man should not be carrying a full, like you could really hurt yourself.
This was your memory.
Well, this is it.
And we realized when you manage a team, it was mostly just, you were
being like a PA for the team.
Yeah, I was a water.
Yeah, I was a water boy.
You were the water boy.
I was the water boy.
You were Bobby Boucher, the water boy.
But I said we would fill this cooler with ice and they're like, oh, if it's too
heavy, just use that hand truck.
And I was pretty good at pulling the like, um, uh, uh, cart, you know, the
cart that you kind of like kick up and then you were good at it.
Yeah.
I liked it.
I liked doing it and I didn't knock it over, you know, by my memory.
And then I, it's why it's ice.
Uh, it's ice because it's so that it can melt.
I think cause it, yeah, it would melt or people would like scoop some out for
like an ice pack is something hurt or, uh, to cool down.
It was too hot.
Uh, I think I got it.
Uh, just somebody give me one of those like shuffle bubble hustle.
Uh, wait, okay.
It was the, um, I am here to share, uh, I'm what was saying?
What's the name of your team?
The Eagles.
Okay.
And wait, what's the school?
Uh, shy Chester middle school.
Sorry.
All right, here we go.
Jason here, manager King.
Acknowledge me as a sexual being.
You want your cooler with not water, but ice scoop it up later.
It'll taste so nice.
I'm here to show some hustle.
I'm here.
I'm also here to do the Chichester shuffle.
A little too fast, like type, type, type, type, type, type down, but I got, yeah.
Well, it's in me.
It's in my blood.
I love shuffling every day.
I'm shuffling and I'm proud to be as alive as LMFAO is.
So I can be shuffling every day.
We're in remember listeners every day is an opportunity to be shuffling.
My name's Mike.
I am, uh, I like to drive LMFAO is alive.
Blew it there, but I got it.