FOREVER!
DOG!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, currently recording in a quadruple steel reinforced bunker to make
sure Deadpool doesn't get in. I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson's hiding here with me. I'm here and
I'm scared. Scared of quips. Scared of snide remarks. Some of his ideas are a bit unorthodox.
They might not work for our show, Jason Sheridan. I'm so sorry, misunderstood the directive,
I left the door wide open so Deadpool could get in. No! Ding dong motherfuckers!
Wow, I hate to pitch so early in this episode, but what if they kept great movie right around,
but Deadpool was the one who hijacked the trams. Oh shit, yeah. They would have done that. Oh,
that's great. That's pretty good. And you get a current movie instead of the general idea
of 40s crime movies, apologies, Jason. Yeah, not that boring old crap, Jason. Yeah, not that old
black and white snooze fest stuff. You get a new guy. Replace the tour guides with Deadpool and
all the actor robots with Muppets. Well, now we're getting really wild here. Take a movie,
take one actor, keep him, the rest are Muppets. Now take that one actor, he's gone, now it's
Deadpool. Yeah! I'm sure that prompt is going to go so viral, I can't wait. Hey, well everybody,
happy Sunday as you're hearing this, I think. We're trying to turn this around pretty quickly.
Yesterday we all experienced Horizons, a Disney D23 experiences thing, and just as that event
itself was upgraded to prime time in a big arena, we are upgrading the D23 recap we've been tending
to do here to the main feed and getting it up a couple days early. So here's your main feed for
the week about all of the exciting stuff that is actively happening, that is happening,
barring any pandemics or end of our country, in theory, these things. Well, not all of the
announcements are for our country, so those will be fine. Unless just the general work,
anyone doing work in America is disrupted. But mostly shovels in the ground, anywhere from 20,
2400, 2026, restriction of the blanks. At the end, sometimes maybe not even those particular
dates. Yeah, okay, I mean, it's, all right, we've done, we've been through a number of these,
and I think we've seen cynicism levels ramp up to the point where there was a lot of, you know,
we did an episode where we bet on stuff and there was a lot of the betting, sometimes successful
betting was on no announcement of this. I polled the audience on, still calling it Twitter,
and there was a lot of like, all right, where do you think we're getting such and such? Here,
here, or not happening? The not happenings were huge. This is where everybody is calibrated,
and I will say, from last night's event, that was not nothing. It was not nothing. Definitely
was not nothing. If you stack up the list, and especially now you can go on the Disney Parks blog
and see kind of like thumbnails of a lot of it, and you're like, well, that's a lot. That is a lot
of stuff. So I want to say that right off the bat. And also, I will say, because the time frame,
yes, anything can happen. Supposedly, according to Disney people, all of the stuff they announced
yesterday will be, I think, completed in five years. That's what they're kind of guaranteeing.
But I don't think any date was said about the big one at the end. A lot of things did not have dates
on them. No dates, and also, no, this is where it's going. Yeah, some of that was missing. Well,
there was a lot of sleight of hand going on for various reasons. Sometimes, for instance,
I mean, we're going to talk about all this, but of course, the big thing is the Monsters Inc. land.
Where is it going? We don't know. There's two pieces of concept art, and one of them shows
something different than the other piece. It's arranged differently, the Monsters Inc. factory
where the door coaster is going. So I don't know if that's just like they thought those were two
splashy pieces of art. Because also, the Lion King land going in France, they said it's animated,
but the promo art shows the live action Lion King. But they did say animated. The most dull tan
characters ever conceived. Right, but the model does have animated Simba on Pride Rock. Oh,
so that, I think, is confirmed. We get animated Lion King at that land, which is good. So I don't
know if some of this is accidental sleight of hand, or it's like there's not saying the date yet,
because they don't want to commit to something very specific, and they get made fun of later.
They want to show cool art, and sometimes their art contradicts, but we're sort of, you know,
they say what we're finding out is not blue sky, but sometimes the art. You don't want the art to
be so like, well, don't do that, because that's not going to work for the space. Like you want it to
be visualized, however. But I guess what I'm saying is like, I will give them credit for saying that
five year thing. That is a pretty, they have not committed to things like that in the past. So
I guess there's a chance that in five years, Villain's Land is done, and like all this stuff
is done, and we're on to another round of stuff. I don't believe that. It seems hard to believe.
I was optimistic about all the stuff that I heard, and now this new thing you're telling me,
I don't believe for one second. It seems, saying it out loud, I don't know that I believe it. I'm
just saying that is what I believe. Unless they were saying in five years, everything will start,
and I misheard, because I have a couple different people have said this. I've seen people say it,
and I've talked to somebody about it, and that's, they're interpreting it like it will be done in
five years, but we'll see. Some of the timelines just feel so far out. Well, what do you mean?
Like in terms of like, and this is going to start construction next year, or 2026. I don't think
anything is starting this year. Like nothing is starting this year. Stuff will start like-
No, no, no. Or Lincoln is. Tropical America starts this year.
Okay. Well, that starts this year, and then the Walt robot stuff has already started.
But yeah, as far as there's like, they announced 2026 is when a lot of stuff,
or Coco was starting in Disneyland, I think. Like starting construction.
So therefore, and the way that they build, I think what you're saying about this five years,
I think they should have said, that should have been like, the number five should have been up on
the screens. If they meant that, that would have been a huge part, or like the finale would have
been, and this is all done in five years. I don't, I think if they meant it, they would have
underlined it more. I do not, if we're opening bets up again, and this is not a bet, this will be a-
I don't want to take you up on this bet. I'm not Disney. I'm not saying that. I'm just saying this
is what I've heard from multiple sources. Remember the Harry Anderson Disney decade.
I remember all of it. Like here's what's coming in 10 years.
I wake up in the middle of the night sweaty thinking about it.
And remember the D23 where they brought out Dick Van Dyke and said that there's American Poppins
right coming. Remember the Play Pavilion. I mean, that's the pall of cynicism that I think has to,
oh, but Eric, I was the one trying to say we got a bunch of good stuff, and look how quickly we've
all reigned on my parade. My new spectacular nighttime parade. I was trying to actually give
a little more optimism. I guess you were. I guess you were. But then I heard that five and it made
me mad. Yeah. I was trying to reign on your parade. I was trying out cynicism with this one
because the last few I went in so optimistic and I was just like, oh. Jason has been experimenting
with cynicism lately. Never encountered it before. It's really wild stuff. That's progress for you,
I guess. I feel like I was getting hit for being like this like wide-eyed optimist when I was
betting about D23. But then I went back to what I actually had said. And really all it was is that
I thought Tomorrowland was going to happen and it did not. But everything else I said was not anything
wild. So like my, I feel like I was actually being pretty reserved in my optimism for this.
But in contrast to you too, and in contrast to the last couple of these people were just like,
this fucking lunatic. Good luck, pal. Keep dreaming, buddy. And I was like, well,
maybe we'll get a new Tomorrowland. And people were like, shut the fuck up.
You don't know what you're talking about. I did kind of. I didn't say that in there,
but I think, yes, some people felt it. Now, I don't want to do this whole episode through
the prism of the betting that we did, but if you're only on main feed and you're on second gate,
then you should know the last week on the second gate, which is our Patreon, we did an episode
where we made bets about what these announcements would be at this panel. And assuredly this is
going to come up through the episode and we'll do a tally and we'll figure out who won the night.
If you want to check that out, that's at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride. But we'll explain what
our bets were and refer to them as we go. But if we're sort of going in order of how we experience
this thing, I feel like a brief nod needs to be given to the high difficulty of watching it.
Oh, yeah. When in the past, Disney has just provided a stream and then we set up all this
stuff. We're going to do a couple of episodes based on it. And then it became, huh, okay,
something for the cast members. And then it's going to wait, is it going to be on Fortnite?
No, only some of it is going to be on Fortnite. How do we do Fortnite? Jason says he can do
Fortnite. I have a Fortnite login and I forgot about the Apple Epic Games feud where Fortnite
is not in the app store. So now you have to download either Xbox Live or download Amazon Luna
and you kind of have to. The hell is Amazon Luna? It's like it's a gaming platform. Some of it is
free with a Prime membership. So you literally add it, like do the thing where you add a website
to your home page, which makes or add it to your home screen on an iPad. That makes an app launcher
and from there you can get into Fortnite. So it's within, it's an app within an app. It's an app
with it. There's like three or four ways to like load Fortnite without the Fortnite app. Were you
playing Fortnite on Luna? What were you playing it on? I have played, I have it on my Switch.
I was playing it on the Switch, but I don't have the online Switch service. You don't have a Switch?
Oh, you don't? Okay, I see. I was going to say, you found a Switch that doesn't have the online
ability? No, no, I just canceled it after the three months. He does dial up Switch. Yeah.
He found a third party Switch on the black market that doesn't have online play. It says Game Boy
Advance on it. I don't quite understand that. Oh, you're playing Fortnite on Game Boy Advance.
Yeah. Oh, okay. Now I see what's happening. Yeah, I really enjoyed watching the panel that way and
I thought the little dots that comprise Josh tomorrow were quite handsome. Yeah, eight handsome
pixels. No, I was going back and forth between two YouTube, I think we all were, multiple YouTube
live streams. The TikTok live stream was pretty consistent. Yeah, I was doing that one and then I
was doing one where there was like a streamer watching it along and it had a pretty decent
stream. And then I would just kind of get, oh, oh, ah, like I would get reactions from this person
and then they would get confused. They'd think they were about to announce something like really
cool and then they go, oh, whoa, what, what? And then it would be nothing. It would just be like
they played a little like part of the Horizons theme or they played like Kitchen Cabaret. Like
they played some reference to some old, oh, whoa, what are we getting? What are we getting? And
then it would be nothing. And then they'd just like be quiet for there. Well, I kind of did that
when the stream got choppy at one point because I didn't, I couldn't tell it was Billy Crystal
walking out. I was like, is that one of the songwriters? One of the songwriters? One of the
songwriters? Was it Randy Newman, the songwriter? No, no. Who was the one who did like the D23 in
Japan where everyone was sobbing? Ellen Menken? Ellen Menken? Yeah, I was like, is that Menken?
I can't make it out. One of the songwriters? Oh, so you didn't know it was Monsters Inc.? Okay,
I see. I couldn't tell it was Monsters Inc. And I was like, oh, is he bringing out?
Right, right. Yeah. He was a white haired man. Yes. I'd recognize Billy Crystal from a mile away.
Why, it's Mr. Saturday Night himself. That's how I recognize it. We've all been primed to know what
he would look like older because we all saw him, what he would look like older when he was younger.
Right. We all know Mr. Saturday Night so well. I mostly know him now as the GIF with the tissue
box that very cruel people on Twitter like tweet, Rando's tweet if someone's complaining about
like injustice in the world. People use Billy Crystal holding a tissue? People use the Billy
Crystal from, I think it's when Harry met Sally and he has a really like droll look on it.
It's like. All right. Don't be sending me any Billy Crystal. This sounds like the cruelest
punishment. You're getting one. If I express disappointment about these announcements and I
get in and I see any Billy Crystals in our feed, we say blocked forever. Yeah. I guess I have to
ultimately think so Cal Hansen Parks, thank you for your stamina for holding the phone up. Oh,
I know. Through a very long presentation. Yeah. This went so, so long. And some of what added to
the length I feel like deserves a little bit of time, which is that if you tuned in at 7 PM,
the announced start time and you hooked up to some guy's phone as did like 10,000 people,
imagine being one of the three people streaming and then you start realizing you got 10,000 people
watching what you're filming. Yeah. Again, I'm not sure. What was the Disney rationale? Why would
they not do it? You had to log in with a Disney VPN and then your stream was watermarked with
your name. If you're an employee, if you're an employee, put your name on it. What is the
why? What is the reason here? No one knows for sure. The rationale people have made online is
that this is the first time they've had two separate tickets for D23, one for the actual
convention center stuff and then one for the Honda center stuff. So people are acting like,
or acting like they're thinking that Disney is trying to make this thing such a spectacle that
you need to be there in person and you need to keep paying us an extra 100, 200, whatever it is,
$300 to go do it. That's the only thing anyone can think makes sense. And that is the only thing I
can think that makes sense. And then they can put it up like a, well, other than, yeah, Jason was
saying like, maybe I have to pay musicians if it's streamed or something. Oh yeah. Union musicians.
There's exactly why. I don't think so. I don't know. There was an orchestra here.
In terms of spectacle, there was definitely spectacle. Yeah. So this was a pretty elevated,
it felt like more than an upfronts, you know? Right. Yes, for sure. They made it very theatrical.
If you were there, it would make sense that they are in a hockey arena. Sure. That said,
did anyone want that? Do you go and you're like, oh, and I also get a musical salute to all of my
favorite Disney moments? Or because I feel like so much of the audience watching this, at least
ourselves, and then people we know who are writers and journalists and stuff are just like, please
tell me some names. Tell me some things. I have articles due. I got deadlines to meet. Why am I
sitting through? Why am I watching Shaboosie? I was told from people in the room that everyone
liked it a lot and it was fun to be there. So for some people it was fun. I think if we wanted to,
and we're not going to do this, is go through the whole performance and I think we could all cut out,
or the three of us at least, cut out half the music and still be like, okay. Because some of
the music felt right where it's like, oh, they're playing the Horizons theme. It's an orchestra.
You're like, oh, this is nice. When you get to hear the Horizons theme and the Honda Center
with an orchestra, and then it's like, oh, we're going to do like a song from a Lion King or
something. And you're like, I've heard this song. You're going to hear the Lion King. There were
some things that felt more appropriate to me or something that was like, oh my God, I'll never
hear this song in a venue like this. It has never occurred to me to want to hear
Trust In Me, the Jungle Book Ka song covered by Rita Ora.
Seems like a big get for this. Come on, Rita. That seems ... I mean, there was some surprise
about music that we liked, I think, but still it was confusing why they were there.
I definitely had no sense there would be this much music, which I guess is good if you're in
person. But yeah, if you are the type of person who is just like, please tell me some details,
tell me some names of rides, tell me some locations of rides.
In terms of being there, I did get a message from Neil from the band Cuckoo and Happy Place
Emporium, vintage shirt collector Neil. He was like, you can get drunk at this present.
Oh, we were wondering.
There are sessions open.
Great. Yeah, so maybe people were drunk, I guess. Everyone was drunk there.
I will also say to you both, there's a meeting. You could have a drink and not be drunk.
What? What do you mean?
Because a happy medium could be reached. So you could be blackout. You could be there and
then forget it all because you went too far. That was what we were asking the last time.
Can you get hammered?
Yeah, yeah. I wanted to be front row hammered, hammered looking at Josh
and then heckling him during the show. You call that an announcement, pal?
Where's Deadpool?
He's coming up later.
You're going to get so much of him.
So I don't know. Some of the music I liked, but also, yeah, I'm watching on a weird stream
and doing three things at once. So I'm like, all right, when's the announcement coming?
One or more things. I don't know if they made the calculation that the audience there wouldn't
want more hyper specific details about things. It almost felt like they were like, all right,
here's two pictures. You've heard it. Now we're on into a song. And I don't know if they were like,
we don't want them to get bored or upset. But you're like, I think this is the room
where they want you to talk about the paint that you're going to use to paint these rides.
That feels like the audience. I could be wrong, but I'd almost felt like they were partly
hesitant because they didn't want to commit to certain things or reveal that they're destroying
a beloved ride. And then another half, I felt like they were like, well, this show's got to
keep moving and we got to get to a song. That's what all these people are here for, a song.
You're like, I don't think that's right either.
I'm not sure. How do you calculate? I guess if you're at, I don't know, D23 is like broad
Disney fans. So maybe a big orchestral presentation. But I also feel like the same people
would want a little more in terms of minute detail.
A couple of the segments they did a little more, but a lot of it was like, here it is. Take five
seconds to look at this picture. Cause now we're onto a song. We're onto five more songs.
Shockingly fast moving through stuff that is like what made me, like, yeah. I would say precisely
two things in it that had me just like grinning like an idiot. And none of it was meditated on
for too long. I'll say what those were as we go. But let's, let's give a little time to what
happened if you tuned in at 7 PM, which is the opening act. And the opening act turned out to be
the band from the Mad Tea Party, which was this limited time California adventure, Alice in Wonderland,
not rave necessarily, dance party type musical celebration.
It's over in the Hollywood land area of California adventure. And it felt like
the year previous, it was the Tron or years previous electronic electronica. They're like
G rated rave. And then I feel like some of the spirit of it carried over into like a very
like, what would you call it? I guess Johnny Depp era Alice in Wonderland aesthetic,
which ended up being mostly covers of popular songs from 25 years or later.
And then a DJ would do like a G rated rave, DJ White Rabbit would do a G rated kind of rave
over in that area. But this is the, this was the band from the, from those music festivities. And
this is something we talked about on the Patreon, patreon.com slash podcast, the red a couple years
ago. And I was surprised to be confronted by it on this big platform to suddenly be have the Mad Tea
Party to talk about. And boy, did it give us all a lot to talk about before the panel itself kicked
in. Yes. A couple things happened. One, Jason said, is this the Mad Tea Party band? Mike responded,
I don't think so. They're not the right vibe for this event. And I was really confused by that
response because I'm looking at it and I'm like, wait, so we're saying it's a different band that
has Alice in the Mad Hatter in it. There's another band. And then you explained. I was first of
all, I was doing three things at once. I'm watching my daughter. I'm mostly listening,
but I'm also on at this point or whatever stream I was watching was far away. I could not see the
band. So I'm kind of listening to the background. That comment was a joke. Obviously the vibe is
right for the Alice band to open at D23. I didn't know if you were criticizing the music
you were hearing or if you were saying that the Alice band is not the right vibe. It wasn't even
that I should have if to punch up the joke, I would have been like that band is too hardcore
for this audience. They're too aggressive. They want more gentle rock bands. It would rock these
stodgy journalists too far out of their chairs. Right. Yes, exactly. But yeah, so I was hearing
it. And also I know I think part of it was that they were doing a mashup that I'd never heard
before. So I was like, well, this isn't them. This isn't the song. This is what I like about
you and Happy. Happy by Pharrell. Now, what'd you think of it? Not knowing what band you're as a
blind taste test. What'd you think of the mashup? I like Happy because it's playing in Universal
Studios a lot. So I do like it. I don't listen to, I don't choose to listen to it ever, but I like
it when I hear it. What I like about you, I think is one of the like 30 songs I never need to hear
again in my life. Yeah, we're pretty covered on that. Also a very theme parky, but I felt like
that's in Knott's Berry Farm ads. Oh, yeah. Yeah. So maybe that's part of it. They're playing what
I like about you. And I was like, oh, do I need to hear what I like about you ever again? Wow.
Do you hear this? Because if we, if I didn't say properly the battle lines of the argument about
Mad Tea Party band, this is something that at least in the Patreon episode, Mike loved was trying to
sell me on and I never understood or got on board. Jason feels more that you round up to Mike's
there with me in the shit. We were in the pit. We were hanging out. I used to say all that I go,
you know, rough in the pit. Did you guys get injured? You guys must have gotten a lot of
elbows. Roundhouse kicked a nine year old when I got spooked. You can't approach me from the sides
or behind him like a horse. He deserved it is what I said at the time. I didn't know. It's just
unconscious. But I, yeah, around six or seven or eight, when we would be hanging out at the park in
the old days, I would say, you know, we could do tonight. We get mad. Yeah. And sometimes we would
and I get a little grin on my face and then we would walk over there for 30 minutes, 45 minutes.
You look at the wait times. Everything's bad. Everything's bad. You walk over to the
back lot area, whatever they call it. And you get mad. Yeah. You hear Alice and well,
I do think I would have gotten mad if I'd ever joined you for this. This is what we enjoyed.
This was the cell that you were doing. And I saw videos then, but now I'm watching them
play the Honda Center. And so I, I, I'm coming out a little testy, just reminding everybody. So
remember, this is the thing that Mike was for 90 minutes was trying to tell me how great this was.
Then it goes on and they do covers of separate ways and call me. And, and I was made for loving
you by kiss. If I heard them do that before, that's new. They, they've been learning new songs.
Well, this was your argument. When I was kind of having some qualms about the quality,
you said, well, the set list is different. I said, no, in the old day, in the old days,
they never would have done call me. They might've done call me. They've sold out.
Never would they have done a call me. They would have been too busy doing rapture. Never would
they have done a call. Right. They've changed it up a lot. Um, but they had been at knots for the
last couple of years, or at least for a year. I don't know if they've been there the last year
or two, but what are they called there? We've said this five times on the show and I can never
remember what it is. Cause once they're not in the office, you know, I just can't remember the name.
You can't place them. Yeah. Yeah. Good. I don't want to insult them, but um,
they finished a song and then they said, uh, all right, we just got a couple more songs.
And again, the panel is late. They said 7 PM now it's 7 20 and we're watching the party band
in your feed. You heard a woman like groan very loudly. Yeah. And she said, we got a couple more
songs like a really like pained noise. They made, uh, multiple people were messaging me,
but I said, man, like, cause a lot of people were watching on bad streams and people were
texting me about it. Well, we w and we were all texting with Griffin Newman. And at some point
deep into their set, we lost Griffin. He officially said, Mike, I do not like this. You were again,
arguing set list and all things. This is not their, uh, this is not their venue. This is not
their venue text in which I like to see them. I like to see them at Disney's California venture
with all the weird furniture and the two big guys playing tweedle D and tweedle dumb with the
accents. Sure. Cause they didn't just fall out of a coconut tree. They exist in the context of all
that's come before. And that's never been more true than context. Sometimes it's true. Maybe
all the time. It's true. I think it's always true. Uh, yeah, yeah. Well, no. And I said, well,
of course, rock bands famously don't really work in the middle of arenas. That's not never really
where they shine. Uh, and then, so you're making this argument Griffin is being firm about, and
then I get a text from another person who will go unnamed for our purposes, who was in the room
and texted me and said, why does Mike like this? That you are, this was, this was started as a night
of tragedy for Mike. I got hammered all night in different ways and not the good hammered.
Not the hammer you could get in the Honda center. I got hammered all night. I did get one, uh,
message of encouragement from someone. Well, I guess maybe I'm revealing who it is, but he said,
as a person in a cover band, uh, I approve of this. Okay. So it was a gentleman who was showing
support for me. Well, this is what you just like cover bands. This is what it boils down to. It is.
Yeah. And you get a lot of like, I feel like it's this, these are just, this is just a difference
between you and I, you hear a song being played on instruments in front of you and you go, yeah,
it's not quite enough for me. Right. If it's a very good cover than wonderful, but you're in
no matter what does not matter. I like, I, the music moves me so much. It can be like less good
quality music. So I'm so sensitive. I'm so hypersensitive to music. He's music sensitive.
My brain is so music sensitive. It's kind of like superpower. Yes. So like you can put,
except for a couple songs, like what I like about you. And then maybe like those three wedding songs
we talk about all the time, Bon Jovi or whatever. Uh, yeah, I can, you can, a band can come in here
right now and I will just like, like Jason, when he smells a pie on a window sill, I will float
toward the cover band. Uh, yeah, I was going to say Mike's music sensitive and I'm at the corner,
uh, in the corner picking up the cool down order. It's like,
that's how you guys manage a party. Yeah. But everyone seeing them there makes me upset because
that's not how they should be viewed. You weren't there by thousands of people with Jason and I,
they didn't give them all of their extra stuff that makes the man tea party. It was like your
rec room, your rumpus room. You could sit in a big plastic chair and view the stage from there.
And that makes it a different viewing experience than this. They've taken them completely out.
They're on a little stage there, no dressing. Where were Tweedledee and Tweedledum? They weren't
there. So I'm just saying everybody was upset. And what did they do? What did they add to,
how are they going to save this for me? They had the tallest shoes. They were so big. They found
the biggest men I've ever seen. They were big boys. We love our big boy. It was beautiful boys.
Big boy season at Mad Tea Party, these two guys playing Tweedledee and Tweedledum would walk around
and kind of like lightly hassle people. And it was interesting and kind of scary, but it added to the
atmosphere of it. So if, oh, so I would understand it if I was in a different type of chair and a
big man was harassing me. That would be your own home. And if there was like six foot tall
playing clubs, like you haven't lived since you had a, you haven't lived until you had a
pre-made cocktail next to a six foot tall jack of clubs and a large man is bothering you.
That's right. Jason gets it. He was there. He lived it. How do they bother? What's an example
of their bothering? Hey, mate. Hello. Yeah, they'd be like, hey, mate, all the way, mate. All right,
that's all they said. Like, I feel like there's some cockney voices. Yeah, no, I think they were
like legit. I don't even think they were doing voices. Yeah, no, they weren't. So I'm the heaviest
goons you've ever seen to play Tweedledee and Tweedledum. I'm trying. I'm trying to put myself
there. Okay. Alice is dressed like Moulin Rouge, the movie from 24 years ago. The Mad Hatter's hat
is taller than most hats. Yeah. And I'm listening. I hear them singing, wake me up and wake me up.
Can't wake up. And then, and now I may get out of my way, mate. You're a piece of crud on my shoe,
mate. Well, you're right. I do get it. Like a Vinnie Jones type. Yeah. Yeah, Vinnie Jones type.
And then they switch into Shake It Off, which was still pretty new at the time. It was only four
years old. And all the kids were jumping up and down. You know that thing where kids don't quite
know how to dance? So they just jump up and down because they're so excited. And you've, you're
halfway through like a neon pink drink and there's like a little alcohol in it. But maybe you had a
better drink of Carthe an hour prior. So it's like, just like kind of act like helping to keep the
buzz going. Yeah. I have to rope in my, one of my favorite places to drink in order to make this
work. And let's not forget you're in your late twenties. Everything is possible now. You're never
going to die. You're never going to die. That's the most important part of the mad tea party is
that you're in your twenties when you're seeing them. So far, this thing only made me mad for the
first time. It's made me sad. Why? What? What do you mean? I don't know. I'll look, you could put,
I'll just listen back to that later today. I don't know what could be wrong with it. Maybe something
about what you might, what you said might make you a little sad. No, I'm just saying that's part of
it. Part of it is being in your twenties. Well, look, things are still possible now that we are
in our. That's true. What are you again, Mike? Whatever it is, whatever the number is, I don't
know. Does this mean mad tea party potentially could come back somewhere? They didn't say it.
They didn't say it. They didn't say it. Honestly, the first part of the D23 panel was like fan
service. Like, but, but not in a, I don't mean that in a shitty way. I mean like, oh, it's the
Soren video recreation. Oh, you mean the intro stuff. You mean the 25 minute intro where they
didn't get to an announcement. Oh, please, Michael, it was at least 45. Yeah, what a bunch of
bullshit. Anyway, let's do more mad tea party material. Let's give the people what they want
right at the top. No, I, yeah, hey, so I think as far as like turning this into a little Oscars,
first of all, and we didn't know it at the beginning, but the Billy Crystal's in the house,
and then that they, I mean, a cold open that's like a parody or a recreation of Soren with the
man himself, Patty Warbucks, amazing. That was great. I really enjoyed that. And I think they,
as someone who has analyzed that video and thought about it a lot, I'm like the edits are the same.
They could have done this a lot crudder, and it could have been knocked out by a team that
didn't have love for the original thing, but it was like, it was pretty pitch perfect. I'm
guessing they did it because whenever they had that other Soren video a couple of months ago
with Patrick Warb, they probably all did it at the same time, I'm guessing. He looked very similar,
yeah. Yeah, kind of PR call, which what a clever little thing that they got a couple pieces of
content out of it. And then I think the big surprise, I thought when they aren't cutting to
the guy with these little beauties and then we're going to cut to the mouse, I thought that was
going to be a cameo from Eiger or Demaro or somebody. I thought that's what they were building
too. But I was not disappointed. If anything, it was maybe better to realize it was the same guy
from the video the first time around. I don't know who that actor is. I don't know if he works
there and thus it was easy to grab him again, or if they tracked down this person again just for that.
But it was nice to see him. That was really fun, yeah. I feel like the audience really popped for
that. They were pretty excited. Yeah, well they were all hammered, so of course they're going to
pop. They were hammered and they were riled up from rock and roll. You got to think about,
if you were there, besides the person who texted me, why does Mike like this? Everybody, besides
that cynic, everybody else is so amped. Honestly, they were probably laughing more because of the
rock and roll than because of the comedy content. Well the rock and roll and the one and a half
ballast point IPAs in them, you know? Yeah, you're describing precisely what I can drink in a night
now safely. The end. I can drink a half. It's good. I like the session ones for many years
because they're a lot weaker. What do you think about the grapefruit? I still don't give a shit
about the grapefruit. Wow, the bald guy is back. Jason still doesn't give a shit about the grapefruit.
Oh and now I've bought enough medications where they're like you can do whatever you want,
don't eat grapefruit on this. Like what? Don't eat grapefruit apparently interacts with a lot
of medications. It's a pretty common thing. Birth control I believe. Yes, yeah. All right, Jason,
don't get pregnant. Stay away from the grapefruit. Yeah. Keep not giving a shit. Be careful. But then
the real big opener live is that we realize there is an orchestra there and then a lot of buildup
to a piano man center stage. Will it be Elton John? Will it be Josh Groban? No, better, way better.
John Stamos. A show kickoff by Stamos in a leather jacket reminiscent of perhaps even literally the
same one he wore when Jesse and the Rippers blew the turrets off of Cinderella Castle in the Full
House episode many years ago. They are, at this point in the show I'm like well they're going for
us having just done a big Full House episode and wore Burton and like. And a tea party.
And mad tea party and they're going for some of us with that. So that was fun. It was nice to see
Stamos get to perform for a big crowd without having to sit through Mike Love implying that
he fucked his mom. It was a nice, felt like a nice break for him. And then he seemed like
sincerely emotional about being there. I mean his fandom is very clear. He got some jokes off about
owning the sign that used to be on Harbor Boulevard. He got some jokes about Disney
adults you know. There were a lot of zingers tonight. There were zingers. Between Stamos
and Deadpool there was a lot of zingers. I agree. I will say, generally, I will be the first to
groan about the comedy content of something. I did not do a lot of groaning. No, I didn't either.
I actually think that whoever was writing this, if it was individually, if it was different groups
for the different bits or one team for all of it, I thought like it was, you know, nothing I thought
was corny, cringy, like inside jokes enough. And like for them a little bit biting at times,
especially with Deadpool. But I actually did like it comedically. Now do I think that it needed two
separate comedy song and dance numbers from, okay, what, Darren Criss, Skylar Astin?
Yeah, I don't know. That felt like, I don't know, that all was fine. But I think, Mike,
you were saying it felt a little redundant. Like, okay, we're now at our like third opener.
Right. I was like, Stamos, oh, he's okay. He's opening show the song. Yeah, I guess. And now
we're here with the announcements. And it's like, no, there's another host of the show? Like,
okay, there's another musical bit. Yes. That's where it started to feel like that's when I said
there's going to be 20 songs to every one announcement for every one announcement. And
I bet you wish you would put money on that. I certainly do. That is the most true statement
of the evening. Yes. So yeah, no, it was at that point, I was like, that point, I was worried.
Yeah. Because I went, oh shit, they don't have anything to say. Yeah, nothing. I started getting
fearful at that point because I go, they've burned 15 to 20 minutes on the main part of this
presentation with just songs, Stamos and these two guys. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know why I thought
this was going to be an hour or maybe 90 minutes. Me too. They said it was going to be 90 minutes,
I think. The runtime was just shy, I think, of three hours. Yeah. Yeah. But they had listed it,
I think, as 90 minutes on the schedule. Okay. Yeah. I was pretty exhausted by the end. I felt
worn out the way I do if you're actually sitting and watching an entire Oscar telecast. I was
starting to fall asleep, then they did the big final announcement and I woke up and then I could
not get to sleep. I slept weird last night. Well, look, I don't want to spoil. I was rammy. I don't
want to spoil. Well, I understand why you'd be rammy because you knew you were getting something
big due to that announcement, but I'll hold it to the end. Yeah. But then we start getting stuff.
Let's talk about stuff that we get. I mean, Avatar right away, right? And here we start
getting into our bets because mine ended up correct on this one, that it is Avatar for DCA
with no area named more specifically than that. Right. And we get some concept art.
I'm relieved to hear DCA, relieved that they didn't say where yet and we're still left to wonder.
But I guess before that speculation, this art looks great. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because it is not the animal kingdom Pandora. We're in a whole different biome. This has been
a great couple of days for those of us who are blue-pilled because you get all this stuff and
then the day before part three is called Fire and Ash. Yeah. I think maybe some people had
grown fond of the seed bearer. But if anything, years ago, before I'd made my switch and you were
kind of carrying the Avatar torch, Mike, I heard the seed bearer and I'm like, well, this seems like
a tedious franchise to me. And now years later, we arrive at Fire and Ash. Yeah. What a fucking
metal motorhead kind of name. This is rules. This is great. I can't wait for Fire and Ash.
Yeah. Number two is water. Number three is fire. Let's go. Yeah. Yeah. The every element. We're
hitting them all. They're not doing like floating mountains in this, but it's because it's more
water-based. It's more like land water-based, but they have this like, I don't even know how to
describe it. It's like half circle sort of pattern that the rocks have taken, like the shape,
this kind of crazy. You see something like that in the movie. I don't know how you describe it.
Yeah. It's like, I don't know. Like a crescent moon almost. Yeah. Sort of on its side and pointed up
and then it kind of shrinks in size as it goes. That's a bad way to describe it, but it's very
cool looking and doesn't, I don't immediately go, ah, they're not building the mountains.
Because that would be my concern if they're like, oh, we're not doing the mountains. I go, well,
that's kind of the big part of it. Also, I think there are still maybe a couple floating mountains.
Oh, you think so? Oh, maybe I missed it. Concept art seems to be, if you look closely,
it's just not like the main deal of it is the floating mountains, but I think we got a couple
little spots of floating mountain. Wow. Yeah. So that just, the idea that we'll get to go to that
whenever we want, as long as we're still living in California, that's awesome. Yes. And the ride is
boat ride. They showed a little bit of it before, but it looks like Shanghai pirates. That's what
people are saying. It really reminds me of, just because I know it better than, I don't,
I'm not too familiar with the outside of the Shanghai vehicle, but I'm looking at it like,
this looks very like Jurassic Park, the ride. Oh, yeah, maybe. Big old kind of,
yeah, not a little calm Disney boat ride, but a big, something equipped for adventure. Yeah.
And concept art is cool. When it gets dark, the darkness that all of those creepy,
fanged creatures crawling around, I, you know, it's still, it's so hard to parse really what,
what ride system is exactly, but it implies to me that it's indoor, outdoor, both. Yes,
because they show it in the like overview of the land art. Yeah. Yeah. So it looks like that goes
outdoors at a point. Love that. That's really cool. You think maybe just one ride at this rate? They
didn't say, I don't know. I heard someone say they think maybe one smaller ride, but I don't know.
I'm not sure. You can't tell from there. Somebody said Satuli canteen, some kind of it, some version
of it. Cause in the, like the bottom right, it looks like there's maybe at least something like
that resembling the quick service in Florida, which is good. And we still, we still don't know
where. I'll say this. I'm kind of coming around to this is going to be Hollywood land. Really?
What makes you say that? Well, so they didn't say anything about Disneyland forward. I wonder if
they'll ever say anything about the phrase Disneyland forward again. Cause all that was,
was trying to get the Anaheim city council to agree to let them build anything anywhere
on their own land. That's almost like the name of the mission and never what they're going to call
the land anyway. So, so I'm still of the mind that when they say it's coming to California adventure,
it could be for that land that was achieved with the Disneyland forward program. Right. So,
so it could, it could be the Disneyland forward area, which is next to the Disneyland hotel.
Like that's, that's sort of what the Disneyland forward art was. Now it doesn't necessarily have
to be there. They could just build a third park on the Toy Story parking lot. We don't really know
a hundred percent what they're going to do. I don't know that they know that, but I kind of
suspect if this is far enough along for them to announce it and then suggest that it'll be done
in five years, it might be in a place that they know for sure they can build on.
And I've heard enough people say Hollywood land now for months and just looking at Hollywood land.
Like the pathway in the concept art looks like a long, like kind of like the entrance to Hollywood
land. Like you're looking at, I'm showing them a Google map right now. You're looking at like
all this real estate. That is a ton of space, I think. And you think in this version, we lose
Hyperion theater. Absolutely. That has to, I think it's, I think it's everything here up until
Carth, like right at Carthay, it basically starts. It feels like they're not like pumping a lot of
life into Hyperion theater. So maybe they're like getting us ready to. Right. And I've heard people
say that's going away as well and not even in relation to Avatar going here. Now you say there's
no transition. This has been your argument. Yes. And I could get, I'm wrapping my head around this
in that like, well, there's not now. And then the toughest thing is going to be Carthay into this.
But I don't know if you're, if you lose all the rest of Hollywood, if you lose that main drag
and Marvel's far enough away, there's a world where this, where this works and you just need
to like build some jungle. Right. To get you through it. To lead you past Carthay. Yeah,
plants and water will do a lot for transitioning. You can put up a big, it just thematically almost
doesn't feel right to transition that hard from old Hollywood into Pandora. But if all of, you're
saying you mean Buena Vista Street. Yes. Yeah. Whereas Buena Vista Street into Hollywood feels
pretty natural. Buena Vista Street into whatever Condor Flats is called now. Yeah. Soren and all
that feels very natural into like Napa. Why all feels very natural. And Pandora would be the
strangest thing to come out of. You've just been in thirties Hollywood, the Hollywood of yesterland
and the Hollywood of the future. The made real, you know, the thing about story is that it means
so much to all of us. Well, that's true. He can't, he got out of that one. He wriggled his way out
of that. That's like a, that's a Trump card. That's a flash bomb to any argument. There's a reason
they call me little tomorrow, tomorrow junior. They do call you little tomorrow and tomorrow
junior. So that's the only reason I'm like more thinking that that's where it's going is just
because like they have, if they're committing to it and it's going to be five years, I feel like
they would want it to go in a place that they are sure they're building. And if they've planned it
out and plan what it's going to look like and what the, what the building is, like, I guess they could
just plug it anywhere in a Toy Story scenario where they use the Toy Story lot. Did they give
a date on when they are putting the shovel in the ground on this? Well, then what's this five years?
Well, I don't know. I think you're holding to this five years. No timeline provided says Carly
Weisel on her Instagram. So what is this five years? You got to get this five years out here.
Hey, I'm just going by what, with what they said. When did they say five years? This was people
talking to PR people. That's not in the panel. That's not anything. Yeah. Well, I'm just saying
that you also in the bet, in the betting episode, you said they have to, they have to do Tomorrowland.
Why this have to, and then they aren't, I, I'm upset. I know. Well, I'm just, this is my theory.
This is, I could be wrong. Obviously I was wrong about the D 23 panel. I'm just saying that enough
people have said Hollywood land now and there's enough room there for it that I'm starting to
believe it. I'm not going to bet. I'm not going to bet on it. I'm just going to say I'm starting to
believe that this could go here. Sure. Sure. The only reason that I'm, uh, arguing against the
possibility is that I just want as much land as possible for this. I do not want to constricted,
but what you're showing me is a lot of land. If we get rid of the theater, that is a lot of land.
Um, you know, one suspicious thing is that if you look at the vague mysterious map of what the kinds
of structures that might be in the Disneyland forward zone, it looks very much like this concept
that they're showing us. It doesn't mean anything because that's not official, but that is like,
but it is art made by Disney. That sure looks like what this picture looks like. They definitely
could change their minds. I don't know. They'd be able to lose a word wieners either. Oh man,
Jason. It's got to eat hot dogs. You love the fries at award wieners. I like the fries. I'm
more concerned about corndog castle. I don't think it's long for this world. Really? I think
that's fine, right? What are we talking about putting there? Well, I think the next thing
that they announced was cocoa. Mm hmm. But where, where in the, I don't think you have,
doesn't corndog castle essentially back right up to like backstage? Mike, you've got the map.
Where's corndog castle? Isn't it by the questions everyone's been asking is, is corndog castle safe?
Look, I just like that spicy corndog. Corndog castle is right here, which is next to that
little gift shop and then in between the gift shop and goofy sky school. What's behind corndog
castle? It's the hotel. Then you're fine. Okay. You're fine, Jason. All right. Relax, relax.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There will always be, you know, I don't remember Walt's quote, but isn't it
something like Disneyland will never be done as long as there's corndogs in the world? That's
right. That's what he said. That's right. It's kind of, yeah, maybe it's something the robot will say.
It'll be great to hear the robot. It's going to sound great out of the robot's mouth. But yeah,
if we're going in, this is where I was, I will say my two big grins in this was like, I think this
Pandora stuff looks fantastic. Yeah, yeah. And right after that, another boat ride, a boat ride
you've never heard of. This didn't come up in the betting. We talked about the possibility of
something Cocoa, but with no genre of ride announced. And that was more, that was something I
said about Magic Kingdom, never saw it come in California Adventure Cocoa. That was a big
gasp for me. This is one of my favorite parts of the panel. Yeah. Yeah. I've never heard it discussed.
I guess somebody, I was talking to somebody else after this and they were saying they had heard it
maybe Disneyland, but I had only heard it in like the idea of it going in Magic Kingdom in Florida.
So yeah, I was not, I was like, Ooh, okay. That's cool. Like that was surprised by that.
Yeah. That they, and now this was a kind of a big gasp at the panel, I feel, because they just sort
of showed concept art before explaining it. And you quickly see there's a boat there.
And then they went on to say that it's sort of inspired by the old school, that it's kind of a
pirate. Yeah. Pirates of the Caribbean reminiscent attraction. Slow moving. I love, I love the boat
situation. I love that we're two new boat rides in California. California Adventure is going to be
stacked if all this gets done. Yeah. And yeah, look, as a fan of slow moving boat rides,
besides one notable exception, I am really happy that in this day and age, we get a new one
in the parks based on a film I think is delightful. And really technologically advanced
audio animatronics. Oh, sure. Yeah. Oh, I'd love to see how these skeletons come to life. Yeah,
that's going to look awesome. If we have to guess where that's going. And if it's not Disneyland
forward, I do have a guess. I think it's going behind, uh, in credit coaster. Cause there is so
much real estate here behind in credit coaster. What is the building you're showing? Is that,
I mean, there's a bunch of buildings, uh, Toy Story made way mania actually is over
here. No, no, no, it's over. Where is it? Sorry. Toy Story is here. I think. Isn't this Toy Story?
Oh, maybe. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I believe. And then so, so there's a good amount of room here.
There's a lot more room there than there is when we're talking about the like paradise.
Paradise gardens park. We say the full name. There's like no room over here. Oh, you're right.
That's what I threw out because they've been doing kind of like, uh, some cocoa festival.
Correct. Like a good thing. Uh, but yeah, you're right. That's not really ride room. Now that I
see it on an, on an overhead, but if it's a slow moving boat ride, it doesn't maybe need so much
real estate. And I feel like you could maybe put it in and slot it in here, but it could just all
be, and you're, you're thinking that because it's Pixar, it's Pixar pier. Yeah. And I don't know
what they would do the entrance to it. I sort of don't like it for, because I think the vibe of
this will not be at all like the, the carnival entry point. Yeah. And I'd love for this to have
some exterior place setting that, you know, be, I would hate that it's like the carnival exterior
and then you're not in the world of cocoa until you're in the building. Yeah. Uh, that's a good
point. I mean, I think that's the only place to put it unless it's a Disneyland Ford and you go
over the road and you go over Disneyland drive, which it might be. Maybe, I mean, maybe that is,
maybe Avatar goes there, maybe Coco's next to it, but they didn't say Coco land also.
That's right. So they just said Coco ride. So that makes me more think that it,
Hey, but listener, if you're, if you're over by paradise gardens park, uh, check out the bathroom
over there has a very elaborate route 66 tile work in it that really doesn't quite make any
sense anymore. I think we have an episode in the can that hasn't come out in which you talked about
the bathroom. So you're getting ahead of the bathroom. We got a lot of content about this.
I just want to remind people to go see it. And in case God forbid it should disappear.
There's a lot of talk about like, I will chain myself to this building. If it doesn't Jason's
chained himself to those bathrooms. That's right. Yeah. I think you can fit like a pirates
of the Caribbean like size building over behind in credit coaster. Yeah. Yeah. If they wanted to do
that. Um, yeah, but I hear what you're saying. The facade should look kind of cool and weird
and inviting and cause they're, yeah, I think there's a chance to like, the vibe should be
more Coco ish, not just like appear there. Yeah. I want a lot of time, but I want a lobby that
lets me marinate in that, in that vibe. Uh, do we think there's any possibility
that any of what we've just said, maybe particularly avatar goes into a grizzly peak
and the grizzly peak. I've heard no talk of that. I, here's what I, I sort of don't believe it as
soon as it's out of my mouth. And part of that is because does that not permanently change
the fabric and the of, and the views of the grand California zone. Right. And I don't think you want
to do, if you're paying for that hotel, I don't think you want a lot of construction for a long
time. And while avatar could sort of that's picturesque and water, I think it ruins it.
I don't know. I, it's not, it's not what I would do if I were in charge of them. Yeah. I don't
think that's happening. I also think it's like, I don't know. I feel like, I feel like they're
going to put an IP on grizzly peak on the grizzly river rapids. One of these days when they find
like, I don't know, I guess, I don't know, I guess they could just demolish the whole thing. It just
seems like a lot of work. It seems like a lot of work. And it also seems like you're losing
something. And then the hotel is not themed anymore to the area. And those trees are finally,
it took 20 years, but those trees grew in nicely for sure. And also I don't want it. I love that
area. I don't want that area. I really like it. I, I tried looking up the, for like around my
birthday in October, like how much is it to rent vacation club points at the grand California?
Cause you always hear like, Oh, try running vacation club points for a cheaper
stay. And I believe it was $752 a night. Yeah. Well, you better start saving.
Well, it's only six 50 or so, the new Disneyland tower. No, I didn't know that you can rent points,
but I also didn't want to ask more questions about this. I knew exactly what was going on in
your head. You didn't have to say that. You clocked my silence. He doesn't know what Jason's quite
talking about. I didn't know you could do it. Uh, he doesn't want to open up this. We're already
going way long on this episode. We know this is going to be a five hour episode. Um, so no,
I saw it. I saw it happen. Okay. All right. So yeah, we moved on. Um, I now I'll, I'll say just
in order of things, one of my bets was that there will be a music performance by a performer
that I have never heard of. I wish I declared that I get $5 every time it happens because
it started to get set. Now I was getting worried because there were plenty that I had heard of,
but then we start getting into, uh, Rachel Potter. I still don't know who the, uh, a cappella group
was. It was Pentatonix. Okay. That would, I would have assumed, but I, I missed the ID on that one.
Um, I, and then this is much later, but boy, do I not know what Shaboosie is. And, uh, now that I,
now that I know, I gotta keep going. That was an electric performance of again, a good night for
Mike musically. You got a life as a highway. I got a life as a highway. I heard of Shaboosie
actually. I don't know him very well. Um, but that I was a lot, I was not paying so I forget
what I was doing. I was giving my daughter dinner or something at this point. So I want to go back
and watch. I hope they, I do hope they put this on Disney plus so I can go back and see Shaboosie do
life highway. Yeah. Shaboosie, uh, I knew about cause Jane and I were watching some performances
from the BET awards because the musical performances, they always go really,
really all out at the BET awards. And Shaboosie, I believe, um, kind of had a big hit with kind
of a country-fied cover of the Jay Kwan song, Tipsy. And then at the end of the performance,
Jay Kwan. Let the record reflect. Jason checked his notes. That was not in his head. Jason looked at
notes. I think you could hear it. You can listen back. You can listen to the note check. Well,
just at Google, I just didn't want to get the, I knew it as everyone in the club get tipsy. I
remember the Jay Kwan song, of course. Um, but in the BET, so he does this performance, tons of
actors on the stage. There's a bar set. And then at the end, Jay Kwan comes out from behind the bar
and everyone cheers. And it was pretty fun. So when everyone does a rousing cheer, hurrah, they say
for Jay Kwan. Everybody in the club getting hammered. Everybody in the club, that being the
Honda center. When they opened up the back wall and, and like Mater was saying, my friend,
I thought it was going to be Lightning Queen. And so I wasn't disappointed to see Shaboosie,
but I was confused. Sounds like you were disappointed to see Shaboosie. You were
hoping to see a car, a talking car. Uh, I mean, I think Shaboosie should have come out
riding on Lightning McQueen. But that would have really made sense. Why was he animated?
And then he's like, but my friend here, and then, and then my friend here. And then Lightning McQueen
comes out. I just didn't even really know Mater knew Shaboosie that well. You're saying more,
you were surprised. You got to follow their socials. Oh, they've been, oh, they're always,
yeah, you know, like Greece together, the Bombers. Yeah. Um, let's, I mean, let's, why don't we jump
around a little bit? Sure. Let's talk about that. That's something I don't think every, like,
you know what? We kind of landed on it right before it happened. And this was this, this was
a mic bit, I believe was some version of Radiator Springs, though it's not exactly, they describe
it as something where you leave Radiator Springs and it becomes more of a picturesque pastoral,
almost European, uh, car race. I don't know. This, this to me seems like this suggests to me
frontier land is going away in Magic Kingdom. This is in the frontier. And like, it doesn't,
I just feel like we're changing, we're changing that as a certain point. I think in Magic Kingdom,
I'm guessing, cause I'm like, where are they at? This is now we're in this weird, you know,
we're talking about behind Big Thunder and actually specifically the bet was behind Big Thunder.
Money might have to be returned to people if it turns out that these things are not meant
for behind Big Thunder. I think they're going behind Big Thunder. Okay. Okay. I think this
in Villains Land is going there. Okay. But then what's, does any, cause what, what goes away
with cars? Because not, not country bear assuredly now that there's a new show. Well,
we're talking about getting rid of the riverboat in Florida, Tom Sawyer Island. That is the rumor.
Chain yourself to it. The rumor is Tom Sawyer Island. Again, I don't know anything. This is
just what people say, but people are saying today that the riverboat and Tom Sawyer Island, and I
don't know if any water, like, I don't know if any water remains, but that's what, that's what the
word is. And you're hearing it more and more. We're hearing it more and more. Have you been
sitting here thinking the same thing that Mike's saying and a guy, and I talked to a guy and you're
hearing it and there's a lot of this and a lot of, I've heard it. This is very politician speak
coming out of me today. Yeah. Yeah. I, this is kind of par for the course. I feel like with
any theme park rumors, so I don't think it's specific to Mike, but I know what he's doing.
Sure. He's doing a lot of it. I feel I'm doing a ton of it. I mean, there's, there's a couple
like live streams I watched in anticipation of this app doing this episode. And then there were
people on the ground and then there were other people I was just talking to speculating. I'm
trying to keep everyone's, I'm trying to keep it anonymous. I'm trying to keep it. I'm not trying
to say which streamers I watched or what other videos I watched. So we're keeping it. I don't,
cause I don't want to get anyone in trouble necessarily either. That's true. But if you name
a name, I name a name. Yeah. We already mentioned SoCal on some parks, which I do watch live
streams pretty regularly and they will go to like six flags and not sing one night and keep the
live stream going for the drive to it. And it is very stupid. Huh? Do they set up a little tripod?
They have like a little tripod in the car and they just talk about what's on the radio and
say hi to the chat. Wow. Okay. So it seems like a lot of work. Yeah. Well, I think they're going to
read, I don't know, country bears and Tiana and everything. I think they're going to call it
something different in that area. Pecos bills is going to go away. Probably people, people in the
last couple of weeks were like, Oh, maybe country bear barbecue jamboree. But then I think it's
probably more Tiana's is going to go in there like a Tiana's restaurant. I don't know what they're
going to call the whole thing. We will get to it, but they've renamed our sort of greater country
area. Yeah. We're Bayou country, which I don't care for so much. I didn't know that. Yeah. That
was a quick, it was during a song. I went to the bathroom once or twice. It was 30 hours. Yeah,
I know. It was a very long. Yeah. So I think I went to the bathroom once during a medley. And then
one time I went to the bathroom and I came back and they're talking about the Spiderman roller
coaster. So I had to scroll back and everything. So it's got like, where is that going?
The gesture you just did for scrolling back was like what a dog would do while swimming.
Yeah. It's what I felt. I had to paddle back. I had all my devices researched where it was in
full effect. The research for it was humming. I like to think you had stuffed animal assistance.
The Apple watch was vibrating so much for the group techs blowing up, you know?
Oh yeah. Now guys, I'm at work. Jason's wrist is like shattered now because of the vibrations
had destroyed his bones from his Apple watch. Just destroyed. It's just purple like when Walter White
burns the plastic off. There'll be a Pooh Bear episode coming out of Podcast the Ride somewhat
soon, but we talk about greater country there. So obviously that's been recorded already.
So forgive us when we're talking about greater country, but it is a good, like I guess they could
call, I don't know, still greater country now, greater country now, but like you could call that
part in Magic Kingdom Bayou country. I don't know. Not sure what, I don't know. I can't picture
enough what it butts up against. Yeah. I'd have to, I'll have to look at the map. We're Bayou
country. We're Bayou country. Now Pooh is in Bayou country. That doesn't make any sense. That is
weird. Yeah. That's weird. I don't know if they're going to, I don't think they're going to change
Pooh out or anything, but that's even weirder because I, on this upcoming episode, I'll spoiler
alert, say I had a problem calling a place where Pooh is critter country because Pooh's not a
critter to me. He's an English bear from an English boy's imagination. Not a critter. A critter is a
down south kind of an animal that gets up to mischief or whatever. A certain kind of mischief.
Yeah, a different kind of mischief. Less polished, stately kind of mischief.
Mike, every few episodes, Mike starts pining for the empire. It was not the same when the British
released all their colonies. Yes. And that ties directly into me not wanting Pooh to be in a
place called critter country. So that, I don't know if that's going to have to be sorted out,
but yeah, we are Bayou country now, which is fine. It doesn't mean anything. I know. I would say
the day-to-day in our lives, it affects almost nothing. Not going to affect a lot, but I do,
I like the word critter. I do too. That's the only thing, and the alliteration of it. As long as we're
allowed to still refer to critters, that this is an area, but Bayou country is full of critters,
then I'm good to go. Oh, tons of critters on that ride. There's a lot of critters on there.
That's why I think critter country is still out there. And I want to get that hot sauce. I want
to get the Mama Odie hot sauce. Sure. Where will you be able to get the Mama Odie? Is that a gift
shop or is that a restaurant? It's a glass bottle. You get it at the shop, at the Tiana shop.
All right. Cool. Great. You can get it. And that's November? November 15th. November 15th. Great.
Pushed back a little bit because the one in Florida is having so many problems.
It barely runs, apparently. It shuts down a lot. The robots are broken.
Well, good. We've got the kinks there. Right. And I think the team then, the team all had
to move to California to finish setting this one up. But there's so many problems that are not
being fixed in Florida. And I think people, I've heard like, they're not quite sure what's going
on exactly. I mean, the bones of it, Splash Mountain was not in super hot shape the last few years.
Yeah. But I think this is like robot stuff. Oh, interesting. I think this is robot stuff.
Again, I don't know what people are saying. But I think the way that the robots, I think when you
go by in the boats, like something triggers the actions and stuff. Okay. I think there's some
problem with that sometimes. But I think there's also like a hundred other problems, though.
Right. I think that's why that has been pushed more to November. I heard people saying maybe it'll be
next year, but November they've announced. Remember they said, yeah. Yeah. I now also,
elsewhere in the Splash Mountain genre of attraction, we're getting Splash Lion King.
Splash Lion King is happening because there is not a Splash Mountain in France.
No, they never did it. But now in Disney Adventure World, the soon to be name of that other park,
of the second park, because we've been shuffling around, what are the expansion zones there?
And now it's starting to seem less and less like there's some iteration of Galaxy's Edge.
The way they announced, frozen for there, correct?
Yeah. With a date for that.
Okay. That one's got a date. And then we are getting King Mountain. What are you trying to
think of a better Simba Mountain? Bride Rock.
Oh yeah. I guess. I know. But I still want it to be a mountain.
Simba Mountain. I want it to be Simba Mountain. Simba Mountain.
Yeah, I know. I mean, you look at it and there's
no question of what you're looking at. It's just so obviously a Splash Mountain inspired.
So go ahead. This is sort of, I mean, it is tangential,
but I was also thinking, I'm like, what else could you re-theme Splash Mountain to?
And it's like, I guess you could do like a Cave of Wonders and have
water spewing out of the cave's mouth and have a flume coming out of it.
Yeah, yeah. That's kind of fun.
Yeah. But then to sort of to Arabianize-
Well, where it's located, yeah.
It's where it helps that this is going to be from the ground up.
But it makes sense. I like it. I like this concept art. Everybody kind of oohed at this.
It feels sort of like, I mean, it is like not halfway around the world, but it's very far away.
So I don't feel like it's not super urgent news to me, but I like this as a genre of
ride. And it also made me think, oh, maybe this is like something that would motivate the changeover
in Tokyo, because Tokyo weirdly quietly just is staying Splash Mountain. Just no kind of
nobody's talking about it. But maybe this will open, be well received, be enticing enough that-
Maybe Tokyo votes to do this. I don't know.
Could they do this in Animal Kingdom? Maybe that'd be fun.
They could. It's just then they have another Splash Mountain, I guess.
They do. But there was a time where there was Star Tours and Body Wars.
Yeah, that's true.
And those were essentially the same. I think that was a wonderful time.
And if the cars- I don't get enough.
And if the cars thing beyond Big Thunder is Radiator Springs, basically,
with just new stuff, it's the same ride system. So it's test track, I mean.
So yeah, I guess it's precedent for that.
That's not unprecedented in Disney.
I bet the exterior of that will look different than the Radiator Springs out here.
Sure.
And these both look like Splash Mountain. These both look like-
Tiana's looks like Splash Mountain, and Lion King would look like Splash Mountain.
Sure.
Sure. Maybe that's the only thing that would prevent it, but maybe not. Who knows?
Yeah. Maybe they don't care.
I will give them credit because it does feel like, at least this time in Imagineering,
they are conscious of not just making the exact same ride on a different coast.
They are, at the very least, dressing things up.
Even if Radiator Springs is the exact same layout,
it's going to be a different ride in a different location.
And it feels like that's common across the board.
It's not just going to be an Indy from Japan or Indy from California.
They're going to do a new thing, even if it's the same track.
It's a different layout, and it's a lot of the same basic stuff.
I wonder what the internal feeling ended up being about Galaxy's Edge, because it's odd.
And what they would have if the two were slightly different and not,
in this kind of singular case in Park's history, exactly, eerily the same.
Yeah. Because, yeah, at the very least, you would change up the restaurants in Galaxy's Edge or
something. A couple things could be different, obviously.
But each prop is the same. It's so weird.
I bet they feel like that was a little bit of a mistake.
Yeah.
It's very exact.
Hey, while we're talking Galaxy's Edge,
there was a Galaxy's Edge mention in the middle of the Fortnite stuff.
Oh, yeah. If you went deep into the Fortnite forest.
There was an actual announcement.
Yeah. So there was a weird tune-in on Fortnite at 830.
It was way later than that by the time it happened.
And then, boy, was there a lot of Fortnite time.
This was what occupied that slot, the Brian Cornell target, the arranged-in-a-board room.
This was the thing that was the most like, well, this has to be done.
We are going to do 15 minutes or more about Fortnite.
What I was shocked by was that all of the biggest power players in Hollywood are in...
You're giving me Pete Docter and Feige and Filoni all at the same time, and it's for this?
It's the Fortnite tie-in.
Very weird.
So strange.
And Chromio.
There we go.
That popped me big.
Chromio.
I was going to say I like them, but you say pop,
and I don't want to support anything that gets the...
Aren't you guys creeped out every time you say popping or they popped?
It's a wrestling term.
Very comfortable with it.
I know, but if you take it out, imagine if you're me.
Aren't you weirded out?
Do you understand why I find it so creepy?
If you're not used to the weirdness on this show after so many years,
I don't know what to tell you.
Yeah.
You're going to have to get another job.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
So that's all I have to say.
I'll do my best to say big applause break.
I get if I'm popping out a new phrase, but that's it.
We've been saying that for years at this point.
It's never...
No part of it has diminished for me.
It creeps me out.
I almost said it popped me hard, which I guess that's a little closer to being a dirty annuant.
I would say it is 100% absolutely something you would say about sex.
It popped me big.
Usually it just means John Cena showed up for The Undertaker or whatever.
And who wouldn't pop big and hard?
But yeah, no, we got a big Chromio performance.
This is the first of all.
The kind of music that they pull from is always so confusing to me,
but I really like Chromio.
I've seen them live.
It was, I would say, a lesser experience to watch them doing grim grinning ghosts
and then saying, y'all heard of Fortnite?
Heard of it.
But still fun.
I don't know.
Yeah, that was funny.
My kid's onto Roblox now.
Roblox.
I have to get Robux for his birthday every year.
Robux?
Robux is the currency, I believe.
Oh, is that what it is?
I thought you meant the juice store.
Oh, no.
No, that's Robux.
No.
Too much sugar.
No, but then, yeah, deep within that, if you were,
I was really barely holding on there until buried deep in it was a,
oh, wait, oh, they're saying a ride thing.
OK, and that's, hey, this is actually a quietly big one.
This is awesome, yeah.
One of the biggest Galaxy's Edge complaints
that we have not had any other missions on Millennium Falcon Smuggler's run,
and we're getting it.
And it is Mandalorian and Grogu.
Mike, what's his face?
I'm Mike.
Who has a damn problem with this favorite movie?
Not what you think, not what you think.
Aren't you proud of the favorite movie?
Not what you think.
OK.
I'm upset with myself because when we were making the bets,
there were two things I was thinking about Galaxy's Edge.
What could I bet on?
Number one, old characters in the land,
or number two, a new level for the Millennium Falcon ride.
He thought about saying it.
And I thought about both of them.
But then I said one is much more expensive than the other.
I bet they're not going to do it,
and I bet there won't be an announcement.
I'm kicking myself for that reason and not because it's not my old friend.
OK, OK.
That's now why I'm upset.
I was worried.
That was a grouchy face.
I was really mad at myself last night for not going with the other one.
Well, if we're checking in on the betting here and there,
that was one of your biggest mistakes.
It was a big bet on that we were opening up the floodgates
and we're meeting all the characters in the Galaxy's Edge.
I still think that's happening, but it was not an announcement.
They didn't say it there, and it was a bigger bet.
And I think both Jason and I benefited from it.
Yes.
Well, Jason, though, had the no mention of Galaxy's Edge at all bet.
So I lost that.
So that canceled itself out.
He said they weren't going to even mention it all.
But certainly, you know what?
Oh, this changes my calculations.
If you took a snack break during the Fortnite segment,
you would think they had to mention Galaxy's Edge.
That's true.
If you didn't hear it, then yes, Jason won.
But does that mean if it was a $10 bet,
does that mean I get the $10 because of the three statements?
I was the only correct one.
What did you say about it?
I said there would be no none of any.
Jason would be incorrect if he said there's no Galaxy's Edge mention.
I was correct in saying no new characters added.
Yeah, but then you also said you thought there was going to be a hotel mention, I think.
What?
Star Cruiser?
Yeah, it's a different bet.
Different bet, OK.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I accounted for that.
But am I right?
Because can we make this ruling?
Do I get $10 in this category?
I guess you didn't make the bet, although I guess Jason's is a separate bet.
So in a way.
It is a separate bet.
OK.
Yeah, OK.
But then doesn't his bet imply, sorry, listener, so this isn't interesting at all.
Yeah, this is very dry.
If the bet was no mention of Galaxy's Edge characters, Mike said yes, I said no,
and Jason said there will not be Galaxy's Edge at all.
Is that his bet in this category?
I think it's in the category.
It's probably in the category, but then your bet is almost the same as Jason's,
but you're just abstaining from even betting at all.
No, I know.
I specifically bet that there would be no characters added.
All right.
We all made three statements and only mine was correct.
We did a lot of bad betting in this episode.
This changes because this changes a lot what's going on.
Sure, yeah.
Ooh, actually.
Oh, shit.
That gets another bunch of money.
Yeah.
Oh, I mean, not radically, but something.
But I am mad at myself because that was absolutely,
I was going to pick one of the two to make a bet on and I picked the wrong one.
I like when I'm heading into something and feel the need to apologize to the listeners.
Yeah, you were right to apologize.
But anyway, here we go.
This is buried in the show, but a big old Galaxy's Edge.
This could change so much.
Yeah, and if it goes well and then they keep doing it.
Well, that would be amazing.
Yeah, then we're, yeah.
And the tie-in was that it uses Unreal Engine as well as the Fortnite stuff.
So cool, whatever.
And in the artwork, they show Mandalorian kind of like zooming by on a jet pack.
Character in the actual ride part of it.
That's really good.
Yeah, yeah.
Because I don't like that there's things that Star Tours can do that Falcon can't.
And now we're sort of getting away from, we're getting closer.
Yes, because all the complaints we've had is Star Tours.
There's like these moments you remember on the actual ride
that you don't get in Millennium Falcon because it's a game
and they just didn't put stuff like that in there.
You don't get actual characters in the video part of the Millennium Falcon ride
like you do on Star Tours.
It feels like maybe they can address all of it.
They could truly fix the ride.
They could fix it.
I mean, maybe the controls are still going to be a problem
because they find those annoying still, but they could do something to those.
But if we're not, if it's not that you get to be in a place
that you maybe have worshipped and thought about since you were a kid,
and you see an incredible animatronic and then you go,
and then the aftermath is that you go and deal with coaxium.
If instead you go on an adventure with currently relevant popular heroes,
that's a pretty big, that's a big shift in just like what are the acts of that experience.
So this one's kind of quietly a really good one.
Yes, I completely agree.
But you might be helping the Mandalorian and Grogu score some coaxium.
I hadn't thought about that.
Am I the only one falling for that?
I don't hate that.
Yeah.
That's fine.
They can go after coaxium.
Yeah, sure.
That's not like that's the problem.
Yeah, yeah.
If you're running through their lens.
Don't eat that.
We need to go get coaxium.
So here's something to maybe devote a little bit of time to.
Is this Monsters, Inc. situation.
So undeniably good news, Monsters, Inc. land.
Entire Monstropolis coming.
Nothing much said about the specific details of that,
although there was concept art where people have kooky googly-eyed ice cream cones.
Those are cool, yeah.
That seems like fun.
But like, you know, seems like a pleasant little, as Monstropolis is,
when they're taking a walk to work, you're like, what a pleasant little town,
and it's cool you get to be there.
Then big piece of this, the door coaster.
And I saw a lot of, I'm ripping off this observation from online,
but this is a big year for things that have been rumored for 20 years.
Right.
Yeah.
We're going back to some old internet rumors with a door coaster.
And I remember always wondering, OK, but what are we?
Are we a door?
How is this going to work?
And then the concept art is pretty jaw-dropping where, no, you're not a door.
You're next to Boo and Mike and Sully, and they're on a door,
and you are on some souped-up suspended vehicle that is powered by the canisters of screams
or laughs.
I don't know where we are in the timeline.
Right.
Presumably screams, because you'll be screaming on the ride.
Makes sense.
So like big old, the big tanks at the top, and your vehicle is the same color as the tank.
This is cool design.
This is like a way to get into that world, which I continue to love and my son likes very much.
All for this.
This ride seems great.
Yeah.
First suspended coaster.
Can't believe this.
Yeah, I know.
Isn't that odd?
It is true.
The more I thought of it, I was like, yeah, I guess they're right.
But yeah, this rumor is certainly like, this rumor is old enough to get a driver's license.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, two have long ago, too, yeah.
I mean, there's pictures of the balloons, like the whatever they call them,
not trial balloons, but what do they call the balloons?
It might be trial balloons.
Yeah, test balloons, high balloons.
Here in Disney California Adventure, in the area with Monsters Inc, with the Manatee Party area,
of course.
But there are pictures people have of like, oh, here's, they're trying to see how high
a show building would be for a Monsters Inc door coaster.
I remember this over a decade ago, over in that area.
So this has been floating around so long, and it's finally happening in five years.
And we get it with Billy Crystal's blessing, which is fun, he's fun.
I don't want to get distracted by Billy Crystal material, because I think what we really have to
talk about is kind of not jokey.
It's the most serious thing we have to talk about, because this is, of course, great news,
great news for Disney's Hollywood studios, which despite having all these blockbuster attractions,
still feels odd and incomplete.
So this is great.
However, as I was looking at it online, there seemed to be an almost definitive group think
that this is replacing Muppet Vision 3D, and maybe even Star Tours.
I don't like this one bit.
It's selfish.
I don't buy any, even with a new experience, I don't buy that Millennium Falcon somehow
makes Star Tours irrelevant.
Love Star Tours.
Why would you get rid of Star Tours?
And then Muppets, come on.
That's the last place we got it.
Did they ever put it back in California?
I genuinely don't know.
No, it's still, is it still, is it even open?
Oh, it's Fuller Magic, Fuller Magic, yeah.
God, I forgot, I just never heard that part of town.
So I just think, why?
Why do you kill two attractions when, in my mind, there is a real dead zone in this park,
and that is Star Wars Launch Bay, former animation courtyard.
Kills me that it's a dead zone because, oh my God, taking this animation tour when I was a kid,
the heart of the park changed my life.
I ate up that tour, and it's so sad that it's been nothing for a long time,
but it has been nothing for a long time.
I feel like, how do you not fill in that dead zone?
Why do you evict the Star Wars and Muppet universes?
I don't know.
I will say this.
I didn't see a consent.
I saw people very sure they knew what they were talking about and say it was
Star Wars and Muppets, but then there were people that were sure it was not,
and it was what you were saying.
Okay.
Then there were people, I don't know what she landed on,
and I saw Alicia Stella saying Rock and Roller Coaster,
and I was like, oh, I don't think it's that.
I'm not that up as a possibility.
It could be.
I mean, it felt like there were three or four places people thought it could be,
and I couldn't find, like, I couldn't find a consensus among everyone.
Everyone seemed confused, and like I said earlier,
the art seemed to suggest different things.
The different pieces of art suggested different places.
I polled our audience, and this is just people's feeling.
I don't know.
Maybe some people voting know something,
but when I say where is Monsters, Inc. going,
65% as of this record say animation slash launch bay.
Yeah.
21% roughly say Rock and Roller, and only 13 say Muppets.
This at least shows you, like, this is more about, like, common sense.
Yeah, common sense.
I think it would be so shocking if it turned out to be Muppets.
I feel like they put so much time and money into making that baseline taphouse,
buy the Muppets, knowing that Star Wars was going to be a mess.
They had to have a pocket that was pleasant to be in,
and kind of in the same way of thinking,
back by Rock and Roller Coaster, that Lightning McQueen show is not that old.
True.
So to bulldoze either of those does seem a little out of left field,
as opposed to the animation courtyard in Star Wars launch bay,
which is kind of nothing.
I guess that Little Mermaid show is getting redone soon.
That's the biggest issue here, is that that is new.
But is there a way to, I don't know the space well enough,
is there a way to sort of leave that its own thing?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Turn the entrance around, like, make you come in from a different part of the building.
I don't know.
I'm looking at it, that's some animation courtyard right here,
and launch bay right here.
I just don't know what the size, it's a land which makes me think they need more space
than the animation courtyard and the launch bay.
But then if you go over here and buy Star Tours, I'm like,
I don't really know how it fits in.
Like, I don't know, what does it take out?
Like, does it, Indiana Jones stunt show is over here.
Well, is that a possibility as well?
It's possible, I guess.
I just, I don't know, is really what I'm saying.
Like, I look at it and it looks difficult to put it,
it looks difficult to slot a land in, in both of these places to me.
It's all strange.
So I'm not sure, I'm really not sure.
I didn't think about Indiana Jones, but with a ride going in Animal Kingdom
is a justification for no two Indies.
But they own Lucasfilm now.
Yeah, and if that's still eating people, if that's still getting the crowd.
It takes people off the board, you know,
it takes people out of the walkways and rides and restaurants.
For a long span of time, yeah.
I just think in that park, where the real problem with that park is like little experiences,
which this isn't going to rectify because that's going to be another like two-hour line kind of.
It's all great, there's just, we're missing like,
we need a lot of D tickets here that we don't have.
Yeah, I mean like.
This remains the problem.
So don't get rid of Muppets.
I know, that's, yes.
Or Star Tours, they're both in that category, I think.
But like you look at the just, this is Toy Story Land right here,
and maybe it's not going to be as big as Toy Story Land,
but that coaster needs a lot of real estate.
But do you not just like kill offices?
What's behind Animation Courtyard that we can't get rid of?
Maybe that's what it is.
Yeah, I think if you look at a theme park map, like what they give you in the park.
Not the overheads, but what they give you in the park.
And it's green in the map.
Green means go away.
That means anything that is green can go away.
I mean, yeah, maybe you're right.
Maybe you just take out all these office buildings here
and you go in through where Animation Courtyard was.
I think so.
I mean, that's the most room.
This is what I want.
Why do you punish these good characters who we know and love?
Hopefully that's what it is.
Because yeah, I feel like it butts up against like the perimeter of the park
if you put it over by Star Tours.
There's also very few, they're running out of room for just like kind of chill area,
I guess around the lake and then Sunset Boulevard back at that opening or food court.
There aren't a lot of places to just chill while everything's like a 90 minute wait, you know?
True, and you're saying that Muppet Zone's a little mellow.
Yeah, a little mellow.
Because no one's going in it anymore.
It's sparsely attended.
Mama Melrose there.
I don't like it.
I just feel like that might be the case.
I mean, yeah, yeah.
I want it to stay.
Like, they cannot possibly get rid of Pizza Rizzo, can they?
A Pizza Rizzo-less Disney world?
Not before we do our episode.
We have to, yeah, we got a lot of-
Next time we go, we gotta do a Pizza Rizzo episode.
Yeah, yeah.
I love Muppets.
I'm not saying that because I don't like it.
I'm just wondering.
I just find that you said like,
oh, you gotta chill out at a place where there's not a lot of people,
and you said Muppets is that area.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, he means a good kind of chill,
like the tap house.
Fairfax area, the tap house.
Sure.
Yeah, around Gertie.
If I had to bet, I don't think it's going away.
I think it's this other, but I think you're right.
Okay.
That's my guess, but I've been wrong many times.
I saw someone online going like,
well, they build an animation court,
or they can connect it to Toy Story Land,
and that feels copacetic having those two lands-
Sure.
... next to each other.
Yeah.
If anyone from Disney is...
Because you just knew, there's no way,
even if it is true and it is Muppets,
they're not going to...
If they say it in that arena somehow,
if they say, we're saying goodbye to the Muppets,
then everybody takes the many, many drinks
in which they're getting hammered in the Honda Center,
and those are all on Josh Demaro's head.
Those voodoo rangers.
Yeah, they're going right for it.
No, yeah.
That would have been bad news.
Yeah, for sure.
Is there a timetable on this?
Did they say?
I don't think so, but maybe I'm wrong.
Assaulting Cart, because Carly laid it out with a nice post.
Oh, yeah, she had a whole...
With the dates.
Scan the F.Crew there.
I don't think so, but I could be wrong.
So, well, I guess I only ask that-
Oh, construction begins 2025.
Oh, they did say that.
Okay, 2025.
So, we'll know soon.
I mean, we'll know soon,
because they'll start demolishing those buildings
behind animation courtyard, if that's the case.
Yeah.
What else?
I feel like that's a lot of the biggest stuff.
Animal Kingdom.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's the big one we haven't hit.
Yeah, Tropical Americas.
Yeah, so Indiana Jones.
No Harrison on stage.
No Harrison, they got a short round, though.
Yeah, yeah, he was up there.
He's great.
It was so nice to see him.
I wish he was on the ride.
That was a cool trick.
Is he on the ride?
No, I said I wish he was going to be on the ride.
I wish he was on the ride.
It'd be fun.
But yeah, No Harrison, that's a little lost for Mike.
That's right.
We're tracking it.
This was the Harrison spot for this.
They thought about it.
I was getting nervous the whole time.
You mean they prepared it in case he decided that.
Well, I think the guest conductor joke,
and it turns around and it's him.
That could have been Harrison.
Could have been Harrison, yeah.
But it was happy to see Key.
You think he's going to wave his arms around
to the degree a conductor does?
You got to put $10,000 in his pocket.
He holed up at Comic-Con.
His arms were going flailing wildly.
I guess that's true.
Maybe he got $10,000 for it.
He might, yeah, possibly.
Just saying, he did his arms.
You better have that Trader Joe's Peanut Butter Pretzel Nuggets
if you're getting me to Orange County.
Are you just saying what you need to get to Orange County
in a Harrison voice?
Peanut Butter Pretzel Nuggets in a bottle,
that wolf bottle of Chardonnay for Trader Joe's.
That he brings to a Halloween party?
Yeah, he brings to Halloween.
I think he could go nicer than the wolf or the stomping grape.
Hopefully.
I like the stomping grape.
But we're getting, yeah, Indiana Jones,
where Dinosaur is being rethemed.
Yes, confirmed.
This is another one I got right.
Confirmed, but no name.
Yes, I said name, right?
I thought we were getting a name.
I think you stayed out of it.
Oh, OK.
Good.
Thank God.
I was thinking we might get a name, though.
Yeah, no.
They kind of, well, yeah.
Well, some names, some no names.
This is starting soon, too.
The construction is happening.
So it's interesting they didn't get it.
It seems like end of the year, yeah.
They didn't give a name.
They aren't sure yet.
But they're closing Dino Land in phases
so that they're giving us all the opportunity
to say goodbye to Dinosaur.
I don't think I'm going to take them up on that opportunity.
I'm not going to get screamed at by the Allosaurus one more time.
I'm scared of the ride, apparently.
So I don't need to do it again.
Well, it'll be a calmer experience for you.
Maybe.
But this should be fun, good.
I mean, all of this is just like home run to me.
And then Encanto, I mean, that's just the Encanto house
is something like that.
There's an iconic structure that absolutely
has to be represented in the parks.
And then I feel like they, boy, they just barely show you.
They show you enough of the ride vehicle
to show you that people will be close together.
But other than that, I don't know.
It feels like OmniMover or I don't know.
I don't know.
It's not a big boxy trackless thing.
It seems like more of a ride you can send a lot of people
through all at once, which sounds great.
They need more stuff like that.
But I don't know.
They don't really show you the ride vehicle on this.
This is one of those where I was like, this is so close
to actually being built.
Give us another two minutes.
Don't give us spoilers, I guess, big spoilers on the ride.
But I'm like, you could give this room
two more minutes of info.
I mean, I guess they did it kind of.
They did say a lot.
It's the rainforest room.
They talked about restaurants.
They talked about the carousel, which is like lovingly
handcrafted and I don't know.
All sounds very...
It sounds good.
I just mean like because it's so close
and I'm sure details are finalized.
The carousel looks very good.
It looks very cool.
But I did immediately think of a joke of, oh, thank God.
Animal Kingdom finally has a carousel.
Because they opened it with such like,
this isn't the normal kind of theme park.
And now...
But Dino Land was always like a theme park.
Dino Land was pretty, yeah, kitschy and part of the league.
It makes, you know, there's precedent is all I'm saying.
Is the theme park fan party line supposed to be
that you're somehow upset that Dino Land's going away?
That I am or we are supposed to?
Yeah, what are we?
Yes, the general we.
There is a little groundswell, I feel like,
for like Dino Land is good, but I don't sense it's so strong.
I think people, certainly people a few years younger than us
look on it very fondly.
She grew up with it, sure.
Yeah.
But I don't sense it's gonna be like
if they close Muppets or something.
I don't think it's at that level.
But there's a little, I've heard there's rumblings
of like Dino Land is good.
Do you think they'll let me personally
take a wrecking ball to Aladar?
Will you drive the thing, you'll drive the...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll learn how to operate it quickly.
I'll apply for a construction job just in time.
You put on a Deadpool outfit,
you might be able to get away with anything.
Well, that's true for life, true for being in life.
So yeah, I don't know, this all seems pretty good
and a good like as classy a way to shove IP
into Animal Kingdom as you're gonna get.
They're doing, they're treating it with care,
they're not just.
They're shoving it with care.
They're shoving it in with care.
I saw a picture of Joe Rhodey taking a photo
of the model this morning from Animal Kingdom.
What if it was for his shitting on?
Oh, it's his burn book.
It's going in his burn book.
He's gonna take it and print it out
and burn a big poster of it when he gets home.
Some sort of ritual that he learned
somewhere in a different country.
Yeah, so yeah, no, it all looks cool
and it will fit thematically with Animal Kingdom.
The look of it I think will fit
with some of the Animal Kingdom stuff.
Yeah, let's bring it back to California
and California Adventure, Avenger stuff,
a lot of Avenger stuff.
Yes, I will say the thing that popped me the hardest
that was, that didn't live up to the popping
that I was experiencing was when they said.
You would say it's a ruined pop.
I don't know if it was a ruined pop.
Not a premature pop.
No, no, no, not premature.
It was the right time.
It happened at the right moment.
Time perfectly.
It was just that.
I popped for what I thought was gonna be a bigger deal
because they said fourth ride in Avengers campus.
And I got excited and then it was like cool,
but it wasn't, I didn't think it was gonna be X-Men ride.
I disagree with you.
Well, here we're in a meet your friends situation.
I'm not friends with any of these people.
Yeah, yeah, these are my friends.
So I just look at the vehicle
and I think the vehicle seems great.
Oh no, I think it'll be really fun.
I think it will be really fun.
This is, wait, what's the name of it?
What are we?
Stark.
Stark something.
Flight lab?
Flight lab.
Flight lab, which is you're on a Kuka arm kind of thing.
So you're able to like swing around, rotate a lot.
And it seems, and you are testing the variety of,
like it's, you can fly seemingly in different ways.
Maybe you pick like, you're pulling the flight patterns
of different characters or suits
depending on which vehicle you get on.
Yeah, I'm guessing like it'll be like,
yeah, you fly like Iron Man, you fly like Spider-Man.
I think they're gonna do like,
I'm trying to think who else, Captain Marvel,
who else flies?
War Machine.
War Machine, I mean,
it's gonna be similar to Iron Man though.
Yeah, I guess.
It looks very similar to the Some of All Thrills.
Some of All Thrills, yeah.
The Raytheon sponsored attraction and interventions.
Yeah, yeah, interventions, Some of All Thrills.
You would program a roller coaster
and then ride it basically.
But it was.
That one too?
Okay, I get confused with Some of All Thrills.
And it's on a big arm like that?
It's on a cuckoo arm.
But it looks like it, yeah, you strap,
it's like strapped over.
But there's no car, you're inside.
Can I ask, is this Stark thing indoors or outdoors?
It's outdoors.
It is.
It looks to be outdoors but like under like a big awning,
like basically they're gonna open up that wall
that's right by the Future Avengers ride.
So like you'll walk down and on the left
is where you'll enter for the new multiverse, whatever ride.
Infinity Defense.
Infinity Defense, thank you.
And then the ride is like right next to,
the Stark Flight Lab is right next to the E-Ticket ride.
Yeah, it's interesting.
And it looks to be kind of outside almost.
Like there's like a, like it'll be open air essentially
but you're like kind of under a covering or something
of the actual E-Ticket show building.
And they said this will all like double the footprint
of Avengers campus, which.
Yes, they did say that.
I don't know if that means.
I'm into it.
I like it, yeah.
Sure, but it's a good.
I like Avengers campus as it is.
I think it's really gonna ruin the purity
of the one thing in the restaurant.
Scott wants it smaller, he said.
Yeah, yeah, downside.
Actually, yeah, smaller.
Cut to Guardians, that ride's a little showy for me.
I mean the bar has a lot of variety
and it's a pretty pleasant place to sit.
So for a second I was like, is he joking?
Does he mean?
No, we're just finally, like we gotta land now.
And also just as a, I mean I was maybe,
I consider California Adventure my park in a way.
And just because I've like, as we all did,
we've like gotten to be around it as it got good.
And as it got mad, it was the place we went to get mad
when we were young, so young were we.
But I'm like, we got four ride announcements.
This park is, does all this not, if it's not already true,
do the four rides not get us to the point
that DCA is maybe in the top three theme parks
in the country, top two, number one.
Number one, does it make it number one?
I don't know that I would say one,
but if Avatar is slotted in there,
that is a massive upgrade.
If the Marvel ride.
What is number one, if not,
is it Islands of Adventure or one of those?
Right now?
Just individual park.
Individual park.
I mean a lot of people still make the claim that Disney's a question.
The people will still claim, and I don't know,
maybe I'm one of the Disneyland is still the best.
And all the parks, just park itself, not resort.
I think after all this,
California Adventure is better than Disneyland.
I could see that argument.
For an adult, different for kids.
Right, right.
I could see that argument.
I mean, yeah, again, Avatar blows everyone away
like it looks like it will.
We did a just Disneyland,
we did a just California Adventure rather,
with our then three-year-olds,
didn't go into Disneyland at all.
Great kick-ass day.
Worked for him, too.
Yeah.
Well, that, yeah.
No, I wouldn't argue with that.
I would have to think about.
I would have to, if I was really going to debate against Disneyland.
Still sacrilegious in a way.
Yeah, I'm not upset by it.
But I think.
But I get that Disneyland is the best argument
as far as its parks,
and Disneyland has so many rides in it.
At the end of the day, there's like something for everyone there.
But as far as feeling like big, cool, new stuff,
yeah, California Adventure is going to,
it's really going to be somewhere in five years.
Press your fingers.
Yes, yes.
In five years.
Do we get timeline on all this?
No, not specifically.
Or no, Avengers, no, Avengers will start next year.
Ray Crayons in 2025, I think.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
So I had two or three years then, probably, for it.
And it seems like they'll be building these at the same time
because they're connected to each other.
So I'm guessing 2027 or 2028.
So then, Infinity Defense.
Yes.
Avengers Infinity Defense.
Which looks, which is funny because Scott Trowbridge,
Mr. Islands of Adventure Spider-Man,
is making a new screen ride with superheroes,
which is funny.
But yes, it's called Infinity Defense,
which is not my favorite title.
It's fine, I guess.
It's not so dynamic, but okay.
I look at that and I'm like,
well, that's the way Marvel things are named.
That sure is the way they name shit.
Infinity War is cool.
Secret Wars is cool.
That is all cool.
Infinity Defense is less fun.
But okay, fine.
That doesn't have to bring us down.
But yeah, they showed a little bit of that.
And yeah, I mean, we've kind of covered this in some ways.
Like, it's going to be mostly screen ride.
I think there's some practical set elements.
And I don't know about robots.
But it's probably that Peter Pan system
that they have in Tokyo Disney.
And I don't know, I'm excited to do it.
I don't know that it's going to be like
a revolutionary new ride or anything.
But that's what I'm worried about,
that it'll feel a little bit like,
yep, this is what rides have been for a little while.
And maybe that's, overall, of all the stuff we've got,
I don't know that there's anything
that's going to physically blow me away,
like Velocicoaster or Guardians in Florida.
Well, it's also not really what Disney does.
It's true, sure.
But yeah, that was the only thought I had.
But yes, this one, and I know I'm just mourning the loss
of the much more ambitious ride they had planned,
that I don't even really know fully what it was,
but it looked a lot more ambitious.
So I think it might've had elements of this flight.
Possible, yes, possible.
That you were in little kooka arms or something.
That might've been the way they did it.
But yeah, I don't know.
I'm excited to see what it looks like,
and my friends will be on the ride.
I mean, there were more exciting Marvel announcements
in other countries, I would say, overall.
Yeah, I know, yes.
Those are what, again, it is that Hong Kong is getting
what looks like a drop tower.
Yes, Tower of Terror Spider-Man,
which looks awesome and looks like this art
that we've talked about many times on the show
that was gonna be this Dubai Marvel park.
And to me, there was a piece of art that looked
like it was a Tower of Terror with Spider-Man
and his web catching the big elevator
or whatever big box that the people were in.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's haunted me for many, many years now,
if you can find that.
And now they're doing it in a different way.
And they're doing it, finally, with a Spider-Man villain,
which has been a complaint of mine
about the other Spider-Man ride that we've got.
It's like, where are the villains?
He's got the almost fun villains.
But what's the villain in this?
Doc Ock.
Oh, OK.
Doctor Octopus attacking what looks to be
like an elevator car and Spider-Man catching you
with his web and pulling you back up
and dropping you down while he's fighting with Doc Ock.
Sounds really good.
It sounds great.
And it looks like, if I'm guessing how it works,
I'm guessing there's a screen in the top of the tower base.
Or the vehicle.
You can see Spidey on top of your car.
That's what I'm guessing.
Oh, cool.
Yes.
You see Doc Ock arms and you see webbing.
So yeah, so basically, again, this is just guess,
but Guardians Tower style, you go up
and you see different screens of action that's happening.
Maybe a robot, who knows?
You could have one Doc Ock robot or something.
But then, yeah, you have a screen above you
where Spider-Man keeps catching you
and jumping on the top of the car,
fights with Doc Ock on the top, in the front.
I'm guessing that's what it'll be.
And it sounds awesome if that's what it is.
That's really good.
That is much more exciting to me,
because that's a legit thrill ride.
And they figured out a way to sort of have
dynamic action happening at the same time.
That's a good reframing of this type of ride.
They've done a few times, but every iteration's great.
Then Shanghai is a Spidey coaster, also really good.
That's really fun.
Yeah.
I mean, I think that'll be really fun,
but I don't know how much actual Spider-Man you'll get.
Because it goes outside.
And I see they showed a piece of art
that's got Spider-Man above you,
and then I think you take off or something.
So you might lose characters throughout.
That's what I'm guessing.
I'm sure it'll be cool and fun,
but it seems like that one will be less full story
you're watching the whole time.
And it's hard to do that on a coaster as it is.
And I guess one big downside is that several weeks ago,
Jaquice Neal essentially confirmed that I will never
go to Shanghai, does he?
I walked out of that episode like, well, cross-off list.
I mean, maybe someday.
Didn't deter me.
Not that I'm going any time soon.
It sounded terrible.
Some of it seemed unpleasant.
If you pick up cigarettes, you start smoking.
Start smoking at 40.
We can finally start smoking on rides, though.
We've talked about this for years now,
and if we go, maybe just light it up.
But yeah, Shanghai, anywhere, I guess.
But yeah, I was like, oh, shit.
This Spider-Man, or Tower of Terror, man.
I know.
Very exciting.
It sounds a little bit cooler.
And I'd start demanding that here,
except Guardians is pretty great.
Yeah, Guardians is great.
So right, I understand why they're not going to make it, but.
Ooh, maybe they end up doing that over in Adventure World.
The Paris one, yeah.
Because that's close to Marvel, their Tower of Terror.
They've got to re-theme it, though, and if it's like a new.
I don't know how much new technology is on it.
So you might.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah, I don't know.
It might be too hard to do that.
I'm assuming maybe it's not.
It's something they can overlay.
I mean, I don't know how any of the technology works,
but if you could build a Tower of Terror vehicle
that is probably the same thing where it's suspended with cables
or whatever, but you could tilt the actual seats inside as well.
Ooh, to make you look up to the top.
Right, so you could more comfortably look up
and see what the screen is showing you.
Yeah, and I'm guessing you could do it where
there's like almost like two layers
that makes the screen look a little more like real versus
just having it be like an LCD screen above your head.
But yeah, if you could tilt it up as well to sort of see things.
I don't know if that's what they're doing, but I don't know if there's anything
they couldn't do easily and re-theme.
That's a pretty big upgrade from hard metal benches.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, and again, I don't know if they're doing it.
I was just trying to think of a way to comfortably make people
be able to look up while they're dropping.
In the Marvel neck of the woods, let's talk about Deadpool.
Deadpool, we completely called this in general,
that of Deadpool appearing on stage.
And boy, we had no idea that it would just become Deadpool for a long time.
And let me say this.
We've snarked about Deadpool.
We've said Chimichanga derisively.
It's not really my deal.
I even rushed out to see this film.
All that said, I enjoyed all of this.
It was good.
I thought it was funny.
I thought it was the best musical performance.
Yeah.
This big performance of Like a Prayer, which is apparently Deadpool's song now.
But this conceit that he had made all of this concept art for rides that he wants to do
and that he did for this kind of thing, cutting jokes.
He joked about Broken Yeti.
He joked about several times about Phantasmac Dragon lighting on fire.
These were like, there's a different type of Disney company that does not
like any sass about any of this stuff.
And I was pretty impressed.
I think I liked the comedic tenor and the aesthetics of this Deadpool appearance very much.
Sure.
I agree.
Did he make a little joke about like, Josh, go backstage, find yourself a new sweater?
Well, this is something I wanted to bring up.
The debate?
Let's go to our From the Second Gate episode.
We all agreed that Deadpool would appear.
So that's the base.
So that's a given.
We were smart about something.
My bet was, well, here, let me say, it's better to go in this order.
Jason's bet was that he would roast the underwhelming nature of previous D23s.
Mike's bet was that he would joke about the attractiveness of Josh Demaro.
I said he would appear, but he would not make any of these jokes.
Now, I was getting ready to say that I was correct on this.
Jason, unfortunately, was incorrect.
Mike, I think you and I have to sign off on this and turn the keys, Jason.
I think that referring to, why don't you go find yourself another tight-knit sweater?
Though it's about the clothes and not the physical appearance,
I am willing to say that this is a joke about Josh Demaro's being daddy.
I will give it to Mike.
OK.
Thank you.
He also called him a dime store something, and I forget what it was.
Dime store Eiger?
I don't know.
I forget what it was.
And then he did make a comment about Stamos being attractive, too.
Oh, right.
But I feel like all that adds up to I was right.
Yeah.
No, you're right.
So that's a win for you.
So yeah, good job.
And you know what?
It was later in the segment, too.
He actually came back, and that was a later thing he did.
So I put that as a win for me, but we're putting it in the column for you.
So congratulations.
I love that we're all right about Deadpool.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
And yeah, I think I saw some reaction of like, jeez, they really had.
We had no idea how much it would be Deadpool.
Down to where, let me say, I think if they did a ride with this tenor, I think it'd be good.
I think, imagine something that Deadpool has set up that is like a parody of rides.
Something that if we lose the Simpsons ride, there won't really be that.
So if Deadpool has set up some sort of thing to shit on Disney and rides and theme park tropes
in general, and maybe the ride itself is cruddy and does bad impressions of the kind of moves
that we know a ride can do, but then there is a sincere threat halfway through and he has to
commit more fully and save us from something.
But does that not seem like if I would not complain about a ride that's all set up,
all shitty, it kind of makes good on the promise of remember that there's that idea of like a
Muppet ride.
Oh, yeah.
I'm conflating the movie in there.
Yeah, there was going to be a Muppet movie where the budget got slashed,
that she was a Muppet movie or made.
But like, I don't know.
That is a ride premise.
I think it'd be kind of cool.
Yeah.
Well, a couple of weeks ago, I said,
Deadpool ride after this thing makes a billion dollars and it just crossed a billion dollars.
Wow.
And the story time is a big hit.
Big hit.
In the park.
It's making body jokes.
I'll say this.
I can't wait to see it.
I think most characters at this point in time are technically Avengers in the Marvel Universe
at some point or another.
Oh, he's in the Avengers movies.
No, obviously, I'm saying put Deadpool in the Avengers ride.
Oh, I think he will pop up.
Because see, it's the latest movie.
I haven't seen it either.
But there's a multiverse element.
The ride's a multiverse story.
Yeah, get him in there.
But yeah.
Get him in Jackman.
Yes.
Hopefully, they will do something like this because Deadpool being in the parks,
and this is it's embarrassing to say something where you're like,
Deadpool gives an energy to the parks.
That is good.
And like, did to the panel.
And did to the panel.
And Deadpool, the guy, whoever they have playing,
probably multiple people, but whoever they have playing Deadpool is doing a good job.
I have on this show said that I prefer a certain characterization of Deadpool
versus the Reynolds characterization.
But you got to give Ryan some credit for making it work
and making Deadpool like the Bugs Bunny of the modern era,
which is what Deadpool is.
Yeah.
It's certainly a type of, like as not a Marvel person,
I just from the outside, a lot of parts of it just seem like piss could be taken out of it.
Right?
Sure.
That's what he's doing, then neat.
Well, it speaks more to how uptight the Disney company is
more than crazy Deadpool is, I think.
But Deadpool, watching these story times with Deadpool,
I'm just like, wow, he went there.
I'm like an older, like, oh my goodness, what is he saying?
And like, this is outrageous.
Collecting your pearls.
Yeah, yeah.
But I go, well, maybe I like this.
Maybe I like a little bit of a bawdier entertainment at Disney.
My God, I thought I was offended, but here I am and I think that I'm popping.
Right, I'm popping hard.
I'm popping hard is what I said.
But yeah, you know, you're right.
And everything seems like it takes forever at Disney
and like, because all these ideas finally 20 years later, they're getting built.
So maybe in 20 years, they'll do Deadpool.
But there's so much stuff.
There's so much Marvel stuff that would make incredible rides.
And this is absolutely one of them.
And it's got the money now to back it up.
What if you did a ride that what I was saying about it, he set it up all shitty.
What if it felt like at the beginning, like a janky carnival, like an awful haunted house?
Yeah.
Like, you know, the kind of just like skeletons popping out, like,
and where it's it does feel like rusty, dangerous, barely dressed at times.
And then it opens up and turns into and you think that the vehicle can't actually do anything.
Awesome.
Yeah.
I'll give Ryan Reynolds credit for this, too.
He was saying that he pitched an idea for the movie that was just an indie budget
road trip Deadpool movie with no fighting.
Something about this.
I'm like, that'd be great.
Like with I forget the character's name, who's like the cab driver
or whatever from the first two movies.
And I'm like, yeah, why don't they do that?
Like, I've argued for this for years now, but it's just like the house style.
It seems very oppressive.
That's what I mean.
It's like, yeah, like, I don't know.
Do a movie where like the costs five million dollars.
That's a talkie movie.
And that looks different.
But yeah, I that's a great idea.
I said we should all blue sky on Deadpool rides and maybe we do that soon.
Okay.
Yeah, maybe that's the second case.
There's a lot of Deadpool buzz after his stunning appearance.
He really blew the crowd away.
Yeah.
But yeah, he's he's made a joke about Logan's run.
There was there was some there was a Wolverine thing because Wolverine's name is Logan Logan.
But then that results in a Logan's run reference.
Well, you're after my heart did.
I think he was doing it run.
Not run dancing.
Run Disney.
Oh, right.
Right.
Oh, that was that.
That was that.
Yeah.
All right.
That's a nice running experience.
Okay.
Um, Walt Robot.
I feel like I'm speed rounding.
Oh, yeah.
Walt Robot.
Another one Mike was right about.
Yeah.
Robot.
And this was all robot.
Yeah.
And this one, I will say this, I by betting the way I bet this year was was I was trying not to
just go with the conservative.
This was the closest to a conservative bet I made.
I was trying to not just go.
Okay.
This is what the.
You've gotten strong.
YouTubers.
But yeah, so so this was the most sure thing bet I made.
Yeah.
Because it just seemed like, well, what else is going in there?
Everyone is saying it's some sort of Walt show.
And yes, they confirmed it.
Walt Disney in his office.
You will get to see a little show that he does.
Will there be a Meghan Trainor feed the birds audio track playing during it?
I don't know.
Hopefully the original will be playing.
That was yeah.
So yeah, we got because they tie it.
You know, they get into emotion when Walt comes up and they get into Sherman Brothers
and that he's just the kind of imagine just sitting in his office and hearing a song
that he loves.
Then you get the full performance of feed the birds.
He did all of it.
And train her.
Yeah.
Which what I don't like about it, as of noted, Meghan Trainor fan.
I feel like they kind of zapped the personality out of her and made her just do it.
Serious.
And that's not what Megan's about.
And I feel like they should have done.
They should have let her go.
Megan with it.
You know.
Sure.
Do it like a bubblegum pop song from 1960 with really tinny drums, you know?
Why was it not more like a feed the birds?
A tuppence of it.
You got to feed the birds.
Gotta gotta feed the birds.
The Megan Maniac has hijacked the show again.
Yeah, feed the birds.
But is she serving the birds?
You know what I'm saying?
Is she serving the birds?
Tuppence of bag.
But is it a Gucci bag?
Is it from a Gucci bag?
La la la.
Oh, man.
You should have bet on that.
I mean, it wouldn't come true, but you should have bet on that.
Why didn't I bet on Meghan Trainor?
That's as sure of a bet as you're going to get.
I swear that's another thought I had.
I go, when is Meghan Trainor show?
I guess it was not when we ruined the betting, but when the thing started
and I saw how many musical performances there was, I was like,
Meghan Trainor's got to be coming.
Yeah.
She's got to be here.
Well, and then we got the kind of a tenuous connection of all for one is here to announce.
Four new cruise ships.
Yeah.
All right.
Bunch of cruise ship stuff in their name, but they don't explain that.
You just get a full performance of I swear and unexplained,
and then they say, but why are their names very appropriate for this?
Because we're opening one, two, three, four, four new ships.
But the ships are not going to be all for one.
No.
There is not going to be one price that gets you access to all four of the ships.
So if anything, I'd say their name is absolutely inappropriate.
This was one of the most confusing things.
I'm never mad when I see all for one, by the way.
Not their fault.
No problem with that, no.
But I was like, whoa, this was tenuous at best, this connection.
Yeah, yeah.
And I feel like there's more cruise ship stuff to talk about before we do it.
I'd just like to do a brief performance of the entire song,
I Love You Always Forever by Donna Lewis.
Is that OK?
Yeah, sure.
I love you always forever.
It's as, because I will love going on ships always and forever.
On that ship front, here's a bet.
I started a stopwatch on this.
One of the bets was how many minutes, this is my proposal,
was how many minutes they will do on cruise ships.
Mike's bet was five, I was eight, Jason went with 12.
But I did say price is right rules, closest without going over.
And actually, either way, even without that, because it nudged up to 10 minutes,
and I'd say 15 seconds, thus getting it.
And now, but Mike had a point of debate.
Well, right.
My question was, do the musical performances then count in our bet?
Because we said how much talk, I do think we said talk specifically.
How much cruise ship talk would there be?
Talk.
So obviously, that all for one thing was part of the cruise ship announcement,
but it was not talk, it was sing.
We didn't say how much cruise ship sing will there be.
There was so much music.
I think it would be impossible to, it would take days to figure out how much talk.
This is also the template, this whole show is a template going forward for these.
I think all of our bets will be different now,
because as soon as the show felt different immediately from years past,
and I was like, ah, I would bet differently on a few things maybe.
Well, we're learning.
As soon as the cruise ship segment started, I went, I should have said 10.
I got too greedy with 12.
But then, I don't know, actually, I felt the opposite.
As soon as it started, I tweeted smart monies on Jason here,
the way these have been paced.
I think they say ships, and they finish talking about ships.
And if they fill that with two entire songs, then they do, I'm giving it to Jason.
All right, he can have it.
I just, I was upset with my thinking after this, because I was like, ah, this music patted out.
Because really, they didn't talk that much about the ships.
I think there was a world where you were thinking there would be 10 minutes of-
With talk, I think it's you.
Right, yes.
I was technically more correct, because they oftentimes go on and on about these ships,
I feel like, of these things.
And this was a quick one, by the way, we're tripling the fleet,
or doubling the fleet, whatever it is, four, I don't know.
And it's just like, we're continuing, we're going to have 10 million people at sea,
every moment of every day for the rest of our lives.
Not to suddenly bring up environmental concerns,
but I've seen a lot of cruise ship companies go like,
we're building more ships.
And I was like, oh, do we need, do we need that?
Do we need that many ships in the ocean?
I'm not excited, any thoughts about what that does.
I mean, it's probably been good.
Flying a plane is also bad.
So Price is Right rules, wouldn't that be you won that bet?
No, close this without going over.
I think that's right.
What did Jason say it was?
I said 12.
Oh, but we all went over then.
Oh, wait.
Wait, you said it was like 10 and change.
It does, I thought it meant that it doesn't go over you.
Oh, you could go over the-
Oh, God, what is the Price is Right rule?
Sorry, listener, sorry.
So if you bet, so somebody says a dollar on Price is Right,
then the next person says 99 cents, anything under 99 cents wins.
Basically, right?
Isn't that how it works?
God, did you undercut the person?
Oh, so why don't I know this before I say it?
Well, welcome to podcast.
If I think at eight, you are not going over.
It's 10 and change, but I went over with 12.
Oh, okay.
So I'm being honest here.
Oh, yeah, if the calculation for music and talking was 10, 15,
then Scott wins.
Jason went over, yeah.
Oh, all right.
Yeah, good catch.
I think I understand the rules,
and I didn't even catch that when you were talking about it.
Oh, okay, jeez, this will be driving
Price is Right contestant Aaron, my wife, crazy.
I still technically won, but you win.
You went over, wow, wow.
I thought I went over.
Anyway, sorry, boring.
Okay, I mean, what do we think about this Walt show, though?
The Walt show, here's what?
We make a lot of fun Walt.
There's a lot of bad things about Walt.
Will I cry during the show?
Maybe, I feel like they're going to get you.
They're going to get you on some kid level of like,
I'll be with my parents or something and my daughter,
and then it'll be like they'll play the original Feed the Bird or something.
I feel like it's going to be good is what I'm saying.
I feel like they're going to get you
and all the jokes over the years of Walt.
It's the Walt show.
I read, I think it was in the LA Times and Tom Martin's article
that maybe it was Theme Park Insider Attractions magazine.
I've read so many roundups, I've lost track,
that it will have an initial run,
and then after that, it's going to play in conjunction with Lincoln.
Right, so it's not, I think what people were thinking before was,
Walt will introduce Lincoln, but that's I don't think what it is.
It's going to be just a full Walt show.
It'll run through the 70th,
and then they'll alternate the Walt show and Lincoln during the day going forward.
I think it's so funny that with any Lincoln chain,
and they've done this before,
it's always like they want to do something else in there.
It keeps being like, well, think about who thought of this Lincoln show is Walt.
It's Walt.
So if we put a Walt thing in there, that basically is a Lincoln thing.
Well, basically is Abraham Lincoln.
So you don't get to be mad, do you?
Actually, you should be very happy, shouldn't you?
I feel like those meetings boil down to someone going,
fine, you take a sledgehammer to Abraham Lincoln then.
This is like a sneaky way to get a different show in there, though,
in a way where you're like, can you argue with Walt?
You can't argue with Walt, he's in there.
And then like, because I think it's a rotating stage now
where you just rotate the show.
You do the Lincoln show, you do the Walt show.
So yeah, I guess you could like, in the middle of the night, in like 2028,
somebody goes in there and just removes Lincoln.
And it's like, just shut down.
And then you don't have to worry about the empty seats in the Lincoln theater.
Now, do we think it's Walt at a desk talking to you about his ideas,
or is there any chance that it's him
needing a little bit of extra nursing of that polo injury?
And we also build a robot of his nurse or helper or whatever.
Yes, I had the same thought.
Will we see the office that Walt would go into
with his nurse to get his polo injury worked on?
Yeah.
Which we determined had to be some sex thing.
So is it going to be?
Possibly.
Yeah.
A weird, whatever it was, it was weird, I believe.
Like she would put a glove on and like just stimulate him over his pant.
Like something was odd about it, I bet.
That was very odd.
She put a glove on.
It just is off the top of my head.
It keeps it medical if there's a glove.
That's what I'm saying.
I think there's some version of it we're not even imagining
that made whatever the sexual encounter was that he would have odd.
But it was no doubt odd.
That's what I believe.
Yeah.
Well, then the question is, will it be like real audio of him?
And like, we'll never forget it all started with him.
Or is it mostly, oh, oh, right there, right there.
Actually, actually a different part needs some massaging at the moment.
Maybe it's not on my back right now.
What is this woman's name?
We've talked about her before.
I know.
I don't remember.
Look her up.
Somebody look her up.
It's been a long time.
I think it'll be like Carousel of Progress,
where they can like light that area of the room.
Oh, sure.
And then you could see through his office
and the nurses in there like waiting for him.
All right.
Google, Walt Scotch Mist Glove Lady.
Walt Scotch Mist Glove Lady Massage Butt Sex.
It's not coming together.
Another drink.
Easy on the ice.
Hazel George.
Nurse Hazel George.
That's right.
We've done an episode on this.
Who then like spent a lot of time with Michael Jackson.
Yes.
That's a second gate episode.
If you haven't heard, go back and listen too.
Because that's fascinating.
Yeah.
Michael sought out Walt's nurse, Hazel George,
and asked her a bunch of questions about Walt.
Like did Walt, I think, didn't he like, did Walt swear?
You're also a glove enthusiast.
Can I bring up Michael real quick?
The night before the panel with all the movies
where they just like everything was a sequel and stuff,
it felt to me in a similar way
when Michael Jackson announced those like 50 concerts
on both like in England and here where you're like,
oh, they need money.
They're looking for money here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like there was a similar feeling I had where it was like,
oh, they need the money.
OK, got it.
Yeah, the famous announced tour, Michael Jackson's
This Will Happen.
Right.
I remember staring at that schedule going,
oh, whoa, no, no, Michael needs money,
and oh, I don't think this is going to happen.
And it did not happen for one very apparent reason.
The real name, This Is It, which proved eerily correct.
Yes, that was it.
They meant the press conference, not the shows.
When Michael Jackson died, did any police detective go like,
this woman was involved with Walt Disney and Michael Jackson.
Was she a person of interest as well?
Did Hazel George give him the propofol?
Oh, she gave him the special.
I'm just saying they both passed not too long after.
Jason's and Michael Jackson truth are in the sense
that he thinks that Hazel George gave him the propofol,
not Dr. Conrad Murray.
Wow, I've never heard this before.
This is a new one.
OK, look, there's been a lot of smirching of my godfather,
Dr. Conrad.
Well, I'd say, and then you go like, well,
we did a forensic search, which led us to discover
that Hazel George died in 1996.
But other than that, I don't see why Mr. Sheridan's theory
couldn't be partially true.
I would like to see him do his Jesse Ventura-style conspiracy
theory show, where he talks about some of his theories.
I'm going to find the culprit in the Black Dahlia case.
I'm going to find the Zodiac killer.
A nurse or so she says.
What does that even mean, really?
So what have we missed?
I mean, I don't think we have to name check
everything in any particular.
But are we missing a big area?
Probably somewhere.
Before we kind of like wrap up.
With the big stuff.
Yeah, and where's the bets?
Before we end with the big thing is this.
There's no Tomorrowland announcement.
I will tell you, my confidence level of Tomorrowland
announcement happening during the whole ceremony,
or whatever it's called, show.
Was high.
Really?
It was high.
Because, and it kept getting higher and higher and higher.
They teased Tomorrowland.
They played some Space Mountain early on.
Obviously, they played other things, too.
But there was like Tomorrowland.
They did a little Space Mountain.
And then as it's going on, I go, OK, they did it.
Avatar first.
That's Disneyland, a California venture.
But OK.
Then they did Walt in the middle.
And we're going along, and I'm like, they haven't
announced one big Disneyland thing yet.
Nothing for Disneyland.
Nothing for Disneyland other than Walt Robot.
That is crazy.
Right, which is crazy.
So we're going along, and I'm like, they're saving it
for the end.
What else could they end?
I'm like, I was so sure that we were getting it at the end.
Because I was like, they have to do one big thing
for Disneyland.
It would be wild not to do one big announcement for Disneyland
as far as a new ride or an overlay or something.
They went wild.
And they went wild.
They ended with a thing that was obviously very exciting
to see for an American park.
But my confidence was high during the ceremony.
As opposed to, here's our audience, a poll
right before the show.
What do you think we get tonight?
Tomorrowland plus PeopleMover?
Tomorrowland, no PeopleMover.
Neither one.
Neither one, 70%.
Well, that's always the easy bet when you're talking
about Disney and a thing like this.
Well, I understand why they said that.
It's where our audience, that's what they felt.
Though they were also wrong then on the nothing yet
for Behind Big Thunder, where we did get some stuff, obviously.
But yeah, Tomorrowland after.
It's also funny that, because we've had this Tomorrowland
plan for a while.
And we're going to step through these big things
about Tomorrowland and talk about the decay
in New Tomorrowland and Rocket Rods
and then culminate in the Fixing Tomorrowland
episode that just came out.
And Mike started putting the heat on us about that,
like, we got to do that fixing.
Scott Jason, we got to do that fixing because it's coming up
and we're going to get it.
We're getting it this year.
So make sure that we do it.
And we got to do it.
We got nothing.
A prominent source that was correct about other things
said that this was happening and it did not happen.
So yes, that source was wrong.
I don't know.
There was a lot of talk about it.
A lot of stuff came out of this as well.
Like, pull was pulled out.
Obviously, they weren't going to pull Tomorrowland.
It's a big thing if it was really ready to go
and they were going to put shovels in the ground immediately.
But I'm sure they're working on something.
But will it ever happen?
I don't know.
I'm still holding out hope.
There's a destination D next year, the D23 in two years.
I think we get it before Disneyland Ford.
I still believe that.
And I still think I'm still holding out hope
even though it did not happen here.
And I'm glad we did the episode because also there's a chance
that Friday morning they were ready to go
with big Tomorrowland plans.
Somebody threw their phone on the desk
with an Apple podcast app open and they said,
listen to this.
And they heard our pitches for Tomorrowland
and they said, this is so much better
than what we have planned.
We got to scrap the whole thing.
Or they heard they're on to us about the sod.
They'll think we stole it from them.
We don't want a sod gate on our hands.
It's possible that maybe they didn't even think about sod.
Maybe they said, you know what?
We should put a new sod in this.
We don't put this into the actual presentation.
People are going to riot.
And they pulled it out and they decided to go
with Villain's Land as the end.
The little one was kind of prickly about the Ant-Man ride.
We need to remove it now.
Right?
Or that could be, yeah.
Last minute.
So we had to do it just in case.
We threw a grenade into their entire operation.
Mike, I appreciate your optimism in this area.
But since I first came to LA for school in 2006,
they have been talking.
People have been talking about they got to do something
with Tomorrowland.
Oh, there's something coming for Tomorrowland.
And it just doesn't happen.
Do we want to go double or nothing
for another Tomorrowland bet?
Sure.
OK.
I would love to get that easy, easy money, Mike.
I would love to take the easy money from you.
OK.
Jason, same.
Double or nothing.
I also, by the way, think that we should keep bets going.
A friend of the show, Van Roba Show, was proposing a bet.
I think if any guest who comes on the show,
we're open for business on the bets.
I think this is a part of the show now.
It is a part of the show now.
And I'm trying to determine what my bet is.
First of all, let's just take a temperature here.
Do you think we will get a Tomorrowland
before some sort of Disneyland forward stuff starts being built?
No.
You think People Mover Track is there forever,
or at least for the next 30 years?
I don't know if it's there forever, but I don't know.
Because I think that's all except.
This hasn't been said, and I think
this is the real reason why Tomorrowland didn't happen.
In addition to what would be cool for the parks,
there is also a broader Disney company need
to service the buckets of what are the big IP and areas
and things that we own.
And you do have to think about these presentations as that.
We've got to service a lot of Marvel.
We've got to service a lot of Star Wars,
which is where I realized was maybe the foolishness
in your thinking.
You weren't so far off.
No, you're right.
But in Galaxy's Edge, the reason to say Galaxy's Edge
is because this is also for shareholders.
And we've got to assure everybody
we're doing stuff with Star Wars all the time to some extent.
So they're going to say something, I think.
Tomorrowland is not something that anybody's got eyes on.
There's no masters to serve there.
So that's why.
And Avatar is clearly one of those, too.
I think they have to show activity in these IP buckets.
And Tomorrowland is not attached enough to one of those
other than that Tron is maybe part of it.
And that's sort of it.
If the Tomorrowland movie had hit and hit big,
Tomorrowland would have been fixed by now.
Or, yeah.
I think he's doing an incredible three now.
I'm not saying it's going to be a crazy over.
I think they will.
I think the people mover track will
be gone by the time Disneyland Forward starts, whatever it is.
Boy.
But I guess that's going to be hard because we
have to parse what that means.
If Disneyland Forward is Avatar.
Mike, do you want to bet that there is an actual bunny who
delivers eggs to your backyard?
Yeah, he comes every year.
Jason agrees with that, though.
So I'll be on one side of this one.
Yeah, that is a different argument.
I think we will get a Tomorrowland announcement
of some kind in the next two years.
No.
That's what I bet.
Jason, how do you feel?
Are you including the next D23?
Yes.
It could be Destination D. It could
be during the 70th anniversary of Disneyland.
It could be the next D23.
I believe there will be a Tomorrowland announcement
in that time.
Those don't feel big enough.
I feel like next D23.
You fool.
Let him make a bet about Destiny.
Let him think Destination D is anything.
They say things at Destination D.
Yeah, what did they say last year?
That they were thinking about things.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, right.
But it's a whole new company now.
Jason, what do you think?
It was two years ago.
And the Mad Tea Party set lists are way different.
And when I say announcement about Tomorrowland,
it means they could just be pulling the people mover
track out and re-theming Buzz Lightyear
and painting everything.
Yeah.
It could be that.
It's not like an amazing sort of.
I think because of serving the IP.
That's why I know.
Look, here's the thing.
I think they're going to get really excited about all
the new stuff they've announced.
And then I think they're going to get really excited
about the Disneyland Ford expansion by the hotels.
And I think with Tomorrowland, they're going to go,
that is Space Mountain and Star Tours.
And that's good enough.
Yeah.
So you're with Scott.
There will not be an announcement.
You don't believe.
Give us an amount.
I want to.
This is another time where I want to be wrong.
This one was 10.
You were going to get five if it was at the end.
You guys are making it even.
You were actually making it even more extreme.
Because I'm saying I think it will be an announcement
in the next two years.
And you're saying they're not going
to pull that people mover track out in the next 10 years.
What would the last 10 years have been like?
How is this so insane?
No, I'm just trying to get on the same page here.
I grew up here.
These are my streets.
I've watched them decay.
I lived through every bit of it.
Each year, it got worse and worse.
You want to tell me about my land?
Mayor of Kingston over here.
I mean, I guess if Tron Aries is a hit, which I don't know
if that's possible, it's cool.
Nine Inch Nails is doing it.
But none of the other ones have been big hits.
Well, the charisma of Jared Leto could fill any number
of computer mainframes.
I've seen people say a Fantastic Four is a hit.
Well, now there we go.
Aesthetically speaking, that's perfect
because it's an Elseworlds 60s aesthetic in Fantastic Four.
Maybe that could do it.
Yeah, that's interesting.
If you turn Tomorrowland into a world fair,
if you turn into the first 90 seconds of the Tomorrowland
movie, you know.
Sure.
OK, my bet is within two years, there
will be a Tomorrowland announcement of some new version.
So does the two years include the next D23?
Yes.
OK.
All right.
That seems like I've, yeah.
What's the number?
What did we bet last time?
10?
10.
Well, double or nothing, it's 20.
And you put five, it was going to be an extra five
if people were there.
All right, well, double them both.
20 and 10?
That's right.
OK.
Well, I'll double or nothing again in two years.
I'll say, well, two more years, that's what it'll be.
And the bet will keep going higher.
It'll just keep going and going.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's hard to count with interest rates
by then and the value of the dollar,
what that 20 or 10 will mean by then.
Right.
It'll be a whole other world.
Of course.
Anything else, like, news-wise to cover,
should I get into the betting stuff and where we landed?
Well, just the villains.
Oh, wait.
OK, well, here.
Villains will segue into betting.
So the big announcement, because it was seeming kind of done.
They actually did get me.
And then it was not done.
There was a scary music cue.
And then the face in the mirror admonished Josh
tomorrow for withholding something.
And we got a big final announcement
of there's no name for it, but we're just, for now,
calling it Villains Land, going in Magic Kingdom.
So let's talk about it first.
And then we'll talk about what it means for us.
Yeah.
It is great.
Great concept art.
This is another one of those rumored forever exciting way
to present it.
We got a little bit of specifics.
We got two attractions, restaurants, shops.
Basically, just one piece of concept art
that kind of implies a coaster.
But we don't really know what villains we're dealing with yet.
Maleficent Coaster in the art, because the dragons sort of buy it.
Oh, OK.
All right.
So that's what people, and it's thorny.
And that's what people assume.
I don't know that to be a fact.
But yes.
So that looks like, if that art is accurate, like an outdoor coaster,
it's kind of this, I don't know what the actual other ride is.
But it is sort of like Epic Universe's Monsters Luria.
It's got a coaster, and it's got some other maybe indoor.
Kind of looks a lot like Epic Universe.
It's very similar to Epic Universe's.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, it's great.
Sounds great.
It was all of a way to close it.
The concern maybe is no timeline.
Five years, I think, keep dreaming.
You want to put money on that five years?
We're not going to get that money for five years.
But I don't need.
I don't care about that.
I don't need to do that.
This moment with the face in the mirror,
this was the most professional wrestling thing of the night,
where it's like, well, that's the end of the show.
Thanks for coming.
And then he pops up.
And that was very fun.
Yeah.
But I think, so look, there's not much to say about it.
It's cool concept art, and it sounds great.
And I think it'll be really fantastic.
But let's talk about the ramifications for us.
Because, well, OK, actually a couple things.
One, right before we get to that, let's get to our bets.
One of the bets was Disney words said out loud, recurring Disney words.
Mike went with imagination.
I went with magic.
Jason went with dream.
Now, this tally got a little wonky for me.
I tried to keep track, but this was a long, long panel.
However, there was an early lead taken early in the panel.
This was a big one.
I threw this out and said it's for $20.
Why not?
Make this the big bonus.
And here's my calculation on this.
I think there was an insurmountable lead gained very, very early on by Dream,
which is Jason's word.
My count is 11.
If I missed part of this, if I went to the bathroom during it,
if I missed Shaboosie doing a rapid fire imagination, imagination, imagination
many, many times, then I did.
But I think count is 11, dream, magic for I'm not sure I heard imagination once in the panel.
Which, speaking of, that means no journey into imagination either.
The horizon's name didn't really lead to anything.
Nothing.
Except for the Spaceship Earth Lounge.
The former Siemens Lounge.
But now everybody can go to this lounge.
Pirate's Lounge at Magic Kingdom.
But yeah, no, Epcot, nothing.
No.
Epcot will spill decay.
That's what I'm telling you, Mike.
The Disney is okay with decay.
And I don't just mean in the villainous villain's world.
Two years.
Okay, all right.
Anyway, then I had another question because we got really thrown by that.
The first number of the show is John Stan was performing A Dream is a Wish Your Heart Makes.
Really made me wish I'd bet on Wish.
But then I had a question, does music count?
I asked the audience, does music count?
They said yes.
It was a close margin, but they said yes.
If we're counting music, imagination's still zero.
Magic 6, Dream 21 becomes a crush by Jason.
But even if you take music out of it, it's still Jason.
So congratulations to Jason on the big bet of the night.
$20 go into your pocket on that one.
Now, if we're talking purely financially, if we were to take that one.
Oh, and also, by the way, if Story, if anybody had grabbed Story,
they would have run away with it.
That would have been so much better.
We're all idiots to not say Story.
So let me say what happens if that one's out.
If not for that final bet, then I'm up $22.50.
This is the high stakes that we're dealing with here.
Jason is down 9 and Mike is down 13.50.
With the final bet, this brings us to, oh, wait a minute.
And actually, this is kind of crazy.
With the little nudging that has happened during this episode
and evaluate it.
And I'll let you guys check the math on this.
But this is what I'm seeing at this point in time.
Jason up $11, me up $12.50, Mike down $23.50, Mike down a lot.
I think the key, it was those tens.
You lost a lot of tens.
I know.
Now, when I sat down with you guys before I made some changes,
Jason was up.
And I was exactly even.
I was at literally $0 thanks to some changes.
I have won financially.
However, however, and this is how I was starting to feel
until the big reveal.
Oh my god, they aren't done.
Oh my god, Villains Land, Magic Kingdom, oh my god.
Jason gets a double scoop of Baskin Robbins flavors
of his choice.
And due to them saying location, though maybe they
didn't clarify behind Big Thunder, I said location.
I didn't say there.
Magic Kingdom equals Jason also gets sprinkles.
Wow.
And therefore, because I only beat you in terms of numbers
by $1.50, once you have calculated the split price
between Mike and I of a double scoop at Baskin Robbins,
Jason is the winner of the 2024 D23 bet.
Wow.
Congratulations.
Jeez.
And not to mention, I think even if the numbers didn't add up,
the joy that came from the ice cream
would surmount any financial loss.
So it's Jason no matter what.
Jason, congratulations.
My god.
Thank you so much.
You win the first ever round of PTR betting.
I mean, I don't want to get into the weeds here,
but were you talking about those salt and straw prices,
Scott?
Or were you talking more reasonable prices,
like a dryers at a home in a freezer section?
Well, thank god we didn't get into a salt.
So maybe if it had been an Ample Hills,
it would have been a different situation.
Oh, man.
Rest in peace.
But thankfully, you chose a reasonably priced,
and I'm glad it's something we can go to very soon.
Do we want to go right now?
I want to go to bed right now.
You want to go to bed right now?
We will take a rain check on the OK.
Well, you're right.
It has been a long episode, so we will not.
You'll have to wait for photos of Jason and the ice cream
and the grin on his face from the ice cream.
Will you wait as long as we'll wait for Tomorrowland News?
Hopefully not.
Jason, hold us to it.
This is not blue sky.
We're putting shovels, as I call spoons, into cream,
into dirt, which is, by that I mean,
the dirt that's ground up Oreo.
Rocky Road.
We're putting little shovels into dirt.
Rocky Road, ease one of the scoops.
Oh, that's one of your choices.
That is confirmed.
Let's blue sky here.
Do you want to make your choices?
Copper cone, flavors, and type of sprinkle.
Do you want to say it here?
I'm going to go with cone.
Great.
Probably sugar cone, the chewy one.
OK, more expensive.
The chewy one?
I don't know.
Sugar cone or cake cone are usually the default cones.
OK, so you're saying that's a cheaper one.
Yeah.
OK, sorry, my apologies.
Waffle cone is usually a little too overwhelming for me.
OK, all right.
Well, you've got to know yourself.
And what flavors are we thinking?
I don't know the second one yet.
OK.
Oh, all right.
I'm thinking about going a wild card, like pecan praline.
OK.
Whatever praline.
So you'd say that you're dreaming up some.
You're starting to think about the kinds of flavors.
Yeah, I don't have shovels in the dirt yet, so.
OK, sprinkles just rainbow?
Maybe chocolate jimmies.
Oh, right.
I forgot it was Jason we're dealing with,
and it could be chocolate jimmies.
Just don't say that to the California teens
at the Baskin Robbins.
They will not know what you're talking about.
Well, I've got some stories for them if they don't.
You know, on the other side of the country,
there's a wide variety.
You know, about 100 years ago.
Well, we will make good on this.
The only dark side to this great ice cream news
is this is going to help his problem.
He's got a problem with the penny slots,
and this is only going to encourage him further.
Oh, yeah, gambling wins.
This could be a real problem for Gamblin' Joe over here.
Uh-oh.
Well, let's take you to the casino after this.
Hey.
Oh, after the nap, after the nap.
Oh, yeah.
You can nap in the car as we go to Pechanga.
Oh, yeah, I'll put the seat down,
and you'll nap in the car as we go to Pechanga.
Oh, good.
All right, this luck all the way to Temecula.
All right, but for now, I guess we'll wrap it up.
Boy, supersized episode.
Boy, hey, we still shorter than the panel,
but boy, do the three of us love to talk about this shit.
Even on a sad Sunday when we're rushing it out, here we are.
Could have done more, too.
Yeah, I know.
If it came up, and there will be,
we'll start picking up parts of it.
And you know what we'll have to do, what it'll motivate is,
as they start saying attractions that are closing,
we will have to start saying goodbye to those.
And in fact, have we missed anything in Dino Land?
Or do we do all of Dino Land?
I don't remember.
I don't believe we have.
Forget how we broke that up.
If it was Chester and Hester only.
I don't.
Did we do Chester and Hester?
Did we just do the roller coaster?
Oh, we did Primeval World.
Well, we haven't done Chester and Hester alone.
All right.
Well, that list will grow.
But for now, I mean, man, boy, that's a blue, blue sky
with Chester and Hester as a PTR listener.
But for now, you survived Podcast the Ride,
a jammed out episode, sort of.
Hey, this is this week's main feed,
so we won't be back here on Friday.
But for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride, The Second Gate,
or get one more bonus episode in our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash Podcast the Ride.
What you will get this week is my birthday shot,
an indulgent topic picked for me by my birthday.
Do you think that this is about theme parks?
Place your bets.
I know where the smart money is.
But hey, we did all that.
We've been on fucking topic lately, have we not?
We sure have.
Let's give ourselves big pats on the back for that.
Big ice cream scoop of off-topic, please.
I'll take off-topic.
Just kidding.
Do you have off-topic here?
This has been a Forever Dog Production, executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.