FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcast may contain
alternate universe Michael Eisner
jaundiced hamburger buns
giving action figures little kisses
and a brief encounter with a rock legend
uh, a fake rock legend
all that plus Guy Selga returns to talk
Tokyo DisneySea's newest expansion
Fantasy Springs
on today's podcast
Goodbye!
Welcome to Podcast the Riot
a theme park podcast hosted by three men
who turn into Sherlock Holmes when it comes to
concept art for new theme park lands
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always
my dear Watson, Jason Sheridan
The game is afoot, Holmes
Is there a third character before I do, Scott?
Yeah, I was gonna say, what the hell do you do with me?
I'm not Moriarty, that's the other side of it
But Moriarty, doesn't he team up with them sometimes
in different versions of Sherlock Holmes?
Ask Mr. Book over here
Yeah, I know, smarty pants
What do you think?
I am not knowledgeable about all the adaptations
maybe that fox, was it Fox Kids?
Was it Fox Kids?
There was a future Sherlock Holmes
Mr. Literary has referred us to Fox Kids
Fox Kids, yeah
You've never read a Sherlock Holmes?
Really?
I've read a bunch of Sherlock Holmes
Okay, but Moriarty never teams up with them in one of them?
He's usually a villain, antagonist
I'm familiar with that
There's gotta be one where he teams up with them
And one where Moriarty
stares at a picture to see
if the shape of a building resembles
Is there currently existing cityscape
that's just reskinned or repainted?
There's gotta be one
And the Fox Kids one I bet there was an episode like that
where he was looking at
concept art and he was trying to figure out
if they had rethemed one quick service restaurant
into a different quick service restaurant
Because he's a brilliant mind
so he could be able to tell just from the art
I can only go so far, my dear Watson
We may need to consult
with some consortium of dorks
The Scott Kids one is in the far
flung future
And Scott, you could be
Mrs. Hudson
the landlady
Does she help them solve mysteries?
Well, she comes through
Mrs. Hudson sometimes accidentally
points them in the right direction
Does she take their money?
Do I get your money?
Then I'll be the landlady
Is there another character
I could intro or guest as
before I do the intro
from this Fox Kids
Is there a new character that you could find
on the Wikipedia?
Not in this
amount of time
Has he been on the Wikipedia?
I just couldn't remember Mrs. Hudson
I'm just going to intro our guest
I'm not going to give him a Sherlock Holmes character
But we could add it later too
He's returning to Podcastaride
He's a writer for Touring Plans
It's Guy Selgo, welcome back
Thanks for having me back
It's so nice to be back amongst theme park journalists
And you can just
Are you giving us that?
You can assign me one of the Bobby's World characters
That's fine too
You'll just go Fox Kids, that's great
What about Life with Louie, like Louie's dad
Any old cartoon
they made off of a weird perverted
comedian in the era
I like that uncle
from Bobby's World
I don't remember his name
Not Howard
Generic
I just remembered that
They have to correct
the name all the time
But who was the uncle, the uncle is the guy you want to be
I can't come up with it, I can't think of the name either
Before we get started, I did bring
a couple of gifts, I'll be quick with this
Hi, thank you
That's so nice
Mike and Jason, I just want you to enjoy
these delicious donuts that I brought you
Whoa
They gave you a total sugar bomb one
They called it raspberry bomb
Jason
I'm giving you a peanut butter and
jelly donut
Scott
You get no donut
That's fine, that is a fine calculation
He likes that
You will receive a cursed item
Oh my god
The opposite of a sweet treat
I will explain why
There have been several episodes of this podcast
where you have admitted to not remembering
the country bear's names
in the country bear jamboree
Yeah, even after the last time we saw you was for country bears
and it's all been out of my head
So you are receiving
what some say is the worst
video game ever made, it's Shaq-Fu for the Super Nintendo
Well you say
punishment and yet
this art will brighten
my house, Shaq in a Shaq-Fu
pose
Even your son will ask daddy
why is our family cursed
and you will have to explain to him
No, hardly, our home is protected
now by an enforcer of justice
Yes
Wow, wow, from a
video game reselling place
Oh this is rad, I might pop this
I got the, you know
I'm a bit of a gamer, I have a
SNES combo
console
recently purchased
for Dr. Mario
I have literally never put anything
in the Super NES slot
so this might be the debut
Thank you for keeping that particular reader
alive on my console
Kick it off, I clocked hours
on Shaq-Fu on Genesis
and it is
it's pretty odd
it's very strange
It is a strange game, yeah
Almost like the combination of Shaq and Halloween
or Shaq and the general
Shaq and essentially any of the Shaq and Soda
Shaq and Soda
And they made a Shaq-Fu sequel
only a few years ago
Legend reborn
All the modern consoles and PC
and everything
How did this not come across my desk?
I think it flopped hard and was very bad
but that keeps in with the spirit of
the franchise I suppose
Well and with different endorsements to check
usually is involved
I think they may have even kickstarted it if I remember correctly
Wow, that's crazy
I'm dying to see another character name
I'm scanning Wikipedia
Setra
Kaori
Ryotsu
Where are these donuts from?
Old Ferry is like
I see them mostly in areas with a lot of
Asian restaurants and things
I live near Buena Park
Thank you for coming up here
You live in the greatest city in the world
Yes, Bee Park
It only took me 90 minutes to get here
Oh my god
I'm sorry
We gotta give you a show then
We gotta make it worth the drive
Well, hey, good news
When you get home and you wanna crash
Sherlock Holmes
in the 22nd century
is available
on Tubi
Like all the best stuff
Tubi's so good
I love Tubi
Are you still working on another character?
No
Oh, did I need another character?
We got a whole hour
We have someone who actually knows about
theme park things
We have to take advantage of that
Guy, you've done a lot
You've traveled a lot lately
You're everywhere lately, I feel like
Yes, I was at D23
You were texting me, asking me questions
Are people into this?
Yes, yes
I guess I accidentally cited you anonymously
on our recap episode
But Guy is the source for
was the audience liking all these songs
And specifically
right before we started recording
there was some discussion of Mad Tea Party
and was Mad Tea Party working out
in the room
People were loving it
They gave out these wristbands where they
had a light on it that synced with the music
during all the songs
There was a big spectacle, there were lasers
What do you think was the biggest hit
or even one that you liked a lot?
Because I imagine that music stuff played
better in the room
And there were some legit big acts here and there
What worked the best?
I think what legitimately
moved people was the Megan
Trenor singing Feed the Birds
People were
sobbing
in the audience
Which I don't like
That's not her vibe is to make people sob
How dare they put her in that situation
She was playing against
type
You're just used to a certain trenor vibe
And she's showing you that she has more range
But in terms of announcements
In terms of announcements though, people were really into
the Magic Kingdom Night Time Parade
That seemed to get a huge reaction
Did we even discuss it in the show?
In a very lengthy episode
What is the selling point with that?
What's exciting about that parade?
I think people are just excited to have a new nighttime parade
It has been a while, right?
Have they not been running one at all
or just an old one?
They were doing Main Street Electrical Parade
and then that ended
before the pandemic, right?
Right, I think
Oh, so there has not been one since
Yeah
And then
We recorded forever
There was a couple big ones we left out
We didn't even talk about Robert Downey Jr.
being on all the Marvel rides
Oh, that is kind of a bit
That it's not just
Well, that's bad news for anybody for sound-alikes out there
Like anybody who is Pepper
Anybody can swivel the head
That's what you gotta do to make the voice happen
So yeah, I guess he's replacing all
Right? That's what your take is on it?
He's gonna do all the voices
I wonder if they'll re-record his little
That's what I'm wondering
Who knows?
Yeah, I don't know, but I assume that's part of the big Dr. Doom package
that he signed
to do the new movies
Well, if we're giving you
80 million dollars
More? Is it more?
I tried to guess a big number
and that was still not the number
I bet it's 80 guarantee
And then there's potential for
Yeah, there's like targets
If it goes over a billion
Then we'll toss some more your way
Well, probably
So yeah, that was in the package
I assume, so now he'll be on
the rides going forward and maybe the old rides
I don't know
I don't know if you caught how they announced it either
But they showed Bob Iger
on the kooka arm thing
and it was blurred out who was sitting next to him
Yeah
And then they revealed the blur
People went crazy
This is where we were at a disadvantage
watching a livestream because when they revealed the blur
I was like, who's that?
From a cell phone camera
really far away
and still not a great picture
up on the screen
I truly was like, is that Stamos from a weird angle?
Or are they showing us?
Is that Michael Eisner?
Imagine if he was doing the voice
Bring him back
It returns
when we need him the most
I don't love wearing a suit
without a big 90's
blocky tie pattern
but I guess this suit is cool as well
If he was still CEO
that would be certainly an intro for some wonderful
world of Disney where he's in an Iron Man
outfit or something
He suits up and then you
throw the thing like a dummy
and he lands in bushes
I think we need some work on that take off
Enjoy the show, folks
We should just write a bunch of new ones
that would have happened in the last decade
That is pretty good
For the broadcast premiere of Wish
Yes, and then like Solo
what he would have done for Solo
on Disney
or on ABC or something
I'm a Solo writer as well
He's in line with
Han Solo or something
Are you together? No, he's alone
And then they cut to the actual movie
and it's like, oh Solo, okay
That would have been a good one
We'll do this off mic
but this is maybe a whole else world
It's a full episode, it's just brainstorming
When was the last time he did that?
Like two decades ago?
We could fill in two decades worth
of hypothetical Michael Eisner
intros
Wish coming out
Mars Needs Moms
We're proud to present the world
broadcast premiere of Mars Needs Moms
And I Need My Mom
And then she comes and acts
and she's the worst actor
With a wig or something
That might be a little silly for him to do
Would he be willing to dress up like an old lady?
I don't know, that's a good question
Now Michael
I guess brainstorming
I'd like to imagine it
This is blue sky, so we can sort of
cast however we want in these scenarios
If only
Well, maybe that's a future episode
But yeah, were there any other
big highlights on the show floor
like Imagineering Pavilion or anything?
Imagineering Pavilion was really cool
They did these little mini presentations
every 15 minutes
where an Imagineer would come up and talk about
themed lighting or the floor
or how they paint something
or sound design
And you could just walk up and wait
and see it and that was nice
And then they had the Elsa animatronic
from DisneySea on display
So that was cool to see up close
The movements on the mouth
looks amazing
And then there was a booth
which was heavily sponsored by Dolby Atmos
And so you would walk through
and it was just a nice themed environment
with swooshing banshee sounds
overhead and then a mighty eekron of course
to take a picture with
And then a baby eekron
that was like an 80's Epcot
figment style puppet thing
So a scientist is like holding
a little baby eekron
and he's like, now you're just feeding time?
Is this anything they do
in Animal Kingdom?
Or that they might do here when it's open here?
I don't know
It sounds great
It sounds similar to the baby raptors
at the Drask World
Drask Park
areas at Universal
with the trainers holding them
Was the baby eekron cute?
It was kind of cute
You believe that though
I do, yeah
We're all pretty
horrified by any depiction of Avatar babies
A little less in the film
although even still
It didn't prevent me from crying
in that part of Way of Water
The only film
that has moved me in the father way
since becoming a father
But I still
most depictions
still a little bit creepy
I'm trying to remember
because I saw photos of that
baby eekron
They usually just have stuff sitting out
That sounds bad
They're sitting out in the sun or something
They have robots and stuff
or costumes and stuff sitting out there
Then they had the Disney Archives booth
which this year was cars themed
not the franchise cars
but movie cars
They had a 1964 World's Fair car
from the Ford Magic Skyway
They had an old 80's Disneyland parking lot
which I actually saw on the 5
when I was driving up to Burbank on Monday
Back to the storage
That's funny
They had the volume
from Lucasfilm
set up, not like a mini one
the full on thing
You could record a little 10 second scene in it
after you waited for 2 hours
That was really neat to see up close
and see it shift with the movement of the cameras
Have you posted your scene?
What did you do in the volume?
I did not do it, a friend did
The scene he got was with a stormtrooper
I think he was just like
let's get out of here
I don't really know what you would do in 10 seconds
It looked cool though
just to see
I saw somebody post it
I think R2D2 was in it
That's something I would have wanted to know
was there before so I could have dressed up
in some ways
not as a Star Wars character necessarily
but as a Star Trek character
I was going to say American Graffiti character
Yes!
I don't know the names of any of the characters
in American Graffiti
No
Just a leather jacket
or a cardigan with a big letter on it
Jason, real quick
do you have a cardigan with a big letter on it
No, I have a number of cardigans
I go back and forth
But not with a big J?
No, I should
I should look into that
Birthday is coming up
I have a cardigan with a big J on it
And if you want to be a really good friend
a big J in it
Hell yeah, Burler
Were people high at D23 at all?
I saw people getting drinks
at the Honda Center
There was one cocktail
that was $40 by the way
Really?
That's like Sphere prices
I'm trying to think
what else
You skipped the parks panel
You didn't go to the movie thing
No, I skipped the movies
No disrespect
I went to the legends a couple of years
It's kind of boring
I skipped that every year
But yeah, parks panel
I feel like I got to be there for that
Just as much as theme park nerds in a room
screaming at stupid stuff
Were you satisfied with the screaming you got today?
What was your feeling coming out of there
in terms of announcements?
This is not blue sky
We're ready to put shovels in the ground
But some of that is so far off
Stuff is going to change
Budgets are going to change
Some movies are going to come out
That's a hit that gets priority
You know it's going to happen
My expectations are so tempered
That's the right way to be
Did you hoot and holler
at any one specific announcement?
Did you just feel like it came over your body
or were you too reserved in the panel?
Of course
I was getting excited for Coco
I think that'll be a cool environment
to ride through
If the Avatar boat ride really is Shanghai Pirates
that's going to be sick
One giant land dominating
attraction that's scenery to look at
if you're not on it
and then incredible to be on it too
sounds great
What is your Avatar location guess?
We won't make you bet
Unless you want to
I just feel like it has to be
Hollywood land
Also with Disneyland Forward
You guys may have said this on your episode
I think we will never hear that name again
That's a good notion
That was the functional campaign
to the city
but it's not a very attractive
exciting term as a new place
Let's go to Disneyland Forward
I agree with you on Hollywood land
This is maybe too long of a conversation
to have on this episode
but we'll try to do it real quick
It's interesting
If they do third park in Disneyland
then they get to make a big splashy announcement
I feel like they get to charge more at once
because it's an extra ticket
but then they have to build it all at once
If they just start adding to California Adventure
in Disneyland they can do it in pieces
but then it's not quite as splashy
and I feel like they only slowly
make money over time
I was trying to go back and forth on
even if Disneyland Forward turns into more stuff
or a third park
I don't know
I don't know if you have any insight or guesses
It's just a guess but it seems like
they really want to add capacity to DCA
I see a lot of people online
are speculating that they're going to replace
Grizzly Peak with Avatar
I don't think they're going to want to lose all that capacity
I think they want to add
That's clearly the thing right now
They're adding to all the parks
That doesn't make a lot of sense to me
and what does it do to Soarin
and the flow of everything in general
You've also got the tricky thing
if you look at that Disneyland Forward plot
that there's so much more
on the DCA side
than the Disneyland
There's a good amount up there
but it starts to get a little awkward space way
I think the Disneyland Forward plan
is a lot better for California Adventure
than for Disneyland proper
It's a three story lot
and a whole gate there
Right
It's weird though
as it stands
it would be the smallest park
easily
That's an awkward thing about it
It's interesting
and the fact that the only thing they've floated
as a possibility for over there
is a mall with a Jockalinsies
I'm almost in support of that
over a park in a way
There are a bunch of new places to drink
that are fun
Yeah, and they could maybe add one ride
You could do a little celestial park
thing over there
Give it one little experience or something
That's a fun idea
As a fan of that Burbank plan
that never came to pass
there would have been a mall with a great movie ride
or probably by 1997
a mall
I guess all that
That's a third park
I feel like that's 15 years away
and if it's just adding lands
then maybe we'll get that in 8 years
Yeah, I think you're totally right
Not to say too much about how we're
putting this together
We are recording this
We discussed the possibility
that we hear what the Muppet deal is
while we're recording
then we'd have to emergency get it up
We are
I'm refreshing Twitter
So far nothing
John Goodman is trending and I don't know why
I am on my
theme park Twitter list
and I do not see any Muppets
talk at the moment
This is the morning and I think it's going to be
released at the end of day
They want the news cycle to forget
But talking about adding capacity
to parks
turning the Muppets and Grand Avenue
area into a construction site
you lose multiple
restaurants, you lose a show
as opposed to
everyone mentions the
animation courtyard
that would add capacity
and not take away a show
in a bunch of restaurants
That would make the most sense
But it's more expensive
I don't know
I've heard all the chatter
and we'll see
We might have seen by the time we're here
I don't know
It's a scary time
in America
for this reason only
There's one big thing that's going to happen towards the end of this year
that I'm worried about
and instead of the Muppets going to close
I'm so glad this is all we have to worry about
It's the only thing I'm worried about
going forward
That's all very cool
Do you want to talk
about what we discussed
You went to Fantasy Springs
which is the new expansion at
our beloved Tokyo Disneyland
Tokyo DisneySea
That's very exciting
We're very jealous
As soon as you brought up this topic
I was like, I guess we should talk about it
even if we didn't go
I still feel like I tried to do it
with only light spoilers
I watched ride throughs
but I didn't memorize ride throughs
I still want some
However, I definitely do want to hear
what it's like on the ground
and just get a shape of the place
Do you want to start off with the story
of Fantasy Springs
I don't know it
This is the official story off of the website
It's four paragraphs long
I know it might take a little bit
but Mike or Jason, can one of you read the story
You're donating the story
You do it
Okay
I'll just do whatever feels right
Let the story guide it
Once upon a time in a land far away
there was a magical spring
where a sprite
Is that sprite you think?
It's not sprit
You never know
The spritz
It's spirit actually
The spirit is in the second line
While the spirit fed beautiful gardens
in great distances where she encountered enchanted stories
Upon returning home
the spirit used her powers to sculpt
stone, branch and bank
into intricate shapes resembling
those she met
As she bubbled and sparkled in pools
fountains and waterfalls
the spirit often sang melodies discovered
on her many journeys
Okay so what do we got here so far
There's a spirit and she's singing and turning bank into
A spirit happened to encounter
many stories that were all
intellectual property of one company
and kind of you know
some of the more popular ones
and not Mars needs moms
Okay yes good recap
One day a duchess who loved
travel and adventure discovered
the beauty of the springs
Wandering along the rivers and streams of the springs
the duchess found herself transported
to magical places
The duchess loved the enchanted
springs so much that she built a little
summer home nearby
As more of her friends visited
the duchess built a grand palace to host them all
Even today should you follow
the water flowing from the springs source
you would come to fabled kingdoms
found in storybook tales
Wow
So like a rich lady
liked this place so she built a mansion there
Yeah
Interesting
Hopefully no spirits residing in the specific spot
where I want to build the mansion
Because I was like alright spirit
and then something kind of like pulled
something from the ground in a magical way but no like a
rich lady
Can I read the next paragraph?
Okay let me hear it
Wow so the duchess then encountered
a very tall man almost a giant
His name was Shaquille O'Neal
He was soon after walked into a dojo
while heading to a charity basketball game
in Tokyo Japan
He went to another dimension the second world
to rescue Nezu from the mummy Setra
Oh wow
It's actually good you brought the game
because it ties into the mythology
It's all one seamless mythology
That's cool
So this story of fantasy springs
Do you think that
visiting the land you will know any of this?
I mean
Do you think this is said
anywhere in the land or conveyed in any way?
Did you know it before
or find it out after?
I read it before
Because I saw someone else point out
Have you seen this story? It's absurd
And then visiting there
This is mentioned nowhere, none of this
Would you say it's more
or less active
This is before all of our time
But if we had to compare it to how much
the story of merry weather
pleasure was present if you went
into the 8 tracks club
But there's no plaques
There's no plaques saying this story
So less present because there were plaques there
But not even a plaque
This is an online only mythology
But is the summer home there?
The summer home is the
fantasy springs hotel
Because I think it says
more visitors
started coming so then she built
a grand hotel for all her
friends who are visiting
So that's how they justify the hotel
And the hotel was very
grand, some parts of it a little bit grander
Other parts
There weren't enough wishes to make it
quite as grand as the most grand
You know how it goes, you gotta budget these wishes
The duchess was a little bit down
on her luck that she didn't have as many
millions as she normally did
The duchess isn't always crushing it
So as we go through
this land, just keep all that in mind
I'm sure you've all memorized it already
Remember that duchess
I like that duchess though is an IP now
of Disney
She's not duchess from the aristocats
She's just a duchess
Different duchess
This land or port
as they're called in Disney Sea
It's located between
Arabian coast and
Lost River Delta
Which is sort of like far corner of
the park, it's a long walk
way past everything
It is a very long walk, a friend told me
that if you walk from Hotel Mira Costa
at the main entrance of the park to
Fantasy Springs Hotel, it's the same walk as
walking from Shinjuku Station to
Harajuku Station
So that's like, I think a mile and a half
Geez, wow
So it's very long
The entrance of Fantasy Springs
actually reminds me a lot of Galaxy's Edge
Because it's these two caves
that you go through, one is an entrance
and one is an exit
So you're exiting kind of
this hyper realistic
lands of the main
Disney Sea into what is essentially
their fantasy land
Right, okay
So it kind of exists outside of
Because it is the first area of Disney Sea
that's not centered around, that doesn't touch
the main waterway that kind of
connects all of the ports
So it almost, you literally do
enter another world in a way
Yeah, and I was going to say this at the end
but now's a good time, it does feel
very disconnected from the rest of the park
And
you know, in every land
and all the other ports, you see Mount Prometheus
and you kind of see each
land's interpretation of Mount Prometheus
So in Cape Cod it's very calm, it's a calm
mountainside, in
Mysterious Island it's an ominous volcano
You can see
Mount Prometheus from one spot inside
Fantasy Springs, and it's an
afterthought, you're inside Skull Rock in
the Peter Pan area, and you just see a
little glimmer off in the distance of Mount
Prometheus
And that is on purpose, because there's so
much thought put into all the different
vantage points in Tokyo Disney
Sea, it's amazing
It's almost like a preview of what that
disconnected California adventure
across the street might feel like
Like a park that is
sort of
disconnected, where you
take a weird bridge or a tunnel to get over there
I mean, does it
does that hurt it at all to you?
Or is it just like, oh interesting, it's just kind of different
It's just interesting and worth pointing out
The caves to get in serve a practical
purpose to park ops, because
it's a backstage road
that is going over you
I mean, you obviously don't see it
But yeah, the walkway to get up to
these caves is also shockingly
large, I didn't measure
it out on Google Maps or anything, but it feels as
big as Disneyland's hub
It is such a far walk to go from
like Arabian coast to
the caves to enter Fantasy Springs
And then as you approach
there's rockwork of
Peter Pan, Anna and Elsa, and Rapunzel
So those are like the three mini lands inside
Fantasy Springs. That's kind of the thing
around all of Fantasy Springs, is there's rockwork
of characters from various Disney
movies. Yeah, and in the hotel
grounds, there's a whole
these rocks are all Beauty and the Beast
characters, and are some of those in the park too
It's not necessarily characters that are represented
in the land, but that you'll see
I don't remember, like Cinderella
Cinderella, the Maleficent Dragon
The Magic Mirror from
Snow White is a hidden
it's hidden in a waterfall, and every once in a while
the face will come out. Oh, I think I did see that
It's like rockwork, it's actually kind of creepy at night
Yeah, oh wow
Also, it's exciting that we
get a bunch more of this great
rockwork that like, for all
of the ups and downs or
complaints or disappointments of
high highs and then various
lows of recent Disney stuff
rocks have been on fire
everything rockwise
and this is that dude Zolt Hormay
again, right? This is Mr.
Fake Rock, yet another
masterwork from this guy. I chatted with him
at D23, he lived in Japan for
three years working on Fantasy Springs
rockwork, him and his team, so really impressive
Do we know if he's involved
in the liberty
demolition of
the Rivers of America to put up
rockwork for the new cars? Cause that
honestly ups the
anticipation for me if he's doing
cool rocks. Some new Zolt, if you're getting
some new Zolt. If it's new Zolt replacing
the Rivers, I feel like that's it. New Zolt just dropped
What's he like?
Oh, he was so nice, so cool
so passionate. He was talking
to me more about just like living in Japan, he was like
yeah, and I saw Bob Dylan and they took my phone away
and he's like really cool
Just random
That's cool, oh great
So, the only other thing of note at the entrance
is a vending machine because
that's a thing in Japan
and they're adding more and more of those to the park
and I just wanted to mention it because all throughout
the land there is these little
springs of water flowing through
and it adds a really nice kinetic
energy to the land. At night they
light up and it sparkles among
the rockwork, so there is a
flow of water going into this vending
machine suggesting that the water
from the springs is like filling up the water bottles
Oh, that's nice
That's cute. Yeah, the water features
are really incredible
It's from the videos alone
Really nice
It seems obvious, you gotta
add water because it's Disney Sea, but
they did it in a nice way
So, before
I move on to the three mini lands
and just heap endless praise
I want
to talk about the
nightmare of accessing
Fantasy Springs and its rides
This is a very American
touch
It is a Walt Disney World
level of frustration
to get into this thing
I don't know, you guys
might be like, oh good
It sounds like a challenge to me
It's a little Puzzle Walter scale
Sounds like I can put my Sherlock hat back
on to figure this mystery out
to figure out how to be efficient
So, to get into Fantasy Springs you
either need a standby pass
for one of the lands rides
You need a paid priority pass
You need a Fantasy Springs
magic ticket
You need to be a guest at the
Fantasy Springs Hotel
Or you need to have a mobile order
from any of the restaurants in the lands
And all that does is get you in the land
Or you need one of the special tassels
from the Duchess's hat
Or you need to be
one of her tassel
You need to be one of the Duchess's gentleman callers
To be able to go in
You need a handwritten letter from the Duchess
I seek this gentleman's pleasures
this evening
So, what is a standby pass
you ask
A standby pass
is like a
virtual queue spot for
Rise of Resistance when it had that
or Guardians of the Galaxy or whatever
So, you go on the app
first thing in the morning when you get in
You grab one of these
You could theoretically grab another
standby pass, but they are often out
So, here's where this becomes super frustrating
Tokyo DisneySea, since Fantasy Springs
has opened
has been opening one hour before
their posted opening time
So, let's say 9 o'clock
So, they are actually opening at 8
But so many people line up
because they're so passionate and there's no annual passes
So, anyone with a day ticket
needs to make the most of their
time at the park
6.30 a.m., 7 a.m.
So, I was like
leaving my hotel at 6 a.m. every day
to get in line, so I could get into
the park and get one of these standby passes
So, these run out almost immediately
especially for Frozen
It's been getting a little
better lately, but it's still
a nightmare
Is it on all three of the main rides?
Yes, so it's on
all four of them
The Tinkerbell thing?
So, the priority
access pass, that's like
standby
but paid
It's
2,000 yen, so I think that's
like 17 bucks
but also runs out very fast
especially for Frozen
Tinkerbell's busy buggies does not have this
That's the only ride that has standby only
A Fantasy Springs
Magic ticket is what you get when you buy
one of the super expensive
Tokyo Disney Resort vacation
packages, which is
minimum one night
I actually did do this one night with a friend
who was born and raised in Japan
It was $1,200
We stayed at the cheapest hotel, which was
Toy Story Hotel
We got our Fantasy Springs Magic ticket
but let me tell you something
You can ride all the rides
unlimited in the priority access
lane in Fantasy Springs
Guaranteed access anytime you want to the land
We did Frozen
nine times,
you also get an unlimited
drink ticket
Tokyo Disney Resort, known for all these
great sugary drinks that change out
seasonally, I was pounding these things down
So any drink you can get unlimited
except for Alcoholic
So that was great
but it was a lot of money
And then the other two
be a guest at Fantasy Springs Hotel
that's self-explanatory
So that's how you get into Fantasy Springs
A lot of people are shut out
I would just go and observe
people trying to get in
and they would have like a little QR code
like here's how you get into Fantasy Springs
Bro, it's like 2pm, long gone
Oh god, oh no
This opened in June
officially, even when were you there?
I was there the week after it opened
Oh well, do we anticipate this
getting better anytime soon or is this what it is?
I've heard it's gotten slightly better
but especially for Frozen it's still
you need to be there at opening to grab
a free standby pass
Would you see like anybody freak out
or was everybody too polite to like
scream at somebody about
coming all this way and paying all this money?
I definitely heard tourist cursing
Okay, tourist
Tourist being like American
The Duchess's ears
Trying to nap
So I was in Disney Sea
for two of the days of my vacation
and one of the days I did it like a normal
guest, I couldn't even get
Frozen, all I could get was Peter Pan
Even though I got there an hour and a half
early, I still could only get Peter Pan
I was too late for Frozen
This is disheartening to me
I know it's changed since then
but when I was there in 2019
after
I have the least tolerance for all this crap
of anybody on this show
so to go to Tokyo Disney
either of the parks and that it is paper
fast passes, my god
I have time traveled to the glory
days of 2002
things are
normal, we function
as a society again
made me so happy, so I am
disheartened here that they've given
into the
famous Disney bureaucracy
They do have other
paid priority access
rides like Beauty and the Beast
but then they do have their free
digital fast pass
system, which is
It's not on every ride
but it's on
good ones and you can use that
When I was there it was a pretty busy day
and it was easy to get
Did they still call it fast pass?
It was very weird
I assume they're going to change this name anytime
It was still called 40th anniversary
access pass
or something like that
They found a way to make it a clunkier name
It was very clunky
Oh, go ahead
Oh, sorry
Fantasy Springs is split up into three mini lands
I guess I'll just go through as the order you see them
when you enter
The first is Rapunzel's Forest
It's the smallest of the mini lands
There is
Rapunzel's Tower
It's like a full size tower
It's really tall
Rapunzel animatronic is in it
I'm telling you
This stops people
dead in their tracks
They stare up in awe
as she sings from her
tower
Not even really taking pictures or doing anything
They're just mouth agape
staring at Rapunzel
She looks great
It's like real hair, real animatronic
She's not singing
the songs directly from the movie
She's very pleasantly
singing them
There's a very light melody going along with it
It's so nice
She's going about her day versus doing a performance
Exactly
You're peeping
In a good way
Peeping is a bad connotation
You're just peeping on this young girl
Nicely peeping
Pleasantly, innocently peeping
Just a nice little peep
Then there's the
Snuggly Duckling restaurant from Tangled
And this is
You think about things where Disney has
recreated faithfully
This looks straight out of the cartoon
They just made it
inside and out
There's no compromises
They changed it up a little to where it's
post movie story
So inside Rapunzel has made these fun murals
It's beautiful
But everything from the movie is in there
The stage with the piano and the fireplace
and everything
What food do they sell there?
The worst hamburgers I've ever had in my life
I just landed on a Google image
right as you said that
This looks horrible
There's like potato salad or something on the burger
There's some kind of slaw
And then a gigantic thick slice
of bologna
It's awful
Jason, what do you think?
Bologna and potato salad
You hooked my attention
Are you booking a flight?
Yeah
I'm booking a flight
And I'm booking the
Toy Story Hotel to get that package
And you're making a date
with the duchess it seems like
I am, yeah
Just looking at the pictures
of Snuggly Duckling
It looks amazing
This burger also an alarmingly soft
and alarmingly yellow
burger
What is up with this bun?
This is truly
nauseating
Is this the chicken sandwich I'm looking at?
Yeah, it's either the chicken or the shrimp
That looks terrible
Well, show this guy
Jason, what do you think?
What was that noise?
I couldn't tell you if it was good or bad
That's like when the ghost host comes back
I'm hearing the Haunted Maid
Oh the French
Champagne
Bologna on the burger
It was that startling
That's what it was
It's not the best
But this person could have made this look worse
They know what they were doing
This looks so bad in the posed photo
I mean
It doesn't look good
I'm just saying that this looks like
I think the worst burger of my life was
Discoveryland in Paris
So it's interesting that Disney
has another
entry in the worst burger in the world
game
You can do worst
Disney burger Final Four someday
That's pretty good
There are a lot to choose from
Even the not actively horrible
just the bland unpleasant ones
in our Tomorrowland are in the running
Has anyone had a good hamburger
in the parks?
I'm trying to rethink
That's a good listener question
Anywhere you can leave comments let us know
Because I'm sure there are
I don't think you can count
Guy Fieri is making something over
at the observatory
This is an in park burger
Well Guy your job is to be in Disneyland
5 days of the week?
6? 4?
A lot of days
But have you ever had a good hamburger
in Disneyland proper or Disney California
No they used to have a good one
at the Grand Californian in the Craftsman's
Grill
They don't have anymore
It had pulled pork on it
That's long gone
I don't believe I've ever had a good burger
Is it truly
a barren genre
in all of Magic Kingdom type parks?
Jason what do you think?
I can't remember
Growing up my parents
dreaded
a quick service food
at Disney World
But he loves that sunny eclipse
That's got a toppings bar
Is the toppings bar still there?
I'm not sure I heard that Jason
I think the toppings bar came back
Finally
We're going to have to double check on that
We don't want to spread misinformation
But do you almost put the toppings
in another category
Separately we have a toppings bar
I think you are using the toppings
to hide the burger
You're not so
cosmic ray poisoned
that you think the burger is good
I think what's happening is that every time you add
another piece of that iceberg lettuce
you're thinking ka-ching ka-ching
I'm saving money or I'm getting a value
here
Another two cents
And the garbage bag
have snacks for back at the room
A garbage bag full of free lettuce
Free lettuce?
Free lettuce and wet
caramelized onions
Jason checks a bag on his plane full of lettuce
Wait I found
a possibilities
I don't know if you can speak to any of these guys
I haven't had any of these
Sci-fi dine in at Disney's Hollywood Studios
or Space 2020
Those are more
a sit down situation
I think it's got to count
Sci-fi dine in I think
I heard the chef
from the one burger restaurant
at Disney Springs
Deluxe
I think he moved over to Sci-fi dine in
after that restaurant
There's a Kobe beef
at Yak and Yeti
That's third party
that could be good
I'm sure it is good
I guess by my previous definition
it counts but of course that's going to be
better than the tomorrow
It's probably like $28 too
Maybe that's what you put a price on
Can you get a good burger at a Disney park for under $15?
The answer is
probably no
Moving on to Peter Pan's Neverland
What about
Rapunzel ride?
Sorry
Rapunzel's Lantern Festival
It's a boat ride that goes
outside
It's one of the few
Tokyo Disneyland, Tokyo Disney
rides that actually goes outside
I've seen videos now of
it getting dumped on with rain
You think splash mountains
outside, big ponders outside, but those
move fast
This is a very slow moving boat ride
I'm wondering how that's going to go long term
You start off
in a boat builder's hut
You see boats in various stages
of being assembled
and then the lanterns being
assembled for the lantern festival
It's very pleasant and nice
You start off
You're gently floating past
Rapunzel's tower
She's singing in it, it's so nice
And then you see Flynn
and the horse, which I can't remember his name
Maximus
They're kind of peeking
behind a rock and looking at her
and looking kind of worried
It's a very cool start to the ride
Then you float through
Rapunzel's free from the tower
Animatronic Rapunzel swinging around a tree
and Flynn is looking all smug
Looks great
Then the next scene is
Rapunzel's glowing hair, which looks
fantastic
They nailed this
Then you go into
one of the best scenes
in the entire land, it's the actual
lantern festival
You're circling around the boat
It's kind of like the kiss the girl scene
The lantern festival ride
The lanterns are everywhere
They're in your entire peripheral vision
It's so nice
It seems like a giant room
It appears as such
It's really big
Then you go past a couple of the people
from the Snuggly Duckling and the ride just ends
It just abruptly ends
No mother
Gothel
No explanation, it's just a couple of paintings
explaining the rest of the story
They don't feel the need to fully close out
the full Rapunzel tale
The ride is a little short
but what is there is pretty good
It seems, dare I say
that parts of this ride
look a little bit romantic
That lantern room
feels very calming
I wanted to smooch someone
very badly on this ride
You didn't just start asking around
The language barrier
That would be weird
Do you think most romantic
Disney ride
would you say that
or do you have a different one
Do you consider
the Bayou part of
Pirates of the Caribbean romantic
Jason does I think
It's in competition
with that I would say
Okay
The Disneyland version
I'm saying
I would throw Mexico
into the discussion
It's obviously
Blue Bayou opening of Pirates
is a superior area
but there's a similar dim vibe
and those Joe Rodi paintings are very nice
and also
there's no creeps
there's no creeps on a porch
which again I think might add to Jason's
affection for it
Jason wants creeps
He's just at his house
He's just trying to sit on the porch
He's looking at June bugs
He's not looking at you
He's concerned about
How's the frog ecosystem around these parts
Last year when we talked about
the grave where I was feeling like
the Haunted Mansion tipping you backwards
was somewhat romantic
That's the only ride that tips you
I always want to stop there
and just take a little break
Yeah because you can take a nap
Sometimes you do stop there
That's real nice
I really want to go on this Tangle Ride to see
how it stacks up
Of course if you're opening up to all rides
most romantic moment
is Optimus Prime
Even if it's not a romantic love you feel for him
It's love
It's pure love
Optimus love
I don't think that's been said fully
I think that's a subtext of what you're feeling too
He's proud and you wouldn't be so proud if he didn't love you
Do you think Optimus Prime
in the ride has kissable lips?
Answer the question
Well I want to answer it correctly
I don't want to say something flippantly
And then he hears this
and he's like what I don't have kissable lips
I love you
His lips really get right in your face
They really do yeah
I think that here's the thing
and I don't want to offend him
Obviously they're not human lips so they're going to be
metallic and I assume
though here's the good thing
because he's just been fighting they're very warm
because the machine has been heated up
So at least when you kiss the metal
it's warm
Hot iron
Would you rather kiss than cold iron?
Unless it's scalding
Unless his lips are scalding
That's a big fight
That would indicate though that he was created
in a bad way that he would
overheat
I think he has just the right amount of heat
It doesn't seem like he's got steam coming out of his ears
So I think it's a nice
80 degree sort of heat
75 degree
Warm enough to let him know he's alive
So that would be a nice aspect
But obviously I'm a human being
I like kissing
organic lips
skin lips
My preference is skin lips not metal lips
But
I might also be careful to dance around
the distinct possibility that he kisses all of his
toys at night
I have a couple of metal toys
But most of them are plastic
The movie accurate
Ninja Turtle toys
They are so beautiful
We're getting closer to skin lips with those
Honestly
I'm not just saying this because we were
involved with the official entity
If I had to kiss a toy
those straight sharks are up there
Because of that real feel
Real feel and the mouth is so big
Even on a 6 inch toy
It's almost the size of a human mouth
That's what I'm saying
I'd watch out for those teeth obviously
But I think I could stay fully on the outside
You would get a lot of teeth
when you kissed
But sometimes people like that
I think there's a way to do it without getting any teeth
If the requirement is kiss
I'm not giving any tongue to ripster
Mattel still listening
I just bought a toy
From the Ninja Turtle line
It's called Belly Bomb
He's got his big mouth in his stomach
He's got so many teeth
He's got a tongue though as well
He would be good to kiss
But it would be scary
I just showed Jason a picture
This is maybe the greatest toy I have ever gotten
It's a beautiful toy
Jason I saw it already
You can move his eyeball
He does look like he's a little bit
Aroused in this photo
He does
There's a part of the room
Where a character starts getting a blowjob
And his eyes kind of roll back
It's very much like
Mike in the room
I spent a lot of time last night
Maybe 20 minutes
Taking different photos of him
To see which different moods I could put him in
This was before this conversation
You were taking last night
Before this even came up
Remember the photos
Of Belly Bomb
9.30pm
I sent these to multiple people I know
Some of these photos
What was an example of what you would say
About Belly Bomb
In your angle
This is a different photo I took of him
Where he looks scared
He's got a gun in one
But he has eyeballs on his hands
Like the Pan's Labyrinth character
You would kiss his little eyeball hands
If he touched your face
A squishy eyeball would go up against it
That would be interesting if it wasn't done
With any sexual intention
I wouldn't mind just feeling it
But this has got to be a friendly path
Not seductive
I'm looking at my serious toy collector
Group text chain
That's kind of a joke
That's a jokey title
I wrote having the eye move
Gives you so many options
And then I sent a couple photos
Sent it to my friend Luke
And he just wrote very expressive
Do you think this is expressive?
Very expressive
He's also Belly Bomb kind of phallic
Let's be honest
He's skin colored
One eyeball is kind of on the end of a penis
Sort of shape
But it is maybe the greatest toy
I ever have
I also messaged the sculptor of said toy
Last night
He did a great job
P.S. Any tips if I were to kiss him?
He didn't offer that up
He ignored that part of the question
What's the next area guy?
I was going to say
I also want to move on
But I would love if by the end of the episode
Jason Ort
Optional guy if you want to name a toy
That you would like to kiss
Everybody think about it
That would look like a pressure on our guest
So I'm saying optional
Through the port
I would love if at the very end
I could throw to you and you could say a toy
I already have my answer
We'll cover it at the end
But for now we'll get back on track
Peter Pan's Neverland
They really did a great job
With this land
One side you see
Skull Rock and Captain Hook's ship
Sitting in a little harbor
It looks great
It's that thing Disney does really well
Where it's a little fantastical
But also based in reality
Sure
The transitioning to a real 3D environment
They really blended that well
You can go in Skull Rock and get pictures inside the skull
And then there's a little
Pirate ship in Skull Rock
Disappeared from Disneyland forever ago
And that's the thing my mom pines for
She loved it there
It came back in Paris
And now to have a committed
Paris is so good
And then there's a little cavern
With a little treasure chest and waterfall
And on Captain Hook's ship
There's a little photo op
With his hook so you can put your hand in there
It's really fun
And then on the other side is the actual mountains
Or I guess volcanoes
From the movie that they fly around
With a nice pretty fake cloud
Around them
The volcanoes puff out smoke
At night again looks really good
More volcanoes in this park
It's interesting
It's like a little other range
It sounds cool
You can't really see them both at the same time
I guess I wish you could
This was one of those things too
Visiting Tokyo Disneyland and Sea
Every year
Just watching the progress over the last 6 years
And that was one of the things you could actually see
Was those volcanoes
And I remember when the scaffolding came down 5 years ago
I was like oh that's going to be so sick
So the main ride
The main ride here
Is Peter Pan's Neverland Adventure
I'm going to say something
So controversial in this room
That I debated my entire drive up here
If I'm going to say it
It's coming out
This is a Transformers slash Amazing Spiderman
Style ride
I think it is the best one of those kind of rides
It's better than these
Wow
Crazy
It is just so fun and nice
And you're flying along
With Peter and the gang
And battling pirates on their ship
And some dude falls in the water
And he's doing all the poses from the movie
And then he takes you and you fly above London
Above the clouds and lands on the clock
It is just so pleasant
It's mixed with a ton of
Really well done physical sets
And little things happen in the physical sets
That sync up with the movies
It's like a really nice mixed media
Kind of thing
3D right
The queue
You go past their tree
That they live in I guess
I'm not really super familiar with Peter Pan
I try not to be
This is another thing
They renamed the lost boys
To the lost kids
I caught that
Are there female characters
Or is that just a
I think there always have been
I'm actually not 100% sure
The guests were
Members of the lost kids
So they wanted to include
Everyone
That's a good interpretation
The queue
You're in this forest and you see their tree
And then you go into their clubhouse
And it looks very hand built
It's like uneven planks of wood
Stuff from sunken ships
It's so nice
And the boat
That you ride in on the ride
Also looks very hand made
You know what
I haven't seen the vehicle until this morning
Because I was curious
Because it's not trackless
It's more like the rides
You're comparing it to
Which gives it that tighter control
Probably a little more thrilling
It has the
High walls so you can't really see
Outside of the ship
Sort of directs your vision
Closes it all in
Did you feel like there was any difference
Did you feel like it could do something different
Than the Transformers Spider-Man ride vehicle
Or was it pretty much
I think it was pretty similar
It's funny that they've gotten into this genre
That they've landed
And all these trackless rides
Now they've landed at what Universal was doing
25 years ago
Can I go back real quick
What was the boat
Was it a Wi-Fi control boat
Does it turn you or is it just sort of a normal
Boat in a trough
Very pleasantly floating you through
Just another one of those
High capacity things
Pump 2,000 people an hour through there
I love that they're into boats right now
I love that we're getting a lot of boats going on
No reason to ignore the boat genre
So
Something else about this Peter Pan ride
Just a weird anomaly when I wrote it
I was mentioning the standby pass
So there's no regular
Lines on these rides
Standby pass or you need the access pass
So it leads to the situation
Where they have
Stopped
Giving out the standby passes
And everything is sold out
And so I went to this
My return time was like
3.30 in the afternoon and I'm going through the queue
And there's like nobody in the queue with me
And then I'm getting on the ride
And it's just me
And I have an entire boat to myself
I have a picture of this on Twitter that I posted
And I went
I'm completely alone because
They were still adjusting
When they're going to distribute more standby passes
Because you really have to be on the app
Refreshing all day
And I've heard people really do that
As they're walking around everything
They're just pulling down to refresh all day
Sounds good to me
I know some people like that
Were in the room with a person like that
So yeah that was
Just an interesting thing that happened to me on there
Can I bring up this discussion of
Your assertion
It's better than Spider-Man or Transformers
I think I buy it
Because I buy that Disney using that technology
Today would be really
Strong
I feel like what you're up against in this room
With that argument is Jason's undying love
Of Spider-Man, Mike's undying love
Of the kissable hot metal lips
Of Optimus Prime
And my undying hatred
Of Peter Pan as a genre
And character
So all three of us are furious
That's why this was so hard
But logically
It makes total sense
To me
Does it get you excited for
If indeed this Avengers
Infinity defense
Is going to be in this genre
Do you think that ends up in the discussion
Of best one of these attractions
I'm not a Marvel fan at all
I've never seen any of these movies
I'm sure it will be totally fine
And people who enjoy that sort of thing
Will love it
You might be a little lost
There isn't the emotional pull
Does the Peter Pan ride fuck you up
Like Transformers
It's like a loving mother
Cradling you
I like it for Pan
But for that Marvel ride
I want to get fucked up
I want to get jostled
Hardcore
I don't think that's what they do
Even an edgier
More adult Disney ride
I just don't think that's their deal
I mean Matterhorn does
But that's kind of accidental
Unless they want to push massages
At the spa in Grand California
They can give out cards
And really fuck you up
Is that an experience you've ever done
A massage
No, my girlfriend has
That's something we should review
In these days
It starts with a T
Tenya?
We've never reviewed the spa
I was going to guess the name of a Mexican restaurant
In my area
We could each get a different service
Like one of us gets a facial
One of us gets a massage
And one of us gets a pedicure
Sure
It'll be like $1500
Each
Each $1500
Guy, let me ask
This Peter Pan ride
Since there's so much footage
How did you feel about
The CG
Footage compared to
Because this is a 2D
Traditional animated film
Yeah, I think they did
A really good job
Especially with the faces
It's just very
Colorful
But then they also gave it
A nice little texture
That almost makes it look
Paper-y
I watched a panel about this at D23
And they showed all the 3D models
And they would rotate them
Does it look like
What was the Zelda
Is Wind Waker the one that has paper
Cell shaded
Not as cartoony as that
It's a little more muted
But it looks great
I've heard a lot of people say
It's a kind of hidden gem of
Fantasy Springs
Yeah, really enjoyed that one
Next
To the Peter Pan ride
Is Lookout Cookout
This is just a quick service restaurant
That also follows the same theme
That looks like it's built by the lost kids
The handmade thing
Just really fun inside
I didn't eat here because all they had was
Baskets of fried
Shrimp and chicken and stuff
It's better than the burger though maybe
I did get twice
I got the drink that they have there
Because I think it's called Peter Pan's
Fizzy drink
And it's the same color as Peter Pan
It's green
And you drop a little thing in it
And it just starts fizzing all over the place
And it's delicious
Which is much needed
Because the next thing I'm about to talk about
In the Peter Pan land
Is the popcorn cart
Okay
Now, the flavor of this popcorn
Cart, if you're not aware
All around the Tokyo
Disney Resort parks
They have flavored popcorn, each one has a different flavor
Some of which are excellent
Fantastic
I dream of the honey
Popcorn
Wait, is it by Winnie the Pooh?
And the area smells like honey
The flavor here
Is roast beef
What?
I heard about this
I'm trying not to be hyperbolic here
This is
One of the worst things
I've ever put in my mouth
It tastes like
Room temperature marinade
That's been left open
Overnight
And then after you chew and swallow
It leaves the worst
Awful, mucky aftertaste
I've ever experienced in my life
Gosh
It's revolting
It's not like
Oh, blue milk and green milk is so bad
Let's take a sip and then
It is truly awful
Is the idea
Also that
I don't know
You hear roast beef and you think of Arby's
But then I read a description
Aromas of roasted meat and gravy
They're almost going for more of that
Old English
It establishes neither
It's neither English comfort food
Or Arby's
When you post almost anything on Twitter
You'll get one or two people in
Like, fuck you
But this one is universally
People agreeing with me
That's a nightmare
I actually felt really bad
Because it's not polite to waste food
In Japan
And my friend who I was with
Born and raised in that country
I can't eat anymore of this
And I just saw his face
He also hated it
And he forced himself to eat the entire thing
Oh no
I felt so bad
Because now that you weren't sharing it
He had to have more
You were splitting it
Over the course of six pained hours
Brutal
All right, Mike
Don't go there and order this
Unless you want to force feeding
Because I know it's what you'll do
Or I will in shame
Go into a bathroom stall
And shove it in my pants
Or in a different bag
And then throw the bag away
There'll be some antics for me trying to get rid of it
Bring it back to America
And then you get held up at the airport
It's a souvenir for bringing popcorn back
To my family I love at home
It's like that scene in Dumb and Dumber
With Harland Williams
With a P
They taste it at customs
And they're so disgusted
They're like just get out of here
That reminds me
For the last
I guess eight or ten months
I've gotten this Tokyo treat
Mail order box
So every month you get a new box
Of snacks from Japan
And 90% of the time
It's so fun
It's so great
There's so many interesting snacks
Where it's like oh we don't make
Chips or candy like this
We don't have this flavor profile
In America every now and then
There is one or two snacks
Where you're like oh I don't
I can't do this
Sometimes they're insane
Over there I remember one time
This happened within
An hour of each other
With some friends
My friend puts his money in the vending machine
And he's thinking I just really need coffee right now
Just sees something that looks like coffee
Hits the button, cracks it open
Takes a swig, it's corn chowder
It's corn chowder
With actual corn
And then me, like not even an hour later
I'm so thirsty, it's hot
Okay water, this looks good
Drink it, take a swig
Scream in horror
It's salty seaweed water
Oh my god
It's just nothing I ever want to consume
Especially on a hot day
So if you knew what you were getting
Maybe not that
You're not going to order seaweed water
But if I knew I was getting corn chowder
Then I'd do, but that disconnect from coffee
That is so
Reviled by that switch out
So the other ride in Peter Pan's Neverland
This is a pretty big mini
Land in the land obviously
So it's Fairy Tinkerbell's
Busy Buggies
This name I've complained of
Fairy Tinkerbell
Why do they do this?
Why do they explain it?
I like this clunky name
I will say I like saying it a lot
Versus all their clunky names
It'll be a good warm up for us to do
Before we start talking for two hours
Do it faster, Fairy Tinkerbell's Busy Buggies
And then you really get your enunciation down
So yeah
This is just a cute little
Kids ride, nothing more
What does it do?
It's a dark ride
But it's outside
So a cute thing about it
Is the cast members working this ride
Have little fairy wings on the back of their outfits
That's cute
The aesthetic really is
Like a little
More detailed
Bugs land
So it's the thing Disney
Loves to do where it's like you're small
Now
Slades of grass and a big thimble
Rides like that
So
The ride starts out
And I don't want to be crude here
But I don't know any other way to say this
They show you a video
Of Tinkerbell explaining the story
They gave her
An absolute dump truck ass
Okay?
She is
I loved her
She is caked up
And I was saving this
Because I also did it in the Peter Pan ride
Because she's also in there obviously
Now can I ask this
Did you go back to the original film
And just double check that this wasn't the original
The proportions from the original
You know I didn't compare them side by side
But I feel like I see enough Tinkerbell
Gifts and that sort
To where I don't remember her being that
Thick
Now let me ask you this, are you the first one to bring this
Because recently, I mean there's obviously from the film
In Incredibles, there's a discussion
Of Mrs. Incredible
And there's the character in the park and stuff
Are you maybe the one breaking this news
To America
In the states
Have you seen the discourse online
I've brought this up to other friends and I've showed them pictures
And everyone agrees so far
So take a look
At the pictures
It's in my review that I posted on touring plans if you want to look that up
I didn't mention a dump truck ass on touring plans
This is podcast the ride though
This is the place to do it
It is where we tend to fuse
Theme park conversation and
Oddly sexually charged
For people who claim to be
PG rated in every episode
Banned kids sex energy
This podcast the ride
Sadly
I'm the only banned kid of the three of us
But that is what it is
So yeah, you go through this ride
Where it's just various environments
Like a snow thing and the idea
Is your Tinkerbell's friends
Delivering packages to her various friends
In the thing
It ends with a mouse
Named cheese
Which is
Is it a new character
It's a new character that
I don't know if they're trying to catch
Him on as like a new thing
But there's no merchandise or anything
And I don't really see many people talking
So I think it's just a thing
Okay, mouse named cheese
Okay, so new characters are Duchess and cheese
Yeah, and cheese is
Cute enough and you know
It's a big mouse and he moves around and he blinks
And you're like, okay, cheese, okay, get off the ride
Probably don't need to do this ever again
Would you like a plush of
Cheese? Is he cuter than Gus
From Cinderella? No
And he's nowhere, he's not in the same ballpark
As Shandu. I was about to say
So Shandu, did you go into
Sinbad though? It's closed for refurbishment
Until September. I think it's been closed since
March or February or something. This is a long
Refurbishment. Oh yeah, my friend
Roger was there early in the year and it was one of my
First questions and he said, no, long refurbishment
Damn
So
Not to backtrack Gus, I'm looking
At photos of Tinkerbell in
All guises and I think maybe
Tinkerbell is always quietly
Ahead of dump truck Gus
I think it's not, what you're
Saying is not, just if you do the general
Image, it might
Also be an effect of what she is wearing
Which there is, you know, it's sort of
Like a, almost like
It's leaves a little bit
Which fan out, that might be
Providing that effect, I don't know
I don't know, if you're looking
At it when I'm looking at it
It seems a little consistent
Throughout all of generations but maybe it's especially
Played up. Well it's also, it was in 3D
Well this one was in 3D
Oh this was on the big easy buggy, sorry, sorry
It's a 3D model on a screen
Before the ride leaves is what it looks like
Okay, okay
Well we're going to have to investigate this more
I guess, so we'll have to
Bring in experts or something
All of a sudden I'm feeling like the Peter Pan
Franchise isn't as bad as I've been saying
Oh no, oh no, I've not been giving
This franchise enough credit
I'm off to Neverland
I hope your listeners don't get
Too horny listening to us talk about
Asses and kissing
Oh well there's no more
Men that are
Roused at the audience than these men
That is absolutely
Their talk, theater of the mind
Belly bomb
Kissing men
Who play with their toys
I wonder what this episode just had
When they were talking about belly bomb
It was before they even got to the dump truck
This is, yeah, this is basically
An erotic podcast at this point
I love that belly bomb talk
Okay we're done with Peter Pan's Neverland
On to Frozen Kingdom
Oh it's called Frozen Kingdom
This is
Is that what the Jurassic Park was called?
No, Frozen Empire
Is Ghostbusters
And Fallen Kingdom is Jurassic Park
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Frozen Empire
Fallen Kingdom
When's that ride coming?
I want to go to the Frozen Empire
House of Tornites
In Florida
Here? Both
Do you think they'll do a house
Because if they're working with Reitman
Are they going to do a house of like
The horrors of being trapped in Studio 8H
And you've got your first ever live broadcast
And it has to go on at 11.30
Not because it's ready
Well the 10 Nightmares of Jimmy Fallon
Jimmy Fallon Maze
Jimmy Fallon in Rockefeller Center
It's called Jimmy Fallon's
To Nightmares
Do you saw this guy? No
There's a legit horror nights maze
In Rockefeller Center that's
That's themed to Jimmy Fallon's Nightmares
Wow, okay
Sounds great
Oh god, oh no, I gotta talk about
Apes with Paris Hilton
Oh god
I woke up and it's still happening
Not cool dude
I gotta do this interview with this puppet band called The Weirdos
Chris Martin and Coldplay
Have a puppet band
And the audience is going to be so befuddled
Even I can't convince the audience
That this is so good
I texted my girlfriend after you mentioned The Weirdos
Because she's into that kind of music
And I'm like, did you know about this?
And she was just like, okay
That's what our audience said too
That's a lot of the responses
I'm gonna clean this to my significant other
And they wrote back, okay
Okay, Frozen Kingdom
So it's very pretty
It's a port with a little
With some boats in the water
And a bridge leading over into the little town
The Arendelle Castle
It's all very pretty
The restaurant inside the castle
Is Royal Banquet
Banquet of Arendelle
It looks like
Inside the castle, like they're preparing
For the coronation
They have some of the best
Fake food and fake desserts
And fake cheese that I've ever seen
Like kind of off in the corner with a bunch of plates
Because I think they mentioned like 10,000 dinner plates
They have all the stacks of plates too
It looks awesome
Can I just say, you brought up a Final Four idea
I've
Audience, what do you think of
The possibility of the fake food
This one's occurred to me
It's a great alliteration that I like
I just haven't had like a ton of ideas of what those are
But if you have suggestions
If you think that's a good idea
Because it sounds like this is out of the gate of viable
The queue of
Runaway Railway out here
Has some pretty good fake treats
And they are selling
The power limes
But there are other things
There's like Darkwing Duck
Like, I don't even know what they call them
But they're like peanut butter, they're fake Darkwing Duck peanut butter cups
That I want for real
That are so enticing to me
Package wise and the way they look
And the popcorn kernels look like Mickey Mouse
Inside the popcorn machine in that queue
So that's definitely on the list
Some of those things are on the list
Do you like the idea or do you have suggestions
That might help us
Not give you too many assignments
Mainly think about what toys you want to kiss
But anyway
That's important
This restaurant instantly became
Probably my favorite food in the entire park
Besides Casbah Food Court
I think that's still my favorite
I got this like seafood stew
Pot pie thing
That was delicious
Tokyo Disney does seafood so well
When you think of seafood at Disneyland and Disney World
It's just kind of a nightmare
Especially quick service
This was really good
I fondly recall
A lot of my meals from Disney Sea
Which is pretty rare for even a great theme park
That's exciting
So now
We get to Anna and Elsa's
Frozen Journey
Which is the marquee ride
My note right here
Just says holy shit
So this ride is
One of those rides where
They nailed it in every way
It's genre defining
It's something that everything will be
Compared against in the future
That they do
It's every aspect of imagineering
Flexing as hard as they can
Impeccable lighting
Perfect use of sound effects
Beautiful scenery
The scope and scale
Of these scenes are massive
It's like some of these scenes
It's like you're in a Costco
And it's just fully themed
But then there's also still little intimate moments
Where there's little story beats and stuff
The queue is very detailed
Little moments where it's like
Olaf walking on the roof
Of the greenhouse
Where you see his little footsteps
Little interactive scenes
It's a different vibe than the queue
Theoretically you could put this
In the same attraction umbrella
As Frozen Ever After
But it seems like
It shares elements with it
But it's leaps and bounds
Just turned up to 50
The queue is a different vibe
There's a lot of paintings
It's very stately
It's really nice
Beautiful lighting fixtures
And things on shelves
The ride itself
It starts off with
You go by the trolls
They're starting off the story
They shoot a little magic lightning bolt thing
That shows a vision of the kids
Then you go into another room
It's Anna knocking on the door
It's the start of
Do you want to build a snowman scene?
The door spins around
It's Elsa looking all sad
The entire room becomes frozen
From her powers
The door freezes, shuts
That door turntable looks so cool
It looks great
With the scale
The perfect use of the projection
Mapping on everything
Let's say this
The animatronics are not
The weird little glow
Little illuminators
The strange little light up faces
We know in Epcot
The best animatronics you've ever seen
This is actually where
It does oddly
Keep something from the Epcot ride
Where you're
On a boat in this ride
But then you stop
Then you feel yourself turning to the side
Then you go backwards through another scene
There's one thing I wanted to bring up
This is not a leisurely boat ride
It's not a thrill ride either
But you are perfectly
Synced to what is happening
Around you
The movement is very deliberate
So you're going by
On a singing
In the portrait
Gallery in the movie
But then you enter another room
And it's Elsa getting ready for the coronation
And then they're singing to each other
In the opposite rooms
And then again it changes course
And then you go through the love is an open door
Scene
So it's kind of jumping around in scenes kind of fast
This is so hard to do
Because boat rides you forgive a lot of like
Well if I kind of sync up to what's happening
That's great, but this is precise
While not being specifically controlled
In the Shanghai pirates way
So then in the next scene
This is one of the coolest ones
And this is kind of the one everybody's taking pictures and video of on social media
So it's after love is an open door
Anna is asking
Elsa for permission to get married
Elsa is pissed
And she shoots her angry
Ice powers
And it turns this
They're in like a little village
And it turns this scene into
Big ice spikes come out of the ground
And these fountains that are
Projection map water on
Freeze and they turn sideways and all of a sudden they're frozen
And the whole area is freezing
All over the place with the projection effects
All the characters are terrified now
They go from looking normal to being
Totally terrified by this ice
Witch that is freezing everything
How many animatronics can like change
Personality mode
It's really impressive
Those spikes
That is an aggro moment
Sound effects like
This moment really jumps out
Even just in a
Audience shot video
It's spectacular
The next scene is
Elsa going up the hill
To start her new life
In her ice palace
And this is when the lighting effects really come into play
Because with each verse
As the
Song builds up
A sweeping light effect
Changes the sky
And then you see the ice palace forming
In the background
And then Elsa
Builds the ice bridge in the next scene
It's actually similar to Epcot
But then you actually go into the ice palace
And it's forming all around you
With the projection effects
But it looks blank when you go into it
And then you're backing out
Cold doesn't bother me anyway
Perfectly synced door slam shot
It's sick
That ceiling
Whatever ride through I was watching
Somebody was like let me just tilt up here
You're in a cathedral
It's insane
So yeah and then
Elsa accidentally zaps
Anna with the ice
And that's a crazy one too
Because again animatronic
Anna standing there
And then all of a sudden zapped with the ice
And you see her body illuminate with the ice
And then be frozen in place
So then
You go through the next scene
And it's like they're just getting through the story
It's like okay now the dude is going to come through
The sword and try to kill Elsa
And then you get to projected screens on
Like sails of ships
That are wrecked in the ice
So then you get to
Anna and Elsa standing there
Elsa is frozen in place doing her
Frozen pose
But then it's like the true love
Cures the thing
So you see Anna thaw out
And kind of go into place
And drop down to the ground
And again it's just one of those things like
How do animatronics look this good?
How do they get the motion to look this good?
Are these the best animatronics in anything currently?
Just the number
There's individual animatronics that are unbelievable
But the fact that this is like
So many of them
Everyone was saying Beauty and the Beast in Tokyo Disneyland
Was the best
But do you even see, did you go on that this time?
Did these look like better than
Beauty and the Beast or similar?
So on Beauty and the Beast
The animatronics don't talk a lot
And so on here
On Frozen you really get to see
The facial animations as well as
The body movements
I just think besides the grand finale
Of the Beauty and the Beast ride where the beasts
Change backs into the prince
I don't think they'll ever top that
Like that is jaw dropping
But
Pound for pound there's so many
Just cool little animatronic moments
On this ride and there's so many of them
I wonder if learning all this like
Changing expression stuff
That would be a good sign for the Walt Disney
Robot coming next year
Because people are very worried
That he'll look so creepy
Trying to recreate what Walt looks like
Some people are like you don't know what they can do now
Well I hope it's cool when Elsa comes in
And zaps him with ice
Walt is frozen
We finally get to see what that would be like
How the whole office freezes
Oh yeah
My pen holder, my scotch
This is what I wanted though
That would be good
George gets frozen in the office over to the right
What if the Walt animatronic
Has the light up face
Oh sure
What if just time constraints
Yeah they use the Epcot version
He looks like a doll face spectro man
Yeah
We'll see
Hi everyone I'm Walt
Why do they make him sound like that
It just matches the stretch of the face
I'm Walt Disney
I'm Walt
Help me
Wow yeah
So yeah and then you go
And then everything, the day is saved
And then they have a party and Anna and Elsa are skating around
The ride's over, amazing ride
10 out of 10
Just worth the price of admission
Worth the nightmare of getting to the park
Two hours earlier to try to get into
It's just so good
Do you think top Disney ride, Disney Sea ride
Or Tokyo Disney in general
It's up there
I still think 20,000 Leagues is my personal favorite
Just because it's so unique
And just so detailed
And you can ride it 500 times and still see something new
But yeah
The Frozen ride is amazing
I guess there's also
You gotta hope that we
Get that
If we're gonna get
Assuming that that is a Disneyland
Forward expansion
I hope we get it at this level
Because like
Hong Kong's not quite this right
Yeah I think that's more Epcot
I'm guessing
That whatever shape Disneyland Forward takes
We are seeing the lands now
In all the other parks
We're seeing like 80% of what we will get
In a decade in the other parks
Happening
I think so although there's a little bit of disagreement on this
Let me bring this up really quick
I forgot in the Peter Pan zone but since we're talking about
The Disneyland Forward stuff
Something that they've shown a lot
Is Peter Pan is a possibility of what ends up
Over there
And I forgot a little bit of push back
About this possibility from friend of the show
Van Rovers show
And he wanted to get involved in the betting that we've been doing
Oh interesting
Van's theory is that they're showing Peter Pan
Because that's something that makes sense to like
Well like an Anaheim City Council member
Knows what Peter Pan is
So if they say oh this seems fun Peter Pan will be there
But he does not believe that that will be
Relevant enough of a property
He thinks that that is like
A placeholder
Like a lie
So then they can put in something like
Avatar or a property
The TBD that will become more important to the company
Basically he wanted to throw out the bet
To us that
There won't be a big
Once we get all of Disneyland Forward
That none of that will be Peter Pan
What do you guys think of this
Proposition?
Well I want to bet that there will be a third part called
Panland
Exclusively for Peter Pan
I see what he's saying
I wonder
Yeah because like Tangled and Frozen make sense
Because Frozen they're going to make sequels after
Sequel I don't know if they're going to ever do a
Tangled sequel
So I get that that's more seemingly more
Relevant
Was there a Tangled TV show?
Something like that right? Like a cartoon
We don't keep up on that movie
We just know the rides
But yeah I think you're right
Is our knee jerk that we will be
Getting this Peter Pan stuff?
I agree with Van actually
Really? Would anybody take the
Can I say what the stakes of the bet are?
His proposition is that this
Bet is worth 40 pounds of Dole Whip
40 pounds?
Did they usually serve it
By the pound?
He looked it up and he
Found that some I don't know if it's like
I don't know if it's just like powder that you make
It from or something he found a link to
Where you can get it in pounds
It's about 80 dollars it's not
So unreasonable
But keep in mind if you could take the other side of it
And he's wrong you get 40
Pounds we all get to split maybe you could get in
On this guy if you want
Anybody have strong feelings about this?
I have Dole Whip at
They sell individual cups now
In the freezer section
I don't know but I'm saying you would probably weigh
Those out easily
I don't want to take
I agree with him I think there's other
You can get in on this
Van if you're listening
You're going to have to share that
Do you disagree with Van?
I don't know I think I do
I think I do
I don't want to fucking pan
Although maybe my opinions are changing in light of
Recent information however
It does seem I don't know it feels like they've said it a lot
And if this ride is so I think it's more about that
That ride is great than any
Like property relevance
I think a lot of that Disneyland forward
That initial concept art that wraps around
The hotel
Can look like
Mountains from Avatar
Mountains from Pan
Wakanda
Afrofuture mountains
Do you have a knee jerk though?
You think we're getting pan in 10 years?
I don't think we're getting pan
Do you think that is a savvy thought
Of like
Something that maybe an older city
Council person will go like oh Peter Pan
Disney yes
Am I the only person, am I the least of the
Treated are going to end up with 40 pounds of
Dole Whip in probably like
Maybe over five years because
We don't know when they're going to say it
It'll be like that Herb Albert cover
With the woman in the whip cream
With you and Dole Whip
Or no with us who we get the Dole Whip
If you, if there's no
If it becomes official that there's no Peter Pan
Expansion
Then you all share
Oh so we'll be in the, people know this reference
Right this Herb Albert cover with a woman
In whip cream from 60 years ago
Well if you've ever gone to a used record store because it is
At every single one
Yeah well as long as you, that's another
Part of the bet now you have to recreate that cover
Okay well if we win though
It's like a punishment
Can I ask something about this Dole Whip
Does it come in concentrate
Like do you have to mix it with something
The question I had, he sent me a link
Let me look, I wasn't too careful about this
I'll try to figure, do you have a knee jerk on this
While I look up the
Oh wait actually he sent, oh geez what he sent is only
17 pounds
You added 23
Pounds to that I'm confused at the link
It's a box and it appears, it's a very
Functional box and it apparently has 17
Pounds of Whip
Alright well, do you think we're
Getting Peter Pan that year
No I don't think so
I think they'll want more relevant
New stuff yeah
The man on an island
Pan Island
I don't know it's weird that I ended up on
Pan Island It is weird
Something is gravitating me towards it right now
I don't know what it is The pirate ship and the skull
Is cool
So if it is the full land that is
Enticing because it feels like a
Cool
I don't know thing to go to
Well let's just keep in mind then that there might be
A Dole Whip party
That we all, that everybody is invited to
And Guy you'll have to join too
And catered by me apparently
And if not then you all
Just watch me eat something I don't really want
17 pounds of it
We're going to have to do this in like 10
Sittings
Citrus based
Foods famously good for eating
A ton of right for the throat
And your teeth
The enamel on your teeth
It's Van's desire
Not even mine
He said you don't have to eat it but you have to accept it
Those are the rules of Van's bet
Okay
It seems like no matter who wins we all get punished
Somehow like everybody gets punished
Depending on just the logistics
The sheer hauling big boxes
Of Dole Whip around
And the smell of melted rotting
Dole Whip too
Haunting you much like the
Crocodile
Haunted hook
Guy you'll be pining for roast beef
Popcorn
Anyways okay what have we missed here
Yeah so yeah exit frozen
On the right hiding the giant
Show building a big old fjord
With water coming out and
You know just looks super nice
So this leads to the
Tokyo Disney Sea
Fantasy Springs Hotel
My note to start off this section
Of my notes ugly
Yeah
I mean the park facing side is alright
It's a little odd but then if you see
That's what I was looking at if you see all around it
It's not that great
Yeah the park facing side is much better
But if you're coming on that
Monorail from Tokyo Disneyland
To the Bayside Station
I mean it just looks like a big stucco
Box with a couple of little flourishes
It feels very vague it feels like if you're
Taking the monorail and you're behind
Bellagio it's not as nice as in the
Front
Yeah I wonder
If this got away from them
Or something cause it doesn't
Really match the rest of the
Land it's pretty enough you know
But yeah there's 475
Rooms in this hotel
419 rooms in
The normal side of the hotel but then there's the
Grand Chateau with 56
Rooms so that's like the ultra
Expensive premium
Rooms that look into
The land do we know how much more expensive
Than a typical than like
I don't know other surrounding hotels
So when I go to
Tokyo Disney and I stay in one of the
On-site hotels I try to pay like
120 bucks for like the Hilton or the
Sheraton right I love it that was a Hilton
But yeah I like that Hilton really nice yeah
Really good lounge in there by the way
Oh yeah yeah yes I liked it
Breakfast I liked it all there yeah oh yeah I still follow them
On Instagram
Yeah but then
You know like Toy Story Hotel that's like
You know 300
To 400 a night depending on the season
Pretty expensive right
And then this is in like the
Seven eight nine hundred
Dollar a night range
Oh so one night at the Contempor basically
You get a theme park
But also it's super in demand
Because it's new and people want to stay in it
And people want to get into Fantasy Springs
So they want to stay there and get the magic ticket
Yeah so I didn't stay here so all
I can really say is what I see from the
Outside and you know it's nice
Enough I guess the one thing
I heard people complaining about is that
It has what looks like a lobby
So you think like oh a lobby I want to go
Relax in here no that's
A lounge you need a reservation to get into
The reservation is super hard to get other than that
No you can't hang out in there
So yeah
But in front of the hotel
This is where most of those
Character rock work
Statues are Ariel with the fins
And the water splashing up
Sorcerer Mickey with the
Brooms dumping the water out
That all looks great
Especially at night when the water like is really
Bouncing off all the lights and stuff
This is where the only
Gift shop in the entire land is
Called Fantasy Springs Gifts
Oh I saw that
On the TDR Explorer
One of his many videos
He's like yeah the main gift shop
Is in the ground floor of the hotel
So it's like in the hotel
But you can get into it from
In the park
I waited an hour in the burning hot sun
To get in here
To get into the gift shop
I think all I bought was a bath bomb
For my girlfriend
I was good with the stuff in there
And now it's like all sold out and it's just
Regular Tokyo Disney merch
And nobody knows when it's going to restock or not
Geez
So
This hotel
Is inside the park much like Miracosta
And it has an entrance and
Exit
To get into the park
So you think that's great
This is only open to guests of
Fantasy Springs Hotel
You can't be at a hotel just on the other side
Right so when I was staying at
Toy Story Hotel which was directly
Across the street from it
If I contorted my body enough I could look out and see
My hotel
And I could not exit it at the end of the night
But you're at a Disney hotel
I don't even let you
So it's not like it's Grand Californian and Disney California Adventure
I don't know why I said the whole name
You can exit through the hotel
From the park but not enter
No you cannot do either
In Tokyo
You can't exit through
You can enter and exit
I think the first two hours of the day they'll let you enter
They'll let you enter after the first
If you're not staying
Have you tried this?
I always thought you couldn't enter
I go in all the time
I knew you could enter
If you were at the Disneyland
Hotel
But you're saying no you don't even stay there
The first couple of hours it's hotel guests only
But then after that they'll let you in
Because there's been so many times
Where I go to eat at Craftsman
That's a great place
You've got to walk so far around
Thank you for that tip
Another frustrating thing that I've heard from people
Who have actually stayed in the Fantasy Springs Hotel
Is that they close that
Entrance slash exit
At 9 o'clock or sometimes 9.15
Either way
If you're doing something else on the other side of the park
And you're not making it there in 15 minutes
The hotel you paid
$900 a night to stay in
You cannot exit
You have to go all the way to the front of the park
To Miracosta to get on the monorail and take it all the way back
That's rough
It seems like there are some
American style
Operations issues that need to be
Smoothed over
As time goes on
And everything is less popular
Maybe they'll open it up to everyone
I don't know, it's just something that they do now
That I think is very stupid
Sounds weird
So operational annoyances
But this
You're raving about most of what we got here
Yeah, it's just
Filled with wonderful
Rides and it's
Pretty and it adds a ton of
Capacity to the park
Which is nice
My only criticism
Is that it feels so disconnected
And that's not really a big deal
But yeah, it gives Disney Sea
Their fantasy land
Yeah, yeah, which is because there's
Analogs throughout
I don't remember the name of the area
But where Aquatopia is is kind of like their tomorrow
And then they sort of have
An adventure land
It makes a lot of sense, it's cool
And the thing
I'm sure I've said this before
It's a park that didn't need it
It was the greatest theme park I've ever been to
Regardless
And things you're saying are the best ride
They're one of the best
Anywhere, it's pretty mind-boggling
Massive
And the biggest expansion they've ever done
And boy it's what
Just really shows you what they're willing to do
With the Oriental Land Company
These rides are like 50,000 square feet
40,000 square feet, they're gigantic
You can see them all when you're staying in the
Hotels on the off-site ones
Right, right, is there more
I'm so into looking right now at the overhead
Google map of all these parks
Is there more room to expand
For DisneySea?
Yeah, there's that corner where they were going to put
The Scandinavia port, the original
Frozen port
And they were going to put it in that corner
It's still just empty
So there's still some room, because I was like, oh this is such a
Big footprint, I wonder what's even left
And then through the
Where the Toy Story ride is
There's like a bus parking lot
There that I assume they could
Oh, I see
I had the map up from earlier
Of course, good, yeah
God, they could keep going
That is wild
If anything were to come
Here, if we were to get anything
In Disneyland forward
What would be your pick?
It'd have to be Frozen
It's just so nice
Even if they did like a little
Pleasant Rapunzel
There's a free ticket that just
Was off in the corner somewhere
Because you know, the ride ending abruptly
It's like, okay, whatever, they only have so much money
They only have so much space
It's like, okay, cut off a couple scenes from this ride
It's not a big deal
But that's actually
What is weird is there's not really any villains
Either, there's no Mother Gothel
In the
Tangled ride
And then really you only see a quick video clip
Of the bad guy from Frozen
It's kind of an animatronic
No Hook?
Yeah, Hook, well that's the only exception
Hook is on the
His funny pirate dudes
So I guess maybe just bring the Rapunzel
In the tower
That would be a priority over the ride
It's so cool
So you could do that
And late at night too, when the park is emptying out
And it's closing, you just can hear her
Kind of gently singing off in the distance
It's so nice
This is spectacular
It's exciting
To hear that they're doing stuff
Of this caliber
And you know
God willing we get
Stuff of this high quality
Over there
And if there's a Tinkerbell in there too
Then nobody complains
What if it's just Tinkerbell land and Pan isn't anywhere to be found
Hell yeah
1000%
Very Tinkerbell's busy land
And then it's just Tinkerbell land
And Peter Pan is nowhere to be found
I think we have fixed everything
She can fly, you can do almost all the same story
And Pan isn't even involved there
And Tee Hollows
Still hanging out in Disneyland
That's true, yeah
So there's precedent
Great, great, well that's the idea
Also really quick, if anybody put on
This episode
In confusion and you're a little disappointed
I guess you've realized by now this was not an episode
About the Fantasy Springs casino
Outside of Palm Springs
So apologies, we will try
We will make that a separate episode
But since it's relevant right now, you should know
That Saturday, September 28th, the Special Events Center
Will be hosting former eagle Don Felder
Whoa, Felder
Felder, they got Felder
How'd they pull that off
I don't know, it's the hardest booking
In the showbiz
But they got Felder, so if that
Fantasy Springs is closer to you than Tokyo
Keep in mind the Felder expansion
Is coming for one night only
And that's not at a sphere of any kind
I don't think it's a regular theater
It's at the lead of the flattest named place
I was like, that can't be right, it's called the Special Events Center
This is unimaginative
Not Disney level naming
Oh, and just to payoff guy
In the Sherlock Holmes universe
You can be Inspector Lestrade
Oh, thank you, there we go
The ally from Scotland Yard
In
The Sherlock Holmes 22nd century
It's Inspector Beth Lestrade
A direct descendant
Of the original
Inspector Lestrade
Just in time for the outro
To say guy
Inspector Lestrade Selga
You survived, but guessed the right
Really, thank you for bringing
This in-depth report
I'm jealous, I wish I could go
And it's awesome, you've got to do it pretty
Frequently
If you go to the gift shop, anything you'd like to plug
Okay, before I plug, Scott
I brought you a donut
I forgive you
What a twist
Wow
Uh oh, roast beef
I'm still cursed
Bologna on the donut too
Yeah, just
Guy Selga on Twitter and Instagram
And everything else
And then of course, touringplans.com
Where we help you save time and money in the theme parks
And report on all the latest Disney news
And yeah, thanks so much for having me
That was a lot of fun, really appreciate it
Yeah, of course, thanks for doing it
Thanks for coming from Buena Park
And of course, let's
Let's go
One more thing, you said you had the toy, what's the toy?
Yes, a couple years ago
They sold a Babu Frick, a life-size
Babu Frick in Galaxy's Edge
And he has a soft rubbery face
Because of course his mouth moves
Because he talks, so I'm going to just
Plant some nice big wet ones
Right on his little
I think we're all in pretty strong agreement
On Babu Frick in general
So it's nice to hear that it's a smoochable toy
I'm going to go to Jason at the very end
But first I will say, as for us
For three bonus episodes every month
Check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
Or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier
Club Three, you'll find all of that at
Patreon.com slash Podcast the Ride
Jason, who you smooching?
You know, I'm going to have to go with a classic
The Playmates, April O'Neil
Action figure in the yellow jumpsuit
All my hall passes
Are fictional cartoon characters
So continuing that streak
Her camera turned into a gun
And so she can protect you also
Yeah, she had a
Full ass gun
You can do like gunplay
Yeah, she
Is like Geraldo Rivera
When he was covering one of the Wars
In the Middle East, would not tell
The anchor back in America
If he was holding, if he had a
Gun on him or not
Ooh, is there a
Is there a Geraldo? I might be changing
My answer, any Geraldo action
Figures out there with real feel
Mustache tickle action
We know some people at Mattel
So maybe we can get this done
Ooh, yes please
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following us
On Twitter and Instagram
At Forever Dog Team
And liking our page on Facebook
Thanks for watching!