FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following half-live podcast may contain real feel action, ghost musks, and a slammin' conversation about the price of roller blades.
Slam into our San Diego Comic Con Report featuring our Street Sharks panel with Griffin Newman on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast hosted by three guys who are as tedious to listen to as a Comic Con Q&A. My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always is Jason Sheridan.
We got to marry those two things, those two levels of tedious.
Or we didn't do the Q&A, sorry, no.
I know, first tedious is not anything, and second we didn't do a Q&A, but yeah.
I forgot.
You're only down two in the first sentence.
Yeah, alright, I'll show myself out. Mike, I rode with you, so I'll just sit in your car.
Alright, that's fine.
Give him the keys.
Give him the keys, yeah, let him have some AC.
Don't clash him.
The AC, though, drains the gas a little bit.
Oh, I'll just sit inside with the windows up.
Let's give him ten more sentences, and if there's any outbursts like that, then no AC.
Teediness is a cute word, though.
Yeah, I do like it.
I do like the word teediness.
Teediness?
Yeah, we're here.
It's a Polly Pocket kind of word.
It is a Polly Pocket kind of word. Yeah, that'll come into play. I guess we could talk a little bit about that real quick.
Well, we will. We're talking about Comic Con today.
We will?
It's related to a Polly Pocket, like, activation.
Oh, I forgot.
Or party at Comic Con.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I thought that's what you were referencing.
No, no. I forgot it because it looked very generic and not worth the struggle to get through the VIP barricade.
Right, and it wasn't. It was too hard.
But all of a sudden, you know, when you're walking around Comic Con in a hotel, you'll just see things going on.
And there was like an event happening with a bunch of people in dresses.
It felt very like people were excited about it.
And these were regular sized people, to be clear. None of them could fit in your pocket.
Fucking bullshit.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
I mean, unless, well, I guess, look, it's possible we could have gotten in there and then seen like one table, a VIP table with lots of tiny, tiny people like Polly Pocket.
Screaming in horror.
Yeah, that would have been awesome.
Yeah.
We have to live like this. We were downsized without our permission.
The only movie we're allowed to watch, too, is downsized.
That's the only way they know how to make those toys is to shrink people down.
That would be what a movie that would be.
Huh?
Well, that's what that could have been an angle for the Lena Dunham.
I was going to say that was what Lena was thinking when she was doing hers, but she's not doing it anymore.
Imagine the pressure that is on, like, OK, so Barbie made $2 billion, one of the biggest films of the decade culturally awards-wise and box office.
So now you go.
You take the toy movie. You go for it. Yeah, seems intimidating. Seems hard. So I understand. I get it.
She's going to lie low.
What if camping was any indication she would have knocked it out of the park?
Does anyone even remember what camping was when I said that word?
I know what you mean. I know what you mean. But if the name of the show wasn't camping and it was something else, I would I would.
Oh, yeah, yeah. If you said anything about it further, I would have gone, oh, yeah, you're right.
And you could have lied to me. I wouldn't have known.
This is another time where I remember nothing about the show, but I kind of remember the poster very visually in my head.
And let me ask, is it David Tennant and Jennifer Garner?
I don't think so.
The stars.
I'm trying to. There's a mush of faces in my head and I'm trying to.
How do we have to look up camping?
Clear it. Oh, wait. Oh, it is. Yeah, it is.
All right, he's got it.
Jason has redeemed himself.
Shows you what I know. Look, it was years ago.
Jason fell on his face.
You're right. He gets to stay.
Scott fell on his face. I'm back, baby.
Not knowing the cast of Camping.
I've also watched Camping.
Clearly you remember it better than I do.
Downsizing. Who am I?
I've watched Camping. I did watch the full first season of Young Pope.
You know, we've talked about, you love Young Pope.
I love Young Pope. You've talked a lot about Young Pope.
I never watched his second season.
Boy, this is, and this is one of those.
That's years and years ago.
That I somehow didn't retain the vast amount of Young Pope conversation.
I think first City Walk, Jason is really like Young Pope-pilled at that point.
That's an old show.
Yeah. That happened a long, that was 2016.
So he was already two years old talking about the Young Pope.
It was late then. We're talking about it more now.
That sounds about right.
We're Young Poping in 20, 20, 24.
He got really into Gangnam Style like three years after it came out.
Yeah.
No joke. He would just like opa Gangnam Style.
We're like Jason, that joke is very old at this point.
Yeah.
It didn't deter him at all. He was very excited to make it.
And he is, he's gone, he's gone easy on the Gangnam Style jokes lately.
But I'm thinking it might be time for a comeback.
It might be time to bring it back.
We never know when you least expect it.
So.
Well let's talk about some things that happened more recently.
Yes.
This very week in fact.
Just to sort of say the plan here.
A week ago today as this is being released we hosted a panel put together by Mattel
for the 30th anniversary of Street Sharks.
And we're going to play that full panel for you in the second half of this episode.
So that's where this is going.
But we figured we would flesh out the first half because it was only a 50 minute panel.
Those tight slots, the tight library slot we had.
So we figured we got a little bit of time here.
Let's talk about some other stuff that happened down at San Diego Comic Con 2024.
Yes.
As we were all down there. Griffin Newman down there as well.
And yeah, I don't know. I think some things were done.
Some activations were attended.
Yeah.
Some big dumb slides and stuff were gone on.
I don't know that. I don't know if anyone went on a big themed slide.
You did go on a big slide.
I went on a big slide, yeah.
You did. I didn't.
Well, I'm glad we're having this conversation because I missed this while I was there.
What was your big dumb slide?
It was at the Adult Swim Outdoor Pop-Up or whatever you would call it.
I was waiting to see AEW Wrestling.
The wrestlers were wrestling Adult Swim characters which is confusing sounding.
And it is. It was still confusing to watch it.
And confusing being.
And confusing doing I think as well.
It was human beings dressed as like Meatwad and then they were wrestling human AEW wrestlers.
And yeah, but they had a lot of different things.
There was shaved ice there. There were slides.
There were all sorts of fun to be had in this big inflatable kind of area.
I don't know if you saw it if you walked by there.
And it was by the back by the water, closer to the Joe's Crab Shack.
Okay, sure.
If that helps you geographically.
It helps me a little bit, but also I'm less Joe's Crab Shack in San Diego centric than you.
Which it seems like it is one of your primary beacons encouraging you to keep fighting on when times are tough.
Well, it is, but also we found a new spot.
We had a new spot that I think is going to definitely be a yearly tradition now.
Sally's Fish House?
We did not do Sally's Fish House, but we went to Mike Hess Brewery which is right on the water.
Oh yes, I just missed you for the second time.
But you and I went there in front of the Van Roos show.
And there's a thing called Hess Fest that happens in a couple of weeks with live music.
I don't think I'm going to make it to Hess Fest, but this is my new Comic-Con thing.
I think we're going to do at least one Mike Hess because it's right by the water.
You get good tacos, not too expensive.
View on the bottom, view on the top.
That's in the Seaport Village area, which is a lot of the lure for me going down.
I've done a trip that was mainly about Seaport Village without even a Comic-Con going on.
You might say that I spent far more time in Seaport Village than I did on the floor of Comic-Con,
in which I spent zero minutes.
I would say that.
I also think that maybe next year we do a full Seaport Village episode.
Maybe.
I was just extolling the virtues of it, but how interesting is that going to be?
Well, there are two Ben and Jerry's locations and there are two Mike Hess Breweries.
And they have different things you can get at each one.
But they are located about a six to seven minute walk apart from each other for some reason.
So all that confusion.
I'm not saying it has to be main feed.
I'm just saying there's theming there.
And there's, as we were saying, there's the carousel.
There's a carousel there.
That used to be in the Burbank Mall.
Yes.
And if the Burbank Mall is part of the history, we are alert.
Yep.
Is it something that happens a mile within where we all live?
And then that is right.
That is the front and center on Podcast The Ride's desk.
That's right.
Just to confirm, the Seaport Village is where the Cheesecake Factory is?
No.
That's the area that used to be a prison that is now, and I don't remember the name of it offhand,
but that is a converted prison that is now a shopping center that has a puesto
and that used to have something called Seasons 52 that is a pleasant generic brand that I like a lot.
I like that place too.
Yeah, Dearly Departed, right?
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Poor one out.
But yeah, I don't remember the name of that offhand.
You've never been to Seaport Village?
I don't think I have.
Oh, my God.
You would live there.
You would move into one of the little houses there.
That would be perfect.
Just one little kind of priest-sized little room with a cot.
Yeah, Young Pope style small house.
Well, hang on.
The Young Pope lives lavishly.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Young priest.
A poor pope.
You could live like a poor pope.
Well, I live like a resident of Sweet Haven.
It is kind of Sweet Haven.
It's a little bit like Sweet Haven, Jason.
How have we never been there together?
I don't know where it is.
Where is it?
It's kind of behind that Cheesecake Factory, and then it just extends out.
Near the Hyatt, which is kind of the northernmost hotel in the row of hotels by the convention center.
Oh, okay.
You've been over there.
I'm sure you didn't realize you were in Seaport Village though.
That's possible, yeah.
It's a cute little town.
It's very cute.
Though I think it's threatened to be taken away.
I think that's on the shopping block.
It's that thing where they want to replace something that's little and fun and charming with a bunch of boring apartments and garbage.
Yeah.
Well, hopefully not.
If there's something that has a little bit of charm to it, we've got to get a sweet green in there as soon as possible.
Yeah.
Please, no.
Seaport Village.
Keep San Diego, not weird, but what?
Charming.
Little.
But yeah, so I spent a lot of time in Seaport Village too, but I also spent a lot of time on the Comic-Con floor.
If you've never been to Comic-Con, it isn't just walking endless amounts of miles on a show floor with a bunch of crowds and looking through comic bins and seeing stuff and being bumped into.
It's not just that.
I can attest it's possible for it to be literally none of that.
It can be almost literally none of that.
Absolutely zero.
But there are, obviously, there are panels.
You hear people talk, varying degrees of excitement, depending on what the panel is.
To me, Comic-Con isn't necessarily about excitement as much as it is about feeling comfortable, feeling like when I was a kid and I would walk and see Walter Koenig talk at the Chicago Comic-Con and you'd sit down and it was so boring, but I was so excited to see Chekhov from Star Trek.
You're chasing a boring chat with Walter Koenig.
Yeah, there's something mundane about it.
I was talking to Griffin about this too.
There's something so nice and mundane, because even though you have your Hall H and Robert Downey Jr.'s there and that is produced and they've gone over what the copy of that is and what everybody has to say, everything else is so not scripted and feels so boring and human to me, including things with celebrities or Q&As and stuff.
Sure.
And I am chasing kind of that sort of like Saturday afternoon vibe where you're sitting and listening to Walter Koenig spin a tale of shooting Star Trek IV or something.
I didn't see him this time, but I'm just remembering being a kid and listening to him tell a story he's no doubt told a hundred, a thousand times at these conventions.
This kind of helps me to understand it.
I mean, it's not my deal, but I see the charm.
I see the Seaport Village in what you're describing.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think that's a big draw of it.
Jason and I have been in many of these panels where a comic book writer will try to make jokes and the audience doesn't like it and it's a little uncomfortable.
He didn't workshop any of this, but now he's in front of a crowd and he does something cool and he's finally getting a chance to see human beings that might actually know his work or whatever.
And he's like eating shit.
And it's great.
It's really fun to watch rooms that are excessively easy to bomb.
Yeah.
Worst environments for a joke going over.
Right. And it's like it's and especially if it's been a couple of days in the con, everyone's tired.
Everyone's a little hot, depending on how long they've been outside.
For how they may not have gotten into their first choice panel.
Right. This could be a second choice if the first one was crowded like or they could be watching it to have the seat for the next.
Yes, that happens a lot to half the crowd is not for you.
They're waiting for like a bigger star in the next panel.
So half your room is not full.
It's full of people not paying any attention.
Oh, that's right.
Like once I might have said this in the show once before, but I was part of some panel that was surprisingly packed of like people making Internet videos.
It was like people from cracked and I think Nick Mundy was on it with me and I'm like this room boy.
I guess some of these videos have more reach than I thought.
But it's funny.
They aren't really laughing, but maybe I don't know.
Maybe they're just quiet folks.
Quiet folks.
And then we finish and then like ladies and gentlemen, the cast of all that.
Kell Mitchell, Lori Beth, and they all go ape shit.
Yeah.
All right.
So we're opening for them.
Sorry.
Yeah.
But that said, we had a very nice turnout for our panel.
Sure, we did.
Oh, yeah.
Nice people before and after like.
No doubt.
Yeah.
Friends of the show.
Julia Presko is there.
Justin Michael is there.
And Mr. Morrow is there.
Nate was there.
Mr. Morrow showed up.
Which I didn't know was going to.
You gave us no indication that, or at least not me, any indication that was happening.
Well, I was texting with him a couple of weeks ago and I told him what we were doing.
So I hadn't known that, oh my God, he just landed and he's on his way.
So I knew he knew about it, but if we saw him, we saw him.
That's another fun thing about Comic-Con is that you run into people constantly.
People that you know personally or you haven't seen in a while.
Good friends.
People you watch on YouTube that review toys that you don't know and you just want to say hello to.
And you get as excited or more excited than any famous celebrity,
which is something Griffin and I would be like, oh my God, did you see what it is?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because you, at some point, you went to something that was a star-studded event in terms of toy people.
Yeah, yeah.
And then he showed me your text to him, which was inscrutable to me.
Right.
It was just kind of like, guess who's here?
James and Walter.
Whoa.
But if those were Imagineers, I would have.
Yeah, of course.
That's the thing.
Yeah, yeah, we share this.
The niche.
Yes, there's niche.
Not even niche.
It's just the hyper specificity of what you like and people.
I am engaged in so many of these YouTube channels with toy people that I have very strong opinions about them.
And it's almost like my reality show now to watch all of this stuff because I have sort of constructed narratives,
even like fan fiction for human beings on YouTube.
Scott and I at the bar one night got a crash course and some of the toy guys from Griffin.
Oh, yeah.
Anise and Justin.
Yes.
And they all watch and we all sort of go back and forth and talk about it.
And so we were all in contact of like, oh my God, did you see who it is?
It's Mad Hatter from the YouTube channel, Mad Hatter, who we watch.
And then it's, yeah, so that's what happens.
There's people I haven't seen in years that you just run into that's really fun.
And I'm trying to still even explain more of what Comic-Con is.
And in addition to all that, as I was saying with the Adult Swim, there's just temporary themed entertainment all over the city.
Pops up everywhere.
That often don't require the badge because it's promotional and they just they want people in there and learn about new properties coming down the pike.
Right.
And so like you go there and it's again it's crowded, but it's turned into a big temporary theme park kind of like there even were rides.
Like there was a Abbott Elementary carnival set up, which I didn't have a chance to do.
But there's a full carnival theme park set up right by the pier.
I passed by it while it was closed.
Griffin and I were trying to parse it.
The AvaFest.
AvaFest, yes.
And then but then that's an acronym.
We're like, what does that mean?
It's a very Abbott Festival.
I didn't know until I looked it up today.
Featuring an exclusive festival playlist created by Questlove.
Questlove dragged some files into a Spotify for AvaFest.
Okay.
I didn't know that either about AvaFest.
Yeah.
It's great.
It's one of the other.
I was just taking screenshots of like stuff that I didn't get to experience.
And I like I'm kicking myself.
I didn't get to go to Mr. Beast Labs slime spill.
I did not do that.
I saw a number of Mr. Beast things.
There was something on the show.
I didn't go to them.
I just saw the giant logo.
There was something on the show floor.
And then there was something like around the gas lamp quarter, which the gas lamp quarter is kind of like five blocks of CityWalk.
In some ways.
I mean, there's sugar in the gas lamp.
There is.
And there is any number of sports bars and taquerias.
There's an old.
No, it's funny.
You say it's like CityWalk, but those are things that are like useful.
Well, human beings might want to go to.
There's aspects that are CityWalk ask for sure.
A thing that yes, you're both correct.
Correct.
But I think I really like is when the generic sports bar or like a Mexican restaurant just slaps up a sticker that says like Biff Bam Pow or like a really shitty Spider-Man cardboard thing that's like bent and falling apart.
Like they just pull it out every year and just put it off.
I love generic comic con.
It's great.
It always makes me laugh.
Sometimes the restaurant goes to some sort of effort and sometimes they have a new menu printed in it as like comic con.
But then just Jason saying sometimes it's just like it's yeah.
Welcome to the superhero cafe.
And it's just like a person in their regular clothes with a cape.
Yeah.
And then just a couple.
Like party city Spider-Man decorations hanging out.
They're just like here.
Enjoy this slop.
You little piggies like Gotham massage parlor.
Right.
Wow.
It's not just a regular massage.
It's a chance to experience the kind of stress relief Batman might need.
That's right.
After a long day of crime fighting.
And that works.
Superman margarita.
This one is 16 ounces not 12 ounces.
Whoa.
And even though I laugh it like Jason laughs at it.
It still works on me.
A little piggy who likes Spider-Man.
It's cute.
That's what I want.
Give me that more of that slop.
And then yeah.
And then there's just as we alluded to earlier talked about earlier the Polly Pocket type thing.
Where you just wander into like parties or activations or weird events.
Scott you and I wandered and talked our way into a unofficial Ninja Turtle event where we ate free pizza and had free drinks was not planned.
Yeah.
It was just sort of like we happened upon it.
And then people were like yeah okay.
Like we just had to download an app in front of them and get at least to the screen that shows that you've set up a screen name for this app.
Yeah.
Clearly it worked this app that I definitely do have and I definitely definitely remember the name of.
I do remember the name of it but it's funnier if we don't say it.
And it was a very funny negotiation process of like well are you on the list.
No.
Well do you have the app.
Not yet.
Can we just download the app and come in.
OK well show me you have the app and you've signed up.
All right.
And then like 10 minutes later while this slow download speeds on the phones are like all right I think.
All right I think I got it.
OK here it is.
In there free pizza free drinks.
Good deal.
That's the comic comic magic.
Yeah.
That's that's you never know.
The bump into we had no plan and before you know it we are trans we were transported sort of to the world of the Ninja Turtles sort of.
Unofficial.
Yeah.
A license.
What we were transported to was a bunch of tables that had pizza boxes and we're like ooh pizza.
Oh no the pizza boxes have toys and merch in them.
Oh yeah.
Well that's free.
That's good but I can't eat any of this.
Oh good.
These other pizza boxes that look identical do have pizza in them.
It's a little confusing to parse.
When I saw Griffin once he did have a souvenir pizza box and in my head I was like are you going to try to get that back to New York.
I think so.
I do want to ask him like how does he do like does he pack an extra suitcase for Comic Con stuff.
Does he ship it.
I imagine because I like what I've gathered about Griffin is that he comes back from anywhere he goes with 12 big cumbersome souvenir glasses.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
He did it in Florida.
There was a plastic mugs all like like bashing into each other.
It's like yeah he just takes a garbage bag like like full of aluminum cans and just like just a big mug sack.
That's his personal item.
There was there's a FedEx in the Manchester Grand.
So I saw a bunch of people with their boxes just boxed up shipping all of their stuff home.
Wow.
So I don't know if he does that but that is an option if you go do one of these things.
That's true.
I think there's one in the convention center itself.
There is.
Yes.
So that's an option.
Yeah.
You want to box up your unlicensed Ninja Turtle like pizza cutter.
Now this was now you allude to something.
This was a little bit of a conflict while we were up there is that I think Griffin was more than happy to take all of the you know whatever materials were were up there and other others of us were as well.
And you made a firm declaration.
You opened the box and you said unlicensed and you refuse to have any of this stuff in your hand.
Yeah.
Well I just like it was trying to trick me.
It was trying to fool me with the logo that looks similar to the Turtles logo.
But if you look there was no Viacom licensing.
There's no actual Turtle characters on it.
It was just sort of stuff to make me think that the Turtles were involved when they weren't.
Wow.
The Turtles were not.
I smelled it.
And people didn't necessarily believe me right away.
But then they looked unlicensed.
Yeah.
Well yeah.
It's the kind of thing you would be right on.
Certainly.
Yeah.
That's my expertise is in noticing Turtle merchandise that's licensed not licensed.
But this and this is the kind of thing.
OK.
We've talked a lot on this show about how Jason comes to life when he is at Islands of Adventure.
Yes.
It is another Jason.
It is.
It's not Jason.
It's the Flash.
He is.
He's another man.
Just like.
Transform.
Yes.
That or if you're like talking about a place where you ate clams on the Jersey Shore in
1998.
These are the things that turn Jason into Mecca Jason.
Right.
And for Mike and you know some of that stuff you know theme parks do it for Mike as well.
But it does feel like Comic Con is particularly where you become Mega Mike.
A hundred percent.
I was I love Comic Con so much.
It is so I like it's it's again it's a big theme park that's like oftentimes shitty
in ways but oftentimes mundane.
And some of which is free.
Some of it is free.
Most theme parks.
I love to perform.
I like getting to go to Comic Con and do stuff which I've done here and there is always fun.
We get the I've said this before the name card that has my name on it.
I have it with me.
I don't know where it is.
You brought it.
I do have it.
I had it in there.
Did you just want to show off to us who also got them?
I know you guys have it too.
Yeah.
I saved my I was so excited to get a name card and discover all the text on the back
of the name card.
Yes.
But I guess it's Comic Con for me is the there's checking involved.
There's a lot of prep now.
I'm very good at doing Comic Con in general.
I think there's a lot of prep because I like to figure out what the stuff is I want to
do.
And then there are parties I try to get into beforehand that then sometimes it works.
Sometimes it does not.
And you got us into I got into a very fun party.
Yes.
That was a great got to go to an IG the IGN party which was fun.
And these parties are like hard to get into but also not in some way where it's like I
feel like when I first started going I was like well no way I'm getting into that thing
over there.
And it's like if you have the right email address you can kind of do it.
But yes I I the last day of Comic Con I walked twenty six thousand miles.
Twenty miles.
Steps I assume.
No no miles.
It might have been.
I don't know.
Again this is another mic.
But it is I don't know it's it's it's so much stimulation for my brain I think is what
it is because like I like to be checking I like to like fidget and stuff but it's like
I'm here I'm running here I'm running here I'm doing this.
There's four things I have to do tonight.
I have to see four different sets of people tonight.
Yeah.
And it's I'm certainly feeling like I'm older and I'm a little more tired during this.
That being said I did just as well as I always did.
And after a day of it.
Got it.
I still fucking got it.
I can still go hard.
We really we didn't do much on Sunday but that's because we were down there with my
daughter and we were staying with Lindsay's mom and stuff and we were doing some more
family stuff.
Boo snooze!
Why'd you do that?
You missed so many you could have met Stanley.
You could have met toy guy Stanley.
Instead of your daughter.
You were your daughter all the time.
Stanley is dead.
Not Stanley.
He's Stanley.
Stanley the toy guy.
All right fair enough.
Well I would like to meet Stanley from the office and don't go to the movie.
Stanley Clatch.
One of the biggest names in action figures.
Every year I almost I also start to question it because sometimes people will be like Comic
Con this and that and then I will go to Comic Con and I'll end and I'll be like I miss Comic
Con.
Bring it on next year.
Yeah.
And I feel that same way this year.
I had so much fun.
I you get into like every year Matt Cardona sees me at Comic Con he insults my shirt.
Makes fun of my shirt.
So there's traditions is what I'm saying that happens.
This year I was wearing you know that shirt I have like little oranges on it.
You ever seen me wear that?
Yeah I've seen you wear that number of times.
He was like that looks like you're looking for a lot of attention wearing that shirt.
And I was like what are you talking about?
And then I talked.
How dare somebody want attention the wrestler.
Right.
That's what I was saying to him.
What do you wear usually.
And then I turned to the person working at like the front who like checks your ID and
I go does your shirt look weird.
And the guy was like really nice young guy and he goes well I guess the oranges look
a little bit like balls.
I go and then I turn the card and I go is this what you meant.
I said do you mean that.
And he goes no that's not what I was talking about.
And I go why balls.
And then I went to what I started polling ever got in your head.
He did get in my head and we're going to throw this poll up and we're going to let the
listener decide if the shirt we took a photo.
What is the question for the shirt.
What is it.
Is the shirt weird for me to be wearing.
That's really what the question is for the listener.
Well look and that's that.
I don't know.
You might want to rephrase it because weird has become the key word of this election cycle.
Well and I don't think I look I don't think it's that kind of weird.
It's not that kind of.
Yeah no.
This is not a JD Vance situation.
No.
I don't think but you have to refresh my memory.
Well and you know what's funny you say weird and weird yes that weird has been used to
paint the Republican Party which is it's really good and seems like it's been very
effective in making just like an average person go.
These people are weird which is right is correct.
The low bar.
You're a basic thing to remind people weird is though too too soft of a word.
Let's be honest.
It is.
Yes.
But I see.
But I get this.
Yeah.
I see how it's like more tangible of a thing to go after than this is going to end the
world and democracy.
Yeah.
Yes.
Feel hyperbolic even if you believe it's true.
It's a little more palatable than like total fucking psycho.
Right.
And it's smart.
That's a smart.
It's they're good.
They're in the real world to use that.
That makes sense.
But what's funny is we talk about weird and I was talking to somebody I just met that
same night where my shirt had been insulted and I was explaining that and this is this
is I hate to drop so many names tonight but I was explaining how I'm responsible for Len
Testa and Matt Cardona becoming friends.
This is what I did.
And this person.
That's a hell of a name job.
And this person said and she meant this in the best possible way she goes oh she goes
your life is weird.
And I went my life is weird like that.
Yeah it is.
That is right.
And she meant it positively.
Well this is what this election is about is reclaiming the word.
I would make it a good thing and a fun thing.
Right.
No.
Well no.
Well let's wait till after the election.
Using it to assassinate them character wise and then.
Yeah.
This is a shirt I was wearing.
I think that's a little understated.
I don't agree with Cardona here.
Of course.
He's out of his mind.
Those aren't big oranges.
No they're not.
I bought one like that a year or two ago.
Like it just didn't fit so I returned it.
But I love the orange pattern.
Of course.
I mean people were supportive.
You're trying to look like Mike.
You like it that much.
You're trying to dress like your buddy Mike.
I think I was first.
Whoa.
Mike Mike when did you get this.
Over a year ago.
Here's a conflict I'm even more interested in.
But yeah but didn't you say two years.
A couple years.
I gotta look.
We gotta find out when.
I'll find.
That's a hell of an accusation.
But he never wore it.
No because it was like a tag.
So I wouldn't have seen it.
It doesn't count as a trend.
And you never heard that he had it.
You didn't hear about a shirt that Jason got.
You got jealous and then got a similar shirt.
The conversation that Jason and I have generally do involve well I got a shirt and then I had
to return it.
Like that is something we would talk about.
Oh I know.
I'm aware of the kind of conversations you have.
The long and short of it I'd love Len tested to get in the ring and break a light tube
over Cardona's back.
Well look I don't need Len to fight my battles for me all right.
I'm just saying if I have to do it.
All right if you can still go you can get in the GCW.
Well I could still do Comic Con.
I could still go to Comic Con.
You think you can go for a short little death match.
As long as it's short.
Okay.
As long as the death match is short.
You can still go and walk to different panels and boxes of comics.
Therefore I could do a death match.
Same thing.
Just a little.
Well just a little.
Yeah a little.
A little death match.
Yeah no.
Jane and I ran into Mike at about four o'clock on Friday afternoon after we had done the
panel.
We went through the kind of crowd like Gaslamp Quarter.
We did a lap on the convention floor.
That was kind of enough for both of us.
And we see Mike at the street corner outside the hotel and he goes you going to the Paramount
Lodge.
It's like no we're going to go take a nap.
Yeah I was on my way to the Paramount Lodge.
I also went to take a nap but I was a little you know in my heart I did I understand the
question.
I understand the desire to get people into the Paramount Lodge.
In fact I ask you now how was the Paramount Lodge?
The Paramount Lodge.
Jason what was that sigh about?
Well it's just what I heard already about the Paramount Lodge.
I'm a little disappointed and I'm glad I didn't make the effort.
Well there was no Frasier part of the lodge.
That was like the main thing luring us.
You're kidding.
Really?
That was some confusing part of the press release that I read and that was something
else.
We went up and asked where's Frasier?
Is Frasier here?
And Frasier was not there.
Yeah because you build it to us as you get to go to Frasier's bar.
Oh Shears?
No.
His new bar Mahoney's.
Mahoney's Tap Room.
His bar from the new show presumably in tribute to the actor who played his father.
John Mahoney yeah.
Yeah yeah.
So not even all right it's not Shears.
It's a bar that I don't know and then they don't even have it.
That was disappointing but pretty like and it was pretty small overall the lodge because
again all your favorite Paramount properties are under one roof we didn't say this.
Ninja Turtles.
Ghosts.
Evil.
Yeah that tattoo show that I can't think of the name of.
Ink Master?
Ink Master yes.
Old episodes of Unplugged.
It's all there.
And we all know it's Paramount.
Was there a Halo thing in the Paramount Lodge?
No.
Okay.
But.
That would have been weird because they had canceled the Halo TV show mere days before
despite saying like check out the Halo Target range in the Paramount Lodge.
Yeah so the Halo not there but you walk right into Tulsa King's Bread 2 Buck Saloon.
Bread.
Sorry.
Number 2.
Bread.
Bread 2 Buck Saloon.
Bread and not bread like the food bread but bread like you were breeding.
Yeah.
An animal.
Right.
Becomes a buck.
That's what they're conveying here.
An animal husbandry presumably but it does sound like some cuckoldry sort of stuff.
I don't know.
Bread 2 Cuck.
If it was.
The Bread 2 Cuck Saloon.
If there was any sort of cuckolding going on I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Sorry the RNC was in a different city a few weeks before Comic Con.
If Jason had heard about that some sort of Paramount cuckolding activation he would have
maybe not taken that nap but come with me.
That's what I think.
Well.
For which side of it.
In what way do you participate in the Bread 2 Cuck.
Observer.
I believe that's called a switch.
Yeah you have Frazier and Niles.
I know there's no Niles representation.
If there's no Niles representation on the show there certainly won't be in the lot.
Niles is out.
But Roz came back I think at the end of the season.
I don't know anything about that Jason.
I do have Paramount plus so I should get caught up.
There's another thing I think me and Andrew Grissom were talking about this.
Yeah and on the new Frazier his old pal, because he was back in Boston so his old friends show
up.
Oh you mean like from the bar?
No.
Roz.
Briefly.
So you don't get to see Clifford.
No.
No you don't.
What aren't you understanding about new Frazier?
Get your head out of your ass.
I actually am pretty excited Roz came back.
Like I loved Roz.
You were a big Roz kid.
I thought she was very funny.
I liked Roz fine.
I did too but I'd be excited about a full participation of Roz not like one episode
ends with Roz's shadow and then in the next one you get two minutes with Roz.
Sure.
Yeah.
I would lose my shit.
I would be like the Robert Downey Jr. on stage if I saw Niles came back unannounced.
Like if Dr. Doom took off his mask and it was Niles.
It was Niles?
It was David Hyde Pierce.
Oh man.
Yeah.
What if they were like who's playing Dr. Doom when it's David Hyde Pierce?
Same thing.
We needed the greatest actor in the world and then David Hyde Pierce showed up.
You couldn't argue with that.
That's a good candidate.
I think David Hyde Pierce actually would be a very good Dr. Doom.
I agree.
I don't know if the audience would give him the pop that he deserves like that.
He might have been more confused than anything, yes.
He's kind of a chameleon in recent years.
His hair and then beard.
Like for parts and stuff I feel like he's a very good character actor.
That's what you say after the mask is unveiled.
Nobody knows who it was.
And then some people kind of murmur, David Hyde Pierce?
Is that David Hyde?
And then you get on a mic.
Actually he's been a bit of a chameleon in recent years.
Does that help you out?
Now will you cheer?
Wonderful performer.
Very versatile.
Wait until you see how long his hair can grow.
And then you'll know.
Then you'll see.
I know you think he's just house, but he can also grow long hair.
He can do Shakespeare.
I had two free complimentary drinks at the Bread to Buck Saloon.
Damn.
I had the specialty, the Golden Driller and the General.
The General was good.
It was a little sweet, but good.
And the Golden Driller was awful.
I didn't like it at all.
I drank it, but I did not like it.
I did not like it at all.
They have a lot of...
There's a photo opportunity for the Paramount's If.
Yeah.
The movie If.
And there's a hopscotch sort of on the ground here.
You could sort of do the hopscotch from If.
Tired of doing your own crummy hopscotch on your own sidewalk or backyard.
Guess what?
Hopscotch.
That's so boring.
This hopscotch doesn't teach me about any movies.
And then, yes, my friend Anise and I took the photo op,
and we were there with one of our favorite characters from If.
Yeah, there he is.
So what's that character's name up there?
You know what?
It's funny.
I thought I knew the name, but I sent it to our friend Andrew Grissom,
and he just said, hey, that's one of the better characters in If.
So all I know about that character is that's one of the better characters.
It's Goobles.
You got your picture with Goobles.
Goobles?
You're supposed to goobles.
Oh, I know.
I think that's Goobles.
Oh, excuse me.
Yes, you're right.
Goobles.
We got free pizza in the Ninja Turtle area.
Wow, there's a lot of competing turtle bars.
That is licensed.
The pictures were there.
And then my favorite part of it is that the show Ghosts, which I don't know.
Jason, are you familiar with Ghosts?
I know of Ghosts.
Okay, nobody watches it.
Ghosts is not evil.
Ghosts is not evil, no.
But you go into a perfumery or something room, and there's all these different scents.
And they're like, you know, ghosts can't taste, but they can smell, which I didn't know.
And I'm excited about this lore, this ghost lore.
And so they had six different scents or seven scents that you could pick one,
and they would give you a little piece of paper that had the scent on it, and you could use the scent.
And I was like, this is interesting.
I've never seen this in one of these activations before comic.
That is unique, yeah.
So I got some.
I was like, I don't know anything about scents.
I just said, musk?
What about musk?
Do you have anything musk-related?
And they're like, oh, we do.
Yeah, absolutely.
And it's this one.
And I think I took a photo of it.
And that was one where I went, oh, that was very nice.
That was, I really.
So thumbs up on ghosts.
I'm feeling good.
You know, I'm looking at the Wikipedia ghost, too.
And apparently Betsy Sidaro is a recurring ghost cholera victim from the 18th century.
I believe Mary Holland also recurring in the upcoming season of Ghosts.
So Pat's guests of this show are here.
Yeah, she's Patience, a Puritan ghost.
All right.
Look out for Patience.
Patience.
And look out for Nancy, friends of the show, Patience and Nancy.
Lenape?
Legends?
I don't know what this is called.
But it's originally, it says, from the mind of a storyteller, fragrance description, sage,
cedarwood, amber, pepperoni spice.
And then, yeah, so they have all these different things.
And there was a very nicely themed room.
And that was the last thing we did, which was good.
Oh, the last thing we did was that I got a free poster for the movie If.
Great.
And I tried getting rid of it.
The rest of it, I would try to hand it to people.
And I almost left it behind.
I had like a quick bowl of salmon and something.
And so I could get a vegetable.
And there's broccoli in there.
And I left it on the seat.
And I was walking down the street.
And I hear, hey, hey, hey, excuse me.
And I go, what?
And I turn around.
And it's like a wait staff person going, hey, your poster?
Your If poster?
Ah, shit.
That would have been a perfect way to guilt free, get rid of the If poster.
I thought the broccoli diversion would work.
And then, yeah, so then we met up with friends that day.
That was really fun.
Saw a lot of different people.
Lindsay got to meet Mr. Morrow.
Yeah, I was going to say, that was part of the Mr. Morrow experience.
I watched this moment from across the table.
And Lindsay did like a full body shiver.
It was unreal.
It was like watching a child meet the real Easter bunny.
If one of the characters from If, who you've only imagined, shows up in your real life,
that was what Lindsay did to Mr. Morrow.
She was, she would have really liked to have gone with us to Orlando last October.
But, you know, she stayed behind, watched Baby.
But the one thing in that, during that trip that she was really jealous of,
it was not Guardians, it was not Velocicoaster.
It was that we got to meet Mr. Morrow.
That was the thing.
She was insanely, like, seething with jealousy over her.
Wow.
So I remember, because I had alluded, oh, I think Mr. Morrow will be at Comic Con.
Maybe we'll see him or something.
But I hadn't told, I hadn't reminded her about it.
She also really wanted to see the Bourne stuntacular.
And I'm like, Lindsay, actually none of us made it to that.
That's not true.
Griffin and I did.
We haven't talked about it at all.
What?
Yeah.
Didn't rush to do that episode.
That doesn't be, actually, well, I'll keep it, I don't know.
I think I liked it enough.
It's just sometimes, you know.
Well, we'll wait until I do it.
Sometimes you'd rather it be like insanely good or insanely bad to fuel that up.
But now I did get to do it.
I got instructions from Julius Stiles on how to move into the next room.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Is it Stiles?
Is it really Stiles?
Stiles, I guess that's a spoiler if you actually know.
Oh, man.
I got to get back down there.
That's your custom theme park celebrity appearance.
Yeah.
I want to go just to see the preview center and do stuntacular and get a bright blue Trolls
ice cream.
Are you going to try to fit in a trip for preview center before the park itself opens?
That park is opening soon.
That park is opening very soon.
We'll see.
I don't know.
The rumors continue that this thing is like March or something.
Yeah.
We're coming up quick.
Keeping an eye on what we're supposed to be there for and we'll see.
Getting a hotel, renting a scooter solely to do the preview center.
I think you should do it.
Jason, it does sound like you.
It does sound like I considered it.
You can do it tomorrow.
Jason, get your phone out and book a ticket.
Do it in front of us.
Tomorrow.
Let us know you did it.
I did it.
We had a funny moment the other day because we were talking about we were going to try
to go back east and see my family in the fall.
No.
Orlando.
No, no, no.
Orlando might come out with his family.
Boring.
You're seeing your family.
But then I was like, hey, Philadelphia to Orlando is really short.
We go to Universal for a couple of days.
That's true.
He's like, I thought you were going to say go see my family.
No.
Boring.
Sorry.
No one should see their family.
Your only family should be the Minions.
Augmented reality.
Little model.
My family are the imaginary family from If.
My extended family, the Island of Burke residence, the Isle of Burke.
Isle of Burke.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
But we'll be back.
We'll do Stuntacular.
If you don't go in a few days, which you should, we'll be back.
We'll be back sooner rather than later to Orlando.
But yeah, but you know what was great was getting to do a little live experience again,
which we hadn't gotten to do in a minute.
And this was a blast to do.
And as we sort of referred to, getting to go to Mattel and see behind the scenes of Mattel
and have their participation and top secret Street Shirts info.
We get into all that in the show.
Is there anything final to say about Comic-Con or do we throw to?
No, it's a lot.
Those were the highlights.
I'm already sort of, I'm already like trying to like, how do we make Comic-Con bigger and
better next year?
And I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't have an answer yet, but I'm working on it.
I'm thinking about it.
Yeah.
Well, it requires a big jump.
I got, I know.
Cause we would have liked to have done some other thing, but we wouldn't know we were
going until kind of recently.
But I was glad this came together and yeah, thanks everybody at Mattel and Griffin for
and you Mike for helping put it all together.
Uh, so I think we'll probably do some sort of little, little break here.
And then after that will be our, our panel, uh, audio is fine.
Like you said, Griffin's made a little blown out, but anything we want to warn anybody
about the first couple of minutes, I think it'll be, end up being fine.
First couple of minutes, it was a little too, it was turned up a little too much, but I'll
adjust that should be fine.
But then Griffin's a little blown up, but I think it's fine.
It's you'll, you'll be fine.
Worth posting anyway.
That's what happens when the panels is about to start and you're plugging in a zoom on
the floor.
That was wild.
Yeah.
The way the emails leading up to the, to the pan, I don't want to throw too much shade
at Comic-Con.
It's like, Oh yeah.
And this will be this.
And then they'll have a person there that'll record everything for you.
But if you want to bring a recorder and then I got there and it's like, Oh, so you're recording
the panel.
They're like, no way.
Not happening.
I'm not doing that.
And I'm like, Oh, okay.
Okay.
So I have a recorder and then what?
Well, I'll just go over the size.
They just plug it in.
I go, okay.
Plug it in over here, but you're in the back.
Why are you, why are you over here?
Why can't you look at it?
Well, no, no, no.
Over here.
Okay.
Uh, the panel starts in two minutes.
Great.
I'm doing so like I left two minutes into us talking to check and I turned it down a
little bit.
So there's also like, there are instructions on by the microphones of how to use the microphones
and we immediately sat down and I feel like we all started moving them and bending them
like, no, no.
We got this.
No.
Yeah.
The instructions made no sense.
I didn't know.
You're fascinated by what's behind the signs.
I gotta say.
Jason is about to refer to it for the third time in this episode.
I'm so excited.
That's a different sign.
No, no.
I'm not referring to the same sign.
That's a different sign.
There's Mike etiquette sign and then what's behind the name.
I'll post the behind the scenes of the signs because I took them all when I left.
Uh, okay.
But yeah.
Hey, look, it's better than if we recorded off a phone, right?
So that's better.
Yeah.
You'll hear that.
There's a lot to do and it'll take a quick break and then you will hear our panel put
together by Mattel with our pal Griffin Newman Street Sharks 30 years of Jawsome.
How is everybody doing?
Hello Comic Con.
What's happening?
Hello.
Hi.
My name's Mike.
Uh, this is, this reminds me of like, we're in like a Senate hearing or something where
I'm like, yes, Mr. Mr. Secretary, I did not help Dr. Piranoid.
I was no part of his experiments.
Welcome to Comic Con.
Please be aware that many members of your audience may be under 18 years of age.
Did you know there's stuff on the back of these?
I never knew that.
Oh, we did?
Wow.
Okay.
Hey.
Thank you.
Great.
Was that for all three or just one of us specifically?
It was Jason only, apparently.
Jason only.
Uh, you know, here's, here's something to calibrate here as we begin this.
Who here is aware of or listener to our podcast, Podcast The Ride?
It's pretty good.
Pretty good.
We're happy to hear that.
So thank you for coming out.
But let me ask another question.
Who here does no idea who we are and you are just big fans of the ultimate fin force known
as the street sharks.
Okay.
This is extremely helpful to calibrate.
I just want to say, uh, in terms of, uh, just balancing out everything and, you know, we're
in the library right now and there might, I don't, I don't want to end up with library
energy.
I actually need everybody to kick it up a notch because we're to celebrate 30 years
of Jawsome with the street sharks.
Let's do it.
Great.
But now, now not too loud, we are in a library, so we need to be considerate.
A little less Jawsome would be fine.
Uh, so yeah, look, I mean, if you don't know our show, it is usually about theme parks.
So why are we here talking about street sharks?
My theory is that somebody mumbled on the phone and misheard what was said.
They do a podcast about street sharks.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Let's get them.
Uh, but you know what?
It doesn't matter anyway, because the podcast, the ride you thought you knew is dead.
Let's remind you of the logo.
This is our normal logo, but it doesn't matter.
It's dead because we are now today, Jodcast the Bite.
That's right.
Yeah.
And in fact, let's reintroduce ourselves.
I'm Scrod Gardner.
That's Jawsome Sharkadin and there's, and that's Pike Carlschum.
Yeah.
And we're, we really, we wouldn't be street sharks.
We wouldn't be like book sharks.
We would be, well, there's, you know, there's like a street smarts and then there's book
smarts and I think we're more book smart than street smart.
Am I wrong?
I see.
Shark was a pun on smart.
Okay.
Yes.
Great.
We got it.
Wasn't it obvious?
I think, you know, I think that we're playing in the right area here because as we have
delved into 30 years of Jawsome with the street sharks, it does seem like puns are a big part
of this property.
So we will try to bust out as many of them as we can while we're here.
You know, something we do love on our show, regardless of where it comes from, is big
silly entertainment, especially from the 1990s, properties that aren't afraid to just be a
big dumb unbridled fun.
And that's what I think the street sharks are.
And that's why we're excited to be here and talk about the property, talk about the relaunch
of the toy.
And new figures or people aware of this that you can get new street sharks this year from
the fine people at Mattel.
And I do say the fine people at Mattel put this thing together and who gave us a tour
of the Mattel facilities.
That's one of the cool.
It's actually a place that is as cool as you might imagine it is.
Like if a kid had to draw their idea of what the Mattel factory is like, it actually matches.
There's a big Hot Wheels loop.
They get that every day.
I work on Zoom in my house.
That's much more boring.
And they do have a William Frawley head from a doll a few years ago.
I was very excited to see that.
We have limited time here, but there was a whole roll of Lucille ball heads in there.
I don't think we're spoiling anything by saying that.
I got very excited very quickly.
And then I went, oh my God, is that William Frawley's head sitting in a glass case?
And the answer was yes.
And then eventually they turned the lights off because they're like, we need to go home.
Please leave, sir.
I tried to break the glass, but it was tough glass.
If I had been a street shark, I could have done it.
If I was stronger.
We're not here for Frawley talk.
We are here to talk about the street sharks.
We're here to talk about how they fight.
We are going to delve into how they bite.
And time permitting, we will address how they kick some serious fin.
Are you guys ready for that?
Great.
As you may know, street sharks are the ultimate fin force.
The only big and buff half man, half shark action figures that empower kids with jawsome
force to bite and battle the world's most evil creatures.
What I have just read is from the official original Bible for street sharks.
For the toys, the advertisements and the series, the people at Mattel opened the shark vault
for us and therefore for you.
As dangerous as that may seem, they were willing to do it.
So we'll be reading snippets and getting some cool stuff out of that.
I hope before Biden leaves office, he declassifies the street sharks Bible.
Yeah, because we cannot.
Our names are watermarked all over it and we'll get into a lot of trouble if we share
it.
I just think, yeah.
He'd be a legend if he did that.
Freedom of Information Act should be in play here, I think, but anyway.
You know, there's three of us, but there's four street sharks.
And I feel like we aren't really matching right now.
We aren't matching and stacking up to the Bolton brothers, the group that became the
street sharks.
So I think we need to up our ranks here.
And that is why I'd like to introduce our fourth Bolton brother.
He is the voice of Orko on Masters of the Universe Revelation.
He has a podcast, Blank Check, and I hope he's actually like in the room and ready.
That's a question I have.
And if not, we'll just do this again.
But hopefully we'll find out.
Do we have with us the round mound of Pound?
Good.
Wow.
There he is.
The completer himself, Griffin Newman.
Hey.
Hello.
Fantastic to be here, boys.
Fantastic.
You have a better sense of the microphones, I think.
You're an expert at these things.
You've done plenty of these.
So I got to admire your microphone work.
Thank you.
Great look, also.
This was just, yeah.
Some people like to cosplay at the convention.
For me, it's all about comfort.
I'm just going to wear whatever's easiest to walk around.
I'm not really trying to show off for anybody, you know?
And so the necklace with the shark tooth, that's part of the comfort?
Oh, I guess.
You know what?
Actually, yeah.
You're right.
That is kind of funny for this panel.
You didn't even think about it.
That's just your day-to-day style.
That's a good walking outfit.
Yeah.
No, you're right.
That does line up pretty nicely.
Well, it gives you a weapon, too, if you're in a pinch.
I got two weapons right here.
Wow.
And a killer bite.
You're going to have to move one seat over.
I'm scared to be next to you now.
And that thing on your head is to protect your hair from getting too hot?
Correct.
Yes.
It's a hair coolant system.
I feel like when hair gets hot, the best thing to do is to wrap it in rubber.
Smart.
Just kind of cook your noggin.
Yeah.
Okay.
That makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
Welcome.
Thank you for joining us for the Street Sharks conversation, for taking a trip to Fission
City.
A symposium.
Let's say the first annual Street Sharks symposium.
Today, this is the Fission City Library.
Your previous familiarity with the genre, with the toys, what do you flash to when we
say Street Sharks?
I think the toys primarily were the thing.
I think the folks at Mattel sent you some of the new figures, right?
Indeed, we did.
We got some figures.
Some are down here, here.
Talk while I fish out some Sharks.
Oh yeah, go.
So yeah, no, we did.
We got some of the new figures.
They're very cool.
Wave one available now.
Wave two up for pre-order today.
Jason knows his talking points.
Jocking points.
What I believe they call the real feel rubber skin, that was a big appeal in the day was
you could walk down a Toys R Us aisle and the Street Sharks had the access.
You could feel them still in the packaging, you know?
You could touch.
They're open.
They came in cages.
They come in cages.
And there was enough room to reach through the cages.
Not enough for them to escape, thank God, but enough for us to real feel.
Yes, of course.
Right.
And a lot of the other anthropomorphic crime fighters at the time, the toys did not have
skin.
Yes.
So they've corrected that mistake with Street Sharks.
And Mike, you and I are both big action figure collectors and we always talk about flesh.
That is where a lot of toy companies fail, where they come short, is in approximating
flesh.
I am still waiting for any human character figures to have realistic human flesh.
Yes, of course.
I feel like that has not happened yet.
If Mattel wants to make a new William Frawley with realistic flesh, I would be very interested.
We'll feel Bill Frawley with light action.
Bill Frawley.
Yeah.
Well, let's bust him out.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the panel, Ripster.
Wow.
Look at that.
And this is, it's both an audio medium and also you guys are far, far away and I can't,
I guess, I mean, I guess we could pass it through the aisles for everyone to real feel,
but it's hard to not go straight there because you're absolutely right.
It is really addictive to touch these figures because like, yeah, like, you know, pants
are hard.
They're hard at the bottom.
But up here, just, oh, so gentle to the, it's really like, you cannot stop.
It's a sensual toy.
Yeah.
It is.
It is like, and they're like, the Street Sharks are jacked and very vascular.
So I'm not, I'm not a vascular man, but I would be interested to feel like somebody's
arm that was very vascular.
So this is the next best thing to doing that.
But Ripster does have like tasteful shoes and casual slacks.
So that's how he balances out his extreme muscles and large jaw.
I think you're getting at something here though, Mike, which as a child, you're fascinated
by super muscly men, but it is a social faux pas to go up and just touch them.
Yes.
And Street Sharks solved that problem.
You know now what veins feel like.
I finally know what veins feel like because of the Street Sharks.
Yes.
Yeah.
Very good point.
And that, yeah.
So the abs, they have so many abs.
Yeah.
Can I say also something that came out of our visit to Mattel was discussion of the,
of the bodies and the jacked nature of the Street Sharks and what we were told from people
who were there 30 years ago when the original toys were designed was that often specific
features would be based on the bodies of the people making them.
There was like, I think a gym was new to Mattel and everybody was going and getting ripped.
So I guess all of the Mattel designers in the 90s looked literally like this.
Well, you had to have those sculpting arms, you know?
Oh, that's true.
In a pre-digital age, yeah, you're required upper body strength.
But that's, they said that, that like, oh, check out this vein.
I got a new vein here.
Yeah.
Got to represent that on Jab.
So good for them.
We'll try to find old photos of what they looked like back then shirtless and release
those to you guys.
Yeah.
But he, okay, wait, Ripster like, Ripster spins, correct?
Like there we go.
Got a power punch.
Power punch.
Yeah.
And then let me, let me bring Jab out.
Jab is here as well.
A round of applause for Jab.
Thank you, Jab.
Great.
Jab, you kind of, you crank an arm and then out that hammerhead goes.
Pretty solid.
Yeah.
They all, they all do cool stuff.
You want to do some real feeling, by the way?
Let me pass them around.
I love to do some real feeling.
The other thing as like a puppet obsessed child myself, the fact that the street sharks
figures kind of doubled, you know, there was an animating factor here.
And they had giant puppets.
Well, we're talking about hand sharks, of course.
Yeah, hand sharks.
Yeah.
But Jason, you're getting ahead of yourself.
I think.
All right.
But yes, I, as a child and as a middle aged man, I enjoy making little toys talk and these
things can bite and talk and I can, you can do any voice you want.
Obviously they had voices in the cartoon.
A lot of them were like, like a lot of voice were like this on the old cartoon, but I could
do anything.
You could make it sound, you can make them sound like, you can make them sound like Jab
could sound like this in your own universe.
You could do anything you want.
And now that yes, I have a daughter that's two years old and now I can really justify
making all these toys talk and not doing it to the wall.
Yes.
Like I was doing two years before.
So yeah, that's, it is very cool.
Well, this, I think what's cool about this line is that they have, the sharks have maintained
their inherent ninetiesness.
They have not hid from the nineties in terms of their style, in terms of their attitude,
in terms of the box fonts, in terms of the, the pants.
And but what they, but what Mattel has done is up the degree of articulation to what we
now expect and demand out of our action figures.
So the, so the puppeting is so much more fluid and, and, and their battle modes are that
much tougher.
Yeah.
I really think like the street sharks is like the pinnacle of nineties everything in my
mind.
Cause like, obviously there were other anthropomorphic animal teams, but everything is just so aggressive
in nineties.
And in a lot of ways they're the face of the nineties to me, just as far as the decade
American culture in the nineties is the street shark.
So if you see some CNN special about the nineties and it's the face of Bill Clinton or Bill
Gates or something, don't trust it.
It should be Big Slam-oo.
It should be.
I would hope, yeah, that there would be a talking head, hopefully me on one of those
specials where they're talking about like the Monica Lewinsky scandal or something.
And I'm like, yes, but you understand, uh, Ripster's pants really for me to find the
nineties.
And you drive every question back to that, like, well, the nineties is when they first
cloned a sheep.
Can you answer some questions?
Why don't you talk about Dolly?
And your answer is Dolly was gene slammed in Scotland in the late nineties and Dolly
didn't wear paint.
Like she didn't wear pants.
She didn't roller blade roller blades.
Yeah.
Dolly could have been cooler.
So we'll not give her the time of day that you raised an important point, Jason, which
is the technology that allows the four human Bolton brothers to become the street sharks
is called gene slamming.
Yes.
And here, this is a picture.
I took a little screenshot of the cartoon.
These are the Bolton brothers being gene slammed right before.
Yes.
Just before slam.
It's a pre slam shot.
I think I love, I mean, talking about the essential ninetiesness, Mike, the Bolton brothers
kind of represent the four social archetypes of the nineties, football quarterback, roller
blader, slacker, and normal guy.
They are all, here's what I also, I was like, they are all pretty ripped before too.
So it's like sometimes like it's, you know, Captain America got ripped because he took
the super soldier serum, but like these guys were doing well before and then they just
got, they got even weller after the gene slamming.
I think there's a core underlying theme of body positivity to the street sharks universe.
As long as you're ripped as hell, you should feel proud of the way you look.
That's the only thing that matters.
And you can be ripped inside in your heart and your mind.
But also if you have the vascular system, it doesn't hurt.
But I feel like they are transformed, their genes slammed against their will, right?
Yes.
And we've seen so many narratives where people are transformed and mutated and they immediately
go through the arc of I'm hideous, I'm a monster.
I have to learn to love myself.
I live in the shadows.
Even Spider-Man, right?
Yes.
He's like, Oh God, I'm a freak.
He doesn't look any different.
He has a glow up.
He loses the glasses.
Street sharks have a three second acceptance arc.
You watch the pilot.
You just watch the pilot so you can affirm this.
Yes.
They transform.
Then they all pass around a hand mirror and each take a look at themselves and the first
balloon brother goes, Whoa.
And the second one goes, Hey, I kind of like it.
And they're immediately on board.
Wow.
They're just taken to the streets.
They're ready to be the sharks.
Which as a kid is what I want.
I don't want all that boring stuff where they deal with emotions.
Oh yeah.
Straight to loving it.
Straight to kicking fin.
They're jacked.
They can eat all items and they live underneath the comic book store.
My dream.
All of my dreams.
Yeah, it is so quick.
Every version of this, other than Street Sharks, has full arcs of a character like, Should
I go back?
I don't know.
Beast from X-Men.
What's the cost of looking like this?
I'm like, yeah, Street Sharks are just like, Hell yeah, let's go wreck some crap.
No cost, zero cost.
Could I get, just in case we don't know the names, John, we have Coop Bolton.
We have Clint Bolton.
We have Robert Bolton Jr.
And then Ripster is John Bolton, who is not former defense secretary, John Bolton.
Just in case you want to know, he had nothing to do with each other.
This guy worked in a lot of, he worked in the Reagan administration, but yeah, he is
not a shark currently.
He was never a shark, as far as I know, but yeah, these are the four iconic brothers.
I will say this, I would love, in the new Street Sharks line, to have the brothers pre-transformation.
I know maybe, most people think of sharks when they think of these characters, but I
want the guys to.
You want the street guys.
I want the street guys, yes.
Do you want them lying down, being horrified by the needles that are coming for them?
I would like the option to display them like this, but I don't need it to be, they don't
need to be stuck to the, whatever, the slabs or whatever.
I want the option, every couple months I change out my displays for my toys, and I would like
the option.
I would also like the display so I could put other toys in, other toys could be gene slammed.
I have a couple Steven Tyler from Aerosmith Toys, and I would love to see what a pre-gene
slammed Steven Tyler looks like.
Wait, you're saying that he currently is post-gene slam?
I mean that, it does explain a lot.
Yeah, well, it makes sense to me.
The ability to spin around with a scarf.
In a lot of ways, Aerosmith Steven Tyler is a superhero to me, and he has special powers
to rock an entire audience so thoroughly.
There is the character Rox, R-O-X, gets gene slammed, he's a rock and roller.
That's true.
If I could have Rox displayed on my shelf with Steven Tyler, and they were sort of doing
a duet or something on the mic, you know like when they share the mic and they can kind
of like go back to back.
If I could have Rox and Steven Tyler.
Like Gwyneth Paltrow and Don Johnson in duets.
A perfect reference.
A perfect reference for all you toy heads.
No more relatable time when two singers go back to back than the film duet.
Duet.
Jason really just playing to the Comic Con crowd trying to get that cheap pop on duets.
Duet nation.
There's too many duets cosplays here to even point out.
Jason, are you going to the duets reunion panel in Hall H later tonight?
I got shut out.
Oh yeah, there's a lottery and you get it.
I missed the pre-order on the toys too.
I'm going to have to go to the panel for sliding doors because I got shut out of duets.
The rumor is that Giamatti is going to come out at the duets panel and announce duets
retribution.
The legacyquel.
There's another rumor also that they're going to do a duets drone show over Petco later.
It's ten minutes and it'll tease the future of the franchise.
It's too exciting though.
Ships will crash.
Big drone duets.
So yeah, I want to have duets figures for sure, the movie duets, and I want to have
duets with all the various franchise figures I have.
We give some love to two of the post-Jean Slammed sharks I'm talking about, to Ripster
and Jab.
They are part of wave one, which are currently available from Mattel.
Let's talk about some of these wave two characters that are available for pre-order.
The other half of the team, Streaks, Streaks with an X.
Do you have a Streaks available?
That's the rollerblading?
Great.
Yes.
Wow.
Yeah, indeed.
Everybody take it in.
There's a tremendous amount going on.
This is one of those, Mike, you're going to have to say the technical term for it, but
he's got multiple sets of hands.
That's something you like.
I do like multiple sets of hands.
I have six sewing kits full of hands at home for all the different figures.
Anyone who collects figures knows what I'm talking about.
There are heads, there are hands, sometimes there are half heads if they just go with
the mouth.
I think the turtles, you can take the top of their heads off and the bottom.
I do look like a mad scientist in a lot of ways because I can make some abominations.
I was going to say, so far, yeah, you have a box full of hands and you wish that toys
felt like human flesh.
I was going to say in a different context.
The phrase, I have boxes of hands at home sounds like a confession.
It is.
Yes.
Jason, do you like this?
Do you want to talk about this guy a lot?
Streaks was my guy in the original one because he had roller blades and I was a very short,
a very chubby child.
I'm not the perfect specimen of health like I am now, but thank you.
That's what he was fishing for, he told us.
I had no center of balance so I lived vicariously through streaks and his roller blades.
I also thought, oh, roller blades, what do those cost?
This is a thing that comes up on the podcast a lot.
I can't have those.
Those must cost a million dollars.
I looked up the other day on Amazon and you can get an adult pair of roller blades for
$40 or $50.
I didn't sense a surprise from the audience in the price of roller blades.
I don't know.
It's pretty established.
He also had big claws and claws were also very big in the 90s, so that was very cool.
Those you can't just get on Amazon.
No, you can't.
You've got to grow on yourself.
I've always been a nail biter, so they're not really growing out myself.
That's an option for you.
Did you think as a kid that the roller blades had a motor in them to make them go independently
of when you would push off?
Why did you think they were so expensive, I guess what I'm saying?
I don't know.
I just didn't know anything about that.
I didn't know anything about roller.
We went roller skating at the roller rink once or twice for birthday parties.
Right, but there were traditional roller skates.
Yeah, yeah.
I was just like, if I put those on, I am going to get injured immediately.
I thought roller blades were futuristic technology, definitely when I was a kid.
I felt like, oh, wow, we are really advancing technologically as a species.
I think because of the blades or whatever you call the wheels, they were neon colors.
And it didn't seem right that you could do that on just one thin, whatever you call it,
thin line of wheels.
It seemed morally right.
It seemed like you were playing God.
Yeah, you were spitting in the face of God when you would roller blade,
because this didn't seem like it made sense from a physical standpoint.
Can I say in the actual description of the premise of the series,
this is from the Shark Vault, from the Bible,
it does talk about the villain of the show,
and how one brilliant genetic engineer chose to play God,
seeking to tailor humanity to his idea of perfection,
which involves sharks, I guess.
Oh, sharks and squids and whales.
Lobsters, yeah.
Lobsters.
Yeah, a lot of them in there.
This is a doctor paradigm we are talking about.
Well, you got two names here, right?
This is the rare, sometimes the hero or the villain post-transformation has an exciting name,
and before, it's boring.
But his before is Dr. Luther Paradigm.
We're already set in terms of villainy from the get-go,
but he ups it and becomes Dr. Piranoid.
Yeah.
Is there a Piranoid in there?
Is there any mode of Piranoid?
You could just put up John Bolton in his place, if you want,
and he's got kind of Bolton vibes.
Villainy-wise.
There he is.
But as you said, often there's this sort of a villainous transformation.
They're scarred, they're hideous beyond belief, they take on a new persona,
they change their name.
The thing I love, cold open, just the opening shot of the Street Sharks pilot
is Dr. Paradigm sitting behind a monitor, jean-slamming,
wearing a leather duster, shaved head, and a bolted metal eye patch.
And you're like, this is his before look.
This is when he's just a guy clocking in to work at the lab,
doing normal scientific experiments, kidnapping people's dads and children.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Like, 90s-wise, I'm like, this is the ultimate version of the genre,
because yeah, it's like, Dr. Paradigm is enough.
Yes.
He is enough, but no, no, they're going to put a hat on a hat,
as they say here, and make it even more extreme.
He didn't feel like he was enough.
Yeah.
That should get an Awe, too, yeah.
Can I read something else from the Bible that I like a lot?
This section is called The Quest.
The Street Sharks are heroes by instinct.
They did not set out to become modern-day Robin Hoods.
But then you have to see what I'm seeing or just visualize it,
because where it says Robin Hoods, they fit in parentheses in an F,
thus making it Rob Finn Hoods.
Yeah.
They committed to the punch.
On message.
They still use documents only.
They still were punning it up.
Very impressive.
Let's look at some of the vintage toys real quick.
Can we give a little shout to, we have missed one of the big ones,
maybe the biggest one, Big Slam-oo.
Let's see a Big Slam-oo.
There he is.
Wow, yes.
Hard to say who's the most 90s.
He's very 90s.
I mean, he's got his athletic wristbands.
And he keeps his football pants on.
Is that the term?
Football pants?
We wouldn't know.
Can I real quick, my dad just listened to one of our episodes
where we were trying to figure out baseball rules.
He was so upset with us.
He was like, I listened to the episode of Sky Dome,
and I go, oh yeah, what do we say?
And he goes, the sports talk.
Oh man, come on.
I go, oh yeah, I don't know.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'll get around to understanding the infield fly rules.
That's what it was.
Maybe we're right by Petco Park.
Maybe I'll get it there.
You think there's a guy outside that'll just explain the rules of baseball to you?
Rules, yes, rules.
Booklets are rules.
Or it's on the plaque of a statue or something.
Maybe just the entire rule.
I don't know why your dad was surprised.
Does he not remember the 18 years of raising you?
It's been a while.
He forgot.
Thought he liked sports.
Yeah, okay, so Slam-oo, and this is the best name for sure,
and it reclaims the naming mechanism S-amoo from a San Diego institution
that does some unsavory things.
So then we need Slam-oo to allow this cool naming structure
to be with us today.
Thank you, Big Slam-oo, for liberating the rhyme amoo.
Yes, thank you.
Amoo.
We could argue in a certain way the entire idea of street sharks as a property
is standing in opposition to that San Diego landmark,
and that the street sharks are not only not held in captivity,
they roam the streets freely.
Wow, yes.
Their cages are easily pliable.
They're just packaging.
They're collectable packaging.
That's all the cages are.
Yeah, it's just a tiny, tiny apartment is what it is,
and they can come and go as they please.
Yeah, every street shark comes with a modest studio apartment
just in case you can't visualize.
Now, that is also a place that I would like.
If I could get the street shark's apartment and see where they sleep,
I would want that, like their big shark bed.
Yes.
But you don't want it to be like a cool lair?
You want it to be little boxy apartments?
I would like the option to have a small studio apartment
and a cool Batcave-style lair.
Now, not to shark-splain.
I was jumping around watching a handful of different episodes last night.
I don't know if this is kept as canon across the entire series,
but there was an episode I watched last night where they mentioned
that they don't sleep because they're half sharks,
that in fact the street sharks must be moving at all times.
So they might not have beds.
Wow, it sounds like they don't have beds.
Or they do.
The beds are just for jumping on.
All right, bedtime.
At the very least, they would have like a waterbed because it's the 90s
and they should have at least, yeah, right.
They could go inside.
Somebody take a note here.
Somebody from a tell.
They could go inside.
Somebody take a note here.
Somebody from a tell.
They could go inside the bed and go on top of the bed
if it's a special waterbed.
That's a cool idea.
Those fins are ripping through waterbeds.
Well, these are different waterbeds created by a mad scientist.
Yeah, you've never seen beds like this.
They're gene-slammed beds.
Gene-slammed beds, uh-huh.
He combined a bed with the ocean.
Yes.
Can rebuild themselves.
That's cool.
Yeah.
All right, a waterbed that can rebuild itself.
Get on that Mattel.
And get on creating the book sharks, characters based on The Four of Us.
The book sharks?
Yeah, that was said, I think, while you were getting ready.
It was a joke in the beginning that went really well.
So Mike is bringing it back around.
It's very clear.
It's called a callback.
Got it, got it, got it.
The only book I care about is the Street Sharks Bible that I was given access to,
which there's also a slam-oo thing.
Here's another thing that I like is when he's built to a pressure point,
that he will then bellow his battle cry of slam-oo jam-oo parentheses
or something even cooler, i.e. alternatives will be considered.
You know, Scott, just because there is a fixed time on this panel,
it might help us if we just started not saying the Street Sharks story Bible in full
and instead just said the Holy Bible.
They can carve a couple words out there.
Yes, the Bible.
The Bible.
We haven't said the most important thing from the C. Ray's Bible
is that an early iteration Streaks was called Blades.
And some of the early toys said Blades.
Some of the designers were like, I had a toy box that said Blades,
and then the cartoon called him Streaks.
So as you're walking around for the rest of the con,
find a stranger and let them know.
Accost them.
Gene-slam them with the knowledge of Streaks and Blades.
And maybe they'll do an exchange and they will tell you what the infield fly rule is.
Yeah, if anyone has access to a gene-slammed baseball
and I can learn more about the sacrifice fly rules, that would be great.
Do you want to show us some, because Mike, you found a bunch of photos of the retro toys.
Oh, yeah, the old figures, yeah.
I was on figurerealm.com.
I want to shout out figurerealm.com.
They have a pretty good archive of a lot of old figure lines.
So that's what a lot of these photos are from.
This, of course, is Ripster.
And these are definitely like, you know, these have been lovingly played with
because they're a little dirty.
Lovingly real filled.
Wow.
Oh, the attitude.
Yeah.
So much attitude here.
And that's Jason.
Whoa.
Jason referenced Rox earlier.
Rox got a round of applause just from people looking at him.
Just the appearance.
That's how you know he's a star.
Yeah, he's got it.
Can you imagine Rox jamming with Aerosmith?
Because I can.
He does have a Steven Tyler-esque mouth.
Yeah.
He has, a lot of rock stars have interesting mouths.
And Rox is no exception.
Rox's real name is Melvin Kresnik.
He needed a name slam.
Yeah, he needed a stage name.
And he accidentally digested contaminated popcorn and water
that was tainted with a gene-slamming chemical.
Well, we've all been there, right, folks?
So yeah, so this was Rox.
This was the toy of Benz,
who was kind of like a surfer guy who helped the sharks out.
He's their human friend and van driver primarily.
Yeah, and he had kind of like a tactical vest.
What would you even, how would you describe that?
That's like a fishing vest.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah, it was a fishing vest.
Tactical fishing vest.
Yeah, so he was a cool guy, I think.
Here's Jason's guy with his million dollar roller blades.
Because you've got to buy the pads, too.
And it really starts to add up.
It is interesting.
Pads, two million dollars.
A lot of the toys, it is interesting.
He didn't have crazy, he just had regular $40 roller blades on,
at least of the figure.
He seems like he didn't have some crazy,
technologically advanced roller blades.
That's where the street comes in.
He has tools accessible to us, the humans, on the streets.
Yes, they're every sharks.
Yes.
But then a big thing was, as we referenced earlier,
the hand shark, which is a bigger puppet
that you could put on your hand, make talk,
and I guess punch things, you could do that.
And this is, of course, a ripster.
And then they had here, this is, of course, slobster.
Slobster.
The character slobster.
Slobster is great.
Slobster I love because there's some great backstory here.
Obviously, all of these characters were slammed together
from human and fish DNA,
but in this case, they go into the specifics.
And we are told that slobster has DNA from Genghis Khan.
I don't know how this was kept and given to Dr. Paradigm.
He just has vials.
You see it at the beginning.
He's just got a shelf of vials with the world's worst leaders.
Well, and then that's what I could be up
because Genghis Khan starts you at a point like, okay, yes, fearsome,
killed many.
Okay.
Then the other one that they say is Colonel Thomas Blood.
Colonel Thomas Blood was a notorious rogue from the 1600s
who tried to steal the crown jewels and failed.
So guy who killed a million people,
sex with all these women, and then also a failed jewel thief.
That is what is in slobster.
And a lobster.
Don't forget the lobster.
You're absolutely right.
And I didn't forget Griffin and I have the receipts to back it up.
I made a little chart of how the DNA of slobster works
just so we could all get eyes on that.
Great.
This plus this, Khan plus Blood plus lobster equals slobster.
And that's your recipe you can take home to make your own slobster.
And slobster is, of course, one of the bad guys known as the seviants.
Combination sea and deviant.
Along with Slash, who's cool, that's a figure you can buy now.
This is deeper in the villain's rogues gallery.
This is, wait, what is it?
This is Shrimp Louie.
Shrimp Louie, not to be confused with Bubba Gump mascot Shrimp Louie.
Can we see the other Shrimp Louie?
Yes, yes.
And you decide, you can decide which is scarier.
Yes.
I will say this.
Shrimp Louie needs to hit the gym.
This is not a jacked anthropomorphic sea creature.
No, I also want to say you said decide which one is scarier.
I think if you ask the boy in this photo, he would say this Shrimp Louie is the scariest thing that's ever existed.
And that boy was not in that photo when we looked at it an hour ago, so we don't know what is going on.
Oh, God.
On to the slideshow.
So let me go real quick back to a couple more retro things.
Non-figures.
You could get a Street Sharks gift pack back in the day that had a zipped pouch, which I guess is not a fanny pack, but close.
You could have a little watch.
They sold the LCD watch here, which is cool.
Do we have LCD watches as kids?
Because I feel like this was a big kid thing for me.
Oh, yeah, big time.
Sure.
And then you could also get rings and shark tooth necklace, which is pretty cool, but it feels like it might get like hard to hold a shark's head on your hand all day if you were wearing that ring.
So not good as a wedding ring.
Right.
The proposal might not work out.
Do you think anyone has ever proposed with a Street Sharks ring?
Slash, does anyone have anything they want to say right now?
Oh, yeah.
The floor is open.
Yeah.
We'll give you the microphone.
So, yeah, I would say, too, I hope Street Sharks rings come back as well.
They're doing, Mondo, the company that makes a lot of like big 1-6 toys, and they're doing like some soft vinyl Street Sharks they just announced yesterday, too.
So I feel, and there's Hot Topic Street Sharks shirts, so I feel like a high-end ring company should license Street Sharks and start making Street Sharks engagement rings.
Like K Jewelers.
You want a K Jewelers X Street Sharks collab.
Oh, sorry, Griffin.
We're a Zales podcast.
I'm sorry?
So we're all about Zales.
That's on me.
Zales could license the Street Sharks, yeah.
Every kiss begins with jam!
Can I, I think it might be worth bringing up that, you know, this has been cool for us to do, but also intimidating because being people in a public-facing setting talking about Street Sharks figures and hyping up what's cool about them, these are some of the biggest shoes there could ever be to fill.
Because some of the world's great talents, one of the world's great talents.
The world's single greatest talent.
Let's just cut to it.
The world's most talented man did what we're doing years ago.
Do we have audio?
Let's find out.
It is not coming through.
Well, you know, it doesn't super matter.
You know what's really funny?
I'm actually realizing he's wearing something very similar to me in this video.
Whoa!
Just to say, yes, this is a young Vin Diesel, and he is doing promotion, he's like showing how the interactivity of the Street Sharks works, and he's wearing, wait oh my god, as I'm adding it up, it's a black leather vest, it's a shark-toothed necklace just like you, and then sort of a relative lack of hair.
Yeah.
That's really interesting.
He's got kind of like a strange Griffin Newman vibe going on.
Wow!
Sort of Griffin Newman before his time.
That's crazy.
And I guess he had like a, he had a permanent head cooling system installed.
He did.
Well, that's why he's a star.
You know, I've forgotten this footage.
He launches Jab's head at a normal man action figure.
So that's also an option, you know?
Yeah, for sure.
I was talking to some of the folks from Mattel about how crazy it was that there is, A, that he was a toy fair demonstrator, which was this job that was often done by like out-of-work actors in New York City.
Okay.
To show off the upcoming toys to the media and the big buyers for the store and whatever.
You very rarely find evidence that people who did that job went on to become major stars.
Sure.
And they were like, isn't that crazy that he started out like this and then became this whole different thing?
And I was arguing, no, I think this is still what he is.
I think he's the rare example of someone who was a toy fair demonstrator and went, I can ride this persona to the top of Hollywood.
Like Dr. Paradigm, it was all there from the beginning.
It was all there from the beginning.
Everything he needed, including the baldness.
He had it all figured out.
Yeah.
There's also, in this video, there's some of these alternate names that you refer to, Jason.
He's like, all right, and here we got Boomer.
Check out what Boomer could do.
And I'm wondering if there was a name switch after that or if it was just Vin Diesel not listening carefully.
Or he also knows them so well that maybe he has nicknames with them.
Yeah, that's what I call it.
That matters more.
You personalize it.
Okay.
So remember, it's Big Slam-oo.
Got it.
Boomer.
Good to go.
Isn't that what you said?
What else on our way?
We got five minutes here.
What have we missed?
The Comic-Con exclusive this year is very exciting because it's Ripster wearing a jacket.
Oh, yes.
Well, let's acknowledge he's a literal pool shark.
He's a literal pool shark.
Yes.
He's got the Q and the pool table and an explosion.
He does pretty regularly play pool in the cartoon.
Yeah, and he's wearing a jacket, which I asked the question at Mattel because I was like,
well, he's got a soft goods jacket on, right?
And then I realized I was trying to act cool.
I knew the terminology for toys.
But that is right.
I was correct.
And I was very excited to act like I knew the biz.
And you call that acting cool, you say?
For me.
This comes from an episode that I believe is titled A Shark Among Us, which I watched last night
and is about the street sharks and in particular, Ripper, trying to break open an underground network
of oral steroid sales to children.
They're all getting Ziploc bags of blue pills called Super Blues that are getting them as jacked as street sharks.
And the street sharks don't believe in that.
If you're going to gain muscle mass, you have to do it the honest way by getting jeans slammed.
Do not buy bootleg Prednisone from seedy sellers.
But so Ripper puts on a leather jacket and sunglasses and tries to just be like, hey, I'm a guy who loves steroids.
Where can I get some?
And everyone's like, what a cool, normal human man who needs pills.
Big blue human guy here.
Pay attention to the jacket and not the face between the ends of the jacket.
But this is basically his like, NARC disguise outfit.
He's a street NARC in a way.
That's actually a better name for what we would be as sharks.
Street NARC.
Officer, they're doing drugs over there.
Or sharks, when we say that.
And you're pointing at people who are drinking coffee.
They're drinking caffeine, officer.
It's a stimulant.
Enhanced tattling powers.
I think maybe there's time to address another thing that probably my favorite part of the Bible that we got to see.
And that is the list of rules, things we should know in proceeding with this property.
And rule number three, parlez-vous sharkies.
And then what you get is a dictionary of how the street sharks talk.
If you were going to write for them the kinds of things you should say rather than...
It looks like you've got some of these.
Yeah, I've got it too.
I'll try to do it in order and maybe we can pass it around a little bit.
A street shark would not say fantastic, he would say...
Fintastic, of course.
Very good.
A street shark would not call something an impossible task, they would call it...
A jaw-breaker.
Very good.
If somebody is not depressed, they are chummed out.
That got our third awe.
Panels and signings and travel arrangements is really chummed out dealing with Comic-Con.
I swear this week it's been jaw-breaker after jaw-breaker and it doesn't make me feel fantastic, it makes me chummed out.
It's also just nice to be up here on stage with friends just blowing bubbles.
Yes, very good. Blowing bubbles, which I will censor and say that's the official term for BSing.
Don't say, street sharks don't swear.
They blow bubbles.
Shut up is clam up.
Throw up is spout.
I have to shout out, just for fun is for the halibut.
And I like that a lot.
You were saying that before you read this, though, too.
Yeah, no, I didn't see the document and I was saying that.
Well, you know what? I think it's been a lot of fun to be here just for the halibut.
And isn't that the spirit of the property? Isn't it really? It's not about anything serious.
It's just a lot of silly fun. It's a property done for the halibut. Can we not agree on that?
Yes, we can.
I think it's a beautiful thing.
And I really hope that nobody, I don't think anyone will be leaving here chummed out after everything we've addressed here.
A reminder, wave one is available now. Wave two pre-orders are available.
The Street Sharks stuff on the Hot Topic website.
And I think with that, you survived. Podcast The Ride, Times Mattel, Times Street Sharks, Times Griffin Newman.
Thank you for being here, Griffin.
Times Vin Diesel.
Wow, Times Vin Diesel. Yes. Griffin Newman, I should say. Griffin Newman and Vin Diesel.
That worked out pretty cleanly. And thank you all for coming out here, making the trip to the library.
Thanks everybody at Mattel for putting this together. Kevin and Scott. We're Podcast The Ride.
We've got a picture on patreon.patreon.com slash podcast the ride. And hey, Finn's up, everybody.
Yeah, that works for this, too. Yay.
Forever. Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.