I'm a big bright shining star.
Park star.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
I was curious how you were going to do that after you said, what is Mark Wahlberg say
at the end of Boogie Nights?
And then I did it in the best possible way, the smoothest possible way.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a lot to take in.
Seamless, actually.
Scott Gardner is well here.
Yes, I could have done that with like a slick like audio trick.
I could have done it before.
I could have put it in later, but I didn't.
We did it live.
The live innovation, fuck it, we'll do it live is what you, is what you want.
I was wondering if you had an idea that I had, which I didn't really want to like make
a whole song or anything, but just thinking about Park Stars.
I've just been singing that phrase to myself over the Crosby, Stills and Nash song, Dark
Star.
That's funny because I was thinking of Baby I'm a Star by Prince from Purple Rain.
I also thought about Star is Born, some sort of Jackson Maine tie-in, which Jason would
have appreciated.
Oh, I'm a huge Jackson Maine fan.
Are you kidding?
We all would have peed our pants in solidarity.
Yeah, Rock Star, another Mark Wahlberg movie.
Rock, well no, Rock of Ages doesn't have star in it because I wanted to do a Stacey Jacks
reference, but.
Now you're just free associating words.
Yeah, now I'm just free associating.
All ages is a type of establishment you can have.
All state is an insurance.
State is a place that you live.
Spoken word, free association poetry that I'm doing here, which is what I do on this
show often.
That is sort of what I do.
It is?
Sometimes.
Well, I don't do it in that way, but.
You know, podcasting is like jazz, you know, free association, you got a torch wielding
mob comes to the door, boo, get him.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm upset too.
But yeah, so there were many.
There's a lot of things with star in the title.
We could have done any of them.
My choice.
My rhyme is all I'm saying.
That's why I thought of it.
The rest did not rhyme.
Oh, because of Dark.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, you're right.
It doesn't make it better, but.
I went with the dirty line or the dirty penis scene from the movie.
That's what I chose.
When are you imagining one of these little figurines, these are figurines of theme park
specific characters.
Are you imagining one of them with what for them would be a particularly large member
to buy at their proportions would be the Abe Lincoln one inch as opposed to, you know,
the four percent of.
Right.
Yeah, I was thinking of the Abe Lincoln one dropping his pants like at the end of Boogie
Nights and then saying that to him to like pump himself up.
You're a bright shining star.
But today.
OK, we're talking about Park stars.
Now, you may know we've spoken about this before on the show.
They were they introduced these things called Vinylmations in like 2008 and what Vinylmations
were were these little basically like they all had the same exact shape.
They were Mickey Mouse and then they would have artists paint things on them.
Oftentimes it was characters, but then sometimes it would be almost an abstraction or like
a ride thing.
And it was sort of the trend that I think was started in 2001 by Bear Bricks.
You've seen these Bear Bricks, very famous people oftentimes have very expensive Bear
Bricks.
I was going to say Kid Robot.
I think it was the first I.
Yeah.
L.A. toy company.
Basically, what Disney did was there was a trend of like art toys and many, many years
later they decided we should do that too, as is their style in general for anything
pop culture related us also and a little worse.
Yeah.
Bear Bricks are these things and they're all just like they have the shape of a bear and
then different artists like draw.
I don't know.
That's not the biggest photo in the world.
If you can see that.
OK.
But they're all like the same basic like plastic shape.
And then you can draw different characters on them.
There's a Garfield Bear Brick right here.
That's like a chrome Garfield that has been painted over this like bear shape.
That's very confusing.
How is he Garfield if he's chrome?
It is very confusing.
And would you believe that I have this in a box in my garage?
Melting.
I don't.
Yes, I know.
It's got to be a movement to move some of my toys outside of there.
I don't have any Bear Bricks open.
I don't even know that I intend to keep this.
This was just on sale many years ago.
And I think I was texting Griffin and he was like, you have to get that.
And I was like, I think I do have to get it.
I have to let that sit in a box in the garage.
They're the size of like a toddler.
They're giant.
This is giant.
And I was like, I don't have any room for this, but it's sitting in a box.
So I may sell it one day.
So Disney years later decided, okay, we better get in on this trend while it's hot.
Five, six, seven, eight, ten years later.
And then a couple years into doing Vinylmations, which I had a few of and I still have a couple,
they started doing something called Park Stars, which were different shapes.
And they would almost exclusively represent characters that you would find in the parks.
Park exclusive characters.
Not always there's a couple that aren't necessarily exclusive to the parks, but mostly things
you would see in the parks.
The dog with the key in its mouth, the redhead on Pirates, Rex from Star Tours.
Yeti.
Yeah.
Dynamite Goat.
From Big Thunder Mountain.
From Small World.
Yes.
For specific characters.
All the three hitchhiking ghosts.
And this is a dream for us, I think.
This is what we want the most possible, is the specificity of a character who you gotta
go to a place to meet and then to tribute that with the specific, because do we need
a Pluto?
Do we need a Cogsworth?
Do you need a Cogsworth?
Well, sure.
I have a Mrs. Potts at home that sits in the kitchen, I kinda like that, but you know what
I mean?
Like the specificity of, you only know this guy if you've been in this place and now there's
a little item of him.
It's the Funmeister.
It's from Pleasure Island.
Mr. Funmeister.
I got that one.
This is a rare line that I have a couple of, because I don't collect much at all, but it's
so up my alley, the theme park specificity.
And you love blind boxes, which is an important detail.
You have to roll the dice with your $15, $16.
Well, I don't because I buy them on eBay, I only get what I know I want.
Did you ever do, Mike, the blind version of these?
Well, I absolutely, so the first few waves, I think I've like, toward the end of the first,
they've done five waves of these and they stopped doing them in 2017, which is very
upsetting.
We'll have a call to action at the end of the show, as far as I see there's a, there's
at least a couple like change.org petitions to get Vinylmations going again.
And if we know anything from the last eight years or so, those work.
Work really well, especially when they're under 500 signatures.
Use your voice.
If we all raise our voices, maybe now we can overturn the opened Tiana ride.
Right, right.
So I think that's, yeah, toward the first wave is when I noticed them and started getting
them.
We did, Jason and I would go a lot to the parks together around this time.
And I think I was almost exclusively just doing buying a box, a couple of boxes when
I would go and see what you get.
Maybe sell one if it's a duplicate or we would trade, I forget.
Maybe we traded.
I don't know.
You get these in the park or in one of these downtown Disney sort of both, both.
You would get it at D Street, which is now the Disney home goods store, whatever that's
called.
But there used to be that hip edgy store at downtown Disney for the collectibles for the
sophisticated fan, not just your normal grandma sweatshirt.
This is vinylmation.
These are exclusive vinylmations.
These are different art prints.
That's where you're going is D Street.
And do they really want an edgy art scene, you know, burgeoning within downtown Disney?
I don't know.
You know, they're a little bit of stiff shirts.
I don't know if they were up for the edginess.
I don't think they were either because they closed it.
It was, I don't know how long it was open.
They closed that.
They closed House of Blues.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
It's too powerful.
They sanctioned great art at downtown Disney.
Yeah.
But you could get them, I'm trying to remember, you could get them in that first gift shop
to the right in California Adventure.
And I think there was a place in Disneyland to get it as well.
But as it went on, I was like, I like all of these.
Why don't I just go on Shop Disney or whatever it was called at the time and buy the box?
I got the 10% off or I got a 10, well, you get 10% off in the park.
But then I would have like a coupon code or something for Shop Disney.
And I just buy the box because the box had one per in the box.
So it wasn't like, I mean, it was still expensive, but it was like, why am I going to go and
just like kill myself buying 50 of these to get the whole set and may as well just buy
the box.
So the last couple I bought the entire box and then I think maybe I sold a couple if
I didn't want them.
But I wanted most of them because they're pretty good.
Did you end up with repeats very often?
Not when I bought the box.
The box didn't really have any repeat.
The box was just that the amount that they had for per line.
Yeah, if you buy the case, you would get one of the basically occasionally a chase.
Early on, I'm sure I did get one or two.
I remember Jason and I were on the hunt for the orange bird early on in one of the first
waves. And I pulled it.
You pulled it because we were doing a whole show and I was trying to shake like trying
to feel the weight because these blind boxes and blind bags, if you've ever played with
any any version of these toys, when you're in the store, it's kind of fun to be like,
OK, I want this one.
And it's a bigger toy.
So then you start weighing them in your hands.
Then you start doing a little shake.
Sometimes they have blind bags that are more like just actually a bag, not a box.
Yeah, with the bag, you can kind of feel it.
So the bag you're trying to feel, you're trying to see, oh, is this the one I want?
And they try to throw you off.
They try to put a little cardboard in if it's like a there's these like bag clips I buy
now that have like Ninja Turtles on them.
But they try to put a little like piece of cardboard so you can't feel, but you can kind
of feel still if you really have the ambition for it.
Tricky cardboard. Yeah.
So we were trying, I think we were at Downtown Disney.
We were at Downtown Disney.
And we were doing, Jason and I were doing this.
We were doing the shake.
We were shaking and weighing. This is God knows 2012.
Doing your rattles.
Doing the rattles.
And I swore I had it because it felt heavier.
And Mike's where he at it.
And I said I could feel it.
He said he could feel it.
And he was right.
Because he did have it.
And I bought one.
I think I bought one and I opened it up as the Orange Bird.
Wow.
And I opened it up and it was the dinosaur from Dinosaur.
Waa waa.
I don't know. That's kind of good.
I like that.
I've seen a picture of that one.
I mean, I like it, too.
I like it, too.
But the Orange Bird immediately hit.
Like it tripled in price as soon as, it's like still 80 or 90 dollars on eBay.
And I have it. I think I so I brought him as well.
I have a little case full.
Oh, he's still rubbing it in my face.
Eleven years later.
Your tackle box.
How many have you got in there?
I don't know. I put this together right before I left.
The reason I have this tackle box is because I had to buy a couple of new tackle boxes
because I put all of the figure accessories in these plastic boxes.
OK.
So I have like five of these at home full of little hands, little heads, guns,
like bowstaffs, nunchucks, different Batman accessories, batarangs.
And you reckon this is this this is common practice and you recommend
the tackle boxes as a good organization.
I don't recommend having a collecting addiction to have to have these.
But if you do have one, I recommend these like Amazon tackle boxes.
I think these are actually more sewing boxes.
OK, yeah.
But yeah, these are pretty good because you can switch.
You can change like the size of the different compartments in each one
because you can pull these plastic pieces out.
Look who has kept their container store brain alive.
You're managing space customization.
I'll pull up.
Well, this is really customized.
See, I went a different route.
Jane's mom, like with Christmas stuff, sent us a box,
the famous blue tin of Danish butter cookies.
And as we were finishing them, I was like, hey,
can I keep that tin?
I will put heads and weapons and like my grandmother before me,
I will use the Danish butter cookie as storage, not for sewing,
for action figure pieces.
Because Jason's got a nice little collection of figures.
I know that sounded demeaning.
I didn't mean it to sound kind of it really did.
I would say I sounded like a nice little starter.
He's trying and I appreciate what he's doing.
And he has a few little pieces.
He doesn't quite have the same size as mine, but OK.
But yeah, you have the new, like I guess it's not new.
It's probably the last 10 or 20 years in trend and action figures
is to give you a lot of options, faces, hands, different eyes sometimes
depending on like how you want to express your character, your toy.
So now the problem is you have to store all this somewhere.
And then sometimes, especially if you have a child
and you don't have a lot of time to reorganize your action figures
every day or every few months.
Every day.
Well, I didn't do it every day before that.
But you could spend a little more time doing that.
In the same way that an old guy who likes a train, who has a little train
set and he likes to like make sure that the shrubs look OK
in his little town where his train runs around,
I make sure that the party I've staged in my Ninja Turtle sewer lair
looks good every day.
I make sure Michelangelo's hat is on right.
I make sure the boombox is in the right spot.
And I make sure that the punk frogs are all having a good time partying.
You guys. So you guys are good because you know each other.
But if you ever want to mingle with the others, right, you know,
because parties are for, you know, you don't just need to stay with your own kind.
But if you're more comfortable there, that's OK, too, frogs. Right.
And then one day, maybe I like introduce the bad guys into the party
to like break it up and like hell comes to the sewer.
Like there's a siege on the sewer.
But they got instruments to fight back with.
They sure do. So everything should be fine. Right.
So so anyway, I have these already and I had an empty one.
So I was like, oh, this will this will be perfect to bring
my parks, a handful of park stars to the record.
Well, you've handed them out.
You gave one row to Jason, one row to me.
I guess you've continued to rub it in by giving me the orange bird.
He doesn't even have it right now.
All I have is the real life man, Wally Boak.
Yeah, I love that.
There are some that where we were trying to remember all the real people
because there is an Abraham Lincoln. OK, yeah.
And there is a Wally Boak.
You know, there's a president, Millard Fillmore.
They only did Millard Fillmore out of all of the hall of fame, right?
And to put Lincoln as Lincoln, it's like a super president.
He doesn't really count as one of the riffraff presidents.
Yeah, of course.
So they did Mark Twain. Wait, I'm looking at another way.
That was it. We were trying to remember the third.
OK, right.
So, yeah, I bought a handful of them.
I still have a lot of them.
I will say right now they are not displayed in my my toy display
because the Disney section kind of fell to the Ninja Turtles
and some of the Batman stuff. Wow. Right now.
Conquered. And it's just it's I don't this shouldn't be an episode
just about my toy philosophy right now or my toy display philosophy,
but it will be a little bit about that. I don't see why not.
Well, I don't see why not being like humble.
I say that really. I'll give you permission.
Thank you. Thank you for doing that.
But it is like just having some like the Disney stuff is so disparate right now
as far as like like if there's a lot of different kinds of Disney things I have.
I have two park stars, but then I have that great Mickey
that Lindsay got me from Tokyo, Disney Sea.
And then I just have it's a very different.
You mean that's like that looks like the suit in the park.
Exactly. Small.
So that doesn't look like a park star.
I see what you're saying.
And then I have some Funko Pops and then I have some Funko Pops
of the actual like what I like with the Funko Pops in general
is the actual buildings, because you can get the Funko Pops
that have, you know, the Space Mountain
that actually have the plastic building, which I like of having a version.
Oh, yes, I have that one.
I got that up on the mantle.
Finally, my son's been playing with that.
And and he's been asking you, you give me that and you gave us
I think you guys Mickey in a Skyliner.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Which those alternatively have been staring at my son while he sleeps.
He asked for a Mickey to be watching over him.
So thank you for that.
My daughter on the way.
Don't wake up.
I got eyes on you, pal.
I'm skylining all night.
You better wake up with a 20 in your pocket or I don't care about you.
Most people have to pay to see this ride.
Not you, I guess.
I was leaving with these and my daughter
caught a glimpse that there were fun characters with bright colors in a box
as I was leaving and she goes, whoa, on the way out.
And she ran over to them and I was like, Daddy's running a little late.
He has to go.
She's like started and then she started getting upset.
I was like, I don't know.
And then I just gave her the 20,000 Leagues octopus.
And I was like, got to go. Great.
Diversion near and it worked.
She was like, all right, fine. New thing.
It was good. Yeah. Arbitrary one.
So there's and then there's other Disney stuff people have given me.
And it almost feels like there's just so much disparate stuff right now.
I can't make a cohesive display with all of it, with the room I have.
And with the turtle stuff, which is overwhelmingly what I have,
it's also uniform, it's all to scale.
Now I have dioramas and it's just completely overtaken this limited.
I mean, it's a wall, but it's a limited amount of display space. Yeah.
So right now, these are actually a lot of them are in a box.
Some of them are not.
So I have like figment and dream dream finder out on the shelf.
And some of the some of the selects are out right now.
And then meanwhile, back in the garage, a lonely chrome Garfield.
Don't I get to come inside?
I'm fancier than a regular Garfield.
His face is melted off because of the heat in Los Angeles right now.
No love for me.
You're never going to be able to pay for your daughter's college fund,
your Neuralink fund, you know, whatever they're doing.
She's going to need a Neuralink pretty soon.
Oh, yeah. No, I'm saying down the line.
Oh, down the line. Sure.
Well, if I keep that Garfield in the box,
maybe the price of that will skyrocket, especially, I don't know, after.
Did the Garfield movie come out? It did, right?
Yeah, it already came out.
I can't tell. Seemingly no impact.
But a lot of things with no impact are big hits that I don't realize.
So Chris Pratt, Garfield. Yeah.
But maybe something. Yeah, wait, I did.
That was such an out of date Garfield impression I was doing.
Hey, it's me, Garfield.
Hey, it's me, Mario.
Hey, it's me.
And tomorrow, tomorrow.
Hey, Cowan. Hey, Owen.
Cowan. Oh, no, Cowan.
My buddy resembles Mike Mitchell.
We got to fight this tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah. Hey, Luigi.
You got to move faster than Cowan.
We're going to defeat Bowser.
My impression is, hey, it's me.
I'm everyone. Hey.
Yeah, let's do all of our.
Well, he can be everyone in the box.
Hey, it's me, Orange Bird.
Hey, it's me, Dynamite Goat.
Hey, it's me, Mark Twain.
But Owen Grady is not in the next Jurassic World.
They're just rebooting fresh.
It's that right?
I don't really. With Scarlett Johansson is in it.
I do know that. I don't know.
But what a move to if there's suddenly an Owen Grady Easter egg.
Yes, that's right.
Nostalgia alert.
Is it 2015 again?
Owen Grady, wow, his fans with surprise appearance
in New Jurassic World.
Are those Claire Dearing's running heels stuck in the ground
or they pull in the ground?
They pull like a sheet off of Claire's dusty like heels
in this movie.
Whoa.
These are the original heels from the original park
that referenced the other original park.
Well, it's really funny if they were like a copy of a death certificate
of Claire Dearing's assistant who didn't pay the boys enough attention.
That really that would be really good if they were 10 years later
treating it nostalgia wise.
They will be.
Maybe. Yeah, maybe.
What were it?
Didn't they?
Isn't one of the wasn't it?
Didn't there was there a newer Pirates that was like, and look who's here?
Orlando Bloom.
Yeah, yeah.
And they got it. Wow.
It's can you believe it's been six years?
Yeah, yeah.
Wow. What a blast from the past.
It was like the fifth one.
I think they he comes back at the end with Keira Knightley.
Yeah. And those are bad.
The fourth and fifth one are bad.
And I think I saw the fifth one.
Is that Ian McShane?
We watched that as Blackbeard anything for who gives a shit.
You said that I thought Ian McShane was an old author, too.
I don't know anything.
He's from Deadwood. Yeah.
He does speak very well.
They all speak eloquently in Deadwood.
You just need like a giant problem gambler to write up your words.
And then I and I say recently, I probably was five years ago.
We watched some of Deadwood and I was like, there's just an episode
where Ian McShane is trying to pass a kidney stone.
Yes. It's great television.
It's very thrilling, although it'll make you worry.
You have a kidney stone.
Well, sure. Any ailment on TV, I worry I have it.
Mike doesn't need to watch something about a kidney stone to worry about.
If I watch Batman and Robin, I think that I have McGregor's syndrome,
the illness that Alfred had, which isn't real.
But they start talking McGregor's syndrome and I go, shit,
I feel like I'm coming down with McGregor's syndrome.
What if I have to freeze my daughter until they find a cure?
Wait, did his wife have McGregor's syndrome?
Well, is that the things that he they're both they they are aligned,
good and evil, looking for the same cure.
Oh, I guess. Right.
It would have to. I can't imagine there were two diseases in play,
but I don't quite remember.
Jason, can you look up if if Victor freezes his wife?
Nora. Nora had McGregor's syndrome.
I guess you're probably right.
Why wouldn't it be that? Right. Yeah.
Huh. That's interesting.
Because he and the cure is diamonds, right?
That's why he steals diamonds. Yes.
Because diamonds might be the cure for McGregor's syndrome.
Yeah. Yes.
One. Oh, yeah.
He say one more giant diamond.
One more.
And then they go to like.
But then he has to put it in that like telescope
at the end of the thing that shoots a beam into the sky.
You were Nora.
Freeze did have McGregor.
OK, Scott was right there.
A fictional condition in the Batman mythos.
Well, I have it too now.
Now that we're talking about it, whatever it is, psychosomatic
McGregor's syndrome, I think that's just what Nora Freeze has.
Mike only has been stealing diamonds.
I'm like a hypochondriac, but it's all for fictional diseases
from comic books and comic book movies, like just different.
Like I have.
What's the what's the virus in X-Men?
The legacy of the legacy of the legacy virus as well.
That colossus sacrifices himself.
Yeah, I can't come.
I can't hang out tonight.
I have the legacy virus.
Yeah, I think I have the thing that makes humans dumber
and apes smarter that enables the planet of the apes.
Have you noticed my vocabulary has been lesser on the show lately?
I think it's because of whatever that was.
Ape syndrome. Yeah.
Ooh, syndrome.
Yeah. So look, I everything I do every even my
my worries are based in some pop culture I absorbed as a child.
Even my true fears.
I am. Are you worried?
I don't know if he's dead.
Is he dead? No. OK.
I was going to say, is Bobby Sherman still alive?
Yes, he is alive.
And you don't have to worry about dying of what Bobby Sherman died of
until he dies.
That's true. Yeah, because my mom will say it like she will put it
still put it in my head or whatever.
Whenever he passes away, she will be like, well, you know, you got to be careful,
depending on how Bobby Sherman died, whatever it is.
If it's a fall, if he has, I don't know, lung cancer,
I don't know that he smoked.
He seemed like a wholesome nonsmoker to me, but I don't know that.
That's the way he was portrayed as far as my mind.
He's so nice. Bobby Sherman seems so nice.
How would he ever smoke or do anything bad ever?
So we'll see. He's so nice.
I can't believe that he died of old age.
Be careful, Michael, be careful about being older.
So so, yeah, so the Park Stars will come back into the display
at a certain point when I become very rich and have a big house
or when I just start shuffling stuff around, which I want to do,
but I don't have too much time for that anymore because you want to shuffle
things out, you want to shuffle things in.
And then having a collection is also this it's a giant
I think of it as like a giant living organism.
You're constantly like pruning.
You're constantly reassessing what you have.
Do I still like this?
Do I want this?
But I want to just store it away for a while.
And it never ends.
Some might say it's an albatross around your neck.
Yeah, I was going to say a curse.
Some might call it a curse,
but some might call it a nice little hobby.
Compulsion is a bit of a compulsion.
There is a thing, though, with collecting,
where I really try to be honest with myself and look at everything I have.
And I do the Marie Kondo thing.
And I'm like, is this sparking joy in me?
Is this giving me pleasure when I look at it?
And the answer? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Got one no, 100 more yeses.
That's a that's a big problem, because actually in some ways
you'd be like, it'd be great if I looked at it.
And I went, no, actually, it doesn't.
It's a compulsion.
It's something where I just felt a need to complete a set
because that exists as well.
The answer is almost everything I have displayed is awesome.
And every time I look at it, I get a little thrill.
I get a little fun in the head.
Like I get a little like shot of adrenaline
because it looks like something I liked probably when I was a kid.
So so I think when we're talking to park stars,
I think maybe if I'm psychoanalyzing myself,
if these things look even more like the actual robots
and characters in the park, they might still be on the display right now.
But the abstraction.
But in some cases, at least for a couple of them,
you got you kind of look and you go, what's that?
And if there's any percentage of what's that?
And not with what you're showing, you're you're taking a few out of your box
and putting them on a little stand here.
And there's that's obviously figment.
It's obviously right. It's obviously redhead.
Now that now this one, I'm a little sure.
Is that Phantom Phantom?
It does say on the bottom of them what they are.
Not the turtle from Electric Light Parade.
I think that's a later series innovation is stamping
or an earlier series innovation.
Well, it's like here's Skippy from extraterrestrial
alien encounter, right? Good full branding.
I well, it's on the bottom.
I read it like you were paid for by the Disney company
to read that full title. Yeah.
Wouldn't it be funny if you had been like paid the whole time?
We didn't know. Yeah.
Only Jason. Seven years.
Jason, taking a deal with Disney.
No, I'm not. I'm just, you know, I'm just back from visiting.
Look out key at Lighthouse Point.
Scott, you up on Lookout Key on Lighthouse Point?
It's their newest cruise destination.
It's full of bugs.
There are a lot of bugs.
There are a lot of bugs crawling on the.
And everything is really far away.
They should do an alien encounter where they just release a bunch of bugs
in the room, like a bunch of insects for real.
Because like, as long as they're not they don't have stingers,
you're not going to get hurt.
But you might get a fly in the mouth or something.
Well, that and that's what I I, you know, the the nut jobs online
are like New World Order is going to make you eat bugs.
And I am on record as saying, give me those bugs.
I want to eat the bugs.
In all seriousness, have you had like bug anything?
Only I think I don't even remember if I bought
like the novelty lollipops that had a cricket or something in them.
Where the tequila with those were like, you know, souvenir shops.
I haven't ever seen. Have you ever seen that?
No. Well, yeah, like big suckers that have like a worm or a.
But they have a scorpion.
It's kind of fun. It's like all day.
How close to it do you get with the tequila with the bug?
Sure. Yeah, but that's like a worm.
Yeah. Yeah, that's not a bug.
But you never had like crickets or something.
You know, like I think maybe I got the.
Or did I try that?
Was there a margarita at the Mexico Pavilion and napkin with the
with a rim of bugs?
Ants, ants. OK. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I kind of like that.
But your world order, you didn't eat.
You didn't eat the pond eels.
No, no, God.
Who knows where that marsh goes to?
Oh, you even if you cook them?
I don't I don't know.
I don't think I would risk. Yeah.
Cooking a pond eel. No. Yeah.
I think once or twice we had like if we were camping with the Boy Scouts,
if someone caught like a big trout or something,
but that's so what you have to cut the scales off.
You have to debone it.
I also would say that eating a trout is nowhere close to eating a pond eel.
No, I don't think trout is a thing that you eat.
As opposed to pond eels is what I was saying.
Well, you're right.
Little guppies or goldies or whatever.
Like I haven't eaten an eel.
I have eaten a yellowtail.
Well, that's a different way.
What would have eaten a burger?
What was the name of the fish you would catch that you would guppies or sunnies?
Sunnies. That's right.
You wouldn't eat the sunnies.
No, we wouldn't eat.
God knows how much meat is even on those things.
Not much, probably.
But yeah, so so if these I think also would trend like my collector brain,
I do like things to look exactly like they appear either on a show or in real life, too.
So I think probably if the ultimate version of something like this,
if Disney were to do it again, I would kind of want a full sized phantom
that just looked exactly like the robot on Phantom Manor.
Because figments kind of style, like I don't know how to describe it.
They're all cartoon versions of inflatable, old fashioned, like punching bags or like
they're just like basically cartoonified versions of all the characters.
And some people, some characters lend themselves more to that style than others.
So some of the ones when you go, like, I don't know what that one is.
It's because they've cartoonified like, I don't know, like maybe that turtle.
Yeah, Wally Bo. Right.
Wally Bo. You know, a little bit of his soul is in every one of these.
They they I was going to say there was a comic book where they an editor passed away
and they put his actual ashes in the printing of the comic.
So his soul is in that.
Yes. Is that guy's name?
Grunwald. Yeah.
Kiss the kiss comic book.
Put blood in the ink.
There's no one.
No one. Wally Bo didn't do any of that for this toy.
We have to make that clear.
Unless it was against his will.
Unless it was against it.
No one dug up his grave.
New World Order Bugs.
Disney has soul capturing devices.
Why do you keep saying New World Order?
I don't know. It's just conspiracy.
It's like an Alex Jones thing.
I think it's an Alex Jones thing.
The New World Order is going to be huge.
OK, right. It's like, yeah, bugs.
Order whatever.
Not Order 66.
But there was like some U.S.
military exercise exercises.
And there were like this preparation for New World Order.
OK, yeah, yeah.
But I don't know.
What other toys are in your box, Mike?
So what we got here?
Yeah, I have the Dream Finder in the water.
I have like the Polynesian kind of icon here.
Now, what I was keeping tabs on, like
I had never maybe looked at the full list of these.
And that's one.
I was like, do I want any more of these?
That is definitely one that I might go for.
Yeah, yeah, pretty cool.
And some. Yeah, that's that's on there.
They have I'm trying to think there are.
There's not really like an icon
of the contemporary or anything.
But they're like even like a park star of the contemporary
because they didn't do buildings or anything
would be really fun, I feel like. Sure.
But they did do 2017 Trader Sam.
Yes, I have that as well.
Eventually removed. Right.
So that's a canceled one.
Like the redhead is gone now.
Oh, yeah. Over here.
She's out of the.
That is not warrior redhead.
I have Trader Sam, but yeah,
they probably would not make him now.
Waldo, Waldo, I got Waldo over here.
That's also on my list of I wouldn't mind having a Waldo.
Do you have Sonny Eclipse as well?
I do have Sonny Eclipse. OK, that's I have bought
Funmeister love that because the Funmeister
lives like almost entirely as logo.
Yes. And that's like he's kind of in the factory
pomo squiggle style.
And I like having a figured that one.
I get your joy seeing that like
Rex. It's not my favorite depiction of Rex.
But I like you, Mike.
I think I like my action figure that just looks like him more.
Of course, the giant one.
They did the plays music.
And Sonny Eclipse, I have loved that.
And Smart One, I have.
And Smart One is important to me because.
OK, so my Aaron and I both always liked kind of like simple
little stout 80s robots.
And our wedding cake toppers were
R2D2 with a little tuxedo
triangle. That was me.
And then the bride was Ernie, who is this little robot with a jetpack,
who is the icon of this event, Expo 86 in Vancouver,
who's who has a veil.
And we've kept those and displayed them in our home.
And then we had our son.
We were like, well, he's got to join the collection.
There's this little alcove in our outside of our bedroom
that's probably like where a phone used to go.
But now it's like, well, what do we put there?
I would have better little robots.
And we got to we got to make one of them our son.
And that's Smart One.
That's really we have a little and the proportions are great.
There's a little robot who's the son of the two slightly bigger robots.
That's really so smart.
Yeah. So Smart One's ended up being very important that that doing that
almost made me because I don't really say his name on the show.
And you're showing him right now. He's always wonderful.
I don't say my son's name on the show.
And I thought when we had him,
what if we just what if we call him Smart One?
What if that's the code?
And but I've never I was like,
that might get very complicated as the years go by.
So I'm not done.
But I was almost like, all right, if I can get used to like.
So, you know, we're out with Smart One.
And in theory, it's like good.
But like actually in practice, I feel like it would be like confusing.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Then that's like then the listeners have to like,
why does he keep saying smart?
What's that about his code for his kid?
And then if I were to have another, then like, does that imply
that's not the smart one?
Yeah, that's a good. Yeah.
Smart One Hendrix. Come on.
We have to go.
And then like Smart Two, like you get a different one
and like customize it or something.
Oh, that's not smart. One and Smart Two.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
So I guess that's OK. Yeah.
I'll give him a complex.
I'm the second. You're number two.
You're always number two.
What happens, Jason, do you have yours displayed right now at home?
No, I still have it in a box.
So I don't have them displayed either.
Which ones do you have again?
I have about a dozen, I think, between the five series.
Yeah, because I always I told you when we were driving over,
I like the thrill of the blind box.
Sometimes he said, yes, Jason said I like he likes the sort of mystery of it.
You said I like the chase, I think.
Oh, I do like the chase, not to be confused with the chaser variance.
Right. Because so they call when there's blind boxes and there's they'll say,
OK, here's here's all the different things you can get in a blind box.
And then there will be a couple of things with a question mark that says the chase.
And that's the mystery thing.
Jason didn't mean that he was looking for the chase.
He just meant he wanted he liked the surprise of opening up the box.
Yeah, I don't think I like some of the variance.
Hey, tell me what you don't like.
I don't know. I just some of the ones that I don't like the diamond celebration ones.
Well, that's true. I don't.
So basically, you know, they would release series, a series of these,
and then they would do like special ones where you wouldn't be blind.
It would just be like the diamond release version of like,
I don't know, the Yeti or something or the Tiki Bird.
And they would just like sort of paint it like a diamond color,
which is really just like silver and blue.
And it's like with these they call these variants in the figure world.
It's like, what do we get?
What are we getting out of these?
What joy are you seeing seeing a character
painted a color that doesn't look like it looks in the park?
Like, it's not so fun.
There's one that's pretty clever, and it's the Abraham Lincoln one
that looks like a penny.
Yes, which I have.
And you can at least appreciate the cleverness of making Lincoln
in like a copper at the very least.
Oh, ha ha ha.
Oh, ha ha ha is what you say.
And that's every time Mike sees it. Oh, ha ha.
I say, oh, ha ha ha.
And I and I was so ha ha ha.
Come on, pop pop pop pop.
Come on, Danny, let's go, ha ha ha.
Do you have the what's his name from the Avengers Club, Jason?
The Colonel? I don't know if I do at the car.
That feels like one you should have.
Yeah, as I'm looking at this list, I was I had the same reaction.
Oh, I should have the car.
I am realizing, as I said earlier, I have the corner
tourists from Dinosaur.
Oh, yeah. I think Aladar did get made. Did he?
There is one that just says I don't think Aladar is in there.
Yeah, there's a generic kind of looking dinosaur in series four.
You think that's Aladar?
I think it's supposed to be Aladar for the
whatever kind of dinosaur you're going to need to confirm that.
I'll keep looking and I'll see if I think I have that somewhere.
I had a mission. Oh, you know what?
I had a mission space astronaut, but I sold it out of spite.
I don't want mission space because I don't like mission space.
What was it?
It was just this kind of like generic astronaut looking guy right here.
He's kind of got a red spacesuit.
I don't think this is because that because Aladar is not blue.
It's not. What is this from?
This is is it like?
Well, it's not like the the
Gertie from Disney and James Studios, right?
No, it's not the Windsor.
No, yeah. Yeah.
Gertie, I mean, yeah, I don't know.
I would have to look go back through here.
This is a thing with the Park Stars was that like, oh, it's the caveman
from such and such, you know, like, no, that's actually from spaceship
or or like anything that could like, oh, it's the astronaut from Epcot.
It's like, no, it's from the original Disney.
Well, there was so it could be mission space.
Astronaut could be a space mountain astronaut.
There was a blue version, I think, that was Space Mountain,
but they use it was basically just the same sculpt
and they would use it for mission space then as well.
Yeah. You know, now I'm seeing it as a Guanadon.
So it could be I think that's what Aladar is, Aladar.
Yeah, I just it's confusing because the color is not his color,
which we know is the cutest, cutest,
very, very beige, as beige as his little shit,
which is the cutest little shit in all of history or prehistory.
As beige as Windows 95 or whatever version of Linux was out in 98 would allow.
So, yeah, so there's I'm just so yeah, you don't have any of yours displayed
just because do you do you have a place in the display for them right now?
Or do you think like you're just going to have to eventually figure out
where to put it eventually?
Well, you know, what part of the problem is, is that I like the tins
I have them all in the tins they sold them in and they take up so much root.
The first few series had tins that you would actually get them in.
They weren't eventually they switched more to paper, to cardboard,
cardboard, thicker stock, but still.
But you would get like these substantial tins
when you would just get one of them or get obviously all of them.
But that was also sort of a fun way to display, perhaps as well,
like put them on top of them or in front of them,
because generally when you buy a toy, I open most of the toys I have,
except for Garfield, who's sitting sweltering in the heat.
But suffering, suffering, some might say.
But yeah, you did feel like there was some extra value in getting a tin,
getting a little tin along with your toy.
And I think I threw some of them up, but I do have some of them
whenever they return to a display.
It's always the quickest thing to go for me is if when I need space
or if I'm cleaning up, it's like whatever the toy came in.
I keep it for a while.
Like you might end up one day and maybe you put them in, like, no out.
He saves so much room when you know, I know I end up doing that as well,
because some stuff, especially now with toys and like certain collector toys,
like the boxes are really great.
So you can like display things and it looks pretty good.
And even if you even click like boxes will come with like a backdrop
that looks cool to display a figure in front of.
So there's like a lot of stuff
that you can actually use for a display.
But if you have a bunch of crap like I do, you probably got to throw the box away.
Like it's just so much room is taken up with with the box.
Yeah, I mean, Marvel Legends, by and large, come in
like kind of generic black boxes, packaging.
But they start doing more and more throwback cards, which in my house
they always called them backers and would drive my mom nuts.
There just be stacks of backers
if we have action figures, partially because the figures were kind of basic.
But the art on the card transport was cool.
Yeah. Well, yeah.
And in like my when I would have my Ninja Turtles,
I would have them all in like a big like suitcase.
And then you would have the like backs of the cards
because they would have like stats on Donatello, like Donatello five, three,
16 years old skills, science, not driving, not driving.
Not driving.
But so I had all that stuff, but I never did anything with it.
But we I kept them forever.
I don't know if I still have any of those.
That's real. Let's talk like.
Why these are gone, you can't find a good reason why
vilemation in general was discontinued, why these were discontinued.
They did five series of them.
I'm guessing what happened was they were replaced by
things called Tsum Tsums, if you've seen those in the park.
There are things called munchlings now.
Have you seen munchlings, Jason?
I think I've seen munchlings and munchlings are not squishamallows.
Munchlings are not squish mellows. Squish mellows.
If we're going into this area, can I say
and I was going to say this for the end is a potential assignment.
But let me let me just because this is exactly where you're heading.
While back, I threw out like what are second gates that you want online
and Avery at Bolton Nerdist had an idea
that I filed away because this is pretty good.
Here it is. An episode entitled Into the Plush Pile,
where you explain the differences between munchlings,
weemos, Tsum Tsums, wishables,
doorables and all the other varieties of plushes in the Disney universe.
I think that's great, Avery.
And then that didn't even include the one Jason just said.
There's a whole other one, which are not Disney specific.
OK, yeah, I don't know that I'm prepared to do that.
Well, not now, but in the future.
I think it's a great place to go to take us into the plush pile.
Like what I know about munchlings, which are like little plush things,
is like they combine Disney and food.
They combine like Mickey Mouse and like here's Mickey Mouse as a cupcake
or here Daisy is as a cup of coffee.
And they're like little plush characters.
I don't know if they're blind or not.
This looks like I'm trying to look this looks like some sort of Disney bear
that's also like a Swiss cake roll or something. Hello.
So I don't know, Jason might have to get into these right now.
I can't have them in the house. Try to eat them.
I did. I looked up because there's a great Funko
that comes with a little Tower of Terror.
And I put off I was going to buy this thing because it was for Disney's 50th.
It was on clearance on Amazon for like months and it was $15.
And then suddenly the price jumped up to 50 or now it's $70.
Yeah, that's what happened. They clear them out.
And then a really cute Tower of Terror Funko plush. Oh, OK.
Look at how cute it's $6. That doesn't do a lot for me.
I'll say that. Really? If you like it, I'm not going to try to dissuade you from that.
But I don't. That doesn't do a lot for me.
That doesn't look anything like the Tower of Terror to me.
Also, is Jason ever fillier than when saying Tower of Terror?
Terror, terror. That brings it out.
Yeah. You know, so it's a plush.
It looks kind of like the turr turr.
We go on a turr turr.
I think it apparently gets worse as I like worked up her time
because Jane's like, I don't know what that sentence you just said.
And I'm like, what are you talking about?
We've been together for a year.
And like, she says it back to me.
I'm like, OK, that does sound like gibberish.
So, yeah, so that's the munchlings.
Soom Sooms are just these little like,
I guess they're like three inches, four inches.
And they're just these kind of like, what would you even call them?
Like little eggs, they're little eggless eggs with like little cute faces
on them that are all the characters, the Disney characters.
There's just there's tons of them.
I don't know. We may have one or two.
But then there's also numeos.
Did we did was numeo in there?
That's on the list. Yeah.
Numeos, which I'm a little more intrigued about, though I haven't dabbled.
Numeos are just little plush, but then you can get little outfits for them.
And that's what I'm all about.
If you can buy a little leather jacket for Mickey,
you can get him like kind of a hip like jean and jacket set here.
And you can really like mix and match the clothes for the plush.
This is I feel like the use of your use of hip has really
expanded on the show in the last couple of months.
And it's always mildly questionable.
Well, Mickey's so hip.
Mickey's as hip as the musicians I listen to who are hip.
Everything is relative when I say hip, as far as this podcast is concerned.
Mike's running into that Mickey 2013 at Emo Night in Echo Park.
Sure. Oh, it's pleased to be 11 years ago.
You can give Mickey, you know, you can finally like kind of have Mickey
like dress like you would want him when you're hanging out with him
in your location of your choice, basically.
So, yeah, you can have Echo Park Mickey.
But if you don't want that, you can dress them any way you want.
You can make Mickey who make Mickey your own is what Numeos should
should be saying. That should be their tagline.
Do they have a night shirt and a big sleeping cap?
They have so many clothes. I don't know.
I hope they do, because then you could have all your care.
Think about this, Jason.
Every Disney character, you can now give them a night shirt and a cap,
and you could all have them like tucked away right by the bedside.
And so they could all be ready to go to sleep 24 7.
They're all mad because they're like, I couldn't have seen Marley.
Must have been a crust of bread or a spot of mustard.
So they're all going through the night before Christmas. Yeah.
The torturing them all with ghosts.
It's Christmas Eve.
They're being tortured by the chains they forged in life.
I'm sure there are Christmas night shirt
numeos where you could do the night before Christmas every night.
Like you do personally. Yeah.
Where you have your own night shirt and cap
and you see Jacob Marley before you go to bed
and you have the candle, I assume, when you go to the kitchen.
Yeah. Yeah. A candle holder.
Because that wax going to drip. Yeah, you're not holding a loose candle.
When you go to the kitchen. It's ridiculous.
If you can, if you can make it so that you can put all of your Disney characters
in sleeping caps and pajamas and keep them, keep them in your bed.
It's a much easier way for post your death, your relatives to come in
and realize that you were a more disturbed person than they knew.
Oh, wow. Who, who had any clue what he was going through?
Yeah. He forged a lot of chains in life. My God.
I don't let my mom go into the room with all the toys because she,
she doesn't like it. She's upset by it.
Well, yeah, because if they have napkin bedding, it's going to burst in the flames.
Stop everything.
That's the craziest thing ever said on the show.
Your mother won't go see your.
Like I said, no, I don't want her to go in there.
That's not her saying.
That's that's not like I can't see my, that's because the way you frame that,
it was like, you know, you don't want to go into the coroner's office
and ID your child like, no, it's them.
No, she doesn't want to like, she doesn't want to acknowledge the reality
that I have this large collection.
That's what it sounded like. Yeah.
But is it her? Is it you?
Well, it's mostly like I just like, I don't want her going in there
because I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear anything like, don't you think you have a little too much
or don't like then she'll try to make like points, like side points that she thinks.
She does this with everything where she tries to make like a point
about another person she knows, but clearly she's talking about me.
And she's trying to, you know, I knew, you know, Mrs.
Collins's son when there was an earthquake was buried in his toys.
Yeah, I think a little I think it must have been a little like
daffy duck got lodged in his throat and he choked on it and never woke up.
So exactly.
That's just an unrelated story to what I've just seen in this room.
Every aspect of my life, this is how it goes.
This is what my mom will do.
And she'll tell a story about somebody else.
And then I go, I know what you're doing.
Oh, I know I'm not.
She'll deny it.
She'll just like as if that story came into her head for no reason
other than just, oh, it's an interesting story, isn't it?
So do you need to so she's around helping out with your daughter.
And do you need to kind of like up, up, up, up, up, up on there?
What's easy about it is that we close that door just general
because there's that's just a bunch of crap in there.
And we don't want the daughter or our daughter is too young
to be in a room with a bunch of little stuff still.
I thought that she's like eating a ton of stuff, but it's better.
It's better to have that door closed anyway.
So if she's watching her, she's not going to open that door.
OK, because of the baby, because of the child.
So that's why right now is not the door is closed for her safety,
not for your grown mother's safety psychologically.
Exactly. Yes.
And it's like you're talking about a porno dungeon.
We get that close.
You keep the porno dungeon wide open, but the toys,
the Ninja Turtle room, the room with the sex swing is off limits.
Yeah. House. Yeah.
You'd be fine with it if you had that.
That'd be less embarrassing.
If my mother saw my sex swing, she would know that I've progressed
and matured in some way.
She sees a room full of just so.
Wait, it's the toys that I bought for you growing up,
but 10 times more of them recently purchased.
Why can you not just have a bunch of vibrators like a regular person?
Yeah, that would be.
Yeah, that would be an easier sell plushes.
No pocket pussies. Yes.
That phrase, my mom would pass out if that phrase was ever
uttered around her.
Look, mom, you should be proud of me.
I bought a pocket.
My dad, when he's listening to this, is going to wait, wait, wait.
I make your dad.
What do your dad sees either of us?
Does he kind of like take a deep breath?
He knows everything he's heard.
Let's go talk to him.
He knows he has it all in there.
I thought he was doing OK.
I thought he could have afforded a flashlight.
I don't know why he's got all these generic pocket pussies around.
They're so gummy.
I've also had an argument where I'm like, Mom, the show isn't that dirty.
I've also had that argument with her in general.
So here's this one.
This will completely disprove what I was trying to say.
There's nothing wrong with having a sex toy or two around the house.
You're an adult man.
Well, he's going to be there's where do you if you're her
and you're listening to this, where do you start?
The last 10 minutes of this is five avenues to unpack.
Oh, no, it's going to be a problem.
Maybe I like try to like unsubscribe my dad's phone or something
for like, how do you how do you close the door on a podcast?
Up, up, up. Don't go in there.
Don't go. Make sure to not go in that one room in my house
and don't go in that one gate on my podcast.
Oh, I just keep my mom.
Not for you.
It's because I'm worried that my daughter will choke on topics in that game.
Right, right.
My mom stays on the East Coast.
She saw my apartment.
She was like, how do you have comic book boxes out here, too?
You're not getting the ones out of my house.
I'm like, yeah, I don't.
How do you transport those across country?
I get a pod.
You did. Yeah.
Did you get one of those pot like you?
No, I'm trying to think.
My parents, I guess, did you try for?
How did I get some of them out?
Huh? That is a good question.
What other toys do we have?
Well, these are a little few more photos of new meals.
So heavy. Here's Mickey and Minnie.
Here are them in sleeping bags to talk about
one of my mother not letting me use napkins as sleeping bags for characters.
These are official sleeping bags.
How big are those?
And now here's hip clothes for Pooh and friends.
Who wears jeans and a vest and a striped shirt.
And yours got like a jean jacket.
Hang on. Are you sure that's really the Pooh?
Are you not showing me a photo of a band on the Garden State soundtrack?
Is this is that just a promotional photo for a set at Bumbershoot?
It could be.
This could be a hip band.
They're playing the NUEMO festival.
Look at the shoes. Look at Portland.
Look at Piglet's shoes.
Look at his cool shoes.
Pooh. Yeah, Pooh.
Oh, no, Pooh's shoes as well.
Pooh's got like brown shoes.
Pooh's shoes as well.
They've never been that high on the show.
Brown Oxford's on.
So like all this stuff replaced Vinylmation stuff in the park.
I don't fully think it's completely the same audience, though.
I still think like this is more this can be more for younger kids.
These park stars are for us.
These are for sick, twisted, older collectors
who like specific characters for the theme park.
And I think that they're a victim of, especially the park stars.
They're a victim of something that just didn't make enough money.
It probably made money, but it doesn't make enough money for Disney
to want to continue doing it. Sure.
Because they'd always like almost always be sold out.
Like the waves would go.
And it's I mean, I'm assuming it's a fairly limited release.
But it's one of those things where like,
oh, Parkstar has only made us one hundred thousand dollars a year.
What's the point? OK.
That's what I'm guessing would happen.
And all the different molds and stuff, you know, it's they're all.
It's like particular to make.
Yes. And it's like you could probably you're going to sell more Mickey.
All that stuff we just mentioned is still like Mickey Donald Goofy.
Different whatever version you want.
Do you want them as a breakfast pastry?
Do you want Mickey as a little egg?
Do you want Mickey as a hip Silver Lake coffee drinker?
Not well, I guess you could have Silver Lake New Meal Mickey drinking coffee
Mickey of a month as a munchling if you wanted.
And then he's also eating egg Mickey from the Tsum Tsum.
So you could really do it up with Mickey eating and drinking himself
in a coffee drinker appropriate clothing
from the New Meal.
But yes, it's not.
Yeah. And there are other certain
clothings that are not appropriate for a coffee drinker.
Well, sure. Very specific.
Some think of a type of coffee drinker, the Silver Lake, sort of
intelligentsia coffee drinker.
Silver Lake is a hip place from a book that I read from 1996.
Silver Lake is a tip.
There you see Jason.
Well, Jason said it and it got in my head.
And Jason knows all about hip stuff and cool stuff.
So that's what I was going to our friend over here in the Atlantic
City Planet Hollywood shirt knows.
Cool. Jason knows.
Cool. So so I just it sucks because I wish they would.
Disney will like obviously they do a lot of licensed products
and other companies make their stuff.
But it's almost like something that like it would have to be produced out of how
it would have to be produced by a different company
that wants to do something like this.
And from what I also understand, it's very hard for other companies
to make park specific stuff.
Disney is still pretty like strict about what you're allowed to make.
If you're just a toy company that wants to make Disney toys,
you can make Mickey, you can make Minnie, you can do stuff like that.
But I think like Hatbox Ghost, you cannot make like they are still
like really like proprietary about their park characters for some reason.
So I think it's I don't I don't ever see them doing anything like this again.
And it seems like it's going to be really tough for another company
to make a parks line.
But but like a company called Super 7 has made some like Haunted Mansion toys
of some of the different characters.
But that seems like that's the only ride they're like kind of flexible with.
But I know they can where they feel like there's money to be made
in the cult of it, that there's the people are picking apart every detail enough.
Yes. But but also just like I think Disney is looking for a certain
amount of money that things can make.
And there are companies that would make park stuff and make a profit on it.
But is it enough to then pay Disney some money from the license
that would make it feel like it was still worth their while
to let them use their characters? Right.
This is kind of guessing on my part.
But you're saying that this is the kind of thing that makes like a cult type of money,
but which doesn't rate if you're Disney.
That's what I think is happening, because I don't know why there wouldn't be
tons of versions of this, why there wouldn't be Tsum Tsums of the Phantom
or of Wally. Why isn't there a Tsum Tsum of Wally Bogue?
Why isn't there a Numio of Wally Bogue?
You want just a little cuddled up baby sized Wally Bogue.
Yeah. A real man who walks this earth.
Mark Twain Numio.
Jason would have the Mark Twain Numio.
Oh, I would love that.
And dress him in all sorts of little outfits, which would be fun.
But obviously, like, that's not for the general public.
That's one little Mark Twain to dress up as eggs and bacon.
Jason Wood, which food would you want Mark Twain to be for muchlings?
Oh, that's a great, great question.
I was going to say dress him up in a little sailor suit,
like he was working on the riverboat.
That's for his Numio.
Oh, that's for his Numio.
I'm talking about for a Mark Twain munchling.
Maybe something
appropriate, maybe like some sarsaparilla.
OK. Maybe a sarsaparilla float, like a big root beer float in his hand.
And his hair is like the foam.
His hair is like the foam.
That's great. Yeah.
But yeah, so I just I'm disappointed
because it feels like we'll never get this again.
Now, I've thought that about toys before.
Well, there's no way we'll ever get blank.
And then it happens.
So I hope I am wrong about it.
But a full like there's still so much to make
as far as characters that have never been made before.
There's what's his name?
Uncle What's his name from the Carousel of Progress?
Uncle Orville. Thank you.
Uncle Orville, all the characters from the Carousel of Progress.
Do they not ever? There's not one Carousel of Progress.
There's a John Vinylmation.
Yeah, he's wearing all of his outfits, kind of.
Yeah, and I don't really like it.
Patchwork. Yeah, I don't love it.
I don't like the I don't like the having to incorporate the mouse ears.
Yeah, some of the characters look OK with the mouse ears.
But yeah, there's a Vinylmation, but like they didn't make those characters.
They didn't make there isn't a hatbox ghost.
There is. There's some big ones that they haven't done.
And I just like I'm again, a sad I'm always sad at the end of these episodes.
Sad that I feel like there's we're not getting more.
We're never going to get all this stuff that we want because it's still sort of obscure.
They were doing more limited run like than like they used to have that line of T-shirts.
The yesteryear line.
Yes, which I have a handful of those with throwback stuff.
Right. And it feels like they don't do though.
Once in a while on Shop Disney, they'll have like a retro shirt.
But they really don't do that as much anymore.
Unless like a ride is closing.
They'll do like a run of shirts of like if they're destroying a classic ride.
They're taking we don't have any great at the door.
There's no great movie ride merchandise until we're destroying the ride.
And then there will be a shirt or two that you can get.
We're taking a wrecking ball to bear Fox's head, but we need the guts in P intact.
So be careful.
Uh huh. So, yeah, I mean, my dream is a full line that's like,
yeah, they're like six or seven inches and they're all to scale, which is important to me.
I'm a real scale hound.
I don't know what you would call it.
I really like scale queen.
I'm a scale size.
I'm a size queen.
I think that's what you could say that about me.
What that means, though, is that I want my figures to scale.
I want to make sure that if the.
You want all your big, your bright, beautiful park stars.
Yes, right.
My big right.
For their size to be adequate.
This is not look at this.
Figment and the Dreamfinder are almost the same height.
This is ridiculous.
It's ridiculous.
That is definitely worth being mad about.
Well, I'm just saying, would you prefer to have them both the same size like this?
Or would you want Dreamfinder to be like seven inches
and then Figment to be like one or two, two inches?
I mean, Figment can grow and shrink and change his outfit and stuff.
So I understand that, but he's not big all the time.
Right. Well, let me ask you guys this.
Is there a if you just have to think about it as a thought exercise,
is there a like a version, would you want plushes of some of these characters?
Would you want six inch figures?
They're just a couple of characters.
You would want like a 12, like a big would you buy a big Figment
figure if it was like the size of that Rex from Galaxy's Edge?
The answer could be no.
I like 12 inches.
We are now dealing with like a major, a lot of space.
It's a lot of commitment. Yeah.
And I do have like big theme park display
signs and stuff, but like it's got I got to love the character.
Right. Do I love Figment?
I do like Figment, but do I do I 12 inches love Figment?
Big question. Big question.
Do you love 12 inches worth of Figment?
How many inches of Figment do you like?
12 tall purple inches of Figment.
Do you want six inches of Figment or do you want 12?
I would have to say I think I think I could handle
six inches of Figment.
So shorter. But would you want it wider?
Yeah. Like a chode? Chode Figment.
Jason, what do you think?
What do you what do you want from like these park characters?
Because like we're all yeah, you want the characters themselves.
Well, what version of them or do you want just more park stars?
I'd love more park stars.
I think I'd like something maybe a little taller,
maybe like seven.
Sorry, not to what up you, Scott.
But that's the traditional like Marvel Legends.
Marvel Legends are like seven inches.
OK, so something I can handle seven.
Something a little taller and articulate it so you can pose them.
I think I'd like that's what I always wanted as a kid.
I had so many like PVC figurines as a kid.
And you would have to imagine it moving
because you couldn't bend like Star Wars
or like Disney character or like PVC figures.
That's what I want. Yes. Yeah.
So six, seven inch scale articulation, little hands,
different heads, different expressions like the ultimates
that NECA makes or Super Seven makes or.
Yeah. I mean, the thing I like about
the park stars or Marvel Marvel Legends
is that you can pose them,
but you can also put them on the top of a dresser or bookshelf or something.
Plushes take up so much room.
So I like the little ones like the like Mr.
Taffy that I brought you guys.
And we have a couple sure around the house.
But like, I don't think I'd want I couldn't handle 12 inches of Mr. Taffy.
I disagree.
I think you could.
12 inches of Taffy.
OK, all right.
Mr. Taffy is too much of a scam.
How is the Taffy soft or is it firm?
Somewhere in between.
12, well. Do you need a massage to get it firm?
You like the Taffy, you warm it up?
You warm the Taffy up before you eat?
If Taffy is hard, you can warm it between your hands to soften it.
We've been over this.
Well, that refreshes it for another year.
It refreshes it.
You can also put it in the freezer and take it down.
Right. Sure.
But I was asking your preference.
Oh, I like Taffy, like fresh off the lot, like pretty soft, you know.
Soft Taffy Jason likes.
Not pull your teeth out.
Give it to him soft is what I would say to a Taffy maker.
OK, so there's a list.
I found a list of of people's wants as far as other characters,
which I guess is a good place to maybe end.
Sure. Yeah.
Be hopeful, not be negative about what we won't.
Yeah, OK, we want to do every name.
And I'm like, oh, they don't have it.
Weezy from Toy Story at the end of the Slinky Dog Dash,
which I think is would be a good one.
Yeah. It's in a movie.
I don't want it. I want things that are only in parts.
Space Mountain Lab Retriever,
which I'm trying to remember what that even is.
Is that a Disney World?
Computer engineer for the 70s.
Yes, they do on Spaceship Earth. Yes.
And I have her too.
They have, let's see, Lab Retriever.
Is that there's a dog?
Is there a dog like when?
Is this something with a there's a dog in like a with like a Victrola?
Was RCA a sponsor?
Yeah, that's that's what this is.
Yeah, yeah. OK. I've never I don't know this section
because this is before my time at Disney World.
But yeah, OK, RCA was the sponsor.
So it's a little dog next to a record player.
Wow. I've never seen this before.
The Haunted Mansion guy holding the gun
in the portrait that turns around with the gun.
Well, you would need both.
You didn't. Yeah. Well, I was just when you mentioned Haunted Mansion earlier,
I was like, why don't I have any merch of the Dueling portraits?
Right. Yeah.
Somebody wrote on here, Steven Tyler with Mike Stanton.
That'd be good. We know what you want.
That'll be my third Steven Tyler toy.
What are the is there like a Simpsons?
And no, that's right.
You got me the Funko Pop.
And then I have a Simpsons Steven Tyler as well.
Well, so I would like a friend of Park Star.
Yeah, go ahead. Yeah.
I was going to say, because there is an Albert from Mystic Manor.
Yes. Yeah, I have him. Yeah.
Is it Henry Mystic?
Oh, yeah. Any of those sea guys?
Right. Yeah, some sea guys.
Well, I also was going to say that, like, yeah, they're like girls.
Camelia Falco, like Tony Baxter, character.
Vinyl. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's a shame. Yeah.
Joe Rody, Harrison Hightower.
But what I would prefer is a very realistic looking figure that looks exactly.
They've scanned Tony's face.
He looks just right.
That's what I would prefer.
But if there's any hope of getting Tony back on the show,
do not start talking about how you want like a little posable Tony Baxter
to snuggle with at night and to dress up in a breakfast sausage.
I'm not talking about munchling Tony Baxter or New Meo Tony Baxter.
Making sure.
Although, wait a minute, we already burnt the bridge with both of your parents.
So we're not going to now burn it with Tony.
Hold on a second.
If New Meo wanted to do Imagineers and we could dress the Imagineers in little clothes,
then maybe I'm on board.
I go to the bathroom while you work this idea out.
You want to put Marty Sklar in like a little puffer vest, which I do.
I can't be so distant because like, all right.
Just ask me, do you want an action figure of Marty Sklar?
Yes, absolutely.
Do you want to be able to dress up Marty Sklar in a little outfit?
No, you freak.
You took it too far.
Well, I'm only a little weird.
This is starting to become the Mr.
Belvedere support group sketch from SNL.
I call him Brock Toon.
Yeah.
So I so there is something if they wanted to start making Imagineers
as these new characters, like any version of Imagineer I am,
I'm in favor of and would probably buy if they want.
So series one is, you know, it's Tony, it's Joe, it's
Claude Coats.
Well, is it?
I don't know what Claude Coats looks like.
Claude, we got to go with icon.
We got to go with I know the face.
I think that's really Mark and Alice Davis.
Maybe one.
Maybe, uh, uh, getting Marty Sklar's in there.
Yeah, Bob Gershir.
Yeah, I think that's a girl's got to have a toy.
There was somebody.
Didn't they make a fungal pop of Bob Gershir or something?
Somebody made Bob Gershir merchandise.
He's got like a clothing line now.
Yeah, he's got a talk show.
I'm not sure what happened.
I'm thrilled for him.
I'm just like, what's going on?
Going up the girl industry.
I'm happy for him.
Yeah.
So maybe there are some girls girl would have a new meal.
And then later, I think you'd, you know, not to say not do it.
I'll buy a coats.
I just think I just I can't picture what Claude Coats.
Claude Coats is wave three.
That's wave three.
That's wave four.
That's when you're starting.
That's when you're doing Joe Lance's zero and Bruce Gordon.
And it's maybe Scott Trowbridge is famous enough to be wavy.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, you want a couple of a couple newer people.
Yeah.
In wave two.
So it's not all old folks.
And you know, before you even get to before you've even made a single one of these tomorrow.
Give me that tomorrow.
Give me every outfit in the world for him.
Wow.
There's not one breakfast pastry.
I don't want to see daddy tomorrow.
You would buy him.
You would give him one of each new meal outfit, too.
So you could give him a new outfit every day.
Given the clear plastic backpack so he can get into the Honda Center.
You forgot to dress our son.
You were so busy dressing and undressing tomorrow.
So so, yeah, somebody also wrote here there are other people giving their wish list.
Divine, of course, which I think we recently talked about.
What?
Do you guys not know what I'm talking about?
I don't.
I think the vine is from Epcot.
And some might say, oh, no, sorry, Animal Kingdom.
And I have no idea what this is.
Really?
I thought we talked about it, but maybe I talked about it with somebody else.
Divine, you might cheating on us.
You might not have some other podcast.
Divine is the tree.
The tree lady.
We were talking about the tree.
OK, who we have not talked about too much on the show.
Scary tree.
Yeah, scary tree lady.
I know the Scott is going to be a problem for you.
No, thanks.
If we talked, maybe I tuned it out if we talked about it before.
But I don't know if she still appears, but it says Divine occasionally appears in Disney's
Animal Kingdom around 10 a.m. and 2 p.m.
Occasionally around the park entrance, sometimes camouflaged.
And there's different like like Divine is like kind of a green.
She's a woman, like a human woman with like a green face and then just like a bunch of
leaves around her so she can hide in the brush, I suppose.
And I guess she's some sort of like maybe stay in there.
Maybe turn your back.
I don't know. I wonder if anyone has seen Divine in person.
I don't know if she's still out or when the last time somebody saw her years and years ago.
Yeah, but can you be sure that you saw her?
You might have seen just a big bush.
Well, Divine episode coming soon when Scott least expect it when he's sleeping.
Well, one of us has to be dressed as Divine when he walks in.
Jason dressed as Divine.
The Peacock from Spectro Magic.
I can't picture that either.
But the Dolphi Spectroman is definitely one.
Unfortunately, that is a good one.
It is a good one.
You know what they had very specific that did make Park Stars?
The like ribbon creature from the Millennium Celebration at Epcot.
Is that what that is?
Yeah, Discman.
Discman.
I don't actually have Discman.
But that is one that they have.
I guess Ellen from Ellen's Energy Adventure.
Well, I would like that.
I want it to be as disheveled as the one I just got to stand next to in the Van Eten gallery.
Right.
Collapsing.
And that's the one where the charm of it would almost be lost if they cutified it in a Park Stars way.
You would want it to be more of a figure that looks disheveled.
I'd like to see them try though.
Try to do a cute version of 1996 Ellen.
I'm not against it.
1996 Ellen.
I mean, yeah, Trump, Park Star, they're not doing a Biden Park Star.
They're done with the presidents.
I wonder if the Hall of Presidents, we thought it was going to be done last time, but maybe
like this next round, let's just, let's get rid of it maybe.
But there's a lot.
I think there's a lot left.
And then there's other characters they just haven't done.
And I don't know if there's any chance of them ever at least doing Park Stars again,
but it looks doubtful to me.
How do you know they should do a Partners statue?
Oh yeah, that's good.
Yeah, sure.
And they could do the Walt sitting, the Epcot Walt sitting one.
The unbuilt, the pooping one.
Sure, did they build that?
No, they built it.
They did build it.
He's pooping in Epcot.
Oh, that's right.
They put in the pooping one.
Less extravagant for sure, but yeah.
So there's still, I mean, they got to attribute all the new stuff from the parks, like the
grass and the cornhole games and the hula hoops.
They could do cornhole, yeah.
A mild bush, the small bush they put in.
I think that's good.
Yeah, all the new stuff.
There's some new characters on the Tiana ride too.
I think specific new characters to the ride.
Yeah, there's a lot of cute animals playing instruments.
There's an armadillo that people are really excited about.
Okay.
So yeah.
Well, and I want those Pan Galactic pizza board characters that I want the most.
Tony Solaroni, Officer Zizek's twin international cousin of Sunny Eclipse.
That's the stuff I want.
I forgot that there is a plush of Tony Solaroni.
Price is high on that because it's a Japan exclusive.
I'm looking it up right now.
They had a smaller version of them too, I thought, but maybe not.
Oh, really?
Japan does these blind, they love blind boxes there and they have so many cool little things
in their ride vehicles and characters there.
It feels like their merch is better than our, everything is better there, blah, blah, blah.
But yeah, I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe they don't have a smaller one.
Maybe I'm misremembering.
I'm seeing one on eBay.
It's plushes.
I mean, I'd like to have that, but I don't know if I'm paying a hundred bucks for it.
This is the thing where I get so spoiled with certain other, like the Ninja Turtles and
other things is because then what you could start to do with Park Stars or any other merch
is you could start to make characters of never built things.
This is like, you could make a Plectu's Galactic Reveal.
You could make characters that we've only seen in concept art and stuff and different
versions of things.
You could have, I don't know, country bears in the different outfits from the three different
shows that they've done or whatever.
You really could start to get obscure with this stuff.
But Disney, yeah.
Josh, tomorrow on the swing, on Swing and Teddy Bear's swing, squeeze it up next to
her or just solo, it's really, I mean, it's up to you, just pairs.
How many characters can tomorrow be hanging out with?
Yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
Or it's a great idea, I mean, so I feel like I could like map out like ten line, like waves
of a perfect theme park figure line full of like, you know, crowd pleasers like Dreamfinder
and Figment and then you put in like Plectu as well and put in other characters and put
in an Imagineer or two, put Sneak Eisner in as like a Build-A-Figure or something, you
know, something to get all that stuff in that we want.
And there's got to be-
Michael Clarke Duncan doing an introduction to Armageddon in France.
Yeah.
Yes.
Benicio, the street clothes, Benicio del Toro doing the introduction for the Guardians ride
at the opening ceremony or whatever George Lucas is wearing at his Michael Eisner opening
Star Tours ceremony in the 80s with the care, like Mickey and Goofy in their like outfits
and stuff.
Michael Jackson in disguise attending the Captain EO opening.
Yes.
Did he do that?
That's a rumor.
Oh, okay.
It's possible that happened.
If that's too outlandish, if we don't think that really happened, then Jack Nicholson
attending the Captain EO opening as Angelica Houston's date.
Right.
Yeah.
We could really-
Whatever he was wearing.
We could really do it up.
This, you know what?
This is something I might actually do by the time this comes out.
I will write out like 10 waves of figures that I want.
Wow.
Maybe I'll do five.
We'll see how ambitious I get.
Yeah.
But it is a fun, it is fun.
Actually, really now I'm just, will you do me a favor if you do that?
Is it okay if a line is just everyone who attended the Captain EO opening?
Yeah.
Because then you get, I think like, you know, it's like Patrick Duffy, it's Coppola himself,
it's I want to say OJ Simpson.
We got a good lineup in there.
Wow.
Well, what you would do generally, you would try to, I think you would want to spread those
out in every wave.
Okay.
It depends.
So you don't get sick of it.
Then you don't get people not buying the whole set.
Exactly.
So people will be like, well, you know, I got the Captain EO opening wave.
It's not as exciting to me.
You want to sneak in a Coppola in one of them and then you want to sneak in.
Yeah.
Belinda Carlisle.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Robert Palmer.
Uh-huh.
It doesn't make sense.
Why is, like the moody blues are all the same height, but famously the bassist is shorter
than the singer.
This is as crazy as Dreamfinder and Figment.
God, it makes me want to do the Captain EO opening.
Can I throw out the, because I was thinking like, you know, we've said something we've
gotten away from maybe is like episodes about specific characters, which I think has been
a good format here.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
We've done it here and there.
If we, let's go with the characters who were in this room right now.
Maybe just, can you tilt yours up, Jason?
I'll make my, like of the ones that you brought.
If we had to pick one to piece off an entire episode about, because this is a good way
to go.
Oh yeah, yeah.
All right.
To tribute an entire character.
Right.
Which there's, you know, plenty you could do.
Almost there could be just a full other Rex episode.
All of them might be redundant.
Yeah.
We've talked a lot of Rex before.
But like, there's good candidates here.
Here, I'll lift mine.
Dynamite Goat is a possibility.
Orange Bird.
Is an interesting one.
That might be the most attractive one off the top of my head.
Wally Bogues.
Wally Bogues certainly coming.
We haven't really touched on him, but Dog with Key and Mouth from Pirates.
That's good too.
We obviously haven't done Pirates in general.
Yeah.
I'm thinking Orange Bird.
I mean, Phantom is such an interesting character to me.
I'm wondering what else is out there as far as info on the Phantom.
But I don't know if Phantom can be separate from Phantom Manor or should it be?
I don't know that either.
Is the pick maybe, is it Orange Bird?
I think Orange Bird is the answer.
Well, let's do an Orange Bird and let's do Into the Plush Pile.
You go learn everything.
You go start doing your research.
Hole up in that room that your mother is not allowed in and allow me to pretend that I
am interested in all the differences between nemos and mush-mushes and everything that
there is just as cover to get more of my parents' psychology specifics out.
Okay, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll forget.
No, I just want to talk about the different models.
Okay.
Now, what did your grandmother think of all this?
It's just a therapy session, really, what this is.
Anytime I get to talk about toys.
I'll need to give you key.
You will need to come by and save me because if I get too much plush, I'm just going to
want to snooze under them and I want to suffocate under all this fabric and vinyl.
Under them?
Under them.
Yeah.
Oh, those big plush piles at toy stores.
I was always like, let me crawl, let me get in there.
My daughter has a big plush pile in this little tent in the living room right now.
So if you saw it, you would have no, you would just go right forward and just go to sleep.
Oh, do you want me to pop over and try to see if I can, I'll pay for the dry cleaning.
I've got coupons.
Why would you have to dry?
Because you're going to sweat all over them?
Yeah, sometimes I get sweaty.
You're going to secrete on them?
I don't know.
Ew.
This is your real daughter.
He said it.
I did not.
He didn't say secrete.
He did not say secrete.
I was just trying to be considerate that if I was going to sleep.
As someone who is entering your daughter's plush pile, I'm going to get them all dry
cleaned.
You see?
That's considerate.
That's a normal thing.
You're right.
We're all saying all episode has been normal.
Sweating is, by the way, secreting.
I didn't mean, like secreting is just stuff coming out.
Yeah, but you said it in the nastiest way.
I did not.
I just don't want the plushes to smell like, I don't know.
Snodder?
Did you think it got in?
It's not weirder when Mike said secrete.
It's because of what was earlier in the episode.
It's because you had it in your head that way and then I just said that specific term
because I'm a smart guy with a good vocabulary and everyone's on my ass about it.
That's what's happening here.
It's incredible that that usurped the strangeness in general of what Jason said.
Actually wasn't it your suggestion that Jason crawl into your, into the plush pile?
I don't even want to start repeating weird phrases.
You have a plush pile meant for your daughter.
I was just clarifying what he meant.
He said it and I was clarifying what he meant.
I don't want it to smell like tied in the green cool rush.
I'm just trying to show this picture of Eisner and Lucas and Mickey and Minnie in those fun
rainbow space space mountain or Tomorrowland outfits and say like,
You think that's going to fix everything?
You think that's going to make us forget everything that's been said in the last two minutes?
Epcot space character outfits is good.
I mean that's Vogue profile, that Vogue photo spread was going around recently.
They don't have good, other than that expensive Tokyo Disney, they don't make good suit like
toys for the main characters, Mickey and Minnie.
There's something that's pretty close right now in shop Disney for Mickey and Minnie,
but they're like in these weird outfits and Minnie is the body of a human woman.
It's kind of strange, but it's close.
The heads are close, but what I always wanted.
That's so confusing for you.
You don't want that.
No, no thank you.
It's just, you know, it's like I need to know that at the end of the day she's a mouse
and I shouldn't be going near it.
But the more, you know, but if she has the shape that I'm familiar with and let's be
honest attracted to, I'm going to start getting some ideas soon enough, I'm secreting and
then this toy needs to go to the dry cleaner.
This is what we're dealing with.
This is what they're selling.
This is what you described as having a human shape?
Yeah, they are kind of, it's kind of a human silhouette.
Minnie is a little more, yeah, like thin in her arms and her body than she is in the
park.
The suit is not like that.
You are still showing her in a red dress with hearts all over it.
It's just so human.
You know, it's just like, I think it's honestly kind of an inappropriate toy to be selling
because people are going to start getting ideas.
Look at her.
You see that dress.
You see those shoes.
Look at her legs.
Shapeless calves.
They used to be puffier.
You can kind of see their clear human arms and legs now.
Yeah, they don't have, they need to make all the characters like that.
They can't be making figures with such caressable calves.
They need to make them more, like they look like a suit.
That's my gripe with it.
That's what I want.
Jason, you want the suit toys?
Yeah, but I want them a little more whimsical.
What do you mean by that?
Like puffy, like the character outfits used to be.
I'm agreeing with you.
Thank you.
I'm saying too much human shapes.
You're giving me ideas.
Thank you.
This mini needs to cover up.
That's not what I'm saying.
Not what I'm saying.
You're saying normal things, regular things for people.
What I'm saying is normal.
Normal things, hip things.
That's what's being said in this episode.
Well, I am saying yes.
I do say hip things.
Whatever happened about, you know, sometimes what's more attractive is what's not revealed.
Well, that's true.
Michael, let me take a look in your office.
And that's why the next second gate will be us storming into Mike's office with his mother.
Oh, I'm not allowed in there either.
I'll just get too rambunctious, too ramby, and I'll just start knocking things over.
Yeah, I don't want that.
So I don't know.
That's the end of the episode, I think.
I think we're good.
Let's get out of here.
I think we've got to get out of here.
I think we survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon to your Club 3, where you
get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
We cannot promise that all future episodes around here or on Club 3 will be as strange
and creepy, but I think it's a pretty safe bet that Into the Plush Pile will be, if not
more so.
I think that's right.
You get a free gift if you buy this set, this Mickey and Minnie set it says.
I don't know what that is.
Wow, a bookmark.
An artist will draw a very, a very tender portrait of you and Minnie making love.
Oh, okay.
That's pretty good.
Oh, I accidentally put two in my shopping cart.