I'm gonna play some bets that is the way Will they announce Pandora at DCA?
I'm gonna guess what Josh Demarro's gonna say, bet on it, bet on it, bet on it, bet on it.
Uh, some Sky Garner, yeah, how about that?
Do you recognize the song offhand?
Do you know what that song is?
No, I wasn't sure if it was an original.
No, oh I wish, if only, no, that is from High School Musical 2 with amended lyrics.
That's sort of, that's Troy slash Zac Efron's song of torment which he performs solo on a golf course.
Wow.
I don't really know the rest of the movie or the, oh but it's great, he like looks at his reflection
in a golf course pond and does a bunch of kicks and it's, I don't know, I assume it really carries
the weight of the movie, again I wouldn't know, I've only seen that, it was exciting to sing that.
I'm not gonna stop, not gonna stop till I get my shot, that's who I am, that is my plan,
gonna end up on top, uh, recommended, good clip.
That's good, yeah.
So, but I sang that because we are gonna bet on it.
What's it, you ask, the D23 Expo Disney Experiences Showcase.
By the way, I'm Sky Garner, that's Mike Carlson.
Hello.
And there's Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And we're all gonna, we're all gonna bet on it.
Let me do some dry explanations of things, feel free to interrupt and goof, but just to
clarify some basics.
As you're hearing this, this upcoming weekend is D23 Expo, the ultimate Disney fan event.
This is occurring as it does every two years, correct?
There's also these Destination D23s, but this big one is this big event in Anaheim,
very close to Disneyland, it is happening on August 9th, 10th, and 11th.
And we are doing a little bit of programming around D23, and specifically what we're gonna
find out at the Disney Experiences Showcase, which is the boring title for the thing where
they announce park shit.
That's what we call it in our hearts, is the park shit panel.
So, a couple of sort of related episodes.
This Friday, the 9th, on the main feed, we will finally be doing the episode Fixing Tomorrowland.
We will reveal our plans, low budget, mid budget, and blue sky, big budget, of how we
would fix Tomorrowland in anticipation of any announcements involving the real Tomorrowland
and the real plans that we could be getting at Horizons, the Disney Experiences Showcase, correct?
Okay, I might be missing some colons or some dashes or something.
That event, however, is happening on Saturday night the 10th, 7pm, a nice inconvenient time,
especially for the East Coast, an inconvenient time for stuff we wanted to do, like do we
look extreme right after, what do we do?
Here's what we have landed on.
We are gonna record together as early as we can on Sunday, and then post an episode as
soon as we can on the main feed, instead of our usual episode that Friday.
So instead of a Friday episode five days early, you're gonna be getting on the main feed
for the first time our reactions to the D23, hopefully, news.
Hopefully, good news.
Or else we have really put a lot of stock, which would be a perfect fall for us to take.
Change is the only constant, you know?
It's the only thing you can count on, and you can count on that and count on, like,
we've got some ideas that we're not ready to share yet, but the sky is blue.
I'd say you could count on that more than you can count on change.
That's the problem.
I'm worried there's not gonna be enough change.
Change should be on the ballot.
I agree.
Sure.
I mean, I would love it if they did a D23 presentation, like the last few,
but they have the Honda Center packed.
Yeah, that's the thing.
This panel is not happening in a big ballroom in a convention center.
It is happening in a hockey arena, and the size of this implies you would think
that we are finally going to get some big good news, something worthy of filling an arena with,
and it sort of feels like this is the last chance for them to stop pulling the shit they have been
pulling of, well, there's something we could be, there's something we've been kind of starting
to wonder about thinking about, dreaming about, maybe for 10 years from now.
Right?
I mean, like, again, we might be in Charlie Brown football territory yet again,
but it does seem like this is do or die.
I've seen Jimmy Buffett at the Honda Center, I've seen Bruce Springsteen at the Honda Center,
and now Josh DeMoro is going to take the stage.
The three greatest of all time.
At the Honda Center.
And the Honda Center is the venue that used to be called The Pond.
Yes, the Pond in Anaheim.
So the hubris for booking that venue and then calling it Horizons, I've said this a couple
times on the show already, that is wild to me.
That is taunting the average Disney fan to get your expectations sky high.
And they've got the money, they just did another round of layoffs, 140 people in the television
division, so they, what's like 40,000 times 140, like they can afford some rides.
They can finally afford some rides, yes, because of these layoffs, which we were worried about.
Glad we got rid of.
We hate layoffs unless it causes a new ride.
That's our stance here on the show.
Yeah, it's like, I don't know, it's really a make or break moment and I can't help but
equate it to kind of a different make or break moment that's been occurring in the recent
past and this is not, this does not exactly line up, I think you'll find that it does
not line up morally, but the fact that Disney is kind of set in its old ways and not recognizing
the threat on the doorstep, in this case that being Epic Universe, it kind of reminds me
of another stodgy institution that starts with a D, the DNC, not realizing that the
threat of a second Donald Trump presidency is very real.
Now I hate to equate Trump and Epic Universe, that's not right.
I'm very excited about Epic Universe and I'm way more excited about a second Trump presidency.
I'm just saying, it seems like in the recent past, metaphorically, Disney has been more
than willing to run Biden, to stick with the plan, he says he wants to do it, he says that
he's fine, so let's get him out there and that's what we're going to do.
No way, no way, it's Brad Summer and the Kamala campaign quickly adopted that, so we're going
nuts. This is what we're waiting to find out is, is it Brad Summer? Are they going to make a big
change that energizes the base and that recognizes what's coming and what they're up against?
Do they get us all excited in an arena or do they trot out an old man who's kind of the equivalent
of saying, we're in a blue sky, we're blue sky and we're doing Coatino, we got Coatino,
come on. Look, I think Disney is coconut-pilled, I think we're doing this,
I think we're doing it, I think we're doing it. Is it cornhole or is it coconut? What is the future
of the Disney company? Let's do it. Yeah, well, we'll find out how coconut-pilled they are.
So we'll see, doesn't it feel like that's how, can we come out of this and feel like the tide
turned and that it's Disney's game again? Here's what I'll say overall, I think there's going to
be a lot more concrete announcements than in years past. I still don't think it's going to blow away
everybody like we want it to. I think it'll be like, well, that was a lot better than last year,
but I don't know, I don't think we're getting, maybe we're just getting right into it. I don't
think we're getting concrete Disneyland forward information. I think we're going to get maybe
teases of lands, but I do not think we're getting, and they're going here, this is going here,
here's the map of it. I think that is only sort of going to be lightly teased. I think it's too
early and I don't think they know themselves. Right, because to me that's what, for us at least,
on this coast, that's the big stuff we want. What is Disneyland forward? What does that look like?
Yeah, we've got the biggest expansion pad we've ever had. I mean, I guess not
DCA itself, but you know what I mean, a really big one. I hope I'm wrong about that,
but I feel like there will be a lot of good stuff. I don't know if there's going to be
anything blow away like Galaxy's Edge was many years ago. That's my feeling in general. We'll
see though. Well, here's what we're doing to make this more interesting on ourselves, is that as
we've declared we want it to do, we are actually doing it. This episode is all about betting on
what's going to occur at the D23 Horizons Disney experiences panel when Josh Demaro comes out.
By the way, I hope that we're, I'm assuming that there's like a YouTube feed of this or else a lot
of our plans fall apart, but presumably as we've had in the past, there is some sort of live stream
that lets us be there, lets us experience the magic from our homes because we are not going,
we did not get tickets to this event. There's a chance I'm going, but I don't know yet.
Oh really? Wow, wow, wow. Okay. Interesting. Well, then you'll have to tell us how thunderous
the reaction to some of these things. I hope you can make it through an episode the next day
without a massive hangover because I know you're going to be doing shots that whole time.
Oh yeah, I have a flask on the floor. I'll come back to the seat like at a basketball game. I
have a big like a thing with a hot dog in it and a big beer, like sitting front row waiting
for Mr. Demaro to tell me what I'm going to ride in seven years. Yeah, it sounds great.
I guess I am curious about that is if it is the regular consent. Yeah. If you wanted to,
without bringing it yourself, can you get drunk at the experiences panel?
Yeah. Well, don't they sell, we've been, did you go to D23? I think they sell beer on the
convention floor at D23. There are a ton of drink stands around the convention center.
So I think you can get pretty lit up. Can beer, can wine, can cocktails. You can really party.
Yeah. So it would be chaos if they had that on the floor at San Diego, I feel like.
Yeah, yes and no. I mean, I think San Diego is, I don't know, we can debate how drunk everybody
would be at San Diego, but I think it would be okay, but it's very crowded there. It would be
fun. More crowded. Sure. Well, sure. Yeah. So yeah.
So we, and we're still kind of figuring out our plans here, but we have like general areas,
right? That we think like very, very possible announcements, things that we think are riskier
bets. And, but what the intention here is to actually make bets with our own money against
each other and see who comes out on top in terms of getting this panel correct. Does anybody want
to assess their own level of confidence here? I don't know that I feel the most confident to
be honest, and I shouldn't like put those cards on the table, but I'm just not on the rumor.
Yeah, you don't do this as much as I do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think Mike is the guy to beat.
Yeah. Mike, I think is guy to beat. I had to look up some of the recent stuff. I feel like so much
is like floated, like a balloon, like a test balloon. Like I was like, wait, did they announce
the tropical? Okay. They didn't announce the tropical Americas redo for dino land and animal
kingdom, but there's not a lot of specifics. Yeah. Like that's happening. The Indiana Jones
thing, a redo of dinosaur is happening pretty much. That's the feeling I'm getting where it's like,
there's permits have been filed. But there's not a name yet. Right. There's not, there's not a name.
I guess that's, that's what the other, the concrete thing is. I don't know much about how I feel about
the rumors, but I love gambling. It is a problem. It could be a real problem. Well, you've looked,
you've talked about it on the show before. I love gambling for very low stakes. You're Mr. Penny,
you're Mr. Penny Sluts. I was about to say you love gambling, but yes, but on Penny Sluts.
Do it now. Would you like this to be a one cent operation? Right? No, I well, that's the foolhardy
thing of Penny Slots. You're really 50 cents slots. That is foolhardy. Yes. You're right.
Why won't they let you just bet one single penny? I think Vegas is fucked the morality there. Just
blow it up. I say, I believe when you revealed your borderline addiction to penny slots on the
Vegas episode last year, I think I made some sort of comment and you said, Michael, it's becoming,
it could become a problem or something. You were very sincere about that. I could be down 79 cents.
My man. I did play the little shop machine down from $195 to $7. Sure. So, but some of that was,
but some of this was an episode with Gabris where he's like, I lost $5,000.
You and me, buddy, we're in the same boat here. Boy, the gamble heads,
they're going to bury us naked because we bet all our clothes.
But it was still, I could have gotten a nice meal for us. Sure. But you were having fun.
Yeah, I was having fun. You're going to have fun today as I take you for all your worth.
I'm going to sucker you into so many bets today. You're going to be wearing that barrel with the
straps, pal. But he's been dreaming of that since he first heard the reference. No, he's trying. I
wore the barrel with the straps in today. So can I do, here's what I think is a sure bet. Can I start
us? Yeah, sure. Yeah. I think they'll announce the name of the Indiana Jones redo. Okay. I believe,
I agree with you. Okay. Well, that's not, see, there should be some disagreement here.
I guess, well, this is what we're going to bump into if we don't get, well, all right, this is
the kind of thing maybe we can take like specific. Also what, all right, we also have to establish,
what is it, what, what amount of money are you betting on that, Jason? I, we, we were talking
about like, uh, what's the entry level five, five dollars. I'll go five. Let's go five. Sure. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not taking this back, but yeah, five, they're going to announce that. I think that's
coming. You think we're getting name? I think so. Cause that's, that's so far along. That's why I
think like that's for sure happening. Work permits filed dinosaur is closing. Okay. Well then here,
all right. Here's how I, maybe here's a way to make it. I will, I will take like an, I will amend it
and say, I think we'll get specific. I think they will officially say out loud that it's Indiana
Jones and inconto, and we will not get names thrown out because isn't that, that's a way we
could do this is like, I like, we agree with each other. However, I think we're only getting concept
art. We're only getting like vagaries. So let's just to, just to start us off with something,
I will say no name confirmation, but no name. And you say name. Yeah, I say name. Okay.
So that's the, I guess the bet is on there. Really name versus no name. Great. Okay. It's
long shot bet. Does Harrison Ford come in? Well, I have that written down is Harrison Ford on stage
for this announcement. Now, if you want to do a little detective work, like I like to do,
he is a Disney legend this year. He is being named a legend. That being said,
you shouldn't have said that. That being said, the ceremony is the day after, not the same day.
Yeah. I don't know if they're getting two appearances out of the,
I don't know. And they also just had him at a comic con. He was at a comic con. He's goofing
around. He, did you see that? He was goofing around as the Hulk made a face. Yeah. He likes,
he's also, again, we it's he's fake. He's cranky and stuff. He doesn't bubble. He looks guy likes
to have fun. This guy enjoys being around. They can get, they could get them down to Anaheim,
put them in a hotel. And if he's already there, and if he's already there, they do like to bring
people out. They brought Dick Van Dyke out for the Mary Poppins thing that they never built.
A couple of years ago. So they would like to have Harrison on stage there. And it would be really
cool if they announced that it will be Harrison's voice on the ride, like it wasn't. Yeah. In
Disneyland. Yes. So I kind of think Harrison's coming out on stage during this part of the show.
Let's see yours. That's so convincing. I don't know if I want. You don't have to take it. I'm
just saying this is what I'm, this is what I'm guessing. This is a guess because he's going to
be there. And it seems like in the new modern Disney company, a big effort is made to make sure
that the stars of said movies are represented on the rides. Yeah. Yeah. Which reminds me,
there was just the Epic universe announcement of like, and you'll join Harry and Hermione.
I'm confused by that. What is that going to be? I have no idea. I don't think Daniel Radcliffe's
shown up to de-age himself. No, he's 40 years old. Yeah. What incentive is there? And they all,
not all of them, I like how many of them seem to have problems with the creator of said franchise.
Sure. Yeah. So, yeah. Don't take me out. All right. Here's what I, all right. I will go,
all right. A hundred dollars that Daniel Radcliffe's on stage at D23. Okay. I would take you up on that
if that's a serious bet. Wait, no, wait. No, pull it. Oh, he's nightcrawler now. Sorry. Harrison.
I mean, how much is that worth to you? That's worth two dollars. I'll do a two, but I was going
to say if you were going to do that bigger, I wouldn't do it because it does seem right,
but I'll do it. I'll do a cheapo. Sure. Two. You and I on for two and Harrison showing up on the
panel. And my voice will be on the ride and it's Indiana Jones. We should guess on what the title
of the ride is. Indiana Jones and the dinosaur dilemma, which is what I've said for a while.
I want them to keep the dinosaurs on the ride and just throw Indiana Jones in there. I don't think
they're going to do that, but I have heard it's an original ride. It's not our ride. It's not the
Tokyo Disney version. It's going to be a new story with Indiana Jones. Indiana Jones and the
chalice of adventure. What word soup can we get? Who the hell is Chester and Hester?
So yes, okay. I do think we'll see, I think we'll see more stars as well if it fits.
Stars, voice actors and such. Yeah, yeah. Let me throw out, I believe we'll get
an Avengers name and I will also, an Avengers e-ticket name. I don't know if we'll get a lot
more information about what that is going to be. I'm talking about the DCA ride, but I think we
will get a name and I will further specify my bet to say it is mealy-mouthed and I don't know what
the hell it means. Okay. I think that I would not take that, but I agree with you. I think we'll
get a title for that. That has to be coming. They've already downgraded the ride and
impressiveness. Of course, the initial version seemed crazy and seemed very expensive and then
Chapec slashed the budget on it. Now it seems more like an Omni-mover. I've heard tell that
it's the technology that's very much like the Spider-Man Transformers ride that they're using
on the Peter Pan ride at the newly opened Fantasy Springs, which is a lot of screens,
but I think it's cool. It's an impressive use of it, but that's what the newer Avengers ride is.
I don't, and this is some of my pan bias. Go ahead. I look at that ride and I'm like,
yeah, I guess so, but I don't know. Maybe my mind would be blown if I were on it. I saw people
saying similar things about just watching a video of the Zootopia Shanghai attraction,
which Jackie's was raving about, and that one communicates to me more. I watched that ride
through and I see how it's better than the pan doesn't feel like anything truly mind blowing.
I could see how it's fun, but I don't know that it's very good. I don't know that it feels like,
oh my God, and maybe the way they have it now, because I could see on some,
from just the YouTube video, some of the show scenes, you have more of your field of vision
blocked kind of, so it really, I feel like maybe makes the screen feel like even more immersive
in a way. I don't know if there's like crates and stuff stacked up over here and then you're
looking at the actual movement on the screen. Your focus is drawn a little more. Yeah, but I
don't know. I don't know. Yeah, I don't know. Does that mean do we all believe then that we get
Avengers e-ticket name? I believe that, yes. Jason. Yeah, see, I was going back and forth if
there is more of a fire under their ass with all the announcements of Dr. Doom,
the Russo is coming back, but I feel like that would be too fast to lock down details of the ride.
Oh, and maybe they want to kind of hedge their bets and wait to see what would be in our best
interest to base a ride around the new stuff, around Doom and such. Yeah, so I think maybe a
generic, like, Avengers defend Wakanda or something. Well, King Thanos is the villain. They
announced the villain last time. But they also announced a king and it's not king anymore. Well,
that's true. So we could change the- It could be changed. I just think that's unlikely because
they've said King Thanos and people like Thanos and they know who he is. I'm guessing it's full
steam ahead. We can figure out a bet here, but I'm guessing it's full steam ahead on whatever
version they have. But we all agree we think we're going to name. I think so. Wow. Yeah.
Nobody wants to take the no just to make it interesting. I'll make that a two. I'll make
that a nobody wants two bucks. Here's a bet. Yeah. We'll see if anybody disagrees with me.
Deadpool on stage. I wrote it down. I wrote it down on stage. Deadpool is now in the parks. We
haven't talked about this yet on the show. This just happened. He is making innuendo jokes. Body.
Body jokes in California Adventure. My. And I'm like, well, this is like the most, and I
shouldn't say thrilling. It's not thrilling, but this is the most, whoa, like we lose our country
bear bodiness. But I'm like, Deadpool is saying body for a Disney park. Like my head was spinning.
Splash Mountain jokes. References to Grindr. He made a Grindr joke. He made a joke about
Wolverine being a bottom. Wow. I was like, whoa. It's all happening. All right. Then I'll put money
that Mike goes to D23 to try to assassinate body Deadpool. Right. Cause I don't like it. Yeah. Yeah.
Put an end to this forever. I hope that show lasts. Cause I think we, I think story time with
Deadpool episode next month or this month. No. Yeah. This one is that the name of what they're
doing? Yes. Cause he sits there with a little book and he like reads a story to everybody.
The Wolverine comes out and they goof around. They make it sort of like a faux bell kind of
the four kids thing that is not for kids. And he gets to be topical. He gets to be taught like
topical. Yeah. This is a thing fully called by, maybe you could say the show in general,
but I feel like especially you, I think you really, you're calling it. Andrew Grissom saw
the show yesterday or two days ago. Said it was good. The audience liked it. You might like this
version of Deadpool better than the on screen version. The one in the film. The performer seems
like he's having a fun time. I am all caught up. Well, I haven't seen the new one, but I watched
the first two Deadpools. I have not seen the third one. Well, that's not all caught up then. I'm all
caught up on the archival. Okay. So, so the archival the Deadpool vaults the Deadpool vault.
I like them. I thought they're pretty funny. Uh, okay. We all kind of, I think agree maybe
Deadpool on stage with, with Kevin Feige or and Josh tomorrow, maybe. Yeah, that feels too. That's
exactly the kind of thing they've been doing. Right. He's across the street. Now let's ask.
Now let me ask you this question. Deadpool makes some reference to Josh tomorrow being attractive.
That's exactly what I had too, Mike. I can't go against you. What do you think? Yes, we both agree.
Jason, what do you think? Do you think Deadpool says anything like, Hey, good looking or like
anything, anything resembling like kind of a comment on this guy's hotter than Ryan Reynolds?
Uh, I'm going to say no. Okay. I want to take a long shot bet that Deadpool makes a joke
about other d23 announcements in the past that the parks panel being lackluster. Okay. So the
bet is now, do you get comments on attractiveness or do you get, do you get like a comment about how
the panel last year, like blue, like behind big thunder mountain, we didn't really see what was
behind there last time or, or it was nothing. Like it was. Okay. Here's what I'm going to do.
Uh, do we just like kind of put a pool, the Deadpool? Okay. Do we call this a five? Sure.
Actually kind of the origin of his name in the movie. It's from a pool. Well, it's from,
yeah, it's a betting pool. It's a betting. Oh, yeah. And he's going to die.
Eastwood mercenary is going to die. Oh, gotcha. Because I liked that as a joke, Mike, but I actually
don't, I don't think it's actually going to happen because I think the attractiveness of
Josh tomorrow is a pretty, that's pretty online only thing. So I, I, I'm not actually going to put,
I'll bet on it. Okay. Uh, um, so Mike bets attractive. We all think Deadpool on stage.
Uh, I think, uh, uh, okay. Mike thinks tomorrow is attractive comment. Jason thinks roasting previous
D 23s. I think neither of those and it's more bland, but we do get Deadpool. Is that fair? Yeah.
Yeah. So we all take a different, this is the way to do it. I think, because we're going to agree
too much. So if we find little, little wedges, I think that's great. And then what happens if we,
uh, and if we're, if we're all wrong, then we all have to take a $5 bill and burn it.
We have to, yes, destroy it because we donate it to something. No, no. Yeah. Take it out of, yeah.
Take it out and burn it off to circulation. Um, in the true spirit of theme park attractions,
what they should have is Deadpool at the very beginning should hijack the panel and stuff
starts going wrong throughout the past stage going wrong. Do you think there's any odds of that
happening? It's a good idea. No, it's too fun. Too interesting. It's too fun. Too interesting.
Here's, here's another one of these where we might get some micro differ. There might be ways to
like break off the bed. It, one of the things that's feels a little obvious and ready and
there they've been like doing those pseudo teases here and there is avatar that avatar is coming to
the Disneyland resort, but where here's the, is anybody up for a location based bet? And let me,
here's, here's why. And if you haven't heard this online speculation, um, there's strong rumors,
strong enough that maybe I should listen to it. They should, that avatar's going in Hollywood
land. They're blowing up monster zinc, all of those sound stages and the bus area, which will be
moved across Harbor. Um, so that also, so the park expands into what is currently a bus area. Yeah.
Um, I, I am going to say, I don't think that I, if to me, avatar feels tailor made for, uh,
Disneyland forward for like blue sky blank online rumors or no, I think, well, there's a couple
bets here, but I'd say my bet would be avatar is going in Disneyland forward. If anybody wants to
bet, they say DCA, but they don't say more. They say it is replacing Hollywood land. Does anybody
have thoughts on what you might want to grab in terms of avatar? I don't, the, the rumor that,
that the avatar land is going in Hollywood land is insane to me. It doesn't make sense.
Really? Yeah. Okay. I, all right. Why would that make sense? It's already like,
they've got Marvel on one side. Then you got old Hollywood in the other. And then there's just in
the middle of it. You're on Pandora. Yeah, that's my, that's my thing. And I saw some video that
pointed out that they, they do not want to move those monorail tracks and monorails exactly there.
Now I like the idea by the way, because if I fantasize about avatar goes there or avatar goes
in like, it's not going to be utopia cause they're doubling down on utopia, but uh, uh, subs,
whatever that, that monorail, I like the idea that like monorail goes in and out of unrelated
property. I just don't think that's how they think anymore. Right. I think that's a very 60s Disney
vibe. So, uh, so maybe this is not a bet that you're going to do. Not a bet I'm going to do.
Do you have any, is there anything you want to throw down avatar wise? I think they will show
more concept art for avatar. Okay. And I think maybe even a hint of what the ride is,
which I've heard rumors of it being the Shanghai pirates type ride, like a wifi boat ride.
But I don't think, maybe they will say it's going in Disneyland forward,
but I don't think we're getting location. I just think we're going to get more art. I think we'll
get, they'll talk about it. I'll, I'll say that they say DCA. I don't want to limit it because
maybe they do say a specific location, but I will roughly say that they say California adventure,
but that could mean Hollywood could mean across the street, Disneyland forward expansion of DCA.
Jason, any thoughts on avatar? I don't think I have strong feelings either. I mean, I think
it makes sense in a real estate perspective that it would take over a Hollywood. Now the thing that
there's no transitions. I'm upset. No, there's no transitions. And then I think I just have a very
low opinion of like, yeah, just bulldoze at all. Make a band to wear out. I don't know. The thing
that makes more sense would just be to wrap Marvel around more. Of course. Yeah, absolutely. I think
so. Yeah. Just, and you could probably take some of those structures and just paint them
more Marvel-y and get more Marvel stuff in there. A new rumor I've heard is that's going to be
Zootopia. Oh, and that makes sense. Any odds of that being said now? No, not a bit. Well,
well, it depends because Zootopia probably has a, there's like a, usually windows of exclusivity.
So perhaps if they say in five years or something, there's a chance, but it's, I just heard this
rumor. So I wonder if that like coincides with the fact that it's just sort of a newer idea.
I think Shanghai's too new and they wouldn't. That's what I think. Yeah. So I don't know that
they'd even want to tease it. I'd like to throw out the notion that, because I think one area
that we've limited ourselves with the little challenges is that like, you know, the bet has
to be on, right? I think we could do things where like, I'm only putting in $1 here, but if I'm
right, I get 50. I think if there's anything like that. Oh. Where there's no punishment for being
wrong, but it's like, I was trying to think of an equivalent, which is like, you know, if you,
I'm only putting $1 into an Oscar pool right now, but it's on twisters. I'm betting that
twisters is going to be the best picture of the year and next year's Oscars and that that's a
thousand to one odds. Is that a thing we can do? I will take a dollar bet on Avatar. What do you
mean? That H shows up at DCA. Yeah. That's where I'm at. That's where Scott agrees. Oh, that's where
well, wait, are we against Mike here? I was proposing that as a, like, do you, if you were
wanted to say, if I'm way weird, right about the Zootopia. Oh, um, uh, oh, Zootopia. Yeah. I,
I don't feel as strongly about that. I'll, I'll take it though that they announced Zootopia for
that area. Okay. Yeah, I'll do that. Okay. I'll take that. What do you want to free for if you're
right? Uh, $10. Just 10. Okay. That's very generous. Yeah. I don't need it. I don't need it.
We can start building these amounts. All right. How about this? Yeah. Open the flood gates,
all characters in Star Wars land. Oh, we're doing it. Okay. We're breaking the glass. C3PO,
all your friends. Yeah. Uh, 25 year old that looks vaguely like Mark Hamill. Luke Skywalker can be
there. Everybody in galaxy's edge. No, I'm saying no. I'm saying no. I'll do that bet with you. And
I, because, uh, here and here's, and it's less because, uh, of any annoyance I have with the,
my friends aren't there thing, which is strong. However, I think that they, uh, they like to like
take their time. They like to say, I think if they're going to do it, they're going to say
Han Solo is coming the end. And then six months from now, you hear another one flood gates,
no way flood gates. Okay. So yes. So in my scenario, they have to say the get like the
world of galaxy's edge is expanding. And now just around the corner, you can meet any sort of care.
Like if there's sort of a vague idea of opening the flood gates, do I still win in the sense that
like they are saying now they're not going to say that like, we're, we're throwing out the old
rule book of like, it has to be in one spot in the timeline. If they just say, they say,
you know, we're open, like, uh, unlimited amount of stories now can be told in galaxy's edge. And
here's a few of the characters you'll be able to meet. Only if I will, I would only agree to that
if it is clearly the one character is not or shapes even from, uh, original trilogy,
because that could so easily mean TV show stuff. Sure. Uh, I like this, this bet to me is only if
it's characters from the seventies and eighties. So if it's Vader, that counts. Yeah. So if they
literally just say, we're going to tell more stories and then they say, and now Darth Vader
will be roaming the streets. Then you get, then I get it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Some of these
might require parsing. Sure. Of course. And we'll do that. We like to parse. What's the number in
your head there? Um, uh, five bucks. I don't know. You don't want to go higher on that. Oh,
it depends on your level of, uh, how far do you want to take it? Jason, are you in on that? Are
you, uh, you think I'm wrong? I think you're wrong. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I think, then I think,
I think Jason and I are aligned. We're splitting then on avatar and on, uh, got it. I know. Yes.
Okay. I toss out a galaxy's edge thing. Yeah, go ahead. I am putting five bucks on no galaxy's
edge. No mention of galaxy's edge. Maybe a mention of like, and the story, you know,
just like, and it's still open. Then maybe that, but they bring Scotch Roebers. You say, yes,
you've heard rumors. Galaxy that just not closed. You're not closing it. I don't think there's an,
I am putting $5 no galaxy's edge. I'm not willing to go against you on that. Cause I,
I just don't think it's like a priority. I think there's other stuff they got to do.
It's not a priority or so you're, yeah, you're going, um, yeah. I mean, I'll take you up on that.
Obviously if I think this bet, so I'll take you, I'll take you up on that bet. $5. Okay. I think
that what I think is going to happen is there's going to be a lot of little stuff, which is kind
of why I'm thinking about stuff that is not so expensive. That might be kind of exciting.
I mean, that sounds like the modern Disney company. Right. And I still, I think they're
going to be a couple of big things, but I think stuff like galaxy's edge characters
is something you can get a big pop from in the Honda center. If you say C three PO is there.
I, I agree with you on little stuff. I just think they're still just trying to milk like,
look, it's the Mandalorian and grow. That's my feeling. I know they're going to parse it out.
But if they bring, if they, but, but with this bet, if they say, oh, you can meet, uh, the skeleton
crew or whatever that new show is, then I win that bet. I disagree. I'm only giving it. I'm
only giving it to you. If it's original trilogy new shows, they've already been doing this bet.
Jason's talking about, sorry. Yeah. The Jason, where he said there's not going to mention it
at all. Got it. I win. Okay. Yes. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Great. Okay. I'm not giving it to you on C
three PO because C three PO is in the new ones. And our two D two is already there. That's a little
bit of C three PO is not in this. You don't get anything for C three PO, but he's, the suit is
already there. If they say we're opening it up, if they just say, now you can meet C three PO,
I agree with you. I don't win the bet. But if they do some flowery language about expanding the
amount of characters you can meet and we're starting with C three PO, I still think I win.
I will do, let me do a, I'll do a sliding scale here. I don't think I'm not giving you the full
amount for that, but the full amount is, uh, original trilogy, but then, and I'm not putting
C three PO. All right. Well, we can parse. We can, we can debate that depending on what the language
of there might, you might have to hear an episode in the future. That's that just turns into fighting
and give me my damn money. Yeah, that might be Star Wars. If it wasn't complicated and unclear,
what was going on? I have something similar to what you just threw out, Jason, which is a bet
on a lack. I'm putting a little riskier because we're, you know, it feels like they've been edging
towards it. It's what we're talking about. I'm putting $10 on no tomorrow land.
Well, I'm putting money on the final announcement for the whole show. Whoa. Tomorrowland. Okay.
In Disneyland. Is this the same bet or is some, is it somehow, do you get a bonus if it's the final?
That's I, we could be the same bet. I don't know if it's a bonus. I, okay. So, so
how about it's like, you know, you, I give you a tip if it's the bonus. Sure. Sure. Okay. That's
fine. You can be a tip. Okay. Cause here's my logic. Here's my logic with this is they like to give
a big exciting announcement to the hometown crowd because those are Disneyland often. Like most of
them are Disney, like Disneyland people. Uh, there are people that travel, but generally speaking,
I think they like to send that crowd home happy. I don't know other than announcing the full
Disneyland forward or what they're doing or a third park or whatever that is. I don't know
what else they could do that feels big. Well, the answer is nothing that feels big. Right.
That's true. But if they've hyped it up Honda center coming other than a Zootopia or I guess
avatar in Hollywood land, I don't know what's on the table that would make the audience go nuts.
The only thing I can think of Disneyland wise is a new tomorrow land. Yeah. So I kind of feel like
that's the last announcement during the panel. I agree with you as excitement in a show. I just
don't think we've heard. I don't think we've gotten anything. And yeah, we've, you know,
we've been doing this show for seven years now wherever, like every three years, it's like,
I saw an Imagineer on the tomorrow on the people mover track. That's not anything. That's not
anything to me. I don't think we're getting it. Here's what I think. And this is maybe the
riskiest bet I'll make, but I'm going, I'm interested in making it. I think, and this is
unrelated to what I'll say about what I want my tomorrow and redo to be, but what I think
is going to happen is that we're going to get a tomorrow and redo space mountain stays the same.
Maybe there'll be some like overlay type thing on it or they'll like refresh it. They'll be,
they're going to replace Buzz Lightyear with something. Star tour stays. And I think
maybe new sort of people mover. Wow. That's like this year we're getting people. I think that's
the only thing they could do Disneyland wise right now that even seems possible to make people
excited because there's no forward is taking a long time. We ain't getting that for 10 years.
And I say, that's fine. Let's get it right. We're sure. Fine. But what else other than the Marvel,
the vendors ride, but I don't think that's going to be the show closer.
But remember there have been these shows where there is no closer, but they just sing a song
about wonder and then we're done. And I wouldn't put it past them to, I mean, it's going to be
more exciting than previous years. And by the way, I hope you're right. I really hope you're
right. Cause there's nothing I want more than a new tomorrow. And I'm cynical. I'm hardened. I
hear you. I don't believe it. But in two, in another decade, what is actually on the table
at Disneyland? It's the Avengers ride. It's whatever's going in Hollywood land, which I'm
still sure will take a while. And it's tomorrow. Land tomorrow. Land has, I think it has to get
done before Disneyland forward. So, and then what would be exciting to announce in tomorrow land,
unless they're completely gutting it, which they're not going to, cause that's very expensive.
There has to be some, when you announce new tomorrow land, there has to be something in there
that's new. Something has to be fun other than just like, Oh, we're painting it and whatever.
Buzz Lightyear is going to be a different IP or something now. So the only thing I can think of,
and I've, there's, I've heard little rumblings of this, but I don't nothing, nothing I'm sure of
like Indiana Jones. The only thing you could do is figure out some kind of people mover that you
could maybe rebuild around the land somewhere. And I know that's a risky bet. I think tomorrow
land for sure is final, but that's the only thing I can think of that you can do. I feel like there's
bets within this bet, because what I proposed was my it's $10 to me. If there's no mention of
tomorrow land whatsoever, you, uh, you get 10 with a tip. If it's the closer, do you, are you willing
to do something else about people mover? Yes. Okay. Uh, this is high risk, high risk, high
rewards. Well, you want to throw another five on it? I'll put a five on it, but you both owe me,
uh, a grand each if they announce a people mover, a grand. No, the five was for people mover.
All right. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. I don't think it's that crazy. I just, this,
Mr. Gamble over here doesn't seem to want to actually, well, a thousand pennies.
Yeah. I have a risky bet. Do we agree on yours? Yeah. No, no, no. And does Jason want in on any
of what Mike is saying? Yeah. I do want to get in on this. What do you think? I would mean no
tomorrow. I agree with Scott. I know tomorrow. I think no tomorrow. That's insane. There's
there tomorrow. And we're in high risk. I don't believe it. Have you not been alive for these last
25 years? I know, but they, it has, something has to happen. It has to be, unless you know the confines
of corporate culture and spending. There's nothing else to talk about. And you're thinking about
structuring a show and sending the crowd home happy. And I agree with you. Yeah. But just hearing
like, oh, there was a bunch of stuff cut at the very last minute before last year's thing. I'm
just worried. I've just worried they're going to do it again this year. So I want to take the
risky bet. They can't do it. I mean, they can cut something, but they can't. So we're now splitting
unless we're going separate thing. No, I guess that doesn't make sense. Okay. So it's Jason and
you are, you're also doing the people mover on top of it. I'm going to say that's wait.
He's saying no tomorrow. I mentioned it all. I said no tomorrow in reference at all. And on top
of that, there's an extra five, not an extra thousand for people mover. So you'll take both
the bets is what you're saying. I will take both no bets. I will take the same bets as Scott. Great.
Wow. I, Jason, I feel bad for ourselves that we're at this point. I want to be a dreamer
like Mike is a dreamer, but I just, they've, you know, they've watered down my ability to dream.
I'm hoping he's right, but I like a long shot. You know? Sure. If Mike is right, the joy I will
feel handing the money over in case we don't do this in a way that is cash. This I will do with
cash and I'll do it with a smile on my face because your bet has led to something that'll
make me happy in this world. What do you think of the closer of the show is? Do you guys have
any ideas? Okay. I have my risky bet. Okay. Okay. My logic is they have to at least show some
resistance, something offering in Florida at Disney world to compete with Epic universe.
So I'm betting that they do give more concrete details about the villain's land. Okay. Well,
they haven't even announced that yet, but you're saying an announcement is coming.
Yeah. I think they're officially announcing it. I have that on my list, so I'm not going to take
that bet. I'll go against it. I don't think it feels right. What's it? What amount do you think?
Well, I got creative with this. Okay. If I am wrong, I will take you both to Baskin Robbins
and buy you each a single scoop, cup or cone, your choice. Can I have sprinkles on mine?
Sure. There should be some other, we'll deal with sprinkles in a second. That's a perfect
little micro bet. Okay. But the seriousness of this bet, I am not allowed to get anything.
Oh my God. You have to watch us eat ice cream? I have to watch you eat. I mean,
I'm allowed to get a bottle of water if I'm dehydrated. If I win, you two have to take
me to Baskin Robbins and get me a double scoop, cup or cone. I don't know what I'll prefer that
day. I am not a double scoop guy, so this is indulgent for me. Are we allowed to buy ourselves
something? Yeah, sure. Whatever. Sounds like it's fine. Yeah. I don't know. Isn't it better though
if we can't eat ice cream? It does seem more. You know what? I'm going to put that in there.
I think Jason has to- I get double scoop, you guys don't get anything. Yeah. I think this has
to be a no because the torture of watching somebody eat ice cream. All right. I'm in on this.
Let's deal with sprinkles. Can sprinkles or other topping be if they get location specific with a
villain's land? If they say we're going to do it, but no location, then that's just the regular bet.
But if they say it's going behind Big Thunder, if they say it's some weird, some entire other land,
yeah, you don't even have to commit to where, but if they give us a specific location, is that the
sprinkle on top? So location he gets a sprinkle, no location he doesn't. Yeah. Correct. Sure. Great.
Okay. Okay. Because this could work out very well for you that you get a double scoop with sprinkles.
Right. If they say. Because do we think that's a Big Thunder thing? Do we actually have-
That's what they teased last time, a couple of years ago. They teased it behind Big Thunder.
They said, well, we don't know what lies behind it. And then they were like teasing different
ideas. And they did tease the villains for that. So that is the logical place for it to go.
They tease some other movies. Well, do we want to go, do we want to do another Deadpool and we,
and we guess what's, what they say about beyond Big Thunder because I sort of like the sound of
Coco because that feels like a kind of realistic, like not so villain. I think villain
world is like too exciting. That's been a dream on the internet for so many decades. And it feels,
and while I do think they'll come up with something really great for Coco,
that just feels like more kind of realistic to me. So let's say, so if, if there's anything
about beyond Big Thunder, I will say that it's Coco. Jason, do you want to say that's villain?
Oh yeah. I would say it's villain. Mike, is there anything else? Well, there's the rumor that it's
like a not as themed radiator Springs over there too. Some people say no, but then some people were
speculating. Do you have any desire to go in on that? Not to feel strongly enough? Not really.
Make this a small one, make it a two. Okay. All right. Sure. All right. Let's do that.
But I think they're going to reveal something for beyond Big Thunder for sure. I think that's for
sure something, whether it's that it's Coco or villains or both. Okay. I think that's happening
because they, that was the end of their last presentation two years ago. So I feel like
that's another thing that's maybe farther along. I'll throw out one.
This, this, I mean, I'm going to do go in a really specific lane here, which is a, a tease that
inside out is coming to the parks in some way without committing to what that's going to be
so that they have, and you know, here, I'll get even more specific. Inside out is coming to Epcot
that way either, well, it could be that or this, if they don't say it, then that leaves it open to
be former wonders of life, to be some imagination. Like we're, we're friends with figment joy and
everybody all hangs, all hang out with figment because I think that move, the smash success of
inside out too, it feels like they want to just like foot in the door, declare, don't worry guys,
we're doing something about inside out. So, so that's my, that's my guess is inside out coming
to Epcot and they don't say any more. The bet is off if they say more that I'll call it a $5.
Anybody want to go in? I think they'll say more. Hmm. Interesting. They'll say more. Wow. Wow. I
don't know where that would go necessarily, but I think they'll say more. I will take you up on,
I think they'll say more. Okay. But I do think inside out has been something they've been looking
at for a while. And does Jason want to get in on a, they don't say inside out at all. Yes. Okay.
This is a good one. This is a very good one. I do. Anything where there's three opinions,
I think is a great area. I do because that inside out imagination has been rumor for years
and striking while the iron is hot. Well, that movie is like the second highest grossing animated
movie of all time. Yes. That absolutely makes sense. However, they went out of their way
recently to say the redo of Epcot is finished. Good point. And that was so specific and also so
weird. Why would you do that? After with, with no satisfaction. No satisfaction. Other than
guardians being a big hit. Yeah. And, and so I think with that and the fact that test track is
down and they're redoing that, I think Epcot, my feeling, Epcot is similar to galaxy's edge. Like
you're not going to get much mention besides like, well, and it's done. Like, you know, check it out.
Yeah. Yeah. That does feel like, well, this is a good one. I think we're, yeah, we got a good
specific. I think they have calling it horizons. There has to be a big Epcot thing, whether it's,
and I haven't even thought through what I would, that bet would be, but like there has to be like,
redo a spaceship or this back on, or we're actually putting something where horizons was like,
well, you want to throw one out? Yeah, maybe you want to get a specific. It's a good question
because it's so confused. Like they, they're in such a tough spot with figment because figment
sells so much merchandise and they don't want to spend money on a new figment ride solely figment.
I could see them forcing figment on an inside out ride. Like he, I guess he makes sense with like
other emotions and stuff to some degree. And he's in the movie. It's an Easter. He's in the first
one. They could probably expand that ride track. Could they knock down the theater?
I don't think it's going to be the space your birth is back on the table though.
Yeah. Are you, do you want to put money on something at Epcot that we've never even thought
about yet? Is that too vague? It's pretty vague. What about it? Do you want to quantify it as an
Epcot E ticket? Would you dare go that far? Or do you want to step that down? D ticket and above.
I'm trying to think how to turn this into a tangible item. I know it's new. When does the
new fireworks show at Epcot start? Mike, it's been open for months. Okay, great. Do people like it?
What is it? It's not harmonious, is it? Luminous Symphony of Us. Oh, you mean that one? Luminous.
What is it called? Luminous. And people like it? I never get it right. I think it's fine.
Okay, because people didn't like harmonious. I liked harmonious. Gene liked harmonious.
Yeah, but you're a freak. What are you talking about? They took down all the barges. That was
the big thing. He's a freak for other reasons. He's a freak for other reasons. I know, I know.
He's a harmonious freak. Hey, look, freak like me needs company. She matched my freak, you know?
Joe Rohde on stage during an Animal Kingdom announcement.
Rohde back. What do you think? I agree with that too much. Okay. Jason, what do you think?
I think no. You say no. I say yes. Well, you guys do it. What do you want? A dollar? Five dollars?
Yeah, a dollar. All right, we're doing a dollar. It's kind of a dollar. Yeah, whatever. Yeah.
Not to, yeah, it's a hard one to be like, absolutely not. Never. Rock and Rollercoaster
replacement. Is that strongly rumored? They're going away. They've already lost the rights to
sell Aerosmith merch in the gift shop. That's news to me. I believe that's a couple months old already
and I think that right now they're just trying to figure out what is going to replace it. Well,
that's why Disney laid all those people off. They're not getting that Aerosmith merch money
in 2024. So I think it might be too soon, but I think within the next couple years it's happening.
I don't think they're saying it at this. Okay. I don't think so either. That ride was just down
for a number of months and apparently that was due to, I think it's a Vencoma coaster and there
is something in the contract where every 20, 25 years they do required maintenance and that likely
was why it was down for a few months. That is why it was down. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not saying they were
doing it. It wasn't due to wokeness. They weren't testing different. They're getting rid of our hero
who did absolutely nothing. They were not a good, upstanding man his whole life and in every decade
of the last six decades. They weren't testing different old men, rock and rollers on the ride,
I think. Bob Dylan was just- But they could have been. Yeah. He was up there, you know.
Oh my God. Bob Dylan Rock and Roller Coaster? Wow. That would be awesome.
Look, he was at the Hollywood Bowl last night. Yeah, that's right. If he was at the Hollywood
Bowl, then surely they'll make a roller coaster after his music. He's just riding the roller
coaster. Maybe we're just spiffing it up for a few months. He went electric, so certainly.
You know how I feel about my fans. Same exact thing. I wonder if we all get in a stretch limousine.
That is of course too coherent of a way he would say that.
He would really, the real thing would be like they're in the recording studio. He's like sitting
in a chair, sternly looking at everybody and then like a handler would have to explain everything.
Oh, just some, all the exposition is in somebody's- Right. Ken Marino.
So you have Ken Marino the lion's like, oh well then your fans all have VIP wristbands,
but now it's a matter of getting them to the concert on time. Do you think that we should put
them in a super fast stretch limo to get them on the concert on time, Bob?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. All right, you heard the man. So let's go, all right,
head into the next room and we're ready to rock and roll. Isn't that right, Bob?
I would love- I hope Bob Dylan is on the red carpet for the Timothy Chalamet biopic.
I bet he will be. And I hope he gets cornered by like,
hey, it's letterboxed. What are your top four movies? And he's like, I don't watch a lot of movies.
Mr. Dylan, do you agree that it's Brat Summer?
What? It's full now.
Mike, you've been talking about this. Oh wait, do we, do we get to a bit?
I'll say a dollar, that new rock and roller coaster.
That makes zero. I don't think we're getting it.
Zero, yeah. All right, I want 50 cents.
Those are little ones, yeah. You've been talking about this Walt
robot. You think we're getting it? Yes.
All right. I think that's coming.
You think we're getting it this year? You think we're getting it? We're a few days
away from a Walt robot. This ties into another bet I have.
I think yes, Walt robot. And how many times do we think Josh
Tamaro says the phrase platinum celebration, if at all, for Disneyland's 70th anniversary?
Because the 70th anniversary is platinum. Right.
So in theory. Right.
Is this like Price is Right, like without going over?
Well, Willie, do you both agree he's going to say platinum celebration?
I do think so. Okay.
Do you think that platinum celebration, I believe platinum celebration will be said
10 times in the whole presentation. I'm going to go more realistic and say four.
Okay. Jason. I'm going to go in between and say eight.
Okay. Yeah. Okay.
How much is this one?
Two dollars. Two.
That sounds like a two. Okay.
Great. Okay. But then yes, Walt robot in Lincoln.
It's another thing where things have been filed. There's paperwork that suggests something's
in there. And chances are it's either Walt robot or Walt projection thing. I think robot.
I'll do low stakes. No, I don't think, I don't know.
You don't think robot, you don't think anything at all?
I think it might happen. I don't know if we're going to get it this week.
I think this is the 70th anniversary. This is the big, this is one of the big things.
Like I'll just do, I'll do a low stakes two again.
Okay. Two. Jason, what are you thinking? Different character than Walt.
No, I don't think different.
Hades from Hercules is going in.
I think it is going in. I think it's a robot. I think it's going in Lincoln.
No, it is going in Lincoln.
But do you think we're getting an announcement?
Yeah, that's what we're saying.
It's not going in Pirates of the Caribbean.
You think we're getting it?
So now I'm against both of you.
Yeah, you're against both of us.
Okay. Yeah. All right. Well, it gives me a buck.
I mean, you're talking about platinum celebration.
I could get down there and buy some of that 69 merchandise.
Oh yeah. They still got that. I got to go. We're going next.
To go back to a few minutes ago, that's why Jason's a freak.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Yeah.
I am black now for all of July though.
Every day is the 69th anniversary when it's, when you're head to toe in Disneyland's 69 merchandise.
Jason, sweatshirt, sweatpants.
XXL, XXL. I just, it looks like you're pushing a cot in a wheelchair.
Like it's, it's looked like you're pushing a twin bed.
They're like, is there a person in there? Is that just sheets?
Deadpool should wear that merch while he's doing his show.
Oh, Deadpool should totally wear that merch.
Oh, just over his suit.
Yeah, he should wear an oversized t-shirt and he should point at it and not make it easy.
Huh? Huh? And there's no joke. And then they move on to the show.
I do like, I like that. I like that.
This kind of goes against, we're already talking about, is there any galaxy's edge or anything?
Do you think there's any discussion of what we're going to do with the Galactic Star Cruiser?
No.
No. I guess I don't feel enough like, but hey, how about, all right,
Buck that they say we're dreaming up new things for Galactic Star Cruiser.
I say no. I say no mention.
I say yes.
You say that.
So you're with Scott.
Yeah, I'll take a bet. I'll take a $1, a vague like-
But that goes against your previous Galaxy's Edge, no mention.
Right. You were contradicting yourself.
Galactic Star Cruiser is not Galaxy's Edge.
I disagree.
You think they're just going to mention Galactic Star Cruiser, not Galaxy's Edge?
It also would clearly be, maybe not clearly, I think it would be some kind of expansion of,
it'd be like a buy-on experience. I don't think there's a way you could say that
without saying Galaxy's Edge.
All right. I don't want to undo my earlier bet, so I won't take that bet.
Okay. So the bet has become no mention of Galactic Star Cruiser,
and I'm the only one going for yes?
I don't think that they'll ever say the words Galactic Star Cruiser.
If they were repurposing the building, I kind of feel like they would say,
we have a new whatever experience and it's this.
I don't know that they want to talk about the failed-
Because maybe it gets like a laugh at the-
Yeah. So if we can clearly tell that that's what it is, that's how we would,
like I'll still give it to you if they just,
if it's pretty clear they're repurposing the hotel for something.
Might have to be litigated more.
It'll have to be litigated more, but-
Okay. Well, then the stakes are low, so I'll say that one.
Right. I say no, I say nothing.
A new experience or something?
Right. But I'm saying like, it wouldn't be like, well, you know, we were so sad to see
the Galactic Star Cruiser close. They probably don't want to say that,
but maybe they say whatever. I don't know what they're going to do with that building.
I know they're thinking about stuff, but it's a tough spot to be in because they have,
it's a small place with hotel rooms and there's, I don't know, I'm not sure.
I think though, anyway-
Do you think that we, is there anything in the area of,
we just get more info about the test track thing that's already been said?
Yes.
Yeah. Do you agree?
I think so.
An amount of minutes, a concept, or what is the, is there a way to bet on this one?
Some sort of a auto executive coming on stage that we've never heard of.
That's good. And what is it? Is it Chevrolet? What is the, yeah.
Chevrolet, yeah.
Do we get a Chevrolet or maybe we all just agree on it?
If a Chevrolet executive comes out, then we all shake hands and smile.
That's fine. Yeah.
Okay. Actually, and that brings me to maybe some stuff about the show itself.
Okay. Well, here's one. I texted you guys this.
I think that in the last, say 15 minutes, a musical performance by a singer who is named,
who I have never heard of. And I have to be honest about what I've heard of and haven't.
But I think it's safe to say I won't have heard of them.
Okay.
Does anyone want to go against that? Or does it feel too accurate?
It does feel accurate. There's also the possibility that
Mack McAnally plays somewhere in here.
Or it could be somewhere else on the convention and the show as well.
Was there some bet then that's music prediction? But I think it's going to be at this.
I think it's going to be at this.
It's going to be on this thing. Well, there's play in the arena.
Is the bet you say Mack McAnally and I say singer I've never heard of?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah. Because there's a chance, the rumors are that maybe a Pecos Bills in Disney World goes away
and we get a country bear themed restaurant there as well. Because we're getting more
country bears out here in the hungry bear space. And we got the country bear like statue in Grizzly
Peak. So there's also now rumor that maybe there's a barbecue jamboree coming to Pecos Bills.
Oh, interesting.
Interesting.
So perhaps there's more bear related stuff. I feel that feels like early in the presentation.
That's a little bit on the lighter side.
Yeah, yeah.
But that's the time where you would maybe want
to bring down the house with a music performer who everyone in the building knows Mack McAnally.
Right. Now, obviously maybe we'd be backing up the other singers from that, but
possibly. Oh, and that, well, that's confusing because some of them are singers I've never heard
of. Oh, that's true.
We get into a dicey area. Either way you want to make that like a two.
Yeah. Great.
Okay. Should I just be firm about the amount of minutes? What I wrote down is eight minutes
devoted to cruise ships. Am I so willing to say the exact amount? That just feels right to me.
You know what? Does anyone want to say a different amount of minutes?
How do we bet on amount of time devoted to cruise ships?
They talk about, I mean, the three of us don't have a ton of interest in those cruise ships,
even though people that go on it swear by them. So I, we're in the wrong potentially
for not being that excited about it.
I like watching videos and reading about them sometimes.
Okay, that's true, but you don't.
That's different than going for an entire week.
Yeah, exactly. Can I go a slightly higher and say 12?
Yeah, let's do it that way. Mike, anything different you want to do?
Well, they just did another round of announcements about like a Cruella de Vil lounge on one of
these cruises. And I don't know, like releasing that stuff right before D23 is interesting to me
because do they have more crew stuff or are they getting some of this crew stuff out of the way
so they don't have to highlight it on the show? Same thing with Country Bear
barbecue jamboree. I'm like, well, why didn't they save this for two weeks?
Unless it's so jam packed. So either they-
Yeah, don't you want to make an arena scream when you say there's a new bear barbecue coming?
Yeah, yes. So I think five minutes. I think there's less crew stuff to announce.
This is good. Closest to that going over?
Yeah.
All right. And let's, hey, let's, can I make that a five? Yeah.
Sure.
A bigger one. Okay. Yeah. So wait, five, eight, 12. Okay. Good.
New bride in Disneyland Haunted Mansion.
New bride. Is that something-
That's a rumor. That's not, I'm not making that up. That's what I've heard. I've heard it.
I think that might be a safe-
I'd like that.
Bet.
I don't like that bride.
That after Jack goes away, we'll have a new bride in the mansion because that's
sort of the most glaring weird effect left over from that. What is it at this point? 25 year old?
To that. Was it for the 50th anniversary?
Yeah, maybe. But a new bride, new thing up there.
I don't have a strong feeling.
That feels to me, that's sort of my hypothesis of where there's going to be a lot of little,
that is fun. That's cool for Disneyland heads. Oh, cool. New bride. There's going to be new
bride here. There's going to be this. Characters. Again, it's not a new big ride at Disneyland,
but it feels like, oh, cool. You're adding to the lore. You're sprucing up the legendary ride.
They've done a lot of sprucing up of the queue. There was a new-
They've been doing a lot of work in there. That's also part of what people are saying.
The gift shop, the leotards on the way out, and then people are saying there's going to
be some new stuff in the mansion, and the biggest rumor is bride, is new bride.
I have no strong feelings about this. I don't have strong feelings either.
It sounds like that's, we're all on board with that.
Pass, yeah, whatever, fine. I mean, I'm almost out of big stuff, really.
I can't tell how to deal with this. Another in that, how much do we do it, is Cotino.
Oh, I know. Story Living by Disney.
In terms of bland people on stage, let me just throw that in. Neither big nor small. Just a middle
three. I get $3 if somebody from Shea Holmes or Davidson Communities, the company's building
Cotino, is on stage. I think no Cotino.
I would like there to be no Cotino. I think no Cotino.
Yeah, yeah. Yes, I could easily see it, but again, it feels like, again, they would normally pad out
presentations with barbecue jamboree. In the past, that feels like they were like,
oh, thank God we can burn four minutes, three minutes on this chunk. We show some art of a
new painting of Big Al, and we say we're playing old music, and these dopes will cheer for anything,
these little piggies. These rubes.
And feed at the trough. But they announced it early. There's just stuff they've been announcing
beforehand, so I think they have a lot. If they really are going to burn a bunch of stuff off on
Cotino, I think it's silly. But I think presentations is where now you have to,
this is something that's been agreed to in a boring room, and they don't realize how boring
that's going to play on stage. It's part of the deal.
It could be a contractual thing, you're right.
I get the logic of it, but I say no Cotino. No story living by Disney.
What if there is Cotino, but not someone from Shea Holmes or Davidson communities on stage?
I'll take that. If he goes no, and you go someone, and I say no someone.
Okay, that's great, that's great. No Cotino, no someone, and I get, okay.
Now here's the one, I don't want to put any, this is like one of the thousand to ones I was
talking about. Let's call it a thousand. I'm only putting in one dollar on this, but I get
a thousand dollars if not only is there Cotino, but also the big finale, the what are we going
to give to these people on the way out the door, is a special musical performance devoted to Cotino.
And if that then is not a singer we haven't heard of, but a singer we have heard of
doing a song of the summer customized, if Sabrina Carpenter is paid to do a D23 original parody
called Cotino. That's that me Cotino.
Well if you'd like to hear. Oh please yeah.
Oh great, excuse me for jumping ahead. I think I did some of this as a Twitter joke,
but here's, here now is the full thing. Say you can sleep, baby I know, such a relaxing condo.
Single family, beautiful homes, that's that me Cotino. Mid-century oasis, oh we're gonna
buy land in Rancho. Story living, built by Shay Holmes, that's that me Cotino.
If it happens in the middle of the show you don't get the money though.
Yeah if exactly that happens and they got the idea from this,
yeah no then I get nothing. I say please please please don't prove them right like our other hit
song. I'll take that, I will give you a thousand dollars if that happens. Rancho Mirage got me
talking. What if three out of four, like what if she's there singing but it's not that song,
but it is about Cotino and then it's the second to last thing. Oh boy then it's, I don't know.
You don't get the money but it would be pretty wild. Yeah yeah just give me something, I don't
know is that worth an ice cream scoop? Might be worth an ice cream scoop. At least an ice cream
if we're gonna be going anyway. Yeah. I like that a trip to Baskin Robbins is in our future.
Is actually inevitable. That's the kind of thing we should do more after the show or before the
show or on a day where we aren't doing the show, it's just the boys go to Baskin Robbins. That's
really the biggest victory that comes from this. I have an idea for, what if let's just, hey screw
it. I'm proposing this is a $20 if you guys are in and this is pretty random I think. This is just,
I don't know, this just go with your instinct but this is kind of like a big pool that requires us
to play, I'm sorry to pay extra attention to the show because now we're gonna have to do a count
and the count is this. We all have to choose a Disney word and we have to count how many times
it is said during the show and whatever word is said the most. Oh. The winner gets $20 for that.
This could be the big, and you know I think listeners should go in on this too if there's
somebody you listen to the show with. This seems like a fun one for everybody to go in on. Yeah.
You know just in your own private, we can't really do a bet with all of the audience.
But the, let me just, just a spark idea. Spark is one you could choose. Yeah that is good.
But I would say that the big contenders here are Wish, Dream, Magic, Adventure. That's probably
not all of them. I Wonder could be in there. Yeah. I'd say, the trouble is if one of them is like
the name of it, they refer to the ship. Yeah. And then, but you know that's the risk you take
because a lot of them are ship names. I could see my way around Adventure but, oh wait,
sorry that was in the list. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Then Adventure. But I think those are the
ones to beat. Let's say, all right, Wish, Dream, Magic, Adventure, Wonder, and I'll let you guys
pick first. Can I go Dream? And it has to be one of those? No. Can I pick Imagination? Oh damn. Oh
damn. This guy's coming in with Imagination. Oh shit. All right. Yeah. Good thinking. Mike gets
Imagination. So do I go Magic? Yeah. I'll go Magic. Yeah. I mean, that's it. Yeah. That's good.
And if we're, boy, we might be hearing a lot of Wish and then going like shit. Yeah. Really?
Well, we screwed this. Well, that movie is still such a big part of the zeitgeist, you know. That's
true. We're all talking about it every day. Yes. How is Wish coming to the party? Well, is that
going to go out on? That feels like a lot there. I think so. Yeah. You know what? Listeners,
do it yourselves if there's an area that we missed. If you hear this and you have one to suggest to
us and we feel passionate about it, enough to put it in our list. But otherwise, we're going to have
to do some spreadsheets and figure out what the hell we just said and get specific about it
so that we can hopefully have the results when we do this, you know, pulled together as fast as we
can episode the next day, Sunday. Yeah. There's other stuff. I mean, we're done with betting,
I suppose, but like there's big stuff like Lion King Land and the Paris parks. There's all these
other rumors and stuff. I do have a question though. What do you think will be the biggest
announcements, I guess, probably ticket wise for Disneyland and Disney World?
Coming out of the show where you go, holy shit. I mean, if I'm saying people mover, that's what I
think for Disneyland. But what like what do you think actually will be? Oh my God, that's crazy.
I guess Villains Land in Florida, if that's what you think. I do. I think my Disneyland answer is
a cop out. And that's an exact date for the Tiana version. You think that's the biggest
announcement? Yeah, I know. God, that's so depressing. That's the most depressing thing
I've ever heard. I don't want it to be the case. But no, that's a ride that's opening in a month.
Yeah, I know. But they haven't given the day yet. But that this is this is the grim. I
I understand. I don't quite but I understand the grim thinking that brought them to it.
I'm not happy. But if they announce Walt Robot, that's bigger than the opening day for a ride
that we've already seen. You think Walt Robot is an e-ticket? Well, I'm just saying it's more
exciting than a date of those. It is more exciting. I said e-ticket or a big announcement type thing.
Are you talking like what is our personal? What do you think just predicting wise coming out,
you go, well, the most excited thing I am for Disneyland is this. For me, it's Avatar. It's
Pandora here. If we get anything more on that, I'm happy. Excited for, I think it's definitely
whatever the Avatar quote unquote experience is. Yeah. And mine is just if Deadpool hits
Josh Demar on the butt or something with his hand. I'm telling you, Deadpool should be like
Swedish chef in Muppet Vision 3D. I agree with you. He should appear in a different part of the
arena. He should sabotage stuff. He should start opening fire at the stage. He does not have,
he has Chimichung where his holsters are in Disneyland. That's funny. He does not have his
guns. I know in Paris he has baguettes and that's pretty clever. Pretty good, yeah. Well, yeah,
I like your Muppet Vision suggestion where like Josh is talking and then his spotlight moves and
he's got to go over here and then like back over here, whoop. And then like, sorry guys, we're
having a little bit of trouble. Maybe it has something to do with our lighting director,
Deadpool. Deadpool. And then you get, and then you have a shot way up in the rafters.
It's, that's a thing in professional wrestling too. When the wrestlers come through the crowd,
I feel like everyone loses it. Everyone gets excited. And then unfortunately, I just don't,
I haven't watched some of the films like you, Jason, so I don't know the character enough. So
I'm just spit balling here that it would be like, Josh, sorry, I didn't really have eyes on the
spotlight. I was busy masturbating. Does that seem like something Deadpool would say? Deadpool
actually is occasionally more subtle than you think. Deadpool, don't come on the crowd. Deadpool,
I know you're way up in the rafters, but these people paid money to be here. Don't come in their
popcorn. You know, what would be great is if they brought Wolverine, the costume Wolverine out on
the stage, took off the mask and it's Jackman. They just stole the bit from Comic-Con. Yeah,
they could do that. I'm not sure. And he just says, thank you for seeing the movie and leaves.
During the parks panel? Yeah, sure. Yeah. Why not? And then Deadpool shoots in his face.
And then Deadpool comes. Even Deadpool, they do the wraparound arms and eat the chimichangas.
Okay. Well, that'd be very romantic. So wait, it's not Ryan Reynolds. It's the Disneyland
Deadpool with real Jackman who just says, thank you for coming to the movie and then he leaves.
Well, I think it's the more unexpected choice. You would think it would be Ryan Reynolds.
Or maybe it's both. Maybe it's both. It could be both. What if it's all about this?
Deadpool's up on stage. He's doing his normal antics. He pulls the mask off. It's Bob Iger.
And then he comes. Oh, okay.
Okay. That would be unexpected. And he could also say thank you for seeing the movie because
he made a lot of money off of it. Yeah. Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to come on all of you.
All right. You survived by guess the ride. Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate. If you want
to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus
episode every month than our regular episodes ad free. And in terms of those regular episodes,
remember this Friday we get Fixing Tomorrowland, where we predict all the things that may be not
said anything close to what we're suggesting, even in the low budget version. I hope that we're
wrong. And then Sunday after Parks Panel or whatever their name for it is. Yeah. Post-Horizon
Sunday. We're going to nurse a post-Horizon hangover, get an episode out as soon as we can,
and tally up whoever made or didn't make money from everything you just heard. Very exciting.
Wow.