Hey folks Michael here just want to give you a quick heads up
We did record some video of this epic battle of Nick Weiger and I playing Disney's Lorcan a collectible card game
So if you want to see that it is live right now on the patreon the video is fine
It's a little bit far away
But you can kind of see the cards and you can see us turning the cards and putting things in a discard pile
So about minute 40 into the audio of this podcast you can switch over to that video and see us playing live
There were a few problems. I did not clear enough space on my phone
So there are a couple chunks where the video is missing, but in that section
I've just put up a picture of the sexy Robin Hood from the 70s cartoon. It's a new picture. He looks very
Good. He looks very sexy
So if you want you can switch over when you're listening to the audio at about minute 40 or so to the video and you
Will hear and see the rest of the podcast if you would like if you don't want to do it. No problem
I'm not offended. Just enjoy what you want and have a good day
Oh
It's podcast the right Club 3 you guys say hi, but otherwise, let's skip the formalities. Okay. There you go
It's a beautiful day for a card game too much too much formality talking about the weather
I
Well, I took up just as much time complaining about the formality look at that the point of that energy was to get straight to
Our guests who were so excited has joined us behind the double paywall
You know, he is renowned for his raving's about burgers
But today he's all about a trading card game made by Ravensburger
It's the Ravensburger boy Nick Weiger Wow that that beats the Ravensburger joke
I had locked and loaded which is that a Ravensburger sounds like a Raven-Symones pop-up that Robert earl restaurants
Oh, I disagree that sounds that's both a good joke and a very viable idea a bad ghost kitchen that would be inside a book
It a Beppo no perfectly viable business idea and by that I mean something that would fail in any
Regular terms, but something that he could write a lot of
Taximony off of now obviously both of our respective podcasts have talked about Robert earl at length. I am curious
How like how many of the Robert earl panoply of ghost kitchens? Have you actually sampled?
We did a thing. I did an experiment during our
Celebrary month where we had Mariah's cookies. Yes
Delivered right both a was it a Stewart Anderson and a book of the Beppo
I think to see which would get there faster and which was of superior quality and
All forms were slow expensive and bad. Yeah, so that's my most that's the only time I've ordered
What is your guys ghost kitchen? You've done a chicken guy of you not coming from black Angus. Yes, I believe so, okay
Yeah
Yeah, we've had
The guy fury one that was the ghost kitchen at Boca real disappointing the guy
Where that where was that good a pet po, okay, I just wanted to hear it and hear it correctly, okay
Correctly in a wrong
Yeah, we think the guys one was really disappointed cuz he's like he's a at least a chef like he's a restaurant guy
It's one thing was like Mariah Carey or whatever like Mario Lopez wants to like lend his name to a bad sandwich like whatever
He's case getting a check
But when it's like when your business is food and like you're you have a food empire
Like wouldn't you want your own restaurant to be good quality food?
So that was a real that was a real bummer the the other ones we did we did mr.
Beast burger, which was a real disappointment and then obviously there was litigation involved after that and then and then tiger bites was just
Wretched and tiger bites was like chicken fingers and I'm like again tiger is a rapper. Okay, and it's like it's
How do you mess up a tendy? You know what I mean? Like it's like that should be like a pretty straightforward food stuff
I feel like you'll get like a frozen tendy that you heat up in the oven that will be better than like what you would
Get from Robert Earl's ghost kitchen. So it's a real bummer
There's something that creeps me out, especially about both
Tendies and cookies just feel wrong coming out of the Bucca to what do I do Beppo?
I guess just a consistent kitchen like I don't it just doesn't feel like the place that should be me
No any of those things. Yeah, I don't know like
Oregano getting in the air of the of the cookie ingredients. It's weird. It's weird
I you know what quick formalities before we we get into things
Obviously
Nick you won by a wide margin. Thank you for bringing this idea to us right at the end of the city walk saga
And excited to do this with you. The runner-up was Little Golden Books about Disney attractions
They you know, there's those these like kind of simple books for kids
It's a small world and Space Mountain and figment
They you know, they've done all kinds of attractions as kids books could be a good one for us parents could be fun
But we do need four more topics for the poll next month. And you know what? How about to match Little Golden Books?
We let's do topics that are all at least tangentially related to theme parks. Oh, that's fun. Why yeah, why not?
You know, there's been a lot of work been a lot of sitcoms and bands and long dead actors
So what let's let's stay mildly on topic though. Even that's like a step beyond
Also, it just said just because Emeril has a restaurant somewhere in a theme park does not mean that Emeril sitcom again qualifies
The 20-year contract that Emeril clearly signed with Universal Orlando is if we can get a hold of it, you know
one thing to bring up also you ended up be one of the topics you ended up beating Nick was
The Nixon presidential library. Yeah, the Richard Nixon presidential library in Yorba Linda, California
Which I there was a moment where I was like it would be funny to pivot to that and just do that episode instead
But I felt like it also felt like the club three
Voters were like it because they wanted this specifically. I don't want to give that toss them like a fuck you
You know, I mean, so like let's let's do the Larkana app. Although I do think by the end of this
You're gonna be begging for the Richard Nixon
It is a place it's a place you can go with themed rooms
It's true
and if you look if you ever want to pull as you know
We try to vest a lot of power in this in the person in the club three seat if you ever want to do some
Nixonian abuse of power and switch this or barge in to any other episode and make it be about Nixon
That is your right. You know what we should do is we should make custom Nixon Larkana cards with different powers
And we could just insert them into our decks
Yeah, I mean he is in the Hall of Presidents right is in the Hall of Presidents
Character yeah in the universe. Uh-huh to tie to Walt. So I think there's many things we could do with that
So maybe maybe yeah, we create our own
Full like our own full or kind of decks right like custom cards like a deep throat card that like applies like a plus
Tube off to one of your cars secretly. Yeah, no one knows about it Robert Earl card. There you go restaurant
it's like restaurateur extraordinaire or something and then like it's plus like plus or negative three points or something because of like the
bad food you've served to your
With his food and then like you'll it's like a really strong
Points for any card that Jason throws down. It gives Jason power automatically
Minus three minus three hit points except playing against Jason and it makes Jason automatically win the game
The lure I have so much lure
I that is true now to say it officially this topic first officially nominated by Nicole Nassuti
Disney Larkana with Nick Weiger
In this yeah, yeah, somebody had to do it per parliamentary procedure and thus you were here one looking out for another appreciate that
Oh, that's true. Yeah
so I
Guess at this point I have to really turn it over to you Nick and to some extent Mike
Because I have prepared nothing and I know nothing
Jason before we started you were saying you were watching a ton of
Larkana tutorials and get to like get to know it videos. I did not do anything of the sort
I don't know what this is and I will require you guys to explain it to me like I'm fine
And I have to say a lot of the videos watch very nicely produced very professionally done
I could not follow a lick of them. Yes, totally inscrutable. It's like it's really
it's a very
complicated set of rules for what should be and what I imagine would be a lot of
Players entry point for collectible card games
Like I imagine if you're like, you know, like whatever you're under the age of 10
And you've never played one of these games before and you're a Disney like fan
then like you might in your tractors of the characters for whatever reason then you might be
Like I meant attracted in the sense of like that. You will like that
I didn't mean like it's like it like they didn't print it on you sexually
I was not trying to say that like but like well, I don't have you seen every card
Maybe some of them are
Sarah Roxanne card is there I know there is multiple Fox Robin Hood cards. Oh, yeah sure
Yeah, we've discussed the meme of the Robin Hood the the Fox Robin Hood passing the the the torch to the
to Nick from
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, it's like it's like that. He's like shaking his hand and he was like he was like
Thanks for taking care of the last generation of furries. I'll take it from here
Wow
Wow, is he hotter? No bullshit. Yeah. Yeah, I know
Like sleazy and like a cool way
Contemporary, but like your attractiveness. I don't know. I don't know if I'm the one to say no Fox Robin Hood is smoother and he's cooler
I he's much cooler. I think there might be an aesthetic quality though
If you grew up with 3d animation
You might just be looking at a you might look for a 3d animated character more so than like a cell cell
Animated care you more of it like it you're like attracted to dimensions different. Yeah, I think so
I don't know. I just could just be like what the visual language are used to right as a kid
I don't know. Yeah, but but I'm just speculating. I do want to I do want to make sure we have time for for Lorcan
I don't know how many I think we'll probably at least get through one game
It's a it's you know, it's a 60-deck a game. So it's like 60 cards 60. I mean, yes
You're correct a 60 card deck and a game like Hearthstone, which is a mobile game is like a 30 card deck
So like that's designed for like a quicker round 60 cards is like I think like kind of the general magic the gathering
Which is like a meteor lengthier gameplay session
So I don't know how long one of these is gonna take because I'll be honest. I have not played Lorcan a before
I did I did spend a lot of time studying the rules and I did spend I did watch a lot of the
Tutorial videos, but I thought it would be more interesting to just try to come in cold and they're like
Let's just see what this is like Mike. Have you gotten any practice games in? I've never played Lurkana
Though you've been collecting the decks, yes
Yeah, you are coming in with that but you've never actually yeah ends up being a big part of the Mike and I've talked a lot
About the Marvel overpower game from the mid to late 90s and a few years ago
We did have people over and try to play. Yeah. Yeah, cuz I have a ton of those cards still
Yeah, and it was admittedly confusing, but I think eventually caught on I think it's a thing where it was a little
Modular like customizable like you can play a quicker version of this than a longer version
Yeah, that's all true. I still don't remember how to play it
I do not know and that's something I was I collected a ton of as a kid
So yeah, and no I haven't I
Have magic the gathering cards. I tried playing that when I was a kid. It was a little confusing to me as well back then
This seems less confusing the magic the other thing. So I did just to talk about collectible card games real quickly
I did play magic the gathering when I was a kid and I
And then I also like, you know, that would the physical game that that's the physical one. I played I mentioned Hearthstone
That's the Blizzard game
That's set in like kind of the Warcraft universe and I played that like like a bit too much
And then also Carlson you and I have both been playing Marvel snap
Yeah
Which I've fallen off of cuz I just it's a thing that's like both a time sink and a money sink
Like I just I'm buying too many of these you buy you spend money. Yeah, well, I buy the season pass. Did you ever buy?
I haven't bought I haven't spent any money actually
Yeah
I would not I would like this the the whatever the season pass was was like
599 a month or whatever and then you get like some cards and right, you know some platinum currency or whatever
So I was I was continually on the hook for that and I reached a certain was like I can't be doing this anymore
That one's a 12 card deck
So like they're really quick gameplay sessions. Yeah, I just signed up for that last night
It's fun. It definitely holds your hand a lot more at least at the beginning
And there's a lot of fun sounds in my friends as Mike says my friends from the Marvel Universe are there
I will say this real quick and I don't like to be braggadocious
But in the same way that Jason was bragging about his sexual prowess the other day on the show
This is a new thing. Yeah, I'm gonna be bragging about my prowess at Marvel snap
I'm excellent. Wow this game. Have you found that Marvel snap is a great way to connect with your partner the opposite in fact
It's a good way to disconnect from exactly. Yes, it's good way to just be in your own little world on your phone
You're playing snap Lindsay. He's got a stack of Christopher Pike books. That's right. Yeah, that's how love works
And our child is just doing whatever we're not sure
She's over by one of the outlets. It's fine. She loves that
Yes, I say part of the joy of listening to this podcast is that you know when you have an episode that's devoted to the Super Bowl
Shuffle that goes into a lengthy digression
Jason Sheridan's
joys of carnality
Explaining what sex is to Mike and I people who have reproduced as if it is explaining the rules of Lorcan Oh to me
It's good stuff. I
Do want to
One more one more tangent before we get into this
So we were going to do an episode of doughboys with y'all last year and unfortunately we couldn't get the scheduling right because of you
you all went to
To Orlando and then Mitch was gonna be out of town
And so the timing didn't work out
But how much I don't know how much you've dug into bucket Lister's but this was a thing that was through bucket Lister's
Which is a company that does like promotions and and like little pop-ups and events in various regions
They so they what they had is they had a family guy a pop-up that was both
This is what we're gonna review for the show
It was both like a miniature like kind of like the the Pawtuck at Pete's so what's the bar and go?
I am the drunken clam. Yeah, I was a miniature drunken clam and then also a family guy mini golf
Yeah, yeah, and unfortunately, we couldn't get the scheduling quite right, but I'm gonna be a
Double show crossover even there were big plans put in this. Yeah. Yeah, but I don't know how much again
You've dug into this but it's really interesting all the the weird like shitty events that they put on
So I've got the I've got the the bucket Lister's LA thing open right now
They've done things
I know that that that our buddies over at your Kickstarter sucks went to one of these in the Nashville area and it was a Simpsons
Pop-up bar and they did an episode of it
And it was like it they were just talked about how cheap it was
but one of the details that I like fixated on is that
Behind the bar was not a guy and mow the bartender cosplay. It was uh, it was sideshow Bob
And it's just like how do you get that wrong? It's like mows bar. How do you not get mows the boat a bartender?
Just so orthogonal from the act what the actual show is anyway
exceptional quality control exactly
Would you ever get a sense of how the family guy experience was like what we missed?
I think it was kind of shitty. I think it was like a little chintzy and if you got some stuff is
A lot of flats. Oh, yeah, like putting greens. It was a nine hole miniature golf course, which I'm an 18 hole
mini golf
Shorter but I
Understood when I saw the physical space like oh, yeah, okay nine holes
We didn't get canceled not just because of our schedules
But we had a date planned and like we'll do it on Wednesday
And it was like this is canceled because we are no longer doing Wednesdays
They started pulling dates I think because they weren't because of poor sales
So that was part of we had to win then we had to reschedule and then the other dates didn't work
It was a whole whole but a range of things around the same time
I feel like we why you and I were talking about going to a thing called Santa's secret, which was a dirty
Show and we didn't that wasn't even for content. No, we're just gonna go
Do that you were really interested in the burlesque Santa thing and Santa's secret in the Beverly which mall
Yes, Beverly Center. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and even Anderson was was
Wrangle that and then there was also they they for July 4th. They recently brought back uncle Sam's secret, which is
Patriotic version of it. I feel they yeah, they were like subbing out holidays for like they're different like burlesque show
So, I don't know if Santa's secret comes back. Maybe we make a priority this year. I'd love to go to Santa's
I love that experience. I guess we could do an episode if we feel like it
What was I don't remember what were some of the things that were supposed to happen at Santa's secret
I think you were supposed to like they were like hyping up that you would learn what Santa's secret was
Like there was some sort of reveal about what Santa had been hiding
I don't think it was just his dick
But it's possible like they're like there was some there was some sort of mystery that was going to be unraveled
Well, cuz it like it was I believe the promo photo was something like a pair of lips
Like, you know dressing like a Santa suit with like a finger like a
And then the the caption was don't tell mrs. Claus
So mrs. Claus wasn't involved in the show I guess no, I think it's like Santa's like kind of horny fantasy
I think is the idea so I imagine there'll be all sorts of like whatever like sexy elves and sexy like reindeer and you know
I mean like it like all just like like kind of a Christmas pasty
Reindeer I don't know
How many angles no bad idea for a burlesque dancer at a Christmas review, you know
Yeah, so yeah
I mean in this scenario like Santa's like very bored in the workshop and he just starts imagining letting his mind drift
Yeah, all the elves making the toys turn into hunks
I don't know dance or something. I think so. I think it's mostly that and it's just an excuse for like kind of lewd dancing
Take a break from carving little dolls in boats and maybe try. I don't know but plug
Well, I also just like I like a hunky Santa I always think that's like a fun thing, you know
Yeah, sure and then it was it looked like it was equal opportunity as far as like ladies and men both
In good shape. Yeah, that's part of the fun of it, too. Yeah
So yeah, I just wanted to go celebrate the human body. It's not even about the sexuality or the maybe oh, yeah
No, it's not about sexuality. I'm not comfortable with that
As far as the scene is the bodies. Yeah, I like that. I like that part. Yeah
Okay, well then
much to play
Don't figure something out and uncle Sam because God and I don't think I don't know regular facts about uncle Sam much less a secret
That flips my notion of what uncle Sam is right head. Don't tell mrs. Sam
All
Right, we do we want to dig in
Because you guys you've come prepared despite having not played it with anybody
You've both got kits you got gear
I hate to
You know call him out especially but why yours is a little bit more professional and slick
Well, I don't know about that because I will say that that I couldn't find so that these the starter deck that it come that
That the Carlson still has a case for here. It comes with a bunch of extra shit
So it comes with like a bunch of counters that you can use to denote like car buffs or D
But card buffs or D buffs and then there's also like a a thing that I think tracks the amount of lore
Which is the the win condition for the game? Yes. Now, this is a this little I didn't bring that this little box
I have is a separate purchase. Oh, okay a different thing
You just purchased the box and it's a thicker box with card stock for your specific deck
This is this so I bought this just like to show off. This is a flashy little like Scrooge
Yeah, it's really you bought that to show off and I didn't clock that it was something to show off and I liked Knicks instead
Generic black case. Yes, that could be but it's a good case used for makeup. It could be used for anything
Well, they have any sort of branding on it. This is in a way like
Toiletries kit that I got with a free bag from a podcast. Yeah, I mean it's nice
Yeah, so but it's very functional
I will say this and I think Scott you will not be upset with me
But I have an extra starter deck that I would like to gift Jason before we start this
He can like kind of go through and see some of the cards and then maybe in dead spaces when we're trying to figure
Out what the hell we're doing. You can go. Oh, look at this. It's Jasper from
101 Dalmatians, that's great. That's great. Can I also can I read really quickly?
We're throwing a lot of like specifics out but another person who officially nominated this topic Benjamin Martin said
Let's see some hot Lorcan a action with Weiger
I also would like to nominate Jason as official flavor text reciter for the episode
What does that mean? And what would that entail on Jason's part? I am I reading like the card?
By like the bit of color
So basically and I have this this Cruella de Vil card right here, which we can use as an example
But there's a bunch of numbers on this thing
So like this this is like the amount of ink it costs to play this number two up here in the corner
This is essentially it's there. They're different names that it has for it that I think are a little bit tamer
But this is essentially like it's a tack and it's health pool
You spend ink you spend
Yes, okay and then lore when we say lore that's not the lore of the world of lore is wind
The lore is yes. Oh, no, that's damage counter
Lore is like points. You're trying to get to 20 lore 20 lore non pluralized
And but ink is yeah spend ink to get lore you spend ink and then
You spend it in one turn the next turn the ink you can't play a card the ink has to dry, right?
I'm not kidding
So so this is this is like a concept that's in a lot of these games
I believe in Magic the other means called summoning sickness and basically it's a gameplay balance thing that if I play Cruella de Vil on
This turn I have to wait another turn. So I've introduced Cruella de Vil to the game board
I have to wait another turn before I can use Cruella de Vil's abilities
So I can't just like throw it down throw down a bunch of cards at once play them all at once and then you know
Whatever, maybe I can I can burst out a win suddenly and they say her ink is drying
That yes, that's the term that you use because you use because you spend ink the currency to play a character
I spending to ink to play Cruella de Vil then the ink has to dry for a single turn before I can use Cruella de Vil's
Let's see, let her now get going ability
Or or use Cruella de Vil to attack one of Carlson's characters
So the flavor text is do we see at the bottom?
so there's all these things that says like their abilities that all their stats the name the name of the card the type of
Card at the bottom it says and and and Sheridan you can read that sure on at the end
Yeah, they in the italics the italics. Yeah, okay, great
Isn't it just gorgeous darling and just as stylish as I am
Wow, so it's just a little bit of pizzazz to kind of like add to the character of the world
It is a little pizzazz. Yeah, and she is a very jaunty outfit
I feel like can I can I borrow one of your cards when you get them open Jason to like get a sense of?
What this of course are and oh Nick you have every one of these cards in a protective sleeve
Yeah, I sleeved these preemptively if I take them out of here. You can see the card back
That is also better than what Mike did. Hey, do you think so?
I fell right in it fell right into the trap because maybe I have sleeves and everything and maybe they're special
Lorcona sleeves
So far that's really cool. Oh, that's right. Oh, we're right to the sexy fox. Yep
My whole deck has that Robin Hood backing basically with a different card protectors. Where did you get these sleeves online?
I don't remember best buy comm perhaps. I forget you're not gonna last five minutes looking at these sleeves
yeah
Yeah, mine mine just has like a generic like black backing you could use in any any card game
So it's it's a little bit less on point
All right on the scale on my lore scale you guys are even you both have okay great Scott
Yeah
also you talk about where you get these Mike and I realized that some of the mythology here and why this has come up on
the show before is
Because do you not do you or do you not find out about Lorcona deals from your beloved deal vibes?
I have in the past. Yes found out because initially when this came out the first
Like the introductory sets they were very hard to find
Sold out you'd have to go and reset like on eBay or something and buy them at big markups
This is only been going for like a year that this is less
I think at this point last November or something and they've released like five sets at this point and it's not impossible to get anymore
It's still pretty popular from what I how like just seeing in target
It seems like you yeah, you see things here and there but sometimes they'll be sold out
But yes deal vibes, especially early days would be like go now
Lorcona available at Amazon or Lorcona available at best buy comm. Mm-hmm. And yes, I think I think I got something via
Deal vibes link. I'm trying to remember which one but it's all blur when you're talking about different Twitter pop-up
Messages I get alerting me to a specific deal or something in stock. It's a kind of a blur at this point
It happens so often when you got to choose like in a given day
How many can you get like do you get a Lorcona pack when he's also offering like, you know
Tricks themed after Deadpool and Wolverine. Yeah or patio furniture, which is what was happening
And I'll take a look I go it was a good deal for that, but I don't think we need that right now
That's a hundred dollars off. Oh, that would be a good good chair and table set for the patio
I don't need we don't need that. Is he the main source of your shopping?
Like the trap I fall into is I spend too much money on something because it's a deep discount
It's like I don't need this. Yeah, but it's like this is like 50% off
I was like, I gotta get you know, I mean like, oh, yeah, we just got we just bought
I just bought like a new cabinet. I was like, wait, I don't we don't really need this
It's like it's kind of functional for our space
but it's also like this is more money than I need to spend on this thing just because it was on sale I
Read a lot on my Kindle nowadays. Yes, and try not to buy too many new books
But then I get really into buying
Used books like interesting like oh cool. That's really I just learned about this book and it's not available through the library
So I can get it used so and did the same thing with like cool vintage t-shirts
So now that's becoming an issue. It's like oh, I have too much secondhand stuff now
Yeah, put him in Wiger's cabinet
Like a gift of the magi sort of situation
Do you have a do you have a used book like go to like do you have like a like a site you look at?
I really like a biblio.com
eat eat books is good to
I feel like I use a like Alibri or Alibri so I can't remember what okay what the site is
But like I yeah, it's the same thing cuz you just see something is like wait
This is like 80% less than the than a new copy and it's like in good condition like I might I like yeah
I'll get this and then yeah book I never read the only issue is with the older stuff from like 70s or 80s the
like
Print is so small. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I'm dealing with that now. I'm reading up
I've been reading this we're working my way through this Paul Schrader book
and
It's the the director what the hell is it called?
It's like transcendental film making or something like that and it's so boring
and it's like it's so boring and the text is so small and it's like, you know, it's
It's a it's like a hundred eighty pages. So I was like, okay, I'll breeze through this
But then like the font point is like the size of like the care instructions on like a laundry tag
So it's like so I'm like reading this eight-point font and it's just like so dull about like talking about you know
I'm
Whatever like talking about some particular like shot size at length and I'm just like man this is like I don't know
It's just gonna take me forever to get through it. Yeah, you're doing it. I'm doing it. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I know you plan. So we're throwing a lot
Yeah, but could I say could I explain what the actual like narrative of the game we're playing is? Yes
So
What happens when you play the game against someone else you are playing as an Illumineer? Yes
We are Illumineers. We are Illumineers like the band the Illumineers the hey ho band
Called the Illumineers, but
Close your sandwich you're calling them. Yeah, they're the ill
Mears they're ill. Yeah, I think they're ill. Yeah. Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah the way you said cool 30 years ago exactly
Yeah, 30 years. That's yeah makes sense. So what we're doing is we're summoning
glimmers of
Disney characters so these when we're playing cards with Cruella de Vil
It's not that we're actually playing with the real Cruella
We're summoning sort of a snapshot of them and making them sentient in the moment
That is the way in which it's being described so they can be different versions of the character, you know
They don't have to be directly like they can be out of doing things out of character slightly, right?
Because you have a before I believe of the same character in a deck
So it's like it just I think is to make it make sense that you can have four Goofy's right ever
But I think it's also a little bit of the that it's the same device
They use in Nintendo use in Super Smash Brothers of like we don't actually want Mario punching link or or peach or peach
Yeah, we don't actually want that. So what they're they're these are dolls that come to life, right?
You know, we're fighting for fun. It's not they're not the actual character. Okay, they come to life as
facsimiles of these care
Not literally okay, but we are you would have loved Disney's work
Simulation and simulacra are very heavy
Like when Mickey kills Pluto in a game, it's not really happening
No, you know, I hope we get to see that kind of thing that happens a hundred presented really others
Yeah, there's deaths in this you're attacking you are tearing other characters
They have all sorts of language for it that I think is this more about like I'm blocking you or whatever
I'm removing from the game
Could be like cutting off Phineas and Ferb's head
And there are like weapons there's like a frying pan there's a skillet yes, yeah, you can hit Pluto with a skillet
There's also songs which we'll get into there are songs
Okay. Yeah, there's characters items
Actions actions and then in newer series. There's locations. Oh, there's locations. Okay
Yeah, I think that I don't know if if you guys
I have a couple of the Ursula returns expansion. Okay cards in this deck, but it's mostly first
Generation. Yeah, that's this that's the same as me
I think I got one expansion pack that came bundled with my started which I think is what you have
Yeah, I have opened my
Starter deck and I have quick start rules
There is a game at in here and then there is the stack of 60 cards that are sealed
yeah, and then there is a pack of
12 cards and I immediately when I saw this pack of 12 cards something activated my brain where I was like
I cannot wait to open these cut like
The primal childlike urge of like if someone gives me a pack of cards like I
Cannot wait to especially the collectible card game too because you could get like a very rare one
Which is what I pulled in one of these starter decks. I I don't have it with me
I have a card that's where they think five hundred dollars. Maybe I have like a bell card
That's very very rare that I pulled out of a starter the that expansion pack in a starter deck
So yeah, that's always that's always like, oh my god
That's always exciting too there I did see there was a video and I thought it was like
Beginner's Lurkana, but it was actually like a stock market. Like here's the current what current cards are going for
Like it was like a collector's market video. I'm like, okay, so this thing is caught on
What are you two in the world of this? Are you just yourselves or a human ear?
We're sorry you're looming ears. Okay. Forgive me. There's a lot
and but and
Why why do looming ears do this?
We're good to win to go on a quest to see who can go finish their quest first
Essentially, okay, and the quest is getting to 20 lore. Yes. Yes. So so this is like again
I you know all these games stem from from Magic the Gathering the same way
They're all like, you know kind of tabletop role-playing comes from from Dungeons and Dragons to some degree
And there you're attacking the other player and so like in that if we're playing Magic the Gathering then Carlson would have like a pool
Of hell of like 30 health and I would be trying to reduce his health to zero to kill him
But I think because it's Disney it's like well, we want to make this a little bit more abstract
It's about it's a race to get to who can accumulate 20 points for their own character first for their own Illumineer, right?
Yeah, so yeah, so I got I don't I didn't say we have to come up with their own personas as Illumineers
I think we can just be ourselves
But I don't know if you want to come up with something where like I'm Michael the great or the great Michael
Maybe I'll call myself the great Michael. This is your chance to inhabit a
Character who is very comfortable with sexuality. Oh, that's no
You're uncomfortable being someone who's comfortable with sex you don't want to be Bernard the mouse
Why well that's but that's already a character, huh Bernard is well you were inhabiting a character
Hard low-key like oh, yeah is Bernard your sort of hero when it comes to sexuality
I'm just saying he's a little guy, but it's pretty confident, you know
He gets Shasha Gabor, right? That's Shasha
Isn't Eva Gabor, I'm always a bar is it a Gabor? Okay. It sounds like a three-topic
Sisters you guys do other things. I'll I'm I always reverse it one is on Green Acres one is in rescue
Wrong. I can't remember. You might be right. Look, you have anything on that
You have to do a Gabor sisters deep dive on club three
1314 year old I was like, oh man the Gabor's they're so glamorous
That's why you're the most comfortable with sexuality you got all Gabor pill when you were little Gabor pill
Gabor. Yeah, I'm the oldest one here
So I remember like being seven and seeing like Johnny Carson like making like using the the Gabor's as like the most beautiful women like punch
Like like I was gonna name like a hot woman. It's like I was naming Kardashians today. I would name the Gabor's
Okay, well I was pretty close yeah, I want all your cards hey
Maybe there's one of the Gabor's in the
viral
Paramount plus a paramount photo that was going around a while ago
Oh, I wonder with all of the you know
Comes back around it's I was just happy to see the forest Kelly
That's really all you immediately honed in on the forest Kelly
Yeah from he was standing next to Tom crew a young Tom Cruise
But a red-blooded man like Jason goes for Gabor, right?
Yeah, no, I wanted to see if there's a photo and Gabor's in it you got a Gabor ommeter perpetually in your
Detecting Gabor there is a grant. There's a company that makes these big Star Trek figures
They're very tall and realistic and they just released the picture of their new de forest
Kelly figure with his like shirt open and he had got a medallion
It's from his look from Star Trek one. I was like, mmm. This is good. He's got a big bushy beard
This is good. I really like this Nick. You're gonna have to come back and play with that
Okay, I had to thin my deck a little bit because I did a count and I realized it's 70 cards because I just think I just
Tossed an expansion cards is 70 allowed. I thought 60
60 is the minute is like the floor. Okay, can have more than four of any type of car got it
So I'll just keep this as is for the the purposes of playing this playstation for cards got it
Okay, so you but you can have two tight two different stitch
Cards yes, if they're like different names or different art, but you can't have more than four of the same like
Foxrobin hood go and do and shootin bullseyes or something, right?
Cuz they'll be variants of of like the same like doc from the seven dwarfs, you know, like they'll be different
There's like this is doc leader of the seven dwarfs, but they're also might also be you know
Doc a guy with glasses or you mean like you'll have some sort of different title to it
Which which that one's you're allowed those can coexist
Okay, so we start with a starting hand and I've got the Disney Larkana app up here
Which has a pretty helpful tutorial and also has like a built-in counter which we can use to track our lore
So the the starting hand we shuffle your our deck and each draws a hand of seven cards, right?
So we'll do a little shuffling here shuffling as I we talk. Yes. Yeah now I do in this
Starter kit does have a mat and did you guys want to use a mat mat?
Yeah, there's a mat in here. There's a paper mat. Let's take a look
Is it I is it actually four? Oh, it's a it pulls out. Okay. Yeah
Is it big enough? It's very tight. It doesn't seem to be the rare show that does an audio unboxing
Well, I think that I think the thing I think what that that has like a place for your discard pile and like yeah
Like this is full. It's not like a full play mat. It's not okay. So this is a
Like a starter mat, yeah
Now Mike are you attempting to I mean we
You're attempting to film some of this
I don't know if I commit to actually posting any of it right and I'll cut that audio out if we don't okay, sure
But yeah in case anyone wants to see some of the exciting
card action here
Card table action. There is an okay. There'll be hopefully an okay video showing you what's going on here
Hopefully check in on my phone won't run out of battery before
How you guys feeling about what you're looking at?
Okay, so we I drew seven cards Carlson
I don't know if you've if you're gonna draw yours and then as part as part of this round we are allowed to
mull again
So you can take any number of these cards and then put them at the bottom of your deck and instead draw some
Replacements so a Gardner, I'll let you take a look at what I got here. Okay
so, you know, I just got a few different characters and
Okay, I think what I'm going to do
Is I'm going to
Mull again some I just just you know knowing how the other versions of these games work other types of these games work
I'm gonna mull again some of these higher cost cards to try to get some more lower cost ones that they could play earlier
So I'll just put like these three back
And I will draw three more mm-hmm. What are you doing Mike?
I'm gonna mull again a
Couple cards, but I'm actually pretty happy with my hand overall here
I'm gonna just actually put one back and then draw another and I'm going to quietly
Go through my starter kit and then I will probably burst out with excitement at inopportune times
To describe what I'm encountering and read that text read that flavor, but I will keep the cards far away
So it's not to confuse any gameplay. All right, and I would say if you feel the need to
Nick or Mike, you know bring Jason in to have him read anything as
I did bring a full set of Robin Hood Prince of Thieves trading cards. So those get mixed in please feel free to play
Which there is back in my mom's house a lot of Robin Hood Prince of Thieves Wow Brian Adams
Which song was that that's the one that's a song that I referred to Aaron and I refer to as three idiots
Because it's the way it's the three musketeers of music Brian Adams sting and Rod Stewart. Oh, yeah, the most like machismo
I don't know how Henley didn't get invited
All of the best like
They're all just screaming their parts no harmonizing just three screamers
No, there was a I think there was a I don't know if they they reteamed or they tried to
Recreate that with a different like trio, but there wasn't there a song for like the lethal weapon 3 soundtrack
That was a similar thing. It was like an invented super group to do like like I think it's it's probably me was the name
Oh, I don't know that wait a minute actually and as you were talking was maybe involved
I got to deduct some lore for myself. I think that's a song maybe from three musketeers
Not from is Robin Hood anything I do I do it for you. Yeah, that's what it is
Yeah, but still Brian Adams. So my first joke was right
All for one from the Disney three musketeers
Movie. Yes. Yeah. Okay. Yeah that song stuck in my head the other day and I'm like that has to be the Chris O'Donnell three musketeers
Right. Yeah, you can't Scott you gained a point from the Gabor sister thing, but then you lost you lost
So your quest is even sort of right now
Carlson, do you want to go first? One of us needs to go first? Yes
Okay, I will go first and then the first player does not draw a card, right?
so what I'm gonna do is I am going to
Let's see here. I am going to
Shoot this is interesting. This is interesting
Okay, keep saying it it'll be true I am going to take here I'm gonna take a boo Jason do you say I dropped my flounder?
Little bit of color here is flounder
Excitement dot-dot-dot adventure dot-dot-dot change you're lurking around every core. Ah
So flounder is screaming in agony
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna take this
Lefou card and I'm gonna put it in my inkwell. Yes
Okay
So I put it down face down here in my inkwell
And then what you do is you take the card and then you turn it
Like to the right to indicate that you're going to use the ink and then I am going to play
Archimedes. Oh, wow. Okay. So so in magic the gathering this would be called tapping your card
I think the language they have in Larkana is exerting your card. So you turn it flip that you turn it
No, I you leave it like that. I think until the next turn
Yes, okay. So yeah
So so you basically turn the card 90 degrees to signify that its powers have been exerted
So yes, so so what you have is like and what was the card you turn into ink Carlson?
The card I took was Lefou fan the flames an action card got it
So that card is now out of play and now it has just become a part of the ink pool
So he so Carlson can use that to
Pull other cards into play for the remainder remainder of the session. Yes. What do you think are the odds that this will take three hours?
That is like a guarantee that's the safest bet you just got 20 lure
Just gotta cut in I open the pack of 12 I got a hologram tinkerbell
So that's pretty cool. You'd be mad if you've realized you gave Jason like 500 bucks worth of
I thought about maybe giving him the pack and then saying but I get to keep the pack inside
I thought oh those exchanges were always so fun in childhood. What do you mean? Oh, yeah that like hey
You can have this action figure, but I get to take it back any time. I want oh, well, I didn't that wasn't what I was
Gonna do
Okay, here's our Hercules card and he's wearing a full lions main like the
Mythological Hercules so what's the what's the little text underneath Hercules like directly underneath what what's like his title you gotta admit
That was pretty heroic
Or wait, no, you want that's a flavor text, but what's that? What's like his title?
Dreamborn hero prince. Okay, so that this is like a different version of Hercules than the default Hercules. Yes. Okay got it
Okay, so, um, so are you are you done with your turn? I am done with my turn. Yes. So now it's my turn
So I can turn cards. I think the first thing is to turn cards into ink. Yeah, and I can do that once per turn
I'm gonna take this Gaston
This is a Gaston baritone bully. Okay chair down. I'm gonna look at that flavor text real quick. That might be fun
Yep, I like that. You should call him Gaston
Without like an E at the end. It's thinking about his stones. Yeah. Yeah Gaston's big stones flavor text. No one
sings like Gaston I
Think Gaston is as valid as Bucca di Pepo
I'm putting this down and then I don't have enough. Unfortunately does not give me enough ink to play one of the other cards in my
In my hand, so I will pass sounds like you don't have a very balanced deck. Well, you know
I got a starter deck. So I don't know what to tell you take it up with Ravensburger
Mr. Ravensburger. All right. Well, okay. I have to Ravensburg. I have to draw a card here
okay, and then I'm going to have to yes, I have to add to my inkwell and
Which card am I gonna strategically add to my inkwell Carlson?
I realize I forgot to draw a card last turn today. Did you're drawing one now and then just moving forward?
mmm
Yes, okay
It's a very polite game for now, I know I was thinking about okay, so what I'm gonna do is I am going to
Put in the inkwell, there's some a lot of pressure doing this. I'm like
I'm going to take Olaf the friendly snowman and put him in my inkwell
And wow, let me let Jason say this little piece of dialogue from Olaf and if you could do the voice I'd appreciate it
I'm Olaf and I like worm hugs
Okay, that is good we all agree
Your move dad and then I will activate I will activate my ink
right now and
I will
Shoot I can't play that
Exert chosen
Have another one. All right, you know what? I'm not gonna exert my ink
Okay, but I am going to quest with Archimedes Wow
And what how much lore do you get from questing Archimedes Archimedes gets one lore?
Okay, so in quest another feature of the Larkana app is that it has a lore counter
So player two on your side Carlson you will get I will increment you you and have one lore
Is there anything that might happen where you guys get like 10 or 15 or 18 lore?
And
It's possible that that would
Accelerate the game a bit you've activated the action of the Domino's pizza trackers
So none of you pass out to wearing this
Multi-hour endeavor
So at that point then my my turn is over and it's Wiger's turn, okay, so I am going to draw a card
I am going to
Turn something into ink. I think I'm going to turn
Cruella de Vil
Fashionable cruiser. Oh into ink. You want to take a look at that Sheridan? Uh, sure
Um, oh wait, I already read this oh then never mind
Okay, I'll put that one down so now I have to ink available I am going to exert this to ink so that I can
Play a card
The card I am going to play
is
I am going to play
Hercules hero in training. Okay, Hercules goes down to Hercules
Okay, yeah, and his ink is drying so you cannot play him correct because he's not he's just chilling right when will his ink be dry
Wiger has summoned a snapshot of the character. Yes, and is it but he's painted him with his bruh his lumineer brush
Okay, I think wait
Illumineer Illumineer Illumineer Illumineer. Okay. Yeah. All right. Okay, so I will draw a card. It's akin to imagine here
It's very yes similar. Okay, I will then
Will use
This a boo. He's got a sword action. Uh-huh a boo from Aladdin
I will put that in my ink well
And then I will turn in this this goes back here and then I will turn my three cards and I will play
One of Scott's favorite characters in fiction Peter Pan fearless fighter Wow, and I would like Scott
Oh
Scott's least favorite episode you wouldn't mind doing the voice and sort of the spirit of Peter
I think the heart would appreciate it
Okay
Nobody calls pan a coward and lives I'll fight you man-to-man with one hand behind my back
Wow, perfect. Wow
Even through my protest
So so disgusting your turn is gross. My turn is gross. I cancel your turn. Okay, that's okay
And Peter remember Peter's ink isn't dry Scott. He's wet still. Yes, Peter's ink is still wet
So my ink is so wet
So what I'll do though is
Archimedes I'm gonna turn I'm in a quest with Archimedes Wow, and I'm gonna get another point on my little quest
So that's very exciting. Yeah, you're you're definitely in the lead now. You got to lore. I've yet to get on the board. Okay
Let's see
So I can draw card first thing I can do. Mm-hmm
I have a
Just keep seven if it's seven you don't have to you can play but yeah
But I mean like that's like what you're starting hand sizes
But if you play enough cards on a turn you can go below. I only have four right now. Yeah
Okay, so
I'm going to turn a card into I'm gonna turn sleepy
From the seven dwarves from the seven dwarves find four ways to describe sleepy
What is this one? This one is nodding off?
Is that an action or is it a character? This is a character sleepy. Yeah, this is nodding
That's his title. So to put sleep mine to into my ink. Well
Yes, I just I really take pity on your listeners because I am bored to tears and I'm playing
You know if you get the variant sleepy he nods off with a cigarette in his hand
That can activate like a fire effect yeah, yeah that roofs made a straw
Kidley
Okay, let's see. How many of these do I want to exert? Sorry. I was preemptive there
I think I do want to do something with Hercules so I can attack you right?
Yes, you can attack me. Yes
You can attack Archimedes because he is sort of prone. He's on a quest right now
Yeah, and and you can't attack pan yet
But you can attack Archimedes and then it basically is just you can attack with two and your defense sort of is three
I know there's other terms for it
So you will deal two damage to Archimedes and he will get taken out of the game and you will be dealt to
Damage and you will be now injured but still in play. Yeah, so I am going to do that. I'm going to
Exert Hercules take Archimedes out of there. Okay, Hercules has killed Archimedes the owl. Yeah, that's great. Here we go
Now we're talking I want every the listener all think of Hercules from Disney. He just murdered Archimedes
You think with a sword or did he like take a big bite out of him?
I think this is the best way we can bring it to life for the listeners
Wow, he just picked up an owl and took a big bite out of its stomach exactly
But Hercules took damage as well. Yes, correct. He has two damage Archimedes did deal him some damage
He got in some nibbles on Hercules leg. So he is hurt
We'll leave Hercules prone to any sort of pan attack I might want to do next game next round
Now damage there are like punch out just paper damage counters. We do have counters which
Calculate I think damage in the app too. I don't know about that
But you can certainly deal it like that and just two little damage token put two little circles on top of the card
Yeah, and I believe that's how it outs how it works, right? The character does have a constant health pool
It's not that it resets every turn it doesn't reset
Yeah, there's can be healing action and stuff got it can do to bring him back
The other move I'm going to do is I'm going to now I'm self-conscious about the pronunciation
But I'm going to put down Gaston. Oh, there we go. That was fun. Yeah, yes. All right. Yes, and his ink is not dry
It's not dry. So I have tapped my three ink so I can put him down. Got it
Okay, so I will now draw a card and I am going to reset my inks
And then I will take let's see here I will take
Let's see. I have another Abu. Okay, that will be going into the ink. There's two monkeys now in my ink. Wow. Well
But that's okay, and then I want I know it's on your side, but I want them both to devour pan so
To a booze eating a human. Yeah
He's a phrase not a forever dog
Okay
Okay, so I'm gonna put down now I'm gonna I am going to
Attack Hercules with yes. Okay, that is what's going to happen now pan has three attack and two defense
So yeah, Hercules has two. Okay. I mean this would this would also take out pan. Yes, it will
Okay, so this is this is I'm sacrificing pan to get rid of Hercules. Oh, no
Pan has been taken off
but then I will
Activate my ink and I'm going to play Maleficent Sorceress
Play this character. You may draw a card night. So I've played her ink is not dry yet
But I get to draw another card right now
So I will have options as you know, can she turn into a dragon?
But can weger throw down a card that lights that dragon on fire?
It's a cut maintenance hours due to the end of a fiscal quarter
Is that card chairman Josh tomorrow a card in this game? And should he be maybe in our
Some daddy I got handsome daddy, I just want to cut in I opened my
60 count card starter deck which was gingerly wrapped in tissue paper
Yes, the first two cards are two of the same
Ariel voiceless and her flavor text is just dot dot dot because she's voiceless
Next card was a shiny hologram Moana card pretty cool. Okay. Okay
pretty cool
So why are you a hologram Mickey Mouse? Oh hell yeah
Mike is it any extra trouble if you just add like kind of a shimmery sound effect every time a hologram
Yeah, if you don't mind maybe we could also just like insert like a local sports game in between when we're trying to decide to sort
of fill the
And he walks
Back to I go well, I think I'm gonna
Jeannie is in my hand now
Let me take five minutes to figure out if I'm playing him or not
Are you don't are you doing with your time done? Yeah, okay great. So I'm gonna draw a card
Mm-hmm. I am going to take
this song card
Painting the roses red right and I'm going to put this into my inkwell
So that is going to my ink pool. So now for ink I am going to now I have a
Lefou card lefou lefou lefou I have a lefou card. I know this I'm just overthinking it now
I got a lefou card which I can now the lefou has an ability that is loyal
So if you have a character named Gaston in your play in play
You play one less ink to play this character so I can play a lefou for one ink now
So I'm going to tap one ink or exert one ink so I can get lefou in the play field
That leaves me with three ink, which I am going to use
to also get
Sneezy into the play field shit so I can tap to
Get Sneezy down and Sneezy has high defensive. He has not a particularly high attack, but he has for defense, which is pretty good
Yeah, and then also I believe this is how this works
So Gaston has a song a singer ability of five so he can sing a song up to a cost of five. Yes
um, and a character with two or more can
Uh can exert to sing this song for free
So I'm going to exert I am going to exert to sing the song legend of the sword in the stone. Oh my god
Um, which gives a chill. Oh wait. No, I don't want to do this. What is that? Oh, that's oh wait
I'm just gonna do it anyway. I'm gonna do it anyway
I didn't really know what this was doing, but I just was excited to sing a song
So exert to sing the song legend of the sword of the stone, uh, which gives a character
A chosen character gains challenger plus three
Uh plus three while challenging but it doesn't really isn't really gonna do anything because neither cards have summoning sickness. Is anybody gonna sing anything?
Well, you don't have Jason Jason. Could you sing the sword in the stone song? Jason Jason
It's the sword in the stone, it's his future. Let's go
Legend is sung when england was young and knights were brave and bold
Okay, so kind of given given big ups to england, uh, you know
I'm realizing also there's 11 and this needs to go separately my discard
Hercules because this is out of play now. I just really so the ink cards. It's fun to play a song
Card is just one ink. Yes, you don't need to look on the card and calculate ink via that correct
Yes, okay
That makes a lot more sense because i'm i was like, how are they remembering how much ink they have no functionally
What you're doing is whatever the cost of this card so like it could be like hey
I'm getting a high ink card in this costs a lot of ink to play
I'm getting it on turn one
So the way to get utility out of now is by turning it into ink so they can use it to play other cards
Okay, but that also like means that you're taking a powerful card out of play for future turns
And how do you calculate how much ink a card requires? So that's in the upper left hand corner there
That the will number three oh, oh that's no that's yes, so that's the ink this is the strength and that's the health, okay?
god this sucks
I'm really caught between deciding i'm deciding should I try to learn?
Or should I not because I won't need to know this by the end of today
Well, hey, you have a you have a lot of time to decide. Oh man
Yeah, we're still uh, we're it's still for this this race to 20 it is two to zero
We're putting in the scores none of that got us closer no
Are we are we now maybe in the running?
This could very well be longest episode ever just by sheer mechanics of what it is
Pick up the pace once we get more cards into play because then you could when you have more ink you can
Put bigger cards on the table that more ability to gain lore faster
If I requested all three of these cards at once I would get four lore
So, you know, he really should do it
That's the thing if I put in if I if I try to pull a joke then I lose time points
That makes it all go longer. That's my personal struggle. Oh, yeah, that's a good point. Uh, uh,
okay, so
Uh, I am going to
I am going to uh, that's a good card, but i'm gonna take jafar keeper of secrets. Wow, and i'm gonna put it in my ink
Um, and then I am going to play just like uncle sam
Yeah, there's got to be a genie without his wrist gauntlets on
And i'm going to then uh take my ink i'm gonna play
Uh a tinker bell peter pan's ally card. Wow, I should have waited and not gotten rid of pan
um, but then i'm also going to
Uh quest maleficent
And get one
Okay, lore points. So scott. We're on the road here. I have three points. Okay. There are three. Okay
Oh, wait, no, you didn't just get three points. No, you're at three points. All right
I have a total so that's something. Okay. Okay. I am good. I'm done now. I gotta say just
I am rooting for mike now purely functionally
He's closest to the exit and therefore I am too. Well, we'll see how this goes
Okay, so it's my turn i'm gonna draw a card
Oh, okay
Did you guys like a hot robin hood card I don't know I yeah
Ba-ba-boom
Um, I don't know. No, I don't I don't know exactly what this means is the thing
I'm I'm like reading it trying to figure out on the air here. Yeah
You take your time. Uh
Okay
Does it mean I get to double tap one of my characters? What does that mean?
Yeah, that's what I wonder i'm gonna hold on this one
In fact, I might just i'm just gonna turn this card into ink because I don't understand it
We can try and figure it out. This is binding contract, right?
I imagine is that is that a little mermaid thing? Is that where that's from? Oh, right
Because that's kind of alive right like the pen comes up of its own volition
So this is a this lets you I believe double tap one of your characters. The ability is for all eternity
So I think you can just like exert a character twice, right?
I think that but I don't know exactly if that's exactly what it is and what that means exactly
So i'm just gonna put that into my ink. So I now have five ink
I'm going to use
Uh, one, two, three four ink to play the knock
water spirit
And then the hell's that from?
Fantasia 2000 it might be I feel like we should know this but I among the four of us
But I don't know what the knock the knock not the group that did my sharona. Yeah
It is cool art. Uh, no, okay
And the knock is not the neck
Is it the nick? No, it's not the nick either the dirty hospitals. No, no
Okay, not that either and it's not nick from knickknack the snowman pixar move, which is the first that comes is it?
No, that's a horse. Okay
Um, I am going to now an exerted character. I can still go after right? Correct and tinkerbell has just been summoned
So tinkerbell's not target not dry. Got it. Uh, I am going to use uh, uh gaston to take out maleficent
Okay, so maleficent's out of play and gaston gets a minus two two minus two counter. Correct. Yes
And maleficent's out. I am going to quest. Uh lafou and sneezy, uh, which gives me three lore
So here we go. I'm on the board
There's three moves great, yeah, wow, wow i'm in it, uh
The knock is from frozen two
I just proved I never saw frozen two. It's into the unknown. That's the song from that
Uh, uh, oh, okay. Here we go. All right. Well carlson is working through this this turn
There is a restaurant I believe shared and i've heard you mention on on ptr, which is uh, romano's macaroni grill
Yeah, yeah
I now I have a lot of fondness for romano's macaroni grill and so my ears perked up when when that was mentioned
I believe the the two of you have not been to romano's is that correct or been it's been forever
It's been a while since you've been in carlson. Have you been to a romano's never
I think look we'll figure out whatever it is
But I think that could be a good candidate because we've never done a dough boys for a for a ptr dough boys episode
All right
I think we might have to go down to carson california, but we we I think we it's doable
That's the closest one. There used to be one in northridge. You remember that's probably been gone for a long time
There is one right in the center of the orlando airport like right in the security that's the one to go to
Let's all do that then. All right. Yeah, meet you guys in orlando
I will say if that doesn't come together my other pitch is to we all go to dean norris from breaking bad's
Barbecue restaurant to mecula. I love that idea. Oh, I love barbecue. Yeah. Well, he's out there. He's out there
Like alan hale jr
Like just hanging out with everybody he's on instagram constantly talking come on down tonight
Uh, you know, we got a you got a jerry jr over here playing guitar on the fatty
We got a bunch of ribs
We got a bill. Yeah, come on down
And then a couple months ago like they would constantly run out of barbecues. We'd be like hey everybody if you're coming down tonight
Don't uh, we are out of ribs
We're out of brisket. Uh, so sorry if you're making the trip
That's so fun
That is actually a standard feature of barbecue restaurants where they they run
They've run out some I follow on instagram will put up stories like crossing off what they're out of as the night goes on
I think they've taken care of their supply issues. I have not seen one of these do not come tonight messages from him in a while
That's too bad though. He should make them anyway
Yeah, there's more stakes to as an actor it's more fun to play sometimes he sings with the musician that's playing on the patio too
Oh, hell. Yeah, man. So that seems like his vibe. Oh, yeah. Yeah, we gotta go. Okay
We could do two episodes. Okay, gator. Were you because he was doing he was around funnier dial
I think you'd already left at that point. I don't think I yeah
I don't think I had a deal like the final season of breaking bad. I remember like the the day after his episode aired
With his when his character was killed
I was like on the phone with dean norris, or it was so weird
It's such a strange thing to like everybody he's just whole thing. He's like yeah, we'll do a funny video about it
It'd be great. It's like all right. Oh, did he makes it was it some video where he like comes back?
He like punches through the yeah, he comes back
I helped out with the script and then I actually directed it. Okay. Yeah, lovely man. Okay
So I'm going to I don't have any cards that will let me put ink down
So i'm gonna just activate my ink and put down bruno madrigal wow out of the shadows
story-borne
Um right there and then I will take tinker bell
I guess i'm
I guess i'm gonna quest with her
Maybe this is a bad strategy. No, I think as we go here. Maybe I my strategy is poor is not thought out
This is both of our of our first games and you know, like the ultimate goal is to accumulate 20 lord
That gives you two more on the board
And uh, so I I think it's I think it's a valid thing to do right now. Yeah, okay, so I am going to
Your turn is done. Correct. All right, so i'm gonna
Unexert all these characters the counters remain on gaston. I am going to unexert my ink
And I am going to draw a card now
My understanding is that adding to my ink pool is optional, right? Like you don't have it's not
Tori each turn to it last time. Yeah, that's that that that's that's what I thought. Okay, so I am going what I'm going to do is
I am going to
Exert all of my ink
And this will let me put down a five
Cost card the queen
Wow witch queen from snow white. Yes, the snow white queen. Wow, this is uh, the the this is
Outstanding oh i'm sorry commanding presence is the title here and I think this character is so
Has so much going on that it does not actually have flavor text
So whenever this character takes a breather jason chosen opposing character gets minus four
Health or attack this turn and chosen character gets plus four health this turn. I don't understand what that is exactly
We'll figure it out. Um, okay. So what i'm going to do is
Oh boy, bruno has a lot of health. Oh, yeah
Okay, it's a powerful card. Yeah, that really is it doesn't make sense. He lives with rats
The rats they'll give him strength
Can I now can I attack the same card with multiple cards I can do that, right?
Oh, I that's good. I'll let you do it. I say yes, I think that's how it works
I think I can I think I can i'll let you do it. Yeah, so i'm going to to take the knock here
Oh my god the knock
I'm going to take the knock and i'm going to exert the knock and i'm also going to exert
Lefou and I am going to take out a bruno
Well bruno isn't uh, you can only attack oh never mind because I didn't oh right, right, right
Okay, then what i'm going to do instead is i'm going to uh, oh right, right, right
I'm gonna take this is what i'm gonna take gaston
Uh who has a three attack and is almost out of health anyway and use that to take out tinkerbell
So tinkerbell has been killed by gaston. Oh my god. So how do you do it? Gaston is also dead
How he's a murder suicide it's a murder suicide
Oh, yeah
Well, I don't I don't I guess I shouldn't have all the characters eat each other
But you know, he's uh, maybe if he's like reaching for a bunch of eggs and then grabs her accidentally and chokes on her
Yeah, yeah. Oh, okay. So he choked. Yeah, so they took them out took them both out. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, that makes sense
You know i'm realizing was recommended in one of the tutorials i'm gonna start doing is that you have a different place for your
Newly summoned characters to remember. Yeah, so i'm gonna start putting them at the lower deck here
Are you doing anything? Are you questing? Are you going i'm going to quest the rest of these so lefou
Sneezy and the knocker all questing and that gives me an additional four
So i'm up to seven more
I was gonna say if it goes any longer scott's gonna be double tapping himself in the lake
So you can get the ambulance here to try to give away
Oh man, I am I you can't be mad at me if it's a medical emergency
I'm mad about some of my some of my choices here, too
Because I i'm i'm running low on a new ink
I think it's funny by the way that that like i'm questing the grandeur of that term
And then that means you turn the cards 90 degrees. Yeah. Wow a quest i'm exerting
It's funny the specific because these all have all these games have the same sort of mechanics
But they all have insist on a specific vocabulary
It's like how zombie movies like none of them say zombies. They're all like, oh it's walkers or groaners
Um, i'm just gonna pass i'm i'm done my turn is done
Well, you should at least you should at least quest bruno and get a lore, right?
But he's only got one lore and he leaves him vulnerable. No, i'm not going to so you're just gonna leave him as is
I'm leaving him as is so I so if a character does not get exerted. They are not vulnerable to attack
I don't believe that's the rule set. Okay. Got it. Hey bad news everybody
All our ink has been exerted repeat all our ink has been exerted
Don't come down got no more next weekend open up some cooking up some great new ink for you, but uh
Okay, I just drew a card
Yeah, um, I am going to uh
Unexert all of my characters and then exert all of my ink
Um, jason loves to exert his ink. Oh, okay
It's very comfortable with it
Okay, I still don't quite understand how this questing works whenever this character quest
Chosen opponent opposing character gets minus four this turn
So I think what I could do you can attack I could I could use it on bruno
But because bruno is just hanging at just idling bruno's not a target now
We could be wrong about that rule, but that's just how we're going to play it for right now
Okay, so I am all i'm going to do this turn then is i'm going to um
I'm going to
Get some more cards in the play field. I'm going to um
Uh tap or exert
1234 ink
And then I am going to play out my hand cruella goes down. Wow another lefou goes down
Wow, and i'll put those in this lower deck so we can see that they are badly
They are summoning they're they have a summoning sickness and then i'm going to exert
My four remaining cards, which gives me another two four
six
Lore so i'm up
Wow, okay scott is exerting now, yes
Very
So it's funny. This is the it's the it's the cool fantasy fighting game. Oh, who's in it lots of lefou's
Well, I think if you have like a better construct like if you don't just take an off-the-shelf starter deck
And you curate a little bit more you can probably have a little bit more like creativity with your bill
I will say i'm getting a lot of dupes in here. I would say I like playing the game
It's i'm actually having fun. It is very fun
It's just a pressure to uh make this sound good or entertaining to vocalize every internal thought
You can't leave anything in your brain. Let me just say we knew going in this was going to suck
And then also I think everyone who voted for also knew it was going to suck
Grim fascination of just like I want to see what this actually is
I I think they should appreciate that club three is the place for experimentation for an episode that doesn't feel like any other episodes
Yes, you're like you're the test lab
I think we they will appreciate we've chosen to fall on the double-edged sword
And add some jokes in here that are making the game longer. Yes. Yeah. Yeah
Every single time we open our mouths. That's great. Um, okay, so I finally have a chance to add to my ink
and
Minnie mouse is going into the ink. Wow
Minnie always classy it says and it says her fashion sense is always spot on and that's true. And now she's ink
And you're not allowing jason to do that voice because it'll confuse things for you too much. No, you caught on
Thank you for noticing that
So what i'm gonna do is then i'm going to uh, uh turn all my ink on my six inks
Oh boy, we got a big boy coming out putting madame medusa into play here
Wow
That it says the boss and then it says that terrible woman
When you play this character banish chosen opposing character with three or less
So I can get rid of let's say
Right here. Sneezy's out. Sneezy is out madame medusa has killed him. Wow. R.I.P. Sneezy. R.I.P. Sneezy
Um, so she's he had a tough life though. He might be happier out of his misery
He's freed of his condition when he's sneezing he says kill me in between
And then what i'm gonna do is i'm going to
uh, uh
I'm going to attack lafou with bruno
I want to make this game longer is what i'm gonna do is gonna die
Yeah, and then he has to is it to r.i.p get dealt. Is that what it was? Is that how it works? You exert it
You exert him. Yeah, but it's two damage. Is that right for the yes. He no. No, he only does one damage
He has a health pool of two, but yeah, so he's only gonna take one there. Awesome. Sorry
I'm happy to go to the afterlife because gueston's already there
Uh, okay, so my turn is done. Wow. Okay
uh, i'm going to take
Uh the queen and the knock and I am going to unexert them
I am moving my other lafou and my cruella up to the front line because they are no longer their ink is dried
Um, this guard pool is over here. You just played madame medusa, right?
Or do you do you want to roll back? I mean does rolling back the video help? I think you just I think you just I just
Or did I finish my turn?
I can't have finished my turn because my characters are unexerted. Yeah, I just attacked
I just got rid of that and I just attacked you attacked. Yeah, so I got rid of two of your cards
And I think it's you. Okay, you haven't finished your turn. Do you have to exert bruno to attack? I think you do, right?
Oh, so he should be like this. I think so. Yeah. Yeah, sorry. Sorry. Okay, you're right. Okay
All right. So it's my turn now. We took a little we had a little bit of a stop down for video
Uh, but I I think we were picking up in the right place
So I I am drawing a car. Oh wait, I had a card. Where the fuck did my card go? It's over there. Oh there
It was on the couch. Yeah, I moved we had like a little bit of a break
So I moved over there and I put my the one card in my hand over on the couch by my back. Okay
So I drew another card
And I I I am going to go ahead and play
Um popsicle. This is an item. This requires one popsicle ink. Oh, it's utopia popsicle
Yes, right. Uh, so so i'm tapping one ink exerting one ink and what this lets me do is it just lets me draw another card
So i'm going to draw another card
Uh, okay
Do you have to exert the popsicle?
Uh, I think the popsicle just gets played and he just goes away
He just goes to the discard pile after his effect. Okay. Okay, uh, but we could catch
um and then
I get to I i'm going to let's see
Uh minus two
Uh, I don't know how this works
I'm so confused
So this is an item that I have I have one item in one character and i'm tempted to play the item
Then maybe we can just figure it out because I think this might let me do something on the board
So I am going to exert three remaining ink and i'm going to play the fang crossbow
The fang crossbow is an item and the chosen a chosen character
Gets
um
minus two
Oh, wait, does this require more ink?
What does this mean? Do you do you understand this carlson?
Uh, well, it's three after carefully. Yeah three inks
So I exerted the three ink to play it down right i've exerted one for the popsicle three more for that item
We're gonna have to send jason back to watch more videos. He's gonna have to watch this
I think that i'm confused as well
I don't know if you can play both of these at the same time or like both those things happen or one of them
You chose one of them i'm, not sure well I can either I can banish a chose a chosen dragon character
But you don't have any dragon so that's moot
But I do have careful aim which lets me give a chosen character minus two
Attack this turn, right? That's what that means minus two attack. I believe so. Yep
So what i'm going to do is i'm going to give the fang crossbow to the queen
The queen has four attack
And since uh bruno has minus one health from a pool of four
I can go ahead and and exert the queen
Right the queen now can attack with four and uh bruno will have minus two attack
Which means the queen will survive despite only having a health pool health of three
Uh with minus two minus one counters and bruno will and bruno is bruno's gone. The queen is killed bruno
Wow, wow, we don't talk about bruno anymore
Fang crossbows go to my discard pile
And then I am going to go ahead and exert my remaining cards or quest my yeah to quest them
So the nock lefou and carilla duvill
All get quested and that gives me an additional four lore to bring me up to 17. Oh my god. Wow
This you know
You mentioned the videos and uh, there was a video that was pretty good at explaining all this from the channel inc born heroes
But I just took a picture of like all the things you can do during a round and it's like six options
Yes, it's too many
you just did like four three or four things and i'm like
I I am so confused like i'm like, okay, so you can do multiple things
In your round. Yeah
basically the limiting factor is is the limiting factors are the number of cards in your hand and then the amount of ink you have
in your pool, yeah, so like
Because I only have four five ink I can't play a six six ink card carlson has more ink available. So
Yes, well, let's see if I can add even more ink to this score by the way 17 to five
Yeah, i'm i'm getting destroyed. Yeah early lead and then well my beloved mini is going to also go back into the ink
Well, wow, she's back my one
Uh, it doesn't matter how many you play but she's got the ability to be turned into ink. What's her description?
This is the same one it's her fashion sense is always spot on get it because of the spots
um, I wonder if there's like there's like a canon justification or explanation for what's happening when a character gets turned into ink because
It sounds kind of grim because they can't come back from being they can't know once they're once they're turned into ink for the remainder
Of that that play session. Well, they're not the real characters. They're just right sketches of from our illumineers paint brush
So in my mind since they're not dry yet, they sort of just melt into just a general ink pool
Yes, and then when they're over here on the board
they sort of solidify in a way where the ink is there and like it now it's like kind of stuck to the
God's easel or whatever. Got it. It's kind of like sperms that don't make it all the way
You could call it. Yeah, that's true. That's a good. Yeah, it's like illuminating illuminating sperms. Yeah
I'll try not to think about it
So so many is just kind of like dissolving into a pool of illumineer sperms just picture that
Yeah, yeah, and mike just has a lot of illumineer sperm like lied at
I got seven sperm. I've just turned over. Um, and I would like to play ursula. Wow power hungry
And that's her she's got two. She's got seven cost card. Look at that. Yeah
So what i'm gonna do then?
With madame medusa i'm trying to should I
Feel so hopeless to just get one lore because like what am I even doing? Maybe I should just attack
It's like a free throw every little bit helps. I guess that's true
Let me um
Attack
Jason
Oh
He's the corner of the card on his face lefou i'm attacking i'm gonna take lefou out
Um, and I will be dealt two or no. He's got only got one
So I only got one. Yeah there because lefou is out there two lore get two lore on a quest
still 17.5, but you got a
Damage I took lefou out
All right, what i'm noticing lefou is a seems a pretty a lore efficient card because he only costs
Right, he's got two ink
Yeah
But he costs one less ink if you have gaston in there and then you can he gets two lore every time you exert him so
Versus like a character like the nock that's a more expensive car, but only gives you one lore
Yeah by exerting madame medusa. Did you gain any lore? No, you only get I haven't quested with her
So so so exerting only gets you lore
This is so dumb
Exerting only gets you lore if you if that's the only thing you do with that character
If you're trying to use that character for another purpose, then like that's that's what their their attention is at. Yeah
Okay, uh, all right. So you're done with your turn. Yeah
All right. I'm going to
Uh, yeah, I mean, I this is the thing i'll play out the turn but i'm going to win this turn
Uh, so i'm going to unexert all of my cards. I have three characters on the board karela the queen and the nock
I drew a card
Which is painting the roses red
I am going to turn that into ink and then exert all of these just for the sake of adding to the board
I'm going to add on gaston intellectual powerhouse. This is a gaston variant
Which has developed brain when you play this character look at the top three cards in your deck
You may put one in your hand put the rest in the bottom of your deck in any order
So i'm going to go take these three out. I have i'll just show it everyone. I have another nock
I have a dock knock in the dock
Those guys are going to the bottom of my deck and i'm going to keep dopey
But dopey is just going to remain in my hard my my my hand where he will uh, the card will remain in my hand
That's why I meant like I conflated the hand and card into hard. It sounded weird. Dopey's gonna remain hard
And I am going to turn
Uh all of exert all these characters and that is going to take me all the way up to 21 lore
It means I win this inaugural jeez that was pretty fast actually
For all the great for the the boy it seemed at the beginning
It's really like that could be at a three hour
Pace but maybe but I don't know like I don't know any I don't understand a lot of what I just saw
But it sure seems to me like wyger kicked ass here. He did. I mean that was a fit
What 21 to 5 is the final?
But we also it's this is the thing is like we're both like figuring out how to play the game and the one thing
I know from from collectible card games is that like you kind of want to control like the board
Uh, because there is an ultimate goal
And if you're just trying to race to i'm going to try to burst down my opponent's health in a normal game
Or here i'm going to try to get my lore score up
What will happen is that your opponent against the advent can can have card advantage and have just more cards available
So they can take more actions so like here just because I have four cards and and and carlson has two
I I think he just has fewer options for what he can do during
If it is a pre-made deck also, I think they obviously it was a good
They they went because this was one of the pre-made starter decks. Yes. Yeah, because I started to get on very uneven
When I was drawing my cards as well. I'm blaming it on the fact that I put my own deck together as well
I would say that's part of what's fun about these you can do that
You can you can kind of go rogue and and and do your own thing
But yeah, that that's that you can actually end up with something more optimized
But some of these starter decks, I think it's just a lot more newbie friendly. Yeah, I mean look at
There's all these cards that went like goofy in a weird like squirrel flight suit kind of a thing rocks nice all these different
So there I I think I was also putting cards in that just looked fun as well
So I wasn't the strategy i'm gonna learn over time when we have our weekly men's lorcona night
We'll turn this into a regular thing and it's not women not allowed
You're gonna be pushing so many women away
Don't you play lorcona women are not allowed but stogies are must
Oh, yeah, so it's gonna stink and we're not gonna be able to breathe properly our lorcona cards are gonna smell like stogie smoke
Yeah, so he hates cigar. This is a real runner
You've been many times you see i've never heard you say a word with more hate in your heart than stogie
Oh, it's from growing up on the jersey shore beaches when someone would just smell
It just it just travels on the wind. It just smells so bad
It I don't love second hand cigarette smoke either but like cigarettes first hand
Oh first hand cigarette is great. Yeah
Uh the smell stogies, uh, I do like uh, this starter deck has multiple dingle hopper cards, which is of course
The fork from little mermaid and what what does the dingle hopper do exactly?
Uh remove up to one damage from a chosen character
Oh, so it just lets you heal so I could use the dingle hopper on the queen and get rid of one of these minus ones
Um, if I have a cut or a wound, I don't want no dingle hopper coming for it. Well, that's just a fork
Going to an urgent care and they're like well, uh, what else I can give you is
Advil and a dingle hopper
Sounds like a medical term like six hundred dollars
Um, if we had to sort of post game it and mike maybe I like I don't know if you want to like kind of assume
the like defeated, you know basketball post game like slumped with
uh towel around your neck like if I uh, you know if I can just throw out a like, uh,
Uh, well, I don't know. What do you think happened there?
Well, I think I need to have more cards that are uh, uh have the ability to be turned into ink
I think I need to have more because you know these these cards you can't without the border on them
But these cards with the border so I want to make sure that I have enough at least one card per hand
Or any time I have a turn, excuse me that I can do that with
Um, yeah, that's number one one thing I noticed about the starter deck is that almost every one of these cards can be turned
Into ink. Yeah, that's like it's just like that border is like so key
Which order the so you see like it's got like the thicker sort of outline
So yeah
This this is actually judy hops here as opposed to the hades card that you have the judy hops can be turned into ink
But hades because it does not have the thicker border cannot be coming. Oh, yeah
Um, and I also think I maybe I was too aggressive in the early goings, you know, I was too attacky
I was too questing
I should have maybe built up more of sort of an army of things had more cards on the table all at once
Because ultimately when weiger was playing, you know four cards once I think he was able to get a big lead going when he could
so your advice to players
Out there would be to not uh blow your load
So to speak, I think that's right. Yes, right
I I think that that part of that might carlson might come from because you've gotten so many reps in marvel snap
And again, that's just like a much faster game. It's like a six turn game
And so I think just the pace of that record like, you know, usually rewards more aggression
Yeah, this is more of an a methodical. Yeah. Yeah, it's a thinking man's game. Not like that marvel snap is
Very much like aggro sort of aggressive type of a person that gravitates like my natural
Yeah, it's a lot of attacking too. It's a lot of attacking there are like different
Elements in marvel snap. We didn't even get into the inky the six types of caught the amber
Amethyst emerald ruby sapphire steel. Well, you can only have two types in one deck two types in one deck. Yes
Yeah, I have an amma am of what is the word amethyst amethyst and ruby deck
This is again like, you know, because they they they yeah
They they want to all have their own sort of flavor
But like they they all pretty much all these have some sort of coloration system
But yeah, I have like a blue yellow deck and I don't know which colors those are exactly I guess sapphire and like topaz or whatever
They say whatever they call yellow
Uh, yeah, what did I just call yellow saffron? Who knows amber amber amber. There you go. Yeah
Um, well, do you are you satisfied with the degree we got into it jason?
Oh very great. Wow. I think we really covered some inks there. Uh, why your post game? How does it feel?
I feel great. I mean like look I was I was ready for defeat
I I know I figured carlson would come prepared
So, you know and I also just was like figured like it's it's a it's both of our first games
So we don't really you know, we're anything that we're learning. Yeah
Yeah, we're but but I feel pretty good because I just I feel like I was I have a much better understanding of how it actually
All works now mechanically. Um, and I also just had a lot of fun. I thought this was a lot more fun than I expected
Yeah, yeah, I like I like the guy I would like to yeah
For us, yeah, not for anyone listening to it
Sometimes you got to do episodes for you we there was talk there was talk of
We should have bet something at the start when we didn't end up betting. Oh, yeah
We're all about betting now. We'd love to bet and I was I totally forgot about it too because I was rolling around different bets
Uh, um, I was like, well, is there a scenario or like if I lose we lose jason to two episodes of doughboys for a week
or something
Um, i'd love that
I guess he did not an exchange month. He does. Yeah treat month
There was uh, you know, there was some talk of a doughboys episode months ago when we were texting of uh an episode about
Uh chicken wings and paul mccartney's wings. Oh, yeah. Oh boy
So yeah, any of those would have been a good good bet to make but we didn't do it
So well, I think there was also the next next time there was also a little bit of like I I
I already feel like I kind of took over your format for this episode this this kind of self-indulgent episode
So I was like, I don't know if I want to be like the stakes like I have another right thing that I want
You to do on the pot, you know
I mean, so I was like, I think I think it was fine just for it just to be a friendly
Yes, I agree. I agree. I agree. Yeah. Yeah, we don't have to lose jason for right
As he would not be allowed to appear on our show for like like there would be no that would have been the rules of it
Wow, the doughboys are reviewing candy apples
The doughboys are reviewing big lollies
Yeah
In a deeply negative episode stogies
It's kind of you put it in your mouth it's kind of food if you stretch your definition
I understand jason's by the way distinction
I understand your distinction between cigarette guys and cigar guys because it's a cigarettes
That's a working class thing and the scar guys like I just think of like tom selleck on cigar aficionado magazine
It's all like nra guys like it's like it became like a really
Right-wing, you know affectation like rudy. Giuliani is like a big cigar guy. This is like the worst fucking yeah
Yeah, so I don't know I think if jason got a stogie in his mouth he might can reconsider though
Yeah, I think he might like it. Let's see. Is that a future?
Find a stogie jason would like oh, no
Just what I need more complications for my health
Excellent. Well, look we've now that we've thrown it out there. You're gonna unfortunately have to do it
Oh shit, just telling your doctors that you've taken up cigars
Yeah, going down the list like you drink like, oh maybe one or two beers a month, right they're like you're a smoker. Well, I
unfortunately a stogie guy
Can you stop that uh, we would really prefer you did not your stogie intake I can't I can't
How many big lollies a month
Oh jesus
Like the fantasy of like jason goes to visit jason goes to dole boys camp for a couple days and then it's like pleasure island
You make them play pool and smoke
I think there's also an element of like when you become a cigar guy you have to go to like cigar
lounges like that's like you hang out in places with other guys who are smoking big stogies and that's like city walk and
Oh, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. Well you start all only wanting to hang out with people with the same like kind of weird mustard coloration
Well, hey I I think it was fun and I boy, you know
As soon as I realized that it wasn't just one point every one lore every turn
I my spirits really picked up and I had a blast
Uh, uh, so thank you for bringing this to us, uh, nick wyger you survived podcast the ride your bravery saved our podcast
Well done freedom fighter. Thank you. We get to give the guest the uh, the most emotional line in uh, in all of theme park
Uh, it's exit through the gift shop anything you want to plug?
Hey, you know check out dough boys podcast about chain restaurants with mike mitchell and and me and also check out uh get played video game
Podcasts me heather and campbell matt abadaka right on. Well, thank you for thank you for also. Thank you for break
This is the first uh, uh non a parking garage episode. Yeah, so we broke we broke the pattern there
I don't know if that I don't know if that changes the rules or if only behind only in the crazy experimental club
Three only in the double paywall. Can I talk about anything other than a parking garage? I think that's fair
It's like when wrestlers it's like if you lose you can never challenge for this belt again. Yes, you know
Just an insane complication. Yeah
Yeah
We should have a next time we play larkana. It should be a career versus hair match. Oh, yeah podcast career. Yeah
Oh man, what would I do? Jesus christ? Yeah, no move back to game video game testing. Yeah
Well, there we go. Uh, hey, thanks for subscribing to club three
Uh more topics in the patreon comments theme park related in some form
Uh, and if you want to add any caveats of uh, you know damage we could get or other trades to fellow podcasts that
Could be made with jason. Let us know and if you want a fan art of josh tomorrow larkana card or a jason larkana card
Go feel free