Have we ever sang Hey Hey Mr. Postman to start one of these?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
That'd be good to do because there's not that many different things to do.
So to say hello on an episode like this?
Yeah I get it.
I mean are we all at once?
Are you just going to take it or?
I really only know Hey Hey Hey, how many hey's are there?
Mr. Postman, hey hey hey hey hey, is that it?
Mr. Postman, look and see, is there a letter in your bag for me?
You know I know that less from the original and more from the Carpenter's version of it
which has a really delightful music video that was filmed at Disneyland.
Things tied together here.
It's actually very nice because it's not, you know, they're not going to let a music
entity that they don't own film a music video there at this point, I don't think.
You don't think they let Meghan Trainor film a video?
Well they let her, they have a lot of-
She's in the family.
Yeah.
You're correct though that it's not like all of those artists are Disney artists as proven
by the Smashing Pumpkins participation.
Right.
Actually that's a good question, any other, of all the music videos, not music videos
but little musical numbers that have been filmed in all these various, do you guys flash
to any like oh that one makes me so happy?
This is so nice, they're on the Mark Twain, they're doing all the old timey Americana
kind of stuff.
Oh, because you know what's another one, there's some 4th of July special that starts
with Tevin Campbell later singer of Eye to Eye doing a cover of Sweet Freedom, the Michael
McDonald song that goes for like 10 minutes, more of a patriotic version with a marching
band.
Shine sweet freedom, that's coast to coast, it goes to Orlando and then comes back to
Disneyland.
Wow.
Big show stopper.
Any other, and do you guys flash to anything though?
I like Glen Campbell wandering through marshland.
Oh that's right, the opening of Disney World, yeah that is a good one.
Gloria Estefan at the, it's timed with the opening of Caribbean Beach, I think they filmed
during one of the, maybe a Christmas parade, does she, I think she does conga.
Seems very possible.
And Goofy might be there.
I mean there's a lot of Gloria Estefan Disney association and numbers, but yeah I gotta
place the one you're talking about.
If we talk much about that, those Sebastian videotapes, what's the guy's name, Samuel
Wright, the voice of Sebastian, that he did these Calypso concerts, the Caribbean Beach
Hotel maybe, those are some nice old home video recommended, maybe we'll watch them
some day.
Hey they were, things filmed at the parks, that means we owe it, that means we could
get episodes out of it.
Two videos, that means two separate episodes, the Sebastian double block coming.
But for now, let's take your questions, anybody see, is there a letter in the bag for us?
Oh I think there are a few letters, yeah, Megan Cherry asked, what do you think will
be the next portal added to Epic Universe?
Hopefully it'll be a long while before they do so, but the parks concept is definitely
designed to expand.
Yes, I don't know that it'll be so long, the way Universal builds.
I don't know that it'll be, you know, more than ten years.
I feel like it'll be under, let's make a prediction, how soon will a new portal be built at Epic
Universe?
Do you think five years, ten years?
I believe there'll be a new one within six years.
I think there'll be a new portal at Epic Universe, Jason, what do you think?
We're starting to bet, which I like on this show, we're starting talking about betting
for D23, and I think we should do more bets in general.
Playing with house money, with Patreon money, yeah, yeah, alright, this is for, I don't
get a cut this month if I'm wrong.
I don't pay bills this month.
Jason, you have a year?
So Scott was eight.
Mine was six.
Yours was six.
Yeah.
I'll go under, I'll say five.
Okay, five, you undercut me like Price is Right style.
Yes.
Okay, very good, that's okay, I'm comfortable with that.
You know, as opposed to Price is Right, this is anti-glamactic because we don't have the
answer right now.
We don't, that's true.
We have to wait five years.
No, time will tell.
Yeah.
But properties are things, what's in the portals?
Yeah, so the thing is, I think they're going to do more of, like, we're getting a lot
of Nintendo.
So I feel like we're getting, like, another portal for Nintendo because, like, Nintendo
can expand out, expand out, but I feel like it's not going to be maybe another, like,
wildly different property.
I know the rumor is Pokemon going into Simpsons Land in Orlando and Zelda going into Lost
Continent, but, like, I think they're going to go, like, hog wild here and I think we
could get, like, a full another, like, Mario Land or something with a different portal.
Maybe that's wrong.
Maybe, I'm hoping it's something totally new, but.
Well, I would happily take every, let's do the Pyramids Land, let's do the land where
everything's big.
Even I will take that.
That'd be cool.
I always think not enough Mario 2 representation.
I love Birdo, but it's a whole other world.
Like, I think they'd be, it's one of those they'd analyze, like, is there really an appetite
for Mario 2?
I'm like, I think so.
It's in our bones, right?
Yeah.
Mario, yeah.
Like, not the canon, but don't we all kind of, like, don't we all want to take a bite
out of a big turnip?
Of course.
Yes.
Mario 2, there is something very, I love all the Mario games, but Mario 2 definitely felt
special and it felt special because you could play as the different characters for the first
time.
Imagine opening a door or, like, you know, taking a, drinking from a vial, a big, big
red vial, and then you go into a weird negative zone of the same place that you were already
in and you got to leave six seconds later.
Also Mario 2 would be space efficient because you could build up, you know, more up happening
in that game.
That's good too.
Yeah, build to the sky.
I will say my wish for it is, and that's not my original idea, I've seen people say this,
retro universal portal.
This should be the next portal they make.
Yeah.
Like, I understand it's not going to be a full portal of, like, back to the future land
because they're not making new movies right now.
But a full-
Shudder when you say that.
I know I say it every once in a while.
It's true.
You know it's true.
I know, but yeah.
It's a matter of time.
Clock's ticking on that.
At least we got, at least there's people alive preventing it from happening.
That's right.
But it's, clock is ticking.
At the very least you could, like, sell it to money people and be like, well, back to
the future is still popular.
At the very least you could sell, like, smaller rides or experiences based on Ghostbusters
back to the future ET, obviously ET's still in Orlando.
But at the very-
Wait, that's a question actually.
If it's not ET, what's, I mean, wouldn't a-
Jaws?
Yeah.
I think the retro universal land would have to be back to the future Ghostbusters Jaws,
right?
Those are the big three.
And if you hit anything else, then you do.
Sure.
I wouldn't be mad at some other ET thing there.
But yes, there would be no reason, I guess, to build a new ET ride, dark ride.
Unless it was to, like, protect the, I don't like that.
I feel like it would get jazzed up a little too much.
Yeah.
We haven't talked about Botanicus' cape, I don't think.
Oh, we haven't talked about that.
Yeah.
He has a new cape.
A big leaf cape.
He has a cape.
And then also in the epic universe, dark universe footage, you do see a Dracula in a cape.
So they got our letters, you know?
Because you mentioned specifically on when we were talking about the reveal that Dracula
did not have a cape and I said the same thing.
I was talking about how I was upset that he didn't seem to have a cape.
But I guess he does have a cape.
Yeah.
So that's good.
Okay.
And they're adding capes left and right in Universal Orlando, which is where we're at.
Everybody needs a cape.
Mario's getting a cape.
Super Mario World Mario had a cape.
Mm-hmm.
And he flew, when he flew.
True.
And he hit people with it.
I'd like to see that cape.
Yeah, yeah.
The cape should be in play.
Absolutely.
All right.
Two is its own world.
World is its own.
I don't know.
Yes.
And then all the recent ones.
Galaxy, whatever.
100%.
Well, even just rides.
Like, Metroid and Star Fox, tailor-made for rides.
No, Star Fox.
Look, Star Fox doesn't get treated well by Nintendo.
And that's a whole nother episode of this podcast, or a different podcast.
But yeah, Metroid has a new game coming out they just announced.
But yes, Retro Universal should be the next one.
You could sell all of that stuff in pieces.
That's the only way it's happening.
It's not going to be Jaws Land.
It's not going to be Back to the Future Land.
But I think maybe if you put all the little pieces together, you could sell it to the
people in charge.
The greatest hits.
I think that's a really cool idea.
Well, this is what the parade is.
This is what their big new parade in the summer.
Creative people know that's what the people want.
So you're getting it in small.
It's vintage stuff for the millennial parents and then the minions for the kids.
If kids still like minions, presumably.
I think they do.
But yeah, so you're seeing it everywhere.
You're seeing the parade.
You're seeing it in the new show they're doing, the new Lagoon show, which looks cool.
And it's drones.
But it's got Back to the Future.
It's got Ghostbusters.
You see a big stay puff in the drones.
We act like Ghostbusters is a given, but is Sony going to just...
I don't know.
Maybe we don't end up with Ghostbusters due to corporations not getting along.
It's possible.
Their presence has been felt in different things in the retro, in the retro sphere at
Universal Orlando.
Would we take, if they're going to take things that they own...
I mean, I don't know.
That Ghostbusters show.
I never got to see it in person, actually.
It seemed cool.
But I would definitely take if Retro Universal Land was instead Jaws Back to the Future King
Kong and it's like an old style revamped so that it's less of a breakdown risk.
But that's kind of a good greatest hits.
And then the portal could be like the old entrance was, or going back to original Studio
Gate.
Yeah, that would be awesome.
So that's what they should do.
But I think it'll be like, oh, a portal, but it's like kind of another Nintendo Land.
That's my guess.
I don't know.
This might be related.
Matt Vullich, what ride has opened up in the last 15 years that was the biggest letdown
and what would you do to fix it?
I go to...
Maybe we've covered this a little bit, but I definitely go to Mario Kart in terms of
how much we built up.
And I guess we already talked about, but I mean, I love the idea of it being more of
like a wild mouse and you're in a little style cart and it's more about like, it's less about
interactivity and more about like quick turns and ducks and weaves and every car is different.
But that's like a cop out.
Is there any way they could take what they currently have and make it...
No.
No?
I don't think so.
What if you just make it faster?
No.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
I think it is what it is right now.
I mean, you maybe could make it go faster, but I think it would be a lot of work.
I don't think that track is prepared for that.
So yeah, in order to change it, I think it would be a tremendous amount of work.
And I don't know.
It doesn't seem like, yeah, it's fixable.
And again, people like it.
So I guess some people claim it doesn't need fixing, but...
You know, now that I've played so much on the Switch, I get why they really honed in
on the items, but I'm also really just trying to go fast, trying to outrun the other items.
This remains so interesting that you are new to Mario Kart this year.
Yeah, I never...
I would play it every now and then at a friend's house, but it was never a huge thing for me.
Now that I'm playing...
Now that I'm playing, we bought the DLC, it doubles the amount of tracks.
You essentially get a whole second game.
Yeah.
Are you good at the game?
Well, we're pretty good, but...
We are good as...
Together we're good?
You're talking about...
Jane and I, well, we race each other, but we usually turn on the auto.
Like, there's steering...
There's an easier steering you can turn on, you know what I mean?
Oh, you're playing in like easy mode.
Yeah, oh yeah.
So you're not drifting.
Because it's more fun.
Who wins more often?
No, you can drift.
I think she wins more.
Okay.
Do you play like on hard or the hardest levels when you're playing the computer, or do you
just race each other?
I'll play against the computer.
A lot of times we'll pick random.
I like to do a full, like, all four circuit.
Okay.
Sometimes.
Four tracks, yeah.
Yeah.
I haven't played in a bit.
I don't know.
I'm wondering how we would stack up in a Mario Kart contest.
Cool.
I'm wondering.
It'd be worth doing.
We could do that.
And fun.
Jason's the one playing.
I haven't played in Mario Kart in a few years at this point.
We like to toggle items, like certain items on and off.
You mean before the race starts?
Yeah, you can customize which items you have.
Lightning Strike is kind of annoying.
You turn it off?
Yeah.
What is this version of Mario Kart you're playing?
We're customizing it.
We're eliminating big, exciting things that can happen.
Turn on easy steering and turn on lightning.
But we're not doing that when we play.
I like Boomerang, but she likes Fire Flower.
Okay.
I feel like.
Do you turn them both on or off?
I'll turn them both on.
Okay.
What?
I say tomato and you say tomato.
Toilet.
She likes the Boomerang and I like the Fire Flower.
Okay.
Do you do any other modifications?
I don't think so.
I think just normal.
Who's your player?
I switch around a lot, but I like Wario.
I like Tanooki suit Mario.
Sure.
I like Toad.
I usually like faster racers.
Yeah.
They should make it so you can.
I would love if you could unlock outside of the Marioverse, a la NBA Jam, you could unlock.
I want to play Mario Kart as Charles Barkley or Christian Leitner.
Yeah.
An old NBA.
Brianna asks, is Harbor Hoedown still on the table?
And quickly I'll just say yes.
I didn't consult with my co-hosts, but I'll say yes.
This was not discussed.
I'll just say yes.
It's on the table.
But they don't.
Yeah.
They don't.
We'll talk about that off mic.
Heather Miller asks, aside from Eisner, who are each of the hosts dream guests?
And I will say right now I got my eyes focused on Mr. Billy Corgan.
I got somebody working on it and we'll see.
I don't, I'm not promising anything.
It might be impossible, but that's my man right now is Mr. Billy Corgan from the Smashing
Pumpkins.
Seems possible.
It seems possible.
I'm just saying I'm not promising it yet, but right now that's who I've honed in on as
I'm working on it.
Nobody else is working on it for me.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh boy.
Hey, that's good.
Yeah.
Dream guest.
God.
I don't have a dream guest.
Yeah.
Eisner is our dream guest number one.
I think collectively.
Yeah.
And then, and then Breck Eisner, you'd have to include in there.
That would be part of it.
Yeah.
Is anybody like in a lot of specials who we could, you know, or anybody who is in a TGIF,
you know, let's talk to Coolie.
Yeah.
I tried with a Jody Sweeten a couple of years ago.
We could try that again.
You tried Jody Sweeten?
Yeah.
That might not be out of the realm of possibility.
They all podcast now.
That's what I mean.
Every one of them has got a podcast.
Like a Kurt Russell might be interesting.
I love Kurt Russell.
Obviously everyone does, but he was around in the old days.
He seems affable.
Yeah.
So that's, that's up there.
I would think.
That's a pie in the sky.
I haven't tried with Kurt Russell.
Yeah.
But you know, is there an old, yeah, Jason, do you have anybody?
Well, he's gone from the company now and I, I think he has a book out, but it's probably
through Disney publishing, but Bob Weiss is at a different company now.
And he worked on a lot of, in addition to being the head of Imagineering, like he worked
on like.
That's probably doable.
Yeah.
Send an email.
Some interesting stuff.
And I think some calamitous stuff through no fault of his, just through timing and budgets.
Don't say anything bad about him here.
If we want him on the show, it's paywall or okay.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
Does anyone want to be our booker?
Does anyone, is anyone better with people?
Oh my God.
We would need a booker.
Yeah.
And pushiness.
Yes.
We need a lot of people to do the jobs we do.
That is a good point.
We do all the jobs, if anyone's wondering.
Yeah, it's true.
We're all operating multiple cranks and levers and pedals at all.
We're all one man bands like Bert and Mary Poppins.
I have one here.
Cassie says, heard there is going to be a Munsters reboot called 1313, but it's horror.
Discuss.
I don't have a lot to discuss, but when Munsters isn't funny, it's just the universal monsters,
isn't it?
Yeah.
Isn't that?
Then the premise is imagine if there was a Frankenstein.
Right.
Well, so.
The Munsters become monsters.
I suppose that the interesting thing is that like a Frankenstein has a father-in-law who's
a vampire.
I guess them all being together.
I guess that's still somewhat interesting.
Yeah, but I don't.
But it's still the monster.
They're monsters now.
Mm-hmm.
So.
I don't really want to see like, I don't want to see what it's like to like, you don't
understand dad, you're a Frankenstein.
I'm a Wolfman.
Right.
That's funny.
We have nothing in common.
Uh-huh.
That's funny.
Level with me.
Am I adopted?
I was going to say they already kind of tried this with the Brian Fuller, Brian Singer one.
They tried this every seven years.
There's these properties that they just like, all right, we're going back at it.
Flintstones are trying it again.
Look, God damn it.
And the press release, the Deadline Articles are like, God damn it, we're trying the Flintstones
again.
All right?
Shut the fuck up.
Flintstones with Family Guy people got pretty, it might've gotten some scripts written.
What do you mean?
Do you remember this?
The Flintstones were going to get rebooted.
Oh, Simon Carlin was doing a new Flintstones, but it never came out.
It never came out.
I do remember this.
It's like the Donald Glover Deadpool where it's like he got pretty far and then they
pulled the plug.
At any moment there are 10 people working on a new Flintstones or a new Scooby-Doo.
There's five Scooby-Doo's on the air right now.
There are five to 10 more people working on new Scooby-Doo's to replace those Scooby-Doo's.
It has only gotten weirder and worse when it comes to new stuff.
And everything, everything in this list Josh Gad is attached to.
And Josh Gad is involved in every single property.
So yeah, I did hear that and I'm, I'm open to it.
If somebody says it's good, I'm open to it.
It just feels a little bit silly to not make the Munsters silly.
Yeah.
It feels a little silly to me to not, to take the humor away from the Munsters.
I would say give it back to any still living original writers.
From the Munsters?
I don't know if those Munsters are from I Love Lose.
Any 80 or 90 year olds, let them take a crack at it.
I don't know if those writers are, I don't know if we got any living Munsters writers.
I think more television.
We have enough boobers.
We have enough millennial saturation.
I want some geriatrics writing comedy scripts.
Let's take a page from Washington.
Why do we allow 20 year old comedians to do anything?
Let's put up blockades and all writers need to be north of 80.
That's a great point.
Let's let 20 year olds be politicians.
Let's write television, let television writers, you got to have an AARP card.
You got to be on social security.
I just doubt that there are a lot of living Munsters writers because I feel like they
were all 70 then.
Oh, that's a good, should we do a little betting on this?
How many Munsters writers are alive?
I bet there's like one.
I bet there's one Munsters writer that is alive.
I don't know if I feel comfortable saying zero.
I'll say one.
Let me go counter to my point and say three.
Okay.
We can figure this out afterward.
One of the creators born in 28 died in 2010.
That's not so long ago.
14 years ago.
He's only been dead for 14 years, so probably a lot of them are alive.
He's only been dead for a very long time.
Yeah, super long time.
Okay, I'm going to throw this one out.
Tomas Maranera, what film that one of the parks would never adapt into a tacky 20 minute
truncated stage show like Beauty and the Beast, would you most want to see adapted into a
tacky 20 minute truncated stage show?
This is a little innovative question.
I like this.
To call out the genre of the condensed mini musical, fitting the entire story into a theme
park run that you can do five times a day.
I had this idea while staring at this question, if you guys want to think on it, but I think
a funny one, again, and they wouldn't do it now, but maybe they should do it now, because
there probably is a lot of nostalgia for Lizzie McGuire the movie, the filmed in Rome, I'm
sorry, the Lizzie McGuire movie, which is now over 20 years old, and that's the point
where there's a lot of nostalgia hunger.
Seeing theme park actors play Lizzie and Gordo.
Those could be face or they could wear giant mascot heads of Lizzie McGuire, that'd be
fine too, but that song at the end is pretty fun, right?
When she's the pop star, this is what dreams are made of or something, I'd like to see
that done on stage, and then having to do a Roman Vespa ride with a cycling background
that people have to move by hand, you get to travel in it, that's a good thing of these
shows, if everybody can get on a plane that just goes five feet and then like, hey, we're
here in Rome, so that's my vote, I want to hear, yeah, let's all of a sudden, out of
nowhere, the Lizzie McGuire movie live.
I in the same ballpark, I'm going to say, that's still very mysterious to me, but I'm
sure a lot of them are on Disney, plus now that era of early, I want Home on the Range,
Brother Bear Chicken Little, Treasure Planet, oh, there's one I'm missing.
These are mostly still a mystery to me, because I was like, I want to see 20 minutes, ooh,
that'd be great, that would actually be a really fun, because then you, oh, Home on
the Range, then you can kind of downplay the Roseanne connection, they seem like they've
distanced themselves a lot from that production.
I think it's cutting into their bottom line, I think we're seeing Disney hurt by the Roseanne
connection every day, they haven't distanced themselves enough, frankly, on the day that
that happened, Disney said nothing, I think they stand by Roseanne's tweet, as her former
employer.
They got to really address the Home on the Range situation.
Maybe they did say something, because they made Roseanne the show.
And then they changed it to the Connors.
But they didn't say jack shit about Home on the Range.
Well separating the art from the artists, like you don't want to penalize those poor
animated cows.
That's true.
Don't penalize the cows.
Rookie of the Year, could we do?
Does that technically follow the, yeah, Rookie of the Year never had like much Parks stuff,
or any Parks stuff, I've never seen a Rookie of the Year anything.
That's great.
And it would have to get songs then.
It would have to get songs.
And I guess, yeah, I guess they have to be original songs.
There's no original song from Rookie of the Year, is there?
Oh, we forget though, the John song, I'm Still Here, will be in Jason's, of course, the Johnny
Resnick song.
You just called that the John song.
The John song.
Isn't it called the John song or something?
Well, I don't know that.
I thought you were calling it the John song because Johnny Resnick sings it.
Well, I do in my head, it's the John song.
I was thinking of the Joaquin Phoenix, I'm Still Here song.
Jim's, I'm sorry, it's Jim's theme.
John's song.
It's Jim and John, J names boring, my name's boring too, I'm not insulting those names.
Sorry, Jim's theme made by John.
Jim's theme, parentheses Jim's theme, parentheses John's song.
Right.
So Rookie of the Year will also have a Johnny Resnick music that has been commissioned for
this 20 minute version.
The singer of the Goo Goo Dolls is doing.
Yeah.
That's a 90's movie.
I mean, it's a little, yeah.
1993.
Coming down the Pitcher's Mound.
It's parodies of Goo Goo Dolls songs.
Going faster than the real Cubs.
But you know, this is a, I feel like any kid who saw this had some affection for this movie
and I feel like this is underrepresented and you could have like that Daniel Stern character
is like real goofy.
He's like, I forget what he is.
Is he a pitching coach or something?
Yeah.
He gets like stuck in the middle of like two hotel rooms.
It's kind of like weird.
He's like doing slapstick in the middle of this movie, but you know, that's a good, that's
a fun character to see on stage.
Sure.
And then just, yeah, having the ball.
You could do like a, like a Phil Hart Magic Donald Duck thing with a cannon where he like,
the Rookie of the Year throws the ball out into the audience and then you see like, oh,
in the back it like, it bursts through the wall or something.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It makes it do some bit like some kind of stereo, like whipping fast sound using the
speakers.
It makes it seem like a ball's going really fast.
And you look back and yeah, Daniel Stern's been like thrown into the, it'd be like, since
my pitching arm has been broken.
Yeah.
It would be both basically like that.
I guess we could just rewrite it then.
He doesn't have to actually, John, Johnny Resnick doesn't have to be involved.
We could just do parodies of everything.
Well, he gets the music money and we, he gets the music.
Yeah, he gets the music money.
The lyrics are us.
And I'm trying to think like, you know, how would you change the lyrics to Black Balloon?
It feels a little blasphemous, but you would have to do it.
Well, it'd be so jarring to people because everyone, as we've determined, everyone knows
the song so well from note one.
It is so instantly iconic and recognizable and people know the words really well.
When it comes time to sing the song, everyone can easily toss out every one of those lyrics.
Yeah.
Rookies, magic arm helps him throw.
That would be a good first line for it.
And people would go, oh, it's a Black Balloon parody.
The thing I'll say about Black Balloon is that the people that know Black Balloon do
feel the way I feel.
I believe that everyone should know Black Balloon, but then there's also people that
haven't heard it.
So it's almost like two separate universes.
What I'd say, I know, well, this is the, you know, the world we live in where we get our
news from different sources and we don't all have the same amount of exposure to Black
Balloon.
Right.
But what I would say to those people and what I'd say to you is I can't change my past.
I can't give myself exposure to Black Balloon that I never had.
Yeah.
I know that you wish that for me.
I do.
And it might have changed my whole life.
Maybe I would be, maybe I wouldn't make fun of you for liking Johnny Resnick so much.
Yeah.
But if I had that emotion, that might've, that might've propelled me to having a girlfriend
when I was 13 that I didn't have.
Well, it didn't propel me to having a girlfriend.
A love of Black Balloon didn't show the kind of sensitive guy you were.
It didn't help.
It didn't help at all.
It didn't.
Nothing could help.
Nothing at all could help.
The cool clerks at the record store, when I went in to ask for a ksingle of Iris, and
they were totally confused.
They're like, well, we have the CD and the whole soundtrack.
Did you say the word ksingle?
Yeah.
I had just learned about ksingles and I was like, well, this is great.
I have a cassette player.
And they didn't exist.
They didn't have a cassette of Iris?
No.
Well, not a ksingle.
You had to ask someone?
Huh?
You went, you have, this is a memory you have is asking specifically.
Right, because they would have a cassette.
Do you have Iris on ksingle?
Yes.
Wow.
And this is like 1998?
Uh, was that when it came out?
97?
97.
I'm like, this was 2011.
The record store hasn't been here for 11 years.
Did I buy a cassette after 1995?
That's a good question.
I did.
I bought ksingles in middle school.
I know that's still in my parents' bedroom because I was listening to a lot of hip hop
at the time.
And I know that I have ksingles of The Locks, Money Power and Respect, and Ice Cube's Push
and Wait.
Really?
Yay, yay, a Push Rhymes like Wait, a Push Rhymes like Wait.
Okay, what year is that?
This is all like 97, 98.
You were actually, you were brought on stage at the Kendrick Lamar pop out show in Inglewood.
To do that song?
Yeah, yeah.
You were in the picture of like 30 people.
You're actually there.
Now give it up for the guy who remembers Push and Wait.
You're to perform half the chorus and that is all.
People went wild though.
Uh, yeah.
You know what?
I know also in that closet I should own up to having a joint ksingle of Puff Daddy's
Been Around the World and all about the Benjamin's Rock Remix.
Oh yeah, I know those.
And I should really go back, I should find that in my parents' closet and due to Diddy's
recent and clearly forever actions, I should go run over that ksingle with my car.
Oh, I was going to say just tape over it with Black Balloon and then you can learn it.
You can work on learning it.
That would make him so mad.
Then I'll tweet at him.
Scott J. Klepper asked like a hundred questions, but the one that sticks out to me, which isn't
really a question.
I mean, it is a question, but he says, my wife says I bet Michael was a late bloomer.
What does she mean by that?
I mean, one of the safest bets that's come up recently on this show.
Yeah.
And I wonder too, like does, does your wife listen?
Does she like just catch stray things that I say and go, I bet he was a late bloomer.
Is it like in that way or is it more you're having a discussion about it?
Cause like that's how I picture it, where somebody walks by and listens to me talking
about something from my childhood and they go, I bet, I bet it was all happening a little
too late.
Or is she saying that the bloom still hasn't occurred?
That's a good question too.
I would just like more elaboration of what the, what your wife means, sir.
How late is this bloom?
How late is the bloom?
There's certainly parts of me that haven't bloomed.
I will agree with that.
I know you gave us your slightly below average teat count.
Some of it, some was, I don't know.
Well, you think maybe that, maybe that is what's happening is that I haven't fully
finished puberty.
It makes a lot of sense.
Oh no, he's going to get taller.
I'm going to get taller.
Whoa, yeah, you're waiting on your spurt.
Yeah.
It was like, I got a half spurt.
I'm supposed to be seven, eight, and I'm only six, three.
So in the next 10 years, I think I will finish puberty and I will finally, like my
final form will be apparent.
Wow.
New, new dream guest for podcast, Baron Trump in five years, once your spurt has
occurred so that the two, the two tallest white men can be in one place and we'll
have to duck to get into the studio door.
Yeah.
But I'm going to take, you know, at my part, we're, we're listening to a lot of
Sabrina Carpenter, you know?
So I'm the hip one.
I'm the hip reference now.
We've got Espresso.
We're watching the music video with Barry Keough.
Also, don't forget that this episode's coming out way later in the summer.
And this is not, by this point is not very current.
No, that's fine.
I've been thinking how I'm like, cause I also, I like Espresso and I've been
thinking how it's going to come up on the show and I'm, I will be God damned if
that song comes up in the typical PTR way, which is like, you know what?
I like a song.
I like a song that is a new song.
I actually like Espresso.
There I said it.
I like Espresso.
Like I will, this will not be the tone.
Whose voice is that of Jason or I don't know.
I don't, I can't say what variety of blooming that voice could be ascribed to.
I do like that song.
I will say that.
We all like Espresso.
You said it very normally and I appreciate it.
I say things normally.
There is a new song.
There is a new song that has come out this summer and this is a song that I
like and I like a song.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm mostly listening to Lefty Frizzle, a song, an old, long dead country
music guy that my daughter seems to like with his hit song, Shine, Shave, Shower.
She really likes that one.
That's your normal morning routine.
It's like daddy, he shines his action figures.
He shaves his action figures and then he showers his action figures.
Yeah.
So anyway, Jason is hip right in the moment he's saying.
There will be nothing hipper in whatever month this comes out
than still Sabrina Carpenter.
Yeah.
I like current cool music too.
I just don't talk about it.
It's coming out.
I just don't talk about it on the show.
And you know what?
And I like, and I like current and cool and hip.
Yeah.
And I won't even say the different things, the different hip people I like.
I don't need to do it.
There's so many different hip people.
I'm so hip in so many different ways.
And there's so many different hip people that to start the list
and then we'd never be done with the list.
And when you get around, when we all get around to learning how to pronounce
Chapparoon correctly, we'll name one of her songs.
Would we ever do a music loop final four?
Maybe.
It's a complicated one to condense.
I think it is a really good idea.
Music loop final four, but like, how do you explain them quickly?
And it's so like, it's just tough to, you know, you can't like do it.
It's all a 10 second synopsis.
I mean, I guess you could like really break down, like what scale it's in
and why that's complicated in the arrangement.
I suppose you could really try from a music theory perspective.
But you think we're going to talk about what scale it's in.
We're going to do pretty scale analysis.
I'm not a Rick Piotto over here who knows all of his scales.
Look, none of us are Rick Piotto, OK?
He knows his scales.
He knows it on the guitar.
Very accomplished.
That is the fastest 60 seconds from I like current and cool and hip to Rick Piotto.
Rick listens to some of the young people's music and he doesn't like it.
He often doesn't like it.
He doesn't like the like simple
chord changes on a Taylor Swift song sometimes.
If you're a guy who knows a lot about record
engineering in the 70s and 80s, there's no way that you like a lot of current music.
Right. He goes through the top 10 sometimes and he goes, oh, come on.
As opposed to you would do.
Well, there'll be an episode one day where we'll go through the current top 10.
Mike will know at least six of them and he'll say, oh, come on.
That's right. Into my ears. Right.
I'll say it there like a come hither in my sound in my voice.
Here. Oh, are you?
Did you? Oh, go ahead.
Joe Glass says, design your dream popcorn pocket.
Novelty popcorn buckets.
We've talked about this a few times recently.
Privately.
Yeah. Privately.
Question one, we have. Question two, privately.
This came up with Griffin.
He was talking about novelty popcorn buckets a couple of days.
I'll say this.
I'm going to sound like a real square.
I want a napkin dispenser on the side.
My hands get too greasy eating popcorn.
Wait a minute.
So your dream popcorn bucket is just a very functional.
It's a regular bucket with its unthemed.
It just has how how many napkins can fit in this napkin dispenser?
I think you want at least 10, because inevitably,
if you're sharing it with someone, you always give them a couple, two or three.
If you have a lot of butter on this popcorn as well.
I do like the butter on the popcorn.
I'm not going to hide it.
OK, so is there any like is do you have like your trademark?
Like you've it's a thing you've created now.
Is there any sort of say like trademark Jason Sheridan?
Is there anything else on the on it other than?
Sure.
Um, this is in my mind, because on the other episode, you were talking about candy
and I was kind of shocked you were naming all these songs
and you did not mention the Archie's sugar sugar.
That is a shocking thing. I agree.
So I would like a functional popcorn bucket that plays with the napkin.
Well, I was going to say the Archie's with their instruments just around it.
Just pictures of the Archie's doing that music.
Well, sugar sugar.
You're getting sugar.
Is that a kettle corn in your popcorn?
Oh, that would be good, too.
Because like the napkin dispenser is first
and then the cartooned Archie's band is second.
So you just want the Archie's because you like them. Yeah.
You want like the cartoon band that sings a song about candy
to be on your popcorn bucket, which is otherwise occupied by a napkin dispenser.
Yeah. And probably I like kettle corn, but I like salty popcorn butter.
So there might actually not be any sugar involved.
I just want my friends.
I want my friends to be serving it to me.
So there's a crunchy, crunchy salty butter.
I love it so much.
They're serving it, but aren't they playing their instruments?
But in theory, if they're on the outside of the bucket, not in theory,
in theory, you're just watching them play.
I am just watching them play.
But a bucket of popcorn serves you the popcorn.
That's true. That's true.
A bucket does serve you.
Yeah. By containing it, it doesn't pick it up and give it to you.
You still have to use your hands. Yeah.
I mean, what we're getting like this question, I assume.
And look, I'm going to I don't want to be so filthy here.
But what this this question is getting at is this recent trend with popcorn
buckets where it looks like some sort of a flashlight.
It looks like something that you're going to have sex with.
This was, of course, the Dune popcorn
bucket that really resembled like a flashlight.
And now Deadpool has sent up this whole idea with his reveal
of the Wolverine popcorn bucket.
That's a very disgusting looking Wolverine head with a giant open mouth,
which is like you're going to Wolverine's going to blow you basically.
And then the studio tour
glamour tram one, you can just destroy your genital sweat.
And you finally be free.
No, you just run over it and then you're free from this curse.
The tram will destroy your genitals.
Yeah, that's what you're talking about.
So you're in Woody Woodpecker is driving it is.
Is that true?
Woody Woodpecker is driving the glamour tram popcorn bucket.
Yeah. OK.
And you can meet Woody and Winnie now. Now?
Yeah. At the tram loading.
I feel like, oh, they're there.
They're back. They've been around in the park.
They've been around, but I think they went away and now they're back.
OK, interesting.
Now, you can't have sex with the the napkin dispenser on your popcorn bucket.
Um, no, but with enough creativity, you can fuck anything.
And like if you need to clean up,
you I guess you could keep the bucket on your nightstand
and then you have some napkins.
That was too far.
You know, we started talking about dirty stuff, but that was too much for me.
Sanitation, thoughtfulness.
That's too much for you.
It's too realistic, honestly.
I guess, yeah, well, now you think about it.
Yeah, you're talking about the opposite of dirty.
We're talking about cleaning up.
So I don't want to have a dirty popcorn bucket.
I want mine to just be a fun little thing to eat popcorn out of.
Yeah, that's what I was talking about.
One that had a napkin dispenser and the art cheese on it.
I was just making sure you were getting at something that was wholesome.
And it sounds like yours was wholesome.
OK, so yours would not.
Your ideal popcorn bucket would not recreate any part of Minnie's body.
No, that's what I knew we were going there.
But that is not what it would be.
And you can't have me.
I was not going to pick Minnie at all on here because there's no way that any part
wouldn't be misconstrued as me doing something perverted.
It can't be like Minnie giving like a thumbs up or something.
And there's popcorn in her hand.
That doesn't work.
I'm not doing that.
It can't be like Minnie's shoe, because people will be like,
you have a weird shoe fetish.
Like you take the beat, the popcorn out of Minnie's shoe.
And then God knows what some pervert is doing with that shoe.
And that's not what I'm going to pick.
Some hypothetical pervert, right?
I've never met who's not in the room and not Winnie, right?
What Winnie the Pooh?
No, Winnie, Woody Woodpecker's partner.
This is we have a real issue with familiarity on this show.
John's theme is just said.
And we're meant to assume what that is.
That was Winnie with no.
That was just wrong.
I just said, Winnie, and I know you just talked about.
But the first time you said it, Winnie and Winnie.
And like, I kind of know it's Winnie Woodpecker.
But it's Winnie's girlfriend.
She's got a little pink dress on.
I'm just saying this is not an iconic character.
I'm sorry, Winnie Woodpecker, but you are not an icon.
And I, of course, even we just talked about Winnie Woodpecker.
And Mike, you still went to Winnie the Pooh.
I know. Well, so that's where I'm like, I think you got a full name at Jase.
As much as I know, you'd like to be on a first name basis and are
on a first name basis with Winnie Woodpecker.
I think it needs a little bit of context.
All right. Fair enough.
I can't have a character because that's where this question goes.
It can't be a character's face.
It can't be figment.
It can't be anyone because people automatically now associate popcorn
bucket with like like a sex toy.
So it's got to be something I didn't, by the way.
Really? No, it's popcorn buckets that are just like, you know,
but recent trends in popcorn buckets is sexual.
The recent trends suggest.
And again, Deadpool took it up a notch.
Deadpool made it so outrageous.
Well, that's what he does.
He takes things up.
And yes, so I'm just I'm going to have to just do some.
I'm going to have to think of something that is like an inanimate object.
That's just kind of a fun thing
based on like something I like.
So let's say what do I like doing?
I like playing video games.
I like playing tennis.
Oh, I like playing tennis.
OK, so here we go.
OK, there is like, you know, sometimes when you get a bucket of balls,
it's or it's like a basket. Here we go.
You see that already.
You already said the phrase bucket of balls.
It's a basket or a bucket of balls.
And it looks like but it's popcorn instead.
And then how would you know it's a bucket of balls
if it's a bucket with other things in it?
Because it looks like that kind of like wire like basket
that you do put a bunch of balls in.
Although I guess that wire basket.
Yeah, that popcorn's falling right out.
Yeah, it can't be a tube.
It can't be the normal like tennis balls.
There's three balls in like a can of tennis balls
because that looks like a flashlight.
It does a tube of who's the filthy minded one now?
A tube of you can't even go by a tube of tennis balls
because you're you're thinking about like, I mean,
people are going to think I'm a pervert.
When you're when I'm checking out from Big Five,
they're going to think like you do.
You do go by tennis tubes from Big Five.
But as you're checking out, you say, oh, and by the way,
I'm not buying this to put my dick in it.
I'm not having sex with this.
I do try to add that under my breath.
That's why I try to check out too wide.
You still need like maybe not for you, Mike.
But I know some customization will be involved.
The width of how do you you need some something
to provide more friction?
You can't just put your penis into a tennis.
Well, you need some sort of sleeve.
Yeah, some some other component has to be in there to like
a sleeve of crackers.
Well, no, that'll cut you right up the like saltine sleeves.
Like that. No, that's too OK.
Well, again, I've not done this.
I'm just trying to think of something,
a popcorn bucket that's not sexual.
That's what I'm trying to do here.
I'm trying to be clean here.
I'm trying to not be a pervert.
So everyone else is the one ascribing perverse things to it.
I'm the one who's doing good.
I'm the one who's making this wholesome.
Yes, an attempt, an attempt at wholesomeness.
And that's why you're avoiding sexy, sexy objects like balls in a tennis tube.
And you you delete it.
I'm still here, Jim's theme, which again, I I did have to look up.
I thought I was going crazy, but it is
John Resnick's solo song from Treasure Planet.
And I just was like, what am I forgetting?
What is Jim's thing?
Oh, you don't even remember that.
I remember that, Jason.
No one should feel crazy for not properly remembering.
I'm still here. Jim's theme.
This is not something that is famous.
This is not something that is well regarded.
Well-remembered the other day.
So I just wanted confirmation that I had the name right.
I'm just saying of all the things to feel crazy about, like, boy, I don't know.
I'm losing my mind.
I couldn't even remember the full name of the song from Treasure Planet
or whether it was the full Goo Goo Dolls lineup or only John Resnick.
Or Johnny Resnick.
I can't even remember if we say John or Johnny.
I mean, I feel like it was Johnny when he's younger.
And maybe he says John more now.
And he's like, you know what?
I'm not a Goo Goo Doll anymore.
I'm a Goo Goo Man.
Well, well, Billy Corgan was going by William Patrick Corgan
for a little like media cycle.
So people change.
People have preferences that change as far as their name.
How about there's a big garbage bank full of popcorn or a pillowcase?
That's kind of fun.
That's like a DIY thing.
And you get a lot of it.
And you could suffocate yourself with it.
Oh, shit. Yeah.
You can get off on that.
Yeah, you could suffocate yourself.
The fact is, any popcorn bucket out there can be used for sexual purposes.
Oh, man.
All right. Well, I don't like all of it.
Let's edit this all out, then.
Let's keep it in the sexual neck of the woods.
Although not really.
This is more of just a way to debate.
Seth Finkelstein, Mary Fuck Kill, boat ride, omni-mover, trackless, dark ride.
Interesting.
Omni-mover, boat ride, trackless, trackless.
So like Wi-Fi control, Mickey Minis,
Runway Railway, Poops, Honey Hut, Riser's Resistance.
Yep.
Uh, who, who, who?
All right. I got it.
Kill, trackless, dark ride.
Wow. Fuck, omni-mover, Mary, boat ride.
I think I might agree with you.
I think you want to settle down with just a with a solid one.
Yeah. Omni-movers with their high backs provide the most private experience.
Oh, I don't care about that.
And trackless, dark rides, ultimately, you know, they're the eye.
What if they're like a flash in the pan due to their ability to break down?
Yeah. That's the one you got to let go.
It's all it's it's at the end of the day, it's not a theme park staple.
Breakdown a lot.
They're hitting like ubiquitous.
It's kind of the go to.
Yeah. Do you agree with this assessment in order, Mike?
I'll switch the F and the Mary.
Mm hmm. It's really good that you clean that up now.
After 15 minutes of discussion of how sexual tennis.
I was saying it in the anti way.
That's why it was more of a clinical discussion versus me being vulgar.
That's what I so I wanted to go back to the wholesomeness of F Mary.
So, yes, I would ask the boat ride Mary, the omni-mover.
OK. And kill the track list.
And still, wow. But we fully.
And all I would K.
And we K. The trackless dark.
That's aggressive, too. Mm hmm.
Yeah. Maybe this is a fun outro.
Austin Beltran, this is primarily a Jason question.
What would be your dream blunt rotation of theme park animatronics?
Oh, good question.
Leave us out of it. We're hip.
Sorry, we're not hip enough to be in the to to to S a B.
I tried. I tried to meet a weed mint in the last six months.
And it took a long time to start.
And then it didn't start till I was going to bed.
You know, I thought I will take a mint.
I will take a minute. I'll listen to Sabrina Carpenter.
I will listen to a current song for this song.
I'll listen to it. I'll eat a current.
I don't remember the new one, the name of the new one, but I like it a lot.
Don't prove them right.
Don't embarrass me, motherfucker.
You know, I like it.
Uh, well, OK.
I'm going to include defunct animatronics.
And I am thinking about people who probably partially
like Timekeeper would be cool because I just think he's cool.
He knows about a lot of stuff, too.
Yeah. But I think the alien from Alien Encounter
and the bird from America Sings probably need to chill it out.
The bird, what's the bird?
The burlives, the bird, the eagle.
Yeah. With the hat.
Wait, so you're you're you're saying blunt rotation in this instance
is something you're deciding because you think those characters need to smoke?
No. Well, I'm going to split it.
I'm trying to think of who the last one would be.
Forgive me. Isn't blunt rotation like, oh, like you're hanging out
and you get really like deep into conversation.
Yeah, I think they're cool guys.
I just think those two are a little high strung and they could stand to relax.
But Timekeeper, the alien is a killer.
Well, it's just his nature.
You know, I'm just saying the alien will maybe kill you.
Well, not if he chills out first.
How can you get that blunt in the mouth before the alien tries to eat your head?
Oh, good question.
I mean, that might be where the Timekeeper can also come into play
because he's just a robot and we can repair the Timekeeper
and take you to when the alien was at a baby and you can smoke him out.
Smoking out a baby alien or even just going to the alien's own planet,
like he's probably more chill when he's not being kept in a
dark room with a very lit cage.
You know, that's true.
Where that was a four, right?
I saw one more. There was no number said.
Oh, yeah. Oh, OK. Yeah.
Or as few. All the presidents, every president.
And then I guess of the last, of course, would have to be
Botanicus. Great.
Yeah. So I think there's my four right there from the Carousel of Progress.
I mean, I just worried he'd be a little too stodgy.
Well, Uncle Werville could probably party.
Yeah. But you might not want that. I don't know.
He might go a little too, too nuts on it.
He might go a little too up.
You've described something that seems stressful to me.
These alien and I mean, Botanicus is obviously the dream.
I think he's number one for all of us.
Yeah. I don't want to speak for Scott, but I think I'm right here.
But unless he's like trying to send you on missions all the time,
you might be the only thing.
Well, he's wait.
Don't just sit around.
You know, everyone has their thing.
The Eagles just going to be trying to bring it back to America.
And it's like, hey, chill out, man.
We're just trying to relax here.
He's going to sing some of your favorite songs.
Yeah, he's going to say all my songs about the sticking hoots.
Goodbye to Tutsi.
Goodbye, boy.
Pop Goes the Weasel hits really hard when you're high.
Oh, yeah.
It's really here. All the subtleties of it. Sure.
Rick Beato breaks down. Pop Goes the Weasel.
Rick Beato can't tell.
Ten reasons why the chord progression in camp town races
blow your mind.
Yeah, I guess the question wasn't for us.
But yeah, I really Botanicus has to go in there.
Maybe we can submit you can mix in.
You could shave off some parts of his big leaf cape.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Get that in the rocket raccoon certainly going in there.
If there's a guy I want to hang with, he's a party dude.
Yeah, I don't think I want that.
He's going to steal from me.
He might look around my wallets gone.
Yeah, he's he's a little bit of a rascal, but he would be funny.
You'd be entertaining.
Yeah, he's one of the most gregarious animatronics, I think, in any Disney park.
Yeah, yeah.
Hondo Inaka, I was thinking, but I don't know that I need him.
I don't know.
He's not so fun.
But I think I know I was going to say Hondo, but no, I'm not saying Hondo, not Hondo.
Maybe he would smoke in an interesting way, though, because of his weird like face.
Yeah, he would have a contraption.
He would have like a crazy water pipe or like a box.
Yeah, like a vape box sort of thing.
That's very complicated.
Didn't Jason say C-3PO, who could use to chill out?
He could really look, you know, is it got to keep it like a small gathering?
Yeah, sure.
It's nice of you to think who might need it, who might need the mellow out.
That's good. That feels like selfless.
That it's not just you. It's not about you.
It's about helping people with the power of weed.
I mean, yeah, if I could also surround myself where I'm like, not the most neurotic,
like if I get some other guys in there.
You've also chosen characters.
I think you'd be a little less like nervous about you might be like nervous
about meeting the timekeeper if he's a hero of yours.
Oh, yeah. But I think he's probably pretty humble and chill.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, really?
Oh, you're a fan of me, really? Oh, geez.
I forget that I anybody even I'm in such a bubble here.
You know, just me and Nineye, you know, I forget people even know of my work.
I forgot about Nineye.
Yeah, I guess we had to invite Nineye.
Jason, what about any of the robots on the great movie ride?
You don't want to smoke with any of your classic favorites?
It is James Cagney from White Heat.
That's right. I'm saying like you could really.
He would be the most I think him and the showgirls from
Footlight Parade, all the pre-code actors.
Would be cool.
Let me erase your answer and let me answer for you.
Oh, OK. Dream Blunt Rotation is all the different dancers from Footlight Parade.
I sure the dancers sharing a blunt.
Oh, and then Jason rising up in the center on a on a big
wheel wave of blunt smoke.
Is there a Robert Mitchum animatronic?
Because we already know he likes it. Yeah, I don't know.
But we do. We know he was arrested for weed.
It almost jeopardized his whole career.
Again, Jason, the familiarity you assume.
We all know. We all know about Robert Mitchum's
weed arrest. Night of the Hunter.
You know, we don't know what that is.
Oh, that's great. It's a classic.
Jim's theme, Mitchum's weed arrest.
This is sort of normal stuff.
A normal American should know this is stuff they should teach in elementary school.
Yeah, a brick of our. Yeah.
Mitchum played Phil Marlowe twice.
Bogey only played him once.
We're going to go back with our time machine.
We can go anywhere in time.
All the most important events like when Jim's theme
from Treasure Planet was written or when Robert,
I can stop Robert Mitchum from being arrested for marijuana.
We squeeze a couple more movies out of them that way.
Yeah, so I my my I'm I'm being selfish
and I'm just trying to pick chill out people.
Jason is going to smoke out of an alien, a murderous alien
and a chilled out alien.
Oh, yeah, the blunt goes in the tiny mouth because then it's easier.
The blunt goes in the tiny mouth.
Yeah. Oh, if you could have the alien encounter alien and the xenomorph.
The xenomorph. Oh, maybe they would find love.
What about two blunts?
Xenomorph, tiny mouth has a little blunt
and then the big mouth has a regular size.
Has a big. Oh, OK.
Has anyone made a like a pier, like a beach front pier
bootleg shirt of that? Oh, that's cool.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess one has to be out to the side.
Yeah. What the big mouth that's coming out of the side and then the little one
comes out and then, oh, that's a good idea. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Ooh. Oh, well, maybe that's a that's a shirt.
And then it says like class of twenty, twenty four at the bottom
because they are there for senior week.
Yeah. So so I think that's that's a good that's for certainly a good shirt.
I'm trying to think of a good like botanical is such a perfect,
you know, weed version of botanicals.
I don't know what a xenomorph.
We don't morph. We don't morph.
Yeah, that's good. All right. Done.
That works for now. We don't morph.
All right. Yeah. Well, I think we're done with this, too.
I think you survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate and for all of these great questions.
Appreciate it. If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP
Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
You know, it's the real dream.
Blunt rotation. All of our great listeners. Yeah. Yeah.