Five, four, three, two, one.
Yo welcome to podcast the ride.
We say it with a little extra ass because I want to take a ride on dat ass.
You know how we do baby.
This is SCO double tizzy.
You know I'm getting busy.
We got Mikey C in the place to be.
Yo, yo, yo, sorry just adjusting the ones and twos.
Oh yeah, you know that's the cool way.
That's how we're calling it this summer.
It's ones and twos.
We don't even know the name of the equipment we're using.
Jay Schizzle, he's all up in that pizzle.
Yo, it's Jason J-A-S-O-N like when the fellas say it, love when the ladies yell it.
That's something you would say on any episode.
Just splice that, put it into a regular intro and see how confused people get.
Yeah, hey, it's podcast the ride the second gate here and this is one where I would say
you don't have to watch what we're talking about for this to make sense, but you might
want to do like a little just dip your toe in.
Yeah, get that toe a little wet, get a little wet in there, get all wet up in it and just
to get a sense of the vibe.
You don't need to watch this full half hour, but I think the vibe is important before we
start explaining some things about this.
If you watch the first two or three minutes, you'll get it, but if you watch the full 29
minutes, it will feel like two hours of your life have passed.
It is definitely a different time zone, this special.
This I think is maybe one of the strangest things we've, I showed it to Jane and she,
I think her response was, why are you punishing me?
What did I do?
Why are we watching this?
Well that's the kind of thing, yeah, I'm prepared to make those kinds of statements.
I think this is one of the most repellent things that we've ever watched.
You called it cursed the first time I said it.
It's pretty cursed and I, well here, just to say the whole history, so we're talking
about something called Six Flags Live and I'm excited about this because it feels kind
of in the spirit of weird, failed, non-theme park or roller coaster endeavors of the Six
Flags organization.
I'm still very delighted by Six Flags roller coaster cuts that they tried to do at Children's
Hair Salon and I'm like, you know, it's the kind of thing you can't force a sequel to.
You got to just bump into it.
So my delight when a little while ago, a Twitter account called Lost Media Busters,
which has some good stuff in general, it's worth following in general, but they posted
a lost half-hour teen-oriented pilot made by Six Flags in 2001.
This was posted to a YouTube channel called Retro Six Flags.
Also has some very interesting stuff on their channel.
Yeah, I did a little dive after and I don't remember any of it, but it was, I was so excited
that there was that because there's a lot of that for Disney and some for Universal,
you know, yeah, Retro, the old, because we do so, God knows this podcast is born out
of like, oh, the way it used to be.
Remember old Disney MGM studios?
And you see almost none of this with Six Flags and I think that the audience for it is pretty
limited because all of the view counts on this channel are all like sub 300.
But it's like area music or voice tracks, like it's stuff we like, but it is really
so much of Disney and even Universal is preserved, but it's really lost media when you start
trying to find Six Flags.
It's really where yet.
I just don't think it's not an area that because, you know, the vibe of Six Flags, especially
around this time, and that's what this episode is all about, is a little bit in your face.
It's a little bit of its time.
So having like the thoughtful nostalgia for the magic of Six Flags just seems so rare
to me.
Yeah.
This is my impression was that they were going to play this in the lines for rides.
Is that right?
Maybe?
Hard to say.
Yeah.
Some of the literature indicates that basically.
So this goes up on Twitter a little while ago.
A couple of listeners brought it to our attention.
Josh D regular history buff, Ben Stans.
And so I was like poker.
It was on my like to do list.
I think I was busy that way that day.
And Jason, you flagged it.
And then not I didn't like buckle down and watch it until our friend Kevin Tully alerted
us to just send us the link without saying anything.
And I said, Oh yeah, I've been meaning to get to this.
And then his next texts really sparked my attention.
This is, I believe, like the video from the ring.
I watched it all.
And now I have this unshakable feeling I'm going to die within seven days.
I think I had only watched the first few minutes when I sent when I sent it to you guys.
And then when I sat down and watched all of it, I was a little like, this is unbelievable.
Yeah.
It's a it's a hell of a it's a hell of a tone to lock into for a while.
And I completely agree with Kevin's sentiments.
He did not pass away, but I, this is over seven days ago.
Yeah.
Yes.
I do worry about sending listeners to watch the given how like real the PTR curse has
been over the course of the whole year seems to have affected Aerosmith, the band in general.
We brought Aerosmith down.
They're no longer able to perform live because of Stephen's voice in case you didn't hear
the news.
Well, because of us is what happens.
Because of us.
Because you believed too much, because you believed in their music and you believe in
him, the man and all of his deeds too much.
Yeah, I believe in all of his deeds.
And I always say that.
You've always said that.
People are saying it, but I'm saying it the most.
Check out Stephen Tyler's deeds.
He did perform Mama Kin with the Black Crows like two months ago.
So I've got false hope that he was fine.
You know, two months ago he seemed like he was singing on stage, but I bet he can't just
sing a full concert anymore.
Mama Kin, that's a heck of a blues, blues jammy jam.
You go rock, you go fast there, but you don't have to belt it out necessarily like you do
Dream On.
So it's not the vocal strain necessarily.
But yeah, we took him down, sadly.
So listeners beware, I guess, if you want to get into this, but given what we've said
about it thus far.
But this is available on YouTube and on retro Six Flags.
It's a half hour.
And just to get into the vibe of it.
So it's called Six Flags Live.
And if it wasn't clear enough from it being called that, and then you get into it and
there's like young hosts with microphones and the microphones say S.F.L. in kind of
like a thin, slithery font, sometimes lowercase, a lascivious font.
I do find it to be a lascivious, yeah, yeah.
A lot of this is lascivious, or what's the term, misogynistic.
That's certainly the case, yes.
But from that S.F.L. shortening, you're like, OK, well, this is certainly Six Flags Attempt
at a TRL, at a Total Request Live, which was a ubiquitous linchpin of pop culture in our
era when we were growing up.
So they had this idea, OK, what if we took Total Request Live, which has provided this
vibrant hub to MTV's operation and lifted all these record sales.
And now it's like part of the Times Square attraction.
What if we did that in Six Flags Parks?
What if it was a TRL in places where roller coasters are passing by every 10 seconds,
so everyone has to shout over them?
And what if we put live in the title, but it seemingly has no way to actually be live?
And what if, on top of that, a lot of the function of it is sports scores?
My complaint about sports scores, too, of the minute, let me digest them.
Give them to me weeks later.
Don't bug me with this up to the minute scores.
Sports scores and lists from magazines.
Yes.
There's so much about like, oh, Rolling Stone said this or L Magazine said this.
Contour Magazine is talking about the 10 sexiest belly buttons of the summer.
What do you think?
There are some confusing belly button shirts.
There's confusing belly button shirts.
The jeans look weird.
That spiky pixie cut.
The one woman has like a shirt that looks like curtains to showcase her belly button.
I haven't seen one of those in like 20 years.
That's an old school thing, I guess.
Nobody ever brought that back?
Belly button like tassels to hide your little belly button.
Well, they don't do a very good job.
There's tantalization of the tassels.
Sometimes you see it and sometimes you don't.
Also, there's monologue jokes, essentially, hidden in the...
Yeah.
There's just segments where people are doing monologue jokes for like a late night talk show.
There's a good amount of monologue jokes and some of them are one take because they stutter
or words are rearranged.
Like 100% of this was one take.
Can I...
Really, in the special, there is this segment and this is like a hard monologue joke.
It is a terrible joke, but the setting of it is really something.
If I could just play this real quick.
Yeah, yeah, please.
Can you believe it?
The Backstreet Boys are finally back on track as far as their tour goes, now that AJ has
graduated from alcohol abuse treatment.
We'll see how long that lasts.
That is a joke about like, we'll see if that rehab takes.
I think you're being incredibly kind by calling it a joke.
I...
It is...
Just a mean statement.
It is very mean, but it is delivered in a lazy river.
I'm like, well, delivering monologue jokes in a lazy river, that's not a job I ever considered,
but I think I would like it.
Not this quality of joke.
Not this quality of joke where it's just, like you said, a mean statement.
You had to film that ad in the pool and it like damn near killed you.
If you had to do that all day every day, it wasn't a lazy river though.
It wasn't a lazy river.
Well, but I didn't...
I didn't have a big floaty, you know?
Okay, okay.
The later spot where I am in a big floaty was very comfortable.
Can we try to make a pilot sort of on the down low at one of these water parks with
Jason in a lazy river where he does monologue jokes?
I'll just shoot it on the iPhone.
Yeah.
Okay.
Which...
What's the one at Knott's?
I'm like at Soak City.
Soak City, okay.
Well, is there a lazy river at Soak City?
Let's look into it.
Soak City becomes Talk City.
Yeah.
Donald Trump's added to get...
Jason...
Oh, is that you drowning?
Well, I fell out of the tube.
Oh, okay.
That's you, not the camera.
I was struggling.
They dropped the camera.
Yeah.
You're just floating in an inner tube asking women as they walk by.
You got any tattoos?
Hey, you!
No!
You got any tattoos?
No, I don't want to bother anyone.
Oh, okay.
So it's just jokes.
Well, it's a different format than Six Flags Live.
Okay, okay.
There's a lot less costing.
Yeah, I didn't say anything about...
I meant actually crafted jokes.
Well, we want to get some views on this though, so we got to see some tattoos.
That's my point of view on it, but okay, well, we'll talk off air.
Do you have Amazing Grace?
The musical notes, but I'm going to call it lyrics for some reason.
That was the history of it, is that Mike kept pushing the show into this sexy place when
Jason just wanted it to be about the joke craft.
Anyway, Jason drowned after that, and they did bring him back with enough CPR, but it
was the type of CPR that had to go for so long it broke his ribs, so he's healing from
that.
Well, I know the rumor coming out about this show is that it's so funny that people are
busting ribs, but it wasn't the comedy that did it.
I did not get a rib removed for a Marilyn Manson kind of thing.
I would really like that rumor.
There's a rumor going around that Jason got his rib removed.
Let's snuff that out.
One single rib.
I know that Jason's the sex positive, the comfortable one of a bunch, but he's not comfortable
enough for that surgery.
No.
Not yet, at least.
Plus, he doesn't need a rib removed to get down to that, baby.
This guy's flexing, y'all.
I'm surprised they didn't talk about that in the ... Yo, there's a rumor going around
about my boy Marilyn M. This special ... There's not a lot of information about where it came
from or indeed the use of it.
Was this going to be an online thing or were they going to show it in the line?
It did seem like that was indicated.
Here's what we know from the YouTube description.
It was produced by a company called Ackerman McQueen.
Hold onto that name for later.
For now, all you need to know is that Ackerman McQueen produced all of Six Flags advertising
content around this time.
It's the same entity that is making the commercials.
When I heard that, I'm like, okay, this makes a ton of sense because the ickiness of the
vibe definitely crosses over to the kinds of ads that I saw in the late 90s that scared
me away from Magic Mountain to this day.
The modus operandi, I think, was to ... It's not sweet little magical Disney ads.
It's full of screaming and terror and push yourself to the limit.
I was trying to watch a few ads to find ones with the vibe.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
It's a lot of the same shit they do.
Things will be heavily tinted blue or brown and sometimes making the park look post-op
apocalyptic.
That's what they're going for.
Can you survive the wasteland?
Then they'll cut to a guy getting blasted in the face by a hairdryer that's a foot off
camera so it looks like the ride is blasting his cheeks back.
I feel like maybe this company and this style of ad is what pioneered the use of my favorite
scream in sound effect media, the Howie scream, the Ru-wah, which that's not the Wilhelm,
but the one with the second level of guttural.
Anyway, I think that was ... Six Facts stuff at that time, just very over-tinted, over-edited,
gross fonts, edgy, could try to scare you, but then in watching a bunch last night, I
was reminded that no matter how do you dare, brave the pits of hell, then it still had
to end with $5 off with a Coke can from your local rounds.
The markets were never cool with getting too scary with these things.
Just a point of clarification, there is no Mr. Six in this special.
That comes later, I believe.
It does come later.
It's fair to say, actually, that this ad company, Ackerman McQueen, the Six Flags relationship
was severed in 2003.
In 2004, they get a new ad company, and that is the dawn of Mr. Six.
Mr. Six was a company coming in hot, we're not going to be doing this edgy Six Flags
Live stuff.
We are going to create an icon that will last generations.
Ackerman McQueen had to shift all their efforts to making the movie Domino, if you remember
that.
Who was in Domino?
Domino, is that Keira Knightley?
It's the bounty hunter movie.
I think it is Tony Scott, but it's really over-edited.
It very much has this aesthetic.
2005, yeah, Keira Knightley, Tony Scott.
Donor is the name, WB Donor is the name of the company that took over, that created
Mr. Six.
Prior to that, back in the 50s, they came up with Takes a Lickin' and Keeps on Tickin'.
Then in 97, they created Zoom Zoom.
Remember Zoom Zoom?
Oh, Zoom Zoom Zoom.
What is that?
Zoom Zoom, there was a Mazda.
There was somebody whispering, Zoom Zoom.
I don't remember that.
I feel like that was on TV a lot.
It probably was.
Yeah, so anyway, that's the Donor history.
I will get to history about the other shortly.
I was going to say, this is also just this era.
People will post Game Boy print ads sometimes from the late 90s, early 2000s, and they're
very sexual.
It was just like, this was what was going on in advertising at this time, for whatever
reason.
Yeah, it was just a weird.
Unaggressive.
I tend to blame all of the late 90s aggression on the singular event of Woodstock 99, but
it was, I feel like that was part of a stew, an aggressive, poisonous stew of 50 things.
And Six Flags Live, certainly a part of it, though you can't put any blame on Six Flags
Live because it wasn't released to encourage bad acts from people.
It wasn't releaseable also.
No, no.
I wouldn't say so.
In fact, I apologize for the degree of sound quality of the, you might hear some really
blown out mics and some pretty unlistenable music.
I'm sorry, let me show you this Game Boy ad.
The new Game Boy Pocket, seriously distracting.
And there's a woman tied to a bed frame, and it's like, I'm not going to, I guess, have
sex with this.
I mean, she could be consenting to this situation, but she's waiting for you to.
She may have put herself in that position, but yeah.
I mean, it's unclear though.
I'll say that.
She has the love of like, oh, are we doing this?
Like, where are you?
But this is for a Game Boy.
Yeah.
This is primarily for children.
Possibly being played by 11 year olds.
I mean, obviously the audience was aging up a little bit at that point, but this is only
what, 10 years after the Game Boy came out?
But I like the idea of kind of a like sweaty, pimply 11 year old being in that room and
going not now.
Kirby is back in dreamland.
I have to help him.
Kirby.
God.
Let me, that's insane, although I'm less offended by this actual imagery and more offended by
the font.
Oh yeah.
Well, that font is lascivious.
It's a nightmare font.
I don't know.
That's less lascivious and more like it's trying to act like it's shaking around, like
it's in motion despite being in print.
Seriously distracting.
It's a kind of font I feel like you'd also see in a like, join the Navy ad from this
time.
Well, those Navy ads were probably sexual too.
The Navy's extreme.
I had a Game Boy pocket.
It was just slightly better looking than Game Boy and it wasn't a massive fit.
It was just like, it could fit in your pocket, but it was a big, big, big, big, big pockets
at that time.
So that was the style.
Oh, that was true.
Yeah.
Did you guys ever have any Junko jeans?
No, no, but I did have big, big shorts.
Kevin Smith style shorts.
Yeah, that seems right.
Yeah, that was all I knew to do, just wear giant clothes.
I think that's what people want.
Will girls like this know for many years?
Huge clothes that don't fit me now.
Huge clothes.
And I am bigger than I was then.
Air walk, you know, got to get my air walks or my vans, you know.
Sure.
Let me play this little, just to give a flavor of it.
Aesthetically, what you're seeing here, everything's shaking around, everything's shaking around.
It's all lowercase, which is edgy.
Capitalization is for newspapers.
Those are boring snooze.
But then you'll get a little vibe of one of the, one of the hosts, one of the first hosts
who appears, who I believe is.
Are there 20 or are there a dozen?
I lost count.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There are far too many.
Yeah, yeah.
But I think, I think Corey, we see here.
What's up, girl?
How you doing?
I know you want to jam.
Put the pig down.
Let's go.
Let's start jamming.
Sorry.
Also.
Okay.
That's a stuffed pig.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, this, this is the kickoff of the show.
There's been like an intro with just a lot of like, it's just said like music, right?
And then, uh, in some brief appearances for pop stars to assure you celebrities won't
be in this.
But then it just, once you get into the meat of the show, it's just a guy named Corey with
spiky hair, just like hopping up to a woman.
Like it's not full on a costing, but sorta.
Yeah, a little bit.
He's like, he's a waving fist.
This could be dangerous if you're not paying attention.
Does Corey have like the Derrick Wibley Sum 41 hair?
Cause that's who I associate, plenty of people have that hair.
That's the guy I associate most with that hairstyle.
I hadn't thought about it.
Yeah, that is, it's very Sum 41.
It's like a, some of the vibes of these guys, of the 20 hosts of the show, some of them
are very new metal, but then there are two, like some of the new metal can be a little
scary.
They're more, these guys all seem like soft.
Yes.
So I, which is why I calibrate their vibe at crazy town.
I think they're very, you're my butterfly sugar, baby.
Cause that band was kind of between metal and boy band and, and like the, because it's
bright colors and nobody's ever, no one on earth was ever scared of crazy town.
No, new metal at least has some aesthetic.
I feel like crazy town.
I feel like crazy town had an aesthetic, but it's a little more grown in a lab.
Crazy town.
You're saying they're not authentic.
I don't know what even they would be authentic too.
They're original.
They're continued.
Yeah.
I mean, that's where, yeah.
They are kind of their own genre, which is so rare to find.
Do you have any more of Corey, you, this was the clip that went around like Twitter and
Instagram.
Okay.
Yeah.
But this is, he means his dance.
He's like hopping around.
Yeah.
That's what he's talking about.
No, we saw him at the backpack.
Oh, he is.
Oh, okay.
It comes up.
So you can see the assets.
Let's see the assets.
Look at the assets of the G bag.
That's what I'm talking about.
Do you like the G bag?
It's German, huh?
Yep.
This has got crazy stuff.
Look at that.
What?
How much is it?
$200.
That's all.
One day paper route.
One day's paper route.
You can pick this up.
So it's all about a backpack with speakers.
But then I don't think anyone's turned around to show it until that point.
So it's just confusing.
And then when he says assets, and then the shot just is of her ass.
I don't know that it's about assets, or I think that's what he's referring to.
It's a $200 backpack with a CD player and speakers, the Osiris G bag.
He keeps saying one day paper route.
One day's paper route.
Now Jason, you did not have a paper route, even though it feels right that you did.
He would have done a paper route to all the residents of a lazy river.
Oh, wow.
If you give him a plastic box to keep the newspapers dry, he'll throw them every which
way as long as it's all people along a lazy river.
A paper route in movies, I feel like it's like a tunnel of love.
It exists in movies and television.
The actual paper route, I just remember someone's sedan driving along, and then just winging
newspapers out of an open window, because it was fucking freezing most of the year.
Much of the year.
You're saying the paper boy video game doesn't exist.
No, no.
Riding a bike.
Anymore.
Throwing tied up newspapers waving at your neighbors.
No, I never encountered that.
Yeah, because I remember a car just pulling up and coming out the window.
Yeah.
When I was a kid.
Paper whips.
But it does feel like, yeah, you would.
Maybe if you went into one of these either beach town or Lake Michigan style things, there's
a bunch of houses on the lake, and you could just float around the big lake and whip the
paper in the backyard.
I mean, a lazy river is my preferred method of transit.
Yeah.
Sure.
Your tip for future, if you're trying to invite Jason to a birthday party or something, you
might get the follow up question, is it along a lazy river?
Along a lazy river.
If it's on my way, I'll try to float down, but.
Is $200 a day what you would get for delivering papers?
I don't think so.
It seems high for the early 2000s.
That seems like it would be the total revenue, not the profit.
Is he talking about the net or the gross?
We don't know, Cory.
Come on.
Be more clear.
That would usually, the paper person would come around on Saturday or Sunday and like,
oh, hey, yo, over the next few months.
You know?
Yeah.
So it's a confusing segment for many reasons.
You're getting, a lot is being thrown at you, vibes wise.
Cory himself is just a lot, frankly.
There's a lot to handle.
I would say that all of the men in it, all of these spiky haired frosted tip guys, okay,
here's the thing.
I don't know these people and I can't slander these people and I can't speak to anything
that they have done in their lives and I'm not going to do that.
I'm just going to say that the vibe is rapist-ish.
Yeah.
I won't call them rapists.
I will call them rapish.
Okay.
It is.
That's not saying anything.
Cory, if you're listening, I'm just, I don't know.
It's a vibe.
The whole special is very corny, but there's no sexuality.
If that makes sense.
No, there's no, there's never any point of connection.
There's never any point where one person with lust in their eyes encounters someone else
with lust in their eyes.
It is either, it is annoyance all the way to hatred.
There's never electricity between two people, even though everybody's shouting about sex
and butts for the whole special.
Even shouting about it in most cases when in groups of people, they seem like they've
agreed to be on a camera.
They do not seem comfortable.
They do not seem prepped.
They seem confused.
There is one moment where I feel like a woman is asking questions and people are just walking
by and they're like, what?
Yeah, things are just being shouted.
So wait, and if we haven't explained this, it's all just like handheld footage in the
general grounds of Six Flags Parks.
It's a lot of Magic Mountain, but you also go to over Texas and maybe some other ones
or in the water parks.
Yeah, Marine World, which was not a Six Flags, Marine World, I believe, was a park.
Then Six Flags acquired it and eventually maybe they left or they ran into the ground.
It's got a confusing history.
It's a history they don't get into.
They don't seem to care.
You know what?
We make a show all about rides and park ownerships and if that's what you thought you'd get
out of Six Flags Live, frankly, you don't get any of that.
It seems to be all about either the latest trends or trying to put the moves on a member
of the opposite sex.
If we were doing the show, we would be asking about the history of the Sid and Marty Croft
Dirty Puppet Show that they did at Six Flags many, many decades ago, but there's no mention
of it.
What is that?
What kind of coaster is that?
Is that a Vekoma?
Cory didn't even know if it was a Vekoma.
Cory also, just in terms of vibe, he's also kind of like a living ... You know in office
space the like, oh, oh.
If that wasn't like a comedy character, if that was just a man who existed as opposed
to a part being played by somebody.
That's the vibe, but they aren't satisfied with Cory because there's just more.
There's a hundred Corys in this special.
There's so many Corys.
They keep introducing new Rapishes.
It's like there's a cloning machine off camera and a new Cory emerges every ...
We got one.
He's ready.
Go, go, go.
Ninety seconds.
They just send him right out.
Do a couple of monologue jokes.
New Cory.
That's their life.
They have to film fast because they're made, but they will melt in the Valencia sun and
cease to exist in three hours, so we just got to whip them through stuff.
Every Cory you're seeing on screen has a three-hour life expectancy.
You just can't keep it up.
It's so exhausting to both be and look at Cory because yeah, almost immediately there's
another guy, David, I think, and David is in ... It's crazy how fast ... David's in
like a sleeveless shirt with a gorilla on it and I think sometimes in a beanie with
flames on it, so you get David really fast.
Let me see.
David seems to ... Well, this is a point ... When you see David, you realize that this entity
has not decided whether the shortening of the show is SFL or 6FL and even when they
decide the logos are different.
Almost every time ... It's a little detailed, but almost every time you see a little mic
cover in this special, it is a different type of ... It's a different logo, a different
branding.
If they were an advertising company, I think they should have had eyes on that better.
Our eyes were on the prizes, baby.
Am I right?
Blah, blah, blah.
That's it.
That's the whole special in five seconds.
There's no script supervisor.
There's no continuity person.
I'm beginning to think there was no script supervisor on Six Flags.
What was the executive producer doing during this?
More simply, there's no one following any consistency, but it just boils down to people
going like, blah, blah, blah.
Yes.
Well, it's like if any boring nerd talks for more than four seconds in coherent English,
then that has to be quickly interrupted by, blah, blah, blah, blah, and then a word that
doesn't exist, like, yeah, we know we're scrazzin', all right.
They're always cutting off the people answering their questions, and then it cuts to indecipherable
stock footage.
There is, very early on, there's a shot of a woman kind of dancing, feeling herself,
and then she full-on rubs her crotch, and then it cuts away.
Yes.
It's almost as if they got footage where, if the footage kept going, you would see that
she was shooing a fly from her jeans, but they cut it at the frame where you're like,
oh, is she going downstairs?
Is she so excited by Six Flags Live she's just going to take care of business?
Who is that excited about Six Flags Live?
She's so turned on by the whole enterprise that she's got to do above-the-jeans stuff
to herself.
Oh my God.
But the most perplexing one is not, I mean, I guess it's sexual if you're stretching
a double entendre, there's a shot of a man with a hedge clipper or a bush trimmer, and
it just kind of trims a bush and then cuts away.
Really?
Yeah.
It's bizarre.
Wow.
Subliminal MTV-style editing made me not even notice what you were talking about.
They do.
There is one piece of foot, almost every scene transitions with the same shot of just bare
midriff woman kind of low pants, and she's just moving her hand.
I don't know if that's the one you're talking about, Jason.
It's like, she's in khakis, it was the very beginning of the first clip, you should, but
they use this 30 times, every single, and then it'll say Los Angeles or Texas on top
of that, so you can keep track of where you are.
This doesn't help you keep track whatsoever.
No, there is one shot when they pan to the one guy, Nick, who's in a bunch, it starts
on a seal in an enclosure, and then it pans to him.
There's no mention of the seal, and it is on him for so, it's got a cut to him.
That's a good question.
Is that, okay, I'm trying to assess the whole thing.
How much actual, of the half hour, how many seconds do you consider actual theme park
content?
Oh, man.
Five minutes?
I don't think even four is going to say that, other than unless you count the existence
of roller coasters or slides in the frame.
I think there's one guy who's talking about the concert that's coming up, and he's like,
we got Texas Rattler back here.
Oh, yeah.
He yells the name of a ride, but yeah, you're right, we don't get any, we don't talk about
that seal.
No, if anything, the longest amount of time is spent on Willa Ford.
You get a lot of Willa Ford, yeah.
A lot of Willa Ford.
I, here, I'll get to Willa Ford, I'm just going to go in order, just because it's easier
for my notes.
Please.
Okay, so we're not long after that AJ alcohol abuse joke you mentioned.
Not long, yeah.
Really soon after, somebody brings up their segment, SFL music news and grooves, and that,
I think it's a woman, talks about how the rumors of Whitney Houston dying of a drug
overdose are not true.
She is alive and well, but we can't say the same about her career.
This is in the first five minutes, like the meanest state, like non sequiturs.
It's the first two minutes.
Oh, Jesus.
They get two, which does make me like, I can remember feeling at that time, all of culture
was like, if somebody is dealing with a drug or alcohol problem, that means they're losers
who fucked up, and they should be laughed at.
Was that not the culture of the, yeah, yeah.
When you are getting a ton of that, I mean, it wasn't from this, again, I didn't see Six
Flags Live, but it's, boy, is it reflective of the culture of it.
Everyone was vicious to Lindsay Lohan and-
Yeah, I was rooting for the failure.
I hate to make a point that a lot of documentaries have made recently, but I hate to tell you
guys, sometimes if you revisit those Jay Leno monologues, they are not especially kind to
the young women of Hollywood.
What?
Jay?
Yeah.
Doesn't sound like a Jay.
I know.
Nicest guy in children.
He brought those donuts to the strike.
Well, striking writers.
The guy who did that do, he brought 12 donuts.
Horrible jokes about women's appearances for many, many years.
I feel like we need to turn one of Jay's lines against him.
We need to turn to him and go, what were you thinking?
His most famous line.
His famous line.
Yeah.
Was that cute?
He saved it all.
Something I continue to not understand.
Can you imagine anything of that nature today?
I guess the Jimmy Fallon hair tussle was one moment that kind of changed the fortunes of
the shows.
Yeah.
So I guess, but that's also like a, that's he's with the possible leader of the free
world who's a horrible man.
I don't understand how like Leno failure, bad, one Hugh Grant joke and everything changes.
So strange.
Yeah.
Oh, one, not to pile on Jimmy Fallon, but I just listened to an episode about the whole
like bored apes, like NFT scandal and stuff.
And the Jimmy Fallon Paris Hilton segment is so funny.
That is something.
I think that deserves to be in the late night pantheon of like the things, you know, your
Don't Blame Conans, your things you've talked about over the week, things that from talk
shows that must be revisited at least once a year, the entire, the Fallon Paris Hilton
board segment is like, that is an unbelievable slice of the culture that I think much like
Six Flags Live that historians, I think that is more telling about the year that it was
made and then a lot of other culture, nobody from Paris to Jimmy to audience.
No one knows what's happening and why.
No one knows why it's occurring.
Any entity that caused that to happen is not in the room and has no control over it.
So you've just got baffled, 100% baffled people, even the people talking.
I'll shout out a recent episode of the show, Western Kabuki.
And they had a reporter on to talk about.
They did the whole board apes from the launch to the temporary blinding every, at one of
the board ape fest, they had UV lights at like one of the concerts and stuff.
However, there's UV lights for entertainment and UV lights for sterile cleaning, sterilize
like stuff.
And they had, they had the, and there were numerous people who woke up in the middle
of the night and were either in terrible pain or couldn't see and they had to go to the
hospital.
And the company eventually issued a statement.
So they were all fine.
Oh my God.
But Jimmy Fallon was not there probably.
Jimmy Fallon was not at that one.
Amy Schumer may have been, there's some very funny.
Thankfully, he was busy jamming out with Billy Joel in Madison Square Garden, doing his funny
Mick Jagger impression.
That's insane.
I didn't know there were board ape fest either.
I would say that a relatively coherent host is Nick, who otherwise goes by NIC, as you
quoted at the beginning.
He is all right because he is the only person who speaks in a black manner who is black.
Yes, very good.
Makes it all a little bit more palatable.
He also, I feel like, is full of fun facts as he talks in front of Goliath, where he
mentioned it like, all right, all the summer, we've got Blue Cantrell, we've got Del the
Funky Homo Sapien, in case you didn't know, Ice Cube's cousin.
I didn't know that.
I did not know that.
I thought that was interesting.
And then we got hits coming up from, he seems to be introducing songs that are not played.
We got Nika Kosta, that's Frank Sinatra's goddaughter.
Also, I forgot about, I did know that.
You did know that?
Wow, you did.
I didn't know that.
Nika Kosta was Frank Sinatra.
And he makes a weird joke about us.
You might want to cop that album, because if you don't, you're going to end up with
a horse head in your bed.
Kind of mixing metaphors, but okay.
It's all over the place.
He also kind of introduces a backup singer-dancer who's going out on their own, but then at
that moment, a woman comes in a frame and starts holding him, and that is never acknowledged.
It is not the person he's mentioning, I don't think.
Yeah, yeah.
So I think not long after that, we start getting into, you kind of start to understand, oh,
they're probably doing the calculation that summer music festivals and concerts happen
at Six Flags, so if we can incorporate that stuff into the show, and we get interviews
backstage with so-and-so, Mandy Moore you get, I'm like, well, that's pretty big.
There's somebody with a big career to this day.
I think there's a gentleman named Nader.
We have a new guy named Nader, a new Cory whose name is Nader, and he talks to a bunch
of people.
Willa Ford is his interview.
You get a little bit of concert footage of Willa Ford.
He talks to her before, walking by the bus, and then after the concert.
There's Mandy Moore by the bus.
Oh, there's Mandy Moore by the bus.
I thought it was extra Willa Ford.
You get a lot of Willa Ford concert footage?
Yes.
Okay.
That's what I'm thinking.
There's some discussion about why Willa Ford was called Gangsta Barbie in a certain age
of her life.
You see that she has a tattoo of the notes of Amazing Grace on her arm, as you referred
to.
And he asks why, and she goes, I favorite him.
They do talk about God for a second.
Very serious.
Yeah, you know, we're having fun here, but ultimately we got to give it up to the man
upstairs.
Hey, he created all these butts.
What are we going to do?
We got to look at his creations.
We got to pay tribute to his bountiful creations by getting our hands up on him.
Notorious G-O-D, Big Ups Baby.
Cory is created by God.
All of them.
Every strand of my spiked hair is created by the Lord above.
He created the inventor of the blonde hair dye.
Yeah, he didn't make my hair blonde, but he did create blonde hair dye in the man who
invented it.
So I am playing God, and I'm trying to play with you, God.
I love you forever, baby.
God created the creator of Dapper Dan and Dippity Doo, which I put in both my hair.
It might have been from Coen Brothers movies and not real.
Who knows?
Oh, well.
Sounds real.
It could be real.
Willow Ford had an ongoing Six Flags relationship, is what I figured out, that if you were,
I think possibly in Chicago, I think Kevin referred to this, that there was a type of
Six Flags ad that was intercut with a shot at Six Flags music video for her song, I
Want to Be Bad.
I don't know if this works.
Six Flags, St. Louis, save $10 with discount coupons from Burger King.
St. Louis, St. Louis.
I like at the beginning in the music video, she pulls off a modest dress to reveal a different
modest dress.
Yeah, it's not terribly, yeah, it's a little shorter.
They don't show you a lot, though.
It's still a little, and like, yeah, she has enough time to sing, I want to be bad.
And then the cut immediately is to new Scooby-Doo Ghost Blasters.
Being bad on a Scooby-Doo dark ride, is that the implication of that ad?
It's a lot of guests enjoying rides in a reasonable fashion.
I don't think anyone's being bad.
No one's being bad.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think probably there were a lot of people being bad at Six Flags, St. Louis, but not
in that commercial.
Not inspired by Willa Ford's statement.
Was that Willa Ford song popular?
I know it.
It was around.
Did it chart?
Was it like a number one for weeks and I don't know that?
Or was it, it felt like it was so in the background of the time.
It felt like a, we got to pretend this is working and there's like a pipeline to create
new Britney's, but I don't know that it actually, here's my guess.
I think it's one of those, the way we say like, wow, nobody watched this show.
It was only number 40, but 8 million people.
I bet like it charted low, but charting low then was like enough money for her to live
forever.
I have here.
I have the, it's, it charted as a number 22 on the U.S. charts.
It was a U.S. dance charts, number four.
I don't know.
But I bet the sales were.
11.
Yeah.
And she is now one of the biggest donors to the Democratic party.
She has so much money.
That's not, that's a joke.
That's a joke.
Yes.
No, like we were saying, like she can live forever.
Like yeah, charting at number 22.
It's like, well, you're, you're set for life as are the next two generations.
She played Anna Nicole Smith and the Anna Nicole Smith story in 2007.
Wow.
Okay.
What was the story?
There was a lot of story left to go after 2007.
Yeah, really?
Geez.
Oh, Bobby Trendy is himself.
Hmm.
Nice Bobby.
Oh, they got Trendy.
She, well, for his uncle, the toast to men from 2003 that I've never heard.
I'll toast to that.
People call a podcast the toast to men, you know, you know what I'm saying?
Like you got three or four white guys in a row.
That's a pun.
You called them like a murder croons.
You called the podcast.
That's right.
Remember that joke from six or seven years ago?
Was not annoying the second time you heard it.
There's something, there's something strange that comes into effect around the concert
zone of this.
And it's not the fact that little Romeo does not appear.
Travel delays.
Yeah.
I know.
We're not sure if little Rome is going to make it.
And then later they admit that he does not make it.
But around, okay, there's, there's already a misfeeling about this special, but at the
concert, you get a date stamp of when the concert is taking place.
It is September 28th, 2001.
Now this is very, I don't know, Jason, would you like to do the honors?
Does that remind you of anything?
Honestly, I didn't know that big events like that were back in Groovin.
In Texas, I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
Big events like a Texas Six Hikes thing.
When did wrestling come back?
Wrestling came back like a week later or something.
Okay.
A week later.
Yeah.
Wrestling and the Onion were the first ones back.
And Six Flags Live.
Yeah.
They were cultural leaders.
They showed us the way.
Yeah.
You know, Mayor Giuliani said, you know, we were like, are we even still going to do
it?
Like, man, this could be the end for, this could be the last SFL we ever did.
But then Giuliani's like, we got to go back to normal sizzle.
So I'm like, all right, Cory, Cory's, all right, Cory's back up in it, y'all.
Just like that ass.
Woo.
Everyone is making bad stitch impression, like they had stitch noises.
For good stitch impressions.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Better?
Yeah.
As the king of good stitch impressions.
But okay.
So then we knew while watching the rest of this that there was the shadow of Night 11,
then later, later in the special NIC is doing a little presentation in front of some flags.
And it was Aaron who said, oh my God, the flags are at half mast.
Oh, we are looking at half mast flags.
That is how close to that is how much right after 9 11 this was, they had to talk about
like maybe some of it was in the can.
They do talk about summer a lot.
So maybe some was in the can.
But I think this was awkwardly like a good amount was left.
Probably.
They lost Cory.
Remember, we only got Cory for two days because he's going to go be one of the extra guys
in a police lineup.
That's his day job.
Central Casting is paying, that's paying more than Central Casting.
We're lucky we're getting, he's like doing us a real favor.
That's lucrative.
But Nate, we got Nader and the concert's coming up, so we're going to close it out then and
and oh my God, it's the kind of if anyone wanted a documentary about this and they like,
yeah, I remember them, you know, we were getting we were on the phone.
It was a normal morning.
We were on the phone with Little Romeo's people.
And yeah, it should be fine.
I don't anticipate any big plane delays.
I think plane travel is going to be fine for the foreseeable future.
And then somebody said, turn on the TV.
Boy, Nader shed a tear that day.
Let me tell you.
There is not a verbal acknowledgment of like in the country was very divided, but we're
all together now.
Right.
And there's no verbal acknowledgment of that or the troops or any of that.
But you have the half mass flags.
No, it's like right now, like we're all united under one flag and also six flags.
Tweety Bird, if only the tattoos were crying, if only the Tweety Bird was shedding a single
tear.
Boy, you know what?
I got to say, the least magic mountain on earth has got to be that one where Osama's
got his cave, y'all.
Ain't no magic in that mountain.
We're going to make sure there ain't no magic in that mountain soon enough.
Yeah, baby.
Shout out George W. Bizzle.
There's no there's no way this wasn't like that.
That joke wasn't in there and they cut it.
There's no way that maybe the cutty nature of it was less than aiming for hyperactive
MTV editing and more cutting every Islamophobic statement, every warmongering statement made
by Nader and Corey.
They do have a political joke though at the end.
And I can't remember word for word, but it's like something about like a lying snake or
something.
And then he holds up a picture of Bill Clinton.
Oh, yeah.
What is that?
That's really confusing.
That was on a card.
They cut out the picture and pasted it on a card and someone had to bring it to Six Flags
so that he could hold it up for two seconds.
I'm not offended by that.
I'm just saying that's the only political joke in there.
So I feel like maybe there was an agenda by the makers of this.
Well, and it was, you know, we were thumbing our noses at the last guy, you know, in such
a pro Bush era when his approval rating was never higher.
But there's no joke about like the Florida Supreme Court handing the election or the
Supreme Court handing the election to George W. Bush or anything.
There was no, there was no joke about hanging Chad, just a guy named Chad who's hanging
out here at the pool by Hurricane Harbor.
There's no joke.
And Nader, look, Nader's in there.
There's no joke about Nader giving the election to Bush either.
No, no.
You know?
That's a perfect opportunity for a joke.
There's one Nader's not messing anything up except maybe the sheets, baby.
With Pee and Poo, Nader's mad incontinent, y'all.
They let Nader go because he was like, yeah, George Bush leading the nation, but he was
also president when the attacks happened, so think about that.
No, no, you do not say that, Nader.
You do not say that.
No, no, General Ashley Clark said he tried to brief him, but he wouldn't listen.
We are pulling you from the LFO interview.
You have lost the right.
Oh, Rich from LFO.
That's a great interview where Rich is like, you know, it's two things, you know, I want
as many people as possible to hear the music, but also I want to eat and make my living
on record sales.
Rich good, yeah, he gives both sides.
Rich gives both sides.
It's a pretty, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He does reason, well, the calculation everybody has to make, you know, giving away their media
for free.
It's really prescient for what the next several decades of media was going to be.
I don't know when the release of these episodes, this is the second Rich Cronin mentioned in
the few weeks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was maybe a little while ago now, but there was a Rich Cronin, yes,
yeah, because I'd recommend his Howard Stern clip talking about Lou Perlman.
Right.
It's unbelievable.
He's a truth teller, basically.
Yes.
I mean, there's a, I like this guy.
He's got a vibe.
Yeah, I like it too.
He's, yes, rest in peace, Rich, but the reason it came up was because you thought one of
the members of LMFIO died.
Well, yes, I did.
I did think that.
And I thought you were thinking of LFO, which two members have passed away, including Rich.
I was not, but that would have been a little more.
Did we ever figure out what, who you thought you were thinking of?
No, no.
Why not?
I knew they broke up and I thought they had broken up and also one of them had died, but
that is not the case.
Well, and I thought Destro was a DC villain and it's a G.I.
Joe villain, so we're all making mistakes left and right on these shows.
Hey, this heat wave that's rocking the country.
Yeah.
Oh, it's not like the heat wave when Shrek and Moulin Rouge were in theaters at the same
time.
Wow.
Was there a heat wave during that?
It's a move.
No, they were just lighting up the box office.
Oh, okay.
And sexy late, we got Nicole Kidman and we got Fiona after the transformation.
Before it ended.
I think now we move to a segment called The Stink on Ink and it's kind of an inane conversation
about tattoos and what color ink you think would come off, it would be the hardest to
take off.
Everybody guesses red.
It's green.
I don't know what that means or who cares, but.
But green was the hardest?
Green was the hardest.
Yeah.
It was 20 times or something?
20 times through whatever the process.
But let's cut to the chase.
Where this goes is anybody got a tattoo that they want to show off and oh boy, the luck
of the Six Flags Live people that it is somebody wanting to show a butt, a tattoo on their
butt and the tattoo that is revealed is Tigger.
And she really has to unbutton and pull her pants down a little to show this.
There's a process.
She goes pretty far.
Not only Tigger, but Tigger looking kind of upset, kind of aghast, kind of open mouthed
like oh, oh no.
It's actually Tigger making the face that anyone would make when seeing a Tigger tattoo
on a butt.
It is a lot of a cheek.
The next one, the woman just kind of lowers her pants a little and it's a Tweety Bird,
which is a little more Six Flags on brand.
It is.
Yeah.
And I know that there's Tweety tattoos.
It's still a little.
I'm like of this group, there is both a Tigger and a Tweety and the Tigger is so inexplicable.
Why would you want not just a Tigger, but an upset looking Tigger?
It actually kind of looks like a Tigger that is about to get a load of something.
I mean, I didn't think of that, but now that you say it.
Content warning.
Come, come, come, come, come.
What was that?
Was that zoom, zoom, zoom?
Oh, that was me doing the bouncy, bouncy, bouncy.
Oh, okay.
Come, come, come, come, come.
I should have done the full line.
You should have been a writer for Six Flags Live.
Yeah.
We're flipping the Winnie the Pooh songs.
We're making them dirty.
We're doing it all.
I can get you a job on this new show.
I'm working on with this guy, Jason down at Knott's Berry Farm.
Really?
Is it a, it's kind of a filthy talk show.
That's the word on 10.
Well, that's what I'm going to convince him to do.
Does the host agree?
Yeah, he does.
Well, the host is unconscious and temporarily not alive for a few minutes and then he gets
back in the wave pool.
All right.
I have a pitch for this show that you make the host go unconscious again while he's unconscious.
Give him a Tigger tattoo on his butt.
This is extreme.
I like that.
Yeah.
That's good.
I feel like for brand propriety, it should, it should probably be Whittles.
You want a tattoo of Whittles?
Because we're at the Knott's.
We're at the Knott's.
Okay, fine.
I got Whittles on my seat.
Whoa.
Do you know that during, speaking of characters getting messy, do we know that during the
Boysenberry Festival that you, the Whittles, the Prospector with a big white beard that
you can meet, just during Boysenberry Festival, his beer is full of Boysenberry splashes.
I think I've seen a picture of him with Boysenberry smears on it.
It was pretty fun.
Yeah, yeah.
It's hard to call that suggestive because it is purple.
No, yeah.
What would it be?
Yeah.
I don't.
I mean, I could make a little comment.
I mean, Barney the Dinosaur is calm.
I don't know.
What am I?
I could.
Barney the Dinosaur is purple cum.
Yeah.
I wasn't happy saying it.
Now I know you like doing a Barney impression.
I do, yeah.
Can I open the floor to what Barney might say while blowing a load of his purple cum?
He could just say that.
Oh, my purple cum.
That's what he would say.
Oh, I did it again.
I love you.
You love cum.
By virtue of talking about this, this is one of the filthier episodes.
Oh, I don't want to say that.
My macaroni painting.
I'm using it for my art.
You know what's funny is that for a show that is kind of explicit or thinks it is, I think
there's so many bleeps.
Oh, yeah.
I think they even bleep the word sex.
It's this perfectly, not even PG-3, this is PG-6.
It's exactly like the combo of Six Flags, we'll kill you, $10 up with Burger King.
It's exactly that level of edginess that is immediately softened.
Yeah.
No, they can't.
I'm hoping that it would get like an 11-year-old audience, so this is the closest they can
get up to the line.
That's the time.
Well, let me, okay, since you said an 11-year-old audience, there's a part, another Cory shows
up.
This one is Ryan.
Ryan is coming at you from Hurricane Harbor.
Now it's like he's surrounded by girls in bikinis and his shirt is off, so we're doing
some sexy talk.
All right, let's get real about it.
Who's sexier, Brittany or Christina?
But the girls are all clearly like 15.
These are not.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And that's not the case in all of the segments necessarily.
I think completely there's a lot of women over 18 in this, but not this part.
And it doesn't get that bad, except then it becomes like, they're talking about like,
what's the coolest thing this summer, accessories, short shorts?
And then somebody brings up halter tops and he says, yeah, all right, well, we ain't wearing
halter tops, right?
Because all I see around here is my ladies in bikinis, yeah, baby.
And he's pointing to the women on either side of him.
For sure, they're like 15.
And I'm not going to throw this at Ryan.
It's not his fault.
He didn't turn around to see, but when he said, yes, okay, he noticed this too.
I saw it.
Yeah, because I'm like, well, hold on now.
He like when he does that, all my ladies, the direction that he points is to a girl
who has wandered up right behind him during the discussion.
He doesn't know that she's there, but for sure, this girl is like 12.
Yeah, there is a full ass child, like has one.
It seemed like her and her friend were just using the path to get by and just kind of
wandered into frame.
That's happening.
It's a very unfortunate point from Ryan.
And they didn't do a second take.
No, no time.
And they didn't cut before that.
Right.
There's not like a good like, oh, wow, that was such a good segment that what the discussion
they got into about who is hotter was so good.
We can't do a second take.
Could have easily done that.
The button is the halter tops thing.
Maybe somewhere in this organization, though, with some idiot like, could we do it with
computers?
Can we get the 11 year old out with computers?
I watched the thing about the new star, new Star Wars.
They apparently did computers on it.
Can we do that?
Well, it also the content of what they're talking about a little before that, the girls
like, I don't know, Christina has that big hair and it just doesn't seem like what everyone
else has.
And they appear to be talking about Christina and get later in the Lady Marmalade music
video.
I'm not specific to that because specifically, I don't believe she was full on in the dirty
era yet.
No.
Dirty was like 2003, 2002, 2002, 2002, maybe two.
So I don't quite they didn't seem to know what they were talking about.
So yeah, I think so.
So her new look as dictated by specifically Lady Marmalade.
It's all like half remembered everything everyone is talking about, unless they're holding the
literal magazine it came from.
And even then, who knows if they looked at it.
Yeah, yeah, that too.
A lot of like, OK, I imagine a show with only one take of everything and where all of the
content is taken from magazines.
And then we're going to read lists that were already bought up by a magazine writer.
And then the very end is a lot of like talking about technology.
It seems like they realized, oh, shit, we've got to talk about the phone and the little
camera.
Well, I think, yeah, I think they, yeah, they well, they frontloaded the sexier stuff and
then they get into the tech tie-ins.
My guess is that they didn't have any actual tech tie-ins and they were just demonstrating
like this is the kind of spot where we could do a promotion for Motorola.
I bet they hadn't secured that the sponsors and secure the Motorola sponsorship for this
underage facets, underage creep fest.
This could be you.
Instead of just a finger, he could be holding up a phone while gesturing toward a 12 year
old girl.
Yeah.
There's somebody named Amber who has a very pink vibe.
And at some point she wears like a just a full rose that's bigger than her neck on her
neck.
Seems like it'd be irritating in a hot theme park environment.
She does a talk about like the Britney with the big snake from the VMAs.
And that's what I remember that at the time it was like, what's pop culture?
Well, it's all about Britney and the big snake.
And then two days later, 9-11 happened and wow, can you just a week ago, all we were
thinking about was Britney and the big snake.
And now we're confronted by the bigger snake of terrorism that may swallow us all.
And this is like, this is, this, this is the people go at like, you know, how can we care
about the big snake anymore?
Well, they can't, they have to, they can't talk about, yes.
They can't, they can't have somebody broadcasting live from Six Flags, Afghanistan.
That was everything out there.
They can't, they can't, they had to cut that segment where they asked me on the street,
like see any good movies lately?
What have you seen the movies?
And everyone just goes hardball, hardball, hardball, like the inexplicable blockbuster
hardball.
Do you remember that Keanu Reeves coached the Little Lake team?
That was like, oh, America wants a feel good movie after these tragic events.
After comedy died.
Yeah.
Comedy died.
I remember that.
Are you going to do a two part, like a double header tonight, Domino and hardball?
Oh yeah.
They're all so good.
Oh, there's a part where there's some shade thrown at movies of the era.
There's like, at some point they're talking about a, well, there's the segment blockbuster
or bust in which there's some pre derisive conversation about the now classic, is it
called on the line?
Yeah.
Joey Fatone.
The movie with some of in sync.
Last pass.
I believe I have now, I believe I have seen all of on the line.
Is there a kid in the hall?
Oh yes.
Dave Foley, Dave Foley and Jerry Stiller in that film.
But then there's some stories talking about scary movies and he says, all right, so we
got some scary movies coming out and get your goosebumps ready.
Get your goovers just that.
Get your goosebumps ready.
All right.
You ready, fellas?
You're going to be popping out tonight.
You know, the kind you didn't really use on Jeepers Creepers.
What's the problem with Jeepers Creepers?
Yeah.
Was that not scary?
Not scary enough for you, Corey, whose name I didn't even write down.
And then he talks up Joyride.
Did anyone know what Joyride?
I remember Joyride.
Yeah.
It's about like teens go Joyriding and then they get chased by like a killer, I think.
Okay.
It was a horror movie though.
It was a horror movie.
Yeah.
That's a Paul Walker before his more famous car oriented franchise.
Joyride.
Yeah.
2001.
Oh.
JJ Abrams wrote it.
What?
Yeah.
I knew there was a factoid about that.
Paul Walker and JJ Abrams.
Yeah.
Steve Zahn star.
Oh, I love Zahn.
Steve Zahn and Paul Walker.
This is a good cat.
Maybe this is a quiet.
Is this good?
And just the voice of Ted Levine as a villain to somebody named Rusty Nail.
Wow.
That's the scariest voice there is.
There's Joyride 2 and Joyride 3.
Like straight to DVD.
It looks like it.
Yeah.
I think there's some Jeepers Creepers sequels as well.
Wow.
This is a bad robot.
It's part of the bad robot universe.
Wow.
That requires attention.
JJ, come back to the Joyride.
This is all has been, he's just been building momentum to be able to get Joyride 4 off the
ground.
So what did I miss there?
There's a part where it just cuts to somebody who just says with a bleep, crotchless panties
have been taken off the shelves in Stockholm and then it keeps going.
Yeah.
I had to replay that because I didn't know what he was talking about.
That made no sense.
Completely incoherent.
Crotchless boob have been taken off the shelves in Stockholm.
Okay.
That doesn't work.
Also with misunderstanding.
Then it goes to Cory.
He says, what's up, Cory here.
Six Flags Marine, what?
If you say it like that, anything's cool.
In this one, they bleep sex.
Everybody talks about where they like to get freaky.
And then somebody says, where's the craziest place you've gotten freaky?
And there's roller coasters going by everywhere.
So this illustrates why that's a bad idea.
It's probably in the casino.
In Encino?
No, in the casino.
On the craps table.
What?
What are you talking about?
This guy's crazy, he likes to dice up his butt.
Anyway, we're going to take it over to Nader in Texas, bye.
Also another part where clearly some of the girls are younger.
And this time it is Amber, it's a woman doing it.
She just does a big screed about what women want on the first date.
First of all, you pay.
Second, no farting.
It's probably the best part of the whole thing, honestly.
Third, don't just think about fucking her.
You got to romance her.
And then that's where you're like, these girls, these are young.
They're very young.
Fourth, don't talk about your ex.
The bitch don't matter anymore.
All right, let's go talk to these girls.
And then approach a nervous 14-year-old.
Yeah, that's pretty much what you said.
Treat me like a person, don't you?
Check your outfit, open the doors.
I'm not allowed to say some of the words that you said,
but if my mom sees me saying them on this, whatever this is,
I'll be grounded for months.
But the sentiment about the flatulence, I would also agree with.
We all got 16-ounce bottles of Diet Coke to do this.
There's like, maybe they would.
We all had to share, but you know, technically,
it's up to us how to divvy it up.
Thinking back to your childhood,
you had friends and people in this room.
There were shows you couldn't watch,
people I knew I didn't watch as Simpsons.
And as I grow up, I was like, ah, that's not gonna be me.
I'm never gonna do that.
But if my daughter was watching Six Flags Live,
I will turn this off right now.
You are not to watch this filthy show.
And then she's gonna be upset.
I'm like, I guess there are things.
I'd be like, you have to turn this off.
The vibe of, this is an evil vibe.
I don't care for this.
And then she'll fight with me.
So I guess there is something.
I guess I would draw the line somewhere.
Yeah, well, you're, look, you've got a journey ahead of you
of finding out how much of your mom is in you.
Oh, I know.
And I know there's already a lot.
There's a lot there already just from-
When you find yourself yelling about paper sheets.
Well, when I'm discussing that this bread
is technically expired because it says it on the package,
and Lindsay's like, well, no, it's a day older.
It's fine.
And I go, yes, but we must listen to the date
on the packages.
So I-
I'm with Lindsay on that one.
Yeah, I'm with Lindsay on that one too.
I've gotten better about it, by the way, too,
over these years.
I've gotten better at throwing stuff out, you know.
Oh, cause you're, as long as it's in the calendar year,
you'll still eat it.
Cause Jason's like, I will save one ice cream scoop
in the freezer for two weeks.
I don't mind the ice crystals.
They're my friends.
You and Albert Brooks' mother in the movie Mother.
Oh, Glenn Close?
No, not Glenn Close, but Debbie Reynolds.
Debbie Reynolds, oh, okay.
No, I haven't seen that full film,
but is that maybe a comp for the Mike and Jason relationship?
That Jason's my mother?
Yes.
Then I'm Debbie Reynolds and he's Albert Brooks.
I think that's probably close.
I could see that being absolutely right.
Well, Debbie Reynolds loves the old times.
She was a song and dance lady.
She sure was.
Yeah, you know, the particularly youthful actor,
90s Albert Brooks, it's just like Mike.
I think he knows exactly what he was saying.
Well, maybe there's a suggestion that Mike
has some components that are not as youthful
as he advertises.
Well, I don't, wait.
What the fuck? I was gonna say,
I don't disagree with that, but I don't wanna say that.
I was upset saying it, even if I think it's true.
There is, I mean, there's a lot of tastes, what?
Do you still have taffy frozen in your fridge?
Or freezer?
Yeah, there's taffy floating around.
Is it frozen? In the freezer?
I don't know where it is, come to think of it.
You lost your taffy? I saw it in the box the other day.
Keeping it safe in the toilet in the,
but he did tell the tank.
There's a decorative box floating around.
But you did tell us how to make sure
the taffy is fresh. You can freeze it
and then you roll it between your hands.
As long as you rub your taffy every couple months,
you keep it fresh.
No, no, when you wanna eat it,
you heat it up by rubbing it between your hands.
No, it's not a maintenance issue.
No, it's just once you only have to do it.
I thought you had to do it every year.
No.
Well, this also clearly needs to be mentioned
every once in a while,
because Mike forgot what the tip was.
I guess I did.
So Jason, just make sure once every at least four months,
you say the taffy fact on the show.
Rub your taffy before eating it.
You don't need to do it periodically to remember that.
Let me take this right into,
let's keep this on the Jason food brand,
because this knocked me out
when I was deep into the special.
I think I was having a little light cocktail
and this will flip me out of my chair,
that we were even considering talking about this on the show
and then we get to a guy,
it ends up being promotion for some weird meat product
that's Godzilla-oriented, but the important part.
Oh, don't even mention me in the same breath
that this is probably the most tasteless thing
in the whole thing. Well, you walked
right into it, because. I guess so.
Yeah, and you'll see where I'm going with this.
Here, I'll do it out of order.
I'll make the second the third,
because it has to be the topper.
It starts with one of the Corey's saying,
hey, has your Vienna sausage become limp?
Has your Spam lost its wham?
Has your Scrapple become Crapple?
Wow.
There's a Scrapple joke in this thing.
That's wild.
Wow, is Six Flags Live and our show
the only media post-2000 with jokes about Scrapple?
Good question.
I don't know about that,
but I still think it's pretty popular back East.
Where do you suppose I might hear a joke about Scrapple in?
Oh, God, the dine, the line cooks at the diner.
You were saying it's gonna be on.
I'm talking about television or.
Yeah, like, yeah.
Or podcast media. Oh, and street jokes.
These are street jokes,
which is really funny you said that
because in my mind I was about to make a joke
that you were about to say street jokes.
Oh, that's more of a street joke.
Scrapple, that's what, yeah.
It's a street meat and it gets street jokes.
Yeah, you hear it in the old neighborhood, you know?
I could see some of the East Coast late night shows
making a Scrapple joke.
Some of the, you mean the ones in New York?
The ones that air everywhere?
I was like, do you mean a Pennsylvania late night show?
Well, they're, oh, I have to look into that.
Hey, Philly Live.
You might need to move back and host one of those.
Quit this job.
Two premises, it's Philly and a lazy river.
You can only do it during the summer.
Those ones in Pittsburgh, the yinzers are out again.
How do you feel with your beloved meat,
the food most associated with you,
being involved in a body joke?
It doesn't quite make sense.
And what they, where it gets to
doesn't make a lot of sense either.
Why doesn't it make sense?
Well, what does it have to do
with this novelty Godzilla meat toy?
What he's talking about.
Well, I mean, that's the thing.
He's talking about floaters, but like.
But actually, I guess it becomes about
the some weird Godzilla meat.
So actually, the double entendre,
it's not even about the double entendre.
It's like you're trying to make you think.
It's actually very clever writing if you think about it.
You think you're talking about my sausage or my spam?
No, we're talking about literal meat.
So it is that, you know, you're so sick of,
I think where Jason's having a hard time relating to it
is the idea that literal Scrapple could become crapple.
No Scrapple is crapple for Jason.
Well, no, I mean, you don't want to undercook it.
It'll be too soft.
Well, I guess that's crapple.
If you want that crispy, you want it soft in the middle
and crispy on the outside, basically.
When was the last time you had it?
Not in a while.
Okay.
Well, that's sad.
We gotta fix that.
Yeah.
Let's talk about the other side of it though.
Scrapple being involved in a double entendre.
You have mixed feelings about that.
I'm okay with that, but it doesn't really pay off.
No, not particularly.
No.
I guess third question, because you are Mr. Sex Positivity,
acknowledge you as a sexual being.
Yeah.
I talk about sex on the show.
Has your Scrapple become crapple?
Gosh, I hope not.
Oh, the rest of my body is out to lunch,
but that still seems to be working.
As long as the Scrapple holds on is a fighting chance.
Yeah, walking a block, it sucks,
but the rest of the stuff, I mean, it's fine.
This is the bodiest episode of all time.
This is our Six Flags Live episode.
I think Scrapple is confusing too,
because as you Google image it,
it's mainly served in loaves and squares.
So it doesn't, a sausage, sure,
but I don't think anybody's got a big,
like a boxy brick-sized penis.
I think some people do.
Maybe.
You think with angles?
The loaves are cut into slices
so you can pan-fry it or fry it on a grill.
Ouch.
I think there are unique penises out there
that you can't even imagine, you can't even visualize,
I believe.
Well, all right, we gotta pose this
to the ladies in the audience.
Yo, does your boy got dick corners?
Let us know in the comments.
When you have sex, is that like
putting a square pig in a round hole?
Some people like the bird corners.
Then there's a promo for the Motorola i85.
Oh, but where the Godzilla meat package goes,
it goes to a bad dubbing joke.
It's like, oh my god, I can't believe they're doing this.
You can't?
Even in two-pounds.
I guess it's like this same time period
of what was that re-dubbed movie called?
Like the Kung Fu Enter the Fist?
Oh, yes, I have watched all of Kung Pao Enter the Fist.
Kung Pao Enter the Fist.
Wow, I watched it too.
There's some part, oh wait, you were guys all there
for my screening of Kung Pao Enter the Fist.
Oh yeah, I think so.
I don't know.
I don't remember, maybe not that memorable.
No, I saw it, yeah, I watched it.
I feel like there were two funny parts
and the rest fell off.
It was a not big time, very good.
No, I wouldn't say so.
No.
So.
The Motorola using the walkie-talkie feature.
I knew a couple people who had that
and they were very annoying about it.
The phone is also a walkie-talkie.
I feel like any time there are people around,
they're really making sure to use the walkie-talkie.
Didn't you have family walkie-talkies?
Yeah, family walkie-talkies.
I think there's a New York Times piece about that.
The short-lived window between the full cell phones
just becoming totally ubiquitous.
And they try to pass off walkie-talkies as like,
keep in touch if your family splits up on vacation.
Did you use the walkie-talkie at a Disney park?
Well, that's the one where, yeah,
I ended up on a security channel.
Oh, right, right, right, okay, that's what I,
okay, that's why I thought that then, I guess.
I was on a boat.
I was on the boat from the boardwalk.
But now, are these phones walkie or no?
I don't think Jason's walkie-talkies
could have given you real-time sports scores.
No, we couldn't have gotten the sports scores.
Via the web.
That's where like, you know, yeah,
you could watch ESPN and get your scores
the day that they happen.
Or you could watch Corey and Ryan
hold up their Motorola i85 and say,
we on the web, it's Sunday,
so we're checking out the scores.
Yo, Padres are, and then not being able
to show them to you.
And this presumably was months ago.
Uh-huh.
This is the strangest,
the whole show is the strangest pitch.
I don't know how, I know it's a pilot,
but I don't know in what, are they gonna,
if it's gonna be, if there's gonna be
up-to-the-minute sports scores,
they have to make one of these every day.
I was gonna say, I think it's gonna be a daily show,
like a TRL.
There were graphics. I mean, I would assume
that's what they're looking for.
That aired on TV or in lines.
It said, back tomorrow at 7 p.m.
I don't know what that meant.
Where? Where it was just
at the end of the video.
Oh no, I know that, but yeah,
where is it back tomorrow?
That's the big question.
The full throttle lounge does seem
like the only appropriate place to play this.
Mm-hmm.
I also just don't believe that a lot of,
I think that today, a lot of the Six Flags TVs
run off of VHS.
And unless they're burning off tapes daily,
running them from the post house,
should we get it to Valencia?
Should we shoot a Six Flags live
during Fright Fest opening night?
Oh, that's a good idea.
That'd be a good way to cover it.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
The opening night of Fright Fest
is the same as Scary Farm this year.
We'll go to both, I'm just saying.
I like going to both.
In the same night, we'll go to both.
Oh yeah, we should go.
Oh, that'd be a time, yeah, yeah.
Or we have to send two teams.
Oh wow, oh, we split into two on that night.
We can split into two on that night.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, back to you over at Fright Fest.
Like, yeah, you know, hey, this girl's got me
feeling like Frankenstein,
because I'm getting stiff.
Ha ha ha.
Fright Fest, all right, for Fright Fest Live,
for Double FL.
Yo, we're here in the sewer of souls.
We just walked by a big pile of shit.
Yeah.
Ba ba bam.
That's newer, that noise.
Did you know that butts aren't just for sex?
There's this other stuff that comes out of them.
Fun fact, it's called poo, and they got a lot of it here.
Ha ha ha.
There's a new movie coming out.
Starring Zachary Levi.
It's called Herald and Purple Crown.
Blockbuster bomb, what do you think?
Ha ha ha.
That delivery was as good as some of those people.
Yeah, yeah, that was perfectly,
yeah, perfectly halfway to sleep.
Hey, there's a new movie coming out.
They feature him in fall.
You might call yourself Fall Guy,
but this Fall Guy stars Ron Gosling.
Ha ha ha.
These are pretty good promos.
We're gonna send you to Fright Fest this year.
Oh, no.
You got anything to say?
What does Cory share, and I have to say,
about Twisters.
Ha ha ha.
Whoa, hey, did you get all spun around,
and your friend did too?
Yeah, I guess you're a couple of Twisters,
but there's Twisters starring Glenn Powell
in Peter's Now.
You're a couple of Twisters.
Right.
These guys spin around so fast,
you end up getting called Twisters,
but for now, the original Twisters are Twisters.
Oh, sorry, Good Packs.
In Peter's Now, Glenn Powell.
Good Packs is not back, he's dead.
Ha ha ha.
Anyway, I'm getting to the end of the list.
I mean, I could shout out, you know,
they talk about the hardness of tennis balls.
They're hard, harder, and morning wood.
They make, at the very end,
they make a woman do a hot dog eating contest,
and at that point, you're like,
no, she doesn't know the context
that she is being presented in.
Dude, now, if you knew what the rest of this show was,
you would not try to put four wieners in your mouth.
Don't do this to her.
Show her the rest of the pilot
before you put her in this position.
The pilot should have ended with, like, a raid happening.
Like, the police, the SWAT team coming in,
and arresting every quarry.
We are liberating all of these women from the quarries.
Whoa, it's the SWAT team who liberated Ellian Gonzalez
when they're here.
Ha ha ha.
Ellian Gonzalez was stuck in Miami for a while.
Miami's home to some of the hottest parties of the summer.
Ha ha ha.
Anyway, I mean, this is, unless you have any to throw out.
That's about all the highlights you've hit, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Mainly, I feel like we have just described
a culture of spiky-haired creeps
and gratuitous butt shots,
and there's just this grime to this thing.
Everything, now you know how true it was
that Kevin said it's like the video from The Ring.
It is like halfway between MTV's Spring Break TRL
and Girls Gone Wild.
Yeah.
It is like the-
It's Girls Gone Wild without any flash.
Right.
But it's that level of like, douchebag with a microphone,
and I'm here, I'm talking really fast,
and I'm putting a microphone in your face,
and you can't question what's happening.
Yeah, and it's-
Yeah, woo.
And you do feel like, again,
I don't think I could have articulated it back
when I was that age watching it,
but there would be a friend with a Girls Gone Wild tape,
and there's just a feeling, a bad feeling watching that.
That's not, that was not that exciting.
I mean, on some level, I'm sure it was like,
oh, cool, even though it's probably hiding my eyes,
but it was still a bad vibe.
I like that you had weird Girls Gone Wild viewings.
I don't know about that.
You had to pretend to be chill with it.
I don't remember, I know I saw it.
I don't remember where, I don't remember who.
I guess I'm trying to block it out.
I saw it without the words covering up the boobs.
It was not a fun vibe.
The seedy, the seedy-est, yeah.
This manages to be incredibly seedy
while not ever actually revealing anything,
while not really putting, while bleeping a lot of words.
Aaron was using it as shorthand for how far we've come.
There was something that was,
we were talking about something that involved
like LGBTQ progress or something.
There was something that felt like, wow,
and in 2024, this is possible, and she said,
and that's crazy, because just a few decades ago,
it was Six Flags Live.
It's like a demarcation of what,
it's a shorthand for this is where it was.
So any progress now, and she's right.
There is just this palpable evil to this piece, I think,
that reflected the time, and I guess it's what they had to do,
but I started questioning, is there a further explanation
of the palpable evil of Six Flags Live?
And the YouTube description on Retro Six Flags
just attributes it to the ad company that made it
that I mentioned earlier, Ackerman McQueen.
So Ackerman McQueen is an Oklahoma-based company.
Also in Oklahoma was a group called Premier Parks,
and they were working together in the early 90s.
Premier Parks ended up buying Six Flags mid-90s,
I forget when, thus making Ackerman McQueen,
the in-house ad entity, and the group that would do this.
I even saw a quote of somebody were putting another guy
in charge, somebody named Lipson, maybe it was Dan Lipson,
that this guy is being looked to generate edgy,
even controversial work, said he's our most aggressive
and irreverent person in the agency, said Angus McQueen,
one of the particular partners of Ackerman McQueen.
So this was part of that mandate, and you have to wonder,
if the ties were severed in summer 2003,
and this was being done in late 2001,
was Six Flags Live possibly one of the things
that burnt the bridge, and thus causing them
to go to a new ad group, and causing the creation
of Mr. Six?
We might owe Mr. Six in some weird way to Six Flags Live.
I owe him all my success.
He's your idol.
Early mentor, early encourager.
He taught you how to be weird.
But anyway.
Stop me to be weird.
Yeah, you said a mess.
My comedy hero.
So I was like, what was the rest of the ad,
the representation world of Ackerman McQueen?
And I looked them up, and I found that they remain
a very thriving entity, and did a ton of business,
in especially the 90s, 2000s, and up until 2019,
when they lost this major client.
But for three solid decades, they raked it in.
They made a ton of money from their biggest client,
and it's a client that you may have heard of,
that is the NRA.
The company that made this, Ackerman McQueen,
or ACMAC, as it's called for short,
was the PR firm, represent doing all public relations
for the NRA, from the 90s till 2019.
Every piece of media we've ever seen,
print, there's a list, they provided public relations work,
marketing, branding, corporate communications,
event planning, web design, social media engagement,
digital content production.
All of this was done by the same group
that made Six Flags Live.
Wow.
So they had to deal with that pesky Michael Moore.
Yes, that was probably one of their biggest challenges,
was getting the organization to look combative
and in fight and shape when that movie came out.
They operated something called NRA TV,
which was on for a little while, and I think is no longer.
Here's, okay, the group's called Ackerman McQueen.
Here is a photo of Angus McQueen.
That is the male in this photo.
Okay.
And that is him next to a roller coaster,
showing his association with Six Flags.
Of course.
When this person died in 2019,
the New York Times headline was,
Angus McQueen, the NRA's image maker.
Wow.
That is how much, this is, the head of this company
is like one of the main people attributed
with the NRA that we know today.
Because at one point in time, in the earlier 90s,
they were not this flagrant, disgusting.
There was kind of a proto version of the NRA.
Was it like a sportsman organization?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I think it was less of like a pack
and this awful kind of militia type.
Right, they turned it into such a crazy issue.
Yeah, yeah.
As far as just like basic regulations.
And I think the main way that they did that
is with this ad company.
You can find quotes saying,
they are credited with the modern success of the NRA.
They gave PR counseling to Wayne LaPierre.
My god.
He started as like a lower level guy in the NRA,
just kind of like timid, quiet, just did what.
And they hooked onto him as the guy they could ride
to get more power as their advocate within the company.
So they gave him PR training so that he could give
like a real barn burner of a speech.
They made, the Six Flags Live people made Wayne LaPierre
the villain that he is today.
Wow.
What a twist.
I never, doesn't it, but don't you feel it?
Don't you feel it?
I feel it feels bad, yeah.
It all makes sense in some weird way.
The New Yorker said,
the NRA and Ackerman McQueen have become so intertwined,
it is difficult to tell where one ends and the other begins.
Oh my god.
Remember that ghoul, Dana Loesch?
Yeah.
She was on their payroll, not the NRA's.
Wow.
Oh god.
That's how it works.
How long?
Because that's the spokeswoman.
Who oversaw the edits?
Do we know?
For the Six Flags Live?
Well, look, what we know is that,
I mean, that's 2001,
and their NRA dealings were 90s up through 2019.
So, absolutely, there were people
who would earlier in the day take a call from the NRA
and then go and work on the edit
and try to get more midriff into the Six Flags Live cut.
Oh my god.
100%.
These people.
Here's, let me get it, let me go a little bit deeper,
and the rollercoaster guy I showed you, McQueen,
in 2019, a tape was discovered by NPR
that was all of the main brain trust of the NRA
the day after Columbine,
discussing what are we gonna do now?
And it wasn't quite the horrible NRA that we know today
that only doubles down after there's a horrible tragedy.
This was a group that was truly shaken by it
as human beings would be.
Sure.
In that call is LaPierre and this guy,
and he specifically was,
he's on tape talking about how
we have to show our best face here
because if we get some of the nuttier people
in our organization, some of those hillbillies,
some of those idiots going down to the school,
then that's gonna look horrible for us.
He's on tape knowing that the worst people in the NRA
are nuts.
Right.
Just like a weird slice of time
and of a certain time for the organization,
but what I just love is the possibility
that this guy, he's on a call going like,
if Clinton comes after us, this is gonna be,
if he makes a scapegoat out of us,
then we could be in trouble forever.
Anyway, I gotta go because we're deciding
between Corey and David and I'm not sure,
David's got energy and Corey's a little edgier,
but maybe edgy is what we want, so I don't know.
Maybe we'll hire them both, I'm not sure.
Anyway, gotta go, Wayne, see ya.
Charlton, see ya.
Anyway, one of them's gonna be on Six Flags Live,
one of them's gonna be the spokesman for Surge Soda.
And I don't wanna lose him, frankly.
No, no, no, we agree, we'll deal with it,
we'll write the speech for Charlton,
but we've got some catchphrases brewing,
but please go deal with the Corey situation.
Anyways, one more little bit to that,
is that this ACMAC and NRA who were previously intertwined
as the NRA has come into a lot of financial trouble,
they couldn't afford to pay this,
I think ACMAC soaked them for money for many, many,
where ardent NRA members were like,
you gotta drop this group, how much are we paying?
And they laundered Wayne Lumpier's money,
there's a whole thing, so it fell apart
in a mess of lawsuits.
And recently, in a lawsuit in 2020, in January 2020,
this is just like dry legal documents
you can go find online.
And here is a little snippet.
On January 24th, 2020, the NRA subpoenaed
non-party Six Flags Entertainment Corporation
to produce the following documents.
And then there's a list of eight,
and number eight is documents reflecting any concerns
about a request to Akram McQueen
for information on Six Flags Live,
including but not limited to documents
concerning Akram McQueen's response.
Number nine is documents and communications
prepared by Akram McQueen that relate
to the following projects, Six Flags Live.
This video that came to us as lost media,
be fun to see that again, was being sought by the NRA.
For what reason?
Why did they need to see it?
And is there anything that could have like,
was it something, were they maybe like,
okay, we think they're stealing a lot of money from us.
We never watched Six Flags Live.
If we put it on and find the most expensive,
multi-take endeavor we've ever seen,
then we'll know if we look at the host's shiny spiky hair
and we know that it's done with the topest quality
of 2001 hair spikery.
The researchers watched the pilot.
It appears they shot it for $300
and pocketed the other $20,000.
Maybe it was proof that these are money launderers.
Look, look at the shabby production.
Not one, there's nothing on the screen.
We have a lot of doubts of whether these girls
were actually paid in Mountain Dew bottles.
Yeah, what if they said Six Flags Live
cost us $100 million to make?
Yeah, maybe that's it, yes.
And they needed to like, your honor,
look at the results of this.
And there was some, the heat's on us, all right,
we gotta do, we need a bigger PR campaign
than we've ever had.
Sir, we don't have the money,
we just lost a bundle on Six Flags Live.
I mean, we're talking nine digits there.
Can we see it?
It's lost, we lost the media, it's lost media.
I would love to show it to you, but.
No way we can, yeah.
This was, I mean, we're talking height,
you know, like IMAX cameras and explosions,
I think, in every shot.
We blew up a lot of rides.
The hosts arrived into every frame in a helicopter.
We spared no expense for Six Flags Live.
Each quarry cost $30 million to pay
because they're so in demand.
Well, that cloning machine is expensive to run.
The cloning machine, yeah.
What's this quarry line item that's just a question mark?
It's like, well, we made a quarry,
put goggles on his forehead,
and just the weight of the goggles just melted him.
Psh.
But keep in mind, the quarries in the production
are just the quarries you see.
There were tons of quarries who died
due to their own stupidity,
who immediately were released out of the machine and drowned.
This more, do you know the prestige?
There's all the tanks under the, anyway,
so that's, we got a whole warehouse full of quarries
like that.
$200 million on green tattoo removal.
It's very expensive if you didn't know.
Green takes 20 times when you're doing
one of those laser treatments.
I would bet the green was the easiest to erase.
No, believe it or not.
No, it's art.
We actually, we had to give them the Tweety Bird
and the Tigger tattoos.
The artist accidentally used green,
so then we had to do 20 times taking the green off
to put the yellow and orange on.
That's ridiculous.
If somebody has a Tigger tattoo that they want to take off,
just use a gun and just blast it off
If you aim precisely, it'll blast that tattoo right off.
That's not a solution to every problem, Wayne.
We told you that.
Not with that attitude, it's not.
Anyway, what a, I could not believe that turn
in the Six Flags.
That's wild.
Live tale.
I just kinda zone out and I see ad agency names
and I really gotta look them up to go, like.
Well, yeah, I know, maybe if you have future clues,
I guess, coming.
And again, they switched to donor,
who I guess are just as evil as a regular ad company.
Oh, yeah.
Specifically, super villain evil.
Anyway, so boy, the more you know, the stuff you find out,
now you know everything about something
you never heard about until we started talking.
And with that, you survived Podcast The Ride,
the second gate.
Thanks for subscribing.
And if you wanna dig even deeper,
if you wanna go even dirtier,
if you wanna be a real dirty dog,
come on down to Club Three.
We don't, none of this fucking talk.
As Club Three subscribers know,
it's mostly yelling and woos.
We mostly just say ass and then the rest of us woo.
So if you don't want any of that intellectual horse crap.
Yeah, there's drawings of both before
and after Fiona on Club Three.
If you wanna find out where Jason has a tattoo
of Yosemite Sam on his body, go to Club Three.
Spoiler alert, it's under my belly button
and then he's shooting my dick with his guns
and he's saying dance, partner.
I'm gonna make Scrapple out of that thing.