FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast technically
has a topic but don't hold us
to it. Beware of jump scares
from horny lions,
grouchy OC conservatives,
and a certain very
loud bar rescuer.
The hilarious James Adomian joins
us to talk about a bunch of bullshit
some of which is So Cal
Waterparks on Podcast
The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast
The Ride, a podcast hosted
by 40 year olds who will likely
drown on the watch of untrained
15 year olds. I'm Scott
Gardner, there's Mike Carlson. It's gonna happen
and it's gonna be even more embarrassing
than you could imagine it being. Like
something like I'll lose my pants first
or something and then I'll be like upside down.
Like it's gonna be a cartoon
death with an apathetic
15 year old watching on.
Well and we're hopefully, we're probably
if like a more knowledgeable
lifeguard could have solved the situation
in 20 seconds but in the
7 minutes it takes for him to get his
shit together. Yeah.
But I don't blame him, he's 15, what is he supposed to do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They should maybe change the hiring policies
in general but that's something we can
discuss and get into. That's a whole political issue
we have to get into later, yeah. Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi, yeah, if it's not apathetic
and comical enough, I'm
gonna haunt the waterpark.
That's cool. It's gonna be a haunted waterpark.
It's a good place to haunt because
they're inherently creepy, they're
creepy when they're not running and they're really creepy
when they're abandoned as some are,
as happens. Yeah.
Some of the things we'll be talking about today.
But when he says haunt, he's gonna haunt the lazy river
and he's just gonna sit in the like ghost
inner tube and like float down and go hey,
hey, hey, hey.
Like he doesn't want to actually do full on haunting.
What are you making, you making taquitos?
Yeah, you don't have the energy to haunt.
Is that a new flavor? Yeah, haunting's an aggressive
act, it's a lot of calorie burn.
You gotta stay on top of someone and you have to like
learn about them and like define their fears.
You're suggesting that haunting is
tired? I think it is.
Yeah, I think so. I don't know.
I think there's an aggressive version and there's a
lazy, if you're just passively around as a
ghost, yeah, that's not the same.
Certainly effort is involved.
The unpaid
emotional labor.
Who's paying me to be a ghost? Who's paying me
to haunt? If I'm not being paid, why should I
put in the effort? If there's dark energy,
it's coming from somewhere.
So if energy is expelled,
it's coming from somewhere. So there has to be some effort
and it has to eventually become depleted.
That's what I believe. That's something I believe for
years. Not just something I thought of
now.
That all of your other less known
podcasts get into for a long time.
We'll get
thoughts about parks,
haunting, dark energy and where it comes from
from our guest. We're really excited he's joining
us today. A podcast luminary,
a prolific actor, stand-up and impressionist.
He's got a new special out called
The Path of Most Resistance. Very excited.
James Adomian, welcome to the show.
Hey, thanks for having me, Scott. Absolutely.
This is a
provocative question.
The haunting...
The specific
mechanics of haunting and all that.
You said something about
unpaid labor which makes me wonder
about the people who are hungry
for the haunting work and they're down by the docks
waiting to be picked.
It's like, I only need two ghosts today.
Yeah, yeah.
You got room in the truck.
You're not scary enough, you're not
big enough.
Scary, existentially scary
or large
inhabitants of
an energy field. I'm a weird
little kid. That doesn't
work.
You can be little, but
there's got to be something imposing.
If you're little, then you have to go overboard
in terms of psychically squeaking.
I just don't know if you're neither here nor there.
You're always hiring the ring girl over there
with the long hair.
She's my same age. What do you do?
Yeah, but you're so cute, Pip Squeak.
You're just the cute one.
She has a way of turning the
cute expectations into
a very unfulfilling sadness.
Come back when you can do that.
Pure scary-wise, I've got it.
I didn't realize there were all these other emotions
I needed to evoke.
That's like a Casper
situation. It's too cute.
Casper is too cute.
Listen, kid, you died young. That's too bad.
But I can't do anything scary
with that.
The ghost
foreman.
He's the agent for the good.
I'm trying to find your work. I really
am, but it's tough out there.
It's tragic, but it's not convenient.
It's okay.
Look, 4,000
little kid ghosts like you every day
come and wash up under the
metaphysical side of the city.
But I died a little bit younger than
them. I was talking to a five-year-old
in the lobby. I was four and a half.
That's sadder. It's my sixth-old-months of sadder.
Well, this is a great
field to explore.
This is employment for after all of our
jobs.
We're also
busy thinking about how we're going to make
money now that we don't think about what
we're going to do after we die.
We're too focused on
not working now.
Not working now, we don't think about not working
after we're dead.
In the afterlife, we'll all become grindsets,
like guys who are all about
grinding.
But unfortunately,
that's usually
attached to some kind of mill
that you're grinding
in a circle.
It becomes literal grinding.
Grinding
ectoplasm.
Grinding bones into
the raw powder that the elements of
hell and the wings of hell are made of.
There's always someone who's like
the one who likes everyone
sad except for the guy who's like
yes, power!
And no one else is having a good time
except for him.
So how do you rise to become hell
foreman? How did he get that?
You definitely don't get to do live shows that way
where everyone's in misery but you're like
good!
It just doesn't work.
It'd be more fun
I think. Power dynamics
on display.
James, thanks for joining us.
You threw out a bunch of stuff
we could talk about. We have this water
parks notion but this is a loose
assignment. We can talk about
zillion things in the
general realm of theme parks or otherwise
and I say otherwise because I have a theory
permission to speak informally about the theme
park. Yes.
You did not have to write a report to get
on the show. This can be loose.
Fuck.
You can show it to us later.
Well, we appreciate it.
We recognize the effort.
I have a theory about
some of what brought you here
today and I could be wrong
but this is what I think.
Brett Boehm who runs the show at
Forever Dog here messaged us about
having you on and I think that
I believe it was on the
very day that you had
been on the best show
and you had done a big
chunk of stuff about
Jon Taffer.
And that is what I believe. I believe
that Brett set us up on some kind of
podcast blind date on
the basis of Jon Taffer because
we're Taffer obsessives.
This is something we talk about a lot
and you boast an incredible
Taffer which I don't mean to
put you on the spot about.
My life's work.
But I was just thrilled to hear
you're a fan of the big guy.
If he came in here, what you've got
plastic on the ground.
Podcast.
Close it.
This should be ballet only.
Our customers don't care about
they don't need they don't need a bunch of frills.
Black Walls is what people like
all right. Charlie Rose.
He is has the wrong advice for
all occasions. Yeah. Yeah.
It's so like
in practice does not
really work. Seemingly as
you said with Tom like his work is
overturned as soon as he is out of town.
As everyone undoes
what he does. It's not
the usual Ozymandias
grind of the hereafter.
Yeah. Yes.
It's very with him. It's just like no he's gone
flip it back over to. Yeah.
I think he's they're all waiting outside. They're all
waving. Bye. Thank you.
And as soon as the car says the production
vans go over the horizon line. Okay.
Turn the sign back because there's always a place
it's called there's a place that'll be called like
you know the
the exit door.
And he comes in and we're going to click
here's your new bar. And then he
unveils it and it's like Mikonos.
This has nothing to do.
We cleared out all the regulars.
Now it's this.
And he's like all those people who came all
the time you don't got to worry about
them anymore. You're going to get college
kids in here now.
And he's like we and it's like we used to serve grilled
cheese in here and he's like but you're serving escargot
now. This is a whole new
menu. And then like that saddles them with more money
like problems.
He basically turns every bar into
like what people don't like about Santa
Monica.
It's brightly lit unwelcoming
TVs
everywhere.
Oh nobody.
Nobody goes to those places. Right.
And then we we bulldoze them
and turn them into bigger dumber places.
We're flipping.
Don't you realize. Bar
flipping.
He always wants to light the liquor bottles from underneath
too. That's very important. Oh is that a
common. That's one thing at least in the first so many
seasons he always wants a light under
the liquor bottles behind the bar.
Every bar has to have lit.
To remind you that they because otherwise people
might not know. Right. That we have
liquor bottles here. If they're
in the shadows.
There's a sports bar in Burbank.
I used to drive by
going to an old job.
Champs. Champs.
Yeah he played in Champs. Champs which I think
was the name before and maybe
after or like
whatever. I forget if they ever changed the name.
Champs.
We're going for a French
vibe now at Champs.
But I would drive by it like
every day and so for
a while the outside
they would just it would be painted white
then it'd be painted black
then it'd be painted wood grain
like I'm like what is going on over
there. And I found out it was
because it was on Bar Rescue.
Oh that was concurrent to when this was happening.
It was their original and then there
was a intermediary
phase and then his version and
the undoing. And then
uh oh that did we
he permanently stained the wood
so we have to go back to a completely
different color. I also
don't like it there was residential
areas all around
like I'm like wait what's
hard. Like just
just have a bunch of TVs. You're a
sports bar. Just sell wings
and mozzarella sticks you know.
And don't over pour
and don't disrespect women.
Those are the other things he yells about.
That's only for me to do.
Right.
One of the things he'll do is that he will
send his wife into a place and be like
and then they'll be like let's see
let's go in there and let's see if he hits on you.
And then he does
and then he comes in and goes like
you hit on my wife. It's like
he didn't know that first of all
that she was your wife and
you guys planned it on camera.
I watched it. I'm watching the show.
You're watching the issuing
of the assignment. You order it. She's like
sure no problem. Go tart
it up. Pull the shirt
down a little bit. Show off what you got.
They did what? They hit on you.
Yeah it's a source of a lot of
joy to us. It's an episode that we've long
threatened to do that our pal Griffin
Newman forces
to do on the main. Oh I mean that we
would love. Yes. That we would love
and a certain percentage of our audience would be
so mad about. But I
think worth it. Scott let me ask you something.
You're going to look around when he has the eye contact
of a pedantic
school principal. You're going
to look around the studio and say that
things are going well.
I think so. Yeah you know people subscribe.
Garbage on the floor.
They don't see that. It's an audio medium.
And that's your excuse that it's
audio only. I think most of
the time it sounds pretty good. Most
of the time there's not some weird ambient
hum through the entire episode. If I locked you in here overnight
would you be scared?
There's no windows.
We're locking you in here overnight.
We're going to see if you're scared.
And I'm going to be locked in here with you.
And we're going to see if you're scared.
I'm scared now.
Are you going to stare at me in that manner
all night? What do you think I'm going to do?
Eight to ten
hours of this.
You're so much taller than me too. This is what's
going to turn this place into a bar
that people are going to like.
You're spiddling all over
the microphones. These are going to be inoperable
if you. It would be worth
it for like a five minute episode I think.
If he just yelled at us and left.
We can do a mini episode. Although you know what I forgot.
He's not going to go for that. He's going to want to take over
and change your podcast.
If we allow him to. I would allow him to do it.
If we describe the full breadth of what's been going
on and like we show him our. We open the books
as the show says.
That's your amount of growth.
It's because you're a niche podcast.
You're only talking about theme parks. You should be
talking about sports in America.
Your GoFundMe is more like a GoFuckMe.
The one
in we have I still believe
is that he posted this last year
him on Tron
Lightcycle Run at Disney World with
his wife. And he like praised
it up and down. So maybe
under like the. You just hit Tron
my wife.
The master control program
hit on you.
I think there's multiple in's because
actually you know what I didn't realize. Did you guys know
did anyone know that the reason the Paramount connection
came about is that he
knew he had contacts over there because
he was a consultant at
some point in the early run of Bubba
Gump. Is that right? Yes.
Yeah. Whoa. We got a lot to talk
to him about. We really do. We've talked about Bubba Gump many
times. It's on universal property
so it counts. Yeah. Yeah.
That's that's in our top purview.
You know the jurisdictional line
like that comes
into play sometimes where there's like I'm the
sheriff of universal city.
I got jurisdiction
from the minion statue all the way down
to the border of forever.
Bubba Gump shrimp
falls within the purview of this
county. If you can see
the minion. If the minion is in your
line of sight then he's still in charge.
That would be
the ancient common law
definition. Be ye
under the eye of the minion.
He does have
the minion does have kind of a like
Brazil Christ statue
type like. Yeah. Like I wonder
if any like maybe I don't know if any parents
in this area were parents in this area.
We could use that minion as kind
of a if you act out that minion
could come down here. God up there.
This reminds me of the crucified minion
that was our
AI manufactured the meme
and then manufactured the outrage about it
afterwards. I miss this
entirely. Don't navigate away.
Don't don't go away.
The videos of just people saying the
same script. Yeah it was the same
it was the outrage script that the
same people the people were going like
you know it's can you believe it. Can
you believe it. Can you believe it
that they've gone this far that AI has gone this far
that AI has gone this far
and it was just an image
AI had created this image of
a crucified minion. OK
with the crown of thorns
and then entirely. OK. Well this was
over the summer. Interesting.
And what who's so what's
the the what's the end game here.
How do you benefit from no one
benefits from it. It's just a cycle
of it's chasing itself. Yeah.
And although I
do like to imagine the extension of
the world where there is a minion
Christ and
you have like you have somebody
like Johnny Cash singing like really
respectful
gospel like
were
were you there
when they
crucified my
lord.
Sometimes
it causes me
to minion
minion
I think that's like
one culture is like flattened and AI
is taken over. That is what like
people will. There'll be an AI Johnny Cash
song like that. That's easily going to
like you can do that now. Really you can make it
now. I also think a lot of maybe AI is
doing a lot of crucifixion of
our favorite characters. Really quickly I
found a crucified Shrek who's
also buff too.
We have two premises here. This is very
hat on a hat. Right. Buff Shrek
crucified for being buff
because that's not what he was on
the. He was
on the hill of Golgotha
and he was next to the minion
when he was crucified.
Was he repentant or was he
the mean one?
I think
I think Shrek was repentant
which is why he had returned to his
monster form.
Which Pontius
Pilate could not tolerate.
Still a monster.
Crucify him. He was
next to the lord of the
minions who looked
up to heaven and referred to Shrek
next to him and said
Translation I'll see you up there my friend
I guess. And then next to them was
just Barabbas going like what the
fuck is going on. Barabbas
was freed by the crowd.
Sorry man. It's getting weird.
It was my favorite.
The only thing that I looked forward to
about church every year was that every year
on Good Friday there would be
a little play and you in
the audience of church
what do you call the audience of church?
Yes everybody had the part to do
the congregation. Yeah yeah. Like I have
a line in this. I get to be
like there's a whole crowd line
and then hearing all of these children
parents my age and then old
people all kind of really hushed
going Barabbas.
Who do you want me to free? Barabbas.
Barabbas.
Nobody would ever put any
stank on it. It's
the only positive memory I have
from years of church. And
that's the betrayal of Christ in my mind.
I think that there's no greater
part. There are some kinds of parts
that are designed for a
great actor. And in the
passion of Christ
I've said this before. Any idiot can play
Jesus Christ. Any blue eyed
fuck.
It's kind of all about looks. You don't have a good
you have someone who's like blessed are the poor
in spirit. No one's listening. Everyone's
watching and thinking of something else while they're watching the
scene. Easy one note. Where you put the good
actor is the role of Pontius
Pilate. Yeah. That's where the actor
because you're introduced to him
as the most powerful
man in Palestine.
And he's like he's sitting there
in a palace with attendants
and he's like who is this?
He doesn't want to do it.
Who is this Jesus
of Nazareth?
And then he interrogates him in person
where he's like are you
the son of God?
Looking around at the people
and he ends up killing, he ends up sending him to be executed
and then the best, there's nothing
you, I mean the
washing of the hands afterwards.
Oh yeah. There's all process. I washed my hands
of this. I didn't want any of it.
That is that.
You saw in the pre-interview
this was not really my vibe.
That's where you put the actor and you
only give him one note.
Which is chew as
much marble scenery as your teeth
can handle.
Bigger. Bigger.
Bigger. Bigger. Yeah.
Make me pull you back.
Yeah. Pontius Pilate
in Jesus Christ Superstar is very
campy. Oh yeah. Wait.
Is that depiction? How do they,
does he get a song?
Is he the one who gets a song
and that's all he does
in the show is the one song
he's in and out but he steals the show.
It feels like Adam
West should have played that role.
Shatner.
Like someone really hammy from
the old days.
You say the son of God. I guess I did walk you
into a Shatner doing this.
What would it be like? Sorry.
Miracles you say.
And from his point of view
it's like when he's talking to the robot
trying to trip it up with logic.
We just watched
the pilot of T.J. Hooker so I guess I have Shatner
on the brain. Okay. So you're almost, yeah.
You're thinking more T.J. Hooker. I'm thinking more
Hooker. How would T.J. Hooker be a different pilot than Kirk?
Right. Exactly. And it's so
different. It would be so different.
It's more grounded. Yeah.
Barabbas was the one who was
parted. Gestas
and dismas were the names
of the people to the right and left
of Jesus. Gestmas and dismas?
I never would have guessed that. And as
you're saying that about like Easter
Good Friday services
I am remembering that
in that little pageant
I was the
mean one crucified next
to Jesus. Really? You were the bad
one? I was the one like kissing
at the audience. Shut up Jesus. Hissing at the
congregation. Wait does it remind me how it works?
There's one who's nice, who they bond
but the other one is like
the one who's mean. I was the mean one.
So you would hiss at the congregation like you were a
wrestling bad, like a wrestling bad guy.
A branches
cross, branches from like
the woods behind the church that
one of the deacons or
something. Were they heavy? No.
But was it tough to hold your hands up in that?
It was awkward. My hands were tied
to wood. How old were you? Probably like
11 or 12. Is there video?
I don't know if there is video
of the, I think that
I would pay $500 for that
video. I would love it. Do you
have any idea what you said? Do you remember any of it?
I don't think I said anything. I think I was just doing
a lot of like grrr. You said you were hissing though
at the crowd. Like at the crowd like
railing at, cause it was mean
and then the one who were pence
like has the
lines. Think about how scary could
11 year old you have been.
To be the most hard boiled
criminal in the world. Yeah.
Wow. Well you gotta
look into that if there is a video. Yeah.
Please. Tell me, do you know how to
spell that name cause maybe I could find some dialogue
while we. Oh
it's either G-E-S-T-A-S
or D-I-S
M-A-S.
Okay yeah it filled me in.
Justus Impentanent
Thief. Yeah.
I was the Impentanent Thief.
Justus. Justus.
What? Okay. I want to imagine he's a
Jester and he has like a big Jester hat
on. Wow he's being crucified.
Now we're
talking. Uh huh. Yeah.
I was at Lollapalooza and I
kept stealing
and I was being crucified.
I never took my Jester hat off.
Your cat in the hat. My big dog
hat. From the 90's.
Hat in that hat.
Lollapalooza hat.
Yeah.
Well you know
we're not here to talk about
actually you know what I meant to say
in the Taffer run. I'm going to put this on the
table. You certainly don't need to take it
but I just thought ahead with
the Jon Taffer discussion and
I just want to show you how
what generous hosts we are. If
during this podcast at any
point you would like a sip of Jon
Taffer's personal
bourbon brand.
This was
We're recording this very early also.
You thought of this ahead of time?
Yes yeah yeah. If you want a little
what is it 1108 AM sip
of Jon Taffer's
browned butter bourbon. I haven't eaten
enough.
Would you want to smell it maybe?
Okay
can I look at this? Yes of course.
At least observe it. Is this like the
hot sauce podcast?
It can be.
There's a lot of things to hate about
this. Oh yeah.
Taffer's browned butter bourbon.
They have the font
of a newspaper from the Civil War
like you're supposed to with a whiskey.
But it's supposed to
be called like
broken wheel.
Something rustic.
It's either something
like a piece of old
machinery that doesn't work
or a sad animal or
a veiled
barren calf whiskey.
Right yeah.
Like disrupted crow.
Or there's some veiled
very veiled reference to the Confederate States
of America.
If you know if you're from
there you know what they are. It'll be like Arkansas
whistle.
But this is
he has this font but it's just his dumb name
Taffer's. Yeah.
This is new. It's not an old thing.
It looks like the old. He's like get me
the font of the old letters.
Browned butter
bourbon. Bourbon is already too
sugary for me.
Even just regular bourbon straight. If I'm going to
drink whiskey I want it to be a
rye whiskey or a Japanese whiskey.
You would hate this so much.
He's like make it more sugary.
Southern comfort is too bitter
for our purposes.
You should at least pop that top and smell
it if you can't because the smell
is like you can't. I don't think there is a hint
of whiskey in this whiskey.
Jesus Christ. Yeah right. Yeah.
Get me a bottle. Get me a
bottle of rejected Jack
Daniels. Then get a
honey bear.
Get a honey bear and upend him.
I want that honey.
The entire bottle of honey bear honey.
Glug glug glug glug
glug glug glug glug.
Milk him.
Melt a bag of
Werther's.
Crafted by John Taffer.
And then he has this thing where he signed
it. Oh yes it's exclusive.
It's not a wet signature though I'll note.
It's printed.
There's this shit that you
see with Makers Mark where there's like
paint drops and shit on the
bottle. Oh but it looks
like it's printed according to the same pattern
each time.
With notes of vanilla and toffee.
Bad.
Those are not things I know.
First of all if you're at the cheesecake
factory.
That's the dessert that you
shouldn't get at the cheesecake factory.
Vanilla and toffee.
What? No. Having
tasted this their definition of hints
is a giant smack in
the face because there is no
there's not a hint of whiskey. There's
not you know you'd be hard pressed
to like oh maybe now all right now on the fifth
sip maybe I detect a little bit of whiskey.
And he has the audacity to have a frying
pan on the back label.
That's what that is.
Which is ironic because at Taffer's
Tavern locations everything
is like sous vide or convection
oven made.
He has a restaurant chain that's like pseudo
failing by the way if you didn't know that.
Which one is it? It's called Taffer's Tavern.
One just closed in Massachusetts.
The one in Boston area.
Yes. Six months ago.
Every time one opens in a new city
you can tell the food critic in that
city is just gleeful.
To give it just an awful
review.
I thought I was washed up here.
Thought I was washed up up here.
Chattanooga Tennessee.
The Taffer's Tavern locations
have a big picture like a painting of him.
Like a showcase.
That's disgusting.
But there's only two locations right now.
You're supposed to trust this guy.
This is some sort of like money scam though.
I think there's many things that have been
additional coming soon that have been there for three years.
To Orlando. It will be
the Orlando location is going to be ten minutes
away from Epic Universe.
We will do a live show at Taffer's Tavern next time.
If there's a room to do it.
If they let you.
Live barcades in the bar?
This really should be a sketch.
I wouldn't judge it for anything. So here it goes.
You have Gordon Ramsay and
Jon Taffer.
Like Spy vs Spy.
Trying to remake each other's bars.
Hell's Kitchen and Taffer's Tavern.
It's disgusting.
There's raw pork everywhere.
We don't have pork on the menu!
Exactly.
Is it an attempt?
Are they undermining or are they fixing?
Is the fixing itself undermining?
I think the idea is they're trying to humiliate
each other in both the fixing
and the tearing down.
This would be so
fun to do. It feels like there are a few comedy
places left to do it. They're all gone.
I just found out because I've been finding
all these old clips of mine
to post
in preparation for the special coming
out. Comedy Central has been
gutted. There's nothing on YouTube. There's
entire TV appearances of mine that just don't
exist anymore.
Adult Swim's
kind of gone. All the money
right now is
draining.
Emptying buckets of content.
Yes. The same thing that happened
to the hardworking
industrial
manufacturing industries
in the 70s, 80s,
and 90s where they would
shut down a steel company
and then chop it up for assets and so forth.
That's happening to every other
industry because there are people
who go to school who should be
pulled out of school and put in jail.
There's entire business departments
and colleges where they teach people
the only way to make money is through cannibalism.
You've got to find
an industry and chop it up for parts.
We send people to go to study
that. Where you're supposed to study
Aristotle's
Nicomachean Ethics.
Instead, you're coming back
going like, no, no, dude, no, seriously,
no. My buddies
are like family and we're like a pack
of investors and we look for things
to fuck up.
Yeah, it's just not a good time right now. It's just weird
time, you know, so we gotta close our shot.
We crunch numbers and
we're shutting it down. Crunching numbers, crunching
companies, we fucking do it.
We slam it, dawg.
I went to crunch school.
Yeah, no, I know it's a bummer.
Now, what do we here, what do we in the lowly
pie, are we saved in the podcast
world ultimately by that
you, Mike, have all of the files
somewhere?
Probably. Unless you crunch
us. You bring this up.
There's some money in it for you
later to not distribute the
files to me and Jason. I took an online
Bain Capital course in my spare
time and I'm just biding my time
before I impact
vulture capitalism on this podcast.
I like that
you're a smart
pod operation because you immediately go
like, oh my god, it could come from me.
I was
looking at the three of you start to
hold your necks and go, wait a minute, this
guillotine thing
could come after me. I'm the bad, I'm the
what was the name of the impenitent thief?
I'm the
guestus.
Although wait, does impenitent
mean, wait, no.
Oh, penitent means
good and impenitent is the bad one.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to saddle the podcast with a lot of
debt. That's what I'm going to do and then we're
going to go into bankruptcy. I'm going to pocket all the
money from the bankruptcy
and then you'll find out it's like all the
money that you still owe is in you and Jason's
name or something. There'll be some scam like
that that I'll pull. You're taking community college
business classes like Idris Elba
and The Wire so you can
figure out how to run the operation,
you know. Yeah, search
will ruin you two actually, really.
I should have known. I should have known it was you.
Well, now we know. Watch
out. Anything you say here,
he's going to profit
off of. It's actually liberating to be speaking
on a podcast in progress knowing
that it's going to be wiped out from Link
Rot and the podcast is
going to be chopped up for parts.
It's kind of freeing. If you don't put any expectation
on like, this is going to be the number one
part of my podcast reel.
Yeah, no,
it's all going to be destroyed. This episode
will never air because I'm going to write it off
like how Batgirl got wrote off at Warner
Brothers. I'll just
send it to the government and say like, this is a loss
that's unreleasable. This single
episode cost 90 million dollars.
We need to collect 90 million dollars
for this and then I'll send a video
in of me deleting the file. I'm going to send it to the Warner Brothers
write off
film department. We have like actually
big, big dollars for development.
Now, we're going to crush these projects
when they come out. Right.
But we have a lot of money
to develop and then kill your project.
It's just, that's what we do.
That's what we do.
Warner Brothers killed the long tradition
of this at Warner Brothers. But it feels fun
to go make a movie, right? To say action,
put on a hat, that's what a director
would wear. To sit in a special
chair. You get to do all of that
and make money. We've been overrating
the step of it where people get to see what you did.
I think
people have not
realized this, I think, in totality.
When you start to get
50 or 75
years outside of
the current times or even like
recent decades, the copyrights
will be gone.
And some of their in perpetuity clauses
will be unenforceable.
And, you know,
barren wasteland, notwithstanding,
you'll have a lot of unproduced pilots
that will finally be readable.
Or at least watchable.
As long as you physically
grab them. Yes.
What I'm saying is
wait until the
large media companies are decaying
and then break in and
steal the hard drives and then
put them out on the internet
in a hundred years. Get close to the
brother of the guy. It was the key to all
the hard drives.
Yeah, yeah. That's what we've learned.
Seduce the guy.
Seduce the guy. Marry him.
USB 3,
USB C,
a lot faster than
Firewire 400.
Oh, so copying the files will be quicker.
You'll be able to get more.
The tough thing will be finding
the connecting cable.
That's really the biggest
technological roadblock.
It's got to be a cheapie
USB cable.
It can't be a nice one because then it won't
work.
So we just need to,
like Mad Max style,
you've got to just wear everything you need
on your person, kind of weird post-apocalyptic
clothes, and just have
all kinds of cables as your clothing.
And then it's on you. Exactly.
A dozen USB C cables.
This came from headphones,
this came from a hard drive.
He scarred himself as a
bundle of cables.
How did he get into the building?
He snuck around
and then when somebody was coming he just dropped
nobody here but a pile of cables.
Yeah, it's like a Metal Gear
solid stealth mission.
Objective complete. You have
acquired Coyote versus Acme.
And then you watch it and you're like,
oh my god, it was bad.
Actually Zaz made the right call.
He was right about this one.
He knew something we didn't because he saw it.
That's what John Cena said.
John Cena was like, well if they didn't release it
there must be a reason.
Did he really?
He's a company man.
Whatever the company says, whatever China says.
If they're a company
he's listening to.
You're once again
inspecting taffers.
I feel like you're getting tempted maybe.
I'm not going to drink this. I just noticed on the top of the
cap that it says the number is
003 and I'm like, I don't believe it.
I don't believe that you have special numbers for these.
I don't think so.
It is pretty
exclusive though because they only sell it in three
states. I had to bring this back from
Vegas where I should also
say I left it in the car
and I think the bottle maybe
3%
exploded.
Not fully exploded.
I have consumed actually a surprising
amount of this, like 60% of it I would say.
And again I'm not after
a milkshake basically.
There's no laws in Nevada you realize.
That's a good point.
Nevada is an
experiment like what if there was
no laws?
That's where Taffer lives.
That's his home state.
I guess you shouldn't drink anything while you're there
just in case it's not regulated properly.
Anyway it's still there.
If you ever want to grab it. And another thing that's on the
table but you also don't have to grab this is
talking about theme parks to any
percentage but it doesn't matter at all.
You did mention some things
that we could talk about but
we don't have to. I realized
it's been a sham.
A terrible facade.
Well for theme parks, deal in facades
you see. Sometimes you go back there and there's
nothing back there. So I don't know if you guys are
from what parts of the country you're from.
I'm from SoCal.
Mike over there is Chicago.
Schaumburg, Illinois.
And Jason's from
Philly, Jersey. Philadelphia,
South Jersey.
So I don't know a lot of theme
parks outside of Southern
California except
because I never really went, when I was in New York
I never went anywhere. Sure. There's not a lot there.
And I didn't even go, because there's
Six Flags everywhere but I just didn't go to them.
Sometimes if I have an extra day
in some city and I see a flyer, I'm like
maybe I will go to Six Flags
on Sunday.
It never happens.
You're going to be...
You need someone locally in town who is like
I'm an adult who wants to waste time.
Yeah, yeah. Doing it solo
ain't great. And what I've found
here and there is that
from my little bit of Six Flags
experience, you're paying for a place that's
worse inside.
You will pay a premium to go to a worse
place. It's an inverse country club.
There will be more weird stains.
The food will attract more flies.
You're making the
right move not going, I think. The food at Disneyland
is garbage.
For the most, I think, some of this has
changed here and there. There's
exceptions to this a little bit.
The big turkey legs?
They taste like, you know
how vegetation
becomes calcified and it turns into stone?
It feels like they dipped it in salt so long
that it's just salt.
They do kind of taste like
ham.
Are you sure this isn't a straightened out ham leg?
No.
The answer is no. I'm not sure.
There's no way to know what that... And it's weird in pink.
There's a bunch of theme parks
I like. We were going to talk about one thing, but
I went to...
This is one of my favorite little memories.
I'm just realizing
Trevor Moore, my friend, my late
friend Trevor Moore of The Whiteest Kids You
Know. We had a lot of fun time. We went to
Disneyland for some reason.
Just the two of us.
He was like, you mean you went to Disneyland?
We went to Disneyland.
We spent the day at Disneyland and we were two
adults, like 30 year old adults.
Smartasses. We were not even
Drunk or Stoned, but we were having the blast.
We were laughing the whole time about everything.
And one thing we remembered was
if either of us had gone alone
then you're weird.
Then you're like the weird creep stranger guy.
Now what I could do
is say, oh yeah, for sure.
Or I could call two, the three of us have done this
many times. It happens all the time.
Well, what we did, we were like
this should be a thing for weird strangers.
Is that they get to have a stranger
who's a buddy. Oh, there's some kind of
a society of strangers.
And we wanted to have
a society of strangers where you could
be paired up with another stranger.
And you have your
long coats. You both have long
coats and weird gates.
But you should have each other.
And somebody's analyzing
the walk patterns to see
these two
kinds of shiftiness.
If strangers come in pairs, it's okay.
Well, you do a single rider
sometimes and you do get paired accidentally
with other single strangers.
Oh, sure you do because they didn't think about it.
Where they were like, well there's three
people on this ride. Right.
Yeah. So then you end up having
sometimes a special little experience.
Somebody you never see again.
You end up with a stranger or you end up with
an entire family. It's like you and five
people from a family. Yes. You join the family.
That's right. I've been on that
where you get into something and there's some
guy who's like, the lap
belt comes down and he's like, oh boy.
I have a little bit
too much meat. And you're in the photo
of that family. Too much of that pork leg.
That family did the cars
ride and now you're in the family photo
forever with them. Right.
There's five of them and it's like maybe that's their one
Disneyland trip of their life and you're sitting
on their mantle forever.
Forever they're going to go, who's that guy?
That's true. We've all been that
guy. Yeah, we might be on a lot of mantles.
We're trapped in a number of family
photos. We are trapped.
We're going to be haunting those photos
when we pass. Very often
what's the kind of thing that's like
a round life
raft that you can kind of steer through the rapids?
Oh, the rapids. That's where you
most end up in a group of strangers. Because there's like
there'll be like
two brothers and a cousin
and then like a
young couple from France
who's like a young
sex fucking, that's
how I describe people. They're a
sex fucking couple. Yeah, and you all get
very drenched. And they're trying to dunk each other
but you outnumber them so you
the French couple is French.
You shift the weight. You shift the weight.
And everyone laughs together.
Everyone laughs and
one person is grumpy. Dad is grumpy
because he didn't want to get too wet and he's
soaked. And then not everybody gets
equally wet on those two so you're kind
of all like hoping the couple gets
it because like depending on how it turns
and the angle when you hit the waterfall
so there's a whole element of like
Russian roulette or something. You're all waiting to see
who's
getting the splash.
The random splash. Russian roulette.
That would be great if some gangsters
take over the theme park.
And they're like, if you survive
dry, you will live.
I will let you go.
It shows you were cunning enough too.
He gets, John Wick has
to go over the rapids
life.
You know something about Disneyland, I
realized, Disneyland
you don't realize
you guys realize it, but you don't realize
it if you're a normal person.
How much of it is just water?
Lots and lots of shit at Disneyland
is water, water, water, water, water.
Or there's like, hey, go look at
you know, go look at
Snow White feeding Bambi
and then
splashing the water at the end.
I noticed
like one of the last times I went to Disneyland
when it's late in the day.
When it's late in the day at like 7pm
you can look around
in line anywhere
and there are
over-excited kids
all over and then like
soaked grandmothers.
Grandmothers who've been soaked
several times.
And grandmoms don't get soaked
because they're important.
So they
look like old cats.
They don't know how to get soaked.
And you see them all over
Disneyland in every line you look at.
Grandmom, and they're like, they're kind
of dazed like, uh-huh, uh-huh
slower, slower.
Chris, come back.
Sometimes the sun is going down
and they need to dry
off because they're going to get cold.
Right. A soaked grandmother
and she's, it's unpleasant, but
also she's like, this is, this is
my last time at Disneyland.
I did not live a big full life.
If there's a cold snap, they fall out of trees
like iguanas in Florida.
The old ladies at Pirates of the Caribbean?
It's okay, they're alive.
You just gotta get them
a cup of tea, a hot tea.
To revive them.
An older lady in her 60s or 70s
usually has like
nice jewelry and she's dressed
nice. And then to see
whose idea this was to make like, make sure
they all get wet before they leave.
And it's not clear to them
necessarily on a ride that that's going to happen.
Right, because it's in the fine print somewhere
where no one reads it. You're tired and whatever.
If you're not like us where you know everything
about every experience before you get on it.
I've been reading about this for years. I know everything.
You just get in a vehicle.
Well, if you get in a boat, that would be a clue.
It would be a clue. Keep your eyes peeled. If you're on
a boat, you might get wet. But it's not like us where
we can tell you exactly what seat to sit in if you
want to get wet or not sit in.
They're just like, the teen
loads grandma into the last row
and that's the wettest row.
She doesn't know what's coming.
If you're ever about to get on the Jurassic World ride
and you're wondering, like are they loading me?
Just shoot us a text. We'll try to guide you
out of, make sure you don't get
souped. That's the term we've used.
Every time I've been to Universal, the
Jurassic World ride is closed. I always
go when it's closed.
And I don't like it because
my experience of Universal is just a series
of screens where they're shaking the seats.
Well, that's a lot.
I had a proposition
if I was going to chop up Universal Studios
for parts like Bain Capital
or something. Cut out the middleman.
Don't even have people walk around
the park. You get to Universal
and you strap into some seat and the whole
experience is just a virtual
walking around going place.
Even the little pet thing where they go through
the doors, that little pet show.
Just do it on screens.
You can save hundreds of thousands
of dollars.
Just get lots of TVs, which is Taffer's advice.
Get lots of screens
in place and then just either
the chairs do the shaking or you just get
seasonal employees, 15-year-olds
to shake people around and it doesn't
matter what's on the TV. If there's
a screen in front of you and you're being
shaken, then Universal's doing its job.
I really hated
the Harry Potter ride because
I never watched the movies or cared about them.
And then it was
a lot of screens
and mist and shit. And they're
shaking the seat.
And I'm like, I don't care about any of this
lore. And it's just
a carsick machine.
That isn't a nerving...
I've watched people who could do better
coasters, like bigger, scarier coasters than me
really lose it on Harry Potter.
If you want to reverse it,
the cord, I'm sorry, I should have set it up better.
Or if you want to flip your mic stand
over so it's like, and you wrap it
around, I don't know. I'll just play with it.
I can't hear it, so it's fine.
You were just saying
the
inherent nausea of the
Harry Potter. Yes, okay, so
right, the harder rides,
those are cool. What is your speed?
If you are going to go to the...
What have you liked over the years?
The best ride is like, is it Colossus?
That style.
You mentioned wooden roller coasters.
Old school wooden roller coasters
that are psychological thrill rides
where it's based on not
how many times can we whip you around
in this limited footprint
in my opinion.
Like, we've invented a new way
to go backwards and upside down.
And residents
of Minnesota aren't allowed
to ride this, even though it's in California.
Your state government,
your attorney general has prevented
Minnesota citizens from riding on this ride.
They don't have what it takes.
But I love
an old fashioned wooden roller coaster
where it's like anticipation based.
Okay, oh this is interesting because
we talk a lot about, Mike likes launch
coasters where they shoot you out in a matter of
two seconds because there is none of the anticipation.
You prefer...
I have not done it actually.
I think it's that way.
That's a fast one though, yeah.
It's the one that zips you up.
It knots?
I think they were just
redoing that one, so I don't know what it is.
I've done hang time, I've done
we did Ghost Rider, that's old wooden coasters.
Ghost Rider is really in that.
Which park is that in?
It overlooks the parking lot.
They all do.
They didn't need so much parking.
They had no idea they would need it.
Now any
experience you're on, you're
in Scrooge McDuck's money bin ride or
whatever, guess what? You're going to be looking down
at a parking lot.
Breaks the fourth wall.
Knots is
unique in
that way of like, oh you can park
half a block away from the gate.
You can see the gate from
your parking spot.
Also, Knots, Knots
is, okay
Disneyland is
on brand.
Everything's clean, white gloves, and
you're supposed to do it a certain way, and there's
an underside, but it is an underside because
there's a message.
Six Flags is like, we don't clean up.
Six Flags is like, there's
gum in the carpets, it's like a W
hotel. And that's especially
Magic Mountain. Magic Mountain
and Six Flags here in LA, they're like,
it's a little bit less expensive
than Disneyland and it shows.
And Knots Berry Farm is like,
we don't have Mickey Mouse
or Bugs Bunny. We've got Snoopy.
Nobody cares
about Snoopy. So here's
the deal with Knots Berry
Farm. You will have,
there's cats, there's feral cats,
and we will not get rid of them.
There's just cats welcome at Knots Berry Farm.
Well, Disneyland has those too.
They help with
vermin. And they are
also vermin.
In some sense.
I don't know how, I've not seen a lot
in Disneyland, but they have a lot in
Knots Berry Farm that just come out at 6
p.m. Also,
Knots Berry Farm has a bunch of
shit that's not rides.
They have all this gold mining bullshit.
Old West,
where it's like, come
shine your boots
down in old tanks, boots shining
barn. And they have all this
old time California
fantasy nonsense.
It was only that when it opened. I know.
That's how it started. Rides were an afterthought.
You don't like the little
dioramas of the famous
missions of California.
It's interesting that it's
there at all. And then they have this propaganda
up on the walls, and I don't mean that
disparaging necessarily, but they
have, I'm used to like Disney propaganda
where you're like,
California adventure
reimagines
the early days of Walt Disney and
Los Feliz. And I get it.
It's your lore.
It's your propaganda. But at Knots Berry Farm
they're like,
this was a conservative theme park.
And young Republicans
used to come here in the 80s.
Wally George fans would get drunk
after a taping,
and come down to
Knots Berry Farm and get drunk on
poison berry.
Take their anger out on small depictions
of Snoopy and Sally. You can see it on the walls.
They're even just like, it was very popular
with conservative Republicans up until
the 90s. There was a Freedom Center
there. It was called the Freedom Center, am I correct?
Yeah, about free enterprise. You can't just say
there was a Freedom Center and not explain
what that means. I think it's very self-explanatory.
There was a Freedom Center, James?
Where do you imagine a Freedom Center would be?
You would learn from Walter Knots.
There was a video playing, or whatever,
talking about...
Here's my 13 points about American freedom.
Yeah.
It's not for everybody.
I don't think the Bill of Rights, one of those old California
farmer guys, here's my
libertarian ideas about
how things should be run in California.
Camp Snoopy kicked out
the John Burt Society club house.
Yes! You think?
That is so funny.
You think Snoopy is like a third-rate
theme park character? No, no, no, no.
Woodstock fucking
bounced the John Burt Society
and lost very far.
Revolution, yeah. And Wally George,
hey Snoopy, I think you suck.
Get off my show!
Hey, my
next guest here is a real loser.
He's a real dumb, dumb
Charlie Brown. Eww.
Watch this guy trying to kick a football. Watch.
Just watch him.
Oh yeah, you're a real...
Hey, shh. Hey, you're a real dumb head
in my opinion. Get out of here!
You do have
a, it's like, it's the only place
I can think of where you can, where there is a
depiction, a full replica
of the, of Independence
Hall right next to a water park.
These things are, and
on your way to both
a bunch of ducks and geese.
It's a strange little ecosystem
over there. None of it makes any sense.
Is that water park, cause James, you had
mentioned a number of Southern California water parks.
Well that was originally, we were going to talk about the
water parks in SoCal, I don't know.
Is that still going,
the water park by Knott's
is still there? Yeah.
Is it Knott's Soak City?
It is Knott's Soak City.
Well, there's a lot of
water runoff in the
process of making
boysenberry, so you gotta put it somewhere.
It's really a functional thing.
Yeah, the slides started as pipes
that was to route them elsewhere.
City of Lena Park doesn't allow you to jam raw
boysenberry down at the sewers, so we made a park.
We thought
it'd be better, make the sewers smell nicer, right?
Here's a little fun fact.
Boysenberry jam
and jelly is great. It's delicious.
Yes. And
of course, another Bain Capital thing,
Smucker's bought
Knott's Berry. Correct.
And they discontinued the boysenberry flavor.
Really? The assholes. Yes!
What? Someone should put
you can't, I can't say it on a microphone.
Someone should fucking
someone should kidnap the guy's kids
who made that decision.
I think it's okay to say as long as you're not saying the name
and none of us know the name, so I think you're fine.
The guy who's
in charge of mergers and acquisitions
at Smucker's, who's going like
I have a certain set of skills
and they involve
preserves and jams
of various kinds.
Turning off jam
pipes.
I'll choke you to death with pectin sauce
if I don't see my daughter.
Well, that's
a shame. I feel like you're getting boysenberry
bullshit somehow there. It's one of the
reasons to go. You gotta go. I think they still have
the pies with the boysenberries in the
pies. Oh, they do.
Smucker's doesn't
sell the jars of it. Jason checks every three
months. You make sure they are. Are there
specific? There's a private label.
Knott's has their own private label
of jam. So you can go down there and get it.
So you can go down there and get it.
We sold it, but hey, we're gonna
redo it
under a slightly different name.
I think I got
one of those when I was down
there, but I didn't open it, so
now it's probably too late.
It's a decorative jam jar at this point.
It looks cool.
I'm starting to decorate
my kitchen to look like a Knott's Berry farm
with like a
dappled apron on the table.
You want that crosshatch pattern?
That tablecloth plaid?
That's a tablecloth plaid, but it's purple
and white. Your aesthetic is like
what Cordelia Knott,
Walter's wife, wanted
for her restaurant. Cordelia Knott?
Here's my
thirteen points about what a loyal
wife should do for a man.
You can tell from the setup
exactly how wrong the thirteen points
are gonna be.
It's the title itself.
There was an old building in Knott's called
the Wife Center where you would learn about
being a good wife.
You can be processed by the time you come out of this
room. We separate the boys from the girls.
Boys can't be wives. You're out of here.
You're not allowed in. That's step one.
These are hungry boys. They're growing, you see.
I wrote a number
of letters to the editor about this
in the Orange County Register.
He was buddies with
John Wayne. That was the thing we found
that when they opened the log ride
there, there was an inaugural ride
with John Wayne, the king of the O.C.
Did he invent the log ride there?
It was before Disney did it. I don't know if it was
fully- First in California, maybe?
I think it was the first to be at least
kind of themed and kind of rustic
and have the log concept.
There were probably weird guys
in the old days that were like
let's ride a log down a river.
For real.
That's from the centuries
ago. To make it plastic and
float in a bunch of chlorine.
And not kill you. Yes.
If he didn't invent it,
he'd perfect it. And to see a lot of
sad, scary, broken men
along the way. That's what we love about
the old- the knots rides with all the
animatronics with the
faces who have seen a lot.
The desperate migrant workers. Yeah.
And broken men.
I don't know what they're trying to tell us.
I found gold!
You realize that there's nothing
romantic about a life like
chasing the remote chance
that you might find
a valuable metal in the dirt.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
That's your only hope.
You have the worst life. You have an awful
life. You're covered in soot and you breathe
more soot. But maybe, just maybe,
if I find a pebble down here.
They give you the little-
you do the little- there's like
there's gold in the water. Everybody gets a
little bit of gold when you pan for it there.
Yeah. And I
will say, I mean, I still have
it from when I was like eight or nine
or ten years old, you know. Really? Yep.
I've still got like a little
cedar chest of
bullshit from my childhood.
Including an amethyst with Google eyes.
That I think we got in Big Bear.
And a whole bunch of stuff from Knott's Berry Farm.
What do you
keep from Disneyland?
What lasts over the course of 30 years?
Disney dollars.
Oh wow. Do you think you have any of those?
I do.
I don't have them in good condition and I found out
they're worth actual money.
They've appreciated in value. Like the promise
of Transformers didn't work out.
The Transformers, like of course
you played with them. What about-
The Transformers didn't pay off.
Disney dollars did.
I guess so. Especially if you've got a
fucking Donald Duck
two Disney dollar note.
Yeah. You can go to conventions
and people have binders
full of them. And you can just like
oh yeah, that one
dollar Jack Sparrow
bill.
That was one of the ones we saw that was like
limited. They only produced so many
Jack Sparrow dollars.
That was the last run in the early
2000s. I want- I always like
the gay villains because I have an old
stand up bit about that from 12
years ago. So
I collect Ursula
and Captain Hook things. Oh really?
Wow. Wow. I guess that'd be a question.
Not a lot. Can't handle a lot. I only
live in an apartment.
Yeah. Well yeah. Square footage.
Then it becomes- if you have to devote a room to it.
I did. I had to get rid of some
stuff. I was like oh no. There was
a pandemic time and I was like just
buy things. Oh yeah.
They were delivered. Oh yeah.
I didn't realize they would come.
Wait, who do you
count as a gay villain?
Who do you bring over? Well, okay.
So in Disney it's definitely like
Ursula.
Ursula's divine, right?
Divine, yes.
Inspired. Divine inspired
or lesbian bartender.
And then Captain Hook or
the gummy bears, it's Duke
Eggthorn which is the same character
basically. Oh that's true.
Captain Hook I mean, come on
Peter.
Oh I didn't realize how Hollywood squares.
Yes, he certainly is
Peter Pan and also
can bring me those gummy bears.
I'm going to squeeze them for their juices.
Every last drop. Get it all over me.
Yes, this is
of course all the Decepticons
in Transformers.
We're leaving Disney now but every single
Decepticon in different kinds
of gay villains.
Megatron, shut up
Starscream.
And then there's like the quieter like butch bartender
who's like Megatron, sound wave
Megatron.
Okay, this is all available on my
stand-up album
Low Hanging Fruit which is also on 800
Pound Gorilla which is where my special is
out. Great, great, great. Okay, okay.
And this is a one-stop shop. And I recorded both
of these things in the Year of the Dragon
or released them.
Oh, these are, oh wow, in subsequent
2012 was
2012 was Low Hanging Fruit
and then 2024 is
Path of Most Resistance. Wow.
So then you'll be back, you're not doing, and you won't do
another one until the next Year of the Dragon. I'm like a
very predictable
comment.
Very predictable comment.
But then the scarcity like with Disney Dollars
is what you. Oh yeah. Yeah, it makes it more valuable.
I'm a little appreciated in value if you
keep me in a nice cedar trunk.
Buy a copy, buy a digital copy
of the special, keep it in a cedar
trunk. Right. Watch what happens.
Here's, let me bring this one up because when you were
throwing out theme park stuff you have experience
with, the one you mentioned that we have not ever talked about
is Wild Rivers because
uh,
Whittier you spent time in?
I went to Whittier College, I went to
High School in the Valley, I went to Junior
High School in Westchester
in Santa Monica. Oh, gotcha. Okay, okay.
So I know I'm all over that stuff.
There was raging, when I was a kid there was raging
waters and Wild Rivers. Okay, yeah.
And that was, that was like the
great rivalry. Oh sure. Where did
you fall on that? We went to both.
And I think our family thought that
Wild Rivers was better but it was a narrow.
I don't remember. Nothing was like so
superior. Right. It was basically
the same thing. Right. Raging waters
is in San Dimas and I believe Wild Rivers
was in OC somewhere.
Irvine. It was in Irvine. Irvine in the
same neck of the woods as
the amphitheater there
which is Verizon Wireless at one point
and Irvine Meadows at one point
and now I think it's all just becoming
apartments. It's gone. No, it's moved.
There is a new, Wild
Rivers shut down a long time ago but there's a new Wild
Rivers elsewhere. Yes. In something called
Great Park in Irvine which is always
I've been to and it's completely... Is it affiliated or
like we got the name? Is it a
Bain Capital estate?
It is, it did
reading the history of it
it is a little
succession in terms of
like well then the lease was for
30 years but they only used 13
of it so then they were
selling this off and they were going to rebuild
it on top of the
land that was an old
I think marine base?
Great.
I'll exclude an ordinance.
I assure you, you mentioned
Boisenberry contaminating
groundwater, something else
contaminated the groundwater
west of this so
they did not end up building
it on that land. So don't go
on any rides that splash you into
the groundwater. It is not on the
groundwater. Groundwater rapids.
They say it has been
cleaned up. Luckily their new
location is right between San Onofre
and Camp Pendleton.
So
there's things about these theme parks
that are like the same where there's always
a lazy river.
Some big tower
where the big one is.
Now I think
Raging Waters is gone too, right?
No, Raging Waters is still there.
No, but they also have
the Six Flags
has Hurricane Harbor
and does Disneyland
have one? Not here.
So
the most recent one I went to
was Hurricane Harbor
maybe five years ago with
my friend. Again, an adult
friend where we were just like, let's go.
You need that.
It was the end of the summer. It was after Labor Day.
It was like this time of year.
They still had
their five day a week hours
but that was the last week that they
had the five day a week hours.
And then they switched to weekends only
and then they closed I think.
So we caught
the tail end and they were
the lifeguard was just like
lifeguard's 18
because they're like, that's the one rule
the lifeguards have to be 18.
Lifeguard that had no interest
at all. Just watching
everything happen like yep
okay you know drown whatever
and I just have to be sitting
here. Everything was kind of sloppy
and rickety at the end of the summer at
Hurricane Harbor.
I bet it's not so great at the top of the summer
either. We decided
not we were both went up the stupid tower
where there's like three options of
elite manhood and they were
like is it the there's like a
black diamond it's like a ski slope. Black
snake stomach. Is that what it is?
Yes black snake stomach.
And there's a scary one at the top we didn't do
where it's like Cobra Assassin.
And they're like if you get stranded up there if you
can't go down the slide you gotta be rescued
with a helicopter. There's no way
down. We have to dislodge
the roof. There's a deconstruct the entire
tower. And a rope ladder.
It was it was rough.
It wasn't scary so much
as I went down and I've done water slides
since I was a child. You cross your arms
over your thing you go you follow whatever the specific
rules are where they're like this one
you make sure you go down ass up.
Whatever it is.
Whatever it is you do the thing
and so I did it and it was rough.
And it was like
it was it was sure you're
sloshing and you're like kind of almost slosh
up out of the thing going down or
whatever where you're in you're in
uncontained water at
some point. It's just you and a
water stream going down.
But then also the plastic
things were rough. The panels were
not fit together right. They don't line
up. That's the worst thing. And I'm
almost naked and it was like
On your skin it's slicing
your skin every
And then like
it was like
and then crash bump
and then down into the final
fucking splooge
area. What do you call that?
That's the term.
It's the splooge down. It's the final splooge down.
You get down into the
final eject zone
and
it broke the skin.
It drew blood.
Did it really? Yes.
And I didn't do anything wrong. I was just
sliding down the slide. And it was
enough. It was enough like difference in
the panels of the plastic. It drew
blood and it hurt and not badly
but I was like ow. Where on your body?
Like my
people are going to love this.
Sure. It was like
it hurt
my ass and back and ribs.
And I think the blood was
on the side of my torsos.
I have two torsos
by the way.
Both look great. Both in great shape.
So you ended up with a bloody ass?
Sure. Why not?
It's not the first time that's happened.
But then the problem
is the guy, the lifeguard
down at the fucking splash
splooge, he was like
get out.
And it
was just normal. And he could tell
that me and my friend one after another
came down and were like ow.
And then like a couple minutes later
ow. And he was
just like routinely like yep get up
get out next one. And then we were like
clambered out with difficulty.
And then he's like
we're ready for the next one.
You know looking up to the top or whatever
with the signals. Unfazed.
Every person screams.
And it wasn't like pouring
blood but you know the kind of scrape
it was like a bleeding scrape.
And I realized like
oh yes I was bitten by the black snake.
There were fangs
every eight feet.
Well we built them into the plastic.
We put snake
in the title. You weren't expecting
fangs.
They're like look.
Hurricane Harbor's got to pay it off.
Okay here's two facts that I learned
about that involve
the lifeguards at these
places. One is from Soak
City. And apparently it's
Soak City. There is a
I found this from people saying like I really like the music
that they play there. I think does anyone
know where the mix comes from? It's kind of nice.
They use Pandora raid. What is it?
But the weird thing is that
what I find weird about the mix
is that between every song there's
a big chime. What's that about?
And other people have answered that that is
for the lifeguards to remind them to
stay alert.
So
not Soak City has to have
a ding that is
meant to like reawaken all
of the teenagers. Remember
do your job. Because otherwise you just
get lost and like yeah oh yeah
come over.
They're playing gotta get up or whatever
you get relaxed.
You get so chill.
I picked something that's like 20 years older than me.
Mine was old too.
I can't think of a modern relaxing song.
Look the chime like that's
one of Walter Knott's you know
principles like you gotta keep them
alert. Teen alertness chimes.
Teen alertness you know.
Just like a theme park needs a
chime to keep the correctly
paid laborers
alert at their
jobs. And you end up with under the
table hand jobs. A proper republic
and it is not a democracy it is
a republic also
requires a series of chimes
to alert those who would
depart from the vision of the founding
father. When Nixon is
elected I will propose
a loud alarms throughout
this great nation every
just to remind people to be
American. My fashion style
was crafted
by
Barry Goldwater.
It's primarily
bow tie based.
The stiffest suits you've ever seen.
You can't bend these at the legs.
If you
sit you can you get lazy.
Stay alert Stan. Something about those
guys that always have white
hair and very thick
black glasses.
You know the black rimmed glasses.
And they all kind of look like
the same guy when they are over
60.
I am just the generic California
old conservative.
I believe in limited and they believe the
same things and they would write the same when I was
a kid. You'd read the same letters to the editor by the same guy.
And it was always
the same every
iteration of every issue of any
newspaper in California used to have the
Reagan guy letter that someone would
write about something. And it was always
like your article of last
week is typical
liberal propaganda.
And as we need
be reminded as the great
President Ronald Reagan said
government is
not the solution.
Government is the problem.
Signed yours
Robert W.
Walker
Pasadena, California
written while wearing a bow tie.
Then you look him up
and realize he owns the entire
city that I went to college. He owns
90 acres.
Just collecting rent and writing letters to the editor
all day. He owns the 405.
He owns all of us.
The problem with the 405
is it is too egalitarian.
A toll road would have survived.
We propose permanent lanes that you stay in
for your entire life.
Giving people permission to switch.
It's willy nilly.
You should pay a dollar to switch lanes.
They can switch but that
costs money. Throw a dollar at it on the highway
and serve you as an elector who will pick it up
at the end of the night.
I have a design from my theme park
that might be useful to people.
Mass Transit was a series of slides.
The other thing
I want to say about, this is back to Hurricane
Harbor. I read a
review. I was going through one star reviews.
Always a good thing to do. And then there are
many. And there was one that said, well there
were a lot that said that half the rides were closed.
One star ass sliced.
This particular one says
half the rides were closed. The reason for this
was a shortage of lifeguards
due to graduation day.
So this is
something that can happen to you. If you go in May
to a water park, what you might find
is that a lot of the lifeguards
can't be there because they are graduating
high school. This was on the Yelp
for up in Santa
Clarita, the Magic Mountain too.
For Magic Mountain in general. In general it was like
why is everything closed? And someone was like
I think school is back in session so half
the workforce is gone. Holy shit.
Like it just completely, you have to shut down
a lot of things. Which then, with the graduation
thing specifically, that leaves you now with
either the employees are
too young to have graduated
or perhaps
did not graduate for
They're doing an extra year. Yes, yes.
We might be dealing with, if you're seeing employees
these lifeguards might be people
who are being held back. Well yeah
they're CPR certified.
You know, they did the full training.
But they are also super
seniors. So
really they should get a pay bone.
For all the experience. They're more educated
in a way than someone who did senior year
just once. Yeah.
They have read a couple of
chapters of The Great Gatsby.
That's
what I've read.
It was all just
an elaborate series of faking it.
I've been meaning to actually read it but I
have not.
That's interesting about
the times of year because I know there are
and you guys of course know this.
I had a friend who was very into theme parks who
knew this. He was a roller coaster buff.
Shout out to Bill
Lynn if he happens to hear this.
My friend from the old days at the Groundlings.
But I know
okay so there's certain times
when you're supposed to go that you have to navigate.
There's not going to be a big crowd but they might be doing
maintenance I guess. Yeah I guess so.
And I feel like
I feel like when it's back
just back in school from a vacation
is a good time.
Because everything's been picked. Everything's
in shape. So now
in September or right after
Easter or something.
But maybe I don't know about January though.
Certainly not for water parks. There's a way you can ride
it. There's definitely a time where Disneyland's
a little cheaper and a little less crowded.
If you can nail right before
some schools are back but not all.
This is a thing that now that I
have a child who is in school
I can't believe it. Now we are like
stuck in the school confines unless we
dare pull him out of school
in order to go to theme parks
with less attendance. Are you allowed to do
that as a parent? Are there like you I know you can
have sick days or emergency days but can you
be like you know what this is a fuck it day.
And I dare everybody down at
the Pasadena.
It's just one of Wolters Don's 13 principles.
I went to Disney World
in like eighth or ninth grade
in like middle of May.
But did your parents lie to
the school about what you were doing?
No, I think I just had to write like
a 500 word essay
of what I did on my trip.
Really? They just didn't care?
You just had to do a report and you could do whatever?
What kind of laissez faire school is
you go to? I read all of
I read Dracula
the novel and
I to you know
get ahead because by the time you get back
we'll have read this. And I read
it and got back and they're like
we didn't get Dracula.
You read Dracula for nothing.
It wasn't particularly
I mean it was a fine vacation read.
Like I was old enough to
13 or 14. You're in Disney
World cramming in Dracula between
every bit of free time. Before I go to
bed or on the airplanes.
Did you dare
read while. No I was not.
And it was one of the ones where it's like
we only have so many copies of the book
here's a photocopied
pamphlet of the book.
He's got a loose leaf.
Yeah it got loose. Yeah it got
paper. That never happened. You never had to buy
like in college. You never had to buy a bunch
of articles like for five bucks
photocopied. Why a bunch
of articles? This seems unofficial like you ran
into a guy in the alley. Yeah I got
textbooks. Come here I got textbooks. It very much
was that. Is Dracula
the only public domain
intellectual
property that didn't make it into
Disneyland or into Disney as like
a main property. It's kind of
a universal because universal is
associated with the classic monsters
from their old moon. They've done more with
Frankenstein, Dracula, etc.
But yeah you're in Disney could.
They could just probably. Dracula does
exist in the Marvel Universe.
Oh that's the way in. I think there was
a big they were just
finishing in the Marvel comics. A big
vampire crossover. Robert
Danny Jr.'s next part.
He's going to be Dracula. I'm not going to be. Don't make
me be Doom again. I've done so
once he's done 20 movies as Doom.
He'll be 80 and he'll do Dracula.
In the 70s they had
the Godzilla license.
So the Avengers and Nick Fury
were Marvel? Like Godzilla. Yeah.
There's like a phone book size collection
or two.
Bum bum bum bum.
Right.
This poses an interesting problem.
Let me throw one thing out
is maybe on the way out the door
here is that because we
when you mentioned Wild Rivers that
sent me down. Well here one
thing first. I want to get everybody's thoughts
especially Jason's thoughts on something they
apparently sold at Wild Rivers. But you
as the treat boy of the show. What do
you think of the apparently exclusive
Wild Rivers snack.
The funnel dog.
A corn dog
seemingly made with funnel cake
batter as the
batter. I don't. I'm into that.
I don't think
corn dog batter and funnel cake
batter is that different.
And I think if
you have a salty enough
or spicy enough
dog in the middle it would
you know compliment like a
sweet corn dog. My memory
of waterpark food. I specifically
have one of course
at Blizzard Beach at Disney
World. We were
there and we you know did
the did the sides
and the we have fries and everything
it was time for lunch. And
like the main lunch counter
they're like what is
their main their main thing was like
meatball subs
and I love a meatball sub. So I was
pretty excited. But I also
like as soon as I started
eating it I'm like this is
a dangerous food to eat without
a shirt on.
So what
what happened? Covered in marinara sauce
shirtless? Yeah because marinara
drips out the back. A meat if you're not
careful a meatball is going to fall right out
the back. Did that happen? And if it's hot
it's going to well I think I dodged one.
I think I caught it with the plate. Whoa!
Oh shit! You like you took a bite
and the bread you squeezed the bread at the wrong
angle and then squirted a
bullet speed
meatball in your on to your
bare chest. Oh yeah meatballs could go in any
direction either side of the sandwich.
And then the meatball lifeguard is like
next!
Come on!
Keep moving!
Is it just is it just my memory did they
have like unique kinds of ice
cream at water parks that you couldn't get anywhere
else where there was like it was like
a guy with eyes and they were like
want to buy this guy and eat his face?
Sometimes one of the
like you can get soft serve
in a little sand pail.
Right. Like bucket at
one of the Disney ones and that's cute.
But it's a lot of soft serve
to fill a bucket.
It's not a huge bucket. If anybody's up for the
challenge. Well.
It's a lot of soft serve to fill
a bucket. Luckily
we have a massive underground
system of pipes here in this
water park that
filters out everything from hair
to an entire bucket
of soft serve. Every
14 cubic feet
we know there's an entire
bucket of soft serve in the water.
You know you just don't want to mix up
the pipes because then the soft serve machine
shoots out chlorinated water
and it's then the wave pool
is full of soft serve. And feral
cats that may have been caught in the filter
also get served from the soft serve
machines. They're all bloated.
They're full of soft serve.
Well maybe
we could get Tom and Jerry as a costume
mascot of this park.
Got enough rats and cats around
here.
There is a mascot that I
want to mention as we wind down because I
can't keep this fact in my head even
if this could be for a future episode. But when you
brought up Wild Rivers in Irvine
this area that
you know some of it became an amphitheater
but all of it just like big
teeming grounds there in Irvine
used to be something
called Lion Country Safari.
I don't know
when this closed but I think it like reached
its height in the 70s. And
all of that land around there
was one of those places where
you could drive your car around
and there were just lions
and hippos and ostriches.
It was a drive through safari.
Now we've kind of relegated all that to San Diego.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
San Diego still does that.
That's Animal Town.
We haven't been there. I haven't done that.
I thought it would genuinely scare my child.
So I didn't do it. But yeah, there was a time
where just right next to whatever that mall
is called, The Spectrum,
there would be lions wandering around.
Apparently at one point a hippo got
loose and was just running around
Irvine for 19 days.
That many days?
Yes. Yep.
Well, he's like, well, they don't know where to find me.
They think, oh, he's heading north.
They go north on the 5.
That was actually off the 405.
There's a why.
There's a why. That was in Wild
Rivers Tagalos. They said it's where the
405 meets the 5. So the hippo
could use that confusion to his advantage.
The hippo started
auditing UC Irvine classes.
And no one really hated
any of mine. Put on a big XXL
T-shirt. Also, bad advertising
to be like, it's where the 405
meets the 5. Because that could send people to
your archrival magic mountain.
Oh, yeah, right.
They meet in two different places.
Okay, I know where that is.
Great.
Here's what I wanted to bring up about Lion Country
Safari.
I think, you know, they were doing
okay for an Orange County
drive-thru safari. But things
really kicked into gear. When they brought
a lion into the fold,
named Frasier.
Frasier was an old, toothless
lion. I could barely
see. He was 18, which is
80 plus for us humans.
This is old for a lion.
And they didn't know. I think he
was with some shady circuses.
And you know what? We'll take him in. We will be
better to Frasier. The question
is, how will Frasier blend with all of
our lionesses who have been
very standoffish when we've
introduced other males into our
drive-thru safari? And then what
happened was, Frasier had
35 cubs with six different
lionesses who had all refused
to mate with younger,
more virile, you would think,
male lions. And this
led to a situation where
they started advertising this lion
specifically, this old, toothless lion
who fucking fucks.
And they started
calling him Frasier the sensuous
lion. This was, I guess,
the thing. People know this from
the 70s.
And honestly, it kept them in
business fully, was Frasier
the sensuous lion. But then here's the
anecdote that really takes it over the edge
is that the popularity of
Frasier was so much that people took a risk
and said, you know what? This sounds like,
to me, like a movie. And there
was a movie that was made called
Frasier the sensuous lion
based on the real lion in Irvine.
What I'm showing you guys right now
is a, like, 70s
drawn sex comedy poster
where there is a sheet
covering up a kind of leering guy
and a sexy, laughing
Dean Martin girl.
Right. Human, human. Yeah, so you're right.
Human's important detail. And then
the most, like, side-eye
pervy face. Having a
threesome with a lion. Yeah, that's
kind of what's implying. Yes, yeah, yeah.
The woman going like, ooh,
and the guy, and the lion.
I mean, there's also kind of the
subtext of, like, she's seeing something down there.
Well, this is in accordance with my
thirteen Leonine
principles.
You separate, you have
the lionesses go to the lioness center
to learn how to please
a male
properly maned male
lion. I believe that the oldest
of any species, lion or human,
should receive the most sexual pleasure
from the youngest, most beautiful
women of their species.
And if this involves
shaming and aggressively
expelling
the younger male members of the
clan, then so be it.
Making them feel
real bad about everything, about
their looks and their beliefs.
Who was in the movie, do you know? Yeah, pretty cool.
They got Elliot Gould and Jane Fonda.
They worked a lot in the sense.
Well, that's how it looks in the photo.
But really, what you're dealing with is in
Frasier the Sentuous Lion, the film.
I'm so glad you asked me who's
in it, because the cast is
lots of names that I've never heard of.
Some with cool names, like Malachi
Throne. I wish I knew more about
Malachi Throne.
But it's kind of, to be honest, no names
until you get deep into
the names who are on the sheet,
kind of down by the knees in this
poster. You get to the name
Peter Laurie Jr.
Interesting. So Peter Laurie
had a son who
acted, and he got into this lion movie.
Rick, I'm fine.
I don't need anything, Rick. Leave me
alone. I'm playing a video game.
Okay, well that's good
that he could have his own career outside of his
father. Nope, wrong.
This was some guy with a
different name who was trying to be an
actor, and he had a weird
face like Peter Laurie, and it wasn't
going anywhere. So he said, you know what I'll do?
I'll become legally
Peter Laurie Jr.
I dare you to say that I'm not
why would anybody do that?
I dare you to say I'm not actually Peter Laurie Jr.
But he was not. You could just do that?
I guess so. Or they made a law after
this guy. Maybe if you try to do it now
you invoke the Peter Laurie Jr.
law. But at the time
this was a lawless time, you didn't have that.
I would go for Orson
Wells.
I don't
It's a really good
scheme though, is to take some
guy that you kind of look like and just say
whatever, fine. I don't
know if I'd have one.
People used to say I look like Zach
Braff, but I haven't heard that in a long time.
I was a more slight man
and when he was more popular that's what
was said. But it never occurred
to me to say I'm Zach Braff Jr.
and see where that gets me.
I'm Lil Zach Braff.
I'm Lil.
If they made Jr.
illegal.
Lil Zach Braff.
It's funny, I was just
reading about, like Michael Keaton
revealed, like his birth name
is Michael Douglas.
And when it came time to
join SAG, it was already
taken. So he called
it Michael Keaton. But now he's going back
to it. He said he's thinking about changing
his SAG name to Michael Keaton
Douglas. Over my
fucking dead body.
I will
I have survived
multiple bouts of
human papilloma virus
from guzzling the love juices
of various
women.
And I did not go
through that delicious hell.
To have my name
ripped away by some kind of bird man.
I believe it's going to come to Fisticuff's
fuck face.
I'm so delighted you do
Michael Douglas. Michael Douglas is the funniest
guy. I could listen to him tell stories.
Stories of sexual conquest.
Forever.
I have to monitor my blood pressure.
He's smoking with a
heart with a what do you call it?
Blood pressure sleeve on
while he has a cigarette.
I have to monitor my blood pressure.
Anyway, I just wanted to educate everybody about
not only Frazier the Centuous
Lion, Peter Laurie Jr., but also
that this is a good ski. If you're looking, you know,
just think about who might read
as your father. I don't know if you have
I don't know if you've ever been compared to somebody
30 years your
older. Well, it's a good angle.
Yeah. When I was skinny, everybody said I looked like
Errol Flynn, which is great.
Errol Flynn Jr. is great. No one questioned that.
Errol Flynn Jr.
I used to have to be more than just probably
a few more generations.
Or you could do like
Errol Flynn the fourth.
Nobody questioned that. And then you subtly
the subtle thing, you spell it wrong.
You put like, you know, one less
R, one more R, three R's.
Then you're not infringing on anything legally.
Errol Morris the fourth.
Great.
Well, that's a good
potential plan for you.
But anyway, anything else on the way out the door?
Any theme park memories or pain?
I think we are.
We've reached the time when the
Disney characters are projected in the mist
above Main Street.
And they're about to herd you
out the door with nothing open except
the shops. Yep. The shops. Extra
hour. Ice cream shop. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's what, yeah.
That's something we could call. I mean, we call it
exiting through the gift shop. That is kind of what we do.
But I mean, I guess with
that we can say officially, James Zedome,
you survived podcast The Ride.
Thank you for a big pile of
memories and oddities.
And for, you know.
Only a minor scrape.
You've mostly
survived. You know, if it
happens again, bring a bottle of Taffer's brown butter
powder. Oh, yeah. Rub it on it. Yeah.
That's probably how many years,
not like an unopened bottle on the shelf,
but how many years
that occasionally sipped from bottle
of whiskey can stick around.
And how can it help
heal a wound if it has very little
actual whiskey content? Right.
That's really the question. Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, let's exit through the
gift shop.
Let's talk about the special little. Hey, there we are.
Yeah, yeah. It's called Path of Most
Resistance. It's my first
stand-up comedy special.
It's out now on 800 pound gorilla
media dot com
to pay what you want.
And as of September 19th,
it's available everywhere, streaming on YouTube.
You can rent it and buy it anywhere you would
do that with a comedy special. And
all the information is on my website, James Zedome and dot com.
Fantastic. Path of Most
Resistance. And it's
it was a fantastic
comedy special about two weeks ago, but
now events of the day have overtaken it.
Oh, geez.
Wait, which events of which
Actually, I should be careful because I don't know when
this is coming out. That's a
real moment of hubris on mine.
It'll be closer to the YouTube
date, I think. I think it's where
I forget I said anything.
You know,
I don't care if you buy. This special adheres
to the 13 principles of Walter
Nott. Very good.
I don't know if you get a
laugh out of Walter Nott on this, but you think you might
at least crack a smile. That is right up
my alley for the level of
obscurity that I like to have.
I know. I love that you busted
it out of Walter Nott. I don't think anybody's tried
a Walter Nott. Well, it's just him, but it's
also any guy like that is the same
guy. Yeah. O.C. conservative
from 48
And they're not there anymore. Yeah.
All those people, their kids moved to
Arizona and Nevada.
Yeah, I know.
It's a shame. Boy, a shame.
O.C. voting blue. I never thought I'd see
the day.
I'm still alive.
104 years old and I've been very
disappointed to see that my
great grandchildren have become
liberals.
Liberals.
I have a blood vendetta
with Snoopy.
There's a room in the Freedom Center at Nott's where he is still alive
in like an iron lung. Disguised
as an animatronic
prospector. Oh, he's in there.
Who did? I did find gold. He's part of it.
I found gold in a boysenberry.
But everybody's like,
boy, that weird old robot, that's not realistic
at all. Actually, it is the
range of motion that a currently living
Walter Nott would have. His heart is
replaced by a large boysenberry.
Yeah, are they feeding that robot?
It's beating boysenberry through his veins.
They're feeding it exclusively
a bucket of fried chicken
and boysenberry pie and it's
like preserving it.
Like the Borg Queen
in Star Trek.
He's like half of her. He comes down from
the ceiling. That's a healthy
republic, if you ask me.
Hey, as
for us, check out, for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate or get one
more bonus episode every month on our VIP
tier club three. You'll find all of that
at patreon.com slash
podcast the ride. Mike, I swear,
if you fuck us on this episode, if you
bury this episode for tax breaks,
if you fuck James over,
this is, think about, to us, sure,
but this is our guest. Look,
if John Cena were to hear my plan, he would say, well, that makes
a lot of sense. I think you should do it. And he would
sign off on it and I want to please him, so
episode probably buried for a reason. Sorry,
probably buried for a reason.
Forever
Dog. This has
been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe
to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever
you get your podcasts. Keep up
with the latest Forever Dog news by
following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page on
Facebook.
Thank you.