He found himself standing next to the flag pole in Town Square in the heart of
the Magic Kingdom in his pajamas. How he'd gotten there he had no idea. His last
memory was climbing into bed. It felt like only minutes earlier. Oh wow okay so
that's a I assume an excerpt from the book that I read. That's how it starts
that's the very beginning of the book. That's not a page of your journal from a
couple nights ago? No that is. Okay just making sure I just I think I thought I
recognized it from the book but I just wanted to make sure. No it's funny you
say that because I had a very distressing dream last night. Oh okay. That Matt
Newell and Mary Holland were getting married again at the Hard Rock Hotel.
That's distressing. Well cuz cuz some of the restaurants at City Walk were
included in the dining like oh you can go here and get a sandwich or you can go
here and get a plat- and I was trying to run around to do them all. Okay hold on
hello Club 3. Hello Club 3. It's Mike and Jason here. Hold on we'll have a message from Scott
one second but I want to unpack what you're saying. The dream was that you
were at the Hard Rock Hotel do you know like the one in San Diego the one in
Vegas? The one in Orlando. The one in Orlando. The one in Orlando when apparently when I
dream I end up in Orlando much like the Kingdom Keepers themselves. So it was
distressing in the sense that you didn't know where the you could get the
sandwiches that you were comfortable with? Yeah I was trying to run around
because like the Dead Coconut Club was included. Okay. So it was just distressing that the kitchen was included.
The nightmare was that the layout of City Walk was a different
layout than you were familiar with. Well we only had two or three hours for the
reception. Okay. And I couldn't even remember if I packed a suit. Oh well
that's distressing. So I was distressed. Yeah if you didn't have a suit for a wedding. Yeah I get that.
You would have had to wear you would have had to go to the t-shirt stand
where the guy airbrushes stuff like what I did. I got the I Love City Walk shirt.
You could have had a guy airbrush a picture. Congratulations. Well that or a
picture of a suit on a t-shirt. Oh that's even better. And then on the back it
would have said congrats or something and then he could have spray paint. He
could have like airbrushed your pants. You could have brought him some white
jeans and then he could have airbrushed sort of formal pants onto the white jeans.
Where were you in the dream? Because for whatever reason around every corner was
Nicole Kidman. Nicole Kidman was there. Nicole Kidman was there a lot and she
looked very elegant as she often does. Well Miss Chase Miss Chase Meridian of
course she's gonna look elegant believe me. I well I would have astral projected
into that dream if I knew it was happening I'm sorry. But look welcome to
Club 3. We have a message from Scott here he says I hello Club 3 subscribers
I'm sorry I can't be there. I promise it is for a good and positive reason. I am
not just avoiding reading Kingdom Keepers please and he says be extremely
thorough as to what library or online program Jason used to obtain this book.
May the DH eyes be with you Scott. That is his message for all of you and he
will return to the show very soon. Very soon. Great well look I'm already all
over his requests so I used the Libby app to borrow a Kindle copy of this book
and I borrowed a collection that was the first three books. Now I only read book
one and the first couple chapters of book two. Okay well we'll get to more of this
sort of these details these tantalizing details these interesting details. I'll
explain how I absorbed the book after this but we do have to it's Club 3 we
do have to do all the administrative stuff. Scott generally handles all
that because next month Club 3 becomes Crypt 3. That is right. You remember that
Jason? I do remember that. Because it's Halloween and it's spooky so last year's
Halloween runner-up was the nightmare experiment which was Hong Kong
Disneyland's attempt at the horror attraction at a horror attraction. Oh a
fascinating subject. Yes well yeah it seems like the scariest thing any
Disney parks ever done on purpose. Not just like a spectro magic doll face man
or something. Paul Lynn Halloween special is also going into the poll because it
was the runner-up in Carlson's Clash of the Kitsch. And now we need three more
spooky topics so leave your suggestions in the patreon comments. Jason do you
have anything you want to throw out to the listeners that you think about as
far as Halloween? You don't have to have that. No I will let I do not want to tip the scales. Does anyone
want to just say I want to hear about Jason's dream journal to hear about the
different malls he goes to and the nightmares he has where the malls are
shuffled around a little bit. They're a little different. They're a little
different yeah. Because that's yeah you could keep a journal for maybe a week
like how often do you have nightmares? I don't know I dream pretty regularly.
Yeah. Traumatically though or? Not not very bad traumatically. Okay not like
last night. No I did wake up in a bit of a state you know. Okay sure yeah yeah but
I'm just saying would your like a seven-day dream journal be interesting? I
don't think so yeah I don't think there'd be enough. Okay it would have to
be a month long so if your vote if you're throwing on a topic would be a
month of Jason's dream journal and that would have enough juicy topics to talk
about on a club three or a crypt three. I think I'd really rather some sort of
interesting theme park topic but if the people say. If the people demand it.
Yeah. Jason's to nightmares which maybe that's look that's a future I
floated this idea out before to my co-hosts of doing a full podcast a ride
haunt a full maze live in person one day but maybe yeah that's Jason's to
nightmares maybe that's maybe that's down the road we collect enough to
nightmares and then we're by the way we're referencing Jimmy Fallon's haunted
maze or mole. Rock-a-Pillar Plaza. He's doing this is a not a joke he's doing his own
Hollywood Horror Nights style maze. And we're looking into it very strongly. Okay
that being said let's get on to today's topic. The Kingdom Keepers which was a
suggestion from Logan. This is what Logan said he said club three suggestion the
boys read through and discuss or and discusses at least the first Kingdom
Keepers book. The story about a group of middle schoolers who wake up as
holograms and battle Disney villains at night at Walt Disney World. And then
Malia chimed in absolutely cosine Eisner era shenanigans in a perfect 2005 time
capsule. VMK animatronics come to life. So here we are Kingdom Keepers.
Kingdom Keepers which I had long seen I had heard about I think I knew the
premise. I didn't realize this was so old I didn't realize it's been this long of
the Kingdom Keepers books have been coming out. Well what I saw it was that
this was kind of in conjunction with the happiest celebration on earth. So Disney
lands 50th anniversary. The books were launched as was Virtual Magic Kingdom.
Right. Which comes into play in the first book and Virtual Magic Kingdom shut down
around 2008 and they had to work that into the books. Yes there's a lot of
synergy in the book. Yeah. And I honestly I was sort of ignorant to this I didn't
realize these were official Disney sponsored books. I almost thought these
were sort of like unofficial like Disney but I thought it was almost like Escape
from Tomorrow or whatever that gorilla filmmaking Disney World book was at
first. Yes. But this is officially like Disney approved. Disney granted the
author Ridley Pearson that's his name right Ridley Pearson. They grants him
access to the parks after dark. Yes. And I think at some point he said like
they're over like 30 times he went into the parks at night. In the introduction
he talks about being shown around by Jason Sorrell. Right. Former Imagineer who
wrote the Haunted Mansion book that we discuss a lot. Yes Jay thank you Jason
for that content. Yeah. Every year. Every year. And we say this page from your book is
good. Yeah. We like it. And has written other books about the parks. Yeah. Yeah so
he got backstage access. Right. Which is cool. I mean I'm very envious of that
because that is like you think about the premise of like OK you get to go into
Disneyland after dark get to go to Disney World after dark. What goes on. Now
here's what I would say. What did they actually learn being in the parks after
dark. Was that so necessary. Like the pirates don't come to life for real
after dark in Disney. No. There are not real padlocked cells under. Right. Pirates
and Caribbean. I think he probably learned the trash disposal tubes. Right. You
know. So he's like so I guess what I'm getting at is like do you think on some
level the author was like I bet I can get some free Disney like after I can go
into Disneyland after dark and like enjoy myself. I think he probably had a
little fun with it. I would think so. I'm just saying like yeah you can your
imagination runs wild. But like what did he learn for the books. Like he learned
how they like polish the splash mountain vehicle like the log while they're
closed or he probably learned that there there is an apartment above the fire
house. But that's at Disneyland. Did they build the apartment. I don't think the
apartment is above. Is there actually an apartment above the fire station in in
Disney world. That's a good question. I don't know. Is there a weird old man who
lives up there. There's not a weird old man that lives up there for real. Could
you ever meet Wayne in the parks. So I don't know. I don't think you could meet
Wayne which is a character from Kingdom Keeper. So really what I'm getting at is
this guy milked Disney. He's smart. He milked Disney for a bunch of fun like
walks around the park when no one was there. Sure. In the middle of the night.
Yeah. But I think you could have come up with all this stuff without it. That's
what I'm saying. You know he's written some all ages graphic novels for D.C.
called Super Sons. Yeah. I hope he melts them. I hope he went to the room the
closet the criterion closet of D.C. got a bunch of trades. Oh yeah. Sure. Well
maybe like he didn't adopt like sons like for real just like to research. I
can't speak to that. I haven't read his full. Yeah. I'm just saying I think he
uses imagination. That's all I'm saying. But anyway this is this I will say this
these books the premise of them is very good. It's very exciting to any like
theme park kid dork. Yes. Adults. And I had not read them. I am on record as
being a bad reader. Sure. So first of all if anyone has a tip on how to read
better and I can read I know how to read. I know the words my vocabulary is fine.
You've heard the show but I think I have some level of ADHD that like prevents
me from focusing well when I'm reading. Oh my attention spans shop. I know but
you're a good you read though. I do. Yeah. I fight again. It is a fight. I sat
down so many times to get through this book and it was like for one thing I
always forget like oh why a genre stuff is sometimes very long. Yes. Because kids
who are big readers want it to keep going. They want to keep free. They want
more. They want more. They want more. Yes. And I'm an old man with a limited
time. Yes. Just give me what the give me the flashy stuff. Sure. You know just
give me the gist of it and let's move on. So yes it's a struggle for me. So
because of that I did an audio book on an audio book. OK. Hey you know that's
great. I mean you laughed a lot though. He's like because I gave up I guess
really effectively I gave up and I was like I can't read it. I can't read. I just
didn't consider an audio book. I didn't know if audio books were available for
these are produced. Oh sure they are. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I did a free trial on
audio book dot com. I didn't even use audible. Oh OK. So I can cancel after
that. Great. And I did. Yeah I did the first one via audio book and then
because I just wanted to make sure I knew it. I read the Cliff Notes on a
different Web site with a different free trial. Yeah. I wanted to make sure that
today for my book report I did a good job. Well you want to know. Remember all
the background of Finn and Maybeck and Philby and Willa and Charlene. Right. And
you pulled that out off the top of your head. You did not look at your thing
because I had to look at my notes to remember the names of all the people
because they're my friends now. Because you're like an unofficial kingdom keeper.
Yeah basically. Yeah. But I just port to like the Hard Rock Hotel and Universal
apparently. All right. Yes. You when you dream you go to a city walk in Orlando.
Yeah. Well that is I was going to actually ask that at the end of the
episode of like where we would want to keep which kingdoms would we want to
keep. But I guess we could talk about you would just be city walk or Islands of
Adventure. Yeah. I'd prefer to be at Islands of Adventure and I'd prefer to
be a little less stressed out. Yeah sure. Well but keeping a kingdom is a
stressful job. That is true. So I don't know if you really want to be a full
kingdom keeper. I think I would spend a lot more time trying to practice and
harness the hologram powers. Right. You're more of like you would be like a
kingdom enjoyer or something. Well I'd be a kingdom enjoyer but then a kingdom
student. Like I would just again and again try to phase through a trash can.
Because we've known some keepers in our day. Oh yeah. And podcast the ride and it
is a stressful position. Absolutely. Hey you podcast long enough you're gonna
encounter some keepers. Right. So yeah let's so we've kind of given you the gist
here of what this is. But yes it's like night at the museum at Disney World. What
happens after all the guests leave and the pixie dust and the magic starts and
what happens I guess is that evil spirits take over and try to take over
the park. Yeah what the overtakers. Right and they're called overtakers which not
undertakers. Now that I'm hearing that out loud I'm like oh that is a very on the
nose name. Yeah. They are trying to take over the overtakers. Yeah. So there's a
lot of I don't want to say it's like kind of clunky mythology but it's like
slightly clunky in sort of a setup way in my mind. Yeah I think the setup is more
I think the exit once it gets moving I don't think it's very clunky but it can
I. Yeah. Okay these five kids they all have a particular set of skills. Right
these are like 13 year old kids. Yes 13 14 and so they they all five of them
audition and get scanned for a new Disney parks endeavor called the DH eyes.
Right. The there's multiple is it Disney digital hologram interactive like
there's multiple explanations for the acronym. Right. Basically there are tour
guide holograms that show up on Main Street. Right. And so they get paid for
this they get like unlimited park passes but if they're going to the park that
their hologram is in they have to wear a disguise. This is what I'm saying about
being clunky a little bit in the setup. I'm just like getting through this and going what is this.
There's more. So they discover that when they go to sleep they become their
partial partial human partial hologram within the park. Uh-huh. And there is an
old man named Wayne who is an Imagineer but he appears to be a million years old
and he worked with Walt. Right. Yes and he gives them a mission that they have to solve a fable.
Right. Of Walt's stone cutters quill. Yes. Right. OK. So is there more? Well I there there is more
because you get to see that these kids kind of become little micro celebrities.
They essentially did predict influencers of like the kids when they go to the parks if they get
recognized people freak out. Right. You know and Disney this is one of the I thought one of the
canniest things in the book is that in the Emporium on Main Street they mention that you can buy the
outfits that the holograms are wearing. Oh yes. Right. I thought that was like oh that is what
Disney would do. Like this is not intentionally cutting but it is a little cutting. Yes there
yes it does seem like it's probably like written in like an earnest way of what Disney would do
but it also reads as something where Disney would just try to milk something that's popular in the
parks. I mean if there were holographic guides in Disneyland for real and they were like famous
or unique character type characters I would want merchandise of them. Oh you know what I'm saying.
Like it would be like oh well I do want what's his name Jill Burt. What's the guy's name. Phil B.
Phil B. Sorry I swear I read the book. Oh I swear I listened. You listened to the book. Phil B.
And Phil B. is an accent is he English. I believe is English. Yeah he's English. And I was saying I
read. I was going to call him Dilby. Dilbert. Yeah Dilby. Because you would be like oh I want a Phil B.
doll or I want a Phil B. action figure. I would be lamenting the lack of Phil B. merchandise if there
was a holographic 13 year old on Main Street giving people guides. Now this is what I'm saying where
I'm reading or again I'm listening to this I want to be very clear I'm listening to this and going
wait what is this. They have completely invented an idea that there would be. Now you tell me this is
it just a little show going on of like the kids being holograms or are they completely interactive.
I think it's a mix. I think they kind of split the difference. This is all a setup for they need to
get these kids in the park quote unquote right within the universe so they can walk between
worlds so that when they go to sleep they show up in the park and then they can they see
pirate animatronics coming to life or like Pooh Bear Pooh Bear and Chip and Dale walking around
which I thought was kind of unexamined. Very unexamined. Very unexamined. Like oh you see
over there look who it is oh it's Pooh and then that's about it. That's about it I'm assuming in
later books that comes into play because I'm like well wouldn't they want as many allies
as they could get. Right you would want Pooh fighting and dying at your side
while fighting the overtakers. Yeah. Pooh sacrifices himself.
Yeah Christopher Robin you know. I've lived a good life oh let me go let me sacrifice myself.
Piglet piglet let me die. Let me die piglet. Christopher Robin is like that one SEAL Team
Six guys the weird squirrely quiet one. He's always sneaking up behind. He sneaks up behind
like Hades cuts him from ear to ear. Right yeah yeah. Pooh smothers somebody with his fluff.
My guts are spilling out and I'm going to suffocate them with my fluff.
Go just go into the light.
So yeah so I saw this on Reddit and this is kind of a thought I had. Do you think that the whole
hologram set up is some sort of like Disney note of like we can't actually have physical
13 year olds in our parks even in a fantasy world and even in a book being put in like direct harm
even though they kind of do get hurt in the books. Right if they're hologram okay when they're
dreaming and they're a hologram if they get zapped with like a laser or bit by a creature
they do experience harm in real life. Right yes that is true so they wake up and they have a burn
on them from Buzz Lightyear's Astro Blasters or Space Ranger Spin but I'm just saying like is
there some like Disney legal was like okay we cannot have books where 13 year olds sneak into
the park at night like there's some like this kind of clunky plot set up is because of mandates
like we cannot have 13 year olds climb the walls of Disneyland. We can't have them do something
illegal or like against the rules like hide in the Emporium until close. We have to have some like
clean way that kids would be able to get into the park at midnight and the hologram and dreams
is a smooth way where they're not breaking any rules and they're technically Disney employees
as well. So like to me it seems like maybe there were some rules that the author had to follow
to make sure that kids wouldn't like imitate the behavior of these five kingdom keepers.
Right I had that thought as well but the thing that goes against it is the last
chunk of the book they are human and they are zooming through the trash can tubes.
Yeah. They are fighting the end of the book they are not holograms they were just themselves
in the daytime wearing but it is daytime it is daytime but they are wearing stolen
chaos memory uniforms and sneaking around and freaking servers and like messing stuff up.
But at that point they have no choice. They have no choice because Maleficent despite being
stabbed with a pen multiple times her power is drained but it could come back.
Yes right so I don't know I was looking around for this like as far as the author I don't think
was going to explain Ridley was not going to explain that like here's what Disney told me
I had to do or couldn't do but I wonder just because like getting through that setup I was
just like oh this seems like a little too complicated but maybe it was some reason.
Speaking of complicated I want to explain this now so since you said complicated I will talk about
what I've discovered all the variations of these books because if you remember back to Goosebumps
there were like a 30 or 40 in the original monthly run and then it became Goosebumps 2000
right because the millennial happened and then there were all these different
sub-series and spinoffs. Yeah yeah. There are seven books in the original Kingdom Keepers.
And then there is oh my god I gotta find it I kept discovering new like spinoff things so
I think after the main series okay there's the return right the kids thought they vanquished
the overtakers right but then it appears it is not they are not vanquished right and there's a
couple of those just in 2023 it appears the books have been relaunched Kingdom Keepers inheritance
and I'm going to read you this plot summary as I wanted to get your reaction on the air.
Good yeah. In the near future the Epcot of Walt Disney World's imagination 60,000 people live in
a communitry surrounding the forward-looking Walt Disney World theme park. Five unique families
are among the residents and some of the parents were once known as the Kingdom Keepers. Their
identities are carefully guarded in order to raise their children without special treatment.
Most of the Kingdom Keepers work for the Walt Disney Company and have settled into quote-unquote
ordinary and rewarding lives. When a messenger carrying a secret communication from Villains
Park in Hong Kong coincides with both a solar eclipse and Eli Whitman's 13th birthday,
a few quote-unquote ordinary kids are thrust into a battle to save Epcot and find their
friend who has mysteriously disappeared. With their friend missing and their parents acting
strangely, the Kingdom kids discover they're in possession of unusual powers as they forge
a bond to rescue their friend and uncover the truth about how real magic has entered their lives.
Oh my gosh the Kingdom Keeper babies. The Kingdom Keeper babies live in a real
Epcot. That's a good premise. I'll say this, that's a pretty good premise. You know what I
would do if I have to plus this up? I would say that the new Kingdom Keepers would be all the
different Disney vloggers. You know I would say that like Mr. Morrow is a Kingdom Keeper.
Ordinary Adventure are their Kingdom Keepers as well and it would be a whole fresh baked Disney is
a Kingdom Keeper at Disneyland. Now obviously these are not people that are official employees
of Disneyland. I'm just saying that would be my spin-off book and maybe you would call them
something. You wouldn't call them keepers. You would keep them what would be a good like
keeper. I guess keeper is such a good like watch, Kingdom watch. I guess they would be Kingdom
Watchers. They would be like, what is it in the Harry Potter books? Is it the Order of the Phoenix?
Like the dozen people that are like protecting the kids and fighting and dying. They watch over.
They watch over. They go to them for information and clues. So right, so like one of the 13 year
old Kingdom Keepers is fighting Maleficent but then like it looks like, oh it looks like uh-oh
the 13 year old is gonna get killed by Maleficent and then Mr. Morrow comes in like riding on like
a big like a stallion or something like the headless horseman's horse. Oh I was gonna say
Gracie the dog can grow and shrink and maybe rides in on her and then he sixes on Maleficent
and then yeah Mr. Morrow cuts off Maleficent's head. That would be traumatic for him. I don't
There is a moment in the book where they eventually solve the fable
of this. They solve the fable that all the Imagineers had not been able to solve
and then they acquire the quill, Walt Disney's first pen, and then they learn that Maleficent
wants its power but cannot touch it herself and also she gets injured if you stab her with it.
Right. Which I'm thinking like well just keep stabbing brother.
You would just keep. Yeah knock that out. Yeah that is one yeah would the modern Disney company
allow so much stabbing in one of their books these days because stabbing in general seems a
little aggressive. Well even just going back to the book would the modern Disney company
allow a lot of this stuff? Yeah sure. I was surprised that there was so much like yeah like
actual like cuts or burns happening to the children because you would think that I was thinking they
were going to get around it because they were holograms so they wouldn't actually like suffer
any damage. Yes. But I would think yeah that they they don't really want these days kids
thinking that the pirates are going to hurt them on Pirates of the Caribbean. Well yeah and I
I don't even even acknowledging that like yeah looked at it in a certain way small world
it's a little creepy you know even just that acknowledgement of like oh yeah it's creepy oh
if those dolls came to life and started following you that would be unnerving. So there is in the
first book a sequence where the dolls come to life on small world. Yes. And attack their
blood. Like start dog piling. Like dog piling and I was yes that that kind of shocked me because
okay pirates on Pirates of the Caribbean are bad guys. Yes. No doubt those pirates are bad dudes
they're burning down a town they're chasing people around and getting chased so yes makes total sense
there are villains Maleficent villain clear villain Emperor Zerg clear villain but then
the small world dolls there's no villain on small world. No. Those are all kids or Disney characters
that are all just representatives of like what the best of humanity has to offer living in harmony
in a perfect idyllic world that is all small world is. So the idea that Disney would allow him to
turn the dolls into evil little monsters is pretty wild. Well like that the dolls are evil
and it's like a horde of zombies almost. Yeah. And even acknowledging someone goes god that's
someone mentions the song's a little creepy. They have done I feel like they have mentioned like I
think it's okay in Disney now to say small world is a little annoying there's been jokes about that
for I feel like decades now but as far as the dolls being murderous not as much. Well yeah that
was very creepy to read it like midnight one night and it is a yes it is it is you could see
where that the lights would be off in there and that would be scary all a bunch of little dolls
coming to life a bunch of like Roberts yeah a bunch of Robert or Chuckie yeah that's a great
if there was ever a full horror park you would have to think there would be that would be a prime
ride of like a horror small world yes it could be filled with IP dolls it could be all original
but if it was like Chuckie's small world and it was just a bunch of murderous little dolls
yeah a song that would be scary and funny. Did you see I saw it just yesterday you can buy
a like simple Chuckie animatronic at like Home Depot or Lowe's or something now. Oh I feel like
I've seen that maybe this is the first year because they the animatronics are unbelievable
in the last couple years that you can buy at Lowe's yeah for your lawn so it doesn't I get
maybe I didn't see them when you're talking about but I have been very impressed by what you can
get for a couple hundred bucks like how crazy and elaborate things are and then when last year
when we went to Shacktoberfest there were these giant animatronics that I don't know that you
could get it at Lowe's but I was like Shacktoberfest is generally done on the cheap yeah so I was
impressed that like oh man these robots must not be so expensive but they're very impressive so
yeah well Dark Harbor is back I know this year and it seems like either new management or
some plus stuff stuff from what I've heard yeah I would I mean in Dark and Shacktoberfest was
Dark Harbor with just a shack overlay because all of a sudden it was just like Captain Shack there
was a lot of like a nautical shack happening at Shacktoberfest yes and this is down in the port
of Long Beach yes next to the historic Queen Mary which I think has also recently gotten a facelift
has it I think they were redoing some of those ruins those ruins were a little janky when I stayed
there oh yeah a few years ago um but hey there were 80 bucks a night so and it's like it was
weird it was crazy to stay on this historic vessel well there was a maze there was a haunted maze
in the Queen Mary last year which is cool and weird um so yeah so so there are murderous small
world dolls in this book the other they don't kill anybody but they're scary no you smile at
them and they and that yes we should have said yes they so the way that you stop small world
dolls from trying to kill you is you smile at them yeah I guess we should have said spoiler
alert but this book came out 19 years ago so yeah it's okay the the other chapter that was like
a little spooky was the splash mountain chapter oh yeah where they're like floating in the water
and then someone activates the logs and they're like stuck because the drop is coming up right
and I'm like that that I am surprised the Disney company let them get away with acknowledging like
oh yeah these currents in splash mountain if you go in the water it could really fuck you up
well that is interesting too because almost it's closer to almost like a mechanical failure
or something that could actually mechanically go wrong with a ride in some ways too which you would
think they would not want that as well yeah they you wouldn't want to people thinking like following
the line at the end of like oh wait if this happens then but then that was where it started
to get a little convoluted because they're floating in the water but they're holograms
and they can't get out or they'll trigger the alarm yeah but then sometimes they can turn to
pure light and walk through things I don't mean to give notes I'm just like oh I had a little
trouble following you know then they got in the log and saved the day okay great right so should
we go back a little bit like there is this is a very teen book yes it's very like uh oh my god
one of the characters thinks like girls are from another planet they're basically another species
I don't know what to make of them man so there's like a lot of that just general teen angst the
tension between girls and boys yes there but there's some like interest there's like butterflies in
the stomach and yes mutual attraction and almost seems like a love triangle was developing
and seems like it comes up from what I saw at the start of the second book where like
there's a magical girl named Amanda she's not a kingdom keeper but she's very important
and uh Charlene the cheerleader dhi she is a little jealous it seems like of Amanda
right uh and of Finn's attention that he gives Amanda right now look here's what I would say
if I had the task of being a kingdom keeper at 13 I don't have any time for girls okay oh yeah I
have a park to protect I have Walt Disney's memory and his history his legacy to protect
I don't have time for this girl stuff okay a hundred percent I mean even when I went on school
trips to parks I was like I'm here for the park I see you guys every day in school yeah it never
occurred to me like yeah I mean you I could maybe I had that same philosophy when it was like look
I'm in I'm in marching band I don't have time for girls okay I am married to my trumpet and I love
the work of John Philip Sousa and that's what I'm focusing on right now I don't have time
for all these butterflies all right sorry sorry ladies I'm busy I do have a very specific memory
in like summer theater one year a girl like I think she liked me and she was like hey it's been
really fun this summer and she like tried to hold my hand and I think I went hey stop we're about
to go on did you really like I didn't want to miss my cue I didn't want to miss my mark you know
I don't think you've ever told that story before I don't think I have I I it was get away from me
yeah we're gonna miss the what we were about to go on like in a crowd of like hey what's going on
like that kind of like rabble rabble like crap we were about we were like going on stage yeah we
were in the wings we're about to walk on stage and it's like now's not the time
I was a little strange she was a little strange like it wouldn't have worked it you know it
wouldn't you mean long term it wouldn't long term wouldn't have worked you know you could have
squeezed back I guess I guess so yeah wow I mean I think I have like 10 of those maybe in the last
oh yeah last so many years of high school sure college yeah maybe not 10 that sounds bragging
well I think I was like 12 like and I was like oh probably still very scared of like 12 or 13
I didn't know what was going on in fifth grade I believe my sister so so my sister was in a class
my sister's three years younger than me she was in a class with this girl in my class like so so she
was so they were in the same class I was in the class with that girl's sister okay uh and and my
sister's friend said oh I know your brother he's my sister's boyfriend she declared this okay this
was not something I signed off on this is not something I proved on and I remember it was my
sister's Chuck E. Cheese birthday I don't think I've ever told this story before uh in fifth grade
and I remember playing the basketball and then the girl in my class who declared that I was her
boyfriend without consulting me without even talking to me very much I remember her coming
over to me when like the family came to pick up her sister and she was just like talking to me
while I played basketball and I remember just like not making eye contact with her and being so scared
so freaked out because I felt this like energy from this fifth other fifth grader and I just kept
playing basketball and like one word answering this girl because I was so scared that she declared
me her boyfriend and I don't know that I ever even turned to look at her and I think I just kept
like feeding the machine to keep playing basketball at the Chuck E. Cheese I uh sit okay around fifth
grade I don't know if I told this story either okay I'm burning off of it uh I'm not gonna have
your seven of podcasts around you're burning off I don't think I at this point in fifth grade uh
there was the first school dance coming up we had just started middle school yeah there was
Halloween dance coming up I think it was just fifth and sixth grade and a girl asked me like
hey do you want to go to dance and I was like yes I'm going I can meet you there and like
because I didn't know I didn't know what I was supposed to do and we're all in cots I'm like
in a Frankenstein outfit and she was like do you have photos of this Cleopatra or something I don't
know I I don't think so please find them but I was so like I I was terrified and we like
she was like hi Jason we're at the dance and we danced together for like one second I'm just so
stressed out by everything going around me yeah and my mom was chaper or like hanging out in case
I freaked out like yeah there was a bunch of parents chaper because there was also a haunted
house in the gym which I did go through but I was terrified the entire time my goodness anyway me and
this girl uh we were friends through high school and uh I I am I was mortified I'm still mortified
that that was my reaction I was 10 years old I was a child yeah anyway she's a professor now she had
and what are you professionally you're a podcast I'm a podcaster
okay all right so well well I don't know hey we both seem to be doing what we love so I hope so
yeah yeah wow so so the book has has these you know these common things that happen very relatable
there is some weirdness you know I remember when I was this age and reading more like
young adult genre books and stuff looking at it now there are moments where adults try to write
like oh this character is a little into this character and it seems a little clunky a little
strange you know what I mean like Finn and Amanda's kind of like being interested in each other
are you saying this is clunky or you're saying other I'm saying like four other books are clunky
this it's a little you get it it's a little clunky there was one very weird chapter
where so there's a kind of a sinister girl named Jez
like Jezebel from the Bible that is very that is we all had a Jezebel in our class when we were 12
or 13 sure that name I'm not saying a type and she specifically says hey there's a girl scout
car wash fundraiser at dangerous dance use cars you should come and then they specifically write
about the girls having water fights and being in one piece bathing suits oh yes yeah yeah and that
was a little odd like I think that is a little yes you're correct a car wash fundraiser is
kind of a go-to for like teen movies and stuff but usually it's older girls uh yes it's not
usually 12 year olds yes yes I agree with you that is very strange I think it was more of a plot
device than anything else because you see Jeze run over to an SUV driven by a sinister figure
right but it's very strange of like the descriptions of like and then Jeze revealed
her purple one piece and her soaking wet hair and I'm like what what's happening yes I don't
know I that made it by Disney I guess I don't know if there's a I read that there were like
they've changed some of these books over the years I don't maybe I misread what I was like
they've changed it to reflect even what the current parks look like more oh okay but I don't know if
they got rid of this weird chapter I mean it's still in the library's digital copy right so I
mean no one's talking about let me ask the audience this do you does anyone have a friend
named Jez Jezebel is that ever who's I'm sure people have been named Jezebel but that really
feels like you're setting up your kid well I have a certain personality uh she she gets freed from
Maleficent's control sure and her hair is no longer white it's sandy blonde and she has a
redemption she has a redemption arc and her name is actually Jess I'm just saying like calling your
son Lucifer would be a bad idea I think well I think it's because she was a little evil it's
meant to convey she's a little of course it's meant to convey she's evil I'm just saying I just think
that that's a funny thing to name your child I'm just saying in the real world do we ever see that
is anyone actually bold enough to name their daughter Jezebel in the last no I don't think
but there has to be one negative connotation that's what I'm talking that's what I'm saying I'm
saying but has it happened ever all all I even I mean I don't know it from the Bible as much as
I know it from like Jim Ross calling an evil female wrestler well Jezebel she's a Jezebel when
he was calling WWE and I think he still says it sometimes if he's on AEW but I'm just saying if
anyone out there knows did they did you have a friend named Jezebel did you have a friend named
Lucifer let us know that's what I want to know any Damien that's a little more common a little more
common but you know no men still yes I would think you would think twice before naming someone
Damien but yes so so answer that question please in the comments or any other social medias
it is very funny when they like want to highlight specific Disney stuff like there's a chapter
specifically at the Wide World of Sports I know I love this I think this is so funny and I went
and explored the Wide World of Sports website a little and you can register now for spring training
oh you can for this is a topic in general we need to tackle I think we're so sports averse
that we have kind of stayed away from it but it's funny it's been there a long time
and I bet there's a bunch of interesting stuff we don't know we consider doing it during the NBA
bubble period that's true just couldn't get it together yes that's right so you can register
your baseball team or your softball team for Wide World of Sports spring training
okay so how does that so wait so how does that work you can you can register a full baseball team
yeah so I think you go and you do like uh exercises and you eat together
how long is your last I think it's like I think the period well I think you go for a few days
but the period that they're doing it lasts like a month oh spring training will be playing
March 10th to April 20th March 10th April so that's like almost yeah that's obviously a month
more than a month yeah so you could get I didn't even realize it so you pay a fee
you put a full baseball team together yeah well there's travel do you know about travel teams
yeah like kids so I think it's a sort of thing where they'll like go and do their spring training
before their season but okay so so you would bring a team of kids down there
yeah and they would just put them through the paces of training yes but could an adult team
could you put together a baseball team of adults and just have them run you through the drills
you think money hey if the money's there the money's right I bet so they don't have a full
like there's not actually a full league that happens after spring training at that complex
I don't think so but oh I mean that's a little too long for us to put a team together
well I was like do they do spring podcast training no could we no they don't do that
could we you know go and make our own curriculum and use the facilities oh you want to use you want
us to teach spring podcast training at the wide world of sports well we could I was I was thinking
we would get you know oh we would get you mean we would get trained well yeah we practice setting
up mic stands on topic no talk of al lewis what are you doing or more tangents we practice
we practice better doing better tangents yeah okay yeah uh perhaps who would be teach I don't know
who would teach that in Orlando yeah who's like I don't know Goofy Donald I don't know that the
characters teach spring training I bet they make an appearance in their little baseball because
Goofy does the baseball short yeah I want to that's just too long to do spring training but
man that is a if we could put together a team a baseball team in Orlando full of all the people
we know now down there sure and then but it would take them could we just do like a weekend
maybe I don't know I got to look into it's interesting I think I think the pitchers should
do like like Japanese baseball players when they're in high school yeah there is very
intense training and they'll like throw 500 pitches in one day well that's because they're
trying to like get their arm just unconscious like being able to sure yeah don't think about it
yeah I'm an old man I can't do 500 pitches in a day well but I don't I don't know how aggressive
you're never gonna make to the Tokyo Dome with that attitude well that is I that's true um my arm
will fall off though uh but I'll look into this because yeah like we got we got Mr. Morrow on the
team we got a bunch of different people I feel like oh you're putting you're putting podcasters
and vloggers Matt Cardona could be on the team sure Len Testa could be on the team yeah all the
different people down there Matt Cardona's fit he might be able to throw 500 pitches in it I don't
know though he's obviously an athlete and a pro wrestler but I feel like he doesn't care about
sports at all like real sports sure pro wrestling is a real sport but I'm just saying yeah I bet
I don't know I bet he I bet I could throw better than him that's what I'm saying oh it's everything
it's sport it's entertainment it's performance art right of course I yeah I didn't want to put
it down I'm just saying but I'm just but but still he'll be on the team I'm just saying I don't know
how good of a baseball player he is but man that's interesting that's interesting is all I'll say
but seeing it pop up in this book was very funny to me it's very funny I there there's I gotta
find it towards the end a lot of the end of the book takes place at Mickey's not so scary
Halloween party yes yes and the specifically uh chapter starts Mickey's not so scary Halloween
party the most fun of any of the park's special events was not to be missed uh-huh that felt like
if like a modern like a book taking place at Disney's catino uh real estate development yeah
like that felt mandate-ish you know that's a famous thing that people do a big that's
in a popular thing people do in Orlando it still felt like a little bit of an ad for
an upcharge event a ticketed event well but so that there is like official language like that
but then at some point ween is talking about where would maleficent hide where she would not be
noticed right because she's not in a ride right um uh and he says the only place she is at Disney
World she's in Fantasmic's and that's not the name of the show there's an s there's an s yeah
there's an s it's just Fantasmic's yeah Fantasmic I mean he's an older man maybe you know you know
older men sometimes put in a plural on something and they yeah they just don't know exactly even
though he's been around Disney for a long time uh yes could we talk real quick about Wayne so
Wayne worked with Walt Disney but we don't he wasn't he's never listed on one of like Walt's
old nine old man or anything no you never get a last name of Wayne which is making me wonder if he
is uh real or not if he I don't think that's what I'm getting a hallucination but he might be a
spirit of some kind that's what I'm wondering I wonder if in a further one of the future books
it's like revealed that Wayne is like a god or something or like god himself or something like
is Wayne is Wayne not really like yes he worked with Walt Disney in the way that god works with
all of us well I yeah he's Wayne I think Wayne and Amanda are connected there's a lot of alluding
to their to Amanda exhibits powers at one point right so and so they seem to know each other
and at some point when Wayne uh takes a borrows a bus and drives a bus so he is corporeal right
you know sure he pulls over at one point picks up Amanda and says like Amanda's very important
follower instructions uh-huh so I yeah I wonder and then well I don't know I don't know that I'll
ever read another full book I might read all of them I suspected you might want to read all of
them I kind of got hooked a few chapters oh interesting um Wayne so yeah Wayne I would
have just like Wayne to drop a credit be like you know I designed I actually drew Thumper's
tail or something or I yeah I um I'm the guy who had the idea to like give Geppetto that hair
yeah like like something claim to fame wise or even just like I was the assistant to Walt's nurse
uh which I always forget her name I always forget her name too but it's a good name she Michael
wow god damn it it's such a good reference too I'm so funny when I come up with that reference
on the top of my head and when I don't it's so disappointing to me Walt's nurse who worked on
his polo injury is named as I google as I google hazel george waltz nurse hazel george um and she
was of course friends with Michael Jackson uh and maybe maybe um this guy Wayne knew hazel george
and he would help like get the different like towels and ice packs or heat packs to help
nurse Walt's polo injury uh yeah maybe Wayne knew I I forgot about this fact what the man
who died at the Riviera polo field where Walt had his injury oh yeah when Walt killed that guy
I don't think but if Felix Winslow the owner of the famous Felix the cat right right right car
dealership uh in downtown LA right that still stands so I wonder yes does Wayne does Wayne
eventually reveal what he did with Walt I don't know but I would like I would have liked a little
piece of information there but yes as you as you said maybe he's more of a ghost I'll keep
investigating okay we'll see if I make it through I'm gonna try to make it through the main series
if it still has me right I'll see about the spin-offs or the sequels we can do a follow-up
episode once you're done with the main series or however long you want to go sure um and then you
can report back if Wayne reveals his credits because is it possible that Wayne like does some
magic and it's revealed to be the spirit of Walt Disney it's possible I feel like it is possible
that that happens but I don't know yeah it feels like another like another like risky thing
that Disney might not want directly to be Walt to be the likeness yeah but I don't know
maybe there were rumors there were rumors that Walt himself there was gonna be more like archival
Walt in Tomorrowland the movie the Brad Bird movie yes and then stuff like that stuff got
cut there was more direct references to Walt so they are very protective of the Walt
right well I have the there's like a 70 page document explaining the pre Tomorrowland
scavenger the mystery box yes all that pre-release stuff was very cool yeah that was awesome
really seemed interesting and was exciting and I would be interested to know what an early cut of
that movie was if it was actually like cooler because it tied into the actual like tied into
Disneyland more because the movie itself didn't quite feel that connected to the actual parks
yeah it was fine I feel like George Clooney and Hugh Laurie are pretty entertaining actors
even like a kind of cut down I don't remember anything past the house in the bathtub
I remember like kind of a CGI world post that with you Laurie but a lot of bathtub
business in the 2000s what other bathtub stuff are you thinking Indiana Jones and the crystal skull
well that's the I mean he does he get in a tub but he gets in the fridge oh he gets in a fridge
sorry I'm mixing a fridge in a tub is that because you store food in your tub sometimes
sometimes sometimes I need to cool down in the fridge or you have like a big side of beef that
is just too big for your fridge and you need to like put a bunch of ice in the well I have the
Flintstones ribs oh when you buy your Flintstones ribs yeah you can't you gotta go to Aldi they have
the best deals right so you get a bunch of bags of ice dump it in the tub and then you put your big
Flintstones ribs well yeah in between triple a coming because my car tipped over because it was
so big your car is always tipping over always tipping over from the giant Flintstones Aldi
funny detail from the very end of the book where they they do at least temporarily
um get maleficent uh and they do oh yeah yeah the end it does involve a trash
chute chase and a big net yes which I thought was very satisfying as a as a kid I was always
like I was either scared of big nets or I was like oh yeah they got him used a big net
you know you were scared of getting caught by a big net well I knew they were very powerful
I mean that's a lot of cartoons big nets you know well quicksand's in that Indiana Jones fourth
Indiana Jones movie that's right yeah um I'm trying to think if I was afraid I was afraid
of quicksand as a kid big nets though I think I just respected them well yeah yeah well when
you say big net do you think of like a big butterfly net or a net that's like on the ground
that you walk into and then it like pulls up in the tree either are both very powerful because
the big net on the ground that would pull you up into a tree I feel like was very common and I was
maybe afraid of that because I've seen that a bunch I just knew if you if a dog escaped you had
to get a big net on hold and catch it that was the guy that was a dog catcher instrument
for sure I feel like Heathcliff episodes would have that a lot yes and any any animal cartoon
would have that but I but the big net I feared more I think in Ninja Turtles three they get
caught in a big net okay and and they would always make us like the big net would always
seem like it was impossible to get out of well and the end of this book too there are a bunch
of adults that just showed up with a big net and why didn't they help those children the rest of
the time uh-huh there's a lot of like I think in real life if Disney had to do this they would make
uh like seal team six holograms and they would just take out Maleficent you mean in real life
if Disney had to combat evil spirits in their yeah they would just hire a bunch of ex-CIA
ex-special forces but you would need like religious people too in some ways because
their spirit like there there's talk of them being spirits as well I feel like that's true
there's talk of how like it's pure evil like Walt knew that like what they describe somewhere
that because so many people come to the parks and believe in everything that just by a it's a
by-product of all these like thousands and thousands of people believing so hard in all
these characters that then the the good characters come to life but then the bad characters who are
evil come to life and Walt knew this was a possibility and because of that that's why
all of these different confusing things that we've talked about have to be put in place
to combat evil spirits um so there's a mystical religious quality in my mind to that but maybe
it's maybe I'm maybe I'm just projecting I don't know maybe I'm just putting that on it I don't
know well I think you need to have like a you're forgetting the magic words story imagination
that's true dreams wishes like a disney you need like a specific disney priest yes like a disney
like somebody's like steeped in disney religion they need who knows the history of everything
who knows the archivist yes you need the guy who started the archive right but we should call
yes an archivist like a disney high priest yes who knows who can do like sort of a religious
ceremony who knows the difference between claude coats and mark davis maybe that's that could be
like um the fuddy duddy mayor's assistant in ghostbusters he was like I'm shutting this maybe
in later books there's like a disney legal becomes a hologram and it's like this is dangerous you
can't keep doing that and then he comes around when he's confronted by the powers of chernobog
sure yeah I think in later books chernobog becomes a big enemy yes I did read that chernobog becomes
from from fantasia chernobog chernobog is scary he's very scary chernobog is the devil in my mind
yeah because chernobog doesn't even have much of a personality it's sort of just a pure
evil entity yes um is wait I'm now I'm mixing up what I read in future books in this in this
book do they mention that Mickey got caught on fire at phantasmic and fell into the lagoon
I believe they did I think so yeah which is another thing where I was like ah they wouldn't say that
in these days especially since Mickey almost caught on fire yeah recently I saw a clip of a
phantasmic at Disneyland recently where it's just there's no Mickey at the end it's just lights and
stuff right and it's like what did they cost cut or what went well there's no dragon now
at all at all I don't think it's the big like cherry picker maleficent right it's regular
maleficent she's just she's just 25 feet in the air yeah but they haven't I supposedly though
they're working on something dragon wise I don't know if that is true or not but something
eventually will come to phantasmic but yes they say Mickey caught on fire and fell into the water
well because there's weird things happening everywhere that the over the overtakers broke
in and stole a bunch of padlocks from a hardware store right which seems like you know that's not
as big of a crime as setting Mickey on fire in my mind yeah one is more egregious than the other
there's a funny moment I don't have the exact wording but they're talking earlier in the book
about like where the clues where the clues and one of them says like maybe the answer is in
Disneyland and I feel like they brush it off like a substance line of like no no the answer is
definitely here like they're like yeah that is a good point that is the park Walt was in
right right I know they eventually the series does go to Disneyland yes but not here this is
exclusively Orlando in this book uh yeah it specifically to the point where at one point
it says like okay let's all meet at the statue of Roy O. Disney
I that stuff all the specificity of all that stuff would make me laugh every time when they're like
let's go to one man's dream one man's dream playing a crucial role in this first book is very funny
yes and I love because these books are very popular or were very I mean I'm sure there's
still a big fan base for them yeah eventually I forget what number book there was a book that
like was like written by the fans like crowdsourced essentially oh has to be well no this is I was
listening to the author talk about it like there was a website set up and like there would be
people that would write their own fan fiction and I don't know exactly know how it worked but
I think he took like 37 different like readers suggestions and then they like wrote the final
book or whatever version or series it was well do you know about um an archive of our own I
think it's called no it's a giant repository of fan fiction oh okay and you could search any
character any story could you search Jason Sheridan from podcast the ride with that papa oh gosh I
don't know because I mean I assume it's mostly literary characters yes it's like could you
Harry Potter Star Wars kind of fan fiction right but could it be Jason could it be podcast or maybe
I don't know I have to poke around could it be you in the Kingdom Keeper series
oh boy as a 12 year old well but you say that I think later on their senior year in high school
they're finishing their senior year in high school so if you defending the Magic Kingdom
and anytime a girl gets close to you you go get away from me hey we have stuff to do we
are defending the Magic Kingdom I have show tunes to listen to also in addition to this I if this
had come well if these books had been published like five years before oh that would have been
like you would have been six years before if when I was going a lot to Florida yeah if I had seen
these books in the MGM Studios bookstore right uh that had goosebumps and I saw these I would be like
I need this right now right if you if there was a book series that that climaxed in one man's dream
Disney's MGM Studios I loved one man I even the last time I was down there I
I thought it was a very nice like museum yeah I thought it was cool I thought it was great it's
very funny to compare that exhibit with the Walt Disney Family Museum in San Francisco which is
very detailed but much more frank about a complicated man sure but the Disney sanitized
version of Walt is very effective they do a good job in general other excuse me other than when
they're doing like kind of the Walt fan fiction of like trying to justify that Walt needed them
to build a bunch of houses out in the desert like other than that stuff it's like Epcot fun myth
the fun like sanitized Walt Disney story is always very they they do a good job of
telling it and keeping the myth of it and I assume the robot Walt next year will do will continue
this tradition now if they have anything about Katino in the Walt robot show at Disneyland I
will be very interested I would be very impressed I would love that I don't think he'll say like
at the like his last sentence would be like and also Disneyland will never be finished
and in 80 years I'd like to build a series of homes out in the middle of the desert called
Katino in tribute to smoke tree ranch I feel like I saw one of the houses is the Incredibles house
oh this just did come out yes I didn't I was like no we're not that campy but like it's like one
house is the Incredibles house and the rest are normal houses is that what it is I think there's
other thematic houses coming but they're not going to be like a row of Incredibles houses on
the street I can't speak to that so like the richest people on the block how many millions
is that house gonna well that's what I'm saying so the richest people in that like whatever you
call it subdivision or something will own the Incredibles house so you'll know like oh we live
in the Incredibles house like those are the those are the fancy people on the block even though I'm
sure all that stuff is going to be very expensive they'll all be fancy on some level but yeah
the fanciest people will live in the Incredibles house I saw there's like pictures or art I guess
art of it yeah like and it is like the mid-century modern very tall ceiling yeah which is a cool
looking house it does look cool but is it going to be like that Simpsons house that they built
years ago for that promotion yeah somebody didn't move in I don't know that may be an episode for us
oh yeah we got to look into that because I think we all tried to enter yes like I want to live in
that house sure I wanted to too but they built Simpsons house in the middle of nowhere
and I think they just in the last couple years had to like demolish it or do something with it
yeah um some other stuff from the books cool BMX bike chase at one point yes Amanda and Finn both
know how to ride their bikes up and down uh ramps and stuff in a skate park yes they are about to
clothesline someone on a mini bike who is chasing them yes it is never quite revealed I guess it's
assumed that's maybe Jess or Maleficent right um but uh what else yeah there's a cool dinosaur
chase a big thunder yeah so so there's a this is I this is I like this a lot the the skeleton
of the dinosaur on big thunder comes to life so this is because you're thinking about like well
what would happen at Disneyland and this is one of the things that I think is very fun and imaginative
and it would be good in a movie I guess what I'm saying that would be a good set piece in a movie
yeah and it's like it's not it's not uh destroying you know it's not like sacrilege
like the small world dolls coming to life and being killers you know it just feels fun well
this is just a monster this is a dinosaur you know it doesn't know any better it's all it's been
reanimated now I think this is a set piece in night at the museum the like oh yes fossils come
to life and chase Ben Stiller yes that is right um I feel like that is that is something a kid
in general would when they see those fossils is like well is this going to come to life
rooting around on the dark catwalks of space mountain was I never considered it but I'm like
oh I would like to do that that sounds cool so I mean just in general like going on the track in
space mountain has always been kind of interesting yeah in general I mean I've seen we've seen videos
now of space mountain with the lights on so it's not like so mysterious it just looks like kind of
you know metal and oh I've seen it I've been on the people mover and it's been oh yeah we
last time we were there I think in Orlando I think that happened to me at least yeah we went
through it and was full lights on so you could see it and it's like you know it's not so exciting
but yeah that as a kid especially you know it would be very exciting to go in the catwalk I
was trying to think too like what else we've talked many many times on the show about where
you would want to kind of linger or host like like like host a party I was going to say that's not
really what I meant but like yeah where you would want to chill out and it's like I think we've
talked about like the pie in have we talked about like sleeping in the bed with the skeleton and
pirates of the Caribbean oh sure yeah so so stuff like that um but that's more as an adult that's
more where I'm thinking versus being out in space I would like to cuddle the pirate with the pigs
I'd like to scoot in there cuddle a pig put my head on the pirate's tummy well and also you're
gonna be in the slop then yeah you'll be covered in slop sure right which would you assume is mud
but also probably fecal matter um it's just slop it's a mix don't think about it too hard well it's
not like is there a trough right by the pirate and the pig on pirates of the caribbean good question
did he get the pigs out of a pen or did they wander out in the chaos right did he act I
because it doesn't it's not near like a pig area right he's just in a butt like a muddy pile with
the pig and he's drinking I assuming he's giving the pigs some moonshine or something as well is
he a park star is there a park star the pig yes I gotta go through my boxes that is a park
star if I have it I don't think I actually have the or no maybe I do um yeah that's not a bad one
that's a that's another chill out chilled out place uh to hang but yeah he doesn't also seem
like he's not that aggressive of a pirate because he's been sedated probably by his drinking yeah
but yeah but Space Mountain is interesting I almost think that I was thinking that they
were going to do it with these books make it a little more like fantastical like Space Mountain
actually was a journey to space oh you know what I'm saying because they actually are treating the
rides a little bit more functional they're very functional right as opposed to like saying well
actually did you know Space Mountain actually does take you to space you think it's actually
just a small building with a roller coaster inside but actually these vehicles do take you
to space now I don't know if this happens in future books but I was thinking it would be more
along those lines where when you go on pirates it actually is you actually now are in the reality of
what 100 years ago 200 years ago yeah um but that isn't what it is it is mechanical it is Space
Mountain is a roller coaster there's just stuff that happens and things come to life because of
thousands of millions of people who believe yes but I'm also like has to be in the new
the later books like well all the bad guys are coming to life and controlling animatronics
right why don't they have allies of good guys who come to life for good guy animatronics you know
well right and then anytime you see Pooh Bear he's just hanging out or like early on in the
book they're like hey is that Tom Sawyer Tom Sawyer yeah shows up once from the distance and
is never mentioned again right this that had to drive you crazy because you're like I want to
hang with Tom very funny Tom Sawyer's smoking a big pipe he is smoking that's that's surprising
like I want a Tom Sordick come over and offer them like snuff or tobacco you want a hit of this kids
yeah how old is Tom Sawyer he's probably about 30 same age yeah yeah okay yeah because you would
we would think it would be like a perfect opportunity I mean Tom Sawyer is not a
Disney doesn't own Tom Sawyer anymore that's a public domain character at this point
but yeah you would think that they would have teamed up with some of these characters
yeah in some ways and maybe again maybe it happens in one of the future books but
I was yeah also expecting something like that to happen because there's plenty of good characters
in Disneyland yeah absolutely certainly the good heroes outweigh the bad yeah but like
speaking of good characters I do have to mention yeah as a product of the early 2000s I feel like
Charlene and Willa are not really fleshed out sure they're not given a lot right I kept getting
confused of like which is the nerd and which is the cheerleader yeah because in the second book
they sort of reintroduce everyone and like any series they you know like a jack you pick up a
jack creature mogul with the first chapter or two they're like he hitchhikes around he only carries
his like ID debit card and passport right and a toothbrush and like if he has a cell phone he's
stolen it from a bad guy right right he's using it so there the second book kind of reestablishes
everyone including a very weird paragraph where they're like Charlene's growing up very fast much
more a young woman than a child just seems more like 18 than 14 and I'm like all right slow down
there slow down there buddy uh-huh uh so and she is very annoyed at Amanda at the start of the second
book got it because they kind of disappear at the end of the first book and then they reappear
there's a weather balloon there's monkeys there's an electrical storm it's a very exciting start to
the second book so it's hooked me oh wow um yeah I um you brought up those characters I don't know
that I would have been able to pull them off the top of my head yeah um I'm looking through some
of my notes here and uh all I all I have is about them and their costumes that they wore when they
met at and this is another thing that made me laugh they met at the ticket and transportation center
on Sunday morning which again in some sort of an adventure book to say and we met at the ticket
and transportation center at Disney World is hilarious and this is you were mentioning this
earlier when they have to all wear disguises or costumes yeah and Wayne has set up uh tarps in the
bus modesty tarps so the girls can change in the back and the boys can change at the front
and the costume can I read the costumes yes uh Finn is a Tom Sawyer paper boy which what does
that mean does Tom Sawyer paper boy in the story it's kind of a mix no I think it's mixing up like
Newsy style paper boys and Tom Sawyer Charlene is dressed as a paddle wheel boat deckhand
okay Willa is a restaurant server Maybach wears the clothing and turban of a crew member at the
Aladdin carpet ride and Philby is a jungle cruise captain but uh Maybach is tall yes so
at some point they uh he gets in a crowd they mistake him for Aladdin and kids want his
autograph right yes yes I though I believe the quick log line rundown is like Finn is a leader
uh Maybach uh is black uh Philby is British Willa is a nerd and Charlene is pretty
that's how it's done uh-huh oh yeah but there's a diverse that's diverse there it is it is a
diverse line yes it they are multiple races and stuff as are Amanda and levels of 13 year old uh
hot yeah yeah okay uh um so uh Finn is a friend named Dillard who is annoying that yes they don't
really they the poor guy gets dumped on a lot uh does anyone know a person named Dillard is there
a Dillard in our audience that's an interesting name too Dillard that is Dillard Archie universe
is it Dillard is that his name is it uh no is it Dilton Dilton is the name it's someone's
Dilton Doily is the name I think Dilton Doily is the character you're thinking of and is she
is he Mage's sister is Dilton Dilton is someone's uh brother brother brother sorry
getting too excited Dilton's significant other Betty Cooper and Cheryl Blass I mean I guess they
all dated each other at some point um character resembling Dilton uh family character background
Dilton is depicted as a stereotypical nerdy teenager um hmm I don't hmm his teachers
particularly professor flutes newt are very proud of his achievements coach keats um I don't know
I don't know who he's really moose mason is Dilton's closest friend Dilton's other close
friends Archie Betty Jughead Jones he helped the gang many times with his various inventions or
with his vast knowledge who did you say he's related to I thought he was related to moose's
girlfriend hmm I don't know you're gonna have to look that up on your own I don't know
Dilton's relation I mean we should definitely find that we could bring this podcast to a halt
until we find out who Dilton is related to um but Dillard yeah Dillard I've never heard that
name before even in fiction I'm not sure I've heard of it as a department store name because
it's so it's one lettered one letter away from Dillard yeah which I I think he didn't really get
a read he should have a redemption arc Dillard yeah he should become rise of I thought I thought
him and Amanda were going to become kingdom keepers oh right but Amanda keeps saying her
family works in administration right so she can kind of go anywhere right which I think is mostly
a plot device who do you relate to more of with all these when you come to all these characters
well in all these books I always wanted to be thin the cool leader okay Finn who feels like
nerdy and unconfident yeah and then all the girls seem to like thin okay but he in the in
the introduction of the second book they mentioned that Philby is British has a shock of red hair
right and all the girls like him but he is mostly concerned about computers and rock climbing he
loves every weekend hitting the climbing wall right I feel like I'm more of a philby
do you yeah okay even though I don't like rock climbing but I like rock and roll
yeah so it's a different kind of rock but I I don't know I don't know that I identify with
anyone too strongly here it seems like all the girls did like you no all the girls do not like
you tell these stories and certainly when we were in the improv world you had some admirers
yeah there were certainly admirers there were admirers I that is true I I certainly once I got
older I realized that I was I when I was younger I thought I had no admirers and then when I got a
little older I realized there were admirers I just was pulling my hand away I was staring straight
ahead at the basketball machine well you had a child with one of them well so that was later
that was later yeah yeah that was fine that was good but yes yes that was fine I did not do no
one should feel bad for me I've said that no one should feel bad what was me I was a little dork
or anything there were nice people that were interested that would have given me a smooch
if I was comfortable with it I just wasn't comfortable with it and I didn't realize I
wasn't comfortable with it until years later yeah that is so I don't want to and I don't want to
act like I'm I was mr macho cool guy either I'm not I'm not saying oh my god everybody liked me
that's not what I'm saying either I'm just saying I was too scared at and I didn't realize it until
a very late age oh what was going on about all of it so I look if Phil Philby is I don't know
who was more attractive the lazy was it Finn was it Philby I don't know I liked I liked Philby I
would have thought he was funny I think as a kid that's really what I cared about he knew all the
facts he knew all the facts related to that yeah they say at one point like and if he didn't know
something he knew how to look it up right I think you were probably you would have been a mix of
Finn and Wayne very old man the very old man mysterious man who worked with wall pretty annoying
at the end if by the end of the book I'm like I didn't just tell them I did not care for Wayne
yeah I was kind of a little creep I was annoyed with Wayne the whole book and early on in the book
I was very annoyed with Wayne because I'm listening to the audiobook and I'm and like Wayne keeps
saying these cryptic things look over what do you think why are you here and this is verbatim when
he said like why are you here what are you doing and Finn would just be like I don't know what's
going on and he keep asking these questions and questions and I'm like Wayne god damn it just tell
this poor kid what's happening he was so mysterious you're like just tell him what's going on Wayne
stop being annoying so yes I was irritated with Wayne the whole time and he never came fully clean
and maybe eventually he doesn't explains why he was being so mysterious but I don't buy it
I think Wayne was being annoying yeah he was annoying so I I don't I'm not a big Wayne fan
at this point you will tell me later when you read all 20 of these books if Wayne gets cool
let's let me get through the first seven then we'll see about the return and inheritance series
I hope it's not stolen valor as far as like working with Walt or he's lying to him about
working with Walt I want I want them to meet in another Imagineer and they say like Wayne
if it's who I'm thinking of he died years ago and it's like he's some sort of ghost or benevolent
spirit I was hoping you were going the way of like they run into an old Imagineer and they go
oh yeah I know one of your colleagues Wayne and that guy goes Wayne that guy delivered coffee to
us once and now he goes around talking about how he worked with Walt yeah bullshit he worked with
Walt he got in the door one time and he was too annoying he kept pitching Walt a bunch of movies
different Hans Christian Andersen movies bullshit that guy we had to kick him out we he would stand
outside the gates of the Walt Disney Studios yelling stuff and holding up signs he had multiple
scripts about the continuing adventures of the Breyer characters and uncle Rivas he's where like
times have changed Wayne he wanted to make 10 sequels the song of the south he wrote it up
in the bible and he kept slipping it under the gate and giving it to security guards
Wayne give it up Wayne give it up Wayne give it up you old crook so hopefully that
happens hopefully they reveal that yeah later on in the book but yes I don't like Wayne
the kids were fine but Wayne got Wayne was too much for me that it's funny yeah I didn't think
I liked all the kids but Wayne was so cryptic it was very like master splintery at first and then
it's like Wayne you're making this so much harder for everyone just tell them same with Amanda like
you're not ready like just tell him right so yeah I don't know if he knew at the start what
Wayne was doing or he was just like kind of a lazy writing thing where it was just like I don't know
yet Wayne will just say hey you'll learn it later you know they have set up there's three guys and
two girls in the kingdom keepers yeah and then there's Amanda and Jess and there's also Dillard
I think this is enough where everyone could theoretically couple up by the end of the books
oh if the girls are real if they're not spirits oh you think some of these girls are spirits
well Amanda has powers Jess did have powers and then Finn hologrammed through her how old is Snow
White in the movie Snow White she is young are they all third all the Disney princesses they never
really acknowledge it are they all 13 is 16 in the original fables yes right so hypothetically
Dillard could get with oh Dillard could marry Snow White or Snow White right which would be
interesting it would be interesting you think that happens in a future book I have seen like
fantasy stuff in movies where like isn't that a thing in Enchanted she comes to the real world
and marries Patrick Dempsey right okay if you if they were uh your same age or you were their same
age who would you take as a bride that's in disneyland oh gosh oh uh not of the keepers like
no of a character right or a friend I mean we don't have to make this romantic it could be
just a friend yeah or or yeah see what happens you'd be interested in going on a date with
so-and-so who it has to be a robot or like a face character or a costume character yeah
I mean cinderella seems very interesting she has an interesting back she does seem
interesting the filth of humanity well you're marrying into money and that becomes royalty
well is the prince dead in that scenario well if you kill him he is oh okay do I oh I become
oh you could I'm just saying you could prince jason you become prince jason um I think I would
I don't know it'd be cool to be friends with like Flynn Rider and Rapunzel they seem very chill
sure I was thinking I could go out with the Alice and Janie robot on star tours oh yeah she seems
very cool yeah like a kind of like she's got obviously she's like a flight attendant
she's got a job she's got a job got a got a career she's on top of her stuff she knows like
she's good at her job confident well put together confident good voice great voice yeah so I'm not
saying I'm going to commit to marrying her in this alternate universe but we'll see where it goes
sure we'll see where it goes I don't know if she she should appear in some future I don't what is
the character's name what is the droids I don't know name we should look that is something we
should do we haven't done the second star tours either oh good we've only done the original version
there's been a lot of changes there has been a lot of changes that is for sure all right go to cosmic
rays also in the book they do yes for juicy burgers some juicy burgers okay that is confusing when
there are holograms they may back makes them turkey burgers right they're turkey I don't
forget that detail specifically it says he makes them delicious turkey 20 years ago they serve a
turkey burger at cosmic rays apparently that's well that was they don't serve turkey burgers now
that was the healthy option no now it's impossible burgers right so so do you think they did in 2005
serve turkey burgers I think that was the if you're trying to watch your figure
you're having a turkey burger instead of a hamburger no I hear you I'm just saying it seems
even for 2005 it seems it seems impossible that they would have served turkey it seems like dad
would be so upset if he saw that on the menu in 2005 in Florida yeah but let me let me let's look
into that because that is interesting it was just a little confusing some time like so they have
they're hungry they get hungry when they're holograms when they're holograms right but they
can also float in water but they can go through stuff right but they're still trying to master
that power like kitty pride of the x-men right so yeah I assume they get more powers as the series
goes I'm guessing yeah I would think because yeah Finn phased through Jess enough that it made her
good again much like kitty probably can phase through computers and short circuit them right
yes so I assume they may be ascend to these like godlike figures perhaps by the end maybe
where they're kingdom keepers now it is interesting that the kids we've kind of touched on this the
heroes of the park are not the heroes these are just random kids that have as you said a certain
set of skills well so you the reader can imagine yourself in their positions I am very curious that
the last book is like senior year in high school do they start asking each other to prom right oh
interesting you think maybe that's maybe a full book of like trying to get up the nerve yeah
because like do Amanda and Jess stick around does Finn ask Amanda right does Dillard end up going
with one of the does Dillard get into the crew maybe Jason goes solo but he brings a little pig
from pirates with him as a buddy I would love that if you showed up at your senior prom with a little
pig you think I'd be the hit I was gonna say that people would have been gone would have been
going nuts going nuts yeah man that would have been a good move I would have spent all my time
with a photo guy handing off the pig everyone's a picture with the pig right and then the pig
would give you a little kiss at the end of the night oh that'd be a dream yeah it's safer than
my prom date who had laryngitis where I like I guess I'm not getting a kiss tonight she had
laryngitis yes she was very ill and looking back I'm like you should not have come
yeah you also shouldn't have shouldn't have bothered sleeping on the floor of our friend's
house like we all slept on the floor in the basement that night yeah it was complicated
she was secretly dating one of our other friends you've talked about yeah it's very complicated
very complicated right but you if you were writing your own kingdom keepers you would
put this drama in there oh sure yeah yeah now I was thinking about this I probably would have
pined for mana but I should have asked Willow right we we probably had the most in common and
I didn't see it I was blinded by the allure of distant people yeah I feel like as a kid what
would have been my fantasy would it have been fighting Maleficent in Disney World or would it
have been moving into Disney World full-time permanently I think it would be the second one
that would be if I'm I don't we're not jumping necessarily to full critiques or plus-ups I guess
but maybe we can um is that you take sort of your all the things I've said over the years on this
podcast about what I liked about x-men what I liked about Star Trek the Next Generation
and what I assume kids like about Harry Potter is that you would go into the special little place
you'd have your own little room everything there makes you feel special it's got its
own type of food it's got its own way you get your food and then you hang out with your friends
from fiction and yes x-men you're fighting Harry Potter you're fighting Star Trek you fight
but the real lure of it to me as a kid was getting to go to a special place where you felt special
that was very unique and had like whimsical magic in different ways happening yeah so I wonder if
they ever move permanently into the Magic Kingdom or the the Ticken and Transportation Center or
the different the Utila doors I wonder if that's an aspect eventually that happens because
I would think that as a kid you would be like I want to move into Cinderella's castle
yes I want to sleep in Dopey's bed on the Snow White ride okay I want to live in the in the
jewel mine on Snow White it it seems like at the end like a bunch of magic they get the pen
they hit the magic a drop of ink falls on the magic plans right and then all this magic and
fireworks very similar to the ending of the Power Rangers movie where they're all like yeah
and there's fireworks that everyone celebrates yeah yeah yeah Van Hagar Dreams one of my favorite
Van Halen songs I think they should have used their magic to clean up 2005 era 2006 era Magic
Kingdom well because when I I think I went to Disney World the summer of 2006 it was very
rainy on and off and it looked a little worse for wear up people eyes yeah and then I came to LA
and saw Disneyland just looked immaculate because they had just had the 50th I was like they should
have cleaned up it doesn't mention the Magic Kingdom looking a little worse for wear one
kid should have been very good at being a janitor and his power was picking things up and making
sure everything looked good and he could have had like a little bucket of paint with him like magic
should be painting yeah you should be painting or there's apparently one guy right now in Epcot
like one um I saw this on Twitter one guy going around and like fixing effects
fixing lighting fixing a guy who works at Epcot yeah like a maintenance operations guy
this is what the rumor mill says although that said the glowing floor uh the glowing ground
they added by special birth is apparently broken and can't be fixed unless they dig it up
is that true I don't know oh okay the way you were setting it up in my mind I was thinking
there's like a vigilante going around Epcot painting like like somebody who's self-deputized
no he's on the payroll but he may have taken this on as a project but maybe that is what
needs to happen because like in Batman Batman takes it upon himself because the police can't
get things done so he's he deputizes himself as the law yeah so maybe that's what has to happen
at Epcot center is that somebody decides they're Batman but instead of like beating up criminals
or super villains they go around with a bucket of paint and different lights new light bulbs
yeah to change things out because somebody's got to do it yeah and maybe it's up to a very
enthusiastic fan to put on a costume and go around to fix things well they should they should be
people working for the company and vigilante so you get the whole Bat family they all have different
Nightwing and Asriel and different approaches you know sure but like Batman or if a really ambitious
Batman who's just like I'm gonna go fix the Yeti on Expedition Everest when the park is closed I
know what to do yeah I know how to get that thing working again if they fix the Yeti I think that
would get them like six months to a year of goodwill right where it would just be you mean
they vigilante or you mean Disney itself I mean I mean Disney itself it Disney itself fixes the
Yeti for real but what if there's like a real like tech nerd who can put on a costume and in
the dead of night sneak into Expedition Everest and fix that Yeti that would be great yeah and
then that would be a hero yeah some people in the company Disney would be like upset upset with this
his tactics he's not going by the book but then there'd be like one guy in the company who's like
no he's good he's a force for good around here maybe maybe they get one of those in later books
like a guy who's like who's gonna fix things I heard the rumors of the kingdom keepers
so I've deputized myself to be a keeper they're like no it's too dangerous like one you're not
a hologram it'll get hurt like this Batman type figure who like every night changes a little
piece of journey into your imagination back to the original ride yes slowly but surely slowly
building slowly building a dream finder animatronic in there yeah somebody yeah somebody
selflessly fixing things I don't know I don't know like what you would even call like a Batman version
imagine I don't know we got to come up with a name here is what I'm saying really like a dream in here
dream in here but it'd have to be like it would have to be a fix in here fix in here man like man
or like super it would have to have kind of a superhero name or I guess the Punisher is a
vigilante the fix the imaginer the imaginer okay that's good yeah yeah imaginer and it's got like
he's got like a symbol on or he whoever has a symbol on their chest of like of like a cast
member badge but it's fucked up yeah it's a little fucked up and then there's like they're
holding like a wrench or something yeah they're holding a little wrench to fix things like a wrench
and a light bulb in the other skeleton hand yes and if it's like paint around the neck like a
bucket of paint like hanging off their neck sure and they go around and fix the parks they just
want to do what's right that's our only drive right it's like I've got to fix this right the
imaginer and if he wards off overtakers this will be it this is not a bad idea for a series of books
yeah the imaginer and then yeah so though you would have like park employees and then you would I
guess you could tell the story from the perspective of guests and there's like some mystery there and
and then eventually you can start to do stories from the perspective of the imaginer and yeah
that's good the imaginers like cave well I'll take something from Jack Reacher some of the books are
written in the third person right some of the books are written in the first person okay so you
hear Jack Reacher's thought you flip around yeah because like at the start of Batman you're kind
of in the perspective of the criminal right away and then Batman shows up so you get to like see
what the fear is like for this mysterious character yeah and then eventually you are
in the back cave and you're like experiencing the story through Batman's point of view oh man
imagine the imaginers the imaginer that's what we're going I think we've determined the imaginer
he's like uh alford or microchip like his helper right his man in the chair you know I kept
imagining the dillard character as the character from the disney stony spider the guy who's like
I'm your man in the chair who is that character the friend Peter Parker's friend in the movies
who was his friend in the movies do you not remember like the the bigger kid oh in the new
movie in the new movie yeah Ned yeah yeah I like Ned I like Ned too yeah I I for some reason I
was thinking about the uh toby mcguire movies oh no yeah Ned he has like no friends in the
toby mcguire movie which I guess is I don't know I feel like in the comics traditionally
Peter Parker has a giant friend group Betty Brant and Flash Thompson that's a whole discussion about
like how cool he should be he's kind of the 90s spider-man cartoon he's kind of cool actually
yeah he's like handsome and cool and that was not necessarily what it is but then he was also funny
and he's different kinds of funny that's a whole look running we're running low on time here for
this episode sure but they should they they're back to square one right uh they should do a spider
and I'm assuming they're going to do like street level spider-man oh look if you believe the
rumors there's a push and pull at Sony about do we want more multiverse or do we want street level
so that's all I don't know that's all rumors right now but that's that pops up into my feed right
from time to time yeah so we'll see but the imaginer is what we care about this new character
we've created the series of books that we're going to write or you'll write and I'll edit
he can be like a Casey Jones figure for the kingdom keepers yeah well he's not a part of
the king he's a different he's our he's different uh yeah but maybe we'll cross over at some point
maybe we'll get our own multiverse going like we'll have a series of books called the imaginer
but then we'll have the other series of books like I'm talking about living and they'll be called
like yeah the park livers park livers they'll be called the park livers well that sounds like
liver though I hear what you're saying but that's unfortunately the name of it is the park oh okay
we'll workshop it no I didn't know okay all right determine the title no notes got it the park
livers and their kids that go and live in the park and they decide where they're going to live
and then they just sort of exist and they have the you know the romantic situations they have the
normal growing up stuff it's just now they live in the different disney parks I think if the magic
continues at the end of every book they should summon the unbuilt magic kingdom resort they
should summon the persian resort the venetian oh well that's good for the kingdom keeper series
yes I think or or I guess the imaginer if he fixes everything in the parks could start to build
he could start to build port disney out here he could start to build westcott he could start
slowly demolishing california adventure and sure westcott which is what we all want sure people
stop him like to have a permit I don't need a permit I do what I want yeah he starts just
putting more classic characters and prequel characters on rise of the resistance I don't
need this is what the people want they want to see their friends I don't need a permit I've got one
man's dream dexter jetstar is now like prominently on rise of the resistance I built 13 dexter
jetstar animatronics in my home base and now I'm going to install them on rise of the resistance
we like him fixing things but it's really taking a turn to the jetstar he's everywhere yeah he is
everywhere but I thought he was just a line cook he is okay now you'll see his other dimensions
when you go on that ride this is a good character I really like this yeah I like the I like this
series the two different series that I've come up with or we've come up with I shouldn't take
credit for them but honestly look oh I'm gonna get rat-fucked out of imaginary residuals they're
both my ideas okay so it's the imaginer what's the other one can't claim any ownership because
he's not here but you can't you can claim like five percent ownership uh it's the imaginer and
you can't I'll say the park liver and the park livers I'm not gonna take any park livers money
okay because park livers is really just sort of a slice of life park livers doesn't have much
action in it where do they live specifically all over oh they're all over so you get chosen as a
like a 12 or 13 year old kid to live at the park you become a park liver okay and are they secret
or do people know about the park livers they're secret so they're kind of like the little rascals
but they're also like the lost boys in some ways yes in some ways I guess they just blend in with
the crowds right but they can they have key they can just sneak in right and then they sort of
live in the reality of the parks as well so yeah they do you can go party with Snow White and the
Seven Dwarfs on the ride because that's a real thing that's happening in the reality of the ride
okay so yeah you could you all you can choose where to live in the park I think or you or you
can get a sign like maybe it's more of a Harry Potter thing where you get assigned this is very
do you know about Game Master Anthony Game Master Anthony yeah familiar but I don't it's like um
a old old internet like mean thing where a guy would every year on a message board post about
like it's my birthday and all the characters from all the video games and movies coming with cake
and celebrate and this was posted for years and years no I don't know this is old internet so
you're saying that's like what this is it's very much becoming Game Master Anthony yeah okay well
yeah Park Livers is like Game Master Anthony okay so I hear what you're saying um well okay I mean
those are those are good sort of ideas I've had coming off of this story is there anything else
about the story that at least the first book you want to talk about um because I have something
that yeah derailed some of my research but yeah uh anyway what no I think I've covered all of this
stuff I I liked it and I will keep reading okay well that's good yeah I don't know I don't I may
never read a book again okay I don't not by choice just because my brain is fried yeah unless somebody
in the audience has a legitimately good tip for how to combat this hopefully without drugs but if
there's some sort of I guess adderall or something I mean I would I would say like like uh comical
crime like Elmer Leonard Carl Heisen I don't think the genre is a problem okay I think my brain is
the problem oh it's always been the problem romance novels a lot of there's a lot of fun
like romance novels I don't want it out there well maybe needs to be like hardcore for me to be
engaged wait uh what uh we're what context are you using that phrase uh hardcore like dirty like
dirty books like harlequin like there's some dirty harlequin stuff I feel like I want it to be like a
pirate like a sexy pirate adventure but it's like just x-rated but that exists it's a movie called
pirates it was very expensive to produce is that true yeah there is a very expensive movie porno
really called pie yeah yeah because millions this is well known yeah yeah it went it was in broke
containment now I don't think it's what do you mean broke containment like it it broke out of
it broke into popular culture I feel like I maybe like 10 years ago have you seen it I've seen clips
of the dirty pirate movie yeah yeah the important stuff and it's called pirates I think it's called
pirates x x x I don't I mean I would assume there's a what what's it railed your racer
like let's get to your thing we don't have time to talk about the porno expensive pirates movie
I'm just fascinated that there's a supposedly a famous pirate porno movie from 2010 that you've
seen parts of I gotta look this up and is well known people know this I think so listeners do
you know about the movie Jason's talking about I mean again there's pornos with pirate that's
not pornos for a pirate I was gonna say the perry feral band no uh but I just didn't know
there was like a big famous one that's that's what I didn't know pirates also known as pirates x x x
wow I was wrong it's a 2005 American year the book was written the same portographic adventure film
uh produced by digital playground and adam and eve it famously had a one million dollar budget
who's in it jesse jane janine carmen lavana teagan presley davon jenevieve jolee and evan stone oh
evan stone evan stone isn't known like some of those names I know I know evan stone sure
anyway we don't have time to get into the porno universe what is your thing I don't know what
this is okay oh really okay so I'm looking into the author and uh yeah as you said he's written
a bunch of different a lot of books um a lot of thrill adult thrillers too right grown up not
porno okay so I'm watching an interview with author Ridley Pearson and he's talking about I
don't know which this is from a couple years ago he's talking about writing these books and he's
written thrillers and he's talking about uh how enthusiastic the fan base is and he's talking
about how much he enjoys he didn't know this was going to be a big hit blah blah blah talks about
the fans helping to write one of these books there was an online community at certain points
talking about all this and great this stuff I'm like jotting it down blah blah blah then he says
I don't remember what prompted this but he was tasked with creating a rock and roll band
of authors what a super group of authors including Dave Barry and Stephen King
wow he put together a band called the rock bottom remainders
a group of authors that were active from 1992 to 2012 and then a little revival in 2015
and there were so many different Amy Tan, Sam Barry, Ridley Pearson, of course Scott Turow,
I don't know most of these names Amy Tan wrote the Joy Luck Club oh yeah yeah right I did know
her and Stephen like Dave Barry these are big names Joel Sullivan, James McBride, Mitch Album
I've read James McBride has written I've read some of his books Barbara Kingslover, Robert Fulgham
is that how you pronounce his name Matt Groening is listed on here oh uh career the simpsons uh
honorary member Maya Angelou oh my god uh and then just like a bunch of people uh uh who have popped
in and out over the years they've had they did a show in 1997 with Warren Zeva
and I was like oh my god like they did a show with Leslie Gore like this is wild and and at
first I was like have I never heard of this before oh Daryl Hammond is listed on here and uh I so I
went to YouTube and I was like oh maybe there's not any clips of this no false there are clips
there are a lot of clips they have they were on the Craig Ferguson show in 2012 that's like
kind of their last performance and they perform like what feels very much like whatever uh Jim
Belushi and the Sacred Hearts feel like yeah sure harmonica kind of like white guy blues yeah I
forget what song it is um and I don't know I haven't even this I found this this morning
what so there's a lot more to go through I don't know if there's the rock bottom
remainders I don't know that they have they need a full episode but I found to play us out
a clip of their tiny desk concert what they did NPR tiny no how many of them are there uh I don't
know um but it was June 1st 2010 that's pretty recent pretty recent yes okay I'll keep reading
the books and I'll keep reading the about the rock bottom the rock bottom remainders
we'll do these in parallel and maybe we'll come back and do a second
kingdom keepers episode in the tradition of the series having a million installments
uh so let me read this okay so I don't think Stephen King is is here in this performance he
was at the Craig Ferguson performance which I won't play today Dave Barry was here Ridley
Pearson Amy Tan was here uh and also at this performance the birds Roger McGuinn
who had been performing with the rock bottom remainders as a guest ringer
in part to help mask the fact that among other things the band hadn't rehearsed very many songs
and they were all a little jokey I think about this but this is an honor I decided to play this
little clip here uh in honor of uh Scott Gardner who is not here and I just wanted to make sure
that he knows we're thinking about him today he's fine and I want him to play yes he's fine but I
want him to be excited about the rock bottom remainders so here is them uh playing uh Sloop
Jambi by the Beats boys
oh
and they sound fine yeah
it's like sort of a campfire yeah a little trepidatious so this is one of my favorite
Beach Boys songs by the way well of course it is yeah but anyway this so I just want to make sure
that when Scott comes back to the show he knows that we've left a little treat for him called
the rock bottom remainders and they you know they love the same music he does you know sure so uh
anyway thank you for listening today thanks for subscribing to club three thank you um put your
suggestions in the comments if you haven't for crypt three something spooky uh yeah maybe save
a full rock bottom remainders episode for the month after sure november don't do that in
crypt three unless unless you find out that they did monster mash or something like a spooky song
I don't I didn't see that but if you find that let us know um but yeah if not um just and if
you have ideas for uh different characters that like a 13 year old Jason Sheridan could marry
in the park a park specific character please or if you know
did they have turkey burgers at cosmic rays in 20 and 2005 let us know please