FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast may contain
sincerity!
Uh oh!
Don't worry, we balance it out by making fun of
Jason's Phillyisms.
Today on the show, we make it about us.
Even more than usual.
It's some big life news on
Podcast The Ride!
MUSIC
Welcome to Podcast The Ride!
A theme park podcast hosted by
three men who now have a collective
three kids
to protect from ever hearing
this show. I'm Scott Gardner
and there's Mike Carlson.
Three kids among us.
Is that where you're going to leave it?
A collective three, yeah, yeah.
Just getting the fact out.
It gets a little personal to reveal more than that.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
I will go a little further.
I will elaborate and say that
yes, among the three of us
there are now three children
which means I can say
Jason, congratulations!
Yay!
Little William Holden Sheridan
has entered
our world.
No, my brain
lesions are my little babies.
They're all more special
than the ones that appeared before
them.
So many little bundles of
joy. My little bundles of joy.
Oh no.
They make you go, oh, your hand hurts now.
No explanation for that.
That's the thing, the little
bundles. The little bundle you can't.
Unexpected chaos
to your life.
God's little angels.
So exciting, but this isn't about
me today.
Although I made it about me.
Who is it, unless the title already was a joke
that revealed it.
Who forgot to wrap it up, fellas?
Oh, I see what you're saying.
You're just being bloody.
He says naughty voice.
Who had a big accident?
No, no, no. I am happy
to say that Aaron and I have
welcomed into this world our second
beautiful child.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I overcame my
100% discomfort with
the act of human sexuality.
And somehow made
this happen.
Yes, very excited. So excited
to share with the audience.
And now let's do the
gender reveal.
It's a good boy.
Once again, copy paste
that from when this happened
four and a half years ago.
I have two
boys. I have two boys that were
recording in the garage and just several
walls away are two great
boys. Wow, the prophecy
of the Disney daddies continues
to become closer to reality.
It's almost there.
If you haven't heard this runner
in a while, the notion that we would
convert into a different kind of podcast
where we're three dads who
have three sons. Three each.
Three sons each. And they're all
a handful. They're all a handful.
We got a long way. I mean, it steps
us there, but just do it a boy. You have a
girl. You have three more
boys to have.
That's a lot of work.
You have a young daughter
and you would still have three boys
to add. You'd have to keep going until
you got there. Yeah, no, it seems hard
at this point, but you're doing great with it.
I'm putting up really good numbers.
It's not a girl and it's not an aberration
in sight as a girl
would be in this goal. In the goal to have
three sons. Yeah, yeah.
That sounded so...
Yes, I wasn't able to
give birth to a life giver.
A human life vessel, which is
what I call women. Baby pod.
No, I'm so excited.
I think we would have been very happy with
a girl too, but given
the number one
reason to do
this. When you're weighing having a second
child, especially if you make
a pros and cons list. And the cons list can get
very long because you know the effort that it
will involve and your life is very hard already
with one. And you're like, how is this ever going to work?
And the biggest, a gigantic
neon pro
in the list was
our first son is spectacular.
He is so great
and with each passing month
just gets cooler and
sweeter and watching him develop his
interests. But he's just a
solid guy and already
the big brother
he has been.
I'll just flesh out the
timeline here, but they have
not even been in the same house as we
record this for 24 hours.
And yet the
indelible, the like, I will
never forget heart melting
memories of
them meeting and my oldest
singing to the new
one and welcoming him home.
And then before bed he's like, I hope it will
be morning soon so I can see
my brother again.
Like my god, it hasn't
even been 24 hours.
He is just, just firing.
Tossing off bar, tossing off baby bars.
It's been so great.
So anyway,
all that to say like,
a sequel, a boy again
given how much we love the first one
is amazing. And I also, it also
gives me the opportunity
to do this with this announcement
of who I now have in my house.
Two brothers
on their way.
Two brothers on their way.
One just poops
and sleeps all day.
It all comes together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry to Sully with the serious
song with
you to have any fun with it because that
is a moment where you go to a Disney
theme park and you all
joy evaporates from
the heat. It's very sad. You're not allowed to
have, is it, wait, now two brothers
is that, that is in American Adventure
and then it's in, has been in
Lincoln. Right. Is there any
anticipation of two brothers going away
now that, now that there
is a split, a joint
custody, if you will. I'm putting things in parent terms
between the
Walt robot and Lincoln robot. That's a good question.
Yeah, because there's going to be a Walt show in the Lincoln
theater at Disneyland. But I think they're
going to alternate the Lincoln show and
the Disney show. So I don't
know if there's. After the initial run, they're
going to alternate. Yeah, I don't know if there's any,
Lincoln is going to come back with different songs.
But with the fun of, now that you've
got Walt and Walt presumably
doing Walt's greatest
hits, putting on the Walt review,
pointing at the map, saying, Disney
will never be complete as long as his imagination
goes. What are the other big Walts?
So never forget, I'll start with a mouse. We're going to, this is
going to be, I actually hadn't thought about the Walt
show to this end and
how much we are going to get
five timers. Let's say, like,
you know, let's say, hey, a thousand timers,
I think is what that show is going to be.
Yes. And I don't think, I think people have confirmed
there's no A.I. Walt voice,
which is what people were worried about.
Oh, so they are
sticking with using
recordings of him and not,
okay. Right. So, yeah,
I think, yeah, you're not,
they aren't going to start deploying, you know,
what James Earl
Jones, RIP, has, what he
announced before his death
that he's passing over to the A.I.
realm. Yeah, he signed his voice away
to A.I. before, so Vader can have
his voice forever. But they couldn't just get a Walt
impersonator, like
Tower of Terror Rod Serling?
Is that too,
that is a serious question. That Tower of Terror was
really, that was East Coast, buddy.
I know. You do it every time.
I called it that last time. But I was like, that was even
ten times from my point of view. But you know what's funny is that I feel like
we've done entire episodes about
the Tower of Terror, multiple of them,
and it never struck me then.
But I think that what's happening is some kind of, like,
you haven't gone back home in a little bit.
I think that is, like,
your voice aching with nostalgia
for your coast.
But it's coming out now, lately.
Tower of Terror.
That's how it's telling you, you gotta go home.
If Phillies clinched
their playoff spot,
I am traveling back home
in October, is that I was like,
I gotta get these tickets now before they
get playoff crazy
prices, you know?
Yes, that's true. But yeah, they could do
a Walt impersonator, I suppose, but it would maybe
not match the actual real audio.
But, I mean, it would be
funny. I mean, it would be funny
if he could, like, plug Cotino
or do some other dialogue
that we've never heard before.
Yeah, yeah. No, if they could have him,
and they could always claim
that it's old recordings.
Yeah, sure. Just lie about it.
Yeah, yeah. Actually, he did have the plans for Cotino.
And he had the plans to put James
Earl Jones.
I got my eye on a young actor.
He was real good in that Kubrick film, and I
think he's gonna go far, so we're gonna use, we're gonna
develop computer technology to capture his voice.
It would mean a lot to me if I got to,
you know, continue
my story in
my home where I lived, and I just wish
Walt could tell me
about that. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe Hazel George has some old,
like, tapes from their sessions.
His nurse Hazel? His nurse Hazel
who would work on his polo injury
at, like, five o'clock sharp every day.
But if, but those tapes
are probably just like,
ah, yeah. Well, you could,
I don't know, you could use them in the show somehow.
I don't know. When he gets up from the desk,
like, they don't, they don't have a lot of that audio
of just, like, kind of moving around.
So maybe that's the stuff you could use.
You're looking for audio of Walt in
agony. Agony
or ecstasy. Oh, okay.
Either way. Close door Walt
is what we want. We all know Uncle Walt from TV.
Yeah. I want to see what he did
when cameras weren't around. Only
hidden microphones. Right.
Or he, or he, or he was
recording in a Nixonian, paranoid
way. Yeah, possible.
What was his choice? I'm not sure. I also,
I, uh,
in that Tower of Terror run I was trying to go, like,
what would be, if, if
the Phillies hired a new player,
is there a name that would get
the most Philly pronunciation?
If it was, like, Trevor Terrarian
or something.
And then the whole crowd, then he comes out and the whole crowd just
goes, Terrrrrrrrrrr!
Ricky Scoocles stepping up.
He went a whole other way with it!
Oh, no no, I love that. That is
a great vessel for Phillyism.
Oh god, I'm trying to think of a name.
Where does it come out the most? What are the...
Wooder.
Yeah
Tommy wooder Tommy get over here Tommy Tommy wooderson
Tommy wooderson
Well, hopefully if it was an ideal filly name out there
Anyways per my stuff. I'm very happy. He is great. Aaron is doing so great
She did incredible the delivery is like it was nothing
Maybe she doesn't feel that way, but I'm looking at her like I can't believe she's someone who gave birth to a baby in
The last two weeks I couldn't believe it
days after the fact and she just like bounced right back in and you know
Handling everything for now our oldest. This is a thing. I have to shift to I feel like I'm doing like
Ceremonial things that are helping me, you know, like I just look alright
I'm not gonna say that I'm gonna keep up the policy of not saying the name on the show
So Mike, I'm gonna need you to be on the trigger about deleting the okay
I end up saying it but here's as close as I will get if you need like if the audience needs a visual or name
Manifestation of the kids. This is a moment. I was really looking forward to recently
We did an episode about Park stars and I probably talked about this before that
I have this little like mantle or a little it's like a little nook in the hallway
we're probably a phone used to go and
I
Put my wedding cake toppers there where Erin and I were represented by fancy robots and when we became a fuller family
I added my now oldest and he's represented by the Park star of smart one
and I did it was a lot of like who is the second one gonna be and
I ended up sticking with Park stars and my new addition
My little one is represented by the fun Meister the pleasure island. Yeah
Mascot which is a very cute Park stars
I like him in Park star for more than I like him in the logo when I like them in the logo, too
Park star I recently purchased
Yeah, yeah, oh right right. Oh, yes, which you did an unboxing but you got screwed on eBay I hate to
Scott's thing, but he got screwed. They said it was on open. I'll nap while you they said it was sleep
I bought a couple where I knew what I was getting and then I bought two which I thought were totally unopened blind box
Right, and they were tape. It just been resealed. This guy got screwed on eBay and I keep telling him
He's got to file a claim. It's easy. They'll they'll give you money back. Sure
Yeah, but then but is it worth the is it worth the hassle for you?
It's not that much of a hassle
Well, you need to send me a link cuz I tried to find a file a claim link and I could not find it
It's so easy. Well, first of all, you should just email the person who sold it to you
Well, I don't want to start something with a seller
But then then that's because eBay will ask if you tried and then if they see you tried then oh, okay
Yeah, how often have you done this Mike a couple times? Yeah, I bought a quarter scale
Adam West Batman big Batman and it came and they said it was new
It was not new would have been opened and I went back and forth and I was like well
I'm gonna open this anyway, and I was being nice and I said I'm gonna open this Batman anyway
Whatever it's clear it's in good shape from what I understand from what I see I open the box
It smelled like a smokers house in there and I went no no no and I went right back and did it and I mean
That's what happened with that when we did the Joe Camel episode
I got all this information from this Joe Camel coffee table
Uh-huh that as I turned the page it just like released ancient smoke. Yeah, but that's a Joe Camel book
That's expected that adds to it Adam West should not be no no
Smoker yeah, no that book was infused with you know, the fine aromas of flavor country
Oh god, I forgot to lick it. I gotta I gotta get a hold of Joe ask if I can lick his book
Yeah, my friend's not not to can't I don't believe Joe cam my friend Joe Carnegie
the only book that when licked produces the reaction of
I
Missed out I gotta get that thing out Jason you start looking
Give me your phone and just give me the passcode and I will take care of it from there
Okay, and I'll take care of anything else you need in there
I don't know why that felt lascivious to me
I got I meant more app wise and mm-hmm, but I guess I could do sex thing. I don't know
Yeah, I mean this is not something that Jason needs currently
But I do wonder if does that apply to your checking brain is that your desire to do things for people
You also don't need to be
flirting online dating
but you feel like as with checking that you your ability to
Do things from afar that help people and you're volunteering it again with this eBay thing
Do you feel like you could like get somebody into a solid little relationship or just a little sexual message?
Yeah
The answer is I don't I don't have any experience doing this but the answer is yes
I do believe I could you do think you could because don't both you and I
Got into committed relationships before there were dating apps at all, right?
and you've
Via the character McGruff composed a song very critical of hookup absolutely
I don't know if you share any of those beliefs or if that
Beaks into your personal philosophy well the end he says delete all the apps
He doesn't like any of the apps except for maybe one or two. I forget
But yeah, no, I I honestly I do I feel like I have a good
I have a good sense of this and maybe I'm completely wrong, but I feel like I've got I've advised people
But I've never taken their phone and done it for them
Yes, you and Geo looked at my dating profiles before they went lie
Well, that's a whole yes, we threw that up on the TV and we were watching Jason go through you all writers rimmed it
Well not well, he would do any Jason wouldn't take any advice from us Jason threw up his his phone
Whatever the app was on the TV and we watched him go through people. I don't remember I remember we were at
What's the French like diner place?
On Vermont Street, I don't know by the old toys are us in not important. What happened there me me me me me?
The French bistro, what was the name of that we like?
Denny's
Denny's that sells wine
We were at st. Patrick's Day at the historic Tamo Shander
And then we went to get something to eat and I was like I'm making dating apps right now Wow
Making great pages. Did you have a note that you're willing to say?
Did you have to was there something you were strongly suggesting he get out of there?
I
Probably I wish I remembered specifically because I think I definitely had notes
All I really remember was you like swiping no on a bunch of doctors
Wait what no, thanks brainiac what watching him swipe no one like
What do you know about the X-Men
Like well, they don't know alt-comedy I
Did not say
Definitely something in that vein where Gio and I were just like dumbfounded
They won't know what they won't know what a second beat is
Drop Harold they'll say second beat. Is that about a heart beats?
I don't want to hear about your heart surgery. I think that would have been more like oh, they don't want a bum like me
You know
Yeah, we were shocked at what you who you were saying no to it's chaos
Eventually, I've learned I know it's now eventually I met Jane on bumble sure work down, right, right
I don't invite and that's then that's a profile that had no input from no idea. I had no input on that. No
Wow, he did it himself. Yeah, you inadvertently did cuz I probably just copied over my all my tinder stuff
Maybe maybe I wish I wish we had a document of us assembling that profile because I do wish I I should remember that
I guess I don't remember a specific about it. Yeah
I know I feel like the audience deserves to know I know they do deserve they deserve screenshots
We are open books and that is why I'm now going to describe every step of the
dilation of how the
Patoson kicked in. Oh, yeah
No, they're like I don't need to talk much about how it played out. But the
The funny
aspect of it like here's my it begins story for this delivery was that I
we were like resting pretty easy because we were at 35 weeks and
felt like
You know like I mean all plans have been sort of like maybes and asterisks and that's in my personal life and that's with
You guys and records and things we wanted to do for the show. Everything was like, you know could be nudged
I was living in that zone for a while which gets a little frustrating
But I was like, you know, it was the end of a long day
Like my my oldest had, you know a glass of milk. He's winding down
We're about to put him to bed and I'm like, you know, this is this is a long one
This is kind of purgatorial. I'm gonna go see a movie. I'm gonna get out of here. I'm gonna see Beetlejuice Beetlejuice. I
Purchased a ticket online
clicked the purchase button and I swear as my finger released like in the exact second of the up of
That motion I hear from the other room. Uh
Scott
Yeah
Water broke. Oh my you're and then like, you know, there's no there's no joy in that moment
That's a you are kidding me
you like, you know the moment where it becomes like
It's now and the degree of energy that I have and on this day right now
This is what I have going into this. Yeah. Oh my god. So then like well no Beetlejuice
I guess I'll try to get that and then you know what AMC doesn't refund for those convenience fees
Yeah, you still I'm out 250 now
I was gonna say when you got that refund Jason would be upset about that
He would have still tried to make the movie already a beautiful little angel coming in the world, but so much tragedy
He's operating at a loss that let's let's milk I can put in his mouth, right?
Oh, I bet like Beetlejuice if you asked three times they'd give you that
They operate if you give Chicago you give me your phone I could try to get that. Oh, that's right. Yeah
Yeah, same you want to unlock take care of that for me too. Yeah, tell this to you this man had a baby
You understand there was nothing convenient about that, right?
so
Anyway, I'm like, oh my god
We got so we got to like, you know, all right call grandparents get still get our oldest down
So things are calm for him, but then like oh god get over there Aaron drove herself incredible
You know, but but then like then things calmed down they did due to the 35 weeks
They they told us as soon as we got there, which was bummer to hear but it just our expectations
They did say at this timeline. That is an automatic NICU stay
Yeah, neon neonatal intensive care unit. So we we knew when we got there
We are not gonna be leaving right this child, which is a tough pill to swallow
But you know
Plus sides to that because you got a little extra care. It was never scary. It was never it was never bad delivery went great
But you know just need a little extra help ended up staying for 11 nights that that dragged out
That was a long time and again most the majority of that not scary
It kind of demystified the what Nick you to me in general because I'm expecting scary boy in the plastic bubble
I don't know. I like I heard it and I got a little shiver and I'm sure people's experiences are that and have been that
But most of was very nice everybody in there all nurses fantastic
and I still got to it required like putting on headphones and like
Emotional music and turning off all the mini be there just like dozens and dozens of beeps and alarms
Happening with all the babies at all times, but I still got to like burrow in and have like true
Bliss moments just staring at him and it was really nice
but the budding comedians have to go back and forth all the time and
Now I'm happy to say as we record this that that last night was the first night that he spent at home
And then all of the gardeners were together and it was really nice. I will throw out a theme park related thing
That meant a lot
Coming back and seeing this particular item
The first that Aaron and I went to knots Berry farm
I want to say post-pandemic but it was not at all post-pandemic who was in that zone of like well
We will open the outdoors again, and there are the knots did all these like food festival
I forget if you guys went to any of those
but
We went we went to one and like they had like shops open too and they had the wood carving thing where you can yeah
Yeah, you get an old
It's something I wanted for a long time because my great-grandparents had one of those just like, you know
Old-fashioned woodcarve sign with a family name on it and we started like, okay, we're doing that
We're so happy to be back here and we got a baby now. This is great. And we filled out the form and
And and like and so what do we put on it?
And I was like our well our names mom dad and so and so right and Aaron said well shouldn't it be the Gartner's?
I was like, oh cuz yeah. Well, you don't want to leave anyone out
Sure, that was cool. That was a little it still took a long time after that to get our heads around it
but ever but I have like certainly stared at the knots the Gartner's sign and like
imagined more of those and what is that story and how does it play out and now all the Gartner's are at home and
the sign is
Remains accurate the knot sign is yeah, even more accurate than ever before
I mean there's accuracy wouldn't have been the issue, right?
If it was just the three names those are three names that right exists
It wouldn't have been inclusive that I guess is the you know, it's important
It's time to get Papa Gartner to fright fest extreme
Well, this is another aspect of it because I'm just I'm trying to tell all the stories here that that pertain to our subject matter and
You know, like I said caught me off guard
The beginning of the 35th week and you know
We were trying to set plans in motion and there were a lot of plans where I was like
I think we'll be okay there that I think we could do
Baby a process started on a Monday night that Friday night what became four nights later
Mike Gio and I were supposed to go to freight fest extreme at Six Flags Magic Mountain
Yeah about that for a while. I'm like I wanted to cuz I and I declared on stage last year in a Halloween show
I'm joining which I didn't even get you guys sold me on it during the show
I was not gonna make that declaration right after all of all the tails you weaved and like I'm doing it this time
And like I think that's gonna be clear. I think I could do that should be fine
Early showed up before that. Yeah, which is so now freaky to think about the possibility of
If we had cut that closer
The possibility that when Aaron's water broke and we had to go to the hospital that I was I could have been deep
It had six flags. You could have been in the sewer of souls
The maze where there's a big pile of shit
Could have been in there your phone buzzes or you like rings or something. Oh my god
And then it's and then having to navigate my way out two miles of walking out of six flags from wherever suit
The sewer of souls is over by like kind of like I think by Tatsu kind of up on a hill
Yeah, in my mind this now how way much land that park covers. Yeah
Well, so that might have been the deepest part of the park
Yeah, and then they're like this year the sewer and soul is extra extreme extra long
two miles sewer
I'm in another county at this point now. Just like now just punching shit monsters or whatever's in there
Yeah, I have to go to be with my child
Scott we were gonna do the West Coast cost of roller coaster. You can't leave now
Okay, you're right quick West Coast customs, okay, I'll buy one of those front of the line passes
I run into the shop like how much of those if you buy them day of?
$225 sure sounds good fair price to me
Go on terrible roller coaster that hurts me you get stuck on the roller coaster
to call
I'm sorry, and then she's like well, what time did you go on the coaster?
Was it after I told you that the water broke and you have to like well, she's like I want to see time stamps
I know it's been a three hour
delay, you see
You told me you were going through the sewer of souls I meant no well that not literally mentally
I meant that I'm in a mental sewer of souls because I'm stuck on West Coast customs
Well, a teen a teen is like hey, sorry guys gonna have to wait till morning. I'll see you tomorrow
Try to rest up everybody tilt your head back make sure that blood doesn't go
It's kind of like babies imagine that you're all babe newborn babies if you can imagine those
Oh god, no, I just tip you don't want your heads to tip forward because then all the blood goes down
You're neck weakens if anybody has any loose $20 bills
I can go buy a Marvin the Martian blanket for you keep you warm tonight
But if not, sorry, you're gonna have to use a garbage bag
I need two $20 bills for that blanket. Just a heads up. It's not a single it's a $40 Marvin the Martian blanket
We can put a tray of Michelada's on a hook and send that up your way if anybody's hungry
That's the only food we have at this hour. Just lick those rims. You should stay sustained
Also, you are by a speaker and we don't know how to turn the sound off
So you're gonna be hearing whoa cool car all night every
45 seconds
Loud exhibit could layering exhibit I cannot conjure what an exhibit song wait
No exhibit has nothing to do with that exhibit is pimp my ride
Yeah, yeah my ride isn't wait. Is there any affiliation between West Coast Customs?
That was that that wasn't the group that did pimp my ride. Oh my god
Isn't that how they kind of got no maybe that's right. Yeah, I don't want to speak. I don't want to speak
And I need to figure it out this is the kind of thing this is really important my new son in yeah, West Coast Customs
I need to teach him both spellings of exhibit. Yeah, you'll take the yeah
You'll take your two boys to Six Flags one day. They'll go into Bugs house. They'll learn where Bugs lives in this weird single room
with no furniture
Like the the room rivers Cuomo lived in at Harvard everybody talks about when he after Pinkerton was such a disaster
A sad room. He had like a sad the pitch black room with the lizard. Yeah
Well, that's scary where Bugs lives at Six Flags and the rivers Cuomo
The work on on pimp my ride was done by West Coast Customs until season five
When it was done by Galpin Auto Sports going forward Galpin Wow
And yet Galpin Auto has no roller coaster. Yeah Galpin. That's unfair
They do have a diner the horseless carriage in the middle of their mile long
Row of car dealerships in Van Nuys. Well, that's good to know
That's a themed experience
Yeah, really almost happened though, and I'm glad the timing played out. Okay timing has been
Insane for me throughout this and this is where I will get to my other piece of news here
Which is that there's this there is an opportunity that I have been pursuing for weeks months
I don't even know
The way things have played out in the literal hour that my new son was born
I received an official offer for a very big directing opportunity
Like a big big thing I don't want to say much about him I apologize for being a to Dr. Strange three. Yeah. Yeah you got
Fine I'll say they the NDA
You can only you can say it if it's guessed, okay
So guys we have a lot of talking to do you're gonna have to care
I did so much bullshitting you're gonna have to catch me up on a lot of mythology. Yeah, I said told him I'm a fan
And I said, please don't ever listen to my podcast
You did pitch them though that dr. Strange teams up with a podcaster named Jason from Philly
By the way, you're not playing Jason
Just feel like we can aim higher on Jared Leto's playing Jason
He's snakes me again
He's method to he's gonna mocap into a shorter body
It's gonna be awesome. He's gonna bring that those jit those definitive Jared Leto box office results
See over and over again, he's sending that Oh equals money, right? Of course. He's sending hot taffy to all the cast members
He's really like twisted this time
He's rubbing the taffy though to
Outside everyone's trailers
No, I can't say too much about what this is don't go imagine
I don't think I don't think you can't guess what this is, but hopefully you'll hear down the road
But it is it is a cool thing. I worked really hard to get it. It's an awesome
It's a it's a type of thing. I have never done before
And it's really unique and it's with old friends and new friends and I'm so excited to do it
The timing has been insane and and I've been barreling towards
Like well is the as a baby gonna show up as I'm getting ready for this if this comes together
Boy, my youngest a real producer a real he like it's like he heard the chatter
Right around him about the timing and he's like I'll take care of them. I'll get out of here
You don't gotta worry about me. You can start doing this thing because that's the deal with this thing
It will be very fast and all-encompassing. It's it's it's kicking in like
Now like so fast. It's gonna be a whirlwind. I'm excited to tell you more
As time goes on shows in season five. We're all looking forward to it
Jesus riding it down with the palm fronds. Someone's got a
I'm I will be ushering
So when you hear the IP that I am I see you're some of your favorite IP out there
And I am ushering onto the screen snaggle pusses back
I
Think sort of a snaggle puss by way of Deadpool
I don't know snaggle bus who breaks the for the snaggle bus who who makes jokes about like another cartoon reboot. Yeah
But
Anyways, I'm I'm thrilled. This is good. This is gonna be really neat. My son is really neat
It's really my son is really neat. You can hold me on that son
If you ever hear this that's how I feel about you
But it is going to be so much work on top of having a very new
newborn and the sum total of all of this is that in the
Coming months you will be hearing less of me on podcast the right
That's as much as I want to commit either way to what it actually means because I don't know how much less or for how
Long I actually have no idea
It's also not gonna be right away because you will hear me throughout
Haunt cast the fright through of a lot of those and maybe even a little beyond and then I don't know maybe
Sporadically here in there. I don't know. So that's all I'm gonna say is less
It may not be a long hiatus. It may not even be like a full all the way through hiatus
I maybe I'm overthinking. I'm I'm hold. I'm doing too much hand holding through this process
Well, look as you're looking at the sheet for dr. Strange 3, you know, all those actors come in and out
You know don't necessarily know how long they shot for and I feel like that might be the case here
Maybe people won't necessarily know. Mm-hmm a lot of stuff. We have a lot of stuff in the can a lot of variable
Yeah, they have told me no actors. Well, I'm in the belly of the beast. No actors will be films together, right?
Yeah, it's all green screen in their every Avenger if everyone who's ever played an Avenger is committed is shooting but may be cut
Right. Yes. So just in case we're getting 400 actors done. So yeah, it's it's a tough one. It's
It's 45 pages a day. Well, you know that a budget of 1 billion dollars
Every continent there's a green screen. Yeah, cuz we got to go to them
No, it's yeah, it's a whole thing and I did the good news is I do anticipate being fired very quickly
Oh, okay. Yeah, I think I'm making it four days if I'm lucky, so I might be back here ASAP. Okay. Yeah
So we'll see anyway. Yeah, I don't know you guys have been been great about it
Thanks for for understanding and sure operating and work with and and taking care of our storied franchise
All right. All right be in my in my absence
Well, well for the next month it will be our IP, right
But yeah, I do appreciate it. It's almost insane
This hasn't happened before like, you know, I feel like I've been able to balance things
animated shows and the like which go
Extremely excruciatingly slowly, but this is gonna be fed
This is like, you know what? This thing is like this is like a launch and I in the past have been a no launch queen
Well, and it is on me to metaphorically speaking rise to the challenge
Civico of being a launch queen. Well, at least creatively
Which I feel good about it and I am gonna do and I'd rather do this than go on West Coast Customs
Pick the ride, which I don't know if that's a launcher. No
Car is a launch
Yes, did you go is that the one you went to when it was a little cub reporter session?
You put the hat on the helm the hard hot hot. Excuse me the hard head
Yeah, I saw it in production and you did the opening day. Whoa, you were like the ride guys
You were like universals. Oh the right video brand the ride guys who go into like they I watched them go on that
What is it celestial? Yeah racers that name epic universe
They went on that and then a cut like as soon as they got on the right car
The rumor is there's a flux capacitor on the back of each car really or at least on some of them. Yeah
That's cool. You know, the vibe is like if you're gonna have zappy energy from some
Yeah, then why not and no lights at night except for like the cars. Oh, I did like that. Yeah, that is really neat
It looks like it's a practical light. Oh like a shooting star. Yeah, that's right
So in the distance you see it is like comets and stuff
We're on I drive and you see that when we're leaving Taffer's Tavern, Orlando
See that we see the glimmering tail of your bleary eyed from so much Taffer's whiskey
But a bourbon excuse me from the sweetest sweetest
Your stomach is clawing its way out of your body despite the fact that you only ate french fries we're gonna
Seems impossible that you would have that big of a reaction to a simple fried potato
We're gonna yeah, and we're gonna oh, yeah, that is we're gonna have that experience. I
For months we've been talking, you know people have been like, oh, you know, this thing's gonna open early open early
And now I'm hearing there's like the big rides are like they're not working yet
Classic stuff
Universe or taffers
I when you said rides it gave me a clue my big mechanical tongue isn't working
It's lapping everybody off
They're crashing into the ceiling fans. You're gonna fix this thing the panini press won't close
We can't make panini
He was inspired by like the big weekend head that you enter at horror nights for his house
My big uvula like crusty the clown. Yeah. Oh you were gonna do horror nights, too
We should have mentioned too. Like you were all set for horror nights
That's happened already. I've happened too. That was right after and I guess like you'll hear some like, okay
In a hot in a pre-banked Halloween episode you will hear me trying to weave the narrative of like
Let's see how much I do this year, right? You just spoil it now. It's not none
There was also the possibility that then the baby then it's like over then the baby is what?
Surprise and one where people cut me slack, right? Right? Are you sure I can't be up there? I can't yell that
I need my rest. Well next year you should declare next year. Oh, wait, let me finish my thought real quick
Yeah, but I feel like I've heard and maybe it's like Alicia Stella podcast or YouTube where it's like
Monsters and Harry Potter not working like yeah
And then like so when they describe but the most the most incredible experience we've ever like well
That's the downside to the platitudes you say about every single ride in this park means that it also might not work
Yes, cuz like is there channel park stop. I'm sorry. Is that the name of it? Yeah, Orlando parks out
Yeah
but like I think that there's just like massive screens and tons of robots Harry Potter thing and like they gotta get it all to
coordinate and then I think she floated the idea that people are like
phased opening
So then I'm like, oh this sucks for us because I'm like I want to go right when it opens but like if there's big stuff closed
I don't know. We'll see. I don't know. We'll be there next year
As long as East Coast Bowser's challenge is there we do have Bowser's challenge
It's right here. Wait is only three and a half hours. Well, that's the nice thing about horror nights
So we walked right on okay walked right on bars or challenge and it's mmm
Doesn't bother me as much when you don't have to wait. No, it changes
Everything I also came in not to repeat things we said long ago
But my feeling about Mario is very different when we got to go on this press day and we did the cool little like Bowser Jr
Game, you know, if there are no lines, that is everything. However, there are never no lines. So
That's good. That's a good tip though. That is a good horror night tip though
And I think it all tickets have it or maybe it's just the express item
I'm not sure but like there's no one in there. We walked right into the toad
Toad place restaurant and oh, that's right. We got that tip. Yeah that the toad cafe is yeah
You're gonna you actually can get in there. So next year you'll do all of it. You said I think I'm gonna have to at this point
I mean, I'm I am especially disappointed admittedly about Fight Fest. I was ready to do it
Yeah, and we can it's not happening in general Geo didn't end up able to do it either
So we got to really commit now next year. Yeah, but that's you know, hey, you know, you can't
That's why there's space between dr. Strange 2 and dr. Strange 3 right Scott Gertner is
You know, you got to wet the appetite. You got to get people excited, you know, give them a little break from the franchise
So yeah, hopefully Friday fest 3 and I've got some other thoughts about things to do, you know down the line
But I do want to say it just if I'm tossing out things and you know, you don't have to listen to anything
I say a while I'm gone. It's hey, it's it's it's yours take
Drive this baby as fast as you want as slow as you want, whatever you want to do
But I will say, you know, don't shy away from big stuff
Whatever you got to do in my app don't like save anything for me unless it's so this
It's another Beach Boys episode or Ben look Leno either save Beach Boys and Leno for me
But otherwise do whatever do whatever you want. November is Space Mountain Pirates
Daddy's away the cats will play
No, I you know what do big stuff actually I say specifically
Do big stuff do the things that the whole audience has been asking for. Oh, I've got a good idea
Yeah, oh, I just had an I won't tell you what it is. Oh good idea. Okay. Okay. All right. I'll tell you
Let me tell you I'll tell you I'll tell you Indiana Jones to November
This would be the time we're doing it. You are finally free
Yeah from the person blocking your dream of a sequel to it. We're doing it already done. We're doing it
Six Flags Friday has to open the door
The door well, but that's a different that's sort of a different the crimson door the red door
Yeah, no, this is like has been open fucking Scots. You're just a boy
It's just the boys are left then then the narc is gone. We can do whatever we want now. Okay, so I mean
Seven years ago. Did we talk about the ice falling cuz Tony Baxter said that there was ice in the original
Bachelor PTR bachelor party, baby
Yeah, we both were going to go wildly counting on the other one to listen to the original episode in neither of us
We're just gonna cover the same stuff. I'm not gonna do it. Yeah, I'm gonna try to do it word-perfect
like
important upcoming alike psycho 99
Do the psycho make yeah very soon. Yeah. Yeah, very good. Yeah, look we have some Jason
I've already discussed some topics also, so
Okay, very good. Yeah
Plans are but and again, I won't be right away. You'll hear me in October
But you know, yeah November is what's gonna be insane for me
and that's why just like
Do whatever you want cover the blockbusters if you need to if you look would this drive me insane to miss this?
Of course
But if you were cornered and you had to do wailing flowers and madam without me, I would understand
You know ultimately at the end of the day
I have a beautiful baby boy and I could cope I could look in his eyes
Yeah, would help me cope with the pain of having missed madam right while I was gone
Well, if you if you have to only if you have to
That's a hard one. Yeah, but I think we're gonna save that for next year, too. Okay. Good. Well, I think we're gonna say
I just got an email. The shoot has been extended for a year here. Yeah. Yeah. Oh Dr. Strange four and five have been added
Before he gets bladed, you know
Where you showing the door?
if you had look if you had to
Convert the entire show into being an album by album Green Day dissection podcast, right while I was gone
I would understand I could I could cope with that if this had to become you talking dookie to me
I
Will I will cope as much as I would love to hear more about how warning influenced your guitar?
Your guitar it's sort of the foundation of my guitar playing honestly is sort of learning those power chords. Well that way
Yeah, I mean like well, that's why we got to get you with
Marin because Marin loves talking about like you drive into like well, so you are you a buddy guy guy
Are you a Robert Johnson guy? Yeah. Well, I'm kind of what's his name was Joe Armstrong. Oh, oh, that's him
Oh, he's the guitarist. Oh, yeah, I'm a beyond kind of ability
Yeah, look castaway
Warning all these songs. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's at the heart church on Sunday
Mm-hmm great song. See this is like I'm gonna soak it up
Well, I can the naming of these songs
we all because knowing that I might leave and that you guys might just
Take episodes to name all of these songs and get it out of your system permanently forever
I think it just get us more excited to say it later, you know when Scott's when Scott's back, you know, we gotta do
Say more names
Anyways, well, we'll we will see how this plays out
I do look I want to say this as I'm doing right now. There are episodes
of this show where I play up my beleaguer mint with
Certain lines of conversation and certain lengths of those lines of conversation
You'll hear that mode of Scott on the show from time to time. You will hear it in future episodes
I would say but let me be very clear. I love doing the show
It's not ideal to have to step away from the show and I'm excited to be back whenever I'm back
This show it's it's such a invaluable creative vessel for me
It gives me sanity and and and something to do when the rest of the careers are very slow and when the career is faster
it keeps me sharp and is a great outlet then to and
At the ultimately I just like having fun with you guys and it's always after
Seven-year we're heading for the seven-year anniversary and it's still a guaranteed
I sit down and have fun and laugh a lot. And so I'm I hope I'm not away from that for too long
Well, thank you for saying that we will miss you we've already done a couple and I really Scott is in the room even when
He's not in the room. Let me just say that too. His presence will be felt AI
It's a waltz style animatronic, what do you think Scott?
So it will yeah a glass of wine
You won't be too far from these episodes if they go the way of the few that Jason and I have already done
And yeah interesting to hear yes, and so yeah, you will be around we will not be replaced
Permanently by mr. Morrow or anything, but I don't know. We'll see
With all this joy in my life well as new in my life that there's still
Like in the back of my head that I walk out of here as soon as I leave
Who comes buzzing in like a bee into a pocket?
But mr. Morrow and suddenly then I come back and there's no place for me
There's no possible my chair is full this Scott chair has been this musical chairs has reached a permanent end
No offer has been made or anything. I so so I wouldn't worry about it
But you know, we'll see we're gonna experiment. We're gonna have a little fun while you're gone boy
and we'll see yeah, we'll see we'll see who who's on the show and
What crossovers could possibly happen that cardona just put up a video where he was talking about being a free agent
But he thinks it's time for a home and I think everyone's gonna be surprised where he lands
Where is where is he just left? What was his he's been around? He wrestles in GCW. He's wrestled in impact
I think he's talking about trying to sign with a WWE or an AEW but Jason is he going with WWE?
Is he going with AEW? No, he's going with PTR. Yeah PTR. Maybe that's what Jason's alluding to
I don't know. We haven't discussed that off Mike, but got to make an offer
Can we make an offer?
competitive with professional wrestling
Yeah, and how much how much of your guys how bad do you want them?
Well, how much yeah, how much does your third become not a third Jason's willing to give up some of his
But yes, congratulations Scott on all this stuff, this is all very exciting and
We will we will carry on but I don't I don't anticipate it being so
Long or jarring to the listeners
Yeah, I hope not. Again. Again. This is going incredibly quickly. Yeah, this is gonna be this is going to be a whirlwind. Yes
Which is some of the excitement of it just just diving in. Yeah, so yeah again
Thanks for thanks for being cool and that goes for the audience too. And it seems like there's some hijinks afoot too and
I would like to do one more little thing that sort of plants the flag for when I'm like fully back
And then hopefully them and at worst saves my job, right?
Because this is what I'm about to bring out. I don't know if this is something mr
Morrow is gonna bring the table interesting. So this is you know, consider this a negotiation tactic
But yeah, this is here's something that I've been wanting to fit into which into the show for a long time since March actually
this goes way back and this seems like the slot because
Back in March. I took a great trip just the then three of us
My family to Escondido to the the Welk Resort. That's something I've brought up here and there
this this very charming little place was a little like shopping center and
You could stand with a statue of Lawrence Welk and then and it's really it's down in San Diego County
So you can like it's you know, it's in the like picturesque area of San Diego County a little more north and
You know a ton to do around there and that trip ended up being
We were having so much fun
We added a day and when that day became our day to go to Legoland and I haven't really talked about that on
The show Legoland was wonderful. We had a great time
Ultimately, I have not been like fast-tracking an episode about it because that's kind of what I have to say about it
So it was very pleasant. My son liked a lot. There's a lot of cool Lego stuff
That doesn't you know, it's neither here nor there it's neither the greatest thing I've ever done ie Casa Bonita nor the
Worst thing I've ever done Elitch Gardens
These seem like the avenues to make a good PTR. So it's caught in that middle
Maybe I don't know we I'm sure we could do it at some point. You should get down there with your daughter Mike
Well, and that maybe it can all coalesce into something
But what I actually want to talk about is something that back in that trip that I did on my way back
A place where I stopped to grab a bite and I actually picked up a couple of things for you guys. Oh
I've been sitting on this for a while
Let me throw it your way crinkle crinkle
Why I'll decide this is for you Mike because this looks like what you put on the rim of an alcoholic drink or a non
Alcoholic drink here. Can you catch that? I think I can that is
Sound effect for the mic. Yeah, really that is some
breaking bad blue rock candy
Officially licensed product
And I will toss to you I mean that's the big ticket item, but I also wanted somebody to get and therefore Jason you will get
Crunch Los Poyos Hermanos
gummy chicken
So we have here official breaking bad food stuff my gosh now
Enjoy that but mainly is this does this make your head Mike go to where I might have picked up these items. Oh
That's a go interesting. Oh
Hmm, and it's on the way to Legoland. It is I mean it's in that county
It's in sort of like I forget if it's Riverside of San Diego
But you know kind of like south. I mean, should I say the town? Yeah, say the town is Temecula
Yeah, do you now that you really did you do it? I went to no way swing in cafe
Dean Norris's
barbecue
In Temecula, which if you're listening closely to the show Mike has mentioned. Oh my god a handful of times
your fascination with this place with an Instagram account where
Dean Norris Hank from Breaking Bad
Slash total recall and all that great stuff before Breaking Bad
Where he he pops in he talks about like I'm grilling up great stuff today. All right, we're out of meat
We're out of ribs today. Don't work coming. You're driving in. Don't come sorry about that
Out of it handle you don't got chairs either
Yes, I went to Dean Norris's barbecue restaurant in Temecula
I've been sitting on this for six months so much bigger news than my six months. My god
And it was the main thing making me want to do because honestly Lego land
I just don't have that much to say all very pleasant nice
Yeah
But but what I was wanting to put in there was this reveal secret was you guys catching a bag of candy meth?
This is six month old candy man. Yeah
Six month old candy. I can't imagine it impacts Jason
Shelf stable. I'm not really worried. This might be years old
in the initial batch of the
During Breaking Bad mania ten years ago breaking bad candy at his
Well, this was one of my big questions is how is his celebrity?
Reflected in the restaurant, right?
Now I didn't have I'd say the full experience especially because I didn't have barbecue what this ended
This was on the way back from Escondido
So it made sense as a breakfast as a pre-drive breakfast a great breakfast nothing too Breaking Bad about it
I mean I may have I'm trying to remember if I
Broke the bacon into my age
Be the way there is a lot of breakfast in Breaking Bad actually, yeah, it does all it does thematically tie together
But I haven't done barbecue. That means I think Mike you got to do barbecue. You got to get down there
I maybe make it part of a Lego land or you know, you're in San Diego for a mount
That's what I was saying. Yeah dad have the full experience and maybe ideal worlds
We got to try to get a whole Dean Norris. Well, I pitched to the doughboys that we take a party bus to Temecula
Not agreed to it
And I was like if we could get Dean on the party bus either to or coming from
Wow, I'm not no one's approved that no one has said this is happening. It's a big leap to from his now
We're talking it. Well, I don't know
Seven people minimum. Why why not? Why should I? Yeah, let's do the fucking party bus
Yeah, this is I got exhausting months ahead of us if at the end of that
Oh, yeah, I was taking a party bus to Temecula to hang with Hank
I think there's no doubt we could talk to Dean if he's around. I don't know we get him on the bus
I mean we get him on the bus if the bus is parked outside the place. Yeah, I'm sure we could do like couple shots
It's technically, you know, it's old town. It's it's not the widest streets. That's the only warning about the bus
But we can't this man. I don't know the whole alien. We might have to like pull up and pull up behind
Yeah, you know old old dusty roads. That's part of the charm of old town Temecula. Yeah, I gotta push
Yeah, I've pushed a couple ideas on doughboys about
Barbecue guy
Great sure who doesn't it seems so it looks solid from the Instagram. Yeah, and
We're worth trying. Yeah boy. Well if we a good little experience I had I'd love to do the full tilt experience
And this is my way of saying as we think about
2025 when my insanity is done and I'm back
I
Know probably before that a little bit, but the this is my way of saying should we make it official?
Celebrity to yes, celebrity to is where we do is happening. We're really calling shots today. Yeah. Yeah
I mean cuz I want to think ahead I want to have a big PCR thing to look forward to
besides an episode at Indiana Jones to for which I am absent
What if it's Indiana Jones to with Tony Baxter
But I waited I think it'll happen but opportunities and I have to turn down others
Well, let's you know, because I've been keeping a running. I I have notions and pitches of what could go into celebrity, too
Yeah, I think there's very cool possibilities and this could certainly be one
if my work is
Delayed if I if Marvel if Feige fires me and rehires me and I get preoccupied again, we could just
Turn it into celebrity April
We could we sure. Yeah, always the bump option. However
Celeb you may is a harder sell. I'd say right
So it's so let's let grammar drive it. But besides that, I think that could be good. So celebrity to coming Wow
2025 and
This added to the list of joy of wonderful things going on. Thank you guys for being awesome through this
Thank you audience
For support and hey you survived podcast the ride big block of Scott news
For three bonus episodes every month check out podcast throughout the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club
Three, you will find all that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride
Which I I really was not avoiding Kingdom Keepers
I promise I promise the day that he was boy that he ended up the day of the water break
I listened to a fifth of it on
Audiobook I even had I also had a physical copy from the library, okay
So it was my intent. So I hope you will there will be no accusations of me
I don't know timing this cannot do Kingdom Keepers. Can you throw out a couple specific?
Do you remember some of the names of the characters?
I mean, I have Finn but it is very closely close to me saying Finn Wolfhard and I know that's not right
It's not right. No, that's an actor in our world at this point
I don't know if you'll have time to listen to the club three episode that we just put out
But the club I will say this the club three episode ended with a discovery of another
All-star rock and roll band made up of non
Musicians was this the rock bottom remainders?
The author of it Ridley Pearson
The fact I can say was was the architect together like they didn't we talk about a weird guy who was the guy who put together?
Ringo's all-star band once. Yes, we did Pearson, right is the catalyst of
Which had what like Amy Tan?
Mac Groening Mac Groening. Yeah, they played with Warren's Yvonne in 97
Wow, they were on Craig Ferguson is their final like TV appearance
But it but if again if you don't if if you want to go subscribe
Listeners if you want to hear about Kingdom Keepers
But also at the end a bunch of authors in a rock and roll band because they did and PR tiny desk concert
Ah, and they did sloop John B
Well, then I am being felt so you're you're around discussion of a band that
Roy Blount jr. Is in and they sounded fine
Sure, they sounded. Okay. Sure. This is a pro
Well, you know the pod bottom remainders is gonna have to all the
Podcasters with mild musical talent are gonna have to get together a project to do kind of in my you know
Maybe that's what it cast away. We'll do cast away by Green Day. We'll do
Morning Church on Sunday
All this stuff the warning era. Yeah use this time use any time while I'm gone to jam
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett bomb Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcast keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook
You