5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Ayy, callin' all daddy-os and nifty chicks
Why don't you doo-wop a doobie down to the podcast
The Ryder Rooney's Big Second Gate Hop
Unless you're cruisin' for a bruisin'
Ayy, it's me, it's Scott Gertner
Oh, no more of that
Scott Gertner, it's Jason Sheridan
Hey, you better watch yourself, Scott
Or I'm gonna tell you to sit on it
Boy, you drop characters so fast
You look like you wanna shooby-dooby down into my fist-a-roony
Hey, yakity yak, don't talk back, Jason
We all caught on to the same type of thing about this
Which requires some backtracking, some explaining
But clearly the same type of thing as a vice grip on all of us
Today we are talking about a Disneyland event called Blast to the Past
To the Past, not from the past
That's the movie about the people in the bomb shelter
This is Blast to the Past
Where Disneyland blasted you to the past
Specifically the 1950s mixed with a little bit of 60s
This is an event that was held in 1988
And was successful enough to carry over into 1989
And we are piecing together what this event was
From some photos, some parade videos
And from a syndicated TV special that Disney put together
In I think the first year of doing it
Hosted by Bowser from Sha Na Na
This is sort of what we're working with
John Bowman
Is that how you pronounce it?
John Bowser Bowman
Who has never come up on this show before
I don't think so
Unless it's just a stray thing
I mean it feels like impossible that we haven't somehow
Because was Sha Na Na or at least him
Not on like the Brady Bunch variety hour
Which we covered a while back
It seems very possible
But that's sort of I think what we're dealing with here
Is 80s nostalgia for the 50s
Which was pretty strong
I mean there was a lot of this in the 70s
And I guess a little bit in the 80s as well
50s by way of 80s
Sha Na Na started
Sha Na Na was like a revival band comedy act
That started in 69
So they started their 50s nostalgia in 69
Because they were at Woodstock, correct?
I believe so, yeah
They are the main
I feel like I've said before on the show
In my theory that Woodstock actually kind of sucked
Because if you really look at that lineup
I mean I think the best of the best of that lineup
Was unbelievable and historic
And rightfully praised
But you look at the full Woodstock
Especially Sha Na Na
Sha Na Na makes no sense
Because they were a 50s doo-wop
It's the harmonizing
Where somebody's
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa
And then Bowser
Who kind of had celebrity beyond and outside of
Sha Na Na was the
Bop-a-bop-a-bop-doo-doo-doo-doo
Yeah, he had the deep voice
Let's unpack your attitude
Because you're groaning
You're huffing and puffing
I just
The 50s nostalgia
Specifically for the
Grease happy days
50s nostalgia
Not even happy
I feel like happy days is more nuanced than
This is like
Throwback burger shop
Nostalgia
And that's the only place I think I really like it
It's like oh if I'm eating a hamburger
And I can pick out the song
On a tiny jukebox on the table
You're right
I like the feeling of flipping
Those little metal pages
And having something to do with the table
I don't think I've been near one of those in a long time
Having the milkshake
In your glass and then they leave
The silver
The gnarly silver cup
That exists so people's hands
Don't get destroyed by a milkshake
Machine
The 50s nostalgia you tolerate is mainly food oriented
Yes
Johnny Rockets style
Yeah, Johnny Rockets probably the most
Known
You have nostalgia for Johnny Rockets
A place that was absolutely
God-awful when we went there years ago
In the first city walk
I had a nice day though
I remember
I ate like a hot dog I think alone
And I was watching out into the fountain area
And I remember going this is pretty good
I'm having a good time here
I think that might have been one of my outings at Johnny Rockets
Where everything is like wet
You had the wet burger
You had the ketchup bottle and just a bunch of water fell out
And I'm like how
How is that possible?
It's not even ketchup water
My guess is all the same things happened to Mike
But you were having a nice city walk day
And you didn't even notice
It was soaking wet hot dog
But I liked it because I was enjoying myself
Just day wise
Watching this
Which
Saying it's syndicated makes sense
Because there's a lot of Southern California stuff in it
But like
Bowser has the
Writing credit as well
And there's really not a lot of sketch
Like there's like him on the
Jungle cruise going whoa
I got lost
I was trying to find the
Wait who is it?
The main singer
Little Anthony
I was trying to find Little Anthony
And then I got on his boat
What's this all about?
I wrote that line
I was impressed to see the writing credit
When we finished recording
I had to go right to getting an MRI
And watching him
Watching him do some of these
Oh can you believe I've been
Doing this for 15 years
I'm like I wish I was in the tube
I wish I was
Xanned out in the MRI
Tube
Rather than watching his bits
I'm going to be thinking about
Palmin
Start tossing
And turning and they're going to go like sir
Please no movement
What are those sounds? Those are normal
The other sounds
We're not hearing that Jason
I think that's in your brain Jason
Splish splash
Just craving the metal grind
Just craving the loud poop
I wish I had the earplugs
I wish I was in the tube
This is fascinating to me Jason
I'm just fully preparing to come in here
As the negative Nellie
And the one to
I didn't know
I assume if there's something that I
Viemently dislike that you two are going to like it
That's just my assumption at this point
So to hear this from Jason is great
Because I'm like 5 minutes into the special
And I'm watching some of this parade
Which is very much in that
Like bang da wang da wang
Shibby wibby wibby
And I'm like it had never occurred to me
So much until watching this
I hate 50s shit
I didn't know it
Now I can shout it from the rooftops
I don't think I knew
And now this special has taught me
50s shit sucks
We've okay so I don't remember how many years ago it was
But there was a discussion on this show
I don't know if it was specifically like
Doo-wop style music
But the two of you were very much in lockstep
Against Doo-wop in general
We've been through this before really
So we blasted before
Now I was not saying
I love bang cha bang cha bang
Like I was not arguing that
But I was arguing I like some of it
But you two were both in lockstep about like
I hate the doo-boo-boo-wop
Yeah you both said that
I remember this and I don't remember what episode it was
Some of this
Like the songs removed from the like
Hey it's a 6th grade dance
And it's bobby sock themed
And I'm like oh god
I don't care about that either
I was never a big happy days guy
And I recently too
I guess I didn't watch a lot of happy days
But apparently they kind of like quietly got rid of the 50s
Toward the end of happy days
I don't know what season it was
But they kind of just like quietly were like
They're not in the 50s anymore
Well especially as like Joni
And Chot and then the spin off Joni Loves Chot
Yeah cause 50s is too exhausting
But like yeah I don't have any
Affection for this
I don't have any affection in general
For like the poodle skirt
Grease is okay
Some of the songs are okay but I'm not a big grease guy either
I'm not a grease guy at all
I think maybe though
Because alright I started watching this
And that was my big alright 50 shit
And then I started analyzing
I was kind of arguing with Erin a little bit
Because she likes some 50 stuff
And she was like I think you need to
Create a separation here
Because there's probably like
Some stuff from the 50s that's not so mired
In the shuwapawada
You probably like
I think what she's saying what you don't like
Is latter day
Retro for the 50s
Which is that's what grease is
That's what happy days is
But I think happy days is a whole other thing
Happy days doesn't annoy me whatsoever
I mean it went for so many years
I think there is nuance in there
And I really like
American Graffiti
Like that's a little more gnarly
Aggressive cartoonish 50s
It's a very like down beat
Tonal like yeah
No that's not like oh gee whiz
It's like it's a you know
I feel like he actually really takes you to
His 50s
But shauna na clearly is the worst
Of it right
Because we
I like Fonzie
I love Henry Winkler
I got no problem with any of that
I got no copy of a copy to
We're gonna shooby dooby
To the main street pop
And also see the fantasy land hop
And I'm like kill me
Kill me
But you know Fonzie may have stolen the bit
From Bowman from Bowser here
Because it started
It's like a year later or something
So maybe he stole it
I'm not saying I know that
Bowser looks like John Casavetti
John Casavetti
With no charisma
Like John Casavetti is a very
Good like interesting
Kind of weird guy like weird
Performer
I don't want to be wrong here
Well when is the
Pilot made for love american
Style
Oh it doesn't start until 74
74 okay
And the love
Love and the television set
Later retitled love and the happy days
Was 72
American Graffiti 73
So Shawna is before
All of this stuff
They are leading
We're not even out of the 60s and we're doing 50s throwback
Is really interesting
Here's a little
Bit of history
Related to everything we're talking about
And some of this
I got from Jim Hill
I was like did they ever do an episode
And they did a little mini episode about
The past event and he provides some very
Interesting context that
So apparently I think they had
The title blast to the past and they were doing
These sorts of seasonal
Events
Or that ran for like a long time
That like you know blast to the past
Is going to be a big deal that goes for a lot of
The year and before that they had done
A state fair thing
Circus
Event circus fantasy
We'll do circus fantasy
But this had been
They had been starting to do these in the mid
80s at Disneyland
As Jim said
Part of the reason for these events was
To adjust
Like local Disneyland
Goers to the idea that Disneyland
Is now open 7 days a week
All year. This was not the case
Until Eisner
I think Eisner era becomes
What do you mean we close the parks
That makes no sense. But then how do we teach
People to come on a Tuesday while there's this special
Event
So Eisner had an
Influence on this thing happening
At all but then also I think they
Realized some nostalgia based
Event would be good to do
And maybe it's something about eras
Right and over here you know
Here in frontier land
There'll be a little like 1910
Zone and then the 80s or
It's in the 80s the 60s
Or what in Tomorrowland or whatever
And it was all pitched to Eisner and he said just 50s
50s only that's the only thing we care about
That's all we should push
And this sort of
Ties into some Eisner history
Because when he was
The head of paramount pictures
He green lit Greece
And when he ran
ABC he green
Lit happy days. So
Eisner is sort of behind
These big pillars of 50s
Throwback you know this
Pop culture that kept the 50s alive
In these giant ways and
Also on top of that
Happy days is going there's a
Pilot I love American
Style episode that started it
And he
His note to Gary Marshall
Early on was like I think we're
Missing a big area we don't have like a greaser
Guy we need a tough
Greaser guy and I think that's what's going to
Push this show over the top
So Eisner created
The Fonz. Eisner created the Fonz
Isn't that nuts? That is nuts
No he didn't name the character
I think what was in his head was a
Six foot tall tough
Mostly silent guy
Which is now what the Fonz ended up
Being but the general area
Of the Fonz comes
From Eisner which this is another
One of those things this you know
So much of the Disney media
That we look at and that we're forced
To mire through so
Veemently anti-Eisner
And this is where like
Before even the Disney
Stuff starts he created the Fonz
Let's give this man that's
Insane and compared to like how network
Notes are today
Does anybody does any
Dumb executive suggest anything nearly
As good as what leads
To the Fonz that's insane
Yeah probably not
A lot of other horrible ideas but
Of course but they didn't
We don't remember those necessarily
Compared to Eiger I mean here I'm picking the worst
Of Eiger but compared to Eiger
Suggesting a TV show based on
Fountains of Wayne Stacey's mom
Week after
Week underage
Sexual hijinks this will be
A huge hit
Well if he gave it to Gary Marshall maybe it would have worked
Maybe Gary Marshall could have made Stacey's mom
The show work I can work with this
He's an
Attractive mom
I like it
Have you considered Penny
I think Penny would knock this out of the park
Tie it in
Tie it in to your already successful
Show she's the blackish
Family's neighbor
She lives next door and sometimes they stop
By then the whole neighborhood
Is a big universe of shows
He's very smart did Eiser
Say also make him as cool as I was
When I was 20 something
Here I have some reference photos and
It's all him
He brought the blue windbreak
Put him in this blue windbreaker
Or was he
Switch it to a leather jacket
That's good because Fonzie
Didn't wear his signature leather jacket
In the first season
I think it was tan wasn't it
His windbreaker
What the fuck
That's not in the Smithsonian
Fuck you windbreaker
I was very
Excited like 12 year old
11 12 year old we went to the Smithsonian
And I was like
I gotta see Fonzie's jacket
And I gotta see the ruby
Red slippers
You liked Happy Days despite not liking the 50s
I liked Fonzie
Happy Days aired a lot
When Nick and I first got
The rights to Happy Days
They showed it so much
I watched it
It didn't stick with me like other old shows
Sure sure
But you see any of it and you appreciate it
And yeah look that's an end of this 50s stuff
That is fine and good
Sometimes and more
Good than what we're dealing with here
Now let's talk a little
You know I don't think the special
Is required viewing for this
Episode I think we can talk about stuff from it
But you know I don't want this to be like a
Play by play of the special because there was also
This event going on
That has some stuff worth talking about
I don't think I realized in my head I'm like
Well this is like to get LA locals in
Something different
As an excuse to go to Disneyland
I didn't realize this was a national event
With a tie in to McDonald's
A national TV ad
With one of the
Biggest stars of the time
Wow
Okay yeah that's about how
Much in video form
That 15 to 30
Seconds I can kind of handle that
And also little Richard
Is you know great
Yeah sure
He gives us all and that's a kick
Ass ad for listeners who aren't looking
At that this is a giant juke box
Which I think might have been part of the staging
Of the whole thing
And also I mean what a good
Event like besides the Disneyland stuff
McDonald's is doing throwback prices
That you could
It was like the monopoly game where you
Peel and win and there were a lot of like
If you
If you peeled the right
Stick or whatever you might
End up getting to go to Disneyland
For 6 dollars
Back when the regular
Price I think was 25
Dollars that's a good
Deal
Right now they're doing like I think you can get
A ticket for 69 dollars because it's the
69th anniversary of Disneyland
So that's the close yeah
That's tricky for them
I know they're trying to skate through this
Somebody said that they're saying it's the
Welcome it's the journey
To the 70th birthday of Disneyland
Let's try
Let's not acknowledge what year
No they are selling
Pins that say 69
On it oh really but are they
Any shirts or anything I don't know
They didn't have like a big 69 Disney
And Mickey like giving a thumbs up
Yeah
We should find
Come on down to Disneyland in 69
Can you get
Walk around Deadpool to
Talk about 69
No 69th anniversary
Walk around Deadpool has a lot of limits on him
Walk around Deadpool should cuss
He should cuss
Hey what's up dip shits
You know
He might say well what up dip
He might say like
If he could self censor that would be funny
That would be funny yeah
Do you have
Jason you've now just watched you boasted
About now having actually watched two of the
Deadpool films yeah do you have a better sense of
The kind of thing he would say I
Yes well
I've read a fair amount of Deadpool comics
So but
I like the movies I thought
I mean the second one if you follow the
Logic too far becomes like
Wait that's a puzzle like
The first one's logic is rock solid though
No I didn't say the first one but there's
Time travel elements in the second one
It's a little more convoluted I guess in the second one
Yeah but I think it's just a gag
Don't think about it too hard because it kind of pays
Off with some jokes in
The credits but if we're
Trying to expand what we know Deadpool
Says beyond Chimichanga
Do you have like a greater sense
Of his vocabulary now
I think so yeah fuck like
If Deadpool
If Deadpool and California
Adventure like hey what's up fuck
Now calls are like
Is that the kind of thing that's what this is
He does and also he only says
Chimichanga is like once or twice a movie
It is I thought it was going to be every
Scene
I thought it was
I thought he said it a lot but he mostly
Says it towards the finale
Like towards the climax
That's funny you thought it was going to be in every
Is there any movie where like a character says a
Thing in every like a catch phrase in every
Scene well I am Groot
That's true
That's at least limited yeah
Yeah yeah
I haven't seen the movies in a while so
Yeah it's the first one especially
I feel like there's some outdated
References even for the movie I like movies
Fine but
Look Scott we can get into like characterization of Deadpool
And what my favorite characterization of Deadpool
Is and it's not quite the Ryan Reynolds
Jim Carrey light
Sort of delivery we could get into that
Or we could talk about almost anything
That's true
Alright John Bowser Bauman
These are my choices
And it's
Either I hear comic book artist names
Or I hear John Bowser Bauman
Here's the rule Scott if you want us to get back on topic
You have to go do do do do
That could carry outside
Of this episode
You know a thing we talked about
On a recent episode was like
Knowing something primarily as a comedy
Reference point and that's how I knew
Seananah
Well yes I was like why do I have
Bowser from Seananah
In my head in a musical way and it's because
Of Adam Sandler's Hanukkah song
This is the main way I think he is known today
Bowser from Seananah
And Arthur Fonzarelli
Look at that
They're on the comedy
Bang Bang podcast Andy Daly
I believe is Donnie character
Of like the other guy from Seananah
And just mostly
I know Seananah from him going like
Like
Over and over again
I remember now that I think
I was saying you guys don't like 50s
Do-wop stuff and I go
Do you like the Heathcliff theme
That was your example of 50s music
I was like well
The Heathcliff theme is good
Heathcliff Heathcliff
No one should terrorize the neighbors
You offered and you remembered
And you're willing to admit that you offered as an example
Of good 50s culture
The Heathcliff theme
You know what I was
I was trying to think of like
In this special
Little Anthony appears
And I like these songs that he plays
And he does think I'm going
Out of my head
I'm like oh wait this I like a lot
I guess I do like 50s stuff then I look it up
That's a 60s song that came out a little later
I realized there's not
A lot from the 50s proper
A lot of I think what we imagine
In movies and TV
Is like popular culture
This is what the 50s look like
It's like well it's kind of what the start of the 60s
Look like
It all bleeds together
I was also in trying to conjure
50s stuff I like
I realized Everly Brothers
I like all those Everly Brothers songs
And then on the way out the door
I caught this fact that I'd never heard before
Did you know that the Everly Brothers
Took up on stage
At Knott's Berry Farm
Yeah how about that theme park
History we never talked about
They were in the second
Of three sets
In 1973
And they just broke
Enough was enough
Let's see Don
Is clearly incapacitated
Playing erratically and forgetting lyrics
In frustration Phil smashes his guitar
And says I'm tired of
Being an Everly Brother
The Everly Brothers died 10 years ago
And then he stormed off stage
And then they still had to do the third set
So which
That was just Phil and Don
Did not
Then did a solo set and then that was the end
Of 73
So there's a little bit of
That's cool
They didn't just kind of quietly
Fuck you I'm leaving
Backstage
Fuck it I'm going on Montezuma's Revenge
And then I'm getting out of here
I was imagining him pissed on a roller coaster
Like trying to clear his head
And calm down so he could drive
Like on
Soapbox
Is it soapbox racers
Wacky soapbox racers
I need to go on a wacky soapbox race
Clear my head and then I'm getting the fuck out of here
No more Everly Brothers
But anyway
Let me say some stuff about the
Events generally
Beyond the special
So let's see Big McDonald's
Promotion
They as part of
They had several special events within the big event
One was
A world record
Attempt at
The most hula hooping
At once
The super duper hooper
A bunch of people
A ton of people
1,200 hula hoopers
All hula hooped
In a super duper fashion in front of the castle
So that happened and then there was also
The world's biggest twist
Also occurred
With Chubby Checker himself
That was even more people
Those 2,000 twisters
That the world's largest twist party
Both of these records
Have been usurped
Since
By spirited groups of people
Backing up a corporation and I say good job
I mean I wouldn't know how to get
A big twist party together
A world record breaking one
Could we get our listeners all to twist
At the same time one day
How long do they have to twist for
Good question I don't know
What constitutes you'd have to talk to the Guinness people
We could do that I think we could do that
It's just one back and forth count
And does it count if everybody's doing it separately
In their homes or cars
Or gyms
They could record it with a time stamp
On video
That's proof that everybody did it at the same time
In today's
With today's technological advancements
And in our fractured world
There's no need for everyone to be twisting in one place
Isn't it more beautiful
To create the ultimate twist party
Internationally
In a lot of ways
There was so much stuff going on
At this event
More than stuff happens now I feel like
Is it very committed to
Lots of mini events
Within the big event
Tomorrowland Terrace transformed into
The Rainbow Diner
There was a beach party
Everybody's rocking with Goofy
Which was a different show over by
Small World
Which I saw listed as a big show happening
In Small World Mall
Small World Mall
Never heard that characterization of that area
I like it
Where the Disney Afternoon Avenue happened
The original
Term of mall
Like an outdoor promenade
Taking it back to the roots
Very cool
There is
I think a quick version
Of that in this special where
It's in
Frontierland I feel like
But Goofy and
Donald are arguing about being
The big Kahuna
I think that's still in Small World
I think that's where it is
You can see that deep back there
Although it's
Tough because
This special
We end up having to look for
And for fun looking for old Disney specials
On YouTube a lot
If it comes straight out of your VHS
Warts and all
I'm happy
We've done it quote
AI restored
Get the fuck out of here
What do you mean AI restored
Have you guys noticed this
This is a thing with a lot of old stuff on YouTube
That people think that you can clean it up
By running it through
So I just ran it through this filter
And then it made it all sharp
And yeah it made everybody's faces mush
And look like weird squish monsters
With strangely sharp noses
And features
The colors are fucked up on this
Just put it out
On your tape
Don't AI restore
This is a garbage process
This one has
The one I watched had the commercial blacks in it
Like the 10 seconds
The really long
Long black space
I'm feeling cranky
And cantankerous about this
I watched
Some guy's home movie
And I don't think he AI
Restored it
And it's pretty good footage
This shows the parade and the music performance
What it was like on the ground
Yes and there's a gift shop
Footage which I love
Just going into the different shops or whatever
In the description he complains about
Splash Mountain going away
But other than that everything is pretty good
Video wise to look at
Yeah Jane was
In the background
Like recent like one or two hours
Like home movies
Disney World
And Universal like 91
Or 92
And just a raw rip
Right from VHS and upload it
And that's good shit
At the Rainbow Diner they would have
Like a different show too
And there was a woman in a red dress
Who would run around while she was singing
And sit on all the dads
Laps and like touch
Their faces like very aggressively
And I was like
Let's get back to this
Let's bring this back to Disneyland
I started getting really fired up
About it
But I was interested to see
We should go let's go this weekend we're gonna go
Hey why don't we go
Pack up the trailer we're going
Let's go today
It's interesting though cause like I wonder
What year that they were like
You cannot touch the guests anymore
When did that go away?
What year? Cause obviously like in modern
There's no performers touching a guest
Anymore at Disneyland I assume
But like this had to go away
I don't know if something happened or if it was just
Maybe it was recent maybe somebody out there
Knows the answer when did Disney say
By the way you cannot touch the guests if you're a performer
Something tells me it was Biden
Oh is it Biden? Oh yeah maybe it was
Maybe at the start of his term
He slipped that into a big bill
And nobody noticed
It's in Build Back Better
Oh it's in Build Back Better
No aggressive face touching
No love for the dads
We love our dads
But we don't show them love
I would be pretty upset if a character
Just started touching my face
This is a woman
It wasn't even like Mickey or Minnie
I guess you hug the characters
If they want
But as far as a human performer
Sitting on a dads lap
In the middle of the day are you kidding me
There's no way that's happening ever again
That's not going to be
What I can't tell is if you are
Mike if you're like good
This filth is gone or if you are
Pining for a bygone era
That's the conflict in all of us isn't it
This shouldn't be happening
But oh
If only a performer would come and touch me with one finger
On the forehead
It's a weird
Struggle we all have right?
If it's in me it's deep deep
Deep down in me
It's less at the forefront I'd say
But okay
It's so funny
Because the 80's were not that far removed
From the fit
It was only 30 years
And I wish there was a parade on Main Street
Right now where everyone's dancing
To like Maisie Star
They're dancing
To the hits of 1994
It is interesting in general because I think there's
Like there's I don't think there'll ever be
Like a big revival
That sweeps the nation
There's not going to be like popular music
Like Big Band again or something
Because there's just pockets of
Revivals happening now
And you can just go and choose whatever
I'm sure there's somebody doing
50's music right now that's 25
Years old
Can I just check something really fast
Maisie Star
I had a feeling
Okay I had heard both
Just checking I wasn't sure myself
That song had a revival
Because a few seasons in
The Riverdale gang
Goes to prom and they slow dance
To that song
That's why you remember that
Then I started to really like that song
I forgot about that song
But I think the Zoomers
Also like
That's one where it's like a two day
Like it just gets a ton of Spotify
Streams and Tiktok videos
But yeah I don't know if
Like we'll ever have like a full night
Like indie rock and stuff
There's so much stuff you can listen to that sounds like
Early 90's rock and roll
But it's not on the radio
It's not sweeping the nation like
Brian Setzer Orchestra did or
Big Bad Voodoo Daddy where it was like
This is one of those like
In the 90's no one on
Earth was calling it rock and roll
This is the most perma 60's
Brain you have
In the 90's Nirvana rock and roll
Some good old
Stone Temple Pilots here with some good old
Fashion rock and roll
Mr. Rock and roll is in this
Special
That's a good point but it doesn't help Mike's case
Oh it doesn't at all
1996 Wilco's being there
Jeff Tweedy is a fairly young man
He talks about rock and roll
In the songs a couple of those songs
Well that's one band yes that's where he's at
Musically am I crazy with this are you
This is one of these things it's just like a needle
In my brain is the rock and roll
That's really what it is
You really do rock and roll
Rock and roll is fun to say
You know I would say boy you know Pavement
For my money has to be one of the great rock and
Rock and roller bands
I don't say rock and rollers like
In a casual conversation I would say you know one of my
New favorite rock and rollers are
I'm really interested boy genius
They really are great rock and rollers
There is a cut off
What is the cut off of rock and roll then
Smash Mouth
Rock and roll I think it is rock and roll
I mean I guess boy genius is kind of rock
And roll it's just very like low key
I don't know it's sadder
A lot of it is sad
A lot of the Phoebe Bridgers music is sad but is it rock
And roll I don't know is it rock
Even what would I call it I'm not sure
I know I know I like
Saying rock and roll though and I don't think
I shouldn't take this away from me it's just a big
It's a big semantics argument
Hey hey my my rock and roll will never die
That's my motto
When it comes to the phrase rock and roll
More so than the music
I would love to hear Mr. Rock and roll go like
We've got a new song from Phoebe Bridgers
Coming right up
Tay off in Kehoe
Is he alive?
That was another question I had
Is Mr. Rock and roll still alive?
Well rock and roll will never die
I know that
But Mr. Rock and roll can die
Because he's a DJ from K-earth that they bring out
In one of these specials or in the special
I should say
I thought Mr. Rock and roll
Was Alan Freed
The DJ who is name checked
I believe the guy
There's a movie called Mr. Rock and roll
The Alan Freed story
But somebody says Brian Byrne
From K-earth is Mr. Rock and roll
They refer to him as Mr. Rock and roll
A number of times
Unless he picked up the moniker
I'm seeing him also
But that doesn't seem fair
I feel like there was a lot
Of Mr. Rock and roll
He has registered the trademark
So he owns it
While it's associated with Alan Freed
He's the only one
Who is legally Mr. Rock and roll
So I can't argue with that
I'm Mr. Rock and roll
That's what I feel about it
Call me Mr. Rock and roll
Because I like the phrase rock and roll
So fuck you Brian and Alan Freed
I don't care what you did, who you discovered
I'm Mr. Rock and roll from now on
Do you consider, let's go into new metal
Do you consider Papa Roach rock and roll
It is rock and roll
That's what it is ultimately
It's all rock and roll
How many Papa Roach fans are like
Oh man, let's go see some goddamn fucking rock and roll tonight
I wanna rock
That's different
But that's what it means, rock and roll is the part of the phrase
Papa Roach doesn't roll, Papa Roach never rolled
Not once
I don't know about that, I haven't listened to a lot of Papa Roach
I haven't either
I know the hits, they may roll
Point me to some deep cuts where Papa Roach rolls
Cut my life in two pieces
Let's all go rock and roll
That's the lyric, yeah
Would you say Mike
It's still rock and roll to you
That's what the song is about
He's right
Billy Joel was right
It's still rock and roll
These artists who said these phrases
40 years ago
Are still right
People go new wave and he goes
New wave, what are you kidding me
This is rock and roll to me
And that's how I feel
What a cool opinion
Let's arc and back to what Billy Joel
Said
I take a lot of life advice from
And philosophy and wisdom from
And by the way, I'm sorry about your recent DUI in the Hamptons
Well, Billy did it
You had to do it
No, he hasn't gotten one
No, Mike did
Oh, you did, okay
Billy Joel is like
Hey, how about some rock and roll music
At his own stage at Madison Square Garden
And it's like, please welcome Papa Roach
Wait, what?
Did he do that?
He's saying like if Billy Joel is trying to be hip
He brings some hip
He's had Olivia Rodrigo
Yeah, that's what I mean
Hip music like Olivia
She rocks
She does rock and roll music
I also, as we're on this point
I disagree with hip
I think calling something hip is the least
Hip way
I think you prove you are not hip by saying that
Olivia Rodrigo, now that's hip
That's some hip cat stuff
That's hip drive there
Hip cat is really what you're looking for
She is a hip cat
That's what I would say, Olivia Rodrigo
She's cool
Can I see your badge?
What?
He's calling me a cop
How do you do, fellow kids and all that
Listening to some nifty music
Like Chapel Rowan, are ya?
I heard that tip from my pal Jason Sheridan
Anyway
The new Beba Doobie song
What?
There's an incubus sample
That I just was made aware of
What's Beba Doobie?
She's an artist, she's probably in her 20s
You weren't quoting Sha Na Na with that?
Beba Doobie
It does sound like a Sha Na Na song though
Hey Dua Lipa
A lot of the modern artists sound like
Sha Na Na songs
That's why it's all rock and roll
It all sounds like that
Do you know the Hot to Go dance?
The what?
The Chapel Rowan
H-O-T-T-O-G-O
I know that
You know this dance
I know the dance a little
Who's hip for Jason or I?
Jason
Jason by a lot
Which is crazy because I wouldn't call Jason hip either
I wouldn't
I think by far Jason
That's okay
I'm more of a classic guy
Who's sort of timeless in a lot of ways
Jason is hip
Jason's going to fade out though
Faster because he's so hip
He's going to become more obsolete
He's too much hip to handle, he's going to burn out
The human body can't handle that much hipness
I know all about the Rizzler and Big Justice
And all the families on TikTok
Doing videos that I don't
Understand
Let's be clear, he doesn't understand it
But he knows it, he can say the names of it
Mr. Rock and Roll
That's my name from now on
That will help with the hip cause
If it's long enough
I could just start calling myself
The Nature Boy
Well there's been multiple Nature Boys
You want to be associated with the Nature Boy
With Ric Flair?
No, I'm taking it back
We're stealing people's names
If it's like someone did it 40 or 50 years ago
It's like fair game
It's the wrestling
Copyright
Now Jason is apparently the Nature Boy
And I'm the Noid
Oh shit
There might only be a Noid
I'm the Noid
What else about this?
His weird
Open mic night standup
Where do they find these
Cafeteria workers
And that is 5 minutes after
These guidance counselors always telling you
What to do, hey
If they knew what to do
They would have a better job than guidance counselors
These hair nets
So the special just to be clear
Mainly
Strings together
50's music performances
Some from little Anthony
Authentic performer
From the era
Some are like the kind of the doo-wop groups around Disneyland
And they show a lot of the parade
The main street hop
It was the main
I'd say big show piece
Of this Disneyland event
But it's all strung together with these
Bowser from Sha Na Na
Who's like what he's like it's sleeveless shirt
It's black sleeveless shirt
And slick back hair
And yeah he's that guy
He's a sub Fonzie right
And I guess I didn't know that was his deal
Is that he is like a the way things used to be
Type standup
I knew about like
Bowser is like grease I didn't know
He might be playing up to it in the
Special the cold open
I think is worth watching
Yeah you alerted us to that I had watched it
When you texted me you were like oh my god this opening
So then I was anticipating it and it didn't let me down
That it's him
I don't think I recognized him at first
Imagine that I didn't recognize Bowser
But he
He's like fixing a car
He's just in front of a house with a car
It's like the cheapest little set up you're seeing
And he's he says like
Don't you
You ever want to just sometimes
Get out of the 80s
Go back to a time
When Madonna
Wait what
I remember that one line
Madonna and child
We said with twisted sister
What would happen when
Parents would come home after your sister
Was babysitting or something
Twisted sister in
My 88 we're still we got a
I'm sick of it I'm so sick of
Twisted sister everywhere
I go there are some lines
In over
Like just a black screen and they do
Say the computers are out
And I'm like very funny we just had
A giant computer outage what you're saying
That history repeats itself
Now this I don't know when
This episode yeah this might come out in a while
Well
I think it was still impactful
I think people still be talking about the crowd strike
Outage because
Good justification actually you know
What's crazy is that the 50s
To the 80s were actually as long
Ago as the crowd strike outage
Was from when you're hearing this
Time kind of folds in you sort of forget
Weird yeah
Because
When a time when Madonna
And child weren't a rock
Singer and her ex
Husband
Is it Sean Penn at this time
Is that who we're talking about
Sean Penn is like Sean Penn
Is like a child is what he's
Saying so actually really
He's planning for religion
In the 50s when we all
When the Virgin Mary
When there weren't the dirty songs about
Virgins we all just worshiped
The greatest virgin of all
They got these crucifix
Now instead of Jesus this fucking
Alpha there
Alpha puppet
Why is everybody talking about this alien
See an alien
Or a puppet make up your mind
I don't even understand
The show concept I guess
Harry and the Endersons
I'm done good with Harry
He's scary oh thank you
With time when we had Harry Truman
Not Harry and the Endersons
What's your problem dude
One is about when a heavyweight
A time when a heavyweight champ
Is scarier than his wife
Like what was this
Was this a Mike Tyson
I don't know what he's
Good news for Bowser that if he was
Frustrated with this time and the pop culture
Of the time it all soon imploded
And none of it is anything we even
Remember or know what he's talking about
Yeah this whole
Event let me ask
Obviously you don't like 50s
In general but this whole
Event feels cheap to me
When you look at like the way that the jukebox
Is set up on the stages
It looks kind of low rent
Even though there's a lot of stuff going on
Think about it as on the spectrum of Disney
Parades
They're tall set pieces
They're pretty big and I think they
I didn't watch a video of the full
Parade but I read that they were like
Here's a big platter of records
And here's a big
This float looks like a drive in
Movie scene
Within if you're
Maybe it doesn't pop on TV
But I bet if you were there watching the parade
You'd think these are pretty big parade floats
The parade actually looks better than everything else
I guess maybe what it is
It feels so different than what Disneyland does now
And it feels like such a weird
Thing to overlay on Disneyland
That it's just like
It's jukebox and 50s and you're like
And then they're playing different music when you get there
It gives it a different vibe
Which I like but it also kind of
Feels low rent to me at the same time
I'm not even saying low rent is a bad thing I guess
I'm just saying it's like
Well we're maybe also in a time
When
This is pre
They start doing things like the Lion King
Celebration where there's a big pride
Rock float and it stops and all
Show happens in mainstream and it looks like
The movie I don't think we've
Done a lot of massive
Temporary
Build
I think you got to view it from like well at the time
This was a pretty committed
To overlay
Not to be defending it
I know what you're saying that it's kind of chintzy
But I think they hadn't done a lot of this nature
Yeah
We recently of course talked about the country bears
As far as recordings could come out
Years later we don't know
But I guess also though
I do like it because
They would never do this again in Disney
I feel like
There's songs that they probably don't own
In the park
Celebrating the fifth
There's no opportunity there for synergy
They don't have
Happy days on the air or something
Where they have to celebrate the fifties
You're right
It's Star Wars
It all has to be
It's Pixar thing
At Disneyland
It's all stuff that they own
Guess what's coming to Disneyland
Right
So the idea that it would be some sort of
Unrelated tie in
Or unrelated event
To unrelated Disney event
Is cool and that makes me also feel like
It's different from anything they'll ever do again
I don't know if there's a good equivalent
Like what I would want them to do
I can't think of a good pitch off the top of my head
They're going to
It's Disney's big celebration of like
Late nineties Miami
Jock jams
I would like that
That would be good
The real
The real McCoy at Disneyland
Would be awesome
And that's what
Gets me high
Had a way
Yeah
This summer at Disneyland had a way
That's awesome
That's not going to happen
Oh no I think it's going to come out
But I was talking about like an alien invasion
At Disneyland or something
Which would be cool like an event at night
For Halloween
With aliens
But it would have to be like the aliens from Toy Story
Or something
It just feels like
We're in a world where we'll never get
Something truly unique
Even this
Even in an overlay way or even some
Limited time events
Even something you said is chintzy
Which is annoying
We should still be pining for
We should still want something like this
Alien invasion Toy Story aliens
That might be on board for us
Because they're cute
The discussion we had is that the aliens could be scary
That's what we were talking about
This on a second gate
Tomorrowland 2055
Yeah
It was like Henson, Labyrinth, Dark Crystal
Puppet like
And they're just horrific
I said maybe they could be attractive
They could be hot aliens
That was my plus up to it
But I don't know if we figured out a really good middle ground
Could they be both horrific and hot?
Sure
I don't know what it looks like
But if you want to draw that up
As long as they sit on Dad's lap
That's your other requirement
If the aliens could flirt with Dad
By brushing their
Three-fingered hand
Across Dad's face
That would be beautiful
But the only sound they make is a blood-curdling scream
Okay, sure
But louder
Obviously
It translates to come up and see me sometime
There I did one
Sorry, I'm stealing your
We're all stealing other people's names
And I'm stealing your catchphrase
Which is also stolen
So yeah
I also just was like
They used to do
Weirder stuff
And it'll never happen again
Characterizing this as weird
I'm not sure I agree
I did say weirder
So that's the Disneyland scale of weird
Okay, right
We're always dealing with grading
There's levels
Let me talk about one part of the special that jumped out
Which is you get a music
Performance in that
Carnation gardens kind of stage
And this is a thing
Where you get the characters
We get to see the characters
At like a malt shop
Counter
Mickey and Minnie and Donald and Goofy
And they're all in their sweaters
And Mickey's in a letterman jacket
And Minnie's in a poodle skirt
And he's got like
M written in cursive
Like Laverne and Shirley
And they perform an
Acceptable 50s
Kind of routine
And then it ends
And Mickey talks
And I'm like, yes, wrong Mickey
Wrong Mickey is back
This is a piece of wrong Mickey
Content that I have been missing
And he
Says
I didn't write it down exactly
But it's something about
Alright, let's go win the big game
Disney High is number one
Disney High
We have new mythology
The characters all go to Disney High
So they're all teenagers now
In this version
Which is great
As Muppet Babies and Flintstone
Babies have taught us
All your characters who you love
Also were babies together
And probably went to elementary school
They've all been with each other
Their whole lives
I think about this era of
High school
Of the primaries in high school
So yeah, I guess you could think of it
They just went back in time a little bit
I was thinking if you have
Geez Mick, if you haven't
Are you
What do they call being exclusive
Going steady
If they
I notice you and Minnie aren't going steady
Do you mind if I take her out
To the mulch shop
Go sit on it
Go soak your head
By sit on it I mean this
My comb that's actually a blade
Sit on it right now
I'm sticking it up
It's a blade up on the chair
Sit down on this Goofy
You, me
We're drag racing down Main Street
Right now
Get your hat right, we're going
Geez, you shouldn't be drunk for that Mick
Don't tell me you want a tattoo
It gives me the courage to go faster
Courage you don't have
See that is a very stressful scene
In American Graffiti where they destroy
At least one car
Oh where oh where
And Harrison Ford, young Harrison Ford
Has my baby been
There's a Mickey version of that song
Maybe there was like a primary
Who we forgot like Petey Pig
If you were with the characters
In Disney High days
Petey Pig was in the group
But then he went after Minnie
Got into a gnarly drag race
Mickey cheated
Rammed him and that was the end of
Petey Pig
Donald take some pieces out of the engine
Here's what I want you to do
Cut the brakes
This never happened
Zip that beak okay
Then he's
Then Petey Pig is burning
Alive and Minnie's like
Oh no oh geez
You still want to go out with him now
Look how bad of a driver he is
Would you rather go out with a guy
Who's not
A shard corpse
Who's captain of the football team
And currently alive
Suddenly I'm looking a little better
Aren't I
God he never changed he was always like that
Mickey
He never changed
The anger issues started in middle school
And by Disney High
They were raging
I mean how are you going to get to the top though
If you don't have a personality like that
How do you rise to the top of the cartoon heap
You need confidence
You need drive
Principal Walt tried to expel me
I put my blade up to that old
Bastard's neck
You could expel me
Then you'd be dead
You smell like booze Walt
You shouldn't be at school
If you smell like liquor
Who are you to talk
I can turn on this intercom right now
One flip of this button
And everybody will know
Your breath reeks Walt
You just had your last laugh
You just laughed
For the last time
To do run run run
To do run run
I was going to go
There were cars parked in the front
Of Disneyland too
Which made it look kind of like a car show or something
I think that's maybe part why
I thought it looked low rent
It was almost like a showroom
What would happen in a park
A couple cars just parked right by the
Mickey face
By the flowers
I think that was a hit though
I think people were like wow
You know certain types of guys
You see people
People of a certain age
Going to 50's cars
Flies to honey
I'm not one to talk about that
Because when the Bob's big boy
If I see old cars
Driving along the street
I'm like whoa that's a cool car
But my first instinct is like Jay
Jay Leno
Are you driving that
Sometimes it is him
Sometimes it is
They get together what Friday night?
Saturday night? Friday night cuff up your jeans
Slick back your hair head down there brother
I think you're a couple big boy nights
Away from being a 50's guy
I don't like rockabilly
Either
I think I don't know
Try to puff up that hair see what happens
You can do a whole thing
A little setzer
Grow those sideburns
I know you like setzer you're not too far from it
You're a setzer guy
I knew the Bryan setzer orchestra
They were doing big band music
You don't like rock this town?
I do actually like rock this town
You like this stuff I think
He was really close
I think it's almost like
Maybe you don't like poodle skirts
There's some part of it you don't like
But actually you are a 50's guy
I know we did
The Ellie Greenwich leader of the pack
Jukebox musical in high school
Did you perform it?
I was just ensemble
They would just hand out
They would like hey come on Jeff
Like you know Ellie's ex husband Jeff
Sorry I don't know this
I know that name as you wrote that song
This is a musical
With very little story
And it's mostly
I think it made me
I like the songs
I was trying to understand
Barely any story
They were brill building songwriters
People wrote a lot of the early rock and roll songs
But it's about the life of
It's about the life of Ellie Greenwich
Yeah
And I think
He knows more stuff
I know I didn't particularly like it
But like
He thinks he doesn't like the 50's stuff
Because it's 30 years after his era
His general era being the 1920's
But I think you do like the 50's
He resents rock and roll
For shutting out the old music that he prefers
Where are all the tucks and tails
Why do all these cardigans have letters on them
I really should
Just real quick I haven't brought him up on the show
And I've seen him a couple times at the smokehouse
There's a performer named Jimmy Angel
That guest of the show Trevor Zamet
Has turned me on to
Who's an 89 year old man who does 50's music
The first Saturday of every month at the smokehouse
And he hates the Beatles
Because he feels that they ruined rock and roll
That's how hardcore he is
When he says he loves the 50's
That's an opinion
Yes there's still
I would say my own mother is a person of that
Who has that kind of opinion
But who's not 89 years old
Not 89 years old but she was
Oh these Beatles I don't know about these Beatles
This slightly longer
Hair than other people have
Right now
But then he always says Jimmy always says 50's is best
Or whatever but then he does like Del Shannon's
Runaway and I'm looking it up I go this is from 1961
This is what I'm saying
So there are hangover
Songs that people who love the 50's
Consider 50's even though
They were in the 60's
Culturally it's 50's that's ours we claim that
Leader of the pack
That's interesting
Is there a video of that?
No
New York Times writer Frank Rich called the show
An embarrassment
Jason did?
I wondered who that guy was
Taking a lot of notes
It would have been fine save for one
Member of the ensemble who was
Distractingly flat footed
He couldn't find his leather jacket
When they did the leader of the pack
Number yes someone else took it
That's why I had a black t-shirt
On and sunglasses good enough
Who cares
If we're in this 50's area
Can I throw out one more little ramp
That's something you just said Mike
You referenced poodle skirts
I have a theory perhaps an easily disproven theory
But I'm going to throw this theory out there
I think poodle skirts are fake
I think that's not something that was real
That anybody actually did
I think like a dozen people
I think
Maybe one famous person
Wore a skirt with a poodle on it
Once and then many years
Of Halloween costume culture
Made us think that
Every girl every day in the 50's
Wore a skirt with a poodle on it
And I think it's pretend
I think it's like now
If you're like 11 years old
And you kind of poke around
What were things like a couple decades ago
Well everybody wore their
All the girls wore their hair in
Pigtails with pink puffs and they wore
Schoolgirl outfits and you go no
One person did that
Britney Spears only did that
That was not a common style of the time
That is my theory about poodle skirts
Fake
I bet you're on to something I don't know
I don't have a good opinion of what the actual
Usage
Of poodle skirts was
I bet it's more
I bet you're right I bet it's also like
The Goldberg's version of the 80's
Where it's like
Everyone on the Goldberg's dress is like
A cartoonish 80's character
And it's like that was not how everybody looked
Yes your neighbor
Has Duran Duran hair
Yeah yeah
And then your neighbor on the other side is like
A poppin locker
Breaking two electric boogaloo guy
Like certainly there weren't just people
Who were normal people
I was alive in the 80's
There's footage of us in the 80's
Yeah I have some memories
We did not look like that my parents
Did not look like that though hair was maybe a little
Different and you can poke fun in it
But it did not necessarily look like
A cartoon 80's person
You know I wanted to talk though
Because my dad was like
He was like a
Really plastic looking
Kind of digital man
Who would jitter a lot
And he didn't come home a lot so he'd just send videos
And the videos would have like a striped pattern
Going and he would kind of go hello
Son
So I guess my dad was kind of a stereotypical
80's guy
Max Headroom type
Max Headroom much
Now what's that? What are you referring to?
I'm just talking about my own father
I don't know what you're referencing
This is my life
I don't really know that much but actually
I just kind of know it as a reference
And my mom always wore a belt
That said boy toy
Every day of my childhood
My mom did too
I think in the 90's
In 2000
Sock hop 50's throwback
For like a school dance or something
It's like alright these
Freaks, these nasty little
Teenagers
Who's this character?
This angry principal who's mad at nothing
This is like
The school administration
Okay if we play tears on the
Pillow they won't be grinding on
Each other
Tears on my pillow
We don't have to play hot in here tonight
Okay if we
Get them all riled up
If we play leader of the pack
I hear that kids today are talking
They enjoy songs about backing
Asses up
And ass is misspelled
The spelling isn't good either
There was nothing sexual in those old rock and roll songs
No!
That didn't rile kids up
No Britney Spears only Andrews
Sisters hits
Did you have a 50's themed dance?
At least one
Wait a minute this character it's not
It's not some principal this is what Jason thought
This is what 18 year old Jason thought
At the time
I did not want to be there
Like most dance I did not want
To be there
I wanted to be home running blockbuster
Video movies eating General So's chicken
Like
What a detail
Are you eating a lot when you're 18?
I could be sewing it right now
When I was like 16 or 15
I could be eating stromboli
And watching the fight club again
You know
I could be innovating
I could be stuffing a stromboli with
General So's chicken
Oh boy
That would be something
I could be watching Memento
That movie is backwards
I'm innovating
Like Christopher Nolan
Innovated storytelling
You're eating backwards now?
I'm eating General So's chicken stuffed
In an Italian stromboli
You're the Nolan of snacking
You're pushing the medium forward
Pennsylvania
What have we not gotten to here
My other
They show a bunch of
This main street hop and there's kind of a medley
Of
Let me really isolate the kind of 50's I don't like
What they show is a medley of
We go together from Greece
Who put the bomb
And what I realized
Here's where the heart of
We go together is not from the 50's
This is a nostalgia from the 50's
As is Bowser
I think this is what I don't like
That song obviously has all the
But then
There's a part where they just do it for a lot
Clingity clang
A shibity shoe
A poopity blip
I realize my version of
Hell is that
If that block
Of We go together was
Infinite
Or if my afterlife
If it was otherwise paradise
But
Guess what
Part of heaven is that there's a constant sock hop
Going take a listen
Clang de clang de clang shimity shmoo
Bibbity blip be blip zoobity zoo
I would choose hell
I will take my chances on whatever
Hell is
That is like
What if hell was more big band
Sort of a big band revival
Because I think I could deal with
If I sometimes get a
Ba do ba do
I can relax to that a little bit
But it like shimity shmoopy
But what if they played the
Heathcliff theme once in a while in heaven
We cover all the 50's greats
Heathcliff Heathcliff or that pound puppy song
That used the let's go to the hop
But they said let's go to the pound
Do you remember that? Did you guys have that video?
Just the stuffed animals
There was a pound puppy movie
I think it was direct to video that was like
Let's go to the pound
Dogs famously would not like
To be at the pound
That's a song you use to
Trick dogs
I thought that was like the main
Theme for the
Show but I did look it up and it's from
It's from the movie pound puppies
And the legend of big paw
So we must have had the legend of big paw
Tape and that's what I'm thinking
I can play it I don't have to play it
Do it at the end
Do it when I
Have the option of getting up and leaving
Yeah yeah
Have we missed anything though
Anything about the special
Look again this is also
Like it's
All this
Introspective and mainly
It's Bowser this is a
Little thing and it just bothers me so much
Is that he goes and finds like
The doo-wop group that's cruising
Around in one of the main street cars and harmonizing
And like hey why don't I
Join you for a so why don't I
Join youse guys there's one
It's the word is you
The S does nothing
You make a fool out of yourself
Out of youse self when you talk that way
And then
He like hey let's do a number
What about blue moon
Bowser
I believe you say
Blue moon the enunciation
It is on the emphasis is on
Moon blue moon
Blue moon god
Why does that annoy me so much
It's one of the worst things I've ever heard
What about blue
Moon that's not the way
Like words go together
And get said you don't put
S's on the end of random words
The emphasis goes on
Moon did you go to school
Bowser or did you put your busy
Cutting class
Smoking in the boys room
Getting away from those cafeteria workers
With the hand nets
In their arms you eliminate
Wobble a ref
Oh mystery meat
Like can we talk about
Mystery meat for a second
It seems to me somebody should have
Solved that mystery so I could
Know what I'm putting down in my
Tum tums
Who likes this? Why would you like
This? I don't think anyone
Did I don't think there was ever any audience
Feedback on shenanah
But shenanah had a show that ran for like three or four years
I'd never heard
That I've completely thank god I've completely
Missed the shenanah show
And did you I didn't know this
Song that's been playing in commercials for
Decades is the shenanah theme
Maybe this was what is that
Shananah shananah
Shananah
But that's a song that existed before them
Isn't it I think that's shananah
Theme song but that's also another
Song isn't that like get a job or something
Oh is it yeah isn't it
So they took their theme
Their name from the song
Unless it's a different unless they like amended
That but like
Yeah that's get a job but the
Silhouettes so they took
Shananah from the background singers
Of the background
Vocals from that song yes
Yeah they did nothing
They did nothing I was actually even giving them
The credit because I was like oh I like that that's
Shananah huh well never mind
No no unless I'd have to hear
The version that you're talking about
No you're probably right then it doesn't make
Sense because I was listening to their albums and it was all
Covers and not covers I even
Enjoyed very much so I was surprised
That I was like oh that actually I kind of
Like I guess that's their theme
I'm glad you've gotten ahead of that you didn't really care
For Shananah because I was also
As soon as I read that they had a variety
Show and this is unfair of me but
As soon as I read that detail I was like
I got mad at you Mike
I got mad I assumed
That this is something that you would like
And that's unfair that's like
Inventing a fight in your head that isn't
There but as soon as I saw that I'm like this is
Some fucking madam shit I'm gonna go in there
And Mike's gonna like it and I got
Everybody's gonna be yelling about Shananah
For like 30 more episodes
Beyond this alright let's
Let's just get you to one chocolate
Malt with two straws
And you share it yeah right
I have no problem if all the stuff we're talking about I have
No problem with malt culture
Malt we can agree on but madam I saw
Specifically with madam I saw madam in a sitcom
Where her weird little legs were
Walking that's a lot more
Interesting than just the guy doing this
Like
That's a lot weirder
To my credit
Is it not but we are dealing with things from
The 70's variety show
Maybe if I had watched
More Shananah show I would have found some clips
And maybe that's in our future
But no it's not
No it's not this is the ultimate
We were talking about wanting to put something in the club 3 poll
That got zero votes
Shananah variety show is a very viable option
We want to run the experiment
No one wants this
I'm interested to see the Patreon
Back end of the software
Can get something
Negative votes in a poll
Yeah
I don't want anybody to hack
Our system but it would be
Interesting could you take
Votes away and can you teach me
To do it in case I need that
If madam sneaks into any future poll
Just trying to get a cloud strike
And join the Shananah poll
You're dying
Jason's thing this year is cloud strike
The blue screens of death are very funny
Scott would you rather
Add a future cause I've brought this up before
The Sid and Marty Croft produced
Variety show starring the Bay City Rollers
Or Shananah
No one wants this
No one is clamoring the Bay City
Rollers
Time moves on
Time ignores these things
For a reason
We move forward we don't have to blast
To the past
I have a video of Bowser
Performing seven years ago
Oh god
Who is this guy to talk about
Underarm shape on lunch
Ladies this is precisely how he
Looks
He's still around too
By the way I cannot believe
In reading the full Bowser
Wikipedia I am shocked
That this guy is not a major
Maga guy
In fact he is a big Democrat
Donor and I'm so good
You know what I'll lay off Bowser
A little bit
To his credit Shananah is kind of also
A comedy act
In some ways
So he is doing it whether we think it's funny or not
Is another story
Clearly Jason and I are big fans of the material
But there is no one else
To balance him out
So Fonz
Fonz was a subtler character
And he had levels he could play with
In this instance I think you can call
The Fonz subtle
I think Fonz was kind of subtle
Fonz can be subtle
Again Henry Winkler a very charismatic
Performer
We are universes apart
I don't care that they both go
These people are not
In the same league
Even though the talent level
Is miles apart
What if quietly
Bowser has been a listener to this show
The whole time
Oh they did one where they are going to talk about me
Oh no
Tears on my pillow
I got to call up little Anthony
Who is also still alive
I looked him up
I love this
I found the press kit on eBay
I love this art
Or not art I should say this is a photo
Of Mickey and Minnie
With their 80's character
Mascot costumes in this big red
Some kind of car
I should know what it is
Convertible
Mickey's got his sweater on
They got a surfboard in the back
A guitar in the back
I would like a poster of this
All the art and some of the
Signs from this thing go up for auction sometime
I like the logo
I think this was probably a fun
You could engage with this event
A little bit but otherwise go about your
Disneyland day
A little bit of extra character
They got legit acts
I think the Righteous Brothers played
I forget the full
They definitely got
Good 50's performers
To play the big stage over
Videopolis
This was probably fun
Bowser mentions it's going over
Videopolis
I wish they would do
Would they ever have
There's a question
When was the last time they would have like
An act play at Disneyland that you knew
Like not just for some sort of
Holiday special
They used to have like Righteous Brothers
They used to have like somewhat known
I mean Righteous Brothers really known
When was the last time you could see
A band that was known
Play somewhere at Disneyland
Jim Belushi and the Sacred Hearts
Might be the answer
He single handedly
Killed the
Never again
After that
He rocked them too hard
So many people were there to see the Sacred Hearts
Because they're such big fans of the band
That they probably crowded
We can't handle it
We can't get this level
Of crowd surge
The system's breaking down
I wonder if the parks just are too crowded now
Where if you had like a band play
Even a moderately popular band
That it would just be like overwhelming
To the park? I don't know
They don't need to do it anymore to bring
People in? I don't know
Yeah I don't know
I'd be nervous if they did
Alright, Disneyland rock and roll summers
And then Papa Roach is playing in front of
Sleeping Beauty Castle
That whole park's gonna bottleneck
Everybody's dyin' to see them roll
There's like multiple bands playing
At Disney that day
Avenged Sevenfold would play
Somewhere in Tomorrowland
You'd have to have a full
New metal night
I would call it rock and roll but people would call it
New metal
New metal night at Disneyland
We'd all be there
If it was new metal night
But that's what we want
That's what we want something coming out of the left field
That would be the equivalent of this
It's still 25 years old at this point
The famous
The corn ever traveling bullet
Will fly through Disneyland
They'll put it on the Tinkerbell wire
Whoa, corn's bullet
Is going through the top
Spire of the castle
Yeah, yes we should
Limp Bizkit, corn
Ultimately still rock and roll
Swing revival night?
Swing revival night, okay
Don't you dare
Whether we talk about that, wait a minute
I could end the episode right now
Before we even do the thought excerpt
Before we even start naming the bands
Let's do it, do we got anything else?
I don't think so
Other than naming bands
I mean get them in while you can
But otherwise I'm going to wrap it up
You survived podcast
The righty ruby dooby
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate
If you want to dig even deeper
Join us on our VIP Patreon tier
Where you get one more bonus episode every month
And our regular episodes ad free
And the listeners vote on the topics there
Do not suggest
Bay City Rollers
Variety show
Unless it is an experiment in zero votes
Which I think that it could win
Yeah