FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast may contain
Canadian Vegetable Drinks
Poo Voices
Commercial Acting Pay Explainers
and Critter Definition Debates
All that plus a discussion of
the many adventures of Winnie the Pooh rides
all across the world. On today's
podcast, The Ride.
Deep in the hundred
podcast woods
lived a boy named Mike
Steffer Carlson. Like most
forty year old boys, Mike Steffer
has many toys.
Many, many, a lot
of many toys, but his favorite
of all is his rumbly-tumbly
little pal, Jason the Pooh.
Now, when Jason
the Pooh speaks, he sounds
exactly like the Disney character
Winnie the Pooh. I mean
exactly. So, when he
speaks in just a second, get ready
for a voice that's one hundred percent
just like Winnie the Pooh.
So, here he is now,
Jason the Pooh.
Oh, bother.
Start the party
without me.
You know, it's Eeyore with a
twinge of Lorne Michaels.
Yeah, it's a little Lorne.
You know, the thing about Rabbit is
you know, Rabbit needs to take the energy down
and you know, because there's a mellowness to the
hundred acre woods. You know,
when Danny and Johnny and I were trying to go get the
beehive from the top of the tree,
you know, we really just got stung a lot.
We wanted practical beehives
in the sketches.
And we got that at the Disneyland
version of this ride. Every other
one they went with honeypots. You know, they
say that when you're the voice actors
when they're creating characters, they combine two
voices and that's what Jason just did.
Yeah, so Pooh is Eeyore
plus Lorne Michaels.
Right, his Pooh version of Pooh is Eeyore
So, we'll check in with that Pooh
constantly during this episode.
I guess we'll have to. I was wondering,
I was like, oh man, I feel like there's a number
of characters in the hundred acre woods
that could be. Who is he going to
nail my ass with?
Just the main one. Probably Pooh,
it could be Eeyore. You made it sound like one of
them at least. You're not Eeyore.
You're not the gopher.
Could be the American original character
gopher.
Pooh though is the most
popular character, so it's not all
bad. You think more popular than Taker?
I think so.
Taker's a little much. Well, when Taker
joined, you know, Taker broke out
because Taker was very physical
and brought an energy, you know.
But Pooh is the thing
where the cast can't evolve, you know.
And when we made it to Heffalump
movie, Taker is the sex.
Taker is the draw for the ladies.
Taker is the sex, Taker is the bounce.
We replaced him with Billy
and Taker
and I feel like they both hit pretty quickly.
But yeah, Pooh, I feel like Pooh.
Pooh is like
Pooh is like your Bill Hader.
He's the Phil Hartman of this.
These are like some of the main
stages of the show. Winnie the Pooh cast
onto. I'm saying
sort of like reliable, dependable,
consistent.
That's Pooh there. That's what Jason is.
Well, Rue I think would be, Rue is
like the Pete Davidson due to youth,
you see. Of course, yes.
Rue, that's another one I'm like,
oh, I, I, whatever
my child like wonder or naivete
whatever you want to call it.
You would
identify with Rue? I think I
identify a little with Rue and Eeyore
and Pooh.
And Piglet. And Piglet.
Oh, I see Piglet with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There is probably
there's certain times when I feel like Jason and I
maybe trade off being like Piglet
and Pooh. And Pooh.
Sometimes Jason's like, oh, why are we doing
this? Why are we doing this, Michael?
What do you mean? We're trying to get into this
Comic Con party. We're going to get arrested.
What do you mean, Michael?
Michael gets really excited about
like a deal.
You know, you get Tigger
energy. Like when you said on this
podcast, who gives a shit or who
gives a fuck about grapefruit? That's almost
sort of like kind of a Piglet. Like what are we
what do you mean, grapefruit?
Who gives a shit about grapefruit?
I think it was coming from a much angrier
place. I think it was coming from an angrier place
than any Winnie the Pooh character can come from.
There's not that much anger.
Also, I hate to tell you this, Mike. You're Rabbit.
Oh, yeah, I am Rabbit.
That's true. Yeah, yeah. If we're
going on the equal playing field
with no dynamics versus another person,
yes, I am Rabbit, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I think
so. It's like when there's a... And Jason
that's where Jason's Pooh because Jason's trying
to get into your place to steal
snacks.
And I'm trying to explain something to Jason and he falls asleep
like Pooh Bear. He's just like
he just zones out when I'm saying that. I mean, that
happens to me. Look, let's be honest. That
happens to all of us when we're talking
to partners about theme park stuff.
We are all a little bit Rabbit where we're trying
to explain the new ride or what we're
happy about or upset about and then the person
just falls. And they all turn into Eeyores, just
energy wise. Yeah, right.
So, we all contain
Eeyores, Pooh multitudes.
We all contain
many Pooh characters. This is sort of a new religion
I'm workshopping right now.
We all kind of do. You know what's something I think we'll all
fall into also
is like, I think we can all have
an owl about us in that
owl will like, oh, I know
all about that and then he'll go get the book
and then pontificate and here's everything I know
about this. And the viewer knows
that he has the book turned upside down.
Right. That's us with our pronunciations
and our falsehoods.
Yes. Everything that we get wrong on a
regular basis. I say yes.
We all think honey is spelled H-U-N-N-Y
in real life. I think
I was trying to figure out the
Pooh astrology of like
Pooh, Sun,
Eeyore, Moon,
Tigger,
Piglet, Rise. And I'm like
I don't remember enough of the specifics
about like, well everyone knows your Sun
sign, but then your Moon, Sun
is really what you are and Rising Sign
influences you and I'm like
Oh, I don't know this well enough.
You got it better than me.
You're more of an owl on that than I am.
But he just owl'd himself. He was trying to be like
an authority, but then he just explained that he doesn't know.
So like, owl has
shown his owl butt yet again.
Yeah. His owl butt?
Showing your ass, that's the phrase, right?
Sure. It is? Isn't the phrase
showing your ass when you like, embarrass yourself?
Am I wrong? It is, but I also
think my tend to be an authority
was undone by the second a-f
of my sentence, where I admit my foolishness.
That's true. You did admit. You're right.
I was pining of like
Oh, I wish I knew this a little better.
You self-owled or something. I don't know
what the phrase would be. Self-owled.
That's maybe not it, but something like that.
Well, we all have affinity
for these characters in
this world, seemingly. And we're here
by the way, in case, because there's a lot
of like generic, Winnie the Pooh
things are always named
many adventures and advent. I even
forget what the Saturday Morning Cartoon was called.
And they all win, which is which,
and it all blends together. To be clear, we are talking
about The Ride, which is at
both American parks, it's in
Hong Kong, and it's in Shanghai.
Just so you know. But I think
it's fair to keep on the table here.
Fondness for the world,
fondness for the characters, because that might help us
calibrate how we feel about these
attractions. Yes, for sure.
And you brought up the Saturday Morning, the ABC
Pooh Bear, because like, I think we all grew up with
the original cartoons, all those
songs, The Ride, Winnie the Pooh,
that stuff. Those I think passed
generationally excellently,
I can say, because my mom really wanted to
show me those, and I loved them, and I've passed them to
my son. Yes. Those
of all the things that don't
transcend generations, Mike
Love quote, I'll say.
Winnie the Pooh, definitely. Winnie the Pooh
is the beach boys of cartoons.
In a lot of ways.
I think in early- Brian is Pooh.
Another one in early Disney
Channel, where they would chop
it up, maybe?
Or chop up the segments
and air it, or just
air the original movie in its entirety.
It got re-released
on VHS, it was released on VHS
in the early 80s, and then re-released
in the mid-90s. Because it was all these, it was these
like, separate shorts, like if you were
watching this in real time, all of the shorts came
out separately, but then all
got combined into sort of the unofficial
feature mini-adventures of Winnie the Pooh,
which is three of them,
that's Tigger Two and Blustery
Day, and whichever one is the bees,
I think.
Yeah. But then
yes, Mike also, the Saturday
Morning cartoon, which I thought
was wonderful, and I love that theme.
The theme haunts me.
Haunts me in a good way.
What a start, there's no
little
prelude, it's just gotta
get it, wow.
Flams in. High energy.
What's with his homey?
No little
fill to get you in there. Starts with the
words.
I think a lot of, I think everybody
sees the symmetry between Weezer and the Winnie the Pooh
universe. Yeah, yeah.
Well, the 90s, around the same era.
Written around the same time, so
one influenced the other. Weezer, yes.
River's presumably influenced by the mini-adventures theme.
Pooh did use some of his success,
you know, his money, to go back
to an Ivy League school and get
a degree.
Like Rivers. I hate to say it, he needed it.
Pooh needed it, there was a big education gap
with Pooh. Yeah, I, since
we were talking about the original
many adventures of Winnie the Pooh,
I didn't know a couple things.
One, I didn't know it came out
in 1977, like
I didn't know it was so recent,
like so close to the 80s.
I also didn't know it was originally released
on a double bill
with a movie called Escape
from the Dark, aka
The Littlest Horse
Thieves. Those are the same movie?
The same movie. Really? In England it's
called Escape from the Dark,
and in America it was called The
Littlest Horse Thieves. Thieves.
These are very different tones of
title. Yeah.
And there's multiple thieves?
Are all the people in the photo or the
poster thieves? I think all the people
are thieves.
They can't all be thieves, there have to be some
good guys, are the thieves good? No,
the thieves are good, they're little. Yeah, yeah.
I think they're trying to rescue horses
from going to the slaughterhouse.
Oh, they're good thieves.
What a scary premise of a
movie, you're getting kids in to see Winnie the Pooh
and now we're thinking about horse
slaughter? They're going to be worried
about Eeyore the whole time.
Is there some plant that wants to melt Eeyore down?
Use his tail to make belts?
It's probably in that Winnie the Pooh, Blood and Honey
are rated Pooh Bear
public domain shit.
That's too twisted.
Sorry, I'm just saying that now
that the characters are public domain,
you can do stuff like that. Blood and Honey
is a kind of cool phrase. It is a good
idea. I mean, Blood and Anything,
Elvis Costell's Blood and Chocolate,
Blood and Anything is actually kind of
a cool title. I guess we could
find one that isn't.
Blood and
Insulin, it's not as interesting.
They're in the family.
Blood and Serts.
You know, the candy
Serts. I don't think that's very cool.
It's okay. Blood and Swedish Fish,
I say because there's Swedish Fish in the room.
Blood and Swedish Fish is okay, depending on what you're
titling, I think. That would be the name
of a really irritating
stand-up special. Yeah, that's true.
Like a Scottish comedian from 2004
put a DVD out.
You Americans?
I can't believe this.
He's certainly fighting against...
Let's talk about the Crusades!
Your
president is so dumb!
That was not Scottish. I can't do
Scottish. That is a really hard line.
Littlest Horse Thieves, my god.
Geez.
Oh, and Alistair Simms' last movie
sat on several levels.
You have to be sad, not that I know
who that is. Oh, he played Scrooge.
Oh, alright, well he must be a great
British character actor,
Shakespearean actor, probably.
I saw the phrase, they're trying
to rescue pit ponies,
and I'd never encountered that, but I have
no idea what that means. Pit ponies?
I'm assuming racing horses
that can't race anymore, farming
horses that can't farm anymore.
Mines, they're in the mines. They're in the mines!
I didn't know horses went in the mines!
I guess they have to pull the cards.
Makes sense.
Welcome to Pooh
Corner, also. Yes.
Loom's large.
Welcome to Pooh Corner, the
live-action, suited
character show that was on
early Disney Channel that had this
really, like,
specific, kind of
haunting, kind of creepy vibe
with its painted backdrops.
Look at the Pooh face on this picture.
Pooh has this, like, thousand-yard stare.
This mascot-suited character.
Jason, you watch this?
Yeah, I vaguely remember this.
I saw that one, because that
looks very similar to the one walking
around the park. There's a
video on YouTube just called Pooh Falls
Down, and it was just
the person in the suit was walking
along with Tigger, and they just
kind of ate shit, and everyone
went, no, no, he fell!
Cast members help him up and get him
off stage, you know, get him backstage
to, like,
collect themselves. I feel like on
this show, if there'd been the episode
when Pooh fell,
it would be to, like,
addiction,
peer pressure,
mental illness.
This show feels
so heavy to me, and I don't think it
always was, but I feel like we probably
all, to some extent, are
aware of the one about strangers
and not talking to strangers.
And just seeing
the notion of strangers
even puncture the world of Winnie the Pooh
at all
is so, like, no,
his fluff and stuff brain
can't handle these
scary concepts.
Don't put Pooh through these paces.
Yeah, the Hundred Acre Woods was this, like,
special place where no
danger like that existed.
Like, I guess
some danger existed, but it wasn't. Yeah, this is
too real world. Piglet, this is
crack.
That's where you don't, it's too.
But also, then, just the vibe of this show
and the show Dumbo Circus,
which was similar suited characters.
Yes.
Scary. They just are both scary shows
that were, in the same way
other, you know, shows almost in
hindsight are creepy.
Zubili Zoo or something, even though those weren't quite, those
weren't suited characters they had face paint on, but they're
a different type of creepy. A different type of creepy
that you go back and you watch and you're like,
this is so unnerving,
but I do think the unnervingness
was making me
extra interested in it. I think there is something compelling
about some of these old shows because of
It lodged in your brain more than like a more
normal cartoon or kid show
that didn't have that
eerie air. Do you think it was probably
just, like, cheapy shows
made at the MGM Studios?
Yeah. In Florida? Yeah. I think for sure.
Yeah. I don't think the, well,
I don't know if we know that. Oh, I don't know where
they were made. I just, I am agreeing with you that they
were cheapy shows. Oh, okay. I don't think
there's any way they weren't cheapy shows because they
kind of had, like, a couple sets. Like, knock them
out. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know
where they were shot though. It's funny you say the word
unnerving because I wrote that down
because, like, there's, like,
uh, uh, stuff
in the ride, like, I like the effect
when Pooh falls asleep
and starts to dream and it's like
a projection thing
and then you go into the Heffalumps and
Woozles. As a kid, the Heffalumps
and Woozles dream sequence
I found so
unnerving. Uh, when you would see
it on the- On the TV. Yeah.
On the Disney Channel or whatever. Yeah.
Like, it just gave me the creeps. I didn't-
The song was haunting.
I don't- And I'm like, why is
this bear? Yeah. He lives in the woods
with his friend. Like, why has he haunted
his dreams? I
don't think I liked it.
I don't remember exactly. Yeah. I think
I, but I think it was more like, eh, we don't need to watch
this part. I wasn't like so scared
of it, but it was not the stuff I liked.
Right. Um.
I want to say that this is maybe
a rare area where I was not
particularly scared. My-
Perhaps my mother could point
me to many terrible incidents involving
Heffalumps and Woozles and I'm wrong,
but I don't- Yeah, I was thinking that because it's, you
know, within- On this spectrum,
it's kind of like a psychedelic sequence,
right? Yeah. And, you know,
you know, the way we are,
we'd be like, psychedelic sequences
for kids, tsk tsk. Yes.
I was like, is it going to go that way? And I don't
feel that way, but because it's
like, I think
obvious precedent,
Pink Elephants on
Parade is way scarier,
more upsetting. I think Heffalumps and Woozles,
first of all, they're smiling, and I don't
find the smiles creepy, and it's such
just like fun, eye-popping animation.
I don't think I was ever
upset by it. I don't think- It makes all
the sense in the world that you guys were anybody
would be. Yeah, I don't have
such a scare. Like, I don't have a memory of
like the end of Pinocchio or anything like that
where I was so freaked out by
the donkey stuff in Pleasure
Island and other things,
and the witch in Snow White and stuff, so I don't have
that memory, but I don't
feel it in my brain that I had a big,
like, any big affection for this.
I could be wrong, but I just don't remember.
The psychedelic stuff, and then
also like,
it's in The Wind in the Willows
and some of the Pooh stuff.
There's like this
melancholy,
now I recognize like melancholy
British countryside.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pining, and I'm like, as a kid,
that, I did not like that.
I like the funny stuff.
Yeah, yeah. You know?
Like the feeling of like long, you're getting like
the feeling of longing. Longing.
And you're five years old. Which now I'm realizing
it's like people longing for a world
before the Great War.
Sure.
Of course this is the perspective
Jason brings to the show.
That's what I, I didn't recognize that
at the time. Keep in mind, Christopher
Robin lives in a post-war,
he lives in a war-torn England.
That's true. So if you ever think it feels
sad, this is,
I'm surprised there's this much heaviness
being brought to the, I think they're all
a blast. I love all the way
there's like sort of a sadness, like a melancholy,
like even to the song,
like, we need to, like,
No, to the main song?
I think so.
I do think so. I think it's sweet and fun
and nice. I think it's that too.
Look, everything you're saying about,
I definitely get
odd feelings from Pooh Corner
and, but
even like, I don't think it even has the
like, to me it doesn't
quite have the melancholy of peanuts or
anything. I think of like,
I think of fun and physical and silly
and he's flying around on the balloon,
he's spitting bees out of his mouth.
I think there's a lot of like, pure
joy. I think I
have trouble
ascribing the notion
to Winnie the Pooh
that it's like melancholy and sad.
At least not like as it's primary
facets. I am talking about like there's
probably five or ten minutes
cumulative that happens
at the beginning or end
of some of this stuff.
When the book opens and it's the theme
and it's like Christopher Robin
there is something there. There is
I don't know if longing is even the right word that I feel
but there is something wistful.
There is some extra feeling.
It's not like the ABC Pooh Bear where it's like
let's fucking go!
That's the energy of the Pooh Bear.
That's the energy
you're ascribing to.
Pooh Bear, Winnie the Pooh Bear
Let's fucking go!
Let's have some fun and shit!
What would Pooh Bear sound
like if he said let's fucking go?
Like Deadpool or Wolverine are
going to say in this upcoming film.
Or it may come out depending on when we release this.
Let's fucking go!
Grab the
Celsius energy
drink and let's go!
It has to be higher. First things first.
Yeah, that did it
He's more like this
Pooh Bear. I can get it sometimes.
I think that's pretty good.
That's pretty good. Jason?
That helps a ton.
That nudge.
That's what it needed.
Let's fucking go, Piglet.
That's pretty good.
I'm pretty impressed by your Pooh.
That's like a little...
That's more like the Sterling Hollow.
Gotta get way back there.
Without saying the phrase to let you say it
What if Winnie the Pooh shared your
maybe your primary interest
in what you like to do when you go to Las Vegas?
The kind of thing that you like to
go to.
But other words though.
You're missing one key word in that.
Yeah, the adjectives.
Douchey pool party
Piglet
I want to go to...
What DJ is spinning tonight, Pooh?
DJ Tigger
T1
GG
8, that'll number 8
and then an R.
Wet Republic hasn't
been the same year.
It's hard. I lose after a little bit.
It's really easy to lose.
Oh bother.
I can reset on oh bother.
Piglet, sing Piglet.
I don't know.
You gotta keep those key phrases.
Just go back to them.
Oh, let's fucking go.
Oh bother.
Maybe does Pooh Bear say let's fucking go
in any of these R rated
public domain movies?
I wonder. He might.
And he should now if nobody's done it.
We could make a Pooh Bear movie.
I just want to let everyone know in case you hadn't heard
you can make a Pooh Bear movie tomorrow.
You can announce it, you can shoot it,
you will not get sued.
You probably can't put the red shirt on
that he wears in the Disney specific stuff
but yeah, you can use the characters.
All of our darkest visions can come to life.
We can swear once.
I believe
there's a sequel coming to Blood
and Honey because Tigger went in public.
Well the same people are also making like an evil
Steamboat Willie movie too.
The Steamboat Willie specific version of Mickey
is now in the public domain.
I'm trying to find
I'm on the IMDB
quotes for
the twisted Winnie the Pooh
Blood and Honey because I was like maybe I
can hand you some crazy phrase that he says
but unfortunately the craziest phrase
there's only two quotes.
Everybody's sleeping on this IMDB but the craziest
quote is from Christopher Robin and it's this
Pooh, you've got to help me. Something's
wrong with Piglet. He killed my wife.
And that doesn't
show up in the Ewan McGregor
Christopher Robin.
Maybe you're mixing up the quotes
and it's from the Ewan McGregor
Christopher Robin movie. Yeah, they could have
it twisted. Maybe that movie's good.
I forgot about that movie existed
and I was like
I wonder if they should make a grown up
Christopher Robin movie and I thought
five more minutes about it and I was like
they did that
four years ago.
Have you invented it in your brain?
I don't know if I've seen a trailer of it.
I've watched it. Now that is a
sad movie. That's like
very sad and melancholy.
I didn't want that. I don't want to be sad.
That's kind of a bummer.
I'm not going to stand up for something that looks
sad from that.
When I was a kid and saw Hook
in theaters
I was like there's a lot of sad parts
of this.
I wanted to run away.
I say Hook is to be avoided
at all costs.
Especially knowing that the man who played
Hook is a real life Hook.
Sure.
And it's a
creepy movie on so many levels
and it's weird that thing that
Spielberg hated
Julia Roberts.
They did not get along.
I think it would be hard to watch it
and it's already got the creepy patina
and now you're going but Spielberg
I thought Spielberg was great. I thought he was everybody's friend.
What happened?
It stresses me out
that he was mad at Julia Roberts.
He's Mr.
like everyone likes him
you would think.
I think of him as like a person.
A normal person.
I don't know.
A normal person should be able to get along
with Julia Roberts I would think.
But I don't know. I'm not sure.
I don't know.
That humanizes Spielberg in some ways
in my mind.
You just think of him as Mr. Movies
and he's this sort of inoffensive character.
I don't even know
what is the Spielberg
George Lucas you could do a character
you could do a voice you could do kind of a bit.
But I don't even know what the Spielberg bit is.
He's just sort of talking about lenses
and talking about
I don't have a good lock on
what he's like even.
There's not a lot of Spielberg impressions are there.
I don't know what it would be.
The only way in
is that we don't have much time
and ET needs your help.
It's the only thing that I know that he says.
He says it kind of hurried. He says it kind of flat.
We don't have much time. ET needs your help.
Magic bikes. This. Magic passport.
Oh hi ET.
Short clips. Not good on camera.
So imagine I'm like screaming at
Julie Roberts but it's actually like that.
Maybe it wasn't screaming.
Just being mad at it.
I don't have much time.
I don't like your vibe.
My notes to you
will be submitted via form.
So long.
Big personalities to manage that movie.
I mean what do you mean?
I think
Hoskins.
I think Hoskins is probably the most
low maintenance.
I feel like he worked in a lot of low budget
British stuff where he would probably
be pretty like chill now.
I don't know but you can also hear his voice going
This production's a madhouse.
Nothing works right around here.
Go stick it up your arse.
I don't know who to blame.
Steven or Julian but I don't like
either of you.
I thought the bloody kids would be the problem.
The grown ups are acting like kids.
And the kids are acting like adults.
Robin Williams is the most
level headed one of us all.
What's that saying?
I thought he was a loon.
I seen him in Popeye.
I thought this guy's a loon.
It turns out he's acting.
It would be really good if there was like
a director after they were done
in the same way that Schumacher was talking about
the actors on Batman Forever and who he liked
and who he didn't and who worked well.
If every director would just put that on record
and then maybe 50 years later that would all
become released.
That would be so interesting to know.
Who you didn't get along with
who you didn't like.
Who you thought did a bad job.
I'm always fascinated by that.
There's just no other way
these famous movies could have been.
There's no other actor that could have played this.
I'm sure like any creative person
like certain casting decisions drove them nuts
and still they go I fucking hate
the way this person played this.
Years and years from now the
Russo Brothers list comes out
and there's only one name on it
and it's you.
They liked every Avenger
and only me.
Was that the one where you were on the big plane
with the wings or what were you doing for
the Russo Brothers?
I did a Smirnoff
commercial for the Russo
Brothers for Canada only.
I was going to be in both
an American spot and a Canadian spot.
And they brought me back twice for the
callback. I improvised in front
of the Russo's twice.
They said they want you for both. They booked
me for both. I said well that's good.
Captain America's coming out. I'm surely going to be
Captain America's friend next movie
then they do one.
Just so you guys know I do a We Need the Pooh.
If you need that.
If you want a Pooh Bear. I have a Donald
but I can't get words out. It's just going to sound
like it. But I'll work on it. For you guys I'll work on it.
I got nine seconds of Pooh until it starts
struggling. And then I got
a call from my agent saying there's
some sort of rule where you can't do two country
spots. You can only do one. They want
you for the Canadian Smirnoff
because that is the more
people in this. And this was a whole big like
Adam Scott. Was it Adam Scott?
I think so. Like campaign
with a bunch of famous people in it.
So they said we want you for the Canada one because we don't want to be famous
people. And that's going to be more of a featured spot.
So I said that sounds great.
So I did the spot. It was
advertising the
I'm trying to think. It's a tomato
sauce. Tomato
like I'm trying to think. It's a drink
that's just like celery and tomato
juice and vodka.
Clamado? Is it a clamado? Is that
clams? There's some other name for it. I think I saw
Dana. The other name for it is the shit I hate.
It's not a good name.
Is it a Caesar? It's a Caesar.
Thank you. It's a bloody
it's a twist on a bloody merriam. I saw Dan Aykroyd
advertising a Caesar recently.
So I did this
popular in Canada. I had
a couple lines in it. Obviously commercial short.
A couple lines in it. I talked to a couple people
who were like these Russo brothers. They love
to improvise. They're going to let you
it's going to be so much fun. You're going to be able to improvise.
And I go well this sounds fantastic.
This sounds exciting. You're not even going to have to stay
focused on the Caesar. You can go off
Caesar. I can go off Caesar. Now I had done this
already a few times. So I know that you're not really allowed
to really go off that hard.
This is 30 seconds. But still
I was like alright interesting. I got there
my lines were all cut. They had already
been cut. And then I go
but improvising is in the face.
It's in the expressions you make and how wide
your eyes go. And I did
the thing and it was fine. It was a perfectly pleasant
day. And then one time
I think I just went like oh
okay. And I did it in a funny way and Joe Russo
laughed. And then the commercial never
aired and I never got paid for it.
You never got paid for it? Well I got the day rate.
Sorry sorry. The day rate's fine. You get
a day. Basically it all works. I don't know why I'm talking about the day rate
you get once. If it doesn't
air then that's all you get. Which is fine.
So no it never aired. And then I was not
Captain America's buddy in the next
one in case anyone didn't know. An insult to injury.
Uh huh. So it didn't happen.
Which sounds like a joke but I feel like Captain America
does pal around with Rick Jones.
He sure does. I think we talk
I think at the time I go Jason I booked two
commercials. Rick Jones a role
is incoming for me. I think
Did you say that out loud? Well I didn't
say it in that. Like I was completely
delusional. But I was probably
like who can I play Jason? What do you think?
And we were trying to figure it out or something.
And we hit on the early 20's
kind of like eventually
get super powers.
And you know why I actually
You know why I even went down this
like went down this trail
was because Dominic Dirkus has
uh no no DC Pearson. Sorry
I thought of another Derek person.
I mixed them up. DC Pearson is in
Winter Soldier.
In the Apple Store.
They did get comedy
riff raff. You could have riff
raffed your way in there. That's what I mean.
So there's still time.
Well something else there's still time for
is talking about the ride in this
episode about the ride. We can cut the last part of it.
We can cut that out.
I don't know. No we're gonna
Yeah but we can cut the last part
but we're gonna watch all of the
littlest horses.
The littlest horse thieves.
Alright so edit.
I've already forgotten the name of the movie.
So edit here and when we come back we'll have watched all of
the littlest horse thieves.
Um guys
I'm a little upset. We just finished
littlest horse thieves and they're so little
and the horses were so scared.
And I don't know if we can go on
with this boo episode but we're gonna have to muscle
through. It's what the horse thieves would have wanted.
Let's fucking go. Let's fucking go.
Let's fucking go. Let's talk about the ride.
This ride showed up
in the Magic Kingdom 25 years
ago this summer.
And it was at Disneyland
not long after. It's been
added to the new parks that they've built since
but never made it to
Disneyland Paris, Tokyo, a whole
other situation I imagine. We'll talk
about it. Yeah yeah.
I think we probably know the Disneyland version
the best. Magic Kingdom, it's
in fantasy land. It
replaced Mr. Toad.
Disneyland, it is in critter country
where it replaced the country bears.
It's a killer. It's killed twice.
Who is the killer?
Blood and honey!
Oh no!
He still has his souvenirs,
his trophies, the heads
are still in the Disneyland one. Mr. Toad's
head is dripping with both blood
and honey.
I think that if this ride
gets a bad rap at all
some of it might come
from those initial
kickings out.
What do you call it when a landlord
kicks out a
eviction.
I think that
might be like a
sting still
to some people. Because these are beloved
attractions both. That was I think
a superior Mr. Toad. An excellent
Mr. Toad in the Disney world
with the two tracks. Yes. Big and expansive
different experiences depending on
which side that you did. Goes down to one
ride with one track.
And then country bears
two country bear theaters
took up a lot of space
and it became this one of the
Poo ride. Now I think at the time
there was the feeling that this was
crass and that Poo
is cute and Poo is moving a lot
of merch in the parks
and we'll move a lot more merch if we can
get an established
Poo attraction
and Poo zone. Yeah. And then we
can really make the merch fly off the
show. This is I remember the feeling on the
internet at the time
felt like it's just crass and
Poo is cute. I though
love Winnie the Pooh growing up. To me
it makes all the sense in the world that there could have been
a Winnie the Pooh ride. Well there wouldn't
have been because Poo was made after the
fifties. But it's like
if there had been a Poo ride
in any of these parks much earlier
mid eighties I think
it would have made a lot of sense. Poo of course
deserves a place in
the theme parks. There were potentially
plans for one.
But it kept getting shelved.
Okay sure. So they were trying
they were trying to figure it out.
I on the other hand
loved Mr. Toad so much
as a weird little child
I was very upset
to find Toad clothes
at a coming soon Winnie the Pooh ride.
And the more I thought about it I was like
I don't think I've ridden
the floor to Poo since the nineties.
Maybe I haven't either. Or early
two thousands maybe. I don't know.
I don't know that I have either.
Are we discovering it? Well look we've been on the Disneyland
one so we're not in such bad
shape here and I watch ride throughs of
all of them. Yeah
I've been on it but yeah enough for a while.
You're not alone Jason and
if you have not made it all the way to
Club Three the
deepest acreage in our
hundred acre wood
then you have not heard our episode
about toadins.
A pretty inexplicable phrase
until you break it apart and learn
that those were the protests
when Mr. Toad's
wild ride was going away in the Magic
Kingdom. Toad Hall
was going to be demolished. And that was definitely
the angle on these things. Basically like
what was interesting about the episode and why people
wanted us to do it was that these were essentially
sanctioned protests
in the park that they
sort of let slide. It was like
alright these are a bunch of nerds from the internet
they can do it. They're not getting unruly.
We'll let them do it. We'll probably make it worse.
We'll rile it up more if we try to stop it.
So there was like a guy who worked there and like
okay be safe fellas. Be good.
And the protests
went fine and then they ultimately had
no effect and Mr. Toad went away
and Pooh came in. But
genuinely there was
some definite
anti-Pooh sentiment.
At least in the Magic Kingdom. And I'd say here too
on the west coast as well.
Less so I think just from reading
archival stuff. Like it seems like the
Toad thing obviously was a bigger
deal because it had a name and there was a
movement more. But there was certainly
country bear fans that were not pleased.
And as you're saying it was like and then the
gift shop goes in. It's
interesting because yeah there's no reason
like Pooh shouldn't have a ride.
Those two things though
happen that kind of put a
cloud over the two rides. And then
the Japanese ride
also now
has a cloud over our American
Pooh rides head in the same
way. So it's like it's not really
fully fair to say these rides
in America are bad. They're not bad.
They're fun. I think you'd be hard pressed
to like actually just go on it
with no, if you have no knowledge
of any of this history
or what was there, if you
are my then three year
old going on this ride
it's a delight. You love this ride.
Like there's nothing wrong
with this attraction.
Maybe sometimes there's the feeling
that there's not enough right
about it. Well right it's like
I long for the
Tokyo Disney Pooh's Honey Hunt
which is an amazing
attraction. And of course the lore
of we could have had this but we didn't
get the, like there's no reason we should
have a version just as good. So
yes there's this, there's all this baggage
that the Pooh rides in America have.
And it's not fully fair. It's
not completely fair because
yes for your average park
goer, your average child
and my child who's
just watched the video of the Pooh ride
she loves this
like video. Just the video. The video.
When Pooh floats away she laughs
and laughs and then goes again. She goes again.
And I go okay so we go back
and I'm like. Teaching her to like ride throughs.
I go wow this is, I know and I
as I said before I don't
like drill
it on, like I don't drill her
with this stuff but I'll put something on and see what she
responds to. And immediately
she responded to Pooh and all the characters
on the ride through the Disneyland version.
Jason as a kid and it's like this is
William Holden. Learn.
Learn to be good.
Learn about culture.
Garfield is not interested.
Just wanders away. Oh you're doing it with your dog.
I'm doing it to the dog.
I did try to get him on the big
you know bigger screens.
Try to get him to watch
Bluey.
Cause I saw videos online
that dogs respond
well to it cause the color
palette is like
bright. It's like
not that they can necessarily see
the colors but they can kind of
see they like it
a little more. He did not care.
Yeah.
Our dog doesn't care about TV.
Although
I say my parents dog
recognizes animals on the screen
and will go nuts. So he for some reason
has like he has the ability
to see TV and know what he's seeing.
Our dog does not have that. He's never
ever looked at the TV and cared.
I don't know why but like if
there is a horse in the very
background of a shot
my parents dog will hop up on the
ottoman and go nuts.
Just bark at full volume until that horse is gone.
He has such good vision.
It's really weird. Garfield is like
10 now and only recently
he started like noticing
his reflection in mirrors
and one day I caught him chasing it
and he has also started
doing whimpers when he wants
attention or a treat.
He never did this. He never ever
did this before. It's new behavior.
So it's new old man behavior.
Your dog's becoming
an old man. He is.
Edwin's old.
Do your
listeners, do your animals respond
to media in this way and do you ever play
this podcast around your dog
or cat? Do they respond to our voices?
Do they like some? Do they recoil at others?
What do animals think of
our voices? It's time to find out.
Sound off in the comments. I hope
by asking that question it's not going to be
like that story that just came out of the
Bitcoin mine in Texas that's like
it's emitting such an awful
noise that it's hurting people
in like the vicinity of the mine.
And like animals are
upset. So hopefully our podcast is not
doing that. The whole town is at the bail on
the town. Yeah and people are getting headaches
and inner ear infections.
But it could be happening because of us too.
They're going to have to piece it together like
all these doctors across the world.
But the reason is that actually
the mine was fine. We all blamed
the mine. What was really going on
is that everyone in that town were ardent
Podcast the Ride fans.
Yeah the dogs howl along
when we start explaining new
restoration systems. A doctor is
like let me ask you this question. What do you think
of King Features Syndicate?
And the person just passes out and they're like I knew
it. Podcast the Ride fan.
And they're like we have to get you
off this. You have to listen to something like smartless.
We have to unimprint you. You need to listen
to better podcasts.
The good stuff. Yes.
And doctors recommend smartless.
Right exactly. That's what I was saying.
It's never caused an aneurysm.
Right. So I am excited because
I am like priming my
daughter for a ride now which is kind
of cool. Like yeah I'm very
excited to see that when she does it in person
what that's going to be like. Which it's closed
right now. We're also we can't go because
we have the cheap pass.
It's all summers kind of. I think
we're back in August. We could be
back in August. Yeah I'm back in August.
We've been looking at going and all of
July is blacked out. Which fair enough.
Sure. And that
indicates a place you maybe don't want to be anyway.
Even though I've heard it's empty all
summer. That's what people have been saying.
Or it's a lot emptier like this summer
than Disney would like.
So there's not as many people going.
Well I was reading
some accounts
that have American flags
in their user names and they're saying
that's because of this new Tiana right.
And even though that's in Disney
World and not Disneyland
just the whole brand has such a
stink at this point that
people are avoiding it like a
plague. User Breyer Ryan
Yeah.
1776.
With the
there are a couple of those by the way if you
haven't seen this people that have Breyer something or
their like icon is
a version of them. He even made that joke and I assume
No that is real. I've seen a handful
of that going on.
It's like the person on TikTok who's like
they closed the ride. I need
my daughter Breyer after.
I've seen people
try to trash the Tiana ride by
taking a video of
the ride that has like stalled or
like the lights have come on because they needed to evacuate
and use like a piece
of the video where there's not
much going on and the lights on
and people evacuating to like make
it look bad like they're
using. Yeah. They're
strategically using pictures to try
to like get a narrative going.
And then they just and then they insert
video of Biden just staring
off into the distance like and then they just play
this and you go by a screen and
just plays Biden.
That doesn't help anything. Yeah I know
there's a lot of screens on the ride now and most of them
are just Biden staring. Yep.
That's what's happening. Occasionally MSNBC
and frankly that takes me
out of it. Yeah. That's not what I want
on a ride. They don't even own that
channel.
They aren't even being synergistic. Truly
it makes no sense.
So you're getting ready for this one and let me see here
I think I can speak to the Disneyland
one more
and I watch ride throughs of all of them just to understand
the differences. And you know
there aren't vast differences I would
say between the four versions of the obviously
Tokyo not included.
But it's very
it is many adventures
the title is correct.
In tradition of the
original feature that put shorts together
you kind of jump through
greatest hits Winnie the Pooh
adventures. It's blustery day
it's rainy you meet
Tigger have the lumps and
woozles. Pooh has a party.
Pooh at the end is
in hog heaven
in a little little honey pit with all
the honey you could ever want. In some
of the other ones but in the
Disneyland one it just goes
it's your birthday! Happy birthday!
That does kind of
come out of nowhere doesn't it? Yeah it's a little
sudden but watching
the Florida one and the Disneyland one
back to back I'm like oh I think they either
had more room or more money
in the budget like it just seemed
a little less
cheap in the way the Disneyland one
is fun but a lot of it is
peanut flats.
Yes true. I
though want to stand up for the
charm of the Disneyland
one. Oh sure.
I now yeah
look if I take out of it that it took out
Country Bears and that's not so hard to do.
I like Country Bears but was I so
addicted to this attraction that
I don't remember being like upset
when it went away. I remember being
confused because it was right before the movie came
out and is that not the worst time
in the world to take the why would you
take out a living ad
for a movie you're putting into theaters.
Very strange.
Didn't hurt the film which turned out
glorious and is a
esteemed classic that we revisit to this day.
Jason didn't look up from
his iPad once while I was saying that.
I was trying to read and screen grab
I had a text.
Just catching up on some business
going through Texas spreadsheet
looking at some receipts.
No about Poo.
It was screen grabs of Wikipedia.
I was just double checking.
Poo P O O H
got it. Yes.
Yeah no it wasn't just a big my
Dookie note is different.
Your what? My Dookie
Dookie note. My Dookie note.
Do you know what that is?
Like doo doo. Like poop.
You never heard it called a Dookie?
You if anyone should know what Dookie is.
I know I'm slow I didn't put the poo
connection to it I'm sorry.
You had to wrap your head around the idea that Jason
keeps a Dookie note which presumably
is some way that he tracks the
color consistency. I thought it was
this thing the youth say. I thought it was like some
youthful thing he was saying and I was like well I'm
lost again. Well you said it
a long time ago. Listen to that
album.
Alright you're right. That's when you were with it
is when kids were saying Dookie.
I bought Dookie like six years after
it came out. I was not ready
for Dookie when I was that old.
1994 I was not ready
for the explosive
raw punk rock of Green Day.
Yeah so I
agree with every one of those words that you
said about it. I bought blood sugar sex
magic in like year 2001
and that's many many years after it came out.
So this is part of it these are cause it's all
your high school music.
In some ways it is cause
the first Green Day album I bought was Warning
I think which is like 2000.
Yeah I know.
It's after Nimrod. You can't
start with Warning. I learned how to play
I learned how to play
the guitar from listening to Warning.
There's still
like pieces of Warning in the way
I play guitar.
So ultimately Warning was
an indelible influence on the
guitar work of my girls. It was yeah.
Learning how to play power chords
from like the song Cast Away.
And it was actually like I
picked it up fairly fast which I think
like made me keep playing.
So I owe a lot to Green Day. Future Club 3
topic.
If anybody wants to throw it into a poll
Mike just plays guitar
Scott and Jason sit and listen and
shut the fuck up. Yeah. My dream.
And we have to with photographic
evidence prove that we didn't leave.
I guess it could be a video. We could do a video.
Yeah we'll just yeah. At least at least
proof. At least with a time stamp.
Several time stamps beginning and end.
Sitting our asses down and listening
to you playing guitar.
Listening to me play guitar specifically the song from
Warning. Podcasting is
conversations and conversations are
about listening and sometimes conversations
are about listening to your
co-worker jam on guitar.
Yeah. Nail Warning.
You all say you're like maybe it could be a video
you kept going into like you know
maybe it could be like you know down low on me and maybe there's like
a fan that's blasting my hair and maybe
a smoke machine.
Maybe it could be at the Wiltern.
Maybe we could shoot at the Wiltern.
We could just sit off on stage. We're on sale.
Sure.
There's a song called Blood Sex and
Booze on Warning as well and that's not quite
Blood and Chocolate or Blood.
There's two words there.
So that's pretty good.
Yeah.
And then the ride not to bring it back
too long to Country Bears.
Did anyone else come across
I never saw this before
I have no idea about this
proposal or how far it got.
There was a proposal for a
Country Bear racing attraction
called Critter Country
500. Oh right.
We talked a little bit about this I think in the
Country Bear week.
Yeah there was an idea to take the characters
in the Country Bear characters.
Yes and there's some art
from it and I wish
that was there. That would be awesome.
Sounds really cool. Sounds really good.
It seems like if the ride is cool
enough that it doesn't matter
that people know the mythology or don't
or they know Winnie the Pooh better or not.
That's the thing. Yeah that's the thing I would
argue until I was blue in the face with any
executive where I was like do you understand
that the ride has to be awesome and if the ride
is awesome people will tell other people
it's awesome and they will come here
to do the ride. Yeah.
This is how all of your
lore was created. It's all
original stuff that people thought was
awesome so they said you've got to see the Haunted Mansion
or Pirates. Yeah.
It was an IP then
it was just a new ride they did.
I don't know why this will never happen
again. I mean I know why but
I also don't know why. I don't know why you would
be like we just have to make something that's so
amazing that feels original and people
have never seen before and they will go
nuts for it more so than
an IP thing or at least as equal
as a good IP. Because people just want to
keep their jobs. Yeah.
I know why. And because it's Disney
they still don't.
So actually
on the end of
not built stuff for the
space I remember the rumor
and maybe I said this back then
when this all came up I feel like I heard
the possibility that something
that they were exploring which and this is going to sound a lot
cooler than what we got is that the Winnie
the Pooh ride would have taken advantage
of the river front
nature of the
of the building and that you
would have like Splash Mountain gone into the
river a little bit and what this might have been
was a gentle kids
rapid flume
type attraction where you're in
I'm going to guess a honey pot
because that is round like
like a rapids raft.
Yeah. That's the term.
But doesn't that sound nice like a little like
because I like any attraction like that
and with a young kid now
and being a scaredy cat kid myself
like anything to like help me in
lure me into the water. So if there had been like
a tiny flume or a
tiny
rapids ride that would have
helped me in the way the tiny coasters help
a lot. The gateway ride.
A gateway ride. Yeah.
They wouldn't like that phrase
on Welcome to Pooh Corner. That's true.
I would advise against that. But
also what you're describing is
like what we always talk about liking
is just something that kind of intersects with
a different part of the park in a way or
Yeah. It uses what was there
and ties it all together. Absolutely.
That is like what I would pitch
if I worked on an imaginary I would be
yelling a lot at the executives and then I'd also
be pitching stuff that goes into other rides.
Like we say it all the time. It's just
like the train going through Splash
Mountain or the Skyway through Matterhorn.
People move or going into Star Tours.
Yeah. So yeah. A little
boat ride that started outside of the rivers
but then like kind of went in it or
a little bit around it and you could kind of see the Mark Twain
or something. Yeah. Everything. I think it would
have spun down a little bit.
And then just bobbed into I think
Man that's awesome. Yeah. Imagine a tiny version
of that drop on Guzzly River
Rapids. That's awesome. I don't know where I'm
pulling that from though. That might maybe
that was just a rumor. I don't know if that was
ever anything they were actually doing. The idea is cool.
The cool idea though of like because it's not
inherent that a poo ride
would be a dark ride, a Fantasyland
style ride.
And that's an innovative way
to do one. Now what I was
going to head for is kind of defending
the critter country version.
That to me is
part of it. I
I still have a tough time getting my
head around Winnie the Pooh in
Fantasyland. It feels weird
to me. Winnie the Pooh feels
like nature, pastoral.
I think this critter country
placement makes more sense
than the Fantasyland version. I don't
like the critter country placement though. Really?
I agree with you about Fantasyland
but I also don't think he belongs in critter
country. I think
he does because
I just I think
the place making and some of it is left
over from
Country Bears being there before.
But I just I like
I like the trees there.
I like the little waterfall. That's
one of my little happy places in the park. The little
waterfall right when you get off that ride. It's kind of between
the ride and the shops.
Like actually gentle
relaxing contemplative
a thoughtful spot as Pooh
would say in the park.
I don't know. I like the rock
work and I think those big
I like those vehicles as opposed to
honey pots.
These are beehives. They're big beehives.
I like being in this line.
I find the line the outdoor queue
very pleasant. I agree with all that.
I like loading outside like Alice
does it too. You get in
outside and then you go inside.
Totally. Yes. I never thought about
that but I like that too. Yeah. I agree
with all of that and I like the Disneyland stuff
better. I like that whole area
like Hungry Bear. All of that is a little
more quiet than like a normal
Disney spot in general. Gentle Browns
it's a little autumn zone.
Over there. I'm glad it's all kind of it seems like
Tiana's retaining the
vibe. Yeah. Like that corner is still really nice.
Yes and they made it fit and it
it's better but
I do think of Pooh Bear
as a big book that you open up
and that's what I think of with the Fantasyland
rides. Oh okay.
This is a good debate point. Yeah.
I also
like the big book. I
was happy when
the new Winnie the Pooh
movie came out in what
2010, 2011
when was that?
You know very like quiet movie
that is not a blockbuster that new Winnie
the Pooh they did but that's not the vibe
of Winnie the Pooh either which makes sense.
That's where the ride landed. It's gentle.
It's aiming for gentle but I think
they did a really good job with that movie making it
feel like the shorts and making the book
a big part of it. Yeah. Because that
is like he bounces on the words
and the narrator it's meta
we go outside and he uses the
words to climb to things
or the words get all bunched up.
I love that stuff.
Now my counter
to you Mike is going to be I don't think they have enough
fun with that stuff. Oh that's true.
I think that I look at
Hong Kong, Shanghai, Magic Kingdom
and there are storybooks
but he's not interacting.
It's just open books
and we're not having fun with that
characters in this world can like
hang off of a queue
or go bouncing across a
paragraph. If that stuff's happening
now I like the book stuff.
I know that they do the book
interaction in Tokyo
and that's one of the many things that makes
Tokyo a superior experience.
Yes. There for sure is that in
Tokyo. I think I'm more so
saying that like I understand
thematically why it makes
sense to me more that Pooh is in Fantasyland
even though it doesn't because it's a storybook.
It's a storybook.
It opens and closes with books like all the fairy tales
do. That makes sense.
It's a dumb thing to be like they all start
with books so they all go in the same place
which is what I'm saying but that is
kind of how I justify it to myself.
I feel like it's different types of books.
I think this is a book in a
kid's nursery in this idyllic bedroom
as opposed to Sleeping Beauty,
Cinderella where these are
like the Bible. These are
these ornate works.
It feels too like
Victorian medieval.
I can't square Pooh in medieval.
That's what's weird. And you think Toad fits better
in that you think? Yeah I think so
because it's like Spires and
English and Countryside.
I think because it's like
structures, buildings, halls. That makes
sense next to a castle as opposed to
Winnie the Pooh lives in like a tree stump.
That doesn't make sense for a castle.
They kind of
2010 in
Disney World, they added
an interactive
queue
where like you can go in little
houses and you play in gardens
and
I think
that Florida
queue, there are giant
pages but you just
kind of walk by them.
You don't really play with it. I mean maybe
play with it in the interactive. And by the way if this wasn't
said, part of why I was doing that big argument
was, I don't think I
clocked this before, that the Critter Country one is
the only one that doesn't have the book.
And I think it's good. I think it's good
that they didn't do book here and they just kept it
forest
leaves, that vibe.
Here's what I think would actually be the ultimate
is if it was some more of the theming
from the Disneyland version, but
placed in Fantasyland not by
the castle stuff.
More like a little mermaid wise.
Oh sure, yes.
Little Mermaid is Fantasyland
in Florida, but
it is not like connected to
the castle in the way that those rides are.
Like feel like they're almost doors you're
entering in the castle in a way.
In some ways I thought of it like that when I was a
kid in Disneyland as well.
Like you're kind of like going into the rooms in the castle.
So like that makes sense
that Pooh shouldn't
have anything to do with the castle.
So that's right.
We're saying the same thing.
We're coming to an agreement.
But yeah, it's interesting.
Because yeah, critter country, I'm like Pooh's not a critter.
I know he's a stuffed
animal, but I don't know.
Critter is from the south or something
and there's like a little animal
with a country accent and they're playing a fiddle
or something. And he's English.
He's English, it's not the same vibe.
Critter, you gotta say the word
like this
or whatever and Pooh
that's not Pooh.
We need a dang Pooh.
Yeah, now if they wanted to do that ride
where they just had like a Slim Pickens
style voice
like do the Pooh story or something
and all the characters had southern accents
then okay, let's fucking go.
Let's do that.
Because that sounds funny.
That sounds good.
So I'm like,
it's a bear, I get it. There were bears there before.
But the country bears are critters.
Do we got somewhere better in Disneyland
to put this?
Space wise? No.
I guess. Fantasy, but Fantasyland
somewhere.
If you could carve out space somehow
in like Parade Route,
Autopia side of
Fantasyland, Autopia Fantasyland
side goes away.
Like Fantasyland but somewhere else.
That's kind of your ideal spot. Is that not
kind of what it is in
Japan? Yeah.
That is not connected. Fantasyland
adjacent. Right.
It's sort of, I'm trying to think, maybe
I'm getting the geography wrong in my memory
but it feels like it's
where the storybook boats are in
Disneyland almost. Sure.
Kind of like that. Something like that would work too.
Not that I'm trying to evict those. No, no.
But yeah, that feels more right.
Because you could build up a little like hilly
sort of facade. Totally.
If they decided to get rid of the theater,
the former Videopolis, that could be a good spot.
That would be perfect too. Up in the hills.
So it's not that Fantasyland doesn't work.
We agree that Castle
is strange. I think Castle is strange.
Well and the ideal is that
something like that happens and that it
doesn't evict country bears.
But it happened.
I think it was probably the right
move for them ultimately.
I think so.
It feels like the Pooh Bear ride is never
that long of a wait.
It feels like it's not that popular.
And I don't know if that's true or not.
I was thinking how.
I think this is a ride that you could use
as, I don't know if this is the right
term, but Canary
and the Coal Mine potentially.
Because if you are, not that this
happens anymore because you have to book many days
in advance, but in the old pop down
days where you're like,
do I feel like popping down today?
How are those wait times? That could be
a ride, that's a wait time
that you look at and you go, that's pretty big.
Maybe I don't bother
making the trip.
Do you guys have those?
Because my big one is
Monster's Inc. If I saw Monster's Inc. at like
45 to an hour, then
I'm not going anywhere near that place.
I think that's different now. I think that could be on a
normal day, it's 45 for an hour.
I think it's sort of changed.
Yeah, I don't know. I feel like that's changed.
And that's maybe just, that's not right.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
Or is there no number that will make you not
go today?
I think I'd go the other
way, and I'd look at what the e-tickets
are at.
If they are unreasonable.
That's what I think I do too, but I think what you're doing
actually maybe makes more sense.
It indicates, if it's stressful over in
Monster's Inc. then it's going to be really stressful
over in Big Thunder or whatever.
It is funny that we all have these sort of general
ideas that still I think
kind of make sense as
far as what a wait time should be.
Because like the last time I was there with my family
I'm looking at the, or I think
with Lindsay and I actually were just alone
the last time we went for a couple hours
and we were looking and it was like
Guardians was 90 minutes
and I was like something is wrong.
This isn't, it's never
it's always an hour. Guardians is always
an hour, 45 minutes or an hour.
Unless it's like end of the day or start of the day.
And I kept checking and kept checking
and we did do Genie Plus
and I was trying to find it. Genie Plus didn't work
and I was like something's wrong and then sure enough
later I learned that one of the
elevator shafts has shut down now.
Or they had to fix it or whatever.
Of course, it's never 90 minutes. Something's wrong.
And I have it in my head.
You diagnosed a problem.
Because I just know
the wait time for Guardians and it's
still that way.
I think I'm more like, I'll take a look at Space Mountain.
Space Mountain is like, Space Mountain
sometimes can be 90 minutes during the day I feel like
or longer. And if it's
like Space Mountain's 35 minutes
or 40 minutes or whatever, 45 minutes
you're like, that's not so bad.
Because that one's always a pretty long wait.
But yeah, poo is an hour.
Forget it. We're in a lot of trouble.
Because I think poo being around half
hour is probably more than it should be.
Yeah, and I wouldn't wait half hour for
poo. 15 maybe?
I did kind of a long
maybe in the 25
minute range and it was a little hot
and that didn't leave the best taste in my mouth.
However, on this particular day
this was my family meeting up at
Disneyland with just
accidentally there, like we got to do at least one ride
together with friend of the show
BugmaneBuzzBuzz and
MamaBug. MamaBug.
I don't know how you say
BizBiz?
BizBiz.
BizBiz, dear.
It was a delight to hang with the whole
and we all, that's a group
of five that's exactly what
fits in the
honey pot, or no, I was in the beehive
rather. So it was perfect.
That's a very fond memory.
Yeah.
This is a good
corner of the park. I mean, obviously
now it connects to Galaxy's Edge.
It's not a dead end
anymore.
But it's sort of off
to the side and
I'm sure this will change when
Diana opens out here because that'll be packed
for the foreseeable
future.
But like, yeah, Hungry Bear
has a lot of seating.
The food's
okay. Sometimes
it's better than others.
And there's a ride without too long a
wake and some shops,
a candy store
you can wander through. You can get the
candy store. You're just waxing
idyllic about Critter Country. You find
longing for the candy store.
You find Critter Country just to be
basically a pleasant place to
be. Yeah, it is pleasant.
Well, because
New Orleans Square really gets
out of hand sometimes with the
crowd. Yes.
That gets really nuts.
A difficulty you have though
with Critter Country is that dead end nature.
I remember in early
kid visits that
like, okay, I think of all the things
in this park, I think he would dig poo. I think
poo could be good. But it is, it's
way out of the way. It is not, there's,
it's not on the way to anything.
It is a gamble. If a day where it's getting
hot and it's getting, like, you get,
that's going all the way into a corner and all the way
back and you're nowhere near Main
Street and the Hub. It ended up being
worth it. We've had, we've had positive experiences
on that with, with our little
The meet and greets are there.
You can go buy it on the train.
Now that's one, like, oh, the
train will be even better
when Tiana's opens back up.
Because I think right now it's just
pitch black when you go through.
Oh, you get to see the finale again.
You get to see the finale. That will be nice.
Yeah, yeah, I'm looking forward to that. Toontown
though is a similar way where it's like, Toontown
it's almost like you're, you're doing
a voyage, if you have a kid, you're doing a voyage
to the moon. And you're like,
okay, it's going to take a long time to get
back to Toontown. Whatever we do in Toontown
then we got to get back out if this goes
wrong. So it's like you, there's not
an easy escape in Toontown. There's not an easy
escape in Critter Country.
And depending on if there's parades, what's going
on, it's like, there is a feeling of like,
well, here goes nothing when we go, we're
going to Toontown. Yeah. Toontown
much worse though, because you
coming back in a parade
route, it's a lot of
garish colors, terrible
food. Well, that's a whole
yes, that's a whole nother discovery, but yes, you're right.
One great ride, one pretty good
ride back there, but
yeah, it's, I think it's
more of a gamble than
Critter Country.
Yes, I think so. And it's a little
more, yeah, it's a little more unpleasant, a little
more loud, a little more aggressive.
This is an interesting, these are different
ways that we are viewing the parks, that I don't
think we ever thought about like making the
trek. If we're going to make the journey
over to, it's like getting stranded
on an island overnight or something, or like
having to do a layover. Are we really
going to really want to be laid over in Toontown?
Yes.
With kids in play. Yes.
It's just a different, I mean, in a similar way
you would be like, Toontown is like,
Toontown's so far away, not so
loud. But now with a kid you're like,
oh, and especially now, if you
get stranded there, the meltdown
happens in Toontown, we're in
trouble. Yeah, yeah. So it's like,
maybe we stick, yeah,
stick closer.
Yeah, I apparently
people are saying that if they do do
Disneyland Forward where they build up
next to the hotel, Disneyland Hotel,
that there would be like
that dead end in Critter Country would not
be a dead end any longer.
That would be the place that crosses over to
how?
Would you have to demolish, would it go through
like the stores?
I've thought about, listener,
if you don't know what we're talking about, that they approved
all of this land over
across Disneyland Drive
that is going to start getting converted
into theme park land. But what we don't know yet
is if it's a full third gate over there
or if it's expansions of Disneyland
and California Adventure
connected by weird bridges.
This all is going to make it, so like,
I've always thought of Disneyland as kind of this nice
clean little circle, and now it's going to
be very strange.
It's going to, like, there's this extra appendage,
you know? Disneyland's going to look like it's got
like an extra vestigial
tail. Yes, it's going to, both
parks will have little tails if it's just
that we're expanding
the current parks. Yeah, so like Splash Mountain's
here, and the parking lot stuff is
all here. So you would have to go out.
You would have to go out. I think you don't,
wouldn't you, would you have to blow up the stores,
the booze stores, or would it be
like a cast? I don't know. Because that's kind of
like a backstage
exit entrance. Well, I think
on the other
side, I forget whether it's
the other side of
New Orleans Square or the other side of
Critter Country, there
is precedent that
was the area where Walt
would have company picnics
early on. Okay. Like we
would entertain large groups. Those were
the kind of beer gardens.
Is there, well, what's there now?
I think the downtown Disney parking lot.
Oh. So yeah, so there's just,
so that's Poo Corner, that's the gift shop, and
then the road is here, Disneyland Drive.
So you could probably just have
like a tunnel or a bridge or something.
I bet it can't be a tunnel, can it?
They blow up a tunnel under the road?
Maybe? I am confused because
I saw someone stayed
in that new
tower at the Disneyland
Hotel, and there are rooms
at that tower that exit
out onto
a walkway that looks
onto just a road and a park
behind it. So I'm like,
wait, how would they wrap Disneyland
forward? There's no
room. There's just a public
road here. You mean behind it? Like
what do you? Behind the
Vacation Club tower.
Oh. I don't know. I think
the hotel is like a dead end.
Yeah. Like the hotel,
because the hotel's not going anywhere.
So north of hotel is Disneyland,
south is California.
I think that's why it can't be like a clean
third gate. Right, unless they switch
that to the other parking lot.
Or they build a land that goes
up above the hotel.
And those towers are about
20 stories or so.
But if they could build a floating land
that casts shadow like Mr.
Burns' sun machine onto
everything at the hotel,
maybe that works.
Go up 20 stories.
Do we have a preference third gate or
expanding out on the sides of the hotel
like that?
It seems weird, but
I think my preference is always third
gate. If it's the parking
lot, if it's the current
Toy Story parking lot, I guess my preference
is that and new gate. Just
because there's more of an opportunity, I feel like, for
interesting stuff. But
I thought that was like more of
a Disney Springs kind of situation.
That's what the talk is and that's what the plans are.
But that was a while ago.
They're zoning it all to be something, like it could be anything.
I just want to know what the new,
because like, to get a new park
name under the current name structure.
Right, right.
Ooh, I'm just looking at my chops
thinking about how much punctuation is
going to be in that, baby.
Disney wish world.
Colon slash hyphen.
Okay, what
else about these ride?
Moments in it, anything
that we like. I like
Heffalumps and Woozles in general.
I think it's very clever.
Like, sure, it's all flats, but I think
they're clever with the flats. I like
that it's, they,
there are those
silhouettes that, like, they've
cut the shapes of the Heffalumps and
Woozles and then behind it,
the pattern rotates
and changes. So it looks like
they're changing stripes and colors. I think
that is a very clever, I think we're doing
some, like, fun
house, you know, like,
cheap but effective
little tricks in there. Well, there's a whole
different vibe, I think, to the
Disneyland version versus Disney World
version. And that way you're talking about
fun, like, a fun house. There's, like, a day
glow neon
thing going on a little bit.
I mean, as far as, let me see
here. Like, Heffalumps
and Woozles, this is from 2022.
They didn't, unless they changed it in the last two years
at Disney World, but I don't believe that's the case.
But there is very much
more of, like, a bright kind of
neon happen. Like, this is Heffalump
and Woozle in Florida.
Okay. Yeah. So more like
the Pleasure Island sequence in Pinocchio
or something. Yeah. And then the Disneyland
one is this. This is the color
scheme, which is a lot more neon.
Right, right. A lot more, like,
black light poster
style. And the whole ride
kind of like that. Yeah. Wait, now God,
now I'm confused about which is which. I feel like
I forgot. Was it always that way here?
That's a good question. Are the Shanghai
ones?
The micro differences between
these are very hard to parse. I know
that Owl's House is
not in Disneyland, but it's in Disney
World. Yes. Well, and it's
got the picture on the wall of
Toad giving Owl
the deed to Toad Hall. Great.
Yes, which is nice. We like that.
Yes. Yeah. Continuously.
I think I like the more
weird, like,
at Disneyland,
if you look up and over your shoulder,
you can see Max Melvin
and Buff mounted
on the wall around the Hevelum
sequence. Yeah.
That is weirder.
That does seem like something you'd
see in a nightmare.
Just a bunch of non-moving
animal heads. Yeah.
They're dead. They are finally dead.
Yeah. They were reanimated
for the show. They ain't singing no more.
Also in Disneyland,
apparently the mechanism
of Pooh is in a hot air balloon
at some point. Oh, right.
That is the repurposed
mechanism that Teddy
Bara used to...
Wow. Bara used to... That's cool. Yes.
...use to get up and down. Well,
that's smart. Yeah.
You have to applaud the Imagineers for
reuse. Yes.
I guess not the most exciting
thing to applaud them for, but... And that
is something you really can make someone
zone out with when you explain
while you're on the ride. Yeah.
That is just...
That fact couldn't excite me more
and be more nothing
to an average person.
This is really...
This is so cool. This is the mechanism from the
Country Bear show that used to be here. Swinging Teddy
Bara used to be this. She would come down from the ceiling
and she started saying, and then Henry would kind of want to go
up there and he was horny for her. But like,
they're still using it. It's still the same. Like,
no way. Nobody cares. Nobody cares.
Then you had the question, what are country bears?
Right. Right. What's Teddy Bara?
Right. Why are the
bears horny? Right. Why did you whisper
all that? Why did you whisper so
long? You said it so fast, too.
I couldn't even keep track of what you were saying.
You were so excited about it. You were speaking another language.
This is a first date and it is
ruined. You were losing
them when you were like, there's a buffalo
and a moose head. Like,
and if you were losing them with that,
you sealed the deal
when you start talking about reusing
that. Sealed the deal in a bad way.
Yeah. Sealed the deal in losing them.
I see. Yeah. Yeah. You sealed
the deal of the breakup.
Of checking out. Yeah.
This is the final straw.
You sealed the deal of the
let's not do this again via text.
Yeah. I know this is
first date, but I feel the need to
tell you I'm taking the kids to
my mother some reason.
Yes.
I don't think
that Disney World, you, we were talking
about right before we started recording and Jason said
the Disney World version is like better. You said
it was more elaborate. It just looked
in video. I was like, this one looks
more built up. And I think there's
elements of it like, they might have had more room
or a larger budget. I think there's
more room and like when you go in
or when you first kind of enter the
ride, there is like
I don't know, kind of like these
three dimensional, like
I don't know what you call them. It's like part of like a
shed or
Owl's House. Yeah. Yeah.
Owl's House like giant
pieces seem to
shift and shake around. Right. Versus
Disney land version where
you just have these flats of like a barn door
with some leaves on them. Yes. And that's
like. Well, we're not comparing
the same sequence here. No, I know.
I like when you go past the barn
doors. That's just an
introductory sequence. And I think that's something
you might see in any. That's not too
different than Alice in Wonderland. I think that's an
unfair comparison. However, I
understand that there are more complex aesthetics
and craft going on.
Right. And I'm just trying to compare a version
of like walking, going through something.
That being said, I still think I like Disneyland better.
I like the color scheme better, even though it's not
quite the color scheme of the like
cartoon. Sure. But
it is a much more fun looking
color scheme. They play up
the blustery day. I think
blustery day is nice.
It's just all nice. It's a weird
ride to be mad at. I don't know if anybody
now is mad at it.
Somebody probably remembers the, you
know, any of the scandals
from years ago. Because like, look
at this. The Tigger here, and this is Disneyland.
Tigger and Disney World.
Oh, so
they do more ultraviolet light.
Yes. Stuff. Yes.
Better lit. Yeah. I will
say, the Shanghai, the
newer versions they've built, I think the rain
effects look really nice. Yeah.
I don't know, maybe they've plussed them up here
in ways I don't realize, but like all of
the projected stuff seems pretty
sharp. Otherwise, nothing, there's nothing
that insane going on
in the other ones. Hong Kong, though,
deeply popular, usually runs
out of fast passes and wait times over
120 minutes
on peak. How about that? We're saying
like I wouldn't do more than 30.
They will gladly do 120
minutes, gladly. They will
forcibly do 120 minutes
in Hong Kong. That's very interesting.
The last button,
Florida, they're trying
to start the party, and they're like, where's Pooh?
And he's in a big honeycomb, and he goes, start
the party without me. Like, really
quick as he's like chowing down
on honey. Yeah. Start the party
without me. Start the party without me. He's got
a mouthful of honey. He's got a mouthful of honey.
And he's just having the time of
his life. That's good. Like, a little
less abrupt, kind of a good joke.
You mentioned Shanghai.
Shanghai almost got
into, there
was, I don't know how much
concern on Disney's end. There was
worry they might have to change it
in the late
2017-2018.
There was
a bit of an issue
that, in China,
people were
making memes of
Xi Jinping, the president,
and comparing him to Winnie the Pooh.
Right. Especially after this
picture of
Xi Jinping
and Obama
walking looks very much
like Pooh and Tigger.
I mean, kind of.
One's taller than the other. Yeah, one is tall.
I can think of
two people here who might look like Pooh and Tigger.
I don't disagree
with that. But I think people
just were tweeting a lot of pictures
of Winnie the Pooh. But they were like, we're going to
make the president mad if we
have Winnie the Pooh here.
They were banning it on
their
heavily fired, well, internet,
heavily censored
internet. And so
there was like, is Disney
going to have to redo this? I think
it probably would have made him look very
stupid if Disneyland Park was
we have to re-theme the
Winnie the Pooh ride.
The party
and the president don't like
this. Yeah. That would
have made them look worse.
Well, I think they should have just kissed up all the way
and just made it an animatronic of
the president. Yeah, put him in the ride.
Just make it his.
He's caught in a tree trunk.
He's caught in a honeycomb.
Xi Jinping
as a rumbly tumbly.
Problem solved.
Yeah, there's some cool stuff in
that version of the ride. And like
it's all just like a little different from each other,
which I like, I appreciate.
It's not quite the like
neon of the Disneyland.
But it does kind of have its own like
lighting, its own kind of color
scheme. Pooh floating off
seems like a really good effect
in Shanghai.
They seem to do that well. But I like this beat in
all of them. I like that
you follow a projection
for a little bit in the Disneyland
one. And it reminds me of following
the croquet ball
in Alice in Wonderland. I think the whole
thing reminds me of Alice in Wonderland, which I like.
I like that like it's
a similar
length of vehicle. It's in an odd place.
Like it feels like
kind of outside of the main four
Fantasyland attractions.
That might be a lot of why I like
the one here. It feels like of a piece of Alice
in Wonderland. Like the oddballs,
you know, but still good
dark rides that have like little
clever effects. And also
isn't just like the next time you're trying to go
to sleep, just like picture yourself
being Winnie the Pooh.
I can't imagine a more relaxing way
to just imagine yourself
becoming opaque and floating
off into the air in
just a shirt, pants, yes.
He's so, that is the deepest
sleep. I am, boy would I love
to get that Winnie the Pooh sleep.
I know. I want that sleep.
Yeah, yeah. The medication has
to be involved to get that kind of sleep.
For me, yeah. Like they have to induce a coma
to get me to actually relax and
fully like have the healing effects
of sleep happen to my body.
It's just like, yeah
I cannot sleep. I
stopped drinking caffeine to try
to do that. I'm like, you know what? That's gotta be
what it is. I'm gonna stop drinking caffeine
and the sleep is gonna get so good and it's gonna be
so restful. That didn't change
at all. No. What the hell?
This was supposed to fix all my problems.
It fixed none of them.
What time did you use to stop
caffeine?
The afternoon caffeine? I would try
to stop it by one, but once
in a while I'd go up till three or four.
Okay. But no, it almost didn't
change anything. Yeah. I was expecting
some crazy cool thing
that was gonna happen. I was gonna be like a different person.
No, same person. Same shit.
Same stuff happened to me.
I have an ambient
problem.
My quill doesn't work so well
anymore. I have to do
the harder stuff.
I have to do the things that really put you
out on your ass. I'll sleep for
24 hours straight.
It's a little bit
creepy. It got to the point where
Yuna-san was keeping me up.
Where are you even getting these pills,
they say. I really can't.
You do have a like, it's
an inward whistly thing to it.
I don't know how you're doing it. Yeah, I don't know.
I would annoy Lindsay with it like 10
years ago.
I think
most of my impressions, it just turns cloying after
a while and weird and creepy.
I think he was like, I think he might
have been strung out when I was doing it 10 years ago.
It's really hurting
my voice for a gentle impression for some reason.
Oh bother.
Oh my.
Wait, just say, I'm just going to feed
him to you. Just say, my throat's torn to shit.
My throat is torn to shit.
Owl,
give me a lozenge.
I do think I used to be like,
oh this is what I used to do. I used to be like,
Piglet, I'm sick. Piglet.
Piglet, I need help.
I need help, Piglet.
Please. And it's like, stop doing that.
That's annoying and creepy.
And I'd be like, no, you don't understand.
Something's wrong with me, Piglet.
I have a tear in my anus.
Poo, I don't, that doesn't
Are you sure about that?
We all have tears, poo. We're made of stuff and fluff.
No, you don't understand. The stress has ripped me
open again.
It's not the same thing as if it were to happen
to the humans. I need you to fix me.
I need you to fix me. Get the string.
Get the needle and thread out of
the cupboard. I'm going to head
into the creek for a little bit. I'm going to go for a round of poo sticks.
Why don't you take a breather?
The door's locked. You'll be here
with me tonight, fixing me.
There's not enough air for
two people in the stump, poo. I hope Christopher
Robin taught you how to sew.
Poo and Piglet are fighting
again.
We're not fighting.
We're just having a disagreement.
Yelling about his
anus. That is what it was. It was,
it was a bit where poo was really,
something was wrong with him. And I would just
do that for a while. And
Lindsay didn't like it. I think you need more help
than a little pig can give you, poo.
I don't think so.
I think you have everything I need.
I need a blood
transplant. A stuffing
transplant, please.
That requires a doctor.
You can't just do that. I'm a doctor
now. Your body might reject mine.
I'm a doctor. I'll put on my stethoscope.
No
offense, poo. And this is a bad time to tell you this.
You're not smart. Poo and Piglet
haven't been the same
since they got into a challenger
situation with Kanga.
I want to make love to you and Kanga.
This is all in Blood and Honey. We're doing Blood and Honey
scenes, I think. Yeah, yeah.
We're just doing it. No, this will
just occur. We just, we said
at the start of this
episode, anybody can make a poo movie.
We just made our little poo movie. We did it.
And it's legal, finally.
Sleeping pills have driven poo insane
to where he maybe
wants to eat Piglet.
And Eeyore is
just keeping far away from
the whole thing. I'm kind of acting
like a Greek chorus.
These two
right again.
We should wind it down.
Anything
else we want to shout out about these
or like, do you want to
I mean, maybe there's a Poo's
Honey Hunt episode at some point down the road.
But like, in terms of like
basic jealousies, I mean
now, okay,
here's my defense versus
Poo's Honey Hunt is that sometimes
you have a space where a ride
could go, but it's not
the space, the massive warehouse
that is needed to build big
state of the art trackless attractions.
Sometimes there are weird little
plots of land that have
the same amount of
acreage as like a Burbank
dentist's office would. And would you rather
have a ride in there or not? Now,
that said, why could they not do
a, you know,
a little ride that's on a
regular kind of track that has some of the
more innovative animatronics
that Poo's Honey Hunt has?
I mean, I'd love the whole thing.
I want a trackless honey pot.
That sounds great, but
you know, the elevated stuff
they do is really
cool. There's no, I mean, like
there's no reason to not have that
advanced animatronics
besides money. Yeah.
And I'm, yes, this used to be a
theater on this land.
So it was not a dark ride or anything.
So I'm sure, yeah, there's not a ton of
land here, but yes,
there were elements that were
much more expensive in Tokyo
that they didn't go with because
it's cheaper and we know, blah, blah, blah.
We've complained many times before.
But Boy
is like Poo's Honey
Hunt almost like an e-ticket to me after
going on it. And it's just
that is a 45 minute wait that I'll
do, that I would do, I think.
Fairly regularly.
30, 45. There is
a difference, yes. Now, they might have
something pretty right about the trackless
ride system. And this is the first Disney
one, correct? I believe so, yeah.
That, you know,
of your myriad
of Rise of the Resistance complaints,
the one that I could get the closest to
is it, I don't
know if I agree with your phrasing about it, not
fucking me up. I don't think I want the vehicle
to fuck me up. But sometimes
these trackless vehicles are a little bit lacking in
thrill because they can't
really turn you
and pivot you and shake you up the way that a regular
track can. So
a trackless vehicle being gentle
makes a lot of sense.
Beauty and the Beast seems very successful.
We haven't gotten to go on it.
And this does too.
Maybe trackless vehicles more often
should be aiming for gentle.
That might be what they're the best at.
I do agree with that. And like
Mickey and Minnie, they work pretty well.
But like my favorite
scene, or one of my favorite scenes
is the dancing section.
And it is because the vehicle does kind of a different
thing because you're taking dance lessons
with Daisy. And it's kind of jolting
you back and forth in a kind
of an aggressive manner. Yeah, you slide
around. You slide around and you're like
there's like a variation
on what you're feeling on a ride.
Depending on the ride, important. And Pooh,
there's a bouncy section of the Pooh's
Honey Hunt that I'm
actually not even sure if the whole
floor is, I'm not sure what's happening.
It just feels like you're all, I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe that's something to investigate
when we do the full Pooh
thing. But like that's the most jealous
I am of that. Because you go in this little
room, there's like screens of Tigger
and then it's the Tigger song
and you're bouncing up and down in the vehicle.
And you know, you already like, if that was your first
time going on a trackless ride vehicle, which at the time
it was, for us.
But like then you go, oh this thing can go
up and down. And that felt like just such
a unique way to
use that ride system too. And again,
I don't know if the whole, maybe the whole floor is bouncing.
I'm not sure. Because like,
why wouldn't you use that bouncing thing?
There's no way the entire floor
is bouncing. It seems silly, I agree.
Would it propel the entire vehicle up?
Or is it an illusion?
It has to be in the vehicle.
Why have none of the other
trackless rides used something like that?
Because there wasn't a character that bounced that called
for it. I don't know, but you could have got shot
and bounced. Think about it. Give me a picture.
How is the entire floor moving?
There's no way. That seems silly, you're right.
Yes. It's too heavy.
Every trackless ride vehicle is very heavy.
And there's people on it.
It probably wouldn't be reliable either.
That everyone bounces correctly and safely.
Maybe you go right on a big trampoline.
And there's a couple people under just pushing.
Or a big robot arm.
No, I like the people pitch. I think they have
full time employees.
I guess it has to be in the vehicle, but it's
I just think they would have used another
used that somewhere else.
Once you introduce a trampoline,
you up the likelihood
of hearing the phrase, oh no, Tommy
fell off and broke his arm.
That's just automatically introduced.
What is that from?
Kids fucking
themselves up and back here at
trampolines just produce
broken arms.
But that room I think is the one I'm most jealous
of.
In addition to just
fancier looking robots.
And yes, like a perfect
use of that ride system.
The gentleness.
Yeah.
Because yeah, I think now I'm a little
bit sick of that ride system.
In some ways where I'm like, yeah,
Mickey and Minnie could have maybe been different
if it was a different ride system.
I really like Mickey by the way. I'm not putting
that right down.
I think that's a very successful trampoline ride vehicle.
I think Mickey and Minnie might be the best one
at the big American parks.
That feels organically.
I think any of them could use this thing that
they can go into different paths.
You know, and I
have the
bizarre leftist opinion that Rise
of the Resistance is an excellent ride.
So I will stick to that and say
that's a very well done ride.
Bernie bro. Biden bro.
Lieutenant Beck bro.
They should build a
track and stride vehicle that has like an arm,
like a kook arm on the part
on the ground.
And then that could like whip you around
aggressively.
But you can still have that smoothness.
I mean, this is not out of the question.
Well, you know what would be cool is if a
trackless ride vehicle went inside
kind of a bigger shell
that drops you and it becomes
a drop ride as well and then you leave
in a different way.
Oh, that is what happens in this ride
that is a good ride.
Another one where you end up outside.
It's just a couple
letter grade.
I didn't get to see my friends.
There could have been friends and you could get fucked up.
Those are two things. You want to get
fucked up with your friends and you don't get
fucked up with your friends when you go on Rise of the Resistance.
So that's just a fact.
You can't deny that.
I want to dislocate my shoulder while
the Han Solo watches.
Han, I hurt myself.
I don't care.
That's exactly what I want you to say.
You my friend. This ride is great.
Luke the giant sliding cannons
grievously injured me.
Yeah, and Luke's just like
haha, he's giving you one of the
good work
young Jedi.
So yeah, I think that
that's a plus up. They can do it.
They can't fuck you up but they can
end your friends. One of those classic
Luke Skywalker chill
lines, chill cool lines
is always saying. Well if it's post Return of the Jedi
when he's kind of got that calm sort of
Jedi thing going before he goes to
Ock 2 and betrays
everyone for 20 years
then he would have that calm. He would be able to
give you a chill line. I suppose, yeah.
Give you a chill
lime. Chill lime.
That's nice.
I mean I can't argue with, of course
I like the ride but would I like to drink a nice
refreshing cocktail with Luke Skywalker?
Here's a Pooh Bear plus up. I would
love that 90s Pooh Bear song somewhere.
I know it doesn't fit the
vibe of a lot of these things.
But I wish that, even throw
me a bone and put that in
Toontown now because they're doing kind of music
or music or jazzy versions
of Disney afternoon
songs. There's like
a jazzy version of Eye to Eye playing in
Toontown which I like and there's a rescue, like a
jazzy rescue rangers.
We need a little more Pooh Bear. They have turned
their back on this song. This is a fantastic
song. I really agree.
Yeah. I don't know anyone, I don't know
who was involved in it.
I don't know who put it together but boy is it
great. And like I just, yeah when you think
about like towards the end
like Pooh Bear I gotta
be there.
Oh man. I like it. As with all
of these songs, they influence my music
taste in a big way. I am
chasing pop songs that feel like the
new adventures of Winnie the Pooh.
It feels in the family of those,
the rescue rangers and the duck,
like it feels. Of course and it's under acknowledged.
Yeah. It doesn't, yeah you're right.
It doesn't show up anywhere. Right. I'm glad we took
this time to say how great that song
is. Yeah. Completely under acknowledged.
Yeah.
You know, play, I would say play it
at the beginning and end of the day
at the park at large. Yeah.
Many times throughout just on
you know
if Main Street Electrical Parade comes back
ditch the song, play that song instead.
Yeah. Use it as the fireworks backdrop.
Use it as the score to rise
the resistance there. We fixed it and you like the
ride now. Oh my god that would be awesome.
Star Wars movie,
Star Wars.
Yeah change the lyrics I suppose.
Looking for maps.
Always looking for McGuffin,
Star Wars.
And silly old Lieutenant
Beck.
Maybe we deep dive
on that song and that's a second gate somewhere
along the line. The Pooh Bear song from
the 90's cartoon.
Who did this for us?
Or just the themes in general I bet.
That is a good episode idea.
Oh just go to the themes. Yeah, you're right.
And try to determine a best one
officially. I have an opinion already but
I could be swayed. Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
Well yeah, hey that's a good one. Let's do
that. I love that. I'm glad we talked about that
but for now you survived podcast
the ride.
And I think we kept things positive
about this attraction. Yeah.
Really quick let me say
your rocket launcher thing Mike.
I forget if that's been on my main feed
ever that you take out a rocket launcher
you pick two rides. Which one do you
got no time to decide. If it was between this
and Buzz Lightyear, Buzz
Lightyear is gone. I think that's more
flat, less charming.
Yeah.
I would, Buzz you're out. Jason
what do you think? Between those two?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a tough one.
I don't know. Three.
It might be Buzz. Two. One.
It might be Buzz even though
this Buzz is better
than Florida's Buzz. Yeah I
guess, I guess I say
Buzz too. I guess cause there's
other Toy Story 2
representation in the park but I do, I really
go on Buzz anymore also.
Probably less so than Pooh.
So yeah I guess Buzz even though I don't,
I'm not like happy about it. Great.
I'm not going to be gleeful when the
rocket hits it or whatever.
But. At least Zerg is dead.
That villain of Zerg finally got what was
coming to him.
Hey but as for us
check out, for three bonus
episodes every month, check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP
Tier Club 3. You'll find
all of that at Patreon.com slash
Podcast the Ride. You want to hear an
even better Winnie the Pooh
related song though? Oh yeah please.
Mike I wonder if this is something you know already.
I wonder. Do you know,
alright, I did the show
the intro in kind of a Winnie the Pooh
narrator way. The Winnie the Pooh narrator is
Sebastian Cabot who played
Mr. French on Family Affair
correct? Which came up on a second gate.
Of course. As an idea
of the kind of boring
stuff Jason and I were talking about.
Here's what a boring tangent
would be about. Family Affair.
Anyway he was kind of a pre-Mr. Belvedere
right? Yes. Stuffy English guy.
Great narrator for Winnie the Pooh.
Do you know about his album?
I don't know. Oh boy.
Holy shit. I'm glad I can.
Holy shit. Never in a million years could you
guess what the Sebastian Cabot album is.
So all you need to know is that he's the
narrator of Deep in the Hundred Acre Way. That's all you need to know.
And he
decided to get with the times.
Address what the kids are
thinking about and liking. Good.
And he did an album called
Sebastian Cabot Actor
Bob Dylan Poet. Really?
It is a front to back
full spoken word
Bob Dylan Covers album.
Wow. And I think this would be
good exit music. Here now
through the same voice that gives you
Winnie the Pooh is
the song Like a Rolling
Stone. No way.
Once upon a time you dressed
so fine.
You threw the bums a dime
in your prime, didn't you?
People call, say
beware doll, you're bound to fall.
You thought they were all kidding you.
Used to laugh
about everybody that was hanging out.
Now
you don't talk so loud.
Now you, you don't seem so proud
about having to be scrounging
for your next meal.
How does it feel?
How does it feel
to be without a home?
Like a complete unknown.
Like a rolling stone.
Now you've gone to the finest
school all right, Miss Lonely.
But you know you only used to get
juiced in it.
Full album
of that. Wow. That's every track
is that. This little like whimsical
arrangement of the
Bob Dylan song. Yeah, chimes.
This is pre-Rocket Man.
It's very Rocket Man-ish.
Yeah, as much as
Dylan inspired many after
him, Sebastian Cabot certainly inspired
William Shatner.
In that story of the
hurricane, the man the authorities
came to blame.
How's it feel?
Feel the
without a home.
And then roll, make sure, let's try when you hit
rolling like a rolling
stone.
Hey Winnie the Pooh, how's it
feel? I don't know. What did I do?
You cut that together with the
Pooh opening clips of that
with the Winnie the Pooh. Yeah, there's
like a way you can slot in.
Gotta get going.
Gotta see a friend of mine.
He's round, he's fuzzy.
I love him because he
Pooh Bear, I gotta
be there.
Forever
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott
Gardner, Brett Boehm,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit Forever Dog
podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple
podcasts, Spotify, or
wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog
Team and liking our page
on Facebook.