FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The podcast you knew
is dead.
From its ashes rises
a hauntcast
full of psychopaths,
dolls who do Rickle-style burns,
and weird little guys.
No late arrivals will be
admitted, for shocking twists
await. For example,
Jason talks about seeing a bunch of
old office chairs.
Guess I spoiled that one, but there's more to come.
Chelsea Rebecca from
Dead Meat joins us to talk
Universal's storied history
with Norman Bates
on Hauntcast the Fright!
Welcome, foolish mortals,
to Hauntcast the Fright!
A masterful work of
suspense which we hope gets remade
38 years from now.
Precisely the same, but with more
masturbation. I'm
the Garewolf!
And joined for this Hauntcast
season by...
Oh, a spiky snarl gun.
Gun, snarl gun. I really
screwed it up, cause like,
ugh, I'm so embarrassed, I'm sorry.
It wouldn't be the Hauntcast
the Fright! month if there wasn't a lot
of hemming and hawing about the names.
If we just set them confidently and moved
on, that's not what we do.
We get caught in the brambles on
these, and we'll see if the next guy
gets caught in the brambles, his name is...
Jackal Skeridan.
Jackal Skeridan's wonderful. Yeah, thank you.
It only took seven years and I started
writing them down, so I would
remember. It doesn't become
like, oh, uh, uh, oh.
But I look forward to every year
when Mike, uh, on every episode
is like, ah, shit.
Trying to remember.
Try to keep it that way, try to keep, uh,
not getting them right. Yes, we are kicking off
yet another Hauntcast, the Fright! season.
We got a lot of fun in store all
October, and I really like where we're kicking things
off today, because we are joined by
a true horror head, and
from The Sounds of it, a big theme park head as well,
from the Dead Meat podcast
and YouTube channel. It's Chelsea Rebecca.
Hi! Yes, if you look closely
in the background of this podcast,
you can see me, uh, out of a window
walking my dogs by, like,
Alfred Hitchcock. Yes.
My spooky cameo appearance.
Thank you for having me. Absolutely.
Thanks for making a cameo and a
full appearance as well.
And not only that, I mean,
so excited you're here. Thank you for reaching out.
I'm so happy to meet you.
And then, and what a great arrival, too,
that you wore the shirt, which is
my exciting eBay
purchase. Um, I
can't believe I already found
an appropriate occasion on which to
wear it. I have a Psycho
1998 promotional giveaway
t-shirt that someone
on eBay is trying to get rid of
lots of them, so
check it out. Yeah, they come in every
size, and you can tell that
some marketing department made them, and
no one wanted them. Okay.
This is not a thing. There is nostalgia.
Somehow nostalgia has not accrued for
98, exact remake.
I just saw somebody try to dig
up a little enthusiasm for, like,
you know what, 98 was, like, one
like tweet or something that I feel like
somebody was like, hey, hey everybody,
didn't we actually like this thing? It was probably
me. Maybe it was.
Maybe it was.
This movie's number one fan.
And this is, you were saying this is a
runner on your podcast. It is. It's been a
runner basically since the beginning
of our show, since, like, 2017,
18. I don't know how
it started. Actually,
no, I do remember. I was playing a
game where I was reading my husband taglines
from, like, horror posters
and making him guess what they were.
And I read the Psycho
98 tagline, which is the
same, and was like, oh, that's incorrect.
It's technically the 1998. And so it
just became a runner
to kind of, like,
break his winning streak in games, just
slip in the 98 Psycho.
There's no way to know. He's right.
Psycho 98,
when I was 13, 14,
and we rented it
because we were a big Hitchcock
family. Like, everyone could agree
on Hitchcock. My mom
really liked Hitchcock.
And this
is not the actor
I wrote down that I was
excited about. But in that
movie, the private detective in 98
is William H. Macy.
And that was a very weird
14-year-old thing. That was like,
look, it's William H. Macy.
You mean, like, you were so excited? I was so excited.
But did you think it was weird
he was in there because, like, you had just
discovered him? No, I think it was
weird that a 14-year-old in the
year, like, 1999
or 2000 had that much
enthusiasm about William H. Macy's
career. I bet
that I had a similar
enjoyment of William H. Macy
and awareness, I will say.
I don't know that it was such an anomaly.
I don't want to make you feel less special. I'm not trying
to do that. I'm just saying that
Mystery Men's around this time.
He was out there. Boogie Nights. Mystery Men was
great. I was also, like,
very into David Mamet's
filmography, which
looking back is very hit and miss.
But William H. Macy shows
up in a lot of those. Sure. Philip Baker
Hall. I didn't know until
Hall's terrific. I hadn't seen, he does
the, he's the psychiatrist scene
at the end.
Right, or is that Forster?
Wait, now I'm going crazy. Oh, yeah, I
forget. Are they both in it?
What, Robert Forster? Yeah.
I forget if Robert Forster's in it.
Oh my gosh, maybe I'm not the number one
psychiatrist. You still could be.
That's true, I still could be.
I don't think we have time to hear
my Robert Forster. Yeah, Robert
Forster is Dr. Simon Richmond.
Oh, he's the end character. I thought that. Oh, and then
Philip Baker Hall's the sheriff. That's
what it is. Okay, okay. Sargam
Tangled. Excited they're both in there. Both great. You
have a Robert Forster story? I do
have a Robert Forster story. Is the story going to be, we
were a big Robert Forster family and then
he was in the movie. It is not.
I have not
one, but two autographed
headshots of Robert Forster
because he did not
like his signature on the first one.
He did it again?
My old landlord
was a floral designer
at a flower shop
and the owner of it
was dating Robert Forster towards
the end of his life.
How do I not know this?
She mentioned it
at one point and I was like,
oh my god, I love her for Forster.
And I didn't
get a letter opener because that was his
thing. He always gave letter openers out.
But he signed a headshot when
I didn't like it. He didn't like
his signature so he signed another
headshot and he gave her both
of them. So I have two
Jason Robert Forster
headshots. That's so sweet.
I love him. Jackie Brown is
one of my favorites. It's in my top three.
Do you have them
framed? Where are they? I don't have them
framed. I think I just have it with
a file with some art
and some other photographs.
It would be fun to frame the mistake
actually.
You saw his process. You saw a
great actor's process at work.
Absolutely.
Chelsea, excited
and we'll focus
on Norman Bates and
all things Psycho here as it relates
to Universal Studios, the theme park. But also
you're big into Halloween
Horror Nights and I'm not sure
about the other one but I know that you were
up there and have done
for many years a red carpet appearance
like you live stream
the Halloween Horror Nights red carpet. This year was
our first red carpet that we
live streamed
and it was the year that it was
107 degrees outside
so a lot of people were not
they were because we
were located right next to
the AMC at
City Walk where they had the doors
just slightly propped open so you could feel
that it was cold in there and I think
by the time people got to where we were they
were like oh but that
I can tell it's real cold in there. They would
just kind of whoop. I'm sorry. Whoever
you are you're not air conditioning. Yeah. John Carpenter
I'll allow it. He walked by
us just flashing peace signs like
hey thanks guys. I gotta go
home and play Sonic or whatever.
He's getting up there
it's great we still have
them you don't want them to whatever
makes you comfortable. We've been fortunate to interview
him before and it was
awesome. We did we barely talked about movies
we talked about video games and the
economic situation
of Detroit because I said I was from
Detroit and he was like oh what's going on
there like what's tell me about
it. Okay.
He's really cool.
That's great. I was shocked to see him like on
the red carpet horror. Yes.
He got out of the house for this. Wow.
That's cool. Got those
music royalties. Yeah.
He was there with his wife Sandy.
Like did he go through a house.
Do you think. I doubt it. I doubt it
right. But like why why not.
At least get ushered through
it before everyone goes.
How were how was everyone
spirits at a hundred and seven
degrees at Horror Nights because I've watched some
live streams and people still
seem to be having fun. Yeah like
surprisingly everyone was
I don't know what no one seemed cranky.
I think it was a I think it was just so
nasty out that it became like a
oh we're all in this together kind of thing.
You know it kind of
went past that point of the
bell curve like it was past miserable
into like well you know we're all here
let's just have fun.
Help each other. Yeah.
Not I saw that they weren't you couldn't
bring your own water bottles in.
Universal was not in the team spirit
as much as the people there.
I think since we were media we were
able to. Okay good. But that's
actually kind of crazy.
Especially since I did see someone
being attended to who I presume
had like a heat stroke or something.
Oh yeah I saw that happen at
Disneyland the week prior too.
On Pixar Pier someone hit the
deck. Yeah and fair warning
if you're going when it's this hot out
this is coming out a bit later so I think
hopefully it's better by now.
Some of the houses are hotter on the inside
and I just I feel so
bad for those actors like the Ghostbusters
house which we were excited
for because it's oh it's Ghostbusters frozen empire.
It'll be cold in there.
Right.
It's so sweltering.
That's kind of what I thought too.
Mike Scollins made a joke to that effect.
I was like that is true
at least there'll be there'll be a cooling
effect. Why did we think that?
I don't know that I fully believe that but I
was like oh maybe there'll be a room or two where they have
some sort of like a freezer open. There is
one maze we went through we didn't go
through all of them we tapped out it was just it was too much.
But there was one we went through where it's
this it's on IP it's like
this radioactive zombie
kind of maze.
It's by the mummy ride
I think it's kind of tucked away in a corner but
that room you walk through at one point and
it's a freezer with a bunch of bodies
hanging up and that room is actually cold
so if you're looking for somewhere
to get just a few minutes
of respite.
It's the freezer in the radioactive zombie
maze. You should try to hide like hug a
corpse in there and like hide.
Meanwhile
the evening weather in Orlando
I've been looking is usually
the mid to low 70s.
It's very pleasant.
You check the weather in Orlando every night you know.
I have like eight or ten
cities saved in my weather app.
You stare out at the moon and think about what it looks like
in Orlando every night. Yeah
like a Fievels situation.
I'm like on the windowsill
and you like transport to the
windowsill of the Islands of Adventure
White House.
Their scare zones are under the same roof.
This is a little
validating what you've said
in terms of the heat at least
at the beginning of the season which is a while ago
as listeners hearing this but
you were there up there for the first night.
The second night
Mike and I were set to go.
Tickets were arranged
and I was going to brave
it for the first time because last
last year's haunt cast was the
first that I've participated in anything.
I think what got me over the hump
was that the things that we did were so
stupid that the names
themselves are so dumb.
We did a haunted car wash.
We did Shaqtoberfest.
I was so delighted by
oh even you know what we didn't end up doing an episode
about I went our friend
Joe Quazzala I followed him to the
LA Haunted Hayride in
Griffith Park which has something that he's a big
fan of a zombie lounge singer
named Monte Rivolta.
I watched Monte Rivolta's set.
No real scares beyond that
other than the general
eeriness of just the vibe of Monte
Rivolta.
But anyway all of these things made me like
last year's for sure my favorite
October my favorite like Halloween
season doing the show or not. So I was
a little bit like this time
think I'm ready Mike get me in.
Then it was the night before
the night you were up there and I was like
Mike hate to say it. I don't
know if I can because like I'm
teetering as it is. I'm a scaredy cat.
I was like I think I can make it.
But you add that heat to it.
And I was like too many things.
I'm an adult. I don't need to do this.
So it's been
rescheduled.
And this is maybe
the element of suspense of the
month in general. Will I Scott
do anything.
Was the year enough to reset me
and make me will I find an excuse
that isn't heat. Was that me making
an excuse to not do
it or was it. I mean it was
so horrible. It was horrible.
I have all these questions
too though. I said well when it's
15 degrees what will it be something
else. I don't know. I don't know the answer myself.
I don't know the answer. I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm excited to find out. I'm excited
to see what it is. And listeners
yeah that's something we'll have to wait all month and
check to find out. We at least need to do the and we didn't
get a chance to do this when we went. We're
planning on going again also. But there is
a Chucky lie
where he roasts everyone.
And I want to see it so bad.
You didn't do it. No we did not do it.
Late night with Chucky in
like the DreamWorks theater.
The Kung Fu Panda. It was great.
We interviewed Zachary
Arthur on the red carpet. We've
talked to him before. It was our first time meeting him in person.
He's one of the actors on the Chucky
show. Like he's the lead
on that show. We asked like are you going to go
do that the Chucky live
roast thing. He was like
that's my job. Like I get paid to
have Chucky insult me all day.
There's nothing he can say anymore.
He said too much Chucky at work. I understand.
Yeah. Yeah. Thick skin.
Wow. Wow. So yeah.
We'll see if Chucky will roast Scott.
Yeah. Yeah. If it was Chuck-O it's the whole other
thing. That does
help me. I would like to say
because there's nothing about me going that says that
then I have to do all of the scariest
things. You can just enjoy the ambiance.
Jason and I should take bets on
how long you last.
I'll say the. We'll figure that off.
The houses that we
did. We did the Ghostbusters house.
We did the Universal
Monsters house which we called Oops
All Women because it's all women.
Like it's Bride of Frankenstein.
It's a female descendant of Van Helsing
and they're like road tripping and killing
female monsters. It's cool as hell.
And this
might interest you. Might tip you in favor
of going through that one at least.
I think for the first time ever that
they have a maze on stage
two. Is it twelve?
Where they filmed the original
Frankenstein. Bride of Frankenstein.
A bunch of the old Universal. Which is why they
have the Universal Monsters in there this year.
Which I think is really really cool.
That is cool. That's the big one.
From my tour guide days I remember
that was the first one you could see and it had the most
exciting montage I could play.
Because some stages honestly not a lot
interesting happened in. Yeah.
But that one it's like you're playing the montage and it's
like it's alive. Say hello
to my little friend. Yep.
They have a scar. Roar dinosaur.
T-rex attack. That was
a good one. You get down the hill and then you
hype everybody up with the coolest stage.
Granted you only see a corner of it.
That's the end of that.
I would like to go on stage twelve.
Wow wow interesting.
I won't say it
now but there's a spoiler from Ghostbusters
Maze that I actually am like oh why
did it get spoiled for me. There's a
good spoiler. And I think you
know what it is. I know what it is.
I was like oh that would have been fun. But I won't say
again we have to go. You have to go. I don't want
you. You'll probably go oh yeah okay.
Our favorite was The Weeknd.
And it was our favorite
because this is the second time he's done a house
and the first time he did a house it was also
our favorite that year. It just
visually it's always so different
than everything else. And there's so much
color and the sound is always
incredible. And it was The Maze I got the most
genuinely scared in. I got
caught off guard by so many. There's lots of like
unexpected changes in scale
in that one that I think are really cool.
Uh oh. That's the. Yeah you have to suck me out of it.
I did actually think of this show
because there are certain points where it's like there's
a big thing in a room and I remember
that coming up. You know this thing.
I do know the thing. That's my thing.
That was yours okay. And genuinely scary. No
you've just sucked me out of The Weeknd Maze.
There's a weekend bar that can give you
courage to go on The Weeknd Maze.
I'm all the way in on The Weeknd bar. You can always just ride the
rides because they don't have lines during horror nights.
Yeah that too. Yeah yeah.
Me being there at all counts as
something. You can get into Toad Cafe easily apparently.
We had friends the same night just walk in.
That's a good idea.
I would like to have an okay something
shaped like a Mario thing.
Not for it to be the most
joyless cafeteria
that feels like
it's a disaster situation
and we can get everybody fed at least.
There's an air of panic and stress
in every corner of the room.
Yeah alright well there's a lot to look forward to.
Well thank you
for this preview of it.
And in terms
of the main thing to talk about
I think this is a great thing.
This is a great slice to take.
A slice I didn't even intend for any pun there.
Of like
Universal's history.
Of like the big cred.
I feel like in a horror sense
to the back lot area
in general.
The presence of Norman Bates.
The Bates Motel and the Psycho
House. This is a great thing to like peel off
as its own thing.
Was there anything that particularly
drew you to that as kind of an area
to meditate on? I just think because
like living in LA
you know it's a city where like
LA tends to destroy a lot of its own
history. You know it's almost like
the theme park, the Disney problem where it's like
this is a business
ultimately. And so do
you prioritize the museum
aspect or do you prioritize the
like new and exciting aspect?
And so it's rare I think
for giant set pieces
like that to survive for so
long. That's not just in like
a private collectors
like it's there. Like if you go to the park
it's there for you to enjoy. And during
horror nights if you take the tram
tour you can get up super close.
Which I think is reason enough
to do the tram tour. You walk right alongside
the Bates Motel and you can get
your picture taken with Norman on the steps
of the house. Wow. Yeah.
Absolutely. I got yelled at last
year because I accidentally stepped on the step.
Oh yeah. My husband also I think
got scolded for doing that. It's
tempting. I didn't do it on purpose
also. I just like I don't remember I was trying to get in position
for the photo. Yeah it's Norman. He's
a nice young man. You want to? I just want to take a photo
with a nice young man.
It's very polite. Sure. Buttoned up.
Yeah absolutely
and it's also like it's sort of
I mean plenty of things have
shot there over the
years but it's not the same as
you leave up the back to the future
set and other things
can re-appropriate that
and give it different. Psycho is sort
of psycho. Yeah. It's
too iconic to read. It's clearly the psycho
house. Yes the clock tower
from back to it's like that
has been used so many other times.
Yeah. But the psycho house
if you ever see it in other stuff
it's there to be the psycho house.
I don't know if you saw Maxine
but there's a scene in that where
they specifically drive
up to the house in a golf cart
and they're like they shot psycho
it's just this moment where they're kind of in awe
of this thing and
yeah she sees
an image of Pearl
in the window kind of like Mrs. Bates
at school. Oh I see I see. Another
aspect of the experience that they
leave Mother
up there in the window.
No it's a neat like
it's a cool
like I'm
flashing back to being
a kid and taking the tram tour
and not at a point where I haven't seen
psycho I just know culturally
and from Simpsons parodies what
psychoanima from like I'll never see it.
But I
it's cool that just kind of
two facades
have
an eerie feel that stays
with you
where there is no tech right.
It's not of course King Kong and Earthquake
are going to give you a feeling and scare you
and Jaws is going to jump out at you but
just that like architecture
is scary to drive by.
Yeah it's kind of it is funny
now that I think about it that that still
exists on the tram
tour where as like other
stuff they've added and the
psycho hotel or motel
and house have outlived like
the briefly I remember the
Fast and Furious like the cars
on the kooka arms do you remember?
The gasoline cars.
It outlived the gasoline cars.
Rightfully so.
That shouldn't have lived as long
as it did. Yeah but just the fact that
it has so much more staying power than
stuff where yeah like you said there's tech.
This is just a guy with a
body in a bag and he dumps it
into a trunk. Yes yeah.
And there wasn't always that.
That was a change.
The Norman Bates show that
occurs and that there is a walk around Norman Bates.
The urban legends.
Oh yes that's true.
Well so yeah I think
you know it's been on the tour since
the tour started
like proper tram
tour starts in 64
and which is
psycho 60 correct?
60 yeah. So they
left that up and it was like
it was a perfect you know probably one of
the primary attractions. Yeah it was in a
different spot it's been moved around a
couple times. Yeah that's something I didn't
realize. I didn't know that until I
was doing some homework for this that it's
been packed up and moved around both the
motel and the house. Yeah yeah
which I wonder like it I'd wonder
that before but it's like it'd be weird because you have to also
recreate kind of the grounds because
the house has to be up on the stairs.
The perspective of it from the.
It's hard to move the motel.
The house I can conceive
of moving. Yeah because the house takes
up less space.
And it's a little bit of an illusion.
And it's hollow.
I could feel you and I could just drag that
thing somewhere.
But the motel no way.
No but I guess you just break
the hotel into pieces.
Yeah it's all the hotels
all empty on the inside as well.
Moving houses
used to be more common
especially in Los Angeles people would
buy a different plot of land and move a
house. I think someone did it
a few years ago and
it was like
news. Really?
To move a house you had to put it
on like a giant truck and you
have to shut down roads.
Is it the jerk? There's a whole gag
with the house on the truck
like that. Am I thinking of the right movie
where there's a whole set piece with the house?
I know what you're talking about and I can't remember what it is.
It's not I don't know if you're
thinking of Freddie got fingered.
He moves his father's house around
him to Pakistan.
But I don't think it's
on a big arm.
Kind of fun sequence.
But this is the original
Psycho House and Dates Motel.
Well I don't know that.
That's the question is if they
moved the literal pieces
or not. I actually don't
know that.
It's like a Theseus's ship kind of thing.
I wasn't sure if it
was one of the ones from the sequels
that survived because that was the one
in the short lived one
in Universal Orlando
was technically the house from
Psycho 4.
Very much from Psycho 4. Built there
in order
to have like an arbitrary
it's like
we're opening a movie studio. We got to film something there.
Alright Psycho 4 is in motion.
You're coming down here and they actually
were filming that right after the park
opened. So June 1990
you could go right up to it
and watch. They filmed most of it at night
so it wasn't really a problem.
But I think there were times where they were actually filming
scenes and the regular
paying theme park people could walk pretty close
up to it. And the juxtaposition freaked
me out as a kid in 91
or 92 whenever my family went
because it's like the five hole
play area is here. The Psycho
4 is over there and there's a
giant hard rock cafe.
And I'm like what is going on? What is this?
It's a very chaotic corner.
And also just the way that it like
it's almost like a sadder
it just descends into nothing
back there is what I remember.
The theme park's over and it ends
at a scary house.
Just like sad dusty
planes. There's like majesty
to the one in Hollywood.
The way they presented it. It really
feels important in the way it's
whatever the two things are there.
Do you think the ones here are
both of them are the original buildings.
I know that the motel's
been refurbished.
I think John
Murdy who does the horror nights
he's the creative director. I think he
was involved in a big refurb
of the motel to kind of bring it back
to what it would have looked like
because it's been used
it was used in the
98 remake.
So a friend of mine
his name's Trevor Dow. He said it was fine if I
used his name. He is Norman Bates on
the tram tour. So there's a chance if
you go on the tram tour or if you do the little
meet and greet it's Trevor.
I asked him do you have any cool behind the
scenes stuff and he was
told me that the original
locations and stuff. He said that
in the remake
the motel used to be
like wooden planks.
I think there was a lot of wooden
stuff on the exterior but then it was changed
over to kind of cinder block.
Which is still what it is now.
So I think the motel's a weird
amalgamation of
original material but then also
stuff they put in for this remake.
Oh interesting. Wow.
Because
they've definitely converted it back to the
old vibe for the most part because
it's like
it's the old sign because that
you can so picture from the black and
white. And the 90s one was kind of more
90s one in general was all like kooky
and a lot of Julianne Moore's wearing like dresses
with weird bubbles all over them.
And then if I'm remembering correctly
what they did with the house
is even stranger. They don't even use
the psycho house
in the remake. They built
a like a front
in front of the house.
So it's a different house but it's
concealing the actual
house. It's so bizarre.
They for sure use the
title in front of it but it's the old
house. It's like the
motel's there so you're like
there's the stairs and then so they just
built this weird house. It's a different house.
That's kind of I mean there's nothing
iconic about that house. Maybe if the movie
had been a hit it would have been but it's also kind of
I don't know that could be where
the puppies are being kept in
101 Dalmatians. There's nothing particularly
it doesn't it's not that like
there's no choice in the house like
the scary the creepy skinniness.
It's such a strange almost
meta thing I think because
when you watch the remake everyone's a bizarro
version of the original characters because
everything is so identical and
I think they were just like why not
do that to the house too? Like the
house is almost like a weird
recast. You know what I mean?
Yeah. But framed with
the same framing. It's so bizarre.
I was glad I watched it. It was a very
interesting watch I thought.
And then that resulted in a weird time
where I might have taken the tour
in this time where then they moved
they kept the facade but they moved
it over. So there was a time
right before the movie was going to come out where you
would go by there and there were two psycho houses
original in 98.
Really strange. Bring it back.
Bring it back. That I would
sign off on that for sure.
So very strange. Interesting.
They kept some of the elements of it and they've
refurbished it and that's been the spot
since
mid 80s I think.
I think the current spot is like
80s to present. It moved around
a bunch before that.
You know what? It doesn't need to be
the same. I don't care
that it moved up the hill.
They recreated the vibe perfectly.
It's 100 feet away.
It's still magical to be
again if you do the tram tour to get
that close to it.
I don't know. Just so aware that
this is the stuff they used.
It's so neat. Yeah.
I don't know if they're doing this this year with the
Terra Tram. You get to walk right
up front by the motel too.
There's skis there.
It goes through the parking lot and they have
people popping out of the motel rooms
and stuff. That's cool.
The first time I got to do that I was like whoa wow
that's cool. I almost wished it was more psycho
themed. Yeah that would
be cool. But I don't know if it was just a bunch of
Normans. Who would you have popping out
of each one? In every room.
Twelve Normans.
Wait now your friend
because you were doing a list.
Anything else he told you about
what that experience is
like? Day to day
what a Norman shift is like.
I didn't get any gruesome
details. I just imagine it's a lot
of sitting and waiting.
But I do think that
they wait in
it's the original. It's cabin one
which is apparently the only
usable room in the motel. It's got all the
furniture and it's made up to look like
the room.
I don't know if they used
the interiors
of the
motel for the movie but it is like
made up. I don't think they did. I was
curious about that. I think that might have been on a stage.
I'm like I brought stuff with me.
Wow. I did homework.
You printed things. I did print
things. Yeah yeah yeah. He hasn't
had to like just when you're playing Norman Bates
you don't have to do like a Leto style
yourself acting thing.
He makes a face and he acts scary.
What's funny is like
on that note
my friend who does it and when I was doing
some kind of homework for this I found
someone else on Reddit saying that they
knew someone who played Norman as well and that
it's something where he knew a lot about
the history of the building and I get
the sense that all the guys who play
Norman are like
really love and care about
this building and the history
and are like very attached to it and are just
you know like I don't know what I was expecting
to get from my friend but this is all
just very like oh here's some like genuinely
cool stuff about not
like oh yeah here's what my day
I sit around and it's boring you know it was
like no this is I get to be in this
really cool piece I don't know and it's
it is in a weird way it's very
they're just very nice young
boys who are very respectful
of the history
that they're surrounded by and it just all
feels very appropriate it feels
that just feels to me like when you go
into the whatever the pavilion the room
to see the American Adventure at the American
and Epcot Center yeah all the people
in there are like museum
level history nerds
American nerds and like
you really feel that from almost
everybody at least not necessarily
the people that work at the barbecue kiosk outside
but the people inside that
are showing you around like I bet there's
Sam the Eagle barbecue
enthusiast but there
may be not as diehard as the people
that will explain like these are George W.
Bush's boots and they know everything about the
boots
I like hearing that there are like
Norman enthusiasts yeah they're almost
like docents it feels like
they you know just because they end up
spending so much time in there
what I remember when they start they started the program
when I was still working there I think I started
2006 and I feel like oh seven
or oh eight they started having and I
sometimes you would like if you were because I started
working very seasonally and I think
I may have encountered Norman
for the first time and it was genuinely a surprise
I think maybe nobody told me
that they were doing that yeah and I just had
to react which is not
I did not think it was an actual
I'm so maniac
just out there randomly but I
remember that it was like I recognized
all the people who were doing it and they were all people who were tour
guides and I think like VIP tour guides
and the people who like really cared
about it so like yeah I think something about it
attracts like film historians
like to do that part
and there's one I know I didn't
because I did that job so long ago and I don't
remember his name but I should
say hi at some point but like I will
I end up at the same coffee shop a lot
with one of the Normans
and I remember him being
a nice guy from working there but I more remember
that he was Norman so there's still something for
me where I'm like oh Norman
I better hole up in a corner and what's the
furthest away I can get here
there's this it's an Irving
so he already got a cold foam
cold brew and then he just came over
and said we all go a little mid
sometimes right Scott
so it sounds like I just looked at
the stuff I brought I do think they might have
shot the motel interiors in there
really really oh my god and
my friend said this is I didn't see this anywhere
online so this might be like
cast member knowledge or just a fun little
secret that I couldn't find pictures
of or anything but apparently
Marley Renfro who
was the body double for the shower
scene because she was willing to do
like on screen nudity
she
apparently recently visited she's
the only living cast member
still yeah she's like in her 90s
I think but she came to visit
she apparently booked it
because she had modeled for Playboy
and so it was like oh yeah I'm comfortable
doing it and
she I don't know how recently
she was there but she apparently signed
the shower like her signatures in
the motel and there is a shower
in there wow that's
what makes me think they might have filmed it
right if there's that much stuff yeah
wow wow crazy
that's very that's fascinating yeah
I didn't see that anywhere online this might
just be kind of a cool thing that recently
happened yeah
I also think it's cool
to see this because like
there's all the other horror stuff
like Michael Myers is around
like Psycho hasn't been like
there hasn't been a sequel for many
years it's like a lot at one
point at one point there were a ton I'm just saying
now it almost feels a little more special going
to see it because oh that's that old movie
and now it's like I get to live
it I get to live it here I don't see it everywhere
it's not on billboards it's not like
there's some specialness about it
because of that in my mind
not that I don't think they should do ten sequels to
the Gus Van Sant movie I'm just saying
to me I feel
I want to see a remake of that
with some like additional
scenes that we can keep doing this weird
like you know
copy of a copy of a copy
how far can we degrade
what this movie ends up being
oh yeah and by the if you did it for
the seventh time would it still resemble
the old one or would enough
variances occur that it's
kind of its own movie now yeah like the half
life of it yes yes exactly
yeah it's degrading
somewhat yeah is there
an episode of the Freddie
Highmore Bates Motel TV
show that's just a shot
shot remake of the Gus Van Sant
that would be good yeah psycho
should be there was that too
really there is per your
statement there's been a lot of psycho there's
been a lot okay fine I forgot about the TV
show but not lately but not lately
is what I'm saying I don't feel like a miracle
there's other stuff that like you see the minions
you go well the minions are everywhere all the time
I feel like so I just it feels good
to me I didn't watch the show I'm sorry
I didn't watch the show
some people like the show I remember that now
yeah the
I think you kind of alluded to
I don't this may have inspired
the notion of putting characters
up there because
there was this story
I don't know if it was urban legend or I think it did actually
happen but I believe
that around
1999 that a
tram tour
was attacked by
somebody dressed as mother
and it was
genuinely upsetting because
it's what I was fearing when I went
by like I'm gonna assume that's an employee that is
Norman Bates but in this case
truly nobody knew what it
was and the guide came back
and was freaked and
when they poked around and figured out
what happened it was Jim Carrey
filming
man on the moon
so in his the anarchic
Kaufman spirit
which we know
much about and we're nerved by
much about in that documentary
but fun
I mean that is kind of like living the dream
I feel like there's probably I think there
are some people who have filmed entire
projects and been on the lot
a lot who do not
care and don't want to engage
with but I love hearing
because I loved it as a kid and I did it
as a job the idea
that an actor would be like oh my god
we're on the tram I'm a theme park
attraction let's go make some
madness happen
so that's fun
we got Jason Anthony Gio and I got to do
this because Gio was working on the lot and he took
us behind Amity on the lake
yeah we got a golf cart
and we got to like I mean no one told us we could do this
but we just like reacted as if jaws had
come out and we were surprised
well you and Gio did I just
was smiling and waving at the door
I missed the direction I was going to be nice
and not bring up the fact that Gio told us exactly what to do
and you just did not do it
Gio and I went oh my god and you were just like
Jason act scared
he said scared I think I had
turned around and was distracted because
behind one of the building
facades there was a bunch of
broken office chairs and I was like guys
look it's like an office chair graveyard
back here for some reason
for some reason I was like how did these
office chairs get here there's no office
close by and then
if there's options A and B
to be excited about Jason will always
find option G
yeah I just thought
it was so strange and then we got in
the golf cart and we drove up and
parked behind the Bates motel
yeah yeah and we
there was a Norman
walking around and there was
a VIP trolley
then people walking around it's like
oh we shouldn't
be here like we are just
looky loose
no one cares no one cares
that is the rule if you sneak onto the universal lot
no one cares just act like
you belong there as long as no one catches you sneaking on
no one cares now
if you sneak back to the
lot with the utility
vehicles and the free gas
pumps people will probably
oh my god
this is again the most Jason-y thing
your scheming of how to get free gas
because you have a meeting
as long as it's gas meant for a
four car tram but as long
as they don't have auto shut
on like they sent me as an intern to
go fill up the gas of the
the golf cart
that's why you were terrified
my husband worked on the lot
when we both first moved out
he was a production assistant so we also would
take the golf cart and go all over it
what was he on what did he do
he just worked for like the studios
post department so yeah lots of
running hard drives and
free gas
yeah
they built out
that side it's by the bar
gate where they built all these
additional sound stages and the
restore facade used to be there
we gotta get him free gas
we gotta get
somebody to get us a drive on
maybe it was diesel maybe it was lead I don't know
I just like to imagine the one that you
like you went on to the bar
side like got under
the fence like glugged as much as you can
and spit it out as soon as you got
out of the
well I also god knows what I inhale
a gallon of liquid
when I was a PA I
had to go pick up like hard drives
or paperwork or something once
at these temporary offices
a day after
the King Kong fire and there's
just people in hazmat suits
and the people in the temporary offices
just had fans going in every
direction that was your time to strike
and they were all distracted by the fire
it should have stocked up on gas
they're
I don't know why we
always get excited my husband and I love the fact that
it has its own fire department
that is a fun thing
that's one of the first things you see too you're right before
stage 12 you're on your way down
I don't know why it's so exciting to me just this tiny little
it's like a Richard
scary kind of
fire department you know
that's what proves it's a real city you're like
universal city that's cute but fake
no no no there's a fire department
Disneyland has a fire department
so there is like something to like
even if it was real or not I feel like it wouldn't matter
there's the idea that there's a special one
yeah have you all seen the Trey
Parker Matt Stone video that
they made oh the secret
yes yes yes
your studio and you yes yes yes
the black and white right
it's an old film strip
that with lots of
big cameos in yeah there's like Demi Moore
Steven Spielberg's driving
the tram
Bruce the shark pops out
and he goes ah it's scary
that he kind of just you know
that's right a nonplussed Spielberg
doing that's a great idea
like eating an apple the whole time
it's oh it's so good
he asks questions and then kind of like between bites
what about yeah
it's so I love that thing so much
when it has the it's a great piece of
I mean like great for the studio
stuff but also like that it
has the South Park energy
in the Trey Parker voice so like
say that and which is like I just
went to Casa Bonita and
I listened to that episode and I
I want to go there
so bad you totally sold me
it's so yeah I feel like I may have led
to a wave of people which I'm so
glad about and his voice is part
of the magic of it I it's so cool there's a
permanent spot that has that but
and since we
did that episode I very recently
in tandem with the documentary they have
made it easier to go
reservations are now open to the book I
still can't imagine it's that easy
with the six hundred thousand people
who are trying to do it but there is
a way I signed up for
the Founders Club email
and Evan Susser also
signed up yesterday he said he
did he said he listened to the episode
and he did what you said turn the episode
off and sign up great
so he actually did it in the order you said
because I really didn't want to I
it deserves to not be spoiled
it really like because there are surprises
especially Blackbird's Cave
just don't do not if you haven't heard it
already don't listen to what I said about Blackbird's Cave
it's so fun you might get
rewarded for your promotion with
a second reservation
one of the rarest
theme park things in the country because mine
was a trade with somebody who did
get to go himself because I think he
he was smart and set up a separate
one a month later too
he nailed it so I do
still have my
yeah I have a backup but I don't know when
I'll get to do it but well you got to
get back to LH Gardens and do all this
stuff that was closed
oh what a time never again never again
I just think with stuff like
the universal video that those
guys made I don't know just finding other people
where you're like oh you like this stuff the same
way I do is so exciting
you know because I
think I don't know I mean I guess now there's more
of the idea of like theme park adults or
Disney adults it's more of like a pop
cultural kind of thing but just
I don't know because there's something that is not
I don't know like theme parks are never the thing
that you think people are going to find
a respectable interest to have
it's just not there's nothing
cool about it
and you have to and it's probably
when I was engaging with
the least was kind of like
teen years 20s
because like you need the
currency of cool and cool music
and stuff but if you get past that
I feel like for me it completely lines
up with like meeting my
wife oh I don't have to date anymore all right
well fuck cool I do not
need to care about that
whatsoever but
I think what is great about it is that like
everybody who shares the interest are like such
like
fun bubbly people for the most
part like everybody's like
everybody does like it in the same way which is pretty
like lit up I think it's a
fandom that's
there's like miserable fandoms there's fandoms
where everybody just kind of like reads off a list and you've seen
this okay good
but I find yeah I think the fandom
tends to be pretty like
I went on this thing it was so cool wow
I think the fandom is maturing and when I say maturing
I mean there is more bad
coming it's growing it's been growing
a lot there's a lot more content creators
we're certainly part of that
but then you know I there's so many different
the Rivers of America was going away in Florida
a lot of people started popping up
on my feet and I went oh this feels like you know what
I should be proud of the fandom for growing up
so I see all some bad stuff now
more often yeah that's true
the sign of success Star Wars has been
a fandom for decades now
and there's so many different pockets
there's the resistance there's the first order
there's different types whatever but this I feel
like oh my god it's kind of it's coming into its
own there's so many different
yeah because ten years ago I don't even
know I was I rediscovered all this stuff
I guess in our late
Jason and I when we got started going to Disneyland a lot again
and I was like oh yeah this is cool and it felt
so small at that time
but now it feels like it's a big industry almost
big enough for some to be toxic
but that
shows that's what I'm saying that's
success and that's showing that overall there's
more awareness about it and like Horror Nights
has its own very dedicated
fandom as well especially Orlando's
because Orlando's leans a lot
harder into its own kind of
lore which I'm not super
familiar with because I don't
really I've only been to
Universal Orlando once and it was to do
Horror Nights specifically
but they have like
their park icons
like every year there's a Horror Nights
icon and often they're returning
characters and they're all kind of
interconnected and related
and there's this whole like you scratch the surface
and there's so much
lore we did a podcast episode
on it once and got so much
stuff wrong and people were
sad and I
realized then like oh wow this is
really really important to some
people I get it you know
but there's not a lot of
the company
is starting to
not only build
out the lore but keep a record of it
because there's it's mostly
fan created
like when we did the
episode about when Horror
Nights was at Islands of Adventure
and it's like oh yeah the Marvel
Island was taken over by Carnage and the
villains like
there was so little
video and photos and stuff
you're saying the fans sort of are like
they're the archive yeah yeah they were
the ones that kind of kept it going when it wasn't
so like on the minds of everybody
yeah and they're I
feel like Horror Nights in Orlando
this year there's a lot more original
their original houses are very popular
down there yeah Orlando does
a lot more original stuff versus
and like oh this house was a
scare zone it was very well received
so it got upgraded or this
is a this house is
a sequel to the house from three
years ago like it's
really interesting I've seen people say
we have to do an episode on those and I feel
intimidated honestly it's intimidating
it feels like not this year not this year I'm not ready
not this year there's so many icons
yes and to what you were talking
about it is hard to get a sense
of the kind of correct
like the canon and timeline
of stuff because so much of it's just fan
documented and you'll find stuff that like
contradicts itself and it's like I don't know
you know I feel like I haven't been
part of it this whole time so as an outsider
trying to get a perspective on like what this
kind of running story is it's so hard
yeah if you haven't been there
for any of it so you can't catalog like
oh yeah I remember that was the vibe of 07
or like they have the opening ceremony where
it's scripted and there's stuff that happens
and you know yeah trying to find video
of that that's this is like a ten
year project for us we'll be ready
in ten years yeah
yeah but we'll be yeah ten years it'll take
to find everything you can always do an episode
on the weird like one off
houses like we spent a lot of time
on that universal the Orlando
Horror Nights episode talking about the Undertaker
themed house that we're kind of
obsessed with yes but
it's great because the wrestler
the Undertaker yes it was a WW
Undertaker WWF
well an Undertaker could be anything
I just want to make sure
about the profession in general
what do you mean
I'm also telling the list
you know a working man
his name is Mark
Calloway
I didn't know that
but what's great is I think
I think at that point in time
Undertaker was in his American
badass era so all the
stuff he's got the like American
flag bandana on and
there's a video of him going through the house
where he's still it's all you know he's
keeping kayfabe and is like yeah
I remember when that happened and
you know it's it's it's
just goes through it like it is a
diorama of things that actually happened
in his real life yes
because it's all these different eras yes
and he's like commenting on each scare actor
and it's like the yeah
my brother in hell
that's forever ago yeah
he's lazily committing to the bit in that
because yes he he had an
era and I'm this is I don't
less well known he had an era where he just wore
like jeans and rode a motorcycle
and had a bandana and he wasn't
undead anymore and it was his
American badass era and
he came out to either Olympus gets rolling
or Kid Rocks American badass
and it was
not the best time
to be an undertaker fan
people were like yeah but we like it
when he comes out of like a coffin and stuff
we like the farm like the nonsense we like it when it
takes him 10 minutes to walk to the
ring yeah and there are druids when
he comes to the entrance and the song
and the music whatever so yes that that
is a funny I don't know what you mean when I was
talking about the 2000s and needing to be
feeling needing to be cool
more that's what I meant I meant I was listening
to American badass all the time yeah yeah yeah yeah
the coolest song
very cool
still cool honestly
or Ball with the Ball you know the
film director Frederick Durst his
previous project
Ball with the Ball that was Kid Rock
I'm sorry to tell you my man oh that was fuck
new metal and
oh man
Kid Rock was new metal
yeah Kid Rock's so weird
I guess you could count on
new metal I don't know
I just get that arrow
rap rock confused
yeah you're right there's no metal in it
per se yeah yeah
I never got into it cause that's what my
pulleys listened to
back in the late 90s that's our punch
and music and
America that's the sound of them punching you
American badass
well the pulleys had
rock and stone cold t-shirts
at that point that's probably why I
never engaged with wrestling then yeah
I didn't realize it was a nerdy thing
yeah again
the fandom matures you know
the fandom has higher expectations
there was nerdy characters to like
the ones I like mankind was my guy
I was gonna say Mick Foley
is like for the nerds for sure
he's one of the nicest people
ever by the way he does the horror convention
circuit so at this point we've done
a few shows with him and he's
so sweet like he's just
very jolly and a legit theme park
nerd yes and always been
there's like him and the hearty boys in Islands of Adventure
photos from 1999
that's really
good wow wow
can I bring up an old Orlando thing but I mean
I think I said most of what I was gonna
say about Psycho 4 but then
that when that house was still
up there and
the motel I don't think that you could
walk through it for mazes
in the way
we do in Hollywood but you could
apparently I just watched a video
that had a brief clip of a show
where it's the Bates Motel
and in front of it
hopping around our
Beetlejuice and the Blues brothers
together so I would
like to know the full context
the dense narrative
like in the front yard
they're just in the
middle of the hotel courtyard
in front of room 6
and hopping I know that's all I know
is the two second clip but boy
it spoke to me
the other fact about
Psycho 4 per things
we've talked about before directed by
Mick Garris
I'm sure you know Mick
what jumped out at me
is that Mick Garris is the
writer and director of Fuzz Bucket
one of the worst things
we've ever watched for the show
this was when Disney Plus came out
and there was a question of like
how deep do they go
what's the weirdest thing on Disney Plus
the weirdest thing may have been Fuzz Bucket
this awful little creature
it was so unpleasant
this is the first time I've heard of Fuzz Bucket
to be honest
I do want to see what it looks like
a picture
we can get a reaction on that and then the kind of thing
he says
it might be a ring situation
where like don't go out
be careful
I'm trying to find the biggest photo
what's Mick Garris
he wrote Hocus Pocus
he did the
Shining miniseries
with Steven Weber
and I'm trying to think what else
he's just one of like horror's elder
statesmen like he's always at horror
events he's very kind soft spoken
and has very long silver hair
like he just he's got kind of a Gandalf
type wizardy presence
where he's very wise
we know him at this point
I'm always still kind of intimidated
by him even though he's very gentle
you gotta ask him about
Fuzz Bucket
I genuinely will next time
you really picked the worst one
you brought that up in such close up on your laptop
he's so happy
he's like so happy
and so zoomed in in that picture
and then it's
like the copy of the copy psycho premise
I always forget what the thing
now in my head the weird thing that he says
is like hey let's get wet
party boy
it's not like it's wet but we thought
it is party boy
I've just searched for my old notes about
Fuzz Bucket to see if I can figure it out
it's not this but I also feel like it's hang loose
party boy or something like that
but I don't think it's hang loose either
I guess it's just how we doing party boy
we would have been right about party boy
because I think in the
episode on this I think we were debating
like it sounds like party boy
but that's kind of a weird thing for this creature
to say cause it's not like in like
ET or something hears something they're repeating
it's just like this guy's calling this kid party boy
which isn't even a phrase
like a familiar phrase
I really think his vocabulary as a writer
is kind of bizarre cause in Hocus Pocus
there's like Yabos
where he's there
I don't know
I'm learning some things
Yabos is some weird
that's something Thora Birch says
it's almost like in Back to the Future 2
when there's all these future
slang terms that aren't real
and that's how a Yabos is like jerk or something
to a kid
I think it's slang for
I thought it was slang for boobs
oh
I thought she was calling them
jerks like a bunch of Yabos
oh did you see her Yabos
oh right weird
oh there he is again
let's get one more photo of Fuzzbucket
he's giving a little like over the shoulder
oh yeah he has a
high
he's mischievous in this
he apparently also says according to my notes
you love Fuzzbucket give smooch
I wasn't expecting that picture to
scroll down I didn't know there was like
a full body
he's got the tail going
we're kicking off a season of Frights Right
this is some of the scariest images
we'll see all month long
he's a contemporary of like Mack and Me
yeah they'd be friends
little guys era
like pre
pre or around the time of Harry
and the Hendersons
but before
Warriors of Virtue
that's that movie right
which movie is that
this is weird 1996 bomb
or 97
Warriors of Virtue were a bunch of
like weird like wolf
or bunny they were like the Ninja
Turtles but what if they were like rabbits
or something nobody's ever
seen like it sounds like
like a Christian
cartoon show or something
you're not allowed to watch the satanic
cartoons but you can watch Warriors of Virtue
it may have been and I just wasn't
clued into that but like
are they kangaroos
we're in the Zubli Zoo zone
we're in a frightening zone here
did we, forgive me guys
did we talk about Michael Eisner
and Fuzzbucket on that episode
we have to right
I am 110% positive
though I don't remember what he
well he did an intro for it
and Fuzzbucket is in the video with him
oh my goodness
and Mickey's there too
and Mickey, Fuzzbucket and Michael Eisner
were all together
next time I see Mick
I'm gonna ask about this
I didn't know him that well so he's gonna be like
why were you even thinking of him
okay
it's not incorrect to say
well there's been a new, cause at Disney Plus
there's a new cult for Fuzzbucket
even if that cult is only 10 people
and they were scared of the movie
we can get back to the like little guys
era
whether it's like one little guy
or like a bunch of little guys, like critters
you know, or ghoulies
there was a thread recently online
I should find it
of all the different countries
ET rip-offs
and it was unbelievable
because they all had different takes on the material
and they all had different budget levels
so some of them were just
the scariest, cheapest looking things
and then some of them were the worst, scariest things
like oh they got some money to do this
but there were multiple countries that did
rip-off ETs
I should find it, I sent this to GEO the other day
I'll find it, I'll find it
do you have something that you've stumbled across
in the years of doing your podcast
that's like
nope, no fondness for this
scared of this, don't like this creature
not really
no Fuzzbuck, nobody
no, I genuinely
I just, no, I can't think of
anything that I'm like super repulsed by
I'm sure if anyone is
listening that also listens to our show
you're probably yelling an example at me
okay, well wait
where do you stand on Art the Clown?
where do you stand on the Terrifier?
David Howard Thornton is a very nice man
it's a weird thing because
horror is tiny
and we all kind of know each other
because we end up doing the convention circus together
so the Terrifier team is like
the nicest, most normal people
and he's a professionally trained mime
he's like just a very
he's super sweet
and I have an Art the Clown
story
the first time my parents
ever came to a horror convention
to help us table and kind of just
see what the horror scene
is like
we were tabling next to David
who plays art and the rest of the
Terrifier crew from like Terrifier 1
and they were doing
an in costume
photo op where people could
take pictures with him all dressed up
and that
same morning my parents brought in
like doughnuts and coffee
and they were, you know, they
see him in costume and they're like hey we knew you were
doing your big photo shoot so we brought you
breakfast and he's being
I'm just watching him being so sweet to
my parents, they've never seen
this movie and I'm telling them
I was like do not under any
I'm like I'm not letting you watch it
that nice girl you were talking
to, Catherine, yeah she gets sawed in half
like the long way upside down
and you don't want to see it
we want to watch your friends movie
that's the thing is like for my parents
their image of art is just this
nice, he's like an actual nice
clown
they're sweet
the Terrifier movies are interesting
the first one I don't like
because I think
it's just kind of mean, like it's a mean
I don't know if any of you have seen it
it's a lot, yeah, yeah
it's just kind of a mean movie
and it is
the director Damian is he's an
effects guy so it is
it is like an effects showcase
so if that's what you're looking for
you'll like it kind of thing
it's very intense gore, the second one
I think is a lot of fun
it's extremely graphic
it is still kind of an
effects showcase
but there is more of a story in this
one and there's some interesting like
almost supernatural stuff going on
and I just
art's fun you know
he's just having so much fun doing the most
fucked up shit you've ever
seen that I can't help but like
it I'm also so desensitized
at this point this is
we go back and forth I feel like every
Halloween season where like
we were scared little boys
and scared young men and then scared
adults so we like
micro dose horror and stuff
but the convention
the small
close-knit community in the convention
world coming like
as fans of comic books and
professional wrestling is so familiar
to me
it's so recognizable where it's
like I have a lot of respect for horror
I see the craft I see the
community but I am
very easily startled
so it's like having okay I did
Baba Duke working up
to a pinhead
and it follows like piecing
myself starting with
I saw the TV glow gonna
do that next cause that just
looks more spooky than scary
and psychologically
taught or whatever
yeah that's more like existentially
scary I think yeah I can handle
that more than like a simple
jump scare cause I'm
a fool I'm very easily
like putting
hands in front of my head
I'm a fool
yeah no it's a I also
for years of course was just like Gremlins
I was like this I've said this a hundred times in the show
this is a snuff film that I will never see
was the thought I had as a child
I was terrified of Gremlins as a kid
the ultimate little guys
and then especially two obviously I'm just
like this is a Looney Tunes cartoon
was made to be a Looney Tunes cartoon basically
but it is so it's like
oh it's like going to a comic book convention
when I was 12
it's like they were right next to each other the comics
and the horror stuff and I was just like this is for me
this is not and you're like actually they're the same thing
it's just like sometimes there's like a gross
cut on the movie
or like in the comics or whatever like it's gross
yeah I was a very easily
frightened kid like I did not like
scary movies growing up I think getting
into scary movies it was kind of a
it was a weird like shift
where I was like oh I
you know working my way up through like
more and more intense scares
and stuff and kind of learning to appreciate them
I found personally like I don't know
empowering in a way where it was like oh
I can like deal with this and I
can appreciate this and I've come to really love
it for that reason it's a reason a lot of people
are drawn to it is it's like
you know kind of pushing yourself
to see what you can handle and there's
always the you can always turn it
off you know this is what
when Scott and I go to this
this is what I will tell him that he needs to do like three
mazes for it to almost like
get his brain reset to it
and feel the accomplishment versus
just the terror or shock of it
because that's what it took
my wife to do and that's what it took me
to do like two or three and then you
go okay the scare actor is
not going to kill me and then you
can kind of you get you're still like jumpy
but you get a little calmer and then you do start
to feel good about yourself
in a way you're like wow look at me look at
this little boy look what he's up to
now and it does you do feel
like a sense of accomplishment
and I feel like it is
like a theme park ride thing like I've
heard Tony Baxter talk about splash mountain
he wanted it to feel like an accomplishment
for kids so you make it
scary going up because they really feel like
they've overcome something and it works
that way in your 40s walking
through a dark house
with a bunch of people yelling at you
like it's the kind of the same thing like and I
guess maybe because it took me so long to do something
like a haunted house it really I'll never
I'll never lose that like little
look at me how about it
I'm doing it
you wanted to be a snooty little boy
I did I did want to be
it took me forever to want to actually
go to horror nights because at a certain point
I was like okay I'm good with horror movies
I love them at this point it's my job but I'm
still I have that mental
wall where I'm like I'm scared of
people and like loud noises
in real life like people jumping out at me took me
along and then yeah once I just
did a bunch it was like oh you get a
sense of like the rhythm of them
like you know what they're going to be
essentially describe that yeah
the rhythm like that you know
how often it's going to happen you know
you see it like because especially horror
nights they're running so many people through those mazes
you often see the people in front
of you get the scare you see the people behind you
get the scare yeah and you also then start
to notice stuff as well okay
that's obviously like you
you after a while then will get impressed
when they get you and
then you will I do feel a sense of
like oh wow I didn't see that coming
I have a weird I'll instinctively
just clap
kind of a scared clap
oh cool great so you do see
you start judging it based on like you tricked
you fooled me I'm a little
know it all I thought that that's
and knowing a lot of people who like are really
passionate about haunts everyone wants it
to be fun you know there's
oh yeah you know it's
it's all fun no one's trying to
actually traumatize you
except for that one haunted I don't know
if you guys are familiar with this that like McCamey
Manor that they just oh yeah
that like extreme haunt that
now fortunately
does not exist I think because they got
sued into oblivion oh my god
this was oh boy McCamey Manor is like
the nasty side of like the haunt
kind of oh really thing
yeah it was it was a thing
where it was like one of those
like immersive
haunts where they can touch you and stuff
yeah and this was supposed
to be like the extreme one
where the whole point was like we don't let you
have a safe word kind of thing
oh I guess maybe I don't know this stuff
oh and this year it's grimy
Russ McCamey some very bad
bad news ones
okay yeah this is terrible
to see this is in Alabama
and Tennessee yes and it's a shame
because he
really makes it hard
for like other people who do the
immersive haunts where again
they're allowed to touch you and stuff but
you sign waivers up the ass
for those and those are like you get a safe
word and that's the whole point is
it can end anytime you want it to
and I feel the frustration on
you know those people's parts where it's like
people think that that's
what this is where it's like us torturing
you and kind of enjoy but it's like
no that's you know
yeah and it sucks that that
because that one was so sensational
and bizarre and
that was the one that kind of got the
reputation as you know
what these things are like when that's just not
this reputation is what I still
think just the
the insidious maze is going
to be yes the lipstick
demon just touching you
yeah there's no touching
she's going to actually take my fingernails
off that's what their waiver said
that it might you might have your fingernails
removed you might get a tattoo
and you might have your teeth
extracted yeah no no
no no no
no I don't care for that it is funny now
that you know we're saying this because like one of the first
things the first year or two of me doing this I went
to Zombie Joe's the local
horror theater immersive
different they put on different productions with Eva Anderson
and it was we went in two at a time
for this one haunt that was like a dark
ride where we got in a little
vehicle and they pushed us around
and then went into a room full of
a couple naked people but
that's the scare for you well yeah I
didn't care for that please
but we signed we signed it we signed a thing
that was like yeah they can touch you and I was like
that's not going to be crazy right and it was
not but thinking about it back to it now
because the last
room we get we got thrown in a room and then all
the performers like basically kind of come
up behind you and then on the sides and
there's like a man in a devil mask and he's like
sort of I just remember he's like stroking
Eva's face and then we just are like more
and more surrounded by all these people
but there was something by at that point
that I wasn't so worried about getting
killed but now that you're saying like
I guess I did sign a waiver I guess
I could have had a tooth removed
or like this is how you get this to stop
kind of thing it was pretty short
I think it was like six to eight
minutes I did what Jason Waller did
and Landon did it
I think they went together now to think about it
but I remember two would go in at a time and it would
be eight minutes but there was some paperwork
before the paperwork
said no safe words the paperwork I guess paperwork
said no safe words so I think I think they were they were
like this is too short to even have it you just
got to finish it out yeah wasn't
that one in North Hollywood
yeah it's still that that's always where they've had
shows and stuff so like there
is a karaoke bar and a house
of pies down the block like I feel
like that maybe takes out some of the
like really big fear
you don't think you can get a tooth removed in a building near
Idelauer the big barrel
the barrel yeah you can get a tooth
pulled out of with the pliers
yeah it doesn't stop anybody from taking
your teeth out yeah you're just
trying to get through and you're like oh I can go to the new
Randy's Donuts location
and it's still open
but if you're all your teeth are gone Randy's not going to be too
fun for you well but if you get a raised
one you can at least gum it
he's right about that
lucky you never give up spirit of Jason
I can just gum
the previous tenant ate salt fish and chips
was a little more
unreliable for eating
a little more reliable
texture wise
yeah so anyway
no one's going to touch you
no one's going to touch you on purpose
sometimes it happens on accident
and you can tell the
performers like you know they flinch a little bit
like oh shit you know
I saw something
this year the day we went that
I thought actually was very cute
there are these giant stilt
performers that are like big crows
they have light up red eyes and they're
really cool looking I saw
a woman holding up her hand
like flat and I saw the
crow pretending
to eat out of her palm
and I just thought it was so cute
it was just like oh giving him bird seed
that's nice
I believe there's a baby
crow this year too
I don't know maybe that was added
I think the giant stilt walker
there might be a nest with a baby
yeah there's a nest with
like an animatronic kind of little baby
crow in there I did see one of the big
crows proudly showing
off the little baby
that's very cute
I can't find this thread of fake ETs but I
there's one like Nuki
Nuki I know Nuki
I'm familiar with Nuki
I'm scared of Nuki
yeah I don't like Nuki off the bat
maybe I would if I saw the movie
squirm and all these guys
let me go back to Hitchcock
do you remember what age you all were
when you first saw Psycho?
probably film school
yeah I might have been
like college
the first Hitchcock I ever saw was the birds
it scared the shit out of me
I loved it
I
again we were a big Hitchcock
family and
Nickelodeon and Nick at Nights
set it up so Saturday nights
it's Nick are you afraid the Darkwood era
Alfred Hitchcock presents
will be right after it so I would see
that and then down at Universal
they hit the Hitchcock show
in Florida so we're like okay
let's rent some of these movies
so we rent it Psycho
and the shower scene
scared me so much
from then on any time I would take
a bath or shower I would lock
the door which is probably
not great as like a clumsy
eleven or twelve year old
to lock yourself out of the bathroom
the faucet broke
and shot up my butt
tell me we can't we can't
but yeah
that scare like
until basically
going to college and shared dorm
bathroom
I was like oh I can't lock the bathroom
oh no you had to get over it
it's scary
the sound too especially
is so effective
I think there's like the story where
they're stabbing like cantaloupes
and stuff to make that kind of
well if we want
some of the real intel about some of these
things I'm going to bust out a document
a sacred document that I don't think I brought out for a long time
this is
the actual official
universal studio
guide manual
the sacred Jedi
text
I'm not letting these burn up
yeah how about this so this is
not only the real script
at least at the time of how you're
supposed to take people through it but then
there's like you have a bunch of stall
material you have the if you were
to get stuck up there how would you
and I you know you were talking earlier
about like your friend cares about the history
of it I was reading all I'm like
I don't think I got stuck up there in any
it's not a place if you know the flow of the
tour you're not getting stuck up there yeah there's not like
an intersection or anything
no there'd be nothing to wait for
where you get stuck is when you're waiting for like
oh we're trying to get into earthquake
but you know the other trams aren't
through it all the way so there's no
you would never get stuck but I feel like the people
put this together love the
movie so much that they're like
we'll give them eight different big
paragraphs they can read because I want
to write it I I enjoy writing
it so much it's it's fine I
think that okay because I think the cantaloupe thing
is mentioned the sound you hear in the
scene was created by knife being plunged into a helpless
cassava melon oh cassava
now we have the type even how about that
and Hitchcock himself felled the knife
for some of the close ups I didn't know that
what chocolate syrup
was the blood oh they love saying
that's a universal classic
black and white so it was a chocolate syrup
I didn't know it was
not Anthony Perkins
that was if I didn't realize till
I don't think I must have not read this at the time
I just not in the entire
scene it's not him he was in New York
doing a play okay not him at all
because it took days and days to film
why seven days of filming and
over 70 different cuts him doing
that play is why at the end of Psycho
when he screams he doesn't make any noise
and originally it was a
okay pretend you're screaming
we'll dub it later and apparently
just in the edit they're like it's kind of
creepy that he doesn't make any sounds
so they just whoa
he was saving his voice for that
Broadway stuff he was doing oh that's cool wow
wow do you have anything else
jumped out of here
boy so many
so many oh my you're not yeah lots of
yeah this is the most like
this is just a messy
by the way
Mike you were referring to this
syndrome on the show of like not this year
not this year not ready I've punted
the tram tour so many times
and again I will say not
this year not ready
I'm really glad we've peeled off this
aspect of it but I'm I don't
even wanna I you don't want
to commit to next year I don't want to commit to next
year but I've I really have thought about
the tram tour and and like
I mean because I think it's like a month long event
is what I've got away I think it'll
it can work
we were talking about at the very
beginning of 2020
of like maybe in a few months
and then we're waylaid by
a worldwide pandemic and
you and Aaron had a child yes
yeah there's always stuff so
so again I will
say not this year not this year but
I would I would love to figure it out for next
year so this hopefully this this document
is getting some play and I can just read
from the from the thing which I
like to do because
this actually brings up an interesting aspect
that's no longer true of the
Bates Motel on the tour but that
there's this hard pivot
because for a long time they left
up some of the Whoville
sets from the Jim Carrey
Grinch oh yeah during Grinchmas
you get a little song and dance
you get yes sometimes there were both of
these things sometimes you would pull up get
a little song and dance something else I didn't
know about until it was happening in front of me
and like what I was in the
middle of a sentence and then like we welcome
you oh okay I better shut up
and then you around the corner and then Norman
Bates comes out like that's the live entertainment
zone yeah the tour
up there but also for a
long time you'd be looking at the Bates Motel
and then there's like big
crazy curvy thing
of my bobs back there which
sort of take away the scariness although
except those were getting real decrepit too
yeah Derby and Whoville
I remember they were very sun faded
by the end yeah
cracking apart
but you add to
they're like well we gotta help people transition
because that's a tough like
how do you swing from that to from Whoville
the residents of Whoville had to put up with
a lot more than a Grinch out here on the back
lot they lived right next door to Norman Bates
on your right are two of the most
famous and then like little jokes you could do
anyone feel like taking a break maybe grabbing
a shower
which is that's the only time doing that job
you're allowed to ask the guests
if they want to take a shower
any other setting you would
and should be fired at that point too
like years in like how many
people remember that there's a shower scene in Psycho
I mean a lot but like is it
60%
I want to give people credit and say
that it's like because has not the Psycho
has not Psycho in the shower scene
has not become like one of that like
that's one of the famous scenes anyone knows
yeah yeah
it exists now as one of the
only movies the way like time
fades away all these bands are gone
Flattens history yeah yeah
I think that's one of the ones that's left
do we think that it's a deserved thing
that Psycho is like the one
I think so from like a horror
perspective especially it changed
so much when you look at
what horror was like before and
after it's crazy I mean I took a class
in college that was like the horror film
1960 so Psycho
to present because it was such
a big change
in terms of like what he showed
what he implied the subject matter
everything I think totally and the fact
that it just made America go
kind of crazy especially
the fact that it has become
something you can watch with your family
is so weird
when you think about
the way that movie was received
when it was released it genuinely
was very controversial
oh and promote it yeah just like
don't learn anything about it
yes he wouldn't let you in
you can't come in after it starts
that stuff
that has a bit like
this is like the beginning of
spoilers and potential spoilers
I just recently I was in
Tampa for a horror convention
and my husband and I took a tour of the Tampa
Theater which is a beautiful old
like like a movie pad like a proper movie
palace it's beautiful and
I learned on that tour that
pre Psycho
specifically it was
common to like because movies
would play almost in like a loop all
day so you could like just show up
halfway through one and sit through it
and then see the first half like that wasn't
uncommon and
the reason that we have like
you know you get to a movie
on time is because of Psycho
and Hitchcock specifically
telling exhibitors like you cannot
let people in right halfway
through because it's just going to ruin
they would just ambiently play
like the Disneyland
silent movie theater
I could be wrong but my
from what I remember of that tour it was
like yeah you buy your ticket price and you
kind of you just want to say yeah
it is almost like the
like a theme park style or it's just
playing a loop of something
I've never heard that
that's really cool wow geez
this is all mega history
my other
like weird little
kid I guess pre teen
kind of Anthony Perkins memory
do any of you know about the book or
film on the beach
yeah I think you told me about it
yeah so this is a book
like
the book Psycho it was a best seller
and then it became a movie
it is a book
about there is a nuclear war
and the surviving
remnants of humanity are
left down in Australia
and they
know their time the clock is
ticking because the nuclear winds the
nuclear winter is coming
and I read
this book in ninth grade
I really enjoyed it I forget why
we read it in ninth grade I
think we were doing like suspense
and genre stuff because we read
and then there were none as well
but the movie
version stars Anthony
Perkins and I remember
being so excited
when the teacher told
oh this movie
it's an old movie it's black and white it stars
Anthony Perkins and I was like
he's Norman Bates
guys did you hear that
no one else gave a shit
absolutely no one else
gave a shit about this
likely more interested
in Limp Bizkit and
American Badass Undertaker
so this is like 1999?
99 2000 and I was just
they're the fools
I liked Anthony Perkins in
1999 and Mankind
I liked all of the different
I knew all the lyrics that Limp Bizkit
breaks stuff
yeah doesn't Mankind also like
love his mom isn't that a thing?
I forget if that's part of his character
initially Mankind was a very
Mrs Foley's baby boy
that's right Mrs Foley's baby boy
Mrs Bates baby boy
initially the Mankind character was a very tortured
pulling his hair out hitting himself
he lived in the boiler room
and he had a feud with Undertaker
but then I think Mick himself talks about
how Mankind turned from that into a
human muppet of like kind of a
silly guy with a funny mask
he had a big like dress shirt untucked
and he had a sock
Mr sock
his finishing move was the mandible claw
and he had like this kind of leather strap around
and he'd shove it in somebody's mouth
and put like some sort of pressure
like the idea was a pressure point on your tongue or something
and just knock you out or whatever
and then that turned into he put a sock
with a smiley face on his hand
and put it in somebody's mouth
and it was Mr Socko
and they sold Mr Sockos
like sweatpants he was wearing around that time
we have an autograph of Mr Socko
that is very impressive
very cool
I forgot the other more recent
Anthony Perkins fact his son
Oz Perkins
director of Long Legs
the recent film Long Legs
Long Legs is definitely
like his best
I love Long Legs
I'm excited he's got another movie coming out
that's a Stephen King adaptation called Monkey
really looking forward to
yeah we got to
this was very cool and is
humble bragging I apologize
we got to see Long Legs
very early the Neon
the studio contacted my husband
and I were like hey we want
you two to see this first
we were like yes
yeah hell yeah
and they were like hey pick a theater we'll set up a screening
we get there and Oz is there
Oz came there to meet us and tell us
about his movie and he was super cool
and afterwards it then hit
me like that's Anthony Perkins son
you know what I mean it was just a weird like
and he looks so much like his dad
and then I also thought he was
illegally bought
pretty good
that's a fascinating filmography
for sure
I think it's a cool like he's really
like you know I think it's
cool that he's really made a name for himself
as a filmmaker and then
the afterthought is oh yeah he's
Anthony Perkins
that's the dream yeah
he's like really transcended
that kind of you know to where it becomes
trivia about him like he's also
related to so and so
similar in the horror genre
the very successful writer
Joe Hill is
Stephen King's son
okay what has he written I'm sorry
The Black Phone
oh yeah yeah The Black Phone
I'm wondering about all
the kids today yes
he is Norman
in Psycho 2
he's young Norman yeah wow
Psycho 4 that's the
ET what's that actor's name
Henry Thomas
do you have I'm fascinated
by this because like I feel like it's
Quentin Tarantino or something interviewer he
was like Psycho 2 is better than Psycho 1
do you have any what's your like most
controversial takes
on movies in this in this
in this vein of like a take
like Psycho 2 better than one
which is hilarious oh boy I like
Psycho 2 uh like
like horror in general
I mean if anything in general
but is it one where you're like you know what like Jaws
5 is actually the best
I genuinely unironically
like Human Centipede
I think it's really good okay
I am a little scared to watch that one too
I've done Human Centipede
it's so insane
it's almost like it's just this other
it does the same thing
that I love about
Texas Chainsaw Massacre where your
memory of it is that you
saw so much stuff
that you didn't see because
it's like
filmed to where it's
I don't know I just think it's they're both very
clever in like the way that they obscure
things and hide and it makes
it makes you fill in all the
gross stuff but then there's the Human
Centipede sequels that are like fuck it we're just gonna show
you we're gonna do what you thought the
first movie was and that's
more process let's see how
I haven't seen the other ones do you find
out too much about the digestive
situation
you know it's
yeah it's more about like
it's a series of like just shocking
yeah listen also
isn't the surgeon who I think
is fantastic I mean I'll go
back and just like less the like
true horror of it and more just watch him like
explain the situation
what I'm doing but then doesn't buy
buy a couple in isn't it like
yeehaw I'm the sheriff now
same guy but he's
in a cowboy hat
there's like the big there's like I think the third
one is like it's a giant prison complex
I don't know
I don't really mess with the Human Centipede
do you think there
if you were imagining like I guess
it could be any horror movie like a Human Centipede maze
at Horror Nights
something like
would that be something that makes sense
or is there's another movie that you would be
like oh I'd love to walk through
I think a Suspiria maze would be really
cool just cause of all the colors
and stuff the problem is like
so many movies that I think oh this would be a cool
maze you realize how
kind of like we were talking about with a
psycho themed walkthrough of the hotel
it's like well you just have like
a bunch of Norman Bates
what is that you know
how do you have like constant stuff instead of when
a lot of movies are like building up to one big scare
yeah where there's one villain
or like one kind of set piece
it's like well how do you
like something like Ghostbusters works
well cause there's all kinds of
creepy crawlies
I guess it's more at Knott's
at Scary Farm there is I forget which maze
I feel like there was one maze where there weren't
a lot of jump scares and I couldn't
tell if it was because everybody was on their break
that happens sometimes
if you catch a maze at the wrong
time like we went through
there was we walked into a room and it was
clearly supposed to be something
happening and it was just kind of empty
it happens when does it happen
well
Scott just look for
some mazes they move people in
and out in black cloaks
so if I hang out at the side
I see a lot of cloaks go by
if you look for the shift change
if you can hear the dinner bell ring
that's when everybody has to go eat dinner
if I can smell fajitas
a couple hundred feet away
that's why I'm banned from horror nights
when I hear the dinner bell I just start heading
these are employees only sir stop it
that was the best the one time
we were talking to people
at Knott's Berry Farm
and like
we're back you know
backstage and just walking by
a tent of people in the makeup eating
their lunch like eating their like
it's like it's the magic
of comic con where you'll see the Flash
villain Captain Cold going to the bathroom
yeah yeah and it's like that is what
I love about comic con that was a
legitimate startling moment we were in an
office building I went to go to the bathroom
you got scared you got freaked yeah a werewolf
came out and he went oh excuse me
you went ah you like made a noise
I did make a noise and he
like held the door for me he was just a guy
using the bathroom before he went back to work
just a guy just a guy just a werewolf
well that's what I
that's why I was scared
just half a guy my husband and I just did a
set visit for something I can't say what
it is yet just in case but we
were at Crafty
and the
monster the thing
in this movie his
stunt double who was also fully
in the full get up walked up next to me was
also getting coffee and I was like this is
this is like the studio lot experience
that you want you know what I mean
like a monster on break was so
exciting yes casual monster
so exciting yes yes well what we were saying
that you go onto the lot and like nobody's around
and you can't it just makes it cool that you can
just hang out on Amity then but like
I want
facades to be wheeled by
yeah it's like the end of Peewee's Big Adventure
yeah yeah I want a bunch of showgirls
I know there hasn't been a movie made
with a bunch of showgirls in decades
but yeah
that's the dream is they're making a
radically different movie of every genre
in all ten of these stages
I know yeah that would be really
I was trying to think like yeah they're using the
flood scene
for something and they're shooting
what is the technical term
for the flood the flash flood
that's in Big Fat Liar
yes it's kind of hard to do
you can kind of only use it as itself
I think it's hard to write a scene where a flash flood
happens organically
have they ever died that
red or am I making that up?
that would be cool
I'm sure you could but that's a
huge effort they die the lake in
Chicago green for St. Patrick's Day
that's a lot of water
so they should have a blood flood
they should have a blood flood
that's a million dollar title
right there hopefully more than a million
it's a hundred million dollar title
all right great
I'll write in direct blood flood
wow
and then you're long gone
and we're talking about you like I should
my controversial take blood flood
three there
that's where it really came into its own
and I will declare I will have written and
shot blood flood by next year
I will declare that next year
this year
I will commit to going into production
blood flood in the next few months
that's a good goal post you can get that done
and Jason Sheridan is a star
of blood flood
very annoying when you're using
your blood flood concept to do
money laundering
and a movie never gets made
it'll be a big scam
it'll be a big Kickstarter scandal
you're not delivering rewards
we've all given money to big scams on
Kickstarter
I love the updates
people we know
people I would know for years like I need money for a movie
and then five years later I go huh
that didn't come out did it
I need money for an escape
did I get the money back I don't think so
I need money for a new identity
a person who fled the city
I wonder where they are now
sorry
looking forward to blood flood
the twisted mind of Mike Carlson
what have we missed anything else about
the aspects of the psycho
experience or the house
has Norman ever been in
just the parks or is he always
over here
that's a good question I've never seen him in the parks
I don't know if he's just walking around
I've never seen him walking around the parks
but I guess
because Frankenstein, Dracula they're still around
they're always walking around
they look funny no matter where
they are in the park
there's not a good spot for them
they'll be walking around
we went during Grinchmas
and they were right by Whoville
which I liked a lot
yeah
I think recently
yeah they're just on the main street
but then the mystery
machine and Scooby Doo gang are
feet away from them
I like when they interact
I like it
Frankenstein and they just have a conversation and character
I wonder if
there was any Norman Bates ever walking around
and if that would even be
identifiable outside of
being in front of Bates Motel
because he is just a guy
it was videos of
Loki
where they had a Loki face character
walking around but it was him from
so it was just a guy
it just looked like a guy that kind of
looked like Tom Hiddleston
Loki and all the
different outfits
without the horns it's not so
identifiable
she's just a guy with a knife
yes
Lucille Ball is still in the park
there's still a woman playing Lucille Ball
and I guess that's more identifiable
than Norman Bates
but that is still old
most people don't dress like that
I am impressed Lucy is still
in those parks
she's been dead for many
decades now at this point
I want her to go away don't get me wrong
you know me I want her there forever
I am shocked that she's still there
I wonder if that was ever
the man in a kind of a suit
it's like a brown suit
when it's translated to color
in real life it's like a brown suit
and a blue shirt
obviously it's all black and white in the movie
Scott I wanted to mention you
I know you're usually the John Forsythe
keeper
the universal souvenir videos
oh yeah
or these mealy mouthed intros
from old actor John Forsythe
movies are the wizards wand
so there's the one for universal
Hollywood the one for universal Florida
and I scrubbed the Hollywood one
and I was hooping
like if it was more modern like whoopee
or something they would have been menaced by Norman
but John Forsythe
did not goof around with Norman Bates
what they had with him
he was in front of the psycho house
with a Hitchcock silhouette graphic
and then it slid away
and John Forsythe was standing
sideways
and then he was like Alfred Hitchcock
and the magic of the movie
so there was no Norman Bates
John Forsythe action unfortunately
that's a shame
I did just remember though there was a video
I was just trying to remember
what the general gist of the
what does Norman do when he runs out
and it's you know
it's like you maybe
see him for a second possibly
before he comes out with
a body
that feels like Janet Leigh
and then puts it in the trunk
cool car they got
it's all set up great
and then he kind of spots the tram
that's the last aspect I like about it
is that you're a part of it
and that you're like your witnesses now
so he's like it's not
arbitrary really that he's coming after you
and then
you get just like a good
fast walk that you know
you probably get the biggest scare in the back
because maybe he swipes at you
but then just kind of stares
and it's still scary even though nothing happened
I remember like one time we rode the tram
and I made a point to kind of look
and see how long he stares
he watches you pull away
you don't get a reset
he's not resetting immediately
they're all committed
it's great
I have seen variation
he reaches into his coat
and pulls out a cleaver
and starts chasing the tram
and what I don't think they've done in a while
is that
so he man dogs the tram
tram goes up the hill
he runs up the stairs and comes after the tram
again
scared the hell out of people
but I think it is a little dangerous
to run up steep
stairs steps with no railing
yeah and that's a steep hill
going up
dangerous seeming stairs yes true
that is scary I had that happen once
and then it's never happened again
and I'm always like a little bit like is he going to be there
is he going to be at the top of the hill
wow all that
it's cool they established it
sometimes it comes out of the house
sometimes it comes down the steps I feel like
yeah I have
maybe I haven't seen the house
maybe logic please but it is funny to think about
Norman he's okay in reality
what's happening he's killed a woman
he's putting her in the trunk in the middle
of the day he looks over
there are 150 people
looking what is his plan
he's going to run over and stab all 150
people very fast
he does not have a lot of time
with one single knife with one
knife so he's going to run over
and then yeah I don't know he does I don't know if he has
a second like I don't know if in the narrative he actually
is getting us I guess we just
narrowly get away
and you'd have to come up with this plan
really fast and I don't
know his working knowledge of the universal
tram tour because I don't know the reality
where this is
I assume it doesn't go by his
house in this world every five
minutes I would assume that but
yeah I think you'd have to
go for the driver first
to get that thing to stop moving or the tires
oh maybe it is tires that
maybe that is what he's doing
a lot of tires though you're
probably right but well if you get one
that might stop it and then you get more
tires so it would take a little while
I feel like to dig with a regular knife
through a big thick tire and you're tired
because you just you just stabbed we know the scene
he just stabbed
many times he had to
change out of the mother costume
right that too he's already
done a wardrobe change
so maybe he's cooled down he's cooled down
yeah he's in a different outfit
because in the movie
the reason the Bates motel is
so empty is he complains like you know they built
the highway so no one comes by
there anymore you think look
at all these potential customers to
fill the rest of the shoes
yeah he might be
in his best interest to just like throw
the knife away and
then she passed out
from hot tub fumes
she was enjoying our amenities
too much she'll be back around in no time
you'll see does Norman ever
kill in the first one he's
always wearing the mother outfit when he kills
I believe
I don't think
there's ever because he's wearing it even in the end he has just
the wig on or something
there was an equally
scary scene where the private
detective
detective Arborgast
yes
Arborgast
like it's overhead and Norma
runs out of the room so fast
and that scared the hell out of me
because I was just trying to figure out if
maybe he doesn't kill the tram because he's
not mother but
at the end of Psycho 2 he hits
he kills his real spoiler alert he kills
his real mother with a shovel
as dressed as Norman
so I guess they in continuity
he kills then just dressed as regular
Norman oh sure so I'm just trying to
I'm just trying to piece together
exactly where he is in his life in this moment
and what his plan
might have been he's killed yeah
right so he knows he kills
as Norman but it's his biggest
challenge this is like
when Deadpool and Wolverine have to fight all of
the deadpools oh my god can you imagine
an action sequence where Norman
kills 150 tram tour people
in like slow mo
just a bunch of blonde women pull up on the
tram like oh my god
he'd have the easiest time
that's what he's used to
miss USA
pageant rolls up
it's like the bus
of all the Lucy's in
rat race
it's like a bunch of like
Maryland convention
that's good yeah that's really good
he looks at camera like no this I can
do
like dubstep music plays
or something oh the theme remixed
yeah oh yeah there you go
it would be very funny
to see the property manager
of the universe backlog go like
oh Norman yeah
he's a little strange but
he hasn't been the same since the
universal Hilton at Sheraton opened
and took away the business
it's in canon
yeah yeah a lot more room
sure but none of the charm
I'm gonna have you deliver that line in blood flood
about the main character
of blood flood oh okay
I haven't figured out it yet but
you'll be managing maybe
managing the hotels I don't know I'm not sure yet
nobody comes to see my downhill
road anymore
all I know is that Jason's character is gonna talk about hotels
a lot that's all I know
a lot of hotel talk and he knows
that like the back of his hand yeah
the thread count on sheets
and then the different amenities
and the different why are all
hotel bathrooms barn doors now
you know just the whole scene about that
the barn doors get me started
actually you know what
that's what causes the blood flood
I hate to make this go longer but what do you think
about the barn doors Jason
okay
this isn't coming out for a while now
but the air condition
at my apartment crapped out
so I am currently
in the same heat that kept me away from
horror nights
the bathroom door is normal
but the headboards on the beds
are barn doors
and I
we were talking about it's like I'm okay
with it I'm more okay with this
than the barn doors as bathroom doors
at least you have so much privacy
you know
I
I'm fascinated I didn't even realize this barn
door thing has been taking the hotel world by storm
where like the door slides open
it's just you have to if you're staying
in a room with someone you better be like pretty
comfortable with that
okay well I'll keep an eye out for it
beware of barn
well that's an update you have to make in a new
psycho what Norman would have to have a barn
door in the motel you have to add one new
line so we recently renovated got all
barn doors now
there's no sound
you know that's the thing is you
can hear everything with the barn door
you can see her fiddling with it
through the shower
you just hear her cursing and it
kind of
so it's good it never works
murder deterrent yeah sure
yeah it's bad for the remake but it's good
for us and it's good for you in the heat
situation that you're less like
with you with the fear that you've had since you
saw the movie you were so much less likely
to and then all you have to do with is that
a maniac with a knife who you've
heard and now have to fight
oh yeah you just have a couple more
seconds of lead time there
at least you can get the jump on it yeah
figure out how to slam that barn door real quick
crush his face try to get
that weird towel rack above
like in the back of the shed get that
with the wall that uses a weapon
oh yeah
well this has been such
a blast so much to talk about here
Psycho and Beyond
I guess we can say Chelsea Rebecca
you survived haunt cast the fright
thank you for kicking off
I can't think of a better way to kick off
the series and thanks for bringing
all your knowledge and fun
this was so much fun thank you
I'm so happy you do please come back anytime
let's exit through the gift shop anything
you'd like to plug ah you can find
me over on dead meat on
YouTube and dead meat presents that's where
our podcast lives among
other things like we have our
horror nights live streams and like different
interviews with people and yeah
what is the kill count
kill count is like the
flagship series that is on like the main
dead meat channel we had to do
some finagling with where things live
because the ever changing algorithm
we have to appease it
the true
horror in this world now
kill count of psycho is
there's not that many really
yeah you got like the
detective you've got
the obviously
the shower scene
I mean the mother is dead
but you're not in the you don't see the
events of it yeah
the sister survives
but isn't there one more
I can't think I haven't seen in a little while
I know it's been a minute since I've seen it
I forget if the boyfriend lives
or not Viggo Mortensen
who also wears crazy
shirts they all went to like
iguanas the like
retro vintage
they just took the cast like
alright here's 20 bucks everyone
buy the kookiest shirts you can find
yeah yeah yeah
you're making me want to now I kind of want to
rewatch the movie I want to watch it too
I want Gus Van Sant to remake the psycho 2 now
it's better
than elephant
delivery
well thank you so much for being here what a blast Josie
and as for us for three bonus episodes every month
check out podcast the cemetery gate
I'm sorry oh it should be haunt cast the fright
the cemetery gate or get one more
bonus episode on our RIP
tier crib 3 you'll find all of that
at patreon.com slash podcast
the ride which per
events of this episode is where
mcgaris' fuzz bucket
lives if you want to hear the full
recoiling play out in real time
then you know
then
pony on up to the patreon party
boy and let us know if we talked about
him and Michael Eisner cause I don't
remember after doing so many episodes
oh we did
40 minutes on just that
really hello fuzz bucket
good to see you
I am a party boy
forever
dog
this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner Brett Bohm
Joe Silio and Alex
Ramsey for more original
podcasts please visit forever dog
podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on apple
podcasts spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts
keep up with the latest forever dog
news by following us on twitter
and instagram at forever
dog team and liking our
page on facebook