Here's what I'm proposing going forward when it's just you and I or when Scott is gone.
We call the episodes Scott Free for two reasons.
Scott isn't here so it's Scott Free and we get away with anything we're trying to do
because we're little rascals so we're going to get away with it Scott Free.
Well I like that.
You get it?
Yeah I get that.
Two different meanings.
So going forward that's how we're going to refer to episodes where Jason and I get to
be little scamps, little rascals, we get to be members of our gang, was that the original
little rascals?
The Naughty Boys, Naughty Boys Unleashed.
Yes right so today is Scott Free, today's episode is Scott Free, my name is Mike Carlson,
this is Crypt 3 of course, oh no shoot shoot shoot!
Is there been an episode we've done where I haven't forgotten to do my Halloween name?
Spiky Snarl Gun?
Every episode I feel like this month has been ah shit damn it from me because I know the
first one was because I was just editing it like literally hours ago.
It's your own horror.
Yes, remembering these stupid names is my own horror, I'm upset.
You're like an innocent victim who just saw Art the Clown heading his way.
Yes I guess I am a lot like that, what year was yours as a skeleton?
Oh Jackal Skeridan?
Jackal Skeridan?
Are you sure?
Yeah reasonably sure.
I thought there was skeleton, was that a different year?
Maybe a different year.
I swear there was a skeleton.
I feel like the last couple of years I've stuck to that.
There's no way to find out right now because we're in the middle of this.
We're doing Crypt 3, the topic that you the listener voted on of course, which is the
what is it called?
The Nightmare Experience?
The Nightmare Experiment in Hong Kong, not the Nightmare Experiment, the sexy burlesque
circus show at Halloween Horror Nights I think in the year 2021 in Orlando.
Right I just by the way now called it the Nightmare Experience.
That's not what it's called.
It's called the Nightmare Experiment.
Nightmare Experiment, Professor JT Woo and his experiments.
Right and this is a thing that was second place last year and has like very handily
won the poll this year.
So that's like an exciting topic in my mind, something I've wanted to talk about.
Yeah for a while I feel like this come up every year almost in our discussions.
So we will read a message right now from Scott.
He says Dear Crypt 3, Scream Scribers, which is good, sorry for missing another Club 3.
I will also probably miss November's Club 3 episode.
As such I will be unable to give full attention and care to the current poll incumbent.
Bugmane does whatever he wants.
That's why I am hereby holding the bug option until the November poll or excuse me until
the December poll.
Let's get five all new episode suggestions and then hopefully sure thing Bugmane takeover
will skittle scattle to the holidays.
Thank you and mind your P's and Q's.
Sincerely the gear wolf.
So Bugmane is not going to be in the poll next month or as you're hearing this now.
Right but he may be invading your Christmas.
That's what it sounds like.
It sounds like yeah you're going to have a very buggy Christmas so prepare for that.
When you wouldn't like that.
You thought that sounded weird?
I thought it sounded even worse.
Prepare for that little buggy, a very buggy Christmas.
Skittle scattle under the Christmas tree.
So that's there's that but let's yeah let's I don't know think about is there any November
type suggestion you have something you'd like to throw out to the listener to try to put
your thumb on the scale a little bit.
Oh hmm well Thanksgiving is obviously I feel like the big holiday.
It certainly is the big holiday.
I would go so far as to say it's very notable.
Oh an election year this year too.
It is an election year.
It's an election every year but it's a presidential election.
It's a presidential one right so it's a big one so the answer is no you don't have anything
to suggest.
No not really I'm just buying time.
All right you don't have to buy time I mean we can just move on.
I guess not yeah we could just.
You could have said no I was going to say no I don't have a good one.
I wasn't even going to try to do.
Black Friday?
Is there a Black Friday ride?
Is there a Black Friday?
There is that Thanksgiving ride that opened it where holiday world yeah which is like
you're going to grandma's house to have turkey and gravy.
Yes well and there's the gravy boat right roller coaster.
Is that what that is?
Is that up yet?
Are we talking about the same thing?
I think we're talking about the same thing.
Okay.
I thought that was like you were going to grandma's house.
I think there's a blaster.
Obviously we don't know enough about it to talk about it.
But yeah so there's that but we haven't been on that I mean I guess we could talk about
it if you really want us to.
But yeah Thanksgiving specials I suppose Disneyland Thanksgiving specials.
We've done a little of it.
But yeah there's not maybe there's some weird Disneyland Thanksgiving thing we've never
seen before.
That's possible.
But yeah anyway it's up to you really.
I'm not going to suggest there's no Paul Lindha Thanksgiving special as far as I know.
No I don't either.
I can't recommend that because it doesn't exist.
But I mean I guess you could suggest we write a hypothetical Paul Lindha Thanksgiving special
or something like you could force us to do something like that.
Oh okay.
We could create and produce and film a full Paul Lindha Thanksgiving special.
But anyway yeah up to you.
On to this topic for today's Crypt 3 episode.
The nightmare experiment which was a suggestion from Mark Gannon and here's what Mark says.
I'd like to suggest that in the upcoming spooky season the boys take a look at the one time
that Disney tried to do a Universal Studios Six Flags not style scary event.
Hong Kong Disneyland's the nightmare experiment featuring original character antagonist Professor
Wu.
A couple of photos of this crazy event are linked below.
Thank you for those photos because I mean it's fairly well documented online but it's
still not like a famous famous thing I feel like.
I feel like most average average perk-overs don't know that this existed.
You know I in the review time kind of round up videos about these because the nightmare
experiment specifically went two years but they said that Hong Kong Disneyland had been
doing more Halloween haunt kind of things since 2007.
Yes and I didn't know this.
No I didn't either because there was Graves Academy which was like a spooky boarding school
sort of thing but nightmare experiment is notable for having Disney characters.
Right so they would do these different events that would be you know a lot more like original
narratives narratives than just you know oogie boogie bash which is like the villains are
out and you're getting candy.
But they're not like crafting new narratives with new characters necessarily.
I don't think I have not been to one of these recently but I was shocked there's like they
used to do a jungle cruise overlay.
Yeah.
You see that.
That yeah that's wild.
It was called Curse of the Emerald Trinity.
Yeah.
And it was like a spooky jungle cruise and they would put you know a lot of its lighting
a lot of its lighting and music as far as what the difference would be but it's cool
like it's cool and they would add like I don't know they had some props like skeleton or
skull props or something but then they had new sea backstory.
Did you read any of this?
Of the jungle cruise?
Yes.
No I didn't go down that rabbit hole.
Oh well I did.
Okay.
I scurried right in.
All right.
Professor Garrett Reed was a disgraced professor kicked out of the Society of Explorers and
Adventurers.
He was an alleged grave robber and thief obtaining artifacts through unsavory means and selling
them on the black market.
He was on the hunt for the Emerald Trinity, a trio of enchanted emeralds said to grant
men immortality, stealing a boat from the jungle navigation company to travel deep into
the jungle.
Indiana Jones warned the archaeology community of his nefarious deeds and Lord Henry Mystic
expressed urgency over finding him and stopping him.
Wow.
So this implies that the other members of C are moral and above board.
It does imply that even though they have implied the opposite before.
Yeah.
Certainly Barnabas T. Polingen is a little nefarious.
Oh sure.
And others.
Obviously Harrison Hightower, very nefarious, doesn't get more nefarious than him.
Yeah.
But this guy trying to get all the emeralds for immortality, he went too far.
Right.
So Professor Garrett Reed is too bad for even the Society of Explorers and Adventurers.
Yeah.
How powerful he is.
So much so that Indiana Jones had to get involved.
Yeah.
That's never a good sign.
Indiana Jones is advising C members also.
Is he in C?
I don't think Indiana Jones is in C, but Jock Lindsay is like C affiliated, I believe.
Yeah.
I don't think Jock is in, but he knows people from C as well.
Okay.
And if you don't know what we're talking about, which I guess Crypt Three, you have to know
because you're a big dork like we are.
No offense.
I mean that in a good way.
C is the Society of Explorers and Adventurers.
We've done an episode on this.
This Disney parks specific narrative involving original parks characters, some that look
like Disney Imagineers that are basically like a bunch of old, I guess they're old people.
Yeah.
Turn of the century explorers.
But then also like land barons and colonizers and like there's different types of people
like Mary Oceaneer seems good and then like, you know, Barnabas is bad or Henry is bad
or Barnabas is maybe in the middle.
I don't know.
Barnabas is the man who owns Big Thunder and they keep doing more of this C stuff in the
parks and I think we like it in general, but there's a lot of it if you really want to
enjoy the narrative.
It's really, they're really fleshing it out.
That TV show, they're taking their time on that TV show.
I would love to know how much money they've wasted developing all the parks properties
into movies and TVs and TV shows because it seems like the Big Thunder Mountain being
developed as a TV show 10 years ago doesn't go anywhere.
There's been multiple C projects I think at this point.
Yeah.
of Battlestar Galactica and Star Trek Next Generation fame.
And that's dead though.
That's over.
He's done with that.
Oh, is he done with it?
Yeah, not happening.
That show is not happening.
Well, not his version.
Not his version.
Okay.
Because for all mankind is hitting season four or five, I think.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know anything about that.
Well, you got to fire up your Apple TV app.
I can do it.
I know how to fire up an app, but I maybe I will.
But yeah, that's that's done.
There was that Seth Rogen figment.
Right.
Where's that been?
There's no talk of that.
I forgot about that one.
There's every like there's so many times when there's a big article and then it's like,
where did it go?
And the answer is nowhere.
Well, you know, when they get these these brand new focus groups of fans to help consult
on the movies to make sure the fans don't get upset.
I wonder what that looks like.
There was an article today that came out saying that big companies are going to employ fans
to watch movies of like IP characters and then tell them, oh, oh, the fans are no.
It says the example I gave is like, oh, if you do this, the fans might retaliate.
How?
What are they going to do?
They're going to complain on the Internet.
They're going to make a video with the most like unpleasant like Disney.
Brian Reynolds has annoyed Brie Larson again and we'll be back Friday after that.
You know, those just as guys making up shit, you know?
Yeah.
Well, they're scared of those guys.
I guess so.
They think that there's a perfect equation.
It really feels like so like I think I think speaking of bug, he has some sort of term
for this.
And it's a thought I had at the same time.
I didn't steal it from bug, but it's almost like self A.I. human beings are actually trying
to think like A.I. before even using the computer in the sense that you're like, all right,
let's just put whatever Spider-Man in the A.I. and it'll tell us what the audience is
comfortable with.
Isn't that just called having a business degree?
Hey, isn't that just called MBAs?
Give that material for later and on a different podcast or a stand up stage on your Netflix
special for my Netflix special.
And I'm going for the record.
I'm going for seventy five applause breaks.
Ellen had seventy.
I want more.
I think you could get ten million dollars to do one of these stand up specials.
Oh, yeah.
With one of just your MBA jokes alone.
Well, you know, we're about we've been comedy for a long time, Mike.
We're truth tellers.
You know?
Yeah, that's true.
We are truth tellers.
I didn't lie at all about Professor Reed.
I told the truth about him.
That's right.
But anyway, yeah.
Well, go and watch a video of this just because there was like an original like piece of story
that was represented through some screens where he like got killed by vines.
Yeah, pretty dark.
But like all this stuff to me, again, I'm jealous.
I've said this a lot this year where I'm like jealous of other parks because this stuff
feels so creative and interesting.
Sure.
And you just don't get it anymore.
You don't get it.
You're just not going to get it domestically, you know, not getting it domestically.
That's right.
There was also like a headless horseman thing, too, that was a tie in to see.
It's like the curse.
I forget.
Curse of the headless horseman or something.
Wow.
But there was so they do so much interesting stuff over there.
And even now, there's like kind of like a Jack Skellington walkthrough.
Is that right?
Is that still going on?
Or is that over?
Because after Nightmare Experiment, I think they did get complaints that like, oh, this
is too scary.
This is too much.
Yes.
So there was a Jack Skellington Nightmare Before Christmas more whimsical kind of walkthrough
experience.
Yeah.
The thing I'm talking about was called The Revenge of the Headless Horseman, which again
was Adventures Club stuff.
Yeah.
And Adventures Club was the thing in Pleasure Island and Disney World that is now closed
that was very sea heavy.
Sort of the start of sea, really.
Yeah.
Right?
That I mean, and that was my shit growing up like that was dragging my family to that
a lot.
My family was very patient with how many times we would hit up the Adventures Club on a trip.
Right.
And I never went.
Yeah.
And it's sad.
It upsets me.
Yeah.
And I just want to sit here with my tears for a good minute if the listener would just
sit here and indulge.
Okay.
Shocking yourself on the microphone with those tears.
But yeah.
So all of that stuff is fun.
And yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if that'll ever translate to a movie or TV show.
I mean, you can make a cool TV show out of anything really, but it's so tied into being
park specific.
I wonder if it will ever make its way, the sea lore into a movie or TV show.
Yeah.
That's a good question.
I feel like it's either going to end up being Easter eggs or it'll be a standalone thing,
but it'll just get noted to death.
Well, right.
I mean, like in what scenario where you're like, okay, this is a movie about like Barnabas
T. Bullion, an old railroad tycoon, you know, like, all right, well, is it tied to Disneyland?
Well, no, no, it's just he owns a railroad.
Yeah.
Okay.
But what do they do?
They own the things from the Disney parks.
Okay.
But are the Disney park in the movie?
No, no.
I mean, I guess you could, you could represent all of it in a real world.
A character points and goes like, oh, they call that big thunder mountain.
Right.
And that's it.
Like, I guess there's a world where like, it's like globetrotting, but all of the things
from Disneyland would have to be represented in the real world.
I feel like they thought this was going to happen when they adapted League of Extraordinary
Gentlemen.
What do you mean?
They were like, oh man, if this hits, we might have a new franchise on our hands.
Oh, well, that's true.
Yeah.
But I mean, I don't know that that was more just like, oh, we're going to do a fun, exciting
kind of throwback adventure movie based on all these old characters.
But that's all like the characters, you know, in a club.
Sure.
The comics are very particular.
They're very, Alan Moore and Kevin O'Neil were very much going for like, this would
be a thing from this time, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, it's, you're right.
It's a similar thing.
I just, I just mean like from a Disney, like if they're asking the fans, the fans are like,
are they going to want more Marvel or sequels to Pixar movies?
Are they going to want like watching a dusty old man steal money from a train?
Like, oh, that's true.
I'm just saying, I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't know that the appeal of it.
I feel like the very special appeal of C is that it is just park specific.
It's just that, you know, you know, is a little dork when you're riding big thunder that there's
a little portrait.
There's a little connection.
Yeah.
That looks like Tony Baxter in the whatever, the saloon or something.
Sure.
So it'll be interesting to see.
I'm not against it.
I'm for it.
I'm just wondering.
But yeah, onto the thing we're talking about, which was a scary haunted maze.
Two of them.
Yes.
There was one and then there was a sequel.
A scary haunted maze, which just off, off the bat, in case you didn't know what I would say,
like this looks awesome.
Yeah.
It looks really good.
The budget seemed to be, I don't know.
I don't know if it was high because it's not like it was, it's a walkthrough.
So it's not like.
The sets are just so intense.
Like they're so detailed.
Right.
Yes.
Everything looks really good.
The costumes look really good.
It's characters, you know, but they're like fucked up.
They're like messed up.
Yeah.
I was speaking of fucked up, I got to mention, did you know, did these names, Tarrant Hightop
and Nivens McTwisp, did those names mean anything to you?
Tarrant Hightop did not mean anything to me before I started looking at all this stuff
up yesterday.
Yeah.
But that popped out to me.
That is the name of the Mad Hatter?
That is the name of the Mad Hatter, specifically the Johnny Depp Mad Hatter in the Tim Burton,
Alice in Wonderland movies.
His name is Tarrant Hightop.
Tarrant Hightop.
He comes from a long line of hatters, of hat creators and the Mercury drove him crazy.
The Mercury did?
Mercury used to be used in finishing hats.
Oh.
And that's what Jeremy Piven, that's why he had to pull out of the play because he had
mercury poisoning.
Well, that's because he ate too much sushi.
He ate too much sushi.
He hits too much sushi.
He got out of that mammoth play by saying he ate too much sushi.
The phrase mad as a hatter comes from hat makers used to use mercury and that much exposure
to mercury would drive people a little mad sometimes.
Wow.
I didn't know this.
Do all Mad Hatters, in all of the Alice stories, have they all been driven mad by mercury?
I think that's the implication.
They all have to make hats.
They're all a little kooky.
I don't know that they're all named Tarrant Hightop.
That's two P's at the end.
Yeah.
That's close to Topsy.
It is very, it is close-ish to Topsy.
Now we're really getting way Scott-free because we can talk a little more Topsy.
Should we call for a full Topsy's second gate episode while Scott is away?
Oh, wow.
I don't know if I'm prepared for that.
Is Topsy original to that movie or is she?
Yeah, I think Topsy is original to that movie, but I could be wrong.
Was she not in a book or something?
I don't know that she was.
If Topsy is in a book, maybe we do a second gate, but if she's just in the movie, I don't
know that we need to.
Yeah.
Like I said, I don't think Tarrant Hightop is necessarily the name and other things.
I certainly don't think the White Rabbit is referred to as, once again, consulting my
notes, Nivens McTwisp.
Nivens McTwisp.
These don't feel like, these feel like human AI.
I need an old-timey name and then the machine spits out Nivens McTwisp.
They're good.
I mean, they're good.
I'm not mad at those names, but I was shocked when I was looking through whatever fandom
page and I went, huh?
I've never seen the Johnny Depp Alice movies, even though they've made, what, $10 billion?
Incredibly successful, also very successful in Asia.
And that's why you see more representation of them in those parks sometimes.
But yeah, so they made this maze and there's like kind of just an empty building, what
is it called?
The Pavilion or something?
The Pavilions and then the next year, they used a different flex space known as Plaza
Grounds.
Right.
And because I was also trying to figure out, is there a spot to even do this in Disneyland?
I don't think so.
Oh, well, there's sound stages.
In Disneyland?
California.
California Adventure.
Yes.
Sure.
Right now there is where Monsters Inc. is.
They could do that there, you're right.
There's the arcade, the old arcade in Tomorrowland.
That is really only open for rentals and like limited time lounges.
Yeah, that's kind of a tiny space, but I guess you could do something in there.
Horror Nights uses a lot of extended queues.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, there's a little, look, because I've been looking at that map a lot lately because
of Disneyland Forward and all the stuff and trying to figure out where Avatar is going.
Sure.
So there are spots they could maybe build a little building, but I don't think there's
anything that's just like, oh, that's ready-made other than what you're saying is the sound
stages in California Adventure.
Right.
Yeah, I mean, Epcot has that big pavilion.
Epcot has more flex spaces.
Disney World has tons of flex spaces.
I'm sure there's, yeah, and Epcot, my God, you could, there's probably so many empty
buildings you could just move a Halloween maze into.
Even newer buildings.
Sometimes we have to turn the lights on in Spaceship Earth and they're like, oh, shit,
we got to run that today.
Epcot's in such bad shape, sometimes they forget to turn the lights off when you're
riding Spaceship Earth.
Yeah.
There's a light switch on the wall.
Disneyland will never be completed.
Epcot is done, though, for Test Track will be redone soon.
That would be so good, though, like, I know there's so much, so much wine and food happening
at Epcot and that's a lot of the money drivers there now, but yeah, you could just take some
of those spaces and turn it into little mazes.
Yeah, you could easily turn the Odyssey.
Right.
Building into a very long maze.
That's, I mean, Disney does not want it to get into this game.
They've per, like, they've stayed away.
They've seen what has happened.
They've seen the money you can make, but they have stayed away.
I guess they feel that their Halloween parties are lucrative enough to not do something special
like this.
Yeah.
And although I, I was shocked to find out that, um, there's not that many nights set
aside for Oogie Boogie Bash.
You're right.
Yeah.
I really thought it was more like, oh, and then when it gets into October, it's five
nights a week.
It's like three, I think.
Right.
It's, it's like, yeah, it's barely like anything.
Even hard nights is dark on both coasts, usually Monday and Tuesday night.
Yeah.
I, yeah.
So I guess I don't know if they've crunched numbers and determined it's not worth it to
put the money into building mazes or anything special like this.
But they did it in Hong Kong and kudos to them.
I guess they maybe never will be able to do it again, but they got to do some weird dark
stuff with these characters.
Yeah.
And there is some, I mean, two years in a row, the man, it's implied the man to Hatter
picks a guest from the crowd and cuts their head off.
It's, um, and it's, yeah, it's not even, I guess it is implied because you don't see
the actual decapitation, but it basically happens and then they pull, like there's a
plant, like, so you'll walk into the maze and you're one of the people there as a plant
is an employee of the park and they're just dressed in plain clothes and they, it's funny
cause I saw a video of it and I'm like, oh, this person's doing a very good job pretending
to just be like a dopey tourist.
Yeah.
And then you go into a place where there's like an asylum and the mad Hatter's in there
and he's wearing white, I guess all white, like he's, yeah, like all white.
The first year it's an asylum, second year it's at the hat shop, right?
And he pulls the, the fake, uh, uh, guest in or the plant and takes like pruning shears
or like whatever, I think it's clippers, like a hedge clip, hedge clippers and like the
edge.
Yeah.
So it's really like, he is decapitated somebody.
How they got away with this, I don't know, cause it's not like this was 40 years ago.
This was less than 10 years ago.
This was the mid 2010s.
Right.
Who in Disney approved that?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess cause they're overseas, they got some special permission to decapitate.
Well, you know, we talked about before, like when they've expanded the parks internationally,
they've had to adapt some stuff.
Like they do the big one always being Phantom Manor, the Hoenn and Manchin equivalent in
Paris, I feel like Tony Baxter is always saying they get scary, they get funny, they don't
get scary and funny.
I know.
And that's something where I'm like, is that true?
I think culturally it's like those mean different things.
But like, um, yeah, they went kind of much more hardcore.
You're an Hong Kong.
Yeah.
Hardcore is right.
They went right.
Okay.
Well, let's do like kind of a Halloween maze.
Well, let's have the manhatter kill a guy, which is, yeah.
So then in manhatter, like, is he a villain in the Johnny Depp movies?
Well, no, from what I read, he's one of the resistance fighters against the red queen,
the evil queen.
Right.
That's a big thing too.
You're like, oh, you've taken kind of at least an anti-hero in some ways and turned him into
a murderer.
Yeah.
That's a extra shock.
That's a big swing.
Yeah.
Right.
Cause like, oh, evil queen or Maleficent tries to kill someone.
Sure.
They were doing that in the movies.
Yeah.
But the, my friend, the manhatter, what happened to him?
Terrence?
What happened to him?
I don't know.
Yeah.
It's like, I mean, imagine like, uh, like happy from the seven dwarves was in the room
and they like pulled an audience member out and he like stabbed him with an ice pick.
Sure.
Happy's a murderer.
Like that would shock anyone.
Yeah.
My friend, Happy's killing a guy?
Get out of here.
Now I'm, I'm haunted for the rest of my life.
I'd expect that from, uh, uh, Doc or Grumpy.
Grumpy.
Yeah.
It was a fit of rage.
One of the seven dwarves, I was looking this up lately or recently, I should say, um, Disney
the dwarves in the like original Snow White, but because like those names were not in the
original story.
Oh, okay.
So like Dopey is not in the public domain for another decade, I think, or whenever Snow
White came out.
Yeah.
Over a decade.
Then Snow White came out.
Okay.
Cause he's kind of, that's an original character.
Right.
So you could, if you wanted to do Jason shared and presents Snow White and the seven dwarves,
you could rename the dwarves.
Oh.
Or you'd have to right now, but tomorrow you could go into production on Jason shared and
presents Snow White and the seven dwarves and you could have one called rage.
You could have one called apathetic apathy, maybe apathy.
Okay.
Yeah.
Getting into inside out to territory, which I have not gotten around to either Disney plus
haven't gotten to it yet.
Uh, you could call them one horny, I guess.
Yeah.
Um, cause generally, I mean, the way that the Disney version, I guess they all just
have names based on their personalities.
I think personalities and what was easy to animate personalities that could be communicated
simply and visually.
Right.
Smoke coming out of ears.
Yeah.
That shows anger, which is another inside out thing.
Oh yeah.
So it looks like really stealing from Snow White in a lot of ways.
Is there any sort of one of those when you read like a fan theory where it's like, did
you know actually Snow White does not hang out with any dwarves.
Those are just seven facets of her personality.
Oh, that she's imagining them.
Yeah.
That would kind of annoying things like a Tyler Durden thing.
Cause like I saw one recently where it was like Donnie and the big Lebowski is not real.
And then somebody's like, no, they talk to him.
Like they do talk to him and he influences things that happened in the movie.
But like people like to make up fan theories is what I'm saying.
Well, if the focus groups, you know, suggest this, I hope it'll make its way into, you
know.
We should focus group this podcast.
Oh, that sounds great.
Yeah.
We should find out.
I mean, I guess that's what club three is really.
Yeah.
It's kind of like, what do you want to hear?
But everyone's kind of divided.
It's true.
It's like the country a lot of, in a lot of ways.
Oh yeah.
Club three is divided.
Very divided.
So yeah, that that's in the middle of the first maze is when Mad Hatter kills a guy.
But yes, it starts.
So there is an original character, which you talked about professor Wu.
And his assistant.
And is it, what's the name of his?
I don't know if his assistant has it.
I didn't see a name, but it might be somewhere.
And it's like his, his lab and he's researching a phantasmagoria and different phenomena.
Is he evil necessarily, or is he just sort of like in over his head?
I think it's one of those like, yeah, he's trying to explore and discover and maybe he
pushes it too far.
Yes.
He certainly pushes it too far because you go through like, and then you go through like,
what is it?
A chamber door.
You go like through a portal.
It is basically.
It's very similar to the, I think of the Poseidon's fury kind of locking rotating chamber door.
Apparently this is like a little Easter egg is like, oh, this is a nod to the map of Hong
Kong Disneyland.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So then you kind of go through this and then that's when the maze really starts.
This is like kind of an intro area where you get, you understand the narrative that's happening.
Yeah.
You see Dr. Facilier, I think that's the first room.
That's the first one.
Dr. Facilier and his like shadow.
And his shadow, yes.
His creepy shadow helps him like disappear.
Right.
And then he's like on a little stage and then he gets like pulled, he gets like killed.
That's the character from Princess and the Frog.
And he gets like pulled into like hell?
Yeah.
Oh, was it?
Some sort of nether world?
I guess he is kind of like the spirits are kind of like, get him.
Right.
So like right there, at least you go, okay, there's a villain.
I guess what I'm saying is like, I'm comfortable at this point.
I'm like, okay, it's a villain and he seems, something's bad happening to the villain of
the piece of Princess and the Frog.
Well you're like the Hayes coat.
You like still the movie rating coat from back in the day.
Oh, yeah.
You like the villain always needs to get his comeuppance.
Right.
Yes.
This was an old rule where old movies, you would have to see a person that did something
bad be punished for that action because you didn't want to teach people bad morality.
Right.
So yes, I, that is, you're right.
I am kind of assessing the different rooms based on that.
Now modern like horror mazes and Halloween horror nights, that's not necessarily true.
That doesn't happen a lot where you see the villain get, get his or hers at the end.
Sure.
Partly sometimes because they just want to keep making insidiouses.
Well, sure.
There's a lot.
Did you know that James Wan and Patrick Wilson are both associated with the conjuring and
insidious?
I did not know that.
I did not know this.
I don't know that.
Is that, was there something particularly interesting about that or you just didn't know?
No, I just, it's just a thing I've learned about reading up on a Halloween stuff this
year.
Okay.
All right.
I didn't know.
I don't know.
I didn't have anything to say about that.
Patrick Wilson directed one of the later insidious movies.
You're hitting me with information that I didn't know, that I'm not sure I care about
at all.
And no offense to either James Wan or Patrick Wilson, who I enjoy the work, their work in
different ways.
Yeah.
But no, I don't, I don't know that, that information doesn't inspire anything from me.
And it's no offense to these men.
I'm just surprised that you're excited about it.
I just thought it was, it was, they were notable, like big horror franchises, insidious at horror
nights, conjuring at Six Flags this year.
I was like, oh, Patrick Wilson is in both of these.
So were there Patrick Wilson character walk around?
Like, are they in those mazes?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Cause conjuring is conjuring universe.
So you got the nun, you got the Annabelle, you know.
Do you watch these movies?
I've just been reading about them.
I have not, I was just reading up on them cause I was trying to get background for all
our haunt talk.
Are you going to watch the movies?
I, I'm thinking about it.
They're very available.
Are you considering it very strongly?
I'm considering it.
I'm looking into it.
I'm hearing about it more and more.
Well that's, now I have to say that cause I am hearing about it more and more from you
mostly.
Yeah.
We're hearing about it more and more from Jason.
From Jason.
Yeah.
These multi-billion dollar series, I'm finally getting around to them.
Well but this doesn't sound like you are.
You sound like you're thinking about, you sound like you're thinking about getting.
Around to them slowly.
I don't know.
It seems like it's not for sure that you're going to watch them.
I'm dipping my little toesies in.
You're dipping your toesies in the Wikipedia.
Yeah.
Well it's a start.
I guess it's a start.
I can't argue with that.
So okay.
In this room, and I couldn't tell because of the video and yeah, was it review time
is the YouTube channel that has a really good video of this, that's what I watched.
Review time had videos on both of them.
It's review and then T-H-Y-M-E.
Someone went.
I watched someone actually go through them.
But they said that Jack, a skeleton of Jack Sparrow then comes into the room.
I didn't see that.
I couldn't see it in the video either.
It gets very dark in some of these videos.
Right.
So I couldn't tell if that was just a projection on the wall or, because I was hoping like
a man in a skeleton costume with like a bandana on his head came in and like kind of Keith
Richards is way through, but that didn't happen.
No, I didn't see that.
It seemed like it was just a projection on the wall.
Low light cameras have gotten a lot better even just in the last few years.
Well, that's true.
Even watching her nice videos, I'm like, well, it's like crystal clear.
Some of these mazes.
That's true.
Yeah.
But yeah, I was like, oh, there's, so there's two, I mean, there's two Johnny Depp's in
this maze, two different Johnny Depp's no low, no tanto as far as I could tell.
But that wasn't a hit.
And I guess it was a hit.
Maybe you would see a tanto in a maze like this.
But maybe not in the year 20, whatever.
What's the year 2024?
So yeah, I didn't, I couldn't tell what that was.
But there is like a skeleton Jack Sparrow in the Shanghai Pirates ride that comes to
life essentially.
Oh, okay.
He starts out as a skeleton.
It's sort of similar to that Beauty and the Beast effect on the Tokyo Beauty and the Beast
ride that everyone goes nuts for because you can't tell how it's done.
Sure.
And it's a similar thing where he like turns or he's like a skeleton or something turns
around.
He's like turns into Johnny Depp.
Okay.
This is mostly skeleton like jail cells.
I think in the fort from the movies or the fort you see the the pirates trying to get
the key from the dog.
Right.
It's it's skeleton pirates.
And this is kind of quick.
This one.
Yes.
And this is just a bridge.
I don't have a lot to say about it because then that's on the way to the CID room.
Which is horrifying.
So yes, CID, which I didn't realize CID, the bad guy who's really kind of misunderstood.
Yeah.
CID from Toy Story.
His name is CID Phillips.
I didn't remember his last name.
I didn't know his last name was Phillips either.
So we're learning a lot of last names on the show today.
But his name is CID Phillips and he was a kid who was kind of like, you know, a troubled
bad.
I wouldn't say bad kid, maybe a little troubled.
And people pointed this out online, like CID would pull the heads off dolls and put them
on bodies of a different doll or a different toy.
And then, of course, all those toys, like, were kind of messed up.
But they were they were misunderstood toys because they just looked a little scary.
But they were fine.
They were nice.
And then they kind of like attack CID at the end.
But people were like, how did CID know that these toys were alive?
Yeah, that's a good point.
Like you feel bad for the toys.
But CID was just a kid.
He didn't know they were alive.
Yeah.
So like, why are we mad at this kid?
But in this house, they're really alive.
Right.
So like, they've done this where CID is like a bad guy on some of the different events
in the domestic parks in Disneyland.
And it's still like, well, what is it?
What is the crime?
What crime did this kid commit?
Yeah.
What did he do?
What, his parents aren't home and they're not paying attention to him?
That's not his fault.
He's a sinner because he's a latchkey kid.
Right.
That is kind of what his sin is.
That is kind of, yeah.
That's the Hays Code interpretation.
Right.
The television raised this kid.
Who knows?
Do we ever see CID's parents in Toy Story?
I can't, I don't think so.
I don't know that we do.
We also don't see CID.
CID's like doing like putting toys, like taking them apart, putting them together weird.
He's not killing like small animals or anything.
No.
So yeah, how would he know they're alive?
Right.
So how, so why should we be mad at him?
Yeah.
That is what I'm saying.
Okay.
But he is represented as a villain in this maze on some level because he's created these
mutants which they are represented.
You see this like little room of like CID's playroom.
Also it seems like some of CID's like house is falling apart.
You've almost painted a picture now of a troubled kid whose parents, I don't know, parents have
let the house kind of decay to some degree.
We really should feel bad for CID or at least just have some sympathy.
Kind of a sympathetic character.
Yes.
We should feel bad now watching that movie.
Andy's kind of a little spoiled brat.
He doesn't know how good he has him.
CID?
No, Andy.
Oh, Andy.
Yes.
Andy.
Well, we don't know.
I thought you were almost jealous of CID.
Oh, of his freedom.
Of his freedom.
Yeah.
Of his freedom to create life.
Well, he is a creative guy.
He's kind of a Professor Wu kind of figure.
Yes he is.
So we go into this room of CID's and it's everything is represented now in large scale
because CID obviously is toy, they were small, relatively small.
Yeah.
But in the room in this maze, they're giants.
They are massive.
So you see like kind of that weird baby and it's not big baby from Toy Story 3.
It's that other like weird baby head thing that's in the original Toy Story.
And then you meet a character who I think is an original named character who was played
by a person named Babyface, a baby doll that wants to be played with.
With all the arms?
How many arms?
Like six.
It was the human performer that comes up.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah.
Okay.
Then that's it.
Babyface has six arms.
And wants to play with you.
Like he's laughing with the crowd.
Is like jumping in the crowd.
And this is scary.
Yeah.
This is a little scary.
Now, let me ask you this.
Yeah.
Somebody who hates going through a maze because of scare, because you're scared.
That's not a surprise.
I'm not shaming you.
That's just, that's the facts.
So would this be too much up to this point or would you do this maze?
I would do this maze.
Babyface seems nice.
Wait, I have it just called six arms doll.
Is Babyface the rotating head?
The giant rotating head?
I would have to go back and watch the review time because I believe he referred to the
character as Babyface who runs up.
Okay.
But I don't know if that's wrong and maybe you saw something different.
But yeah, would you, I'm just saying, would this be too much for you?
Because that is like basically what happens in horror nights.
Somebody pops out in a scary looking costume and kind of runs up to you.
I think the six arm baby looks sweet.
I think it looks misunderstood.
It is misunderstood, but don't you think some of the other characters from the horror nights
mazes would be misunderstood?
And Chucky is funny too.
Oh, Chucky is funny.
Chucky is funny.
The murderous little doll.
I wish they would let Chucky cut loose a little more in that late night show.
That's another episode.
I guess we've talked about it already at this point, depending on when this comes out.
But yes, I, there's some issues with that Chucky show.
We haven't.
Sure.
We'll have talked about it or we'd-
They canceled, they just canceled this TV show on Peacock.
Right.
But I'm just saying like, if you went through a horror nights maze with the 15 Chucky, however
many Chuckies there are, you like Chucky, but would that help you get through the maze
scare wise?
Who?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
Is it, Chucky is more my size.
Is that better?
You are bigger than-
Like Leatherface and Mike Myers are cute.
You are bigger than Chucky.
I am bigger than Chucky.
Chucky is a doll.
He is a doll.
Some listeners might think Jason is doll sized from the way-
I am not doll sized.
He talks, but he's not doll sized.
Uh, so, so you're not sure.
Yeah.
I will see if you'll be pushing my ass in a wheelchair through these mazes next year.
Oh, or is that, is that on the table?
That would add a new level of fright for everyone.
I feel like.
You think that's a possibility?
I think it's possible.
I, I would consider maybe-
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
I thought you were just going to not do it, but okay, all right, I'm, I'm, I'm on board
if you want to do it.
Cause I don't really want to try to hobble through with a kid.
No, no.
Cause then if I get startled, I'll be like Charlie Brown getting the baseball through,
I'll spin in the air.
You will get startled and you'll fall through part of the set, I'm sure.
I will, yeah.
That is not what we need.
I will fall into the lunch room.
Okay, well, we look now that, you know, Scott has had his second child and he's now saying
next year will be the year.
Oh, is he taking the first one?
What do you mean?
No, no, no.
Next year he's going to take his first born to these mazes?
No, no, I'm sorry.
That's horrible.
I'm just setting it up to explain why he didn't do this year.
No, no, you're right.
He's not, he is not taking his first born who is not that old through a fright fast maze.
This is apparently a thing though, in the discourse about horror nights sometimes.
People are like, there's a kid there in a stroller and it's like, what the fuck?
We talked about this, Gio and I talked about this last year at the Fright Fest, we go,
Gio counted the amount of strollers or the amount of different things.
Oh, I forgot.
It was over 10.
Oh, yeah.
And we were like, my goodness.
Yeah.
So, okay.
That's it.
If all four of us went to Fright Fest next year at the very least.
The three of us and a five-year-old, you mean?
No, four of us.
Oh, oh, us and Gio.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, if the kids can come with, I guess.
It's a lot of elevation.
You guys are going to be pushing that wheelchair out that hill.
No, believe me, as soon as I said Fright Fest, I went, oh, that's going to be a lot of pushing
uphill.
Yeah.
I'm going to have to train for that.
Or you just get one of the-
Start with horror nights.
Yeah, horror nights are a little easier.
And we could, have you used the elevator to get down in the lower lot?
Yeah, it sucks.
Okay.
It sucks.
It doesn't go, do you know how it works?
I don't think I do.
It doesn't go all the way to lower lot.
It goes halfway down and then you get in like a minibus or a pass van and that puts you
out-
Oh, we have talked about this.
Oh, yeah.
Behind Transformers.
That sucks.
They are literally, team members have been very polite.
They're like, look, if you can get out, you will get down to the lower lot much faster
if you get out of the wheelchair and use the cane and take the escalators.
Wow.
Because it sucks.
It is very odd that the, that elevator is there, but it doesn't go all the way.
They should let, I mean, this is, I, we've, that's not happening, but they should have
had a thing where the roller coaster that they're building would take you to the lower
lot.
Oh, that'd be great.
And that literally could work.
Yeah.
That would be faster than-
That would be faster.
What you're describing.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's interesting that maybe you'll be at a haunt next year.
Yeah.
Wow.
But would you do Fright Fest or you'd rather do horror nights, you think?
Yeah.
We'll see.
Interesting.
I think whatever is funnier.
Well, Fright Fest generally is funnier.
Yeah.
You could go through the Sewer of Souls.
That's true.
I could see the big shit.
It's been running for many years.
It doesn't seem like there's any end in sight for that maze.
No.
Because it's been going as long as Gio and I, the first time Gio and I went many years
ago.
I'm curious if they're going to get all the license mazes they got this year.
Yeah.
And they had all these.
Well, we'll find out next year.
Yeah.
You like this scary baby.
You like baby face.
I think, yeah, I think it's nice.
It's nice.
Maybe all the arms remind me of when Spider-Man has extra arms.
No, I like that too, but he's scary when he's got extra arms because he's got like the
spider face.
Yeah.
You like it.
Okay.
Well, maybe there'll be a Spider-Man.
No, because Disney has it.
I was going to say they would do a Spider-Man maze with his six arms, but they won't.
So yeah, after this area where you see Sid's like playroom essentially, that's when you
get to this Manhattan room and it's kind of like a long hallway and this will happen
on a lot of horror type mazes is that there's like a big set that's inside another room
and you just look in and then sometimes you'll have the performer pop out and that's what
this is.
And it's a very cool, elaborate, scary, sterile looking set.
That's very white.
They have one of the Queen's guards.
Yes.
What I saw listed is armored cards and I thought that was a play on the word armored cars and
Jane thought it was a play on the word armed guards.
So I guess sound off if you think it's armored cars or armed guards.
Well, wouldn't it be guards because they're actual guards?
Yeah, but it's one letter off from armored cars.
But why would it be a plan?
Cars are not a car.
It's like imposing like armor, like a Brinks truck, but they're not a car.
Yeah, we had literally a god of this.
We talked about this.
She and I yesterday for a few minutes where I'm like, I think it's like a take on armored
cars.
She's like, I think it's a take on armed guards.
But they are guards.
They are guards.
So how would it be?
Look, I'm happy to let the listeners sound off on what they think it is, but I just don't
know in what scenario.
It's cars.
They're not cars.
It's not Lightning McQueen.
It's just because it's one letter off.
It was bothering me.
Okay.
Well, if it bothers you, I get that.
Are there any armored cars in the Cars universe?
There must be, right?
Must be.
But yeah, there's got to be a spy car in that second Cars.
I've seen it, but I don't remember.
Is there like a James Bond car with like a gun in it?
Well, that would probably be Holly Shiftwell, wouldn't it?
Does she have a gun in her nose?
I don't know if she is armed.
How many guns are...
How many...
Did they develop guns in the Cars world?
How many characters in Cars have a gun in the glove compartment?
Yeah.
That's my question.
And is the glove compartment represented in the movies?
I don't know.
These are the questions that keep us up at night.
That could be.
If they kept doing these horror mazes in Hong Kong, then maybe they would have done like
an Evil Cars.
Yeah.
Like an Evil Cars room or something.
So yeah, they take the fake cast member, Mad Hatter kills a guy.
Mad Hatter kills a guy in front of everyone.
Tarrant has blood on his hands.
Yes.
And it is scary.
And yeah, I don't know what kids would make of it if you brought your kid into this.
They would be freaked.
Yeah.
I would have been freaked.
And what's interesting too is I was like, oh, surely they shut this maze stuff down
that year.
But no, they did do one more.
Yeah.
Because I thought, okay, this room is why it's gone.
There's no doubt.
But no, they did this room again.
Right.
Just changed the room.
Because I was like, oh yeah, surely like Bob Iger was like looking at review time or something
on his phone one night and he went, what?
The Mad Hatter's killing a guy?
This has got to stop.
I've got to get to sleep.
I have to be up at four in the morning to run on a treadmill for some reason.
Well, and do you think it was a two-shower day, right?
That's a good day.
You got a two-shower day.
That's a good day for him.
He'd shower in the morning and then before going to an event, he would shower again because
he had the shower in his office or has the shower in his office.
Sure.
Yeah.
And he lived, what was the phrase?
He lived for those two-shower days.
Lived for the two-shower.
That seems like, honestly, is that a quote from Bob Iger's book or is that a quote from
Jason Sheridan from an episode of podcast The Ride?
Just you saying like wistfully, I love, I longed for those two-shower days.
I'm not saying you like showers, but it sounds like a folksy.
That's more like an convenience for me.
I'd take two showers in one day.
It just sounds like-
I mean that I got like goo on myself or something.
Well, do you think Bob Iger got a lot of goo on himself?
I don't know what the rich get up to, Michael.
It's not my business.
Goo play?
They're into some weird goo stuff and you're not talking about semen, I don't think.
No, I'm not talking about that goo.
Right.
No, I'm just talking about like rich people.
Rich people goo.
Gold flecked, like Goldschlager.
They're always playing around a Goldschlager.
Okay, and that's why you would have taken their shower.
Maybe he just wanted to be fresh though when he went to a premiere or something.
I suppose that's true.
Yeah, he wanted to be Spiggins Pan for the Lone Ranger premiere.
I'm sure Lone Ranger premiere day was a two-shower day for Bob Iger.
There's no way it wasn't.
Sure.
I wonder if you could find photos of him doing something earlier in that day with a different
outfit on and then see what outfit he was wearing at the premiere.
You probably could.
Yeah.
This sounds like a Len Testo thing.
Was that a Tuxedo premiere or was that a more casual premiere?
Was Bob dressed as Tonto for that premiere.
Oh, that'd be great.
You know what?
I forgot to say this up top.
Last Club 3, we were talking about Kingdom Keepers and we were talking about Sunny Eclipse
Cosmic Rays selling a turkey burger.
I was skeptical that in 2006 that you could get a turkey burger from Cosmic Rays in Disney
World.
Okay.
You said yes.
Yeah.
That was the healthy choice.
I said, I know that, but I don't think that was available in 2006.
I texted Len Testa.
I said, Len, how can I find out what the menu was for Cosmic Rays in 2006?
And Len texted back one second.
And it was very quick that he pulled up, and I got to find it.
Hold on.
Forgive me here.
He pulled up the menu on a website of Cosmic Rays in 2006.
First I think he accidentally sent me the wrong, he sent me Pecos Bills and there was
There's no turkey burger on there.
And here it is, Cosmic Rays September 2006 menu right here from web.archive.org.
And I think it's from, it was from all ears.net.
That's right.
They have the actual menus.
And if you look, there is not a turkey burger to be found.
There is a turkey bacon wrap sandwich you can get.
Now to be fair to you, there was a veggie burger sold, but it was not turkey.
Obviously it was not turkey because it's not veggie, but here is the full menu, 2006.
Where did Maybach find all that ground turkey meat?
Now, here's also what Len found.
He found a place in Disney World in 2006 where you could get a turkey burger.
Okay.
Under Fountain at the Dolphin Hotel.
Now, that's not quick service in the parks.
No.
So I still think I come out on top in this argument.
Not that it was a big argument, but you can get, it's under Fountain Specialties.
You could get an Ahi tuna burger, a turkey burger, and a vegetarian sloppy joe.
That's under the specialties.
You can get other stuff too, but that was at the Dolphin Hotel.
So Len has come through yet again to help save an argument I was making, I guess, is
what I'm saying.
So yeah.
So what was I saying I'm going to text Len about just now?
Well, the bigger question was why do the holograms need to eat?
Oh, well, that's from Kingdom Keepers.
That is a good question.
I don't know if Len can answer that question.
So maybe in later installments I'll find out.
Yeah, but right there.
That's interesting.
There's an episode into just looking through the menus for Disney World quick service restaurants.
I mean, there is.
Let's be honest, there is.
Yeah.
Especially now that we have a resource, we have, we know where to look, but yeah.
There was no turkey burger at Pecos Bills, Tall Tale Inn in, this is 2004.
You could get a chicken wrap, half pound bacon double cheeseburger, a quarter pound cheeseburger,
a quarter pound hot dog, or a chicken salad at Pecos Bills.
Okay.
So thank you, Len, for adding clarity there.
Len really, if Len could just be like our fact checker, if Len could move out to Los
Angeles and just sit in the room and go, Len, what do you think Lowe's like, he's like the
Joe Rogan guy.
What's that guy's name?
I do not know Joe Rogan's guy.
He always goes, oh, it's like, shoot.
That's a funny reference, I suppose, if I know it, but he always goes, oh, bring that
up, whatever his name is.
And then the guy like brings up, it's usually the guy that brings up something that completely
contradicts a long thing that Joe just said, where he goes, yeah, there were aliens at
the White House in 1975.
There are pictures, like you have to see, you have to see, oh, bring it up, bring it
up.
Whoever that is.
And then they go, Joe, that was a hoax.
That's like a Photoshop.
And he goes, oh man, well, they looked real.
That's like usually how the exchange goes.
Sure.
Anyway, that Len should do that for us.
So let's go back to the maze.
So that was pretty much the end of the first maze.
Well, there was a, yeah, there were little clips of like Chernobog and stuff at the end.
Chernobog and there's footage from the cartoons and there's, they say, like, get out of here.
There's a fire.
Right.
So, so you got like a little wrap up.
It's almost like the end of Great Movie Ride, where you go, and the greatest hits.
Yeah.
And a couple more villains on screens.
And it's kind of short.
I mean, the mazes in general at theme parks are kind of short, but I think I'm giving
it, I'm grading it on a curve, certainly because it's Disney and they don't do these, but yeah,
it's a little short.
I think I would have wanted another couple of rooms.
What do you think about Maze of Madness the second year they did it?
Is that, did you find that longer or was it about the same?
Yeah, it might have been a little longer, a little longer.
And maybe it wasn't, maybe it's just watching it through YouTube.
Yeah.
It's like the video, the video is long, is basically as long as a video walkthrough at
Horror Nights or something.
But maybe I was expecting a bigger, maybe I'm really just looking for the bigger finale.
Yeah.
Because it felt like, oh, the finale is just screens.
And it felt like you wanted like a big, oftentimes at Horror Nights or not, the finale will be
like a big like puppet or animatronic or something that like scares you.
This is, well, okay, let's talk about the, I'm all over the place.
Let's talk about the next one before I start going off into different tandems.
So Maze of Madness starts much the same way.
You go into the professor's library office, but then the very friend, and it's implied
that the professor is not there, he's missing.
The first scene you go to is a terrifying Pinocchio.
Yes.
This is so freaky.
This might be the scary, this might be the most upsetting thing in any of these.
Well, it's, yes.
And it's, it's very freaky because of a similar thing with The Mad Hatter where Pinocchio
should be your friend.
He's your guy.
Yeah.
He's your little wooden guy.
He is now a human performer with prosthetics and makeup on and looks haunted.
He looks like haunted Robert the doll.
He is chained up.
He's chained up.
The implication seems to be he never got out of Stromboli's carnival.
Right.
He's been performing forever, ever since he's been kidnapped.
And they're playing a haunting version of I've got no strings on me.
Which is, I wonder if it's like similar to the age of Ultron trailer.
You remember they were, there's a haunting version of got no strings on me in the Avengers
age of Ultron trailer.
But his skin looks like it's melt, it's supposed to be wood, but his skin looks like it's melting.
And he's just, he wants you to help him essentially.
He doesn't murder someone like Mad Hatter, but seeing this character in this way would
have freaked the shit out of me.
Is this just how Scott perceives Pinocchio in any instance?
I think so.
I think that this is how he, yeah, we see cute little Pinocchio from the original movie.
He sees a human being dressed up with wooden skin, chained to like a dirty carnival, trying
to get free.
So I mean, it's a good thing I guess he's not here today because yeah, this is an adult
wearing little shorts or little suspenders with wood skin and chains.
And there's another one where if Bob Iger's sitting at home and he's looking on his iPhone,
he's checking out review time, one of his favorite theme park channels.
He's going to go, wait, we did what?
What did we approve here?
And it's also, here's the thing about Pinocchio's outfit.
It's dirty.
He's tall.
He's tall Pinocchio.
Human-sized Pinocchio, like I said, and his outfit is dirty.
Like the white, like part of his big collar, he's got big blue bow tie and it looks like
almost like he had makeup on.
It's like when you wear like some sort of makeup on your neck and maybe you were on
a white shirt or something and it gets on there.
This looks like it just, he sweated it all off.
It says on the fan page, he's been a slave performing.
There's also dirty puppets all over the-
There are dirty ass puppets all over the wall.
Yeah.
This is wild that they would approve this.
I don't even know that this is what I would want.
That's even how disturbed I am by it is like, if I was dreaming up a maze, I don't know
that I want to see dirty Pinocchio and his dirty puppet friends.
At least this version, like I feel like I watched a video about the Halloween stuff.
Pushcartons Williamsburg, the carpet bagger went, that's a YouTuber.
He's been doing it a while and he goes everywhere, I feel like, but there is a fairy tale themed
like scare zone kind of thing.
I'm for like twisted fairy tales in general.
I'm just saying from Disney, this is maybe too much to see my friend, my version of Pinocchio
like this.
The CG one was bad enough.
Now that's a good idea.
We see the CG one chained up and dirty.
That's good.
And he has like makeup all over and wooden skin.
And then I'm comfortable with it because he's not my friend.
No offense to him.
He's just not my friend from childhood, like the original Pinocchio.
He's more of an acquaintance.
Knew him in passing.
So yes, this is right off the bat.
This one I think wins for scariness because I'm like genuinely upset by it.
Then you get a little Monsters Inc.
And this is more along the lines of what I think they would do even if they did a maze
in the domestic parks where you see like the hazmat suit characters and it's like a moody
hallway with some lights.
Yeah, just changing the lighting and sound and stuff.
It's like, oh yeah, hazmat suit is creepy.
That's our movie thing.
Even though these guys are like comic relief in the Monsters Inc. movie.
So like in this scene, like this is a little kind of transitional scene.
This is kind of a fun thing that I could see them doing now even because nothing so nefarious
happens.
Ra's.
There's some Ra's.
You get a little Ra's voice.
Yes, that's true.
The character from Monsters Inc.
And then we get to the Mad Hatter.
The big, other than not just the Mad Hatter.
And Jason, forgive me, what's the name of the White Rabbit, the real name?
The White Rabbit or the Mad Hatter?
Well, you know what?
Hit me with both.
Terrence.
No, not Terrence.
Damn it.
Terrence Hightop and Nivens McTwisp.
Nivens McTwisp.
So you come and see these two characters.
It feels like someone's like, what's the most British name you could just make up off the
top of your head?
I don't know.
Like Nivens McTwisp, great.
Right at that.
Nivens McTwisp.
Yeah.
So you see them and they are very Tim Burton'd out.
For some reason, more so to me than the last year, even though that's not true.
But they are scary, but fun.
But fun.
I will say they are fun.
This is all faade, like a fake storefront.
Yes.
And they have a whole sort of faade that looks like a nocturne alley in Diagon Alley.
Sure.
Whatever it's called.
That little dark area.
The spooky alley.
Yeah.
So it looks like the, you know, it looks like a narrow British street from 150 years ago.
And it looks great.
This looks great.
That hatter exterior of his haberdashery looks very good.
With all this head cutting off, you'd think he was more like Johnny Depp's Sweeney Todd
than Johnny Depp's Tarrant Hightop.
Oh man.
Your Netflix special is going to be packed.
It's going to be packed with all, either you're going to make like an Amber Heard comment
or something about poop in the bed.
Oh no.
But that's a whole nother.
Oh yeah.
Didn't Johnny Depp refer to, whoever pooped in Johnny Depp's bed, didn't he refer to it
as taking a grumpy?
I believe.
I think that is right.
I'll edit this out if it's not correct, but I'm almost positive that he said like dropping
a grumpy or taking a grumpy when he was referring to poop.
I think.
Pretty sure.
I don't know that from anywhere else other than Johnny Depp.
So I think that memory is correct.
There's no poop in this, but this is very Sweeney Todd, this section.
It's not a barber shop, but it's like a blade and it looks like an old timey, it could have
been an old timey barber shop.
But this is cool.
I want to see this.
I mean, I know Scott would be upset by this and some of the pictures like this, look,
look at this.
This is scary.
Yeah.
And they look very, especially white rabbit, cause it's an animal, but look very Zoobilly
Zoo.
Yes.
Which is a terrifying show I watched as a kid, but was fascinated with.
But yeah, this scene, I think this scene is even better than the first year.
I think I like the scene better.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I think so.
Cause I think the first year they were kind of going for more of like an old timey asylum
sort of thing.
Yeah.
And it looked good too, but this like, there's more depth to this and there's like, it really
like looks, it looks permanent, I guess is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
It looks like it wasn't just a temporary maze.
So much of this stuff looks so expensive.
Yes.
And I liked the interaction between the two characters.
Then is next Beast Castle.
Is that the next room?
Yeah, Beast Castle.
And then Hades is the end.
Right.
And then Hades is at the end.
And there's not a good video of Hades, did I miss that?
I didn't find good videos of either of these.
Yeah.
Cause the review time, they don't have the video section of that.
Then like Hades goes, like there's other demons and they go to hell and stuff or something.
And that makes it again, those are the villains of the, I assume Gaston is in there.
No, I think it's just like a suit of armor, isn't it?
Oh, okay.
Cause I didn't see, I didn't see what happens cause they, they, he puts pictures in that
walkthrough.
Yeah.
Do you have it written down?
No.
I just had the fandom page open.
You hear the, the voice narrating the top of the story.
Suit of armor comes alive at the end.
I think that he was the one who caught Professor Wu to punish him for what he did.
So very Hays code coded.
Wait, what did he do though?
Yeah.
He opened up the barriers between all these realms.
I think.
Oh, and Hades is upset by that.
I guess so.
He loves chaos.
Why would he be mad?
You know, that's a good point.
That doesn't make sense to me.
I mean, I think that's what happens in the maze.
I'm just saying it doesn't make sense to me from a narrative perspective.
It's like, wouldn't he be thrilled?
Yeah.
I think it starts to lose some of the heat at the end of this maze, you know, like trying
to justify, like, wouldn't like Peter Pan be mad at him?
Like, what did you do?
The barrier between worlds has been, it's been destroyed.
That's really not Peter's area of interest though.
It's not his interest, but if he has to rise to the occasion, he will.
Okay.
Well, I feel like rising to the occasion is more grown up coded.
Yes.
And he doesn't want to grow up.
But don't you think Peter rises to the occasion in Peter Pan?
I suppose he does.
He saves the day.
You don't think, you don't think he would, like, if he had to fight aliens or fight inter-dimensional
beings, like he wouldn't rise to the occasion?
Oh, now this is, this is intriguing me.
I've never thought about Peter Pan fighting aliens or inter-dimensional beings.
Well, think about it.
It should be one of these mazes.
If aliens invaded Neverland, oh, we got to sell this.
We, I think that's public domain too.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, quite frankly, it was my idea, so I don't know.
We're not selling anything.
Well, okay.
I'm going to sell it tomorrow.
You weren't going to do anything with it.
You're doing Jason Snow White and I'm doing Michael's alien Peter Pan.
Okay.
Peter Pan and the saucer men from Mars.
And we both got these focus groups that are breathing down our necks.
Right.
The, so I'm just thinking, like, wouldn't it be, it wouldn't have been like a hero to
stop it.
But I guess Hades, I mean, maybe Hades is mad that like the, because Hades is, you know,
hell is his territory.
So maybe like some of his hell friends got out.
Maybe that's true.
Yeah.
So maybe it's something like that.
I mean, obviously some villains don't all have to be friends with each other.
They could have competing interests.
Once Hades persuades the guests that the professor is guilty for what he did, he transforms into
a demon.
Yeah.
The narrative kind of, uh, I mean, it's not so important to know.
But yes, it's, uh, like, I get, like, I guess it was there a walk around Hades or do they
sort of say, ah, Hades grabbed him and see you later.
Oh, that's good question.
I would assume there is a Hades, but I didn't see any pictures because if there is a walk
around Hades that okay boogie this year.
Yeah.
I've seen that like, obviously they have the suit, but I didn't see like any of the promotional
material with Hades, which feels like that would have been, that would have been like
a priority to be like, well, we've got to show Hades because he's such a, a fun bad
guy.
Yeah.
Um, I'm sure it played well.
It does feel like both mazes, the, the Mad Hatter was the main event.
Yeah.
It feels like that was where the most money was spent, but it is, yeah, it is an interesting
what if, if Disney were to go down this rabbit hole, uh, this, um, what's the McTwisp hole?
Nivens McTwisp?
Nivens McTwisp hole.
I don't know why I can't remember anything today.
Um, but yeah, I, I, I'm like seeing all these photos, like, like this is Dr. Woo photo and
like I wonder, like maybe ultimately because kids are coming, it just doesn't make sense
to do it.
It just doesn't.
That seemed to be the review time takeaway of like even in Hong Kong, they're like, uh.
Because there's a larger, I know this is, this is interesting because, you know, from
the time they did Alien Encounter onwards, the debate of how intense are we allowed to
make a Disney experience because obviously there's adults that want something a little
more intense and now Disney owns a bunch of properties that are scary.
Oh yeah.
They always have had some scary, right, aliens, predator, planet of the apes.
Where does that fit into Disney parks?
Does it fit?
Yeah.
Cause it's like, man, that would be cool.
And now obviously they're doing a Villains Land, but I bet they are doing so much focus
grouping trying to make sure that it's Villains Land, but it's not too scary.
Like it's, I'm sure.
Like there's not just going to be a xenomorph greeting you as you go into Villains Land.
I would love it if there was a xenomorph in Villains Land in Disney World.
I don't think there's going to be.
Sure.
I don't think Predator is going to be roaming Disney World.
No, that would be great if the Predator ruined the Villains Land.
If they said we're draining the rivers of America and the Predator would roam in the
ditch.
We're draining the Villains of America as we are trying to catch the camouflaged Predator.
Or they just announced Predator is now camouflaged and roaming Disney World in Magic Kingdoms
specifically.
Instead of being the grand marshal of the parade, one lucky family will be abducted
by the Predator.
Right.
I guess, I mean, we want Predator in the Disney parks.
That is for sure.
We all agree Predator belongs in the parks, but is it ever going to happen?
Because it has to be a separate park, right?
Like you can't do Predator in an existing park.
I guess they essentially need some sort of adventure park, some sort of islands of adventure
park.
It does feel like that.
It does.
And it feels like you could put something like this in a park like that.
But I don't know that money wise they'll ever think that it makes enough sense to do it.
But yeah, you could put a whole, you could make it a, yeah.
You could put Springfield next to Kohog.
That's right.
To where that would go to.
To the Nostromo?
Yeah.
Foxland.
Right.
It would go in Foxland, but I don't think Foxland is going to come.
So I don't think, I don't think we'll ever get, I mean, you could do a safer version
of this.
You could do like a sea narrative with like characters like that and then use the Disney
characters and then they don't have to kill anybody, but it could be a walkthrough.
They do like a cabaret show, like on the cruise ship.
Like a sexy show?
Yeah.
Well, that's a whole other.
Like a musical show.
Okay.
Is it sexy though?
No, it's very chaste.
It's a family program.
Okay.
As long as it's chaste.
On a Disney cruise ship.
This was a thing that I was thinking like even, and Universal is going to do it soon.
I think that's what they're doing with this fan, whatever this fan event that I can't
think of the name of where they're having Star Trek and Ghostbuster representation
in March.
They're doing like a non-horror ticketed event.
Right.
Coming up, which I'm very excited.
I don't think I've said this on the show.
They're going to recreate the Enterprise-D.
Good.
And this is just because I was stupid and didn't go and see the Star Trek experience
in Vegas.
This is my dream.
Yeah.
To live, I think even, and no offense to the X-Men's mansion, living on the Enterprise-D
is all I wanted to do as a kid.
Well, I just, I sent it to you.
I only learned about the X-Men event.
Is it in Chicago or Milwaukee where like they rent a mansion and there's panels and they
essentially convert this mansion into the Xavier school for a weekend.
We should send you, at least you get sent there next year maybe.
Yeah.
Because it, I mean you got Chris Claremont walking around, you got Gail Simone, the current
writer of Uncanny X-Men was there recently I think.
I am interested in it, yeah, but my point just basically was just like, okay, like non-horror
mazes, themed environments, walkthroughs, which Haunted Mansion was almost a walkthrough.
That was the initial idea in Disney.
And then it's easier to get people in and out by putting them in a little vehicle.
But obviously walkthroughs work fine because haunts have been making tons of money forever.
It's interesting though to see it like in another non-horror genre.
Yes.
Like how will these be well received enough?
Could this be the testing of like, would this, could this hold a full attraction?
You mean universal or are you talking about this Disney thing?
No, the universal thing.
Like a year round walkthrough.
A year round, yeah, walkthrough.
I bet the thought is, and this is based on nothing but my speculation, I bet the thought
is well, these ticketed events make a lot of money and we have these spaces and I know
they start disassembling and assembling for Horror Nights next year as soon as the haunt
is over.
But I wonder if they've sort of crunched some numbers and figured things out and like, well,
what if we put a bunch of other stuff in those buildings for a few months and charge an extra
amount of money and see if it works?
So I'm sure they're testing that out and they could do a full fledged version of it in Florida
if it works.
It would be interesting down the line to see if anything from one of these short run events
get promoted, you know, because they did do the Walking Dead maze for a number of years.
That was year round until they're like, oh, this costs a lot of money to put up, it costs
a lot of actors even if it's mostly sound and lighting, you know.
And that's now basically, I think that space is just Horror Nights permanently, I think,
because it's over by where the mystery machine is always hanging out.
But there's a maze right there too.
There is just a full Horror Nights maze.
It's a Quiet Place maze this year.
Oh, okay.
Which, but yeah, so like, I think that this type of experience, because like we did Delusion
a couple years ago, which is this, basically they do it every year.
It's like a very immersive 30 minute-ish thing.
You walk through and there's big sets and performers and you're involved in the narrative.
And I was like, this to me felt like something they should do as the finale of the star cruiser,
the galactic star cruiser, where like you give somebody like a 25 minute immersive walkthrough
maze type thing.
And that's not, it doesn't have to be horror, but like, I do think there's a lot of value
in doing stuff like this.
And I don't think, and Disney has just not done it, and I guess money-wise it doesn't
make sense for them.
But they're cool.
All that to say they're cool.
And I feel like they could do it in a lot of different ways.
Like even using the star cruiser building as a walkthrough maze thing that's like an
hour long, where you run into human performers and maybe new animatronics and lighting effects
and like all that stuff is so cool.
And I feel like Disney does not do it enough.
An immersive thing like Delusion or Sleep No More trend for many years in New York with
a Disney budget would really be something.
Right.
Yes.
Like Horror Nights, I'm sure it's expensive to make all these new mazes, but Horror Nights
I feel like sometimes I feel like it does not, does the Knott's mazes look better than
Horror Nights?
Do they have a bigger budget or are they just like able to work like better because they
don't have a big.
I think it's just doing less with more maybe.
Because I suspect, and maybe this is wrong, doing more with less, excuse me.
I suspect sometimes with the Horror Nights mazes that it's like the exact same layout
as the year before and as the sort of the same like dead spaces and they just like fill
up the rooms.
Sure.
That could be wrong, but it feels right to me because sometimes it feels very same-y
in there.
I think they repeat a lot more Knott's.
Well absolutely they do.
So mazes come back a lot and I feel like there's only two usually new, two new a year at Knott's.
There's an expectation with Horror Nights.
That is fair that Horror Nights is putting new stuff in so that it's more work to do.
But yes, all that to say is that if Disney had like these little spots to do like new
mazes and new kind of immersive experiences like they could just sort of plug and play
things in there.
But that's not the reality.
That's not the reality we live in and we can't always get what we want, sadly.
But this was cool.
They have stopped doing it.
But now I want to really keep an eye on like Hong Kong like because there's other stuff
too that I was in.
There's like a shield thing that happened in Hong Kong.
Oh, a Marvel thing.
Yeah, I learned about that.
I came across that doing this.
It was called Marvel's mission, Dimension of Danger.
Excuse me, Dimensions of Danger.
And I just, yeah, I just learned about it.
It was in, as we said, the pavilion.
You would help Doctor Strange recover the portal Nexus before Hydra does.
Along the way, you'll battle the forces of evil alongside Black Widow and Hawkeye.
Join forces with the mighty Thor Odinson in Odin's vault.
Lend Star-Lord a hand in the collector's museum.
So it was like a walkthrough maze thing with like a little narrative, like an immersive
thing.
So, yeah, come on.
Come on.
Let's see it.
Let's do it.
Is there, I mean, like having a Deadpool walkthrough would be great.
There's so much you could do.
Is there one property you want to be immersed in?
That has to be Disney or Universal?
Disney.
Because we're, I'm lamenting the lack of Disney stuff here.
Yeah.
But is there one you would want like, obviously Marvel, but you have to remember that the
Marvel is not the Marvel of Marvel Superhero Island.
No, right.
It is the MCU aesthetic, reality based.
It's not comic book style.
I think the world, I think WALL-E.
You want to be immersed in WALL-E in the garbage planet?
Like all the robots, like all the robots in the hover chairs and stuff.
Oh, later on in the movie.
Not on the trash planet.
Yeah, later on in the movie.
I mean, if you are helping WALL-E and Eva clean up Earth, that could be fun.
If you meet creatures and other things.
Here's what I think would be fun to do.
If you could, and there's no space for it, at least in Disneyland.
If you, like hypothetically, you could build a little building behind pirates somewhere
and you could get off pirates and then you could go through this immersive thing where
you walked through, as we showed, as they portrayed in the other maze, the pirate jail.
Okay.
And you could sort of walk through the back of the ride.
They obviously wouldn't actually be the ride.
Yeah.
But you could like portray different parts of the pirate's ride.
Oh, you could see other scenes.
Yes.
And you could do the same with the Haunted Mansion.
That's good.
Mansion would probably be.
Yeah.
Maybe that one makes even more sense because then you could go through different rooms
And then like one of the windows looks out into, you know, not the stretching room, but
looks into the like dining room.
So you could see it from different vantage points.
And maybe it's just a projection or obviously it's not, again, you couldn't make it actually
in the ride.
I mean, they should do that with the store they're building next to Mansion.
Well, that's pretty small though.
Yeah.
But if you do projection and stuff.
Oh, well that's, yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
Like screens, almost as if it was a shed.
It was a dirty shed.
Dirty shed.
Yeah.
You could look into the mansion.
You could peep into the mansion.
You could creep on the mansion.
Sure.
But like stuff like that, people would go wild and that would, they would pay a lot of
money for that.
Sure.
But yeah, to see like the famous, to go into Barnabas T. Bullion's desk, you go into his
office and see his desk.
Root around in there, try to find some of his personal effects.
Find his gun in his desk because you know, he had a gun.
Oh yeah.
So yeah, that's a good question for listeners too, EF.
Other than just suggesting next month's Club 3, is there a maze, a Disney property maze
that you would want to see?
Sure.
Because I, yeah, there's a lot of stuff they could do and yeah, like Star Wars, I think
truly you could do a really crazy maze.
Yeah.
I think that's easy.
And certainly with that giant empty galactic star cruiser, like yeah, make it a theatrical
show.
Right.
Make it a theatrical show and have it, what's the, Skeleton Crew is the new one I think
coming soon.
That's about the kids.
That's like Amblin, Star Wars.
Oh, that's the Stranger Things.
And that's, and that's where people have put together online that boy, some of these characters
look like Captain EO characters.
So put them in there too, is what I'm saying.
Anyway, you've survived Podcast The Ride Crypt 3.
Thank you for listening.
Jason, do you have any other thoughts on your way out?
No.
I made a note.
I was telling you, oh man, I have so much stuff to do before.
Yeah.
So much stuff to get to.
And you immediately forgot your Halloween name.
Well, I forgot my, that wasn't even a thing I was like worried I was going to, I wasn't
even thinking about that.
That's why I forgot it.
I definitely wrote right before we started Cosmic Ray Burger, because I wanted to make
sure that I got to the Cosmic Ray, because on the last, this is only for subscribed,
the elite subscribers to know this about the menu at Cosmic Ray's.
Well, finally they've gotten some closure.
Finally they've gotten some closure.
And don't tell anybody on the other tier or on the main free feed about this.
Because we'll know.
Because we'll know if you do.
But anyway, take care.
Happy hauntings.