Welcome, foolish mortals, to Hauntcast the Fright, the show that's more fun than a forced-rigged
game of Mario Kart against your boss.
I'm TheGarowolf, joined by, there's no way I'm gonna remember these names.
Well, it's changed, I'm now Spike Dracula's son, that's my name.
You are, huh?
Yup.
Now, I notice that there's not much of a rhyme going on, is that just due to the, becoming
more aware of Dracula's son from talking about the Monster Mash?
That's exactly correct.
Great, great.
Well, sounds good, I'm glad that you have the son construct in your name to properly
honor this great character.
I can be anyone's son now, for some future Hauntcast, I can be Werewolf's son, I can
be any Frankenstein's son, it doesn't matter.
We'll see what happens.
Any heretofore unacknowledged son.
Now, I turn to the name from the third host of the show.
Oh, Jackal Scarridan?
Great, fantastic.
It does me well to hear these, it does me well to see you guys even in Zoom form.
We'll explain why we're on Zoom form, and you might know already, because there's a
bicoastal thing happening here, and let me tell you why.
Every Hauntcast season, there's things that we revisit, perennial experiences, these Halloween
events that have been going for decades, your Halloween Horror Nights, your Not Scary Farms.
This year, there is a new kid on the spooky block, and that is, of course, Jimmy Fallon's
To Nightmares, the Jimmy Fallon Tonight Show themed haunted experience that is emanating
from Rockefeller Center in New York, and we've discussed it on the show a little bit.
Our ears definitely perked up when we heard the news.
And while we believe that Jimmy Fallon's To Nightmares will become a decades-long institution,
and there will be many, many years in which we can visit and revisit what will soon become
a Haunt stalwart, we still wanted that first year on the ground energy.
We had to know what year one of presumably 50 would be, and we were worried that all
of us being here in LA that we would miss it.
Luckily, a New York correspondent rose to the challenge, and we weren't surprised by
this because if there is a challenge, he will complete it.
Please welcome Griffin, the Completer Newman.
Thank you very much for giving me my credit as a Completer.
If you would quickly just...
I did change my display name on the Zoom for the season, and if you could please introduce
me by my proper topical name.
Oh, yes.
I mean, there's a dot, dot, dot, but I think I'm still...
I can do it.
I see it if you need me to do it.
Why don't you?
In case I'm...
I think I'm seeing it all, but you go for it.
Okay.
And Mike, put a little stank on this.
Oh, okay.
Bobby Boris style, I'm assuming stank you mean?
I would love that.
Stank could there be.
Grief Fang Boo Maniac.
I was missing some.
I'm glad you read it.
I was going to just leave it at Grief Fang Boo Man, so thank you for...
Boo Man is good too though.
I don't know how it is you're seeing the whole name.
I just want to squeeze every last drop out of it.
I did complete Jimmy Fallon's To Nightmares, but I don't want to take the lion's share
of credit here because this was not a task that one man could complete on his own.
Indeed, indeed.
I was not a solo correspondent on this one.
Yes.
And I'm very glad that that is the case.
And now I'm thrilled to do the second introduction of the episode.
Griffin, you host the excellent podcast Blank Check, a show which, unlike The Tonight Show
starring Jimmy Fallon, hasn't gone through producers like Toilet Paper.
Your show has been guided by the same steady hand for many, many years, who is also an
excellent on-mic personality on the show.
He's never been on Podcast The Ride, and I'm thrilled this is a great excuse to do it.
He having joined you for this experience, very happy to welcome to Podcast The Ride
producer, Ben.
Ben Hosley.
Hey there.
Glad to be here.
Hello, Ben.
I see Ben has changed his name though.
You're going to have to do it.
Yes, I got it in at the last minute.
At the last second.
So let me let me do my magic right here.
I'd like to welcome Brains Howlslay.
Hello.
Very good.
Yeah.
I'm so glad to be on the show and I'm, you know, very I don't know, I don't know how
to feel about what I experienced, but I think it was good that Griffin had someone there
with him, just to kind of make sure that like it was in fact that mediocre and terrible,
like just needed someone else to be there to witness and confirm that.
But also an interesting different perspective, right?
Because Ben walks out and immediately asked me like, what is that supposed to be?
Ben is coming from a place where he doesn't have a reference point of what a Halloween
Horror Night is, a not scary form is.
You know, like Ben is comparing this to like what like teenage, like fair haunted houses.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah.
Entry to a genre then and presumably a strange entry.
I don't have really a frame of reference, so I, I, I'm there, there was a, I was perplexed.
Okay.
This is where I'm so thrilled that, you know, like basically when Griffin said who he, who
was going to be in his To Nightmares group, I was immediately like, oh boy, I think Ben
has to join because I feel like you provide like great visceral emotional response to
the materials on Blank Check.
And I was like, I feel like I would be disappointed if we just got like a text read or just heard
a little bit of your thoughts.
I got greedy.
Like I want the, I want the, the real deal on Mike.
You need the Hossley pipes delivering those thoughts too.
That's right.
Here I am on a Sunday afternoon, ready to tell you all how I feel.
We have forced an extracurricular zoom and you know what?
You bring up the, the, the timeline and there's, there's another reason to bring up the timeline
and that, that is this, that so we're, we're doing this in kind of a window.
I haven't been recording with the guys very much and I thank you all for doing it on the,
on the weekend as I'm sort of balancing work stuff and baby stuff.
And basically Griffin has, this is just an interesting thing about when we're recording.
Coincidentally Griffin has sent a gift over for or, or in honor of my, my new son, my
second son and total coincidence, it is supposed to show up in the exact window that we are
recording this right now, not even intended, but that is a little like a ticking time bomb
that hopefully will go off by the end of the show.
Hopefully there might be an unboxing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the goal.
You might have given the arrangement of where I'm recording this in my house.
Now you might even see a delivery truck pull up in the window behind me.
You might see it and I won't.
Could you put up, put up a sign that says deliver straight through the window and then
you could just hand it through.
It'll take me away from, yeah, all right, I'll leave you guys to talk.
I'll scroll a note and then like, oh, I'm going to have to pop a screen out, but I'll
do that.
That's worth it.
It's like Mr. McFeely coming into the house.
I'm Mr. Rogers.
You could also do a whole thing with it and then get the delivery person a mic.
We get a new character out of it.
Yes, absolutely.
We should really schedule more things of this nature.
This is, well, this is a bend move actually.
I feel like you've done like coordination of items that arrive mid-episode.
Yeah, I mean, it's been 10 years almost.
When has that happened?
I mean, we did a pie reveal kind of recently.
Eva Anderson brought a pie for a recent Twin Peaks episode from Tweety's, the real
RR Cafe diner.
The Mission Impossible episode.
That's what I.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
A note was read, right, right, right.
You had a messenger show up.
I did to deliver a Mission Impossible style.
This message will self-destruct.
And it was a letter in a manila envelope that led us to a tape recorder taped under
a chair that played a message pre-recorded on mini cassette by our friend Patrick Willems
that I think revealed some third thing.
Yeah, it revealed some third missed take from our past Mission Impossible episode.
Sure.
A famously convenient format, mini cassette.
Yeah.
Who doesn't have a player?
Yes, I do like formats.
Yeah.
Griffin, just to confirm, this is a delivery.
It's not going to be like a terrifying art, the clown impersonator.
Showing up in that window.
Look, we all know I'm not sure I'll jump out of my skin if I see a little art, the
clown in this tiny zoom window, not not to carbon date this episode too much.
As we said, we're we're you know, we moved things around in the scheduling to
accommodate everyone's busyness.
We are recording this in the midst of art, the clown weekend art, the clown
fever is spreading across America.
This is no longer a thing that's only invoked by Mike and Jason on PTR.
It's like to do a confused Scott.
No, I now know what this is.
Sorry.
What the fuck is art?
The clown.
Hey, great.
I'm not alone.
Okay.
I have learned, but now we have a new art, the clown newcomer.
Does he have to know how is this going to benefit?
Ben, this is a great question.
I should ask this more often.
Do I need to know?
Well, if you go to Home Depot and want to buy your Halloween animatronic of him,
he's just really, I believe there is a Lowe's or Home Depot art, the clown
animatronic, I think so.
Well, Ben Jason did not explain to you who it is.
He just gave you more clues.
He just gave you more hints.
Okay.
So I don't know how much real estate do we do?
We need to do another episode with Griffin where we explain what this
franchise is to another person who's not interested in it.
I think we need to wait for two more movies before we do that episode.
Yeah.
Good point.
Great.
They're ordering him out at this point.
Ben, are you Googling art, the clown?
I am.
He's like a, he's like a scary French kind of looking clown.
Hmm.
Yeah.
He is, I guess.
Like almost mime adjacent.
Yeah.
I guess this, um, uh, doesn't this new one feature, uh, uh, I'll say PTR
legends and, and Jay Leno portrayer, uh, and I will say friend of the show
because I ran into him at Tamo Chan Enter, Daniel Roebuck.
Yeah.
Am I making that up?
Robuck is in, Robuck is in there.
Yep.
It's all tying together.
I don't, which ties us to tonight's show.
All set.
Right.
This is right back.
True.
Yeah.
Yep.
I don't think Terrifier is a Christian film, but he is in it.
He is, let the record state, he will do non-Christian films.
Right.
He likes Christian films and monster movies.
And those are the only two things he likes to work in now.
I mean, not jump ahead, but it does feel like Roebuck in to nightmares
as a sort of haunted Leno and even perhaps if Roebuck isn't available,
any sort of haunted Leno, I, I don't want to sort of, uh, telegraph
our opinions too early on here.
I think Ben and I shared a complaint about how little of this had to do
with the specifics of who Jimmy Fallon is.
Yes.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
And I mean, do we really even know very much about him kind of in general?
Even if we just want to take the most surface level front-facing, he is
the host of the Tonight Show.
Start from there, work out with that.
Yeah.
Yes.
The nightmares of a very specific, I mean, cause all, all right.
It's a thing about nightmares.
Okay.
Well, aren't all haunted mazes about somebody's nightmare, a human in
general's nightmare.
And that's what, from what I could tell the little that I know about this, I'll
lean on you guys to explain it to me.
But I know that there's like a scarecrow and a haunted gas station.
And these could be the nightmares of anyone, not the host of the primary late
night institution of the last 60 years.
It's a really specific job and person to say, we're going to see their
nightmares and then it seems like almost none of the nightmares are specific to him.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I mean, I'd say there's definitely an off the shelf vibe to a lot of the
nightmares, I'd say three or four feel a little more specific to him, if not
personal, at least specific to him.
And I was a little more intrigued by those, but I also think maybe, and I,
you know, I don't think any of us have the intention of this episode turning
into a full deconstruction, the way the race through New York episode was, but
but I do think you're, you're once again hitting the wall of how much does
Jimmy Fallon really show us of himself?
You know, if you're trying to build something off of his personality,
that is no longer, he's the MC, he's hosting, he's interviewing, he's
playing a game with someone, but is really trying to be an extension of his
worldview, do we really know what that is?
Right.
And is it successful in the way that Jacktoberfest might've been successful
by just adding like a silly over like Shaq is a captain on a boat, which is
delightful, but also doesn't say a lot about Shaq the man.
So I'm saying there's a way to do it, but does it do it?
Does it do it?
That's the question.
We walk out of this and Ben is like, okay, so what is this?
What is that supposed to be?
What are the other versions of this?
Explain to me where this comes out of.
And I give him a sort of a quickish spiel and he's like, but Jimmy Fallon's
a weird guy to do that around because his name doesn't really conjure anything
that immediately translates into like horror.
And I was like, you know, Ben at Halloween Horror Nights, they've been
doing the weekend has a house every year.
And Ben's like, that makes sense.
You say that I get it.
There's precedent in the imagery of his music videos, of his vibe, but also just
like an aesthetic that can be represented visually without him being there.
And I was like, Janelle Monáe is doing one in LA and he's like,
okay, that sort of makes sense.
And then Ben, what do you say to me?
Do you remember this?
I do because I started being like, okay, well, who's a celebrity who's not
necessarily like directly coming from like a horror kind of background in some
form, but just like a media personality who I feel like would be at the top of
my list to do this.
And the first name that I came up with was Shaquille O'Neal.
Ben immediately lands on track.
Wow.
And look, and you had no idea.
You did not know the kind of which I assume he filled Griffin filled you in on.
No, no, I would argue Ben's pitch for what Shaqtoberfest should be is better
than what they've actually put up.
Right.
So my pitch was it should just be a haunted house.
That's a little bit smaller so that you're getting Shaq's experience
through his day-to-day life.
Moving through the world close to Mike's experience a little bit, not
nearly as much, but a little bit.
That's getting close to your nightmare.
That's true.
Yeah.
You're living through his specific horrors, like what To Nightmares is
purporting to do, a glimpse, a walk through the mind, the haunted mind of
Jimmy Fallon, Ben immediately went to what would Shaq hate the most and how
does he place us in his giant shoes?
Like a tiny little airplane bathroom.
Terrifying for Shaq.
You kidding?
Wow.
It's based on the tweet, the famous tweet, Shaq's famous tweet about being
at Knott's Berry Farm and he said, and I'm going to paraphrase here, but he
tweeted, I think it's about a decade ago at this point, he said, I'm at
Knott's Berry Farm and I think he said like, my butt's too big to fit in the
seat and he goes like, ow, that's me yelling or something.
Like he tweeted this little tweet and that's what you're talking about.
That's like the Knott's Berry Farm roller coaster is too small for it.
Yeah.
So there you go.
I feel like this requires the, I feel like we got to do the official reading
because this is one of the most well-regarded tweets outside of Kevin Smith.
No, no, no.
You, you got very, very close.
I just do.
I just fully want to pay homage to the, to what is a very excellent tweet from 2009.
Wow.
From the beginning of tweets.
I'm at Knott's Berry Farms and my butt's too big to fit into seats on ride.
Ah, that's me yelling.
This is really incredible.
This is like one of the, uh, very important, it's like any number of
drilled tweets or the Kevin Smith, uh, clip around teen area tweet.
This is like a formative tweet.
Should be in the leather bound book.
Yeah, it should be in the, like the leather bound book that opened and
closed like, uh, classic Disney animated films.
Uh, it's, uh, I love the pitch.
I totally agree.
And it's so funny you flash too.
And then what, what actually existed, Ben was something called
Shaqtoberfest that was just, what if there was haunted stuff near a ship?
And now that same thing is back and it doesn't have Shaq's name on it.
And it seems to make no difference in what the event is or how it is run.
Fair enough.
Okay.
So this was just kind of a, uh, let's attach a celebrity to this thing.
I think so.
And it's so funny this all came up because I was thinking, because
we covered this last year and I was thinking how there is kind of a symmetry
here with Jimmy Fallon and Shaq, both celebrities who are loathed to attach
their name and face to any product that does not meet their extremely high
standards, both a crusty, the clown level of discernment on what they will
or won't attach their brand to.
Well, here's, okay.
So let's, let's start unpacking this a little, right?
Cause we, I'm trying to remember the exact order of events here, but
this thing gets announced.
I receive some number of messages on various platforms from people in
various corners of my life going, you're obviously going to this, right?
And then I feel like our group text, there's sort of a, like, look,
you, you are your own person.
We grant you autonomy.
We are not forcing your hand, but is this something you would want to do?
And I very quickly was like, yes, I feel obligated to do this.
I'm happy to do this.
I would be morbidly curious no matter what.
I don't want to walk through this alone.
I immediately message Ben and go, would you do this with me?
And Ben goes, yes, I'm down.
Um, in the lead up to this, cause I, I, they announced it, whatever,
I think in August, and then there was even like a sign up for the wait
list of first access of tickets.
And I was like, is this thing going to sell out quickly?
Am I going to be like Oasis reunion?
Like hovering over the computer, refreshing, trying to get a slot.
I felt very happy that I got a slot.
I paid extra for a VIP flex ticket access, which only grants you, you are
not married to your specific 15 minute time slots.
You can show up any time on that day.
Um, and then I very quickly afterwards see, oh, these slots are wide open.
They're not being filled.
They're offering all sorts of deals, temporary sales, incentives, discount codes.
Um, we've realized scheduling wise, it would have been easier if we, uh, went
a week earlier and thus recorded this episode a week earlier, it was a pretty
seamless process for me to transfer those tickets.
I didn't save money, which I thought I would.
I thought maybe by refunding, uh, I'd be able to buy new tickets at a
cheaper price that did not work out.
Um, but, uh, but yes, it does not feel like the thing is a runaway
success that having been said when we showed up there, there was quite a crowd.
When we left, it was barren.
And the thing in theory runs from five o'clock to 10 o'clock every night.
If not 11 o'clock, maybe is closing.
Uh, we were in the five o'clock window.
I think our tickets were maybe five or five 15.
We were probably done with the thing by five 45.
Definitely spent more time trying to figure out where it was and to get through
security than the actual attraction itself, which Ben recorded the audio on his phone.
So we have a real stopwatch of it being exactly 10 minutes.
Okay.
Um, but when we got out of there, probably at five 45, close to six,
there was no one in the lines.
I don't know if it's just like, that's part of the reset cycles of the hours.
I don't know if we went at the busy hour.
I don't know.
Uh, I do think they have now reduced the amount of days it's running, much
like the tonight show itself, which is no longer doing episodes on Fridays.
I think all of Fallon's endeavors are dropping.
I think they may be pushed the reservations into a shorter window each week.
Uh, but this thing's supposed to run for five or six weeks.
I did notice on the site right now, there is a Columbus day weekend special.
Uh, so there's another sort of like push to move tickets.
Um, but, but anyway, uh, in the lead up to this episode, we've just been
taxed and texting about, uh, uh, Fallon miscellania, right.
And at one point, Scott, I think you threw out like, is there an entire episode
just for like a catch all Jimmy Fallon side projects?
Cause we were talking about his two Warby Parker co-labs, of course,
uh, flippies and spinnies.
Yes.
And you're familiar with these, correct?
No.
What?
Oh, you got to keep up on war on Warby flippy Warby's flippies and spinnies.
So here's, here's the distinction I want to try to establish in this
crusty, the clown spectrum, uh, you're, you're putting out there, right?
Shaq will put his name on fucking anything, but there's something kind of
charming about how guileless he is that it doesn't feel like he's even
pretending to specifically care about these things and he's like, not
co-signing war crimes, you know, all of it feels kind of innocuous and silly
and chintzy.
I also like, uh, my ex-girlfriend directed a commercial campaign that he
was in and had a lot of conversations with his handlers beforehand and was
really worried about like, this guy does fucking 25 things a day.
He's going to give me nothing.
He's going to be an asshole.
He's going to big time and was like, Shaq came in and was the most locked
in talent I had worked with in a long time.
Wow.
Was great, was collaborative, was full of energy.
And it was one of like six things he did that day.
Like the crusty, the clown element of like, yeah, buy my cereal where it's
like, oh, he doesn't care about this.
And he can't even pretend he cares about it.
Shaq.
I'm like, he is good at being a pitch man.
And I think puts in the work to that, even if he probably has to be
reminded of what product he's pitching when he shows up to film that app.
But once you tell him, he knows.
He likes it.
I think he knows.
Fallon, all of Fallon's side projects, he puts out there as if like, this
means so much to me, every Fallon project is his megalopolis, is his like forever.
I have lived with this dream of passing something onto the culture.
Ben Flippes and Spinney's are collabs that Jimmy Fallon did with Warby Parker.
Warby Parker has done collabs with many other celebrities and they go, Hey,
let's work on a line, tell us what your favorite colors are, which frames you
like, and we'll come up with special limited editions.
That was not enough for Jimmy.
Jimmy wanted to get engineers involved.
Jimmy said, when I'm bored sitting around, I take my sunglasses off and
I spin them in my hand like this.
I hold the arm, one arm of my sunglasses in my hand.
I spin them like this and the spin just isn't very smooth.
Could you design a sunglass that has a 360 pivot?
Oh my God.
That's so stupid.
It's a fucking fidget spinner, but you wear it on your head.
Correct.
A fidget spinner you wear.
And there are like 15 minute videos of Jimmy Fallon talking about the R&D of
figuring out how to make Spinney's work.
And sketches where he made the Warby Parker guys like do comedy with him.
Like the flat Warby Parker founders you have to watch.
So when Jimmy came to us with this idea.
But in this like, and I thought there has to be a better way, as if he's solving
some huge issue in our society, the rigidity of a sunglass fidget spin in your hands.
And that he, that wasn't enough for him.
He had to innovate again.
And he created flippies, which are the, the lenses flip backwards.
So the sunglasses are basically double sided and the arms are double sided and
can like invert, they're like reversible glasses.
So they have two different looks.
Okay.
You got it.
And pitched it.
We don't, no one likes Jimmy Fallon, right?
Correct.
He stinks.
You're like cut through the clutter there.
I hate, I like, it's like so visceral.
I'm like, I just am, I'm getting so angry.
Just the glasses really pushed you over the edge.
It sounds like that was the last straw.
Comedy is good, but these glasses really, no, the comedy is good.
We can't, we can't, we can't deny that.
Right.
If the glasses were funnier, you would like them.
Yep.
Right.
That's what it is.
If they were like X-ray specs or something, or like googly eyes have popped out.
That would make a lot more sense.
That's funny.
They had a Groucho nose and mustache underneath.
Yes.
Oh, stylish, professional Groucho mustache for the glasses.
That's a great modern product.
Warby X Groucho.
Oh man.
That's not far away.
You know, I'd be lining up.
I'd be lining up at one of the handful of Warby Parker physical locations.
This is not far, Griffin and I have been texting about Laurel and Hardy
action figures that are being produced.
So I feel like more like Groucho X something is coming down.
There's a certain point.
Mike, I have also texted you about Laurel and Hardy action figures.
What are you doing?
Spread this conversation out.
That's right.
And then let Anne just make sure that you leave Ben and I off.
Don't accidentally add us.
I was going to say, Scott, will they change your mind if you learned that it
hit the stretch goal of having sashes and fezzes to put on the action?
Yeah, they have fezzes now.
You got to have fezzes through interchangeable parts, specific films.
Yeah.
What are their sashes for?
Why do they?
Why would they have the famous sash wearers?
Maybe.
Yeah, I don't even know.
No one on this knows.
Well, this has been my crisis of faith.
This has been my like sort of dark night of the soul with Mike is when I text
him late at night about wandering planet toys, Kickstarter campaign for highly
articulated and detailed Laurel and Hardy action figures, I say, you know, I
don't really care that much about Laurel and Hardy, but I like the precedent
they're trying to set.
Do I support this campaign because that gives them the encouragement to possibly
lead to other old timey comedy figures?
I would want.
Right.
Yes.
To answer your question though, about the Fez and the sash.
No, that didn't entice me to want to be on the text thread.
Oh, OK.
Interesting, interesting.
I watched both of the full length
Fallon Warby Parker videos and in the one for Flippy's, he says that he pitched
them the product as Hear Me Out, Parker Warby's.
He was going to flip it because it flips the notion of sunglasses in general.
He wanted that to be the name and they went, we don't get what that means.
And then he explained the application and they went, well, there's a reason
glasses don't work like that.
And it seemed like it was a very long and belabored process because it's just like,
well, the glasses, the hinges won't hold up to scrutiny.
If you do something that's got that much of a sort of like novelty factor to it,
it kind of sacrifices the integrity of them as functional glasses.
And after years and years of persistence,
Warby Parker team refused to give up and they made the breakthrough.
But we're at the gift shop after to nightmares.
And I pointed and I went, well, right.
This is why this is happening.
There was a copy of Jimmy Fallon's newest children's book.
I think it's called Five Sleeps to Halloween.
Yeah, yeah.
Which you were that was something that you made us aware.
I certainly knew that he, like a lot of celebrities, writes children's books.
This seems like one of the best ways for the modern star to make funny,
make money to and make funny and to make make both make.
Yeah, to make a lot of funny for a lot of kids,
you know, to slap your name on a on a children's book
that you did not write and certainly did not illustrate
or perhaps even get eyes on the illustrations
before you were holding the book on your show to tell people to buy it.
But Jimmy has done this more than a legend.
You texted us the number.
You texted us a list at some point, Griffin, of ten.
Five more sleeps till Halloween makes ten.
He wrote one prose book for adults along with his mother.
I hate this place.
The pessimist guide to life in 1999, I guess, at the peak of his like
SNL cutie pie status.
But then he has written 10 children books since 2005.
Hmm. And they've been increasing like in speed.
Oh, it's it's one in 05, one in 11, one in 12, one in 15, one in 17,
one in 19, one in 20, two in 22, one in 24 so far.
I'm veering to a bigger question, which is if there is a big if
if there is any question as to the quality of the program,
the tonight show starring Jimmy Fallon, would it not be better
if the host focused his efforts
a little more on the job that he has, which has which is a job
that is so important to some two comedians that people have gone
mad in pursuit of it.
And yet he has the chair.
He's in it. What people have grappled for and nearly died for.
And instead, he is not only he's writing 10, he's writing more kids
books than ever.
He's inventing multiple types of classes.
He's doing mazes. He's doing rides.
He's doing songs.
He's hosting entire other shows.
He's I is he not on three shows at the like?
I don't know. Maybe you should hunker down.
Every time he goes on the tonight show to promote one of these new side projects,
he delivers the pitch for the product as if it is
Jimmy Kimmel doing a monologue about his son's health
at the beginning of an episode.
It is done with this degree of like.
And this this is, you know, we have fun here,
but I just need to take a moment to tell you folks something.
We are doing a haunted maze, a Rockefeller center.
Can you go on a talk show if you were also the host of that talk show?
He will be the first to figure out how to do it.
Isn't that just called being at work?
He does.
He has more to promote than any of his guests possibly could.
It's it's it's such a pile.
And they're just I think something cumulative happens to where they're all.
Are we also aware there's not OK.
So Halloween is covered by a children's book and this experience,
which we will talk about.
Then as soon as all right, Halloween's over October 31st, November 1st,
we flip to Christmas instantly where he is putting out
a new Christmas album called Holiday Seasoning.
What? Yeah, yeah.
New holiday record record, because, of course, it's digital.
But you can also.
But what really caught my eye was that you can buy a vinyl of this,
which is in which is red and white peppermint colored.
So you could spend thirty five dollars on Jimmy Fallon's Holiday Seasoning.
And when you get now the full tracklist has not been revealed.
And I'm sure we will go through it thoroughly as time goes on.
But one track that they did say is on it is a Christmas song
that he did with Ariana Grande and Megan Thee Stallion.
And of course, if you have those caliber of artists,
you want to put that song on your peppermint record.
How could you not?
But maybe there should be a how could you not?
Because that song is called Masked Christmas.
This was a song that he put out for Christmas 2021.
And it's a song about like instead of
cookies, we're waiting for the booster and we're going to in twenty
twenty three years later, you're going to spend thirty five dollars
to get Masked Christmas to get a song where it's like
like this year, the jolly old elf is Dr. Fauci.
So is this album just a grab bag compilation of holiday songs
he's done across 10 years?
I believe so. There may be some original things.
I don't know. Dolly Parton's on.
I don't know when any of it was made from.
But certainly some percentage of it is grab bag. Yes.
Can't he just be like other late night hosts and buy 200 different cars
and spend his time working on them?
Because that's what Letterman did and Jay did.
Spend his time getting burned by them.
Rolling up his denim sleeves and catching on fire.
He already released five more sleeps till Christmas in 2020.
Five more. Five more sleeps in the franchise.
Within. Oh, Halloween is the spiritual sequel.
He's basically got a couple different threads going on in the children's books
because Snowball Fight seems to be its own standalone thing.
Then Thank You Notes, I guess, is somewhere in between children and adult book.
I guess he has two Thank You Notebooks.
So let's amend the data to that.
That's a segment.
That's a segment on the segment of the show and a book series. Yeah.
And we'll talk about Thank You Notes again in a bit.
Oh, good, good, good. Yeah, this guy's going to end up to make amends
for that old Chris Rock blackface bit.
He's going to end up putting out five more sleeps till Juneteenth.
It's coming.
His other book titles are Your Baby's First Word Will Be Dada.
Everything is Mama.
This is Baby.
The aforementioned five more sleeps till Christmas.
Nana Loves You More
and Kon Poyo, A Bilingual Playtime Adventure,
which was co-written by Jennifer Lopez.
So it feels like he's got a couple different sub franchises
going on in his book world.
He's got the holiday thing.
I imagine five more sleeps is going to hit up every major holiday.
Kon Poyos feels like it's setting up a new thread of can Jimmy Fallon
be granted permission to make books about different cultures
as long as he works with someone of that culture.
OK, yeah, right.
And then it's just baby mama, dada, grandma.
Oh, we got a lot of we got lots of a family to go.
Oh, so that can go for 12 more.
Wow. He figured it out.
No one has more franchises within their their human shape than this guy.
Jack Park couldn't even imagine this number of franchises.
I think every one of these books was still on sale at the gift shop at 30 Rock.
I went to see if there was any proprietary to Nightmares
merch worth getting.
There was a tin lunchbox and a T-shirt.
And that was it.
Neither one, I thought, were worth the cost.
There was also a pretty deep shelf
stocked with the Tonight Show with Jimmy Fallon shot glasses
and a little placard underneath it that said Jimmy's Tuesday.
Oh, really? My joke, I added, OK, no.
We were like, oh, that's interesting.
Probably he was just leaning into it and just admitting to it.
Oh, my God, this, though, there are shot glasses.
The shot glasses exist, and there were a lot of them.
But also just like Ben, do you remember some there was like
there was like a hoodie that just said Fallon in bubble letters,
like not any like sort of logo treatment of the show.
Yeah, yeah, it there was
a Christmas ornament
that was so depressing just to consider
some poor soul out there
already having bought the ornament and then each year
taking it out of the box of ornaments and hanging it on the tree with care.
God, isn't that depressing?
It's an awful, awful vision.
It's too heavy.
Where's never strong enough branches for this?
Can we just get rid of it? No, it's from our trip. God damn it.
We saw we went to the taping.
We got to see Jennifer Lopez come out and talk about their bilingual kids book.
And then we bought the ornament. It was a cherished memory.
Griffin, I am surprised you didn't go in for that tin lunchbox.
Have you thought about
texting anyone who like works at
Saturday Night Live or Seth Meyers like, hey, could you employee discount?
Yeah, could you get your employee discount?
I know you're not ready for prime time player.
Could you go use your employee discount at the 30 Rock gift shop?
Look, it's it's I it's not it's not something I would be afraid to do.
I will say I looked at it.
I was half considering it.
It was thirty six dollars and there was no thermos included.
Oh, well, that's the track of what is the what do you think?
The not ready for prime time player discount is in the NBC gift shop.
Do we think it's 30 percent?
Do we think it's better? Do we think it's worse?
I bet it's 30 percent tacked on.
There may be a surcharge.
And it's way less for featured players.
Featured players. Yeah, that's that's some of what you earn.
Yeah. Can I can I throw out in the litany of
you know, because I'm glad this is also turning into a catch all of
of Fallon's output in the in the last four years.
And I, you know, I could set this up or I could just start playing the track.
And I'm curious if you guys have previous experience with this.
Tell me if you can't hear it.
I haven't thrown to a zoom link video, thankfully, in a long time.
But hopefully this just hopefully the incredible
opening note of this song just starts playing right here and now.
Now, this is the one I want on vinyl.
It might be. I don't know if they put on Frosted Out.
I've been looking. I don't think that.
And let me let me just do a quick bit of his verse.
That if you don't know, is from the heralded
feature film, Unfrosted, the directorial debut.
What was that director's name?
Is that up and coming director?
I just know he hadn't made a film before and it was a hell of a hell of a movie
to come out of the gateway.
I think he did. I think he acted in it as well.
The name is someone whose work you've been studying a lot as you embark
on your future film directing career.
Yeah, yeah.
Looking to make such a big splash with a debut feature.
Yeah. Another man with 200 cars.
Yeah. Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A normal thing to do with your comedy money.
Yes. And he is proof that if you just invest money in cars,
you will be a great normal man with a good head on your shoulders.
Yeah. Yeah.
No chips on those shoulders whatsoever.
You have what looks like a normal New York brownstone,
but is actually a parking garage with an elevator system to store all your cars.
Which lets you know. Is that real?
Is is far away from where he actually lives.
It's a completely separate off site.
An entire property he bought just for the cars.
That's what he has.
But he also has like a secret big dog garage in L.A., I think.
That sounds correct. Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
You imagine he's going to drive the cars cross country
when he does an L.A.
Comedians in cars. Right.
That's right. Right. I think he has a right.
He has a secret. You're right.
Yeah, you need a space satellite bat cave kind of a thing.
Are comedians still getting in cars, guys?
Have they? I don't know if they've gotten in cars recently.
Yeah, it's been a minute.
There's been a minute at the very least, but I will say it was really tough.
Disappearance. I think people weren't there was an unwillingness.
Yeah, you just could.
You couldn't have two comedians in the same space like that.
Just pure per social distancing rules on drinking coffee as outlined
in the song Masked Christmas, of course.
Sweet morning.
It's really the main components of the show just erased.
Yeah, a sweet sweet morning.
He got shared in our text thread as well when it came out
before the movie was released.
And we were all sort of flummoxed by it.
And how much Jimmy sounds like he's really going for it.
Like, it's not a comedy song performance.
It is part of this weird side thread of Jimmy Fallon and Meghan Trainor
being like, she gets me.
She respects me for the musician I am.
We do the same thing on the side.
So curious to see if in the context of the movie, it's like, oh, Meghan
Trainor and Jimmy Fallon appear on screen as pop singers or, you know,
or jingle writers who are coming up with a theme song for pop tarts.
Like I was like, there has to be a reason these two people wrote
and performed a song for this movie.
Not at all. It's just in the end credits of the film, they play this song.
Jimmy Fallon is never on screen.
Meghan Trainor is never on screen.
The end credits of Unfrosted are always on screen.
The end credits of Unfrosted are like B-roll of the cast on set
lip syncing to this song.
Which again, something I'm going to, you know, I'm going to carve out
time on my project to do and I'm making sure that even with the stress
and putting it like, okay, but make sure we get the music part.
Make sure we get the cast goof around and have a fun dance.
Make sure we license Sweet Morning Heat.
I don't want it to be a different song.
Yeah, I just assumed it would be too Sweet Morning Heat.
That's going to be a lot of the budget is licensing that, Danny.
Full homage. It's worth it.
I also, my favorite, the biggest laugh to me in the movie, Unfrosted,
among many, among thousands of great laughs, really funny detail.
My friend Danny caught that at the very, very end,
the final note of the song is like, give me that Sweet Morning Heat.
And then it's like, Jerry himself is on screen dancing to it.
And he, on Heat, points and anyone with any performing or dancing
abilities would know you like, hold it for a second.
Like that's, it would be anybody's performer instinct, I think.
He just like, Heat drops it as fast as humanly possible.
He just like, bails.
He like, he, it's like, he does not want to be seen.
Like there's, there's crew guys around.
There's men who carry heavy items.
They're going to see me dancing like a wimp.
I got to get out of this.
I don't want to control why they're laughing.
I believe Jerry is not a fan of Sweet Morning Heat.
He wrote it, Mike.
He wrote the song.
He was on a talk show though.
And I swear he was doing his best to pretend.
That's just my reading of it.
And I can't remember if it was on Fallon or another.
It was on maybe Fly on the Wall or so.
I don't know if it was a podcast.
But I swear he did his best because he's very cranky and it's hard.
Like, it's hard for him to lie about stuff that like he knows is bad.
I think that's my guess.
I'm not saying I know for sure.
So I think he did.
And he's definitely very proud of Unfrosted.
Like if you watch and read all his press for Unfrosted,
it's clear that he genuinely is very satisfied with the movie he made.
Yes.
I think he probably wanted it to be more like an old jingle,
not a modern day Meghan Trainor song.
That's my guess.
But maybe what do I know?
Can I get one thing out of the way?
Because I do feel like we should transition to talking about the experience,
the terrifying experience Ben and I had proper.
Jimmy Fallon does not appear visually one time into Nightmares.
Really?
I know this was discussed with Shaqtoberfest,
where you guys were disappointed by the lack of like visual Shaq representation.
You know what, let me amend this.
Yeah, he is in one moment.
He's in that moment where he turns to the werewolf.
You're right.
There is one time he appears on a TV screen.
There's a good amount of audio from him.
And there are a couple characters.
Beautifully performed.
There are a couple of characters.
Subtle, nuanced.
Played by scare actors who, I guess, are purporting to be versions of him,
variations on him.
But like his lift on this seems to have been 90%
what feel like voice memos recorded during a lunch break.
And then one shoot that feels like it happened behind his desk at The Tonight Show.
They dress it up a little differently.
They stylize it a little differently.
He maybe is supposed to be playing a different character at that point.
We'll get into the inner logic of it.
But it was interesting how little Jimmy there was.
While also the structure of this thing is basically...
We said the whole attraction in total is like 10 minutes.
I want to say fully five of those minutes are spent in liminal spaces in between scare rooms
where you are looking at a video screen and otherwise totally unthemed,
like closet-like in between hallway space.
You're looking at a video screen that is sort of like writing out in real time
as if it were a thank you note.
Jimmy's description of what the next room is going to be.
And there's audio in between.
Audio over that.
I wanted to ask about that.
Why does it look like silent film cards?
It's very weird because it feels like they got stuck halfway in between it being a sort of like,
oh my god, bloody letters appearing on a page magically, a haunted book.
It almost is like they're stuck between Evil Dead, Necronomicon thing,
and just feeling like it is like fucking Laurel and Hardy intertitles.
Which, by the way, I think is maybe a stretch goal that Wandering Planet would include if
they get up to the final tier.
Oh wow, old timey title cards.
Because they also have film reel stands that have been introduced in the stretch goals as well.
So yeah, that might make sense.
The future, whatever, title cards.
But yes, that was Jimmy's lift on this.
And I question how many, if any, of these ideas came from Jimmy.
Now, let me counter a little bit and say from what I heard,
because here and there we've all known people who've worked at that show.
What I heard is that people saw like, all right, after the show,
a writer's meeting is occurring with him and a couple people,
and they are going through to nightmares stuff.
I think it's, but what's really weird is that I think maybe it did all come from him.
And yet felt generic, even if it was his idea.
Between the five of us, we know a fair amount of people who have worked on that show.
A lot of them left or were let go right before this project started in earnest.
By following up with some of those people,
I've sort of cracked a timeline of how quickly this thing might have come together.
Because it does feel like even in possibly June or July, this thing was not even a notion.
And by August, it's announced and September tickets are on sale.
But yeah, I mean, I just, I don't know if it's.
I believe, let me put it this way.
I can fully believe that Jimmy Fallon was personally rubber stamping every major idea in this.
OK, I would just like it doesn't make sense, though, that if he's the one giving the ideas,
he's going to choose the least interesting stuff that doesn't come straight from the public's
idea or the public's idea of the tonight show.
Maybe. I mean, yeah, it's should we just should we should we try to dig into this in earnest?
Sure. And I have a video walkthrough queued up to sort of remind myself, Ben, you have the audio.
You took as well. But let's say we were trying to figure out how to all meet.
It was Ben and I and Sarah, who you guys have met.
And we were all trying to figure out what the best meeting place is.
Ben says, I'm here at the entrance for the event.
I go, where is the entrance exactly?
He went, I don't know. There were a bunch of signs on the subway directing me.
Now, this is like Rockefeller Center, Times Square area.
There are a lot of trains that go to this area.
Ben seemingly took the right line to the right exit that directed him straight to the door.
Sarah and I maybe spend 20 minutes trying to figure out how to get to this.
30 Rock is like a very big building.
I had been led to believe this thing was like taking up empty office space in 30 Rock,
which is part of what I find fascinating about the idea of Two Nightmares is like,
oh, it's like two birds, one stone.
Jimmy wants to further reach out, brand every corner of the universe in his image,
in his twisted worldview.
But also perhaps there have been mass layoffs within the NBC Universal Company
and there is unoccupied office space that needs to be monetized.
We got to do something with floor three, yes.
Yes. So we walked to main 30 Rock and trying to, from the website,
follow the directions to where the entrance is.
Then I realized, oh, this is not in the main 30 Rock building.
This is part of 30 Rockefeller Plaza,
which basically encompasses like, I don't know, a three or four block area, Ben.
I believe so.
There's like this sort of famous 30 Rock ice skating rink is right behind the main building,
which is where Jimmy does his show, which is where SNL tapes.
So we've now walked through the entrance to the exit of that building
and realized it's not in that building at all.
Now the dream has died of I'm going to experience
Jimmy Fallon's twisted nightmare in the very same building where Jimmy Fallon works.
We're going to cross the skating rink.
30 Rockefeller Plaza is a little bit of like an outdoor mall as well.
Yeah.
So walking by different like flagship retail locations and restaurants
and then getting basically to, I think it's called Atlas Plaza,
which is sort of where the tree goes.
Is that right, Ben?
Yeah.
Is that where do we remember?
Where is that?
Was the supermodel cafe?
Oh, that's a great question.
Was that in that fashion cafe?
Excuse me.
The fashion cafe, right.
That was a supermodel themed restaurant.
It had to be a right around there.
Is there a big Barnes and Noble around there?
There isn't.
I think there maybe was at some point in time.
Okay.
But Jason is bragging that he wants to go there and read a book.
Well, Mr. Book here.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
Oh, is there a bookstore near there?
Oh, I'd love to read.
I read the other landmark I know is there's an outlet of Magnolia Bakery
and I don't want to go on a tear about banana pudding, which is delicious.
I was shocked when I did eat there and I'm like, oh my God, this is amazing.
You're shocked the banana pudding was delicious?
No, I was shocked that it was like, oh, this is like lives up to the hype.
Oh, okay.
You had heard about that specific banana pudding
and it was as good as you thought it would be.
Yes.
Okay. Well.
So I'm trying to figure out where this is.
I mean, this is the problem is that like there's a little bit of like
fuzzy math about what gets to call itself part of 30 Rock
because there are these annex buildings.
There is this sort of like downstairs food court underneath the rink.
30 Rock is such a like legendary address.
But not everything there is.
It sounds like plenty is like really cruddy and mundane.
Yeah.
So we're immediately in this sort of annex building.
Then going down to the basement where there is,
I want to say like a Banana Republic, Ben,
do you remember what the clothing store was?
Yeah, it was a Banana Republic.
And there was a burger place.
Guys, we were in a fucking basement to go see.
We're in a basement.
Stupid bullshit.
And it feels immediately realized, oh, this is like empty retail space.
Oh, God.
That's what this is.
This is clearly like and then we met up with a friend afterwards
and was telling him about this event and he was like,
I have heard for a fact that they're really struggling to fill
those spaces across the 30 Rock buildings,
especially the annex ones.
Since the pandemic, I bet this whole thing was born out of
what's a thing we can do to get something in here immediately
and like turbocharged sales.
Now, I've gone down a bit of a rabbit hole.
I have not found anything to back this up.
I don't know, but like the second I saw it was like,
oh, this is clearly where four businesses used to be.
The whole thing made a lot more sense.
Interesting.
So like it's a spirit Halloween.
Yeah.
It's Jimmy Fallon spirit Halloween.
I like the idea that it used to be like a TJ Maxx
and now it's a Jimmy Fallon maze.
That's what it feels like.
A TJ Maxx next to a Ross next to a Burlington Coat Factory
and that's a lot of floor space.
That's like the mall by the Portillo's in Buena Park.
You just listed all three of those things.
AKA paradise.
That's right.
The 30 Rock Plaza is a little maybe more like the New York equivalent of the Americana.
Where it wants to have this air of being a little more upscale.
Right, right.
Which I also think has then made it a struggle for them to fill that space
because they don't want to put a spirit Halloween in there.
They think that will ding the prestige of the location
but doing something that's maybe more synergistic
and vertically integrated within the company does not feel that way.
The weirdly kind of intense security check-in.
You know, you're in this underground mall
in what feels like it's about to transition to an entrance to the F train
and the lines were all sort of bifurcated and split around corners.
We went to a person who was wearing a To Nightmares shirt.
She said, no, you have to check in with that person first
and then she'll send you back here.
There was a lot of that and then you're in a line that then is cut off
and then you're told to transfer from one line to the other line.
I was trying to explain to Ben.
I said, Ben, remember you're a journalist.
Take notes.
We're going to have to explain all of this.
And I said, on PTR, the theming of the queue is very important.
Unskippable, some might say.
Sure.
It depends if it's unskippable.
Depends.
We, of course, have Race from New York where the queue is
a replica of these very buildings, the 30 Rock experience.
And it made me yearn for the nonstop excitement of that queue.
Being in the real version of it, poorly run with people who seem stressed out.
Ben, do you remember your immediate take on the attendees?
Yes, I was taking in who was there with us
trying to think about what are their lives?
What brought them here today?
I know why I'm here.
And it seemed like it wasn't a lot of New Yorkers.
It seemed like a lot of tourists, which makes sense for the area.
And my guess was that some few different concierge service people
have been, you know, they've been given a hundred dollar bill under the table
to start pointing people over to the frigging Jimmy Fallon experience.
Because the sense I was getting was that it was, yeah, this is this is striking me as like
people who are in their hotel lobby and are looking at the pamphlets that, you know,
sometimes when you stay especially at chain hotels, they'll have pamphlets for local things
that you can go and do.
The brochure rack.
Exactly.
I love the brochure rack.
Yeah, it was a coin toss for some of these people between taking a day trip to the Hudson
Valley Lego land or to Nightmares, which only takes up 30 minutes of their time all in.
Did you guys consider bailing to just go to Nintendo New York, the big Nintendo store?
It is right there.
Yeah, we didn't consider it.
We were very serious.
We had our press passes inside the brim of our caps.
The doors.
Yeah.
Yes.
You said press and VIP.
You had both tabs.
VIP flex.
Ben also, because he was waiting there while we were trying to figure out where the entrance was,
sent a video.
Yeah, there were like a group of maybe 10 to 12 shrouded hooded figures that walk through
the lobby into the entrance of the Jimmy Fallon experience.
And I initially was like, am I going to have to fucking wear a stinky shroud or something?
Is that going to be part of this?
But Griffin, I think, correctly guessed later that that was probably the people who were part
of the experience in costume, covering themselves up to be able to get in to get into place.
They were like complete Grim Reaper robes that looked like Ghost of Christmas yet to
come in Muppet Treasure Island, where there's just a void.
You can see nothing specific to not ruin the surprise.
But it did immediately make clear, oh, there's no back entrance.
These scare actors just have to walk through the same shitty hallways the rest of us,
with hoods over their heads, to get in through the front and quickly assume their places.
Now, this is a specific element of Halloween Horror Nights, where if you go at the right time,
you can catch a shift change.
You're like 30 minutes on, 30 minutes off.
And I don't think that's a thing we've said yet.
This is like Halloween Horror Nights creative involved in this experience.
Is that confirmed?
I believe it.
What he said, Jason said it, so.
Oh, me?
According to the Sheridan press?
I saw it in the marketing material that it is.
That makes sense.
You mentioned like a cross platform Comcast Endeavor,
and I think it was like all under one roof.
You know, one division of Comcast and another working together.
Well, here's one company I saw credited on this, RWS Global.
We offer everything and everyone you need to deliver an unmatched
guest experience from ideation operation anywhere in the world.
Hmm, very specific to learn about what this company does.
Yes.
Here are some things they have listed on their site.
MSC Cruises.
Ferrari World Abu Dhabi.
Oh, yeah, we know Ferrari World.
They just list Halloween experiences in general,
and the photo is from SeaWorld Howl-O-Scream.
Oh, right, right, right.
Yes.
OK, so that's.
They did the Friends experience in New York,
which I think has been quite successful.
Which I assume you guys all did regardless of,
you know, we didn't send you to do it.
We should have.
We actually skipped it this week just because we were doing To Nightmares,
but usually that is a weekly hangout for us.
Well, you know, you live in.
We just get together for coffee there.
That's kind of just what we do on a weekly basis.
Yeah.
You guys live in New York City.
Your lives are the Friends experience.
Yeah, this is true.
You're living it.
You meet at a coffee shop or you meet in a fountain.
I mean, this is interesting.
There are a lot of like there's some pretty respectable credits here,
but like it seems like they do the stage shows at Hershey, Pennsylvania,
that they work at some degree on the Radio City Christmas Spectacular.
I don't know if they are associated with Horror Nights or not,
or this is just getting folded into a certain degree
because it is part of the universal portfolio.
Well, there's a lot of these third party logistics companies
that do like some of the more grunt work stuff
in terms of bringing a show or a themed experience to life.
A lot of these are outsourced.
Well, we're going to have to dig in.
We're going to have to send some emails
to really figure out who's responsible for this.
Well, when they say the people behind Halloween Horror Nights,
they mean that like it's somebody who like plugged in a strobe light, you know?
Sure.
Well, it's the cloak manufacturer, you know, they got to get the cloaks.
We use Halloween Horror Nights branded cloaks, yes.
Yeah, get people on and off stage, you know?
I did think this was one of the more kind of abrasive security processes
for any sort of experience like this I've ever come across.
Jesus.
It was very disorganized.
I mean, everyone I worked there was doing their best job in a weird space
that also is like there are people walking through these hallways
who are just getting off from work,
like working that as an office building and are frustrated
that like to get from their office to the subway,
they have to walk through a queue for a haunted house.
But there were a couple things that jumped out to me.
One, they extensively asked everyone if they had knives or pepper spray.
Specifically, it was just those two things.
And if you have them, you need to check them in with us
and leave them here before you go in.
And then there were a lot of pre-warnings
about things you could or couldn't do.
And most of them seemed to be about what would scare the actors.
Well, I couldn't tell if it was in response to some bad incidents
that have already happened or not, if that's just projection on my part.
But they were like, you are allowed to film this.
Please feel free to film the entire experience.
Take any photos you want.
Do not use the flash.
It will scare the actors.
The actors are not allowed to touch you.
Don't worry about that.
If an actor does touch you, please let us know.
But also in exchange, you are not allowed to touch the actors.
That will scare them.
They kept saying these things about like, if you do this,
these scare actors will be scared.
They did not get the bravest set of scare actors, it sounds like.
They got scared at the drop of a hat, like a Laurel and Hardy movie.
Maybe that was the problem.
There was a miscommunication and they got scared actors instead of scare actors.
Oh, yeah, wanted scared actors.
Don't yank their sashes and don't touch their fezzes.
Right.
Final security checkpoint.
Just one thing that has never happened to me before
as a person who wears a hat almost every day of my life.
They asked me as I walked through the metal detector to take my hat off and shake it.
What?
They were like, share your hat above your head so we can
in case a knife or pepper spray falls out that's been tucked
top your dome.
What did you do if you if you like duct taped a knife to the top
or the top of your hat, wouldn't it be secured enough to not come out when you shook it?
It was interesting.
It just set a tone of wow, this feels more like the TSA
than any sort of theme parky experience I've ever been part of.
And then I would say that vibe continued through the experience itself.
OK, so we sent a skeptical Ben through a TSA line in an office building,
which was sad for like lack of filled retail space.
More than spooky Halloween vibes.
Yes, you did.
All right.
Well, I cop to it.
I owe you an apology and I haven't even heard about the experience itself yet.
The first room I want to say I thought was pretty good.
Maybe it was lowered expectations, but I walked in there and immediately felt like
this is more holistically themed than I expected.
It was a sort of dare I say it, Hollywood Hotel Tower of Terror-esque vibe.
It was like decrepit old building.
And you're waiting for a kind of grand elevator at the end of the room.
You're sent in with a group.
So we were with maybe five other people we didn't know.
Does that sound right, Ben?
So we're all in this sort of holding room.
That's like the final loading room before you're going to go in.
And there's a long Jimmy audio track that's being looped.
That seems to have a couple of variations, but he's basically saying something like
you didn't record this part.
I think your recording started right when we entered the experience itself.
But he's saying something like, oh no, all my To Nightmares start like this.
There's a really creepy old elevator.
Hang on a second.
This is the beginning.
There's no explanation of what a To Nightmare is.
Not that there needs to be.
I'm not a dumb person.
I can make the leap of why it's...
Although, hang on.
Can I?
All right.
I guess the host of The Tonight Show would have To Nightmares.
That is the single way in which it's been made specific.
It's something only Jay Cohn and Carson Barr, Steve Allen, knew.
Everyone else just has regular Nightmares.
No one else has To Nightmares.
I couldn't barely knew it.
Yeah.
That's what's such a shame is he only sort of got to experience To Nightmares.
The biggest of all, I guess.
But there's no justification of what a To Nightmare is.
They invoke the word.
They make you hear the word To Nightmare.
But do not explain what a To Nightmare is as opposed to a nightmare.
No.
Zero preface until we walk into that room.
There's no Jimmy Fallon like, hi, welcome to my To Nightmares video to set the tone.
I was waiting for a Spielberg E.T. ride-esque.
There's none of that.
So you're in this room.
I think I had to point out like, wait, I think that's Jimmy's voice.
It's kind of playing like in a loop at a low volume.
And he's just sort of saying like, oh, no, all my nightmares start like this.
Oh, no, this is like a bad sign.
Like that kind of vibe, which let's say also he's been pushing this thing really hard on
The Tonight Show every night for like a couple weeks.
Wow.
He was introducing a new character, which would then get posted all over the social media,
a proprietary character from To Nightmares.
And his framework for that every night was him going like, guys, I had another To Nightmare
last night.
Like trying to present it as if not like, hey, I'm really excited.
We have the spooky experience at 30 Rockefeller Center.
But like rubbing the back of his neck like, hey, I'm sorry to the audience.
I didn't sleep all night.
Had another To Nightmare.
And in this To Nightmare, and he's introducing element by element as if the backstory is
these are just the last 30 nights of Jimmy Fallon's attempts to sleep.
Yeah, he did the exact same segment for at least 10 nights in a row with the same format
where he describes a To Nightmare that he had.
And it's just real details of a spooky story that is not, that's kind of like a PG, like
for 11 year olds type spooky story.
And then there's a fake and then it builds to a torrent and then like, and the monster
said, he said, tickets are available for Jimmy Fallon's To Nightmares.
They did the exact same sketch for 10 nights in a row, which is again, really where you
like, boy, you imagine that like an up and coming, if you're graduating college and your
dream is to write comedy for the biggest show in town or even like, you know, they've they've
as we've said, they've hired many of the funniest people I've ever met.
And then here's what the actual contents of the show are.
10 nights of the same nightmare sketch.
The only change being that this time it's a scary farmer instead of a scary gas station guy.
And look, I don't know if you guys have talked about it at all in any of your
Haunt Cast the Fright episodes, since it is kind of a big news story right now.
But the sort of the fumble of Universal possibly revealing the design of the upcoming Wolfman
movie for the first time as a walk around character connected to Horror Nights,
but not even within the maze at like an open air direct sunlight stand up like pop up kiosk
that looks terrible for one day.
Yeah, for one day.
But then like, of course, 20 people film it on their phone and it goes viral across every
like hardcore horror movie fan website.
And they're like, what is this fucking design?
And even the people who are generous and are like, well, that's like a rubber mask.
Obviously, it's going to look better in the movie.
They're like, it still looks shitty.
Fallon was making the same mistake every night, which I don't actually I will say,
I don't think I have any criticisms, major criticisms of any of the character designs
in the attraction.
But after we went on it and I went back and rewatched some of the videos of him
introducing them on The Tonight Show, they all look worse in that format in high def
standing behind him, brightly lit or in like a standalone Instagram grid picture.
Right. It's like it's like when I saw the Minotaur with the lights on.
Yeah.
And I felt even worse for not having done the escape room.
Like it's not the great way to see it.
No, no, I would have set up more.
I mean, because this is another just not to be like persnickety here.
But I felt unclear while walking through this.
If this is meant to represent one horrible night sleep for Jimmy Fallon,
or is he doing sort of a roundup of here are different nightmares I've had before
because this intro, the non intro at the beginning where he's like, oh no,
all my nightmares start like this makes it feel like,
okay, you are about to go on the waking nightmare.
One long nightmare where all of these things happen.
But then I have a whole other question.
Why are we here?
Why are you there?
How are you in his brain?
There's no attempt to justify why we're seeing his nightmares, his nightmares come to life.
No, I mean, you get through that first room, you go into an elevator.
This last sort of employee says like, okay, everyone go through this room.
When you get out the other side of the elevator, you're going to meet, I think her name was Tina,
who will be your tour guide.
I warn you, she's a little spooky.
And then we go into this elevator alone and they sort of do a half-assed version
of like a haunted mansion through lights.
We make you feel like you are being lowered even though you're not moving anywhere.
No, it's not an elevator.
It's just made to look like an elevator.
That room does not move a inch.
No, and there's some Jimmy audio happening over that.
And then the doors open and this woman comes out
who's sort of doing a version of like a Tower of Terror bellhop, spooky bellhop kind of thing.
But more than anything does kind of feel like a TSA employee
who is constantly having to yell at us like, no, this way, this way.
Because this is an attraction that needs to turn people through so fully
that you have no opportunity to like explore rooms on your own pace.
It feels like you are rushed in and out of every room.
Every single room basically has the exact same rhythm of a door opens.
You have your introduction in the liminal space of Jimmy Fallon being like,
in one of my worst nightmares, there's an alien chasing me in the woods.
And then like door opens and it's the woods.
You're in indoor woods.
Right. And this woman is like, quickly, guys, quickly.
And you just have to make it from one corner of the room to the other.
And it's really like, pasta, pasta.
Let's keep it moving.
And there's some decent set design.
There's some really like good looking spaces
and you do not have any chance to actually take it in
because this woman keeps being like, hey, come on, you're falling behind.
Let's go, let's go.
Hurry up, faster, faster.
And it's like no slight on this woman.
It felt very much like the the Back to the Future escape room
we did at City Walk Orlando, where clearly sometimes they would push us
to the next room because the group behind us had solved a puzzle faster than we had.
And yeah, by that, you mean you mean that which that the level keeper did, correct?
Correct. I'm sorry.
You just heard the episode and are remarking on that.
What you heard.
Yes, I was on that trip, but then I feel like the level keeper did some of the things
and I did some of the things.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yes.
No, some things you arbitrarily sat out and stayed at your hotel
and then we met up with this ghost and you guys never had a chance to meet.
Right.
And we each took a different live show and didn't pass each other in the hallway.
I never met backstage.
There's no photo of the two of you.
Yes.
It's a shame because I'm a big fan.
Yeah, I think the cowbell thing, I think his voice is really consistent.
Oh, yeah, it's his thing.
Yes.
Yeah, I love his thing.
But no, it had that feeling of like you have your own personalized tour guide
and their job is to get you into the next room in that liminal space as quickly as
possible so that the following group can do that room.
I was going to say, are there cues?
Because like you're talking about doors opening, a normal horror night's maze or not maze
is all the doors are all open.
There's no cue or doors open.
There's an organic flow.
Right, so you just kind of walk at a pace, which you still,
depending on how many people are there, you don't get a good chance to sit and look at
everything.
The whole thing felt it.
Look, it felt somewhat emblematic of New York real estate.
You want to do things in New York, going to be in a tiny box crammed in.
You're not going to have some spatial, some backyard where it's like, all right,
this is the New York real estate version of a horror night maze.
The rooms are really tiny.
It's kind of built like a railroad apartment.
It's really cramped.
There is no organic flow.
So I think the first room you get to that was a little fun off of the elevator was what
purported to be Jimmy Fallon's bedroom.
Now you might be wondering what size bed does Jimmy Fallon have?
A twin, of course.
Yes, I would say this does not have the same sheets that I have from high school.
I think he literally says that, doesn't he?
He does say that.
Yes.
And it's odd because it's like, it's a very easy fix to just be like,
my dream, I'm in my childhood bedroom for some reason.
But he doesn't say that.
It very much looks like the bedroom of a 15 year old.
But there's booze bottles everywhere.
Broken flippies slammed against the wall.
Watch your feet, everybody.
Flippies.
The failed flippy models.
Take all, take all your rings off or you're in for a scare.
This is all the result of one fall of mine.
I mean, this is the problem is, we certainly, we can get into this, but
we're joking about like, well, what are the nightmares of Jimmy Fallon?
How do you make this?
The public doesn't have any association with how he presents himself.
Yes.
We all could very quickly come up with 10 rooms that I think represent real scares of Jimmy Fallon.
Which is just a room that is all table corners.
Waiting, waiting for the phone call for the opening weekend gross of Taxi.
Waiting for the phone call for the opening weekend gross of Fever Pitch.
A press pit of only Rolling Stone reporters.
I had a bad, I had such a bad dream.
I had a dream that there was a writer's strike and all the other hosts agreed
to pay their entire staffs out of their pocket for the duration.
And not just for two weeks, which was my plan.
Oh no.
A closing down Virgin Megastore that only has seedy copies on clearance of the bathroom wall.
This first room got me a little, I don't want to say excited, but it was like
you're in a room, you're not moving through.
It's very clear.
At some point, they're going to open a door and say, okay, onto the next room,
which is how this whole thing works.
Like you're sanctioned to one room until they very quickly bring you over to the next.
Why?
Why if this is, if there's a precedent, if there's maze after maze and it is quote
from the Horror Nights people, why do they do it with doors and rooms?
I think it has to be that the space is just not fucking equipped for this.
I don't know.
Like I was, but this first room, you're not forced to run from one end to the other.
You're in the bedroom.
There's a longer audio track playing.
And then he's like, and in my nightmare,
I'm stuck.
I got caught in the bed.
And then they have an effect that's basic, but I found a little effective where like the,
the quote unquote wood of like the headboard of his bed is actually some kind of screen.
And there are scare actors behind it who are pushing their hands through
as if they're trapped in the headboard of the bed.
And I was like, that's a little spooky.
It's a little atmospheric.
I think one person jumps out from some corner of this room.
And then our tour guide is like, okay, quickly next room.
Then you're in the hallway.
You're in the book again.
I want to get the order of these, but every other room after this is basically save for
the werewolf one, which is the biggest exception of all in all care areas,
quickly run through one end to the other end.
I think that maybe the being stuck in bed is a manifestation of, I think this real nightmare
is that he slept in one day and there was a day where he,
he didn't have three separate shows to host.
And thus he had to spend the day with his family.
I tried to take a photo of something that was under the bed and it came out
too blurry to make out, but there were my kids.
They're reaching for me.
They want their dad to be around for two hours.
Oh no.
What are their names again?
We will not credit them, but Ben and I reached out to someone.
We know who used to work on the show and asked them if they had any insider knowledge.
And they said, I imagine one of the rooms is Jimmy forced to spend time with his family.
Wow.
All right.
It was kind of guessing, but
it's like, this is like, if you guys can make this out,
this is like what the text looks like on the screens.
It's like Nosferatu or something.
Right. Appearing in this like glowing way.
And the text of the first one is being in the middle.
I'll try to do it my best, Jimmy being in the middle of the woods is bad,
but you know, it's even worse being in the middle of the woods while being haunted by aliens.
Like that's the level of energy he gives it.
Haunted by them?
I'm sorry. It did say hunted. I'm sorry.
It did.
Okay. Oh, sorry.
All right.
Door opens tour guides like quick, quick, quick.
Then you see a board with a bunch of like newspaper clippings
of like crimes and conspiracies going on.
I did notice there was a missing sign where the missing information is it's a picture
of Jimmy Fallon from some sketch while he's dancing.
Tight pants.
And it says missing.
There we go.
Yeah.
Jimmy Fallon, 49, 59, 192 pounds, short brunette, bowl cut, eye color hazel wear,
tight white pants, striped shirt, last seen tonight show rehearsal.
There's a phone number here we could try calling later.
But so there's like a little bit of theming there.
And then you're basically like, once you're past this wall, you're just in quote unquote
the woods, which maybe takes up all of 25 feet and there's flashing lights.
And there are like two aliens that jump out at you.
And this becomes the pattern that basically every room has, which is door opens,
maybe one wall of light theming.
You're told to get to the other end of the room as quickly as possible.
And two people are going to jump out where you can almost set your clock
to the timing of where the scares are going to be.
You can see them coming.
Yes.
They're positioned in a way where they reset to the same spot and they're not well hidden
in a way that I think is a choice that was made to not overly scare people,
to give them some expectation of what's to come.
So that means each group really only, I think like each time I felt like
the characters popped out twice more or less, right Griffin?
Like no more than twice.
Two jumps per room.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because that maybe that's why you have to have groups in it once to all experience
just the two set scare actors.
Because like there's so many scares happening in a horror night's maze.
If you just walk through it like a line, you're going to get some scare.
But it feels like it would be very easy to walk through this whole thing
in a straight line without getting scares because there's so few.
Yeah, even our group of like eight or 10, depending on where you were in the line,
which is not fixed and everyone gets scrambled up in those liminal hallway spaces
before you enter the next room.
It's like sometimes you'd walk through a room and be like,
I was not in a good position for the timing.
I missed the jumps, you know?
And you like watch the person ahead of you get them.
But then what you're seeing is that person resetting back to their place.
And then it happens again for the person behind you.
It's also sort of hurried and they're trying to get in there.
And as Ben said, you basically enter every room and you can immediately clock either,
oh, there are two open spaces here that someone is going to jump out of,
or you can see them and you're waiting for like, when are they going to jump?
Or the other trick a lot of the rooms use is like there are 10 of some kind of creature
and eight of them are dressed up mannequins and two of them are going to move.
And you're like, which two move?
Is it possible that there at some point were more scare actors in this experience
and many, many of them quit due to Jimmy Fallon's To Nightmares being a toxic work environment?
The rooms are small, like you couldn't fit more in.
Another important thing about the scare actors,
they never actually scream or make any kind of noise.
When they're making some kind of action, it's pre-recorded.
Yeah, that's kind of a hallmark of a lot of horns.
Oh, I was thinking that you were going to say like,
they didn't want to yell because they're desperate to be liked.
They want to be liked so much, they don't want to yell at you.
I did hear the familiar voice of one Papa Higgins doing the voiceover.
Higgins senior.
Gas station dad, which made me really happy to see that Higgins is getting
an additional paycheck for doing voiceover for this while all of the actors
are getting paid less because they're non-speaking.
That's a really nice balance.
Nice trick.
Is that true though? Is most of universal pre-recorded audio tracks?
Well, it's to do with timing and consistency, but it's also so that
someone isn't working a multi-hour shift screaming and just killing their voice
that they're working there for like two months or six weeks or whatever.
It depends though.
A couple of the rooms have like semi-extensive dialogue though
that is being delivered in theory by people whose faces you're seeing.
Is it all a tribute to Jimmy Fallon's lip sync battle?
Yeah.
Another part of his empire that hasn't come up yet.
Quite possibly.
Alien room, the woods were just kind of generic.
You're sort of like immediately feeling the come down of,
oh, is this what every room's going to be?
The setup of the bedroom works a little better where you're just like,
can we all stand here in place and then have some spooky things happen around us?
Versus this like, go, go, go, you're on a mission, but there's nothing to accomplish.
You know, it did feel almost closer to an escape room in the intensity of it,
except you had no agency.
And the aliens themselves kind of look like Cirque du Soleil versions of Xenomorphs.
In the moment, they're fine.
When you see the full light versions of them, they look kind of shitty.
The second room is far and away the most interesting.
The second room, the text in the hallway reads,
and I just want to restate you're in each of these hallways for at least 30 seconds.
You just wait for the next.
It's like you're on a high, like a middle school field trip
and the tour guide is like, I won't start talking until everyone has landed.
And it's like they're waiting for your whole group to make it past
the last room into the space and then they close the door and then the video starts
and then the door opens and then you go to the next room.
Uh, this, this text just says there's a serial killer on the loose
and they'll kill anything that moves.
And then this room you get into and it's like weird supply closet,
like janitorial, like toilet paper rolls and like cleaning supplies.
And then you're in this like concrete brick room
that is filled with a hashtag the panda stuff.
Okay, here we go.
There is like a disembodied hashtag mascot head.
There's like hearts drawn on the wall and what seems like blood,
like massacred hashtag merchandise.
And then there's like a guy staying there who jumps out,
the first scare actor and he's seemingly like chained to the wall.
He's wearing the body of a hashtag costume, the panda's suit
and is yelling at you like, she's crazy.
She wants to kill everybody.
Okay, I'm going to throw things to Ben now and say, and ask what,
what in the world did you know at this point about hashtag the panda?
I knew nothing.
So what I mean, what else is there to know?
I mean, all I knew is that it was a panda.
So I just made the leap of like, okay,
this is a serial killer that wears a panda costume.
Ah, okay.
Right, because her victim is wearing the body suit,
but his head is uncovered and he's screaming like, please help me.
She's on the loose.
And then you whip around and the other side of this very small room,
there is a woman with pigtails.
She is wearing like a baseball like ringer tee.
She's got a giant knife and she's wearing a panda mask,
but it's not the classic hashtag mascot head.
It's like almost like a purge style version of a panda mask
with stitched up mouth and blood on its face.
And she's just going like, sort of like stabbing motion at you.
I feel like hashtag the panda has outlived hashtags.
I agree.
Well, they basically don't exist anymore.
I mean, they're not super useful anymore.
Yeah, they do nothing.
No, it's almost like you would make a hashtag joke
if you were a Seinfeld-esque out of it comedian
who doesn't actually pay attention to what's happening on social media now.
Have we ever discussed what the origins of hashtag the panda are?
Because I know, I think when Chase Mitchell was on your guys show,
he talked about how part of the bit was that it was funny to make one of the writers
wear the costume and dance a lot and get really tired and sweaty.
Yes.
That's the entire point of hashtag the panda.
The hashtag, it's almost like an anti-character
that has now become a fundamental character
in all of the themed entertainment you can go visit of Jimmy Fallon.
After we go through this, Ben, I'm like, did you get the hashtag the panda thing?
And he's like, what are you talking about?
Can I explain this?
And he was like, is this a popular segment?
I was like, no.
I don't even know the last time they've done it on the show.
I remember this being kind of a thing 10 years ago, but never went super viral.
I think it just lined up with the theme park ride
and them needing a proprietary character they could trademark.
But I dug in because I was curious.
I was like, where did this actually come out of?
There was some thing like 10 years ago, eight years ago,
where there was a panda at some zoo that they were worried was depressed or wasn't mating.
And they put a TV in its pen to try to cheer up its spirit.
And the bit, which I think is kind of funny, was like,
oh, Fallon is now going to do a segment of his monologue every night
that is jokes narrow cast to this panda.
And then they would cut to a feed of, quote unquote, the panda in its pen.
And it was a tonight show writer or at that point, a late night writer in the costume.
And as Fallon would make the jokes, hashtag would get excited and dance.
And they'd be like, we're doing it.
We're cheering the panda up, which is kind of a funny bit.
So how do we all feel just hearing this right now?
Do we feel good?
Because I feel like this urge to actually scream.
This sucks.
Here's the worst part of it.
OK, so then they do this segment a lot.
I guess it gained some popularity.
Fallon announces the panda is now going to be our official mascot.
And we want and that was the other thing.
It was every night he wanted listeners to tweet a hashtag Fallon Panda
to make it go viral, to try to get, I think, the zoo to let him visit or some shit, right?
But there was some hashtag campaign.
And then after a couple of weeks of this, they do a segment on the show that's like,
he's now our official mascot and we want to name him
and we want to let the viewers vote on what his name will be.
And the viewers voted for hashtag.
And it was almost like a Boaty McBoatface thing of everyone trolling him and being like,
you're pushing this hashtag thing so much.
Hashtag Fallon Panda, what should his name be?
And they're like, hashtag the panda.
OK, and from that point on, there's basically been no bit.
And I dug into what are the last couple of times they've done hashtag.
And it basically seems like once a year they will have hashtag come out and do a dance.
And then the end of the segment is hashtag takes off his head
and reveals that it is a celebrity.
And the implication is, oh, Lenny Kravitz has been hashtagged the whole time.
They've done this like 10 times.
But they did this with the whale on.
This is so the most done thing ever.
And then hashtag is not.
So hashtag was never like a panda who likes social media or anything.
It's just there's no there isn't a bit.
There's no so far away from the bit.
It's abstract into nothingness.
And here is a room that is devoted to a hashtag, the panda fan who is so chaotic
and unhinged in her love of hashtag that she started chaining men
and making them wear panda suits and torturing them.
There's like, I mean, I'll send you guys the photo,
but the wall felt like Buffalo Bill style shit.
Right.
Of like her insane ramblings of like hashtag fan, though.
And she's a hand.
She's for sure a fan of hashtag.
It's not like a writer dressed up as hashtag.
It's had enough of Jimmy's shit like.
Mike, great question.
I wish they gave us more of an explanation.
OK, I read you what the prelude.
It could be any.
That's what I extrapolate this to be.
Right.
For Ben, he's just like that room was chaos.
What does that mean?
And for me, I was like, well, this is the first room
that actually has something to do with The Tonight Show.
It's interesting.
It's almost like an evil masked singer or something.
Like the Fox show where they have a celebrity under the.
Yeah.
I don't think it's something as dark as what I described,
but it could be anything.
The point is, you know, obviously we're laughing.
We're loving it.
This is we understand it.
It's successful on so many levels.
And I, you know, why?
Why scream, Ben?
I don't understand.
No, you're right.
Obviously, a smash success.
Now you understand the full context.
This is a room that basically doesn't have hiding spaces.
Like once you get past the first custodial rack sort of corner,
then you're just in a room where like in one side
there is a woman with a knife and another side there's a guy in a cage.
And they're both like cowering a little bit and then jumping out more
and both speaking in these prerecorded audio bits.
So if we psychoanalyze this as one of Jimmy's nightmares,
he is one of his greatest nightmares.
One of his greatest to nightmares is that he's afraid of the hashtag on some level,
whether he feels tied down to the comedy of it, perhaps like.
Or but it's also it feels distanced from him where what he's afraid of is
someone being too fanatical about hashtag.
So maybe he's like, yeah, he's worried about his fans.
There's a lack of viewpoint that's coming very clear at this point.
You know, at Horror Nights in the past two years,
they've had like a walk around David S. Pumpkins.
And I feel like whether you like that sketch or not,
like it's a pretty distinctive look.
And someone goes, oh, it's yes, David S.
Pumpkins got the Halloween suit.
He's got the big hair.
You know, I don't I don't know that people are giving that same reaction
to just seeing hashtag the panda paraphernalia.
No, no, because you're not even seeing hashtag.
A thing that I think is barely known.
You're seeing things that are riffing on the supposed cultural influence of hashtag.
I mean, David S.
Pumpkins, I want to put a pin in that for a possible plus up conversation at the end of this.
But then the next hallway space, the text is,
I'm a talk show host in the 50s holding a puppy, but it bites me.
And I start to what?
And then exactly we're just these explanations are getting shorter.
You're sort of like more confused.
Once again, his like deliveries are really kind of like tossed off.
And then you enter what is kind of the most interesting room, Ben?
I don't know the most successful, but the most interesting.
Define interesting.
You are in the guts like the backstage area of a TV studio with a bunch of on air signs
and like mixing boards and like old school TVs mounted.
And you're like, oh, this is like 50s Rockefeller Center.
And then the TV screen comes on.
As Ben pointed out, this is the one point, the only point where Jimmy
appears visually in something he specifically did for this attraction.
Jimmy Fallon is on the TV screen in black and white sitting behind his tonight show desk,
but styled as if he is Steve Allen.
He is wearing glasses.
It is not him.
He's having a nightmare about being having the same job he has, but seven decades earlier.
And he is doing a classic talk show animal segment, right?
Holding this adorable little puppy.
And then he acts like the puppy bites him.
And then he's like writhing in pain.
He's like, oh, no.
Then the TVs go off.
In the room, there's sort of two big kind of like foggy glass panes.
That I guess are maybe supposed to replicate, like you're in the backstage area behind a curtain
and you can only see the silhouettes of what's happening.
Well, you're in the control room.
So you're like, you're looking out onto like, I guess maybe above the stage
of where the filming is happening.
You see a silhouette of a man writhing in pain and then it like morphs into a werewolf
in like what feels like it's just a projection, right?
Of like a shadow.
And then the two doors open up and a guy jumps out wearing a late night talk show suit
that is somewhat tattered with a werewolf head on.
I see.
Okay.
Animal segment gone awry instead of normal comical animal peas or something.
A werewolf scenario breaks out.
But yeah, I agree that no part of this nightmare should be that he does his job from today,
but in the fifties, because that was a time where functional alcoholism was celebrated.
That's one of his greatest dreams, not his nightmares.
If only he could time travel and work from then.
But there was no Mario Kart back then.
That's true.
I don't think this room is scary.
I don't think it's very effective.
In a way, it's the least scary because you're just watching the shadow happen and you're like,
well, the werewolf's going to jump out of there.
It's only a question of when the doors open.
You know, but I'm going to have the time from the doors opening to prep me for the guy jumping out.
But I did in this room go like, well, this is sort of maybe
the thought experiment of how this thing should work,
which is like a nightmare specific to being a talk show host.
Should this not all be in sort of like a spookier version of 30 Rock?
Is it not more interesting to make all of these spaces like fake
behind the scenes TV shit where then spooky stuff happens?
And I'm like, there's a little bit of like A to C I kind of like and like,
what's the thing that a talk show host has to do that could go awry in a scary way?
Well, you do animal segments.
What if an animal segment backfired?
Yeah, a chimp could rip your face off.
But even still, I'm like, a puppy doesn't turn you into a werewolf.
Right.
Why is it not you yourself, Jimmy?
Why is this in the 50s?
What are all these weird over thought steps in between?
Just like why does the why does a race through New York go to the moon?
It's and then there's a tube that gets you back
magically from the front of your of your Tonight Rider.
No, there's like there's an overshoot of the premise.
And then it doesn't have to be maybe maybe they would say,
wasn't that inside baseball or something?
But couldn't it be like people understand that like, I don't know, the lights caught on fire.
It's the nightmare of Saturday night and Jason Ryman's acclaimed sound is fucked.
The sound is fucked.
The actors are getting into fistfights.
All of these things definitely happened.
My counterpoint to it being to inside baseball would be
you're selling people an experience within 30 Rockefeller Plaza.
And throughout the idea, like, do you think this is just an add on ticket
cost to people who are already doing the tour?
Which is a very popular like New York tourist attraction
to go through the 30 Rock tour, which is excellent.
Yeah, I imagine there's a lot of spillover between the two.
In which case, don't you want something that's owning a little bit more like
this is the most historic building in television history?
Like, this is where you are.
I just want to play for you guys quickly.
Like, this is what you're seeing in the werewolf room,
which is like as if you are behind him while he's doing the show, like right behind his desk.
Seeing him in silhouette and you're seeing the TV screens, but you're seeing this
and then it turns into a werewolf.
And then, right, there's a long time of seeing the werewolf silhouette
and the lights go out, a guy jumps out, end of room, quickly, quickly onto the next one.
Yeah, so he's there.
You know where he's going to be.
But yeah, I'm totally with you that there's and also like with 30 Rock
and with this being a famous tourist attraction in general, I mean, just like
zombie pages, the pages all got zombified and there's dozens of them.
Scott will get to that, but that was another thing where we were like,
isn't this more fun if it's just Jimmy Fallon being like,
you know, there's one television studio here at 30 Rock that they say is haunted.
Nothing's filmed there in 70 years.
Sure, or his studio is haunted.
Right.
Like, do a Tower of Terror type thing where you're like something bad,
make up a fictional story of something bad happened in studio like 27F.
Right.
Have the big Atlas statue, the big metal Atlas holding up the world come to life and like
scare the poor, you know.
And then it's like Megalopolis.
Right.
And then, yeah, it just it seems like Jimmy's to Nightmares
are really based on a lot of horror movie tropes.
Well, here's the next one.
Maybe you should try
Subsplutient Time Tea or Melatonin before bed
instead of watching all these dank horror movies and having a bad work-life balance.
The next one is, I'm standing outside an old gas station in the middle of nowhere.
I have a really, really bad feeling about this place.
They're becoming like vaguer and vaguer,
less and less passionate every time.
It's just like, what's a basic sort of horror setup?
This also goes back to the things starting and seemingly his childhood bedroom,
then moving to like the woods where you're being hunted by aliens.
Then it's like hashtag the pandas biggest fans janitor basement,
then the 50s version of a television studio.
We're moving around so wildly where it's like,
I think Jimmy Vaughn primarily lives in upstate New York, Westchester these days,
like all millionaire celebrities,
multimillionaire celebrities who quote unquote live in New York actually do.
It's moving interchangeably between city stuff and rural stuff
in a way that really deprives it of any identity.
It gets specific to him a little and then as vague as could be.
Right, because this is the vaguest shit I've ever seen,
which is you enter the next room and it's just sort of like zombie movie gas station.
It's sort of post apocalyptic.
It feels like it would be in fallout or whatever.
It's any sort of like run down rusty gas station,
quote unquote in the middle of nowhere at night.
And then there's like a dad and a daughter who both have like weird makeup.
I don't even know how to describe it.
They're not supposed to be zombies or creatures.
They just both kind of have like spooky face paint and a little blood.
And they're standing by the pumps with knives and they,
I think this is Hagen's voice cameo.
Did Jimmy like play last of us on like PS5 or PS4 recently?
And he was just like, then we'll do a last of us.
It's a last of us.
And they're like, oh, I guess so.
That's where when you are saying that you have heard that Jimmy would hold
these writers from meetings at the end of work days.
I do believe he was there and was going like, come on guys, more ideas.
But everything feels like a first draft idea of just like, I don't know.
What's like a thing?
Aliens are scary.
I saw signs.
What if aliens were in the woods, you know?
Texas Chainsaw Massacre, rural scary nothing, you know?
Yeah.
Our tour guide on this one said something of like after his video intro played,
she's like, you know what's really scary?
Those rising gas prices.
Like she made a kind of universal tram tour style joke off of it.
And I was like, huh, I wonder if that's in our script.
I wonder if she's having fun.
Also in most of the other rooms that she's shepherding us through,
she was saying things and you couldn't make them out because the audio was so loud.
And I'm like, maybe there is funny interplay happening in the writing
and we're missing it every other time.
Right.
Wow.
I have a broader question for both of you.
Were either of you at any point scared?
There is one room where I actually felt like the scare actor kind of got me on timing.
And I think I even turned to them and went, well done.
Like involuntarily, I was like, whoop, you got me.
Okay.
All right.
That's something.
I think I had one of those too, where the timing lined up just right.
For the most part, I was making, because again, these were small rooms.
Small rooms.
So I was making really like direct eye contact with an actor who was supposed to have scared me.
And I didn't want to, I'm not like going to be a jerk about it.
So I would just kind of be like, just to give them a little nod
to sort of just be like, thanks for that.
There was a lot of that kind of like you're making direct eye contact with someone in a very small
room who has failed to scare you, who is now having to reset to a position three inches away
from where they currently are.
And you just kind of have to hold a look with them and say like, I see you.
I acknowledge you.
Thank you for your effort.
Wow.
We are performers too.
We understand.
We're cut from the same cloth.
Keep at it.
This is basically a jobs program for the New York improviser community.
I'm glad you all have a nice month and a half of work, you know?
Yeah, that sounds more stressful for me because I want to deliver for the performer.
It's like when you're seeing close up magic and you're right on top of the
performer and you want to like be like, oh, wow, look what you did.
Like, I know that like, if you're not giving the person that it feels bad.
So like, if you don't get scared, I would feel like shit.
This absolutely had this energy.
And I want to say, I thought every scare actor we came across was very committed,
like did their job well.
I think this is not the failing at all of any of the performers.
I think this thing is like designed poorly.
Like the Tonight Show starring Jimmy Fallon itself.
The individual efforts of all of the talented people working on the show
are somehow held back by something, something at the very top.
But yeah, it's like guy with a knife, woman with gas station handle.
I mean, I'm just like watching this walkthrough,
getting through the gas station room took less than 30 seconds.
And I've now seen 15 straight seconds of the screen in the liminal space
before the text comes up.
Like the reset times are so much longer than the scare times.
This one says there are creatures that look like they've been trapped for decades.
I don't think they're human.
Which we're just getting so vague now of like, what do you mean?
I had a dream where there was a shadow.
I was in a room and it wasn't fully lit.
I couldn't see the whole room.
Okay, that's all you need to know.
Go.
I genuinely don't even know how to explain this one.
I think it's supposed to be a rundown subway station.
And then there are creatures with like full unmoving masks
that look a little like Sam Raimi deadites.
But it's just like strobe lights flashing and then them jumping out at you.
Hmm.
I wonder if there was any consideration of being able to re-theme this next year
without the Jimmy Fallon IP.
Quite possibly.
I don't know.
Maybe they're not thinking that forward.
I think this has to have meant to be a subway station.
I don't know.
A couple times I would like see something I want to stop and take a picture of for posterity.
And I could feel how much I was stressing the tour guide out
that I was creating like a five to ten second lag.
Especially because I'm trying my hardest to make sure the flash
is not going to go off and scare the actors.
Scare the actors.
Yeah, this is so funny.
I don't think it's on purpose, but if it was,
this is the twisted mind of Jimmy Fallon.
If he created an inverse, a flippy of a haunted maze
where instead of the actors scaring you,
there's a bigger threat of you scaring the actors.
Blinding the actors with a phone flash and they trip over their own feet and fall over.
This is an interesting thing, though, because I don't go through these mazes
and I usually get scared in a traditional way.
I don't feel the feeling of guilt,
which is something that this is really, this is really outblowing in a way.
Oh, you need more of that.
Yeah, Mike, you need more of that in your life.
That's right.
And that's what this maze would bring out of me.
I don't want to speak for Ben, but I was feeling things walking through this.
I was feeling guilt, shame, regret, embarrassment, my proxy.
That's what good art does.
It was conjuring emotional responses.
The next text is rule number one of being in a cornfield.
Get out of the cornfield.
There's a killer scarecrow who will stop at nothing too, dot, dot, dot.
At this point, they're all relying really hard on these ellipses
that feels like they just couldn't land the plane on what the statement was.
Less of a cliffhanger and more like, I don't know.
Well, filling something later, you know, I feel like you kind of liked this room.
The cornfield.
Yeah, I mean, it was it had a bunch of like
like corn stalks hanging from the ceiling to sort of simulate
the experience of running through a cornfield.
This was the one time where I felt like I actually didn't see
the the person who was going to jump out and scare me.
Like I actually was a little surprised.
The cornfield, it being so densely packed with corn stalks helped obscure them.
But I also feel like this is one of the rooms where there are some dummies.
So you're genuinely unnerved.
You can't predict which one's going to move and jump out at you.
I mean, this was a classic example.
If like if we were able to explore this room a little bit on our own time,
I think it would have been fun, but it was maybe 10 feet by 10 feet
and delivered to us as another security checkpoint to get through LaGuardia Airport.
Maybe this is reflective of being in Jimmy Fallon's brain
and that in the way that you couldn't stop and focus on one thing,
that's like how he can't focus on his show or the flippies or the books.
It is a race from one endeavor to the next and one cameo he said he'd do.
And I said I'd be in this movie and I said I'd stop by today's show
and I said I'd make an appearance at my kid's play and there's no time to stop and enjoy any of it.
Like outdoor rural space inside New York City room is kind of a fun vibe
and felt like it was evoked fairly well.
But also you're getting, I mean, you cannot get less specific than cornfield with scarecrows.
Yeah, there's like no twist on this.
Okay, next liminal space, the Jimmy text voiceover is
there's a mad scientist turning people into mutants using gamma rays.
That's it. That's the full.
That's the setup.
That's the full setup.
And then you go into a room that has a kind of classical mad scientist character,
wild wacky hair.
Ben, I feel like you and I both agree that we like this performer.
Yeah, he was really going for it.
It also really just shading really a lot of yeah, big acting energy.
Yeah, he's sort of like an evil Doc Brown and he had like a,
you know, a lab coat with a radiation symbol on it.
And yeah, despite the fact that he's all his dialogue is a pre-recorded track he's lip-syncing
to he's doing a bunch of shit.
He's pulling a bunch of levers.
It feels like this is once again, the better way to use the smaller space they have
is to like place you in a room and have narrative elements happen around you rather than
walk through this room and have people jump out at you who cannot hide very well.
So this is like he's doing his like mad scientist experiment and then he pulls some shit
and then some like electrodes go off and then a guy jumps out with what I would describe
as almost like John Carpenter, they live face.
That's I guess their definition of mutant.
He's wearing a suit.
He's got sort of like blue and red like kind of radioactive face paint and he's like,
but there's sort of a lot of windup of the scientist doing this experiment
and then this guy jumping out at you.
It's at least a little fun.
Now, this character, the one who jumps out at you, his experiment was presented in Jimmy's nightly
introducing new characters from tonightmares as quote unquote mutant Jimmy.
And he is wearing a Jimmy style suit much like the werewolf character who was not on their social
media and on the show referred to as werewolf Jimmy.
He was just referred to as the werewolf.
But this character is supposed to apparently be Jimmy's nightmare of the scientists did this to
him, which feels like another sort of branching like maybe there was one version of this where
every scare room we're seeing is this happening to Jimmy.
Maybe all of these are specific to Jimmy's experiences.
Like every room feels like it has a different take on what this is supposed to be.
Right.
Is the science relative to him?
Does the scientist look like Lorne Michaels?
Like Lorne's forced me to become this.
Maybe like a great question.
Like is that maybe where it's come?
Whether he knows it or not is maybe that inspiration for this room.
Possibly.
I think that's a little bit more of the kind of the take.
I want the slant, the sort of point of view I'm looking for in this.
The next room.
Sorry.
Oh, right.
Okay, gentlemen, Jimmy's about to get a little topical.
Oh, always.
I know right now, up until this point, we've been dealing with sort of like abstract totemic scares,
but Jimmy, he looked at the newspaper and he said, this is what's really terrifying.
What's happening today in our society.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
And I quote, I'm in a giant warehouse where they're building humanoid robots and pumping
them full of artificial intelligence.
Pumping them full of it.
This is when we all stopped and started clapping before we even got in.
Yeah.
Ben's got a single Chris Pine tear rolling down his cheek.
Yes, Scott, as you point out, pumping them full of artificial intelligence.
Yeah, that's how it works.
Yeah.
AI is, yeah, it's like goo.
Yes.
And then you're just in a kind of like lab-like room, you see there's a manager's office where
the window is a video screen and you see blurry through the window, a robot seemingly attacking
someone, and then there's sort of this longer corridor that is, how would you describe the
robots?
They kind of, they kind of look at the robots, they kind of look at the robots, they kind of
I was going to say like that, but like crash test dummy.
You're probably, yes.
They all have like identical jumpsuits and then rubber masks.
And the rubber masks are a little creepy and this much like the scarecrow room is like,
there are like eight of them, they're sort of like hanging like this, like they're in
sort of like storage chambers, deactivated, and then two of them are going to jump out.
Okay.
And is it like, so do they look more like a lot, like do they look like robots?
What you're describing doesn't look like a robot to me, it looks like a dummy, I guess.
See if I can get a picture.
I'd say they, yeah, I'd say even the humans that come to life look more like dummies.
Okay, so yeah, it looks like somebody, like they've been enchanted by some magic or
something versus an actual robot that's mechanical.
Yeah, yeah, I mean it feels like a, it does not feel like a very up-to-date
perception of what an artificial intelligent, artificially intelligent robot would look like.
Right.
It looks a little bit more like something out of a 90s Disney Channel original movie.
Kind of look like they were pumped full of AI.
It's the best way I could describe it.
Okay, now I understand it, now I get it.
It's very clear now.
Very clear.
It's pouring out of their ears.
Like some sort of bartending robot that's actually a human in a haptic feedback suit
controlling it from another room.
Jason's being topical now too with the recent Tesla unveiling of the Tesla unveiling robots,
the autonomous robots.
This is what they look like if you can make it out.
Oh wow, that's creepy actually.
I don't mind the design, design something.
I actually found them creepy and I feel like I, and I couldn't make it out because once
again this event is so loud, but I swear if I'm not mistaken, the one robot jumped out to me
and I think genuinely responded by like, it didn't quite scare me, but I was like,
ah, spooky robot.
Like I said something like that.
And I believe the scare actor said something in response to me.
What it sounded like to me was we don't speak English.
I'm not spooky, I'm a pump full of AI.
What the hell are you getting about this?
But it definitely sounded like a real voice coming from under the mask.
And they were fired for saying any words probably right after that.
Yeah.
Their scare is they sort of just act like they're malfunctioning.
Like they just kind of shake a lot.
Right, right.
But this is, I think you guys are sensing the repetition of the pattern.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
The next closet space, the text voiceover is, I'm on stage with the world famous boy band
Blood and Guts.
Oh no.
And they're hungry for dot, dot, dot blood and guts.
Okay.
Now I would describe Blood and Guts as looking like the kind of band Mike would like.
If they opened D23, you're saying?
Their name is spelled B-L-O-O-D-E-N-G-U-T-Z as one word.
Okay.
He says world famous boy band.
So I'm like, oh, interesting.
Is it going to be like spooky one direction?
And then you get in there and they kind of just look like,
Ben, how would you describe it?
Like mutant slayer?
Yeah, but like even kind of leaning more just generic punk.
They do not look like a boy band in any way.
No, right.
That's not their vibe.
This is the room.
Walk into this room.
This is the room when he went through with Prince Harry.
The two actors after they left were like, that was Prince Harry.
You were describing maybe that nights are dropping off and this thing has not been
doing that great despite the fact that they made Prince Harry and Demi Lovato go through it.
And they've plugged it on the Today Show.
There's been on air promos every night.
They have really done as much with that mechanism as they can to get there.
They forced very famous people through this thing.
That set up of I'm on stage with world famous boy band Blood and Guts.
I'm immediately I'm like, okay, this is getting a little more specific,
descriptive after a couple rooms that are like, you know what's scary?
Monsters.
And you walk in and there's a monster and you're done with the room.
I'm like, okay, we're creating IP.
Blood and Guts is a new thing.
Jimmy's on stage with them.
This is a specific nightmare he has about hosting the Tonight Show and musical acts.
And what if a musical act goes wrong?
And then you get to this room and it just looks like the backstage area
of a mid-sized concert venue.
There are like Blacklight concert posters that also sound like they were written by Mike
that just have words like rock on them.
I like that.
It's going to have enroll or else it's not Mike.
Roll is his own poster.
Okay.
Then they're just like a lot of like equipment crates and like amps.
And then in the center of the room, there is like a dummy that looks like a dead person.
And there is like one guy on top of him with like a studded belt and a black vest,
but no shirt underneath who is like chowing on his neck.
So like John Stamos and Full House when he was in Jesse and the Rippers.
A little, yeah, it's just kind of like generic.
Like he looks more like a leather daddy, but then with some vaguely like zombified elements
and he's attacking this dummy that you're like, I'm pretty sure that's actually a dummy.
It's not going to come to life.
And he's just eating this thing's neck from the time you walk into the room.
And then once you get into the room, he turns around and sort of snaps at you,
like bears his teeth at you.
And then I think at some point a second band member comes out and also screams at you.
But that's the entire room.
This was one of the times where someone scared my back.
So I didn't experience it, but I sensed that someone had popped up from behind me,
but it wasn't effective in any way.
Zombie, zombie Lou Pearlman jumped out behind you.
Oh, that is scary.
Tremendous blind spots in this thing, considering how small the rooms are,
where it really is like if you're looking two degrees in the wrong direction,
you miss the thing.
Or if you're like a second behind, you miss the thing.
It's got to be very precise as far as how they're loading people in and out.
Yes.
And then this, I think this was the final one band or the final proper room.
The text is I have a recurring nightmare where all the pages remove their human masks
and they're actually bloodthirsty monsters.
There it is.
Okay.
All right.
We're thinking in tandem here.
So we're getting back to sort of, oh, the specifics of his job,
the in and outs of the days of working there.
His greatest fear is that the lowest paid people he ever has to come across
are actually trying to kill him.
They're the actual monsters.
He has nothing but fear of an anger toward them.
And that's the only reason he refuses to learn their names
because he's worried that underneath they're actually bloodthirsty monsters
or perhaps people who would speak on background to Rolling Stone reporters.
It just feels like a wild punching down to end the thing on.
And then there's like, yeah, what feels like a little bit of a like talk show set up,
two couches on a room, mass on a wall.
Your tour guide is like, quickly, we got to get out of here.
And then the final stretch of this is just you walking through long curtain hallways.
It is basically being in the black lodge from Twin Peaks.
That's what it feels like.
The curtains are blue.
Scary.
Nothing scary happens in the room.
And the room is the smallest one of all.
But then she's like, we got to get out.
We're so close to the end.
And then you walk down this hallway for what feels like maybe 20 seconds.
It's very narrow.
And a lot of people jump out at you in the hallway.
Okay.
What's a lot?
And I'd say in this hallway, there may be six people in alternation
who are jumping out versus the two in every other room.
Okay.
That is, that's good.
And they just have kind of what feel like all leftover monster masks.
It's not tied to the other stuff in the maze.
Not really.
I mean, I couldn't tell.
It's happening so quickly.
And there is that feeling of like, come on, guys, we got to get out of here.
The tour guide is really positioning this as, oh, right.
I think that's part of it is she went like, wait, this isn't part of it.
It's supposed to be over.
They, at the very last second, do this thing of like, wait, this part isn't
part of tonight, there's something's gone wrong.
You got to get out of this hallway as quickly as possible.
And then it's just all these assorted monsters.
But some of them might be reuses of other monster faces we've seen before.
Some of them might just be like, when you say the pages rip their faces off
and reveal their bloodthirsty monsters, I'm like, okay, what's the take?
You know?
What do they represent in the sort of annals of monsterdom?
And it's just some different things.
But then you get through this hallway and you walk out and you're back in
basically the same security clearance area we were in 10 minutes earlier,
where a guy just goes, hey, thank you.
Survived to nightmares.
Come over here for a picture.
Uh huh.
Okay.
They make you take a picture with your entire group.
So we were in a picture with a bunch of strangers and they're like, you guys,
please stay clear of the sign.
Make sure there's space for the sign and the photo so everyone can see where you are.
I know where this is going.
They're doing a lot of moving around the sign.
Ben was right next to the sign.
They push Ben out to stand like three inches away from the sign.
And then right when the guy takes the picture,
the trap door opens up and someone pops out of the sign and screams.
Okay.
Everyone just really inch it over.
You're not going to want to be anywhere near that.
It's going to be a dangerous sign.
Actually could fall on you.
It's really for your own safety and not because a guy's going to jump out.
And what is that?
What does that performer look like?
Great question.
It was the, our guide.
Oh, it was our guide, but done in monster form or were they even transformed?
So there, I don't know.
You're right.
She does something where she's like, she's like, uh, you should probably get out of here
because I'm going to get you or something like that.
So when you run out, we lose like, yeah.
More direct light.
You're right.
It is our guide.
I think we couldn't see it before because all the rooms are so darkly lit.
She does have kind of a general like pale face, dark circles around eyes, spooky makeup.
Yeah.
But it is just the guide.
But there's some kind of thing where she's not on her side anymore at the end.
And then when we go to take a picture, it's like she, she reappears and she thankfully
screamed right in my ear, which was great.
So we did get some screaming in the end.
Okay.
That's something.
But that's, that's the end.
Then you're just out and there's like an iPad with a QR code.
You can scan to get your photos on your phone.
Okay.
Can I ask?
So there's no quest love in the roots crew?
Zero.
I would say not even anything that alludes to them.
Interesting.
Yeah.
I mean, look, unless maybe like some of the roots members did the voiceover for the pre-recorded
tracks, but it's like, I recognize Higgins at the gas station, his voice, there's hashtag.
There's a tight pants Easter egg.
Sure.
There were a couple of Easter eggs like that.
I'm trying to remember whatever it was.
I saw in the bedroom that I couldn't get a picture of, but this was the other part of
it is like, it did feel like there was a little dare I say it, pizza riso party room-esque
theming where it's like, well, if you actually look at the walls, there's some fun details
and they're Jimmy specifics of the show.
And every time I tried to stop to get a photo of one, I felt like I am fucking up this
whole thing.
So maybe you would have to go to the last one of the night.
If you could get in the last slot of the night, there would be no pressure.
No one would be behind you.
And maybe we could, we could tell that real, the real hardcore details that the super fans
might notice.
I'm sure the, the girl and her dad are represented somewhere in there.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
You know, but the last one of the night, there'd be the rush for everybody to go the fuck home.
Come on.
Let's go.
That's true.
We're really going to turn on you more than all the tour guys.
You might get angry.
You get angrier screams or something that way.
People would be mad at you more frustration would come out in the performance.
Is there a season pass option?
Like that's a great question.
Frequent fear pass.
I think they call it.
Yeah.
One of the places does that would be interesting.
I believe this ended up being about a $45 ticket per person.
I mean, I added the flex thing, but the flex thing is only I think six or $7 extra.
There's a service charge for both the ticket and the flex pass.
I do not think the flex pass did anything for us.
There was at no point where it felt like, cause it gave, there were two different QR codes,
one for the ticket and one for the flex pass.
They never scanned the second one.
What did this experience cost you per minute?
Let's assume, assuming we'll take any cue.
Certainly there was entertainment value to being scanned TSA style and told,
don't scare the monsters.
You're paying for that too.
But if we're going purely off of the 10 minutes of the maze,
what does each minute of To Nightmares cost?
Let me do a final tally here.
Great.
At 10 minutes and 30 seconds, do we round up to 11?
Do we give them that generosity?
Let's be nice here.
Like Jimmy.
Okay.
Very nice.
The nicest.
So nice.
Midwest nice.
Yeah.
We're all waiting with bated breath.
I think it costs about $13.50 per minute.
For three of us to do it as a group.
Right.
How does this compare to the going rates for like a phone sex line?
2024.
Yes, those in 2024.
Well, Griffin and Ben, I did look up,
I was trying to see if I could find any staffing notice or like backstage for performance.
And the one job that came up a couple of times is a LinkedIn posting
for CCTV attendant for this attraction.
Your responsibilities are monitor activity,
observe live CCTV feeds to identify any suspicious or unusual behavior among guests and staff,
collaborate with security, communicate effectively with onsite security,
providing detailed intelligence about any concerns or incidents.
This is a $768 a week position.
That is a six day work week, 3.30 PM to midnight.
So that is roughly $128 a shift.
I do think that sounds like a more fun experience than going through the attraction.
Like you get a bird's eye view.
You get to look at a bunch of monitors that have each room in full rotation.
You're watching multiple groups go through.
You get to see the actors reset.
Appreciate the set design.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
You get paid versus paying for it.
This is CCTV room security.
It appears one guest is carrying pepper spray in one hand and a knife in another.
Please investigate in the cornfield room.
They were both under his hat.
We don't know how he got it through.
He was wearing a cat in the hat hat.
We should have made him check it more thoroughly.
See, here's a pitch I throw out to Ben when we are walking out.
Yeah.
That if I get the idea of, oh, do a seasonal Halloween attraction
in this empty retail space in this New York landmark, right?
I get them wanting to make it co-branded in some way.
We go to the gift shop, which is not connected to this, is back in main 30 Rock lobby
because I want to see what the merch is.
It's just the fucking lunchbox and the shirt.
You took a long walk to a gift shop.
It was not an exit through.
It was a long walk.
No, no, no.
And the shirt is just the main poster image,
the painting of Jimmy awake in bed with all the monsters around him.
And it's one of those graphic teas where the image is too large,
where you're like it takes up too much of the chest
and it also feels like it would actually be kind of rigid to wear.
Oh, yeah.
I hate that feeling.
The worst.
Yes.
So I was like, I can't buy this.
I'll never wear this.
I'd only wear it on the zoom.
It looks uncomfortable.
All the employees, like especially the security checkpoints and stuff,
we're wearing these polos that just said to nightmares on them
that I thought were kind of fun.
And I was like, I could wear this.
I will buy this.
Okay, you get that if you get the job.
That's why I do the modern job.
Yes.
But we're walking around the gift shop and I'm like,
where's the to nightmare section?
How can there not be to nightmare stuff?
And to nightmare is just a little corner of the larger Jimmy section.
But the rest of this gift shop is Saturday Night Live
and it's the office and it's law and order SVU
and it's whatever the Kelly Clarkson show.
And I just go like, hey, just like bad pitch.
Isn't the better idea to do like 30 shock?
30 shock of Feller Plaza.
Do like a synergistic New York scare room thing.
But it's like across the NBC portfolio.
And you have a David S. Pumpkins room.
You let Jimmy conceptualize one room.
Yes.
You do some haunted today's show.
Oh my God, Al Roker, the weather's so bad.
It's scary.
Blood rain, whatever.
You do like fucking 10 rooms.
You do haunted Dunder Mifflin, whatever the fuck it is.
That's good.
Isn't that more appealing to people?
Don't you think that gets more people through the door?
Yeah, broader.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Zach Levi is here.
He wants to revive Chuck.
Matt Lauer is trying to get into his old office.
You're stuck.
You don't have the button.
You can't open the door.
There's no, it's a buttonless button room.
I think your scenario, Griffin, is more people would do it
and then be able to remember a single detail
to tell their friends about that.
At the very least, you're doing it.
You go home and you go.
There was an Al Roker room.
There was a this.
There was a that.
And you're appealing to different audiences.
You're making a big tent.
I mean, the people who are right in front of us in line
when we were at the final security checkpoint.
I look like a husband and wife.
And the guy I asked the woman,
so does he do this like every year?
And like lending credence to Ben's analysis,
it just feels like everyone who was there was like,
I don't totally know why I'm here.
I don't quite get what this is.
You know, people seem to look side.
Maybe this is just the best scare option within Manhattan.
I mean, there's not a lot of competition, right?
To see Jimmy's nightmares.
Like it didn't feel like and then the experience itself
doesn't really make anything out of that.
Right.
Look, this used to be the studio for the Steve Wilco show
and we just build a bunch.
We just build a bunch of tiny rooms to fill it.
Yeah, I mean, it sounds like it's maybe not going
so well for them this year.
I don't think it is.
Yeah, you saw it on the ground.
You didn't get good vibes.
What we're hearing about shutting down days and everything.
Yeah.
Could this be the end of the road?
I don't sense a lot of power jockeying,
unlike the Tonight Show to try to take over to nightmares.
Well, yeah, they should have had more rooms faster.
Because then it starts to get scary, right?
If you're like, it's like fucking 20 rooms.
It's like, there's a werewolf.
I keep going, you know, then it's like overload.
You kind of get scared from that.
Right.
I say triple the rooms.
Yeah.
Great.
That seems about right.
That's a good speed.
I'll say this triple the rooms or just one big room
that you're in the whole time.
And then have everyone just do their thing at the same time.
Right.
So then it's in intelligible.
You have no idea what's going on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that exploratory feeling.
Yes, yes, which maybe is close to the Jimmy Fallon experience.
Being pushed to the brink.
Did you have other general thoughts, Ben?
I'm trying to remember some of our unwinding after.
Yeah, well,
I think we were just, I think we covered a lot of it.
We were, I mean, it was just this thing of.
It was never clear exactly how we related to the experience as the audience.
There was no stakes to it.
It was just kind of like being given a tour rather than for the experience.
Yeah.
Kind of like being given a tour rather than feeling like you were immersed in anything.
Right.
And like they wanted you out as quickly as possible.
Yes.
Why did you have us here into the nightmares?
Rushes through there.
There is a little bit of that feeling of like wanting to be everything for everyone
needing to like broaden the tent and be so accessible to an extent that it ends up being
nothingness.
Where we walked out, texted one of our friends who previously worked on The Tonight Show.
They said, how was it?
I said, bad.
And they responded, it wasn't funny at all.
And I realized they didn't mean like, were you having fun laughing at it?
They were like, were there any successful jokes in it?
Mm-hmm.
And I was like, this thing is not trying to be funny.
The only part of it that felt like a joke was the gas price crack that the tour guide made.
And for the first moment, I was like, oh, right.
This thing could have tried to be funny.
Right.
In the absence of being terrifying, it could have like, if this thing was the exact same experience
it was, but it had jokes in every room, I'd be like, well, it's kind of a thing.
You've never been to like a funny haunted maze before to this extent.
Right.
That's true.
No, I didn't even think about it.
I, I, I don't, I mean, it's not, maybe it's because I haven't
thought of Jimmy Fallon and funny in the same thought lately.
Not that I've never not thought that.
I'm just saying I didn't realize that even when you were talking about it.
That's not a thought I had.
I didn't say we're out of the jokes.
It's because he's such a good, he's such a good singer.
You think of him as a cool singer, so much more than.
I think of him as number one, nice.
Number two, singer.
Number three, cool.
Number four, entrepreneur.
The more I send out cover time, great at games.
Game master.
Reinventor of glasses.
There were no games.
We thought glasses could be.
No games.
No glasses.
There were no games.
There was no breaking room.
Like we're like the scare actors just couldn't stop laughing.
Oh, yeah.
A break that you can't stop.
A break that never ends is a Fallon nightmare.
There's so many he does.
There are a lot that you could tap into legitimately and in a snarky way.
One of the rooms being a big ring that you get inside
that keeps tightening and tightening and tightening on you as a group.
There's one room that's just all wall to wall freshly coiffed presidential candidates.
So many.
Which do I scruff?
Don't touch them.
Don't murder your ratings.
The floor could all be hair and you have to walk this narrow pathway to avoid touching the hair.
You can't touch the hair, so you have to be very careful.
Your ratings go down every time.
And they're like, you see the ratings on the wall and if like you nudge it, it ticks down.
And you get in Colbert's and you're hearing echoes of Colbert.
Ooh, relevance taking on the powers that be.
What if he's reelected?
And there's still like kind of this thought in the thought in the
that they could represent this somehow that like there's still a thought that like
Jay is still out there to take the show back.
You could have a jump scared Jay in every room and it would work.
It would be effective.
It could be good shape, good numbers on garage.
Weirdly better than yours.
You do it on antenna TV.
Jay has the files to prove that he would still draw more in the ratings.
He's still been doing the research like he used to.
You do have to think that in the blue sky face that there were some self-aware ideas
and they're like, don't pitch that.
You're going to be it's going to be a shit show if you make that like don't bother.
Well, that's right.
We're saying like, you know, couldn't they have bothered to try to make this thing funny?
You think about every night Fallon pulling aside a very qualified writer's room
of incredible comedians and saying, hey, would you mind staying another hour
to pitch on my haunted house and not encouraging them to come up with comedic ideas?
Mm hmm.
Like, I don't begrudge what anyone on his writing staff contributed to this event
because this is not part of their job.
They should have never been asked to do this.
I question if they were paid extra to work on this.
And if I were in the same position as them, I'd be like, I don't know.
Fuck it's scarecrows.
Jimmy's kind of leaning away from like funny.
He's kind of going for more just like, yeah, I think he just wants to scare people.
So let's just kind of like next pass less funny, less funny.
But like to Jason's point, you know, maybe they did start out with funny ideas
and they just kept being like overanalyzed to the point where it just became like nothingness.
Look, we got shipped a bunch of masks and set dressing that they're not using
at Horror Nights Orlando.
And we have to work around that.
So start coming up with ideas for Werewolf, Corn Maze, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Boy, boy, bizarre.
Where does this leave you, Ben?
You not knowing the genre at all.
And I don't feel like being the sense that I get in broad strokes is that Griffin turns to us
and it turned to us initially because he does not really get to talk about theme parks on the show.
There's not really a blank check interest in theme park.
So where does this leave you?
Are you just like, this is all stinks.
Is this the worst possible entry point for you?
Well, it's been a while since I've engaged with any kind of theme park related stuff, I will say.
So yes, I definitely didn't feel like excited necessarily to want to try and engage with more.
But I'm not dissuade totally.
I know that this was a cheap attempt at a cash grab and that it was fucking bad.
So or or a tax write off of the cash grab doesn't work.
Very smart.
There's two sides to every coin.
We did a Six Flags Great Adventure New Jersey trip and episode, I guess, about five years ago now.
Yeah, to do all the Batman rides.
And Ben being a Jersey boy has history with that Six Flags.
I do.
But you know, that is a certain level of theming that stops at a very specific point.
And I know you've spoken very lovingly of Gatorland.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, are you familiar with Gatorland in Florida?
Never been.
Whoa, you're a Gatorland guy.
Privately owned.
I wouldn't say it's well maintained.
But it's it's basically just a really trashy roadside amusement park where you can see
Floridians put their head inside of an old titer alligator's head or mouth rather.
But I loved going.
It was near where my grandparents lived.
And I haven't been back since.
But yeah, I'm a big proponent of that institution.
Oh, and well, well, now we know if that is the bar.
I mean, yeah, yeah.
Jimmy Fallon's To Nightmares is never going to get anywhere close to a place with live gators.
Like that place is actually genuinely scary.
Like, yeah, you could potentially fall into a pit of gators and be in alive.
Well, that's them.
OK, OK.
Well, hey, future episode to bookmark, then potentially Gatorland with Ben Hosley.
But I guess for now, Fallon has failed to meet the Gatorland standards.
But I'm so happy we got to hear about it from you guys.
Griffin Newman and Ben Hosley, you survived haunt cast The Fright.
What a pleasure.
Really great to have have the both of you and get a little extra blank check flavor.
And I hope you don't have any regrets having not only.
All right.
So do an unpleasant thing for 10 minutes and then talk about it for over two hours
on zoom.
Oh, OK.
But here's what I'm going to do is I will say let's exit through the crypt shop,
which is oddly disconnected from the main.
I will let you say anything that you want to say about blank check or anything else
while I go to the door and see if this present is.
Oh, yeah.
I will say let's exit through the gift shop or the crypt shop.
Is there anything you two would like to plug?
Yeah, listen to blank check if you don't already.
I sell clothes.
I have a brand Griffin's wearing one of the shirts of mine.
It's a pair of my buried jeans.
I did, in fact, buried jeans in the ground and I'm now selling them for one thousand dollars.
You can go to my website.
Also, yeah, much more affordably selling shirts with pictures of the buried jeans.
Yeah.
So you don't have to get the real thing.
You can get a shirt that has a picture of them.
You can get all of that stuff and plenty more at congratulations.
That's why you lations dot com.
Nice.
Yeah.
The blank check we're doing David Lynch is taking us through the rest of the year
covering his movies and Twin Peaks.
Uh, our Patreon blank check special features where we do kind of bonus stuff.
Earlier this year, we did a Terminator 2 3D episode,
which was me trying to get Ben and David to understand the majesty of what I believe
I referred to on my podcast, the right episode with you guys about that same attraction as
my favorite movie of all time.
They did not get it.
It was a kind of heard it.
I know I felt it not being appreciated whatsoever.
Right.
There's the PTR episode where all four of us are like, yes, we agree.
High water mark.
And then that episode is just Ben and David being like, what the fuck is this?
What am I watching?
This woman is really there in the room.
That's on a screen.
The original Megapolis.
You had to be there.
Yeah, exactly.
And not to tip our hand too much, but there is another PTR blank check
crossover episode that I have pitched to you guys for next year
that would perhaps put to the test even more so Ben and David's
tolerance of hearing people describe rides they've never been on.
Oh, right.
Oh, now I remember it.
Yes, I do like this idea.
I'm excited to.
They don't know Ben doesn't know this bit.
They don't know.
It wouldn't be until it'd be a little while off.
But some point in 2025, you maybe can see that coming.
Griffin, do you want to plug the Wandering Planet Kickstarter too?
Yeah, I think they are fully funded now, right?
They are, but I think they're still, I don't know, if they get enough money,
they can add more stuff, I think, you know.
I mean, look, what do I want?
I want Buster Keaton.
I want Fatty R. Buckle with double-jointed elbows and knees, interchangeable parts.
I want add-on tiers to be able to put them in.
There's sort of a baking ephemera.
I guess Laurel and Hardy were piano movers, right?
That feels like a glaring hole to not have a piano available as a tier.
Right.
Frankenstein, you want a Frankenstein.
Well, that's Abbott and Costello.
Oh, shit.
Well, Mr. Old Movie.
Well, as we started talking about Laurel and Hardy,
I think I've spent more time watching the trailer
for the Steve Coogan, John C. Reilly biopic.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Than I have actually watched Laurel and Hardy.
Also, they have, Jason, they've made, I have a Frankenstein figure on the shelf over here too.
Oh, sure.
I don't know how quickly you guys are looking to turn around this episode,
but at the time of this recording, there are four days left
in the Laurel and Hardy collectible action figure one 12 scale campaign.
They have raised $87,000 out of a $40,000 goal.
They've more than doubled.
And how many, I'm always intrigued by this.
The number of backers is like always going to be lower than you think for that amount of money.
It's like there's 300 backers.
802 backers.
800 backers that want these toys.
$87,000, yeah.
Right.
I feel like maybe Ben is putting it together that whenever
Griffin is talking about things that you and David don't want to hear about, he's doing it with us.
Right.
I am making that connection.
We hear the receptacle for the unwanted interest.
Yep.
And then the deeper inception tier of Mike and I's solo text thread for something you guys don't want.
There's solo pits too.
Okay.
Well, let me pull this up and let's see what we got.
This is a fake out.
This is another box that I had because that is not here.
It was a prop box.
A letdown maybe much like Jimmy Fallon's to nightmares.
So I will have to amend and post to social media whatever this present is.
I have my guesses as to the content of it.
I mean, my biggest guess is are there Kingo products developed specifically for newborns?
But I don't know the answer to that.
It's an interesting line of thinking.
And I think you might still be a little surprised by the reality of what you're receiving.
Oh, boy.
Well, I'm sorry we can't do it on air, but I thank you for it anyway.
We'll update the audience with that.
But thank you both for taking so much time and going to that thing.
And hopefully we can all do something together not on Zoom for podcast or for fun.
As for us, for three boonest episodes every month, check out Podcast the Ride the Cemetery Gate
or get one more boonest episode on our RIP tier Crypt 3.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Also, I just want to say follow us on social media and don't just follow us,
but go in there, get in the comments and have a long drawn out debate about whether or not
Griffin is good.
I think we love to see it.
And it's about consistency.
And that's why we want to see it on every single episode.
And we do.
But I'm saying just keep it up because eventually we're going to figure it out.
I think there's a debate I even prefer witnessing, which is arguing with people
who say that I am good, that they can't possibly feel that.
That they're wrong about their assertion that you're good.
I don't believe you mean that for real.
It's always a great argument.
So get in there, hash it out, hashtag it out.
Hashtag it out.
And we'll have a grand old discourse.