Welcome to Hauntcast, the Fright, the Cemetery Gate. We're in an awkward position because
we're recording these out of order. Do we have the scary names yet or do we punt? Because
the listener may have already heard them. Oh yeah, good question.
We can just punt. We should punt.
Alright, great. So you'll hear the scary names in the past. For now, I'm Scott Gardner, there's
Mike Carlson. How much is this blowing your mind? What an inception of dates, eh?
Yeah, we are out of order and I feel like I've been like, I'm in a different timeline
or something. I'm in a different multiverse. Halloween multiverse.
Yeah, I mean, we're just, our priorities are just, you know, we're a little bit in the
past. So our priorities are getting Joe Biden elected and, you know, giving Donald Trump
the proper break and for the heroism of surviving the shooting. That's where, if that places
this in a time of when we're recording it. Right.
And we wish, but yeah, Godspeed Joe. I think he's going to pull it out. Jason Sheridan.
Well, I'm an RFK man, you know that. Yeah, yeah. I am too. And I think he, in a way,
like aligns with the Democrats and I think he's going to be good for the Joe cause at
the end of the day. Sure. And I don't think we're going to find out several more instances
of animal abuse. Okay, yeah. Bizarre things that he, I think he, you know, how many more
could there be? I just also, I went to Vegas yesterday and I put five grand on JLo and
Ben Affleck staying together. Nice. That's smart. Cause I believe in them and I don't
think anything's going to happen. Yeah, yeah. That's good. Well, you've been talking about
betting more. That reminds us, we should do some of that D23 betting. Maybe we should
actually do the D, again, that's a future thing. Yeah, yeah, yeah. But that's, yeah,
if you're going to bet on something, that's, that's the thing to bet on. And I bet, I bet
against Ben Affleck hanging out with RFK's daughter. Kick Kennedy. Well, now, now I'm
lost regardless of what time it is. Kick Kennedy just threw me now. I'm just floating through
space. I'm lost like Sandra Bullock in gravity. I'll tell you this, that will never happen.
All right. I just, well, we should put more money on it off air. Is Kick Kennedy a nickname?
I actually don't know if Kick Kennedy is her real legal name, but she's referred to as
Kick in articles I've seen, including the 2012 Town and Country Magazine article where
it's revealed that RFK used a chainsaw to cut the head off of a whale, tie it to the
top of the family car and drive five hours back to their house with his two kids in the
back and the whale juice falling into the car. So he put plastic bags on the kid's head,
cut mouth holes in the plastic bags so they wouldn't suffocate and drove with this giant
whale's head just bleeding the whole time back to the house. This story, especially as you're
hearing this, you may have heard this. I heard the vaguest, I saw in my rear view mirror at
some point, whale, never put it together. I'm happy that I heard it from you. You need to hear
that from somebody you trust. Right, of course. I also think the media might not have used the
phrase whale juice. I'm glad you've gotten your colorful description. I believe the article is
about Kick Kennedy and I think she may have said whale juice. I think she may have said juice
specifically. So anyway, I'm betting that Ben Affleck doesn't end up with her at all.
No, no. RFK Jr. is like, he's like Tom Green in Freddy Got Fingered. Apparently after he was
denying it for a while, but now RFK is admitting to having seen a deer on the side of the way,
hit a deer, ripped apart his innards and wore the suit, wore the bloody carcass as a hood of sorts.
RFK Jr. went into a delivery room, delivered the baby himself and then swung the baby around by
like by the umbilical cord. These are very offensive antics, RFK. Well, hard times make
hard babies. They should. RFK, because he's had a lot of hard times. He worked several times in a
cheese sandwich shop and he, you know, sure he didn't do the tasks of the day. He just stacked
a bunch of piles of cheese on top of other piles of cheese, but he did technically do the shifts,
despite his dream of being an animator. Right. I was most interested in that he is the center
square on one of today's topics. Did he pull a little time as well? Yeah, he's next to Cronk.
Oh geez. Wow. He actually, wow. That's funny. They feel like they mostly used canonical villains,
but they also let RFK Jr. do a spin. That's interesting. Yeah. Yeah. That's, that's, well,
it's some of what we're talking about today. This is, this will like evolve a little bit,
but here's where this started is that a while ago I did a post like, well, I think the post
was main feed wishes. So you didn't get your wish, but we are doing this. There was one that caught
my eye, got a lot of likes and I could file it away for a while. And this is from Kendor,
their wish for an episode about Villains Game Night, the bizarre Hollywood squares style game
show they play on Disney cruises using pre-recorded actors. And this had a strange photo that was a
screen divided into nine, sure enough, with little podiums. And it was a bunch of Disney villains,
all participating in some kind of game show, sure enough, all, but actors playing the Disney. This
is not, you know, CGI or animated depictions of these classic villains. These are actors. And that
image haunted me for a while. So as we got into haunt cast season, I'm like, maybe this is the time
as when in a time when villains rain, let's let them have their game night. Yeah. And that's also
just, it is, there are like little things that are also in our like zone of interest. Game shows,
Hollywood squares, which is very to me, even though there was a nineties and 2000s versions,
very seventies to me, like that feels. Well, yeah, it feels inevitable to talk about. Yeah,
Hollywood squares has come up somehow rarely specifically despite being the like main,
uh, like layer, I would say of the, I'm gonna use the word layer where, uh, uh, where all of the
carrot, all of the old character actors who we waste a lot of time talking about the seventies,
strange relics, your Paul Lins, your Sandy Duncan's, uh, and ones we haven't even mentioned,
but, uh, I'll just, I'll say it, madam, madam was only squares, but then you also get to the
nineties, two thousands. And one of our guys was always on Bruce flange. Oh, right. So there's,
there's a lot of PTR legends, future legends that were involved in the Hollywood squares.
There's a full time Hollywood squares channel on Pluto TV. And I was flipping through and saw,
I mean, okay, I know there's, you know, there's especially that version. There were reasonably
big stars on that show. Well, I think Ellen DeGeneres was the center square for a long time,
yet it really stopped. I was just flipping through, passing by quick. And then I saw Michael
Jackson. I'm like, hang on. Michael Jackson feels like too big of a star in the early two thousands
to be on Hollywood squares. Then I backed up as fast as I could, landed on it and discovered it
was impersonator week. Okay. Not in the squares, but the contestants. So confusingly it was
contestants, impersonators who look like Michael and Janet Jackson saying, I'll take Jeffrey
Tambor to block and a voice that doesn't sound like Michael at all, but an eerily, maybe the
best Michael Jackson physical impersonator I've ever seen. Wow. Just play. And he, he pulled it
out, I think. And he was like, if you win this round, you get a new car. And the new car was
presented by a Ricky Martin. So mediocre that I wasn't sure until 30 seconds in it was a Ricky
Martin. Oh, wow. It was kind of, cause like, I don't know if it's just a guy and a guy who I
looked a little more white to me than not. So if it's just kind of a tall white guy with a nice
haircut and a black shirt, it can't be so sure it's a Ricky Martin. Also there are real celebrities
on the show. Why? What's the point of impersonator week? Yeah, I guess. Well, I don't know that not,
again, not as big, the stars aren't as big as Michael Jackson. Yeah, I guess that's true.
It's still almost like an insult to the stars you do have. That's, that's bizarre. Carol Channing.
Uh huh. And the Carol Channing is still alive and doing it in the 2000s. Wow. Answering questions
from a perfect looking but terrible sounding Michael Jackson. Jason, you got to get on that.
Carol Channing's involved? Oh, yeah. That's one of your girls. I could see that being a current
hall pass. If you ran into a Carol Channing impersonator. I, unfortunately, they're not
fictional. I feel like that's been the running theme is that all my hall passes are fictional
characters. Right, right. Yeah. But what if she, Carol Channing, sorry, passed away five years ago.
She was 97. It was only five years ago? Yeah, she was 97 years old. What, what harm would it have done?
You know what I'm saying? A spirit, we're talking like, acroid Ghostbusters, first Ghostbusters
situation. Oh, you would, oh, you're talking about the ghost. The ghostly head of the famous
hair of Carol Channing moves down into your lap. And I do the like, oh, like I do it the wrong way.
Well, I was going to say something different. So yeah, I like what you're saying. Wait, wait, wait.
I'm going to ask you to do the sound after I first say, well, hello, Jason. I feel like.
You didn't, that was the sound. Sorry, sorry, go. Hello, Jason. Oh, it's very hang kill. It's a real
hang kill. That's all right. All right. Well, I was going somewhere else, but I'm glad you took it
into a Halloween zone with the ghost. I appreciate that because it is called Cast of Fright. There's
still time, there's still weeks ahead in which the spirits may gather and fingers crossed, Jason
gets a ghost blow job. Oh my God. This is well, unfortunately, but Madam is fictional, you know.
Yeah. Who are you talking about? You would all pass with Madam. I think, I think. Madam's alive,
by the way. I think she would be over you. Are you saying Madam's alive? Madam is alive.
Wayland Flowers has passed away, but Madam is alive. What do you mean by Madam is alive?
What's your game here? We don't have the weirdo anymore. Let's all turn the mic. All right.
Turning the weirdo like cha-chunk, it's on mic now. Madam is a puppet. Madam has never canonically
died. Madam is alive. So. Yeah, I see what you're saying. Unlike the late great Hannibal Lecter,
she has not been canonically. The late great Madam. Lambchop didn't die. Sherry Lewis died.
Mallory Lewis, Sherry's daughter is doing Lambchop. I guess by a lot, but if we're going from the top
down, then the top puppet Kermit, at least to me, Madam might be yours. To me, the top puppet Kermit
did not die when Jemison died. So I guess so. Are people doing Madam though? Oh, why did I ask
that question? I don't want to know the answer at all. We've gotten messages. People are still
doing Madam, performing as Madam. So Madam is alive. So Madam's not a ghost. That's all I'm saying.
So if you're talking about hooking up with Madam or me, I don't know who you're talking about,
Jason. Madam would not be a ghost. She would be alive. Okay. Okay. I just want to make this
very clear. All it takes, I think, is you getting your hands on a Madam puppet
and then moving the Madam puppet wherever you see fit. I have had an idea, and we haven't done it,
and we're not going to do it this year for Honkest of Fright, but I've had an idea
for a seance for a long time, but now I have to add in calling the ghost of Carol Channing into
the seance. So I've added things now to this plan. It's not going to happen this year,
but one of these days, one of these years, we will do a seance, and part of it is now going
to be summoning the ghost of Carol Channing. You really want to mess with the spirit world?
I absolutely do. If it gets your hall pass taken care of, then yeah, we will go to any length
in this realm or others. And I will bring a Madam puppet who is alive,
who is still alive. She will be in the room with us. It is really only a matter of time
before you have a Madam, because you want it for the show. You bring up your daughter,
likes your puppet stuff a lot. It's going to be like, look, Lindsay, it's a business expense
and an invaluable home expense. Do you want me to bond with her daughter or not?
What better way than with a clackety, dick-faced old lady?
I'm tired of the third degree, Linz.
I make the money in this house.
You spent five grand on a perfect recreation of Madam. You had a puppeteer or a puppet maker
make it. You had like an artisan make it in Spain, and they sent it over. They had to
overnight it for $500 with the most care and packaging you've ever seen.
The finest hair from the most beautiful horses.
A horse was killed in order to provide the hair for my Madam puppet.
Sure. They actually told me they could have just like cut the hair off, but I said, no,
kill it. I don't want anyone else getting that hair and making their own better Madam.
Right. I bought the poison and sent it to Spain.
It sounds like most of the money in this case was spent on international shipping.
Well, that's a big part of it. If you find the best puppet
maker, it's obviously somebody in Spain.
Best puppet makers are in Spain. Best horses are, I don't know where.
Where was Geppetto? Where was he from?
Italy.
Italy? All right. Maybe it's Italy. I don't know. Spain or Italy. They're close together.
Again, you're burning money because you sent it to the wrong country,
so then you had to get it back and send it to the right country.
You just sent it to the country in general. To Spain.
To Spain. That's not specific enough.
Return for not being specific enough.
Yeah. All right.
Well, we sure have talked about that now.
Okay.
The point is Hollywood Squares was a game show in which there was a kind of scarily big set
where enough to stack three sets of B-list actors on top of each other,
and you would perform a ... Their contestants would face off against each other in a giant
tic-tac-toe, which was based around answering questions correctly, and they'd kind of
devilishly lie and poke her face. Do you think that's right or do you not?
Yeah. Or if you were like a Paul Lynn, you would have jokes ready to go,
I think, for a lot of these questions, and then you would say it, get a laugh,
and then answer seriously.
Then answer for real. Yeah. Get your double entendre out.
Fake or fake answer.
So that's the format. A big trivia-oriented tic-tac-toe. So that brings us to this cruise
ship entertainment. We have not done a lot of cruise ship stuff, and so I needed to get my
head straight about which ship we're on and what we're dealing with here. This was entertainment
for the Disney Wish, which is the fifth Disney cruise ship. That's not going to help me because
they're all named some Disney word like that. But this is a pretty recently launched ship,
whatever you want to say, Summer 2022. A lot of crazy entertainment on this. We probably do need
to look into the cruise ships a little more, just for oddities that are only there, only in these
specific vessels.
I've been watching. I have been putting on Travel Vlogger, like going on the biggest cruise ship
in the world, or going on this Disney cruise. And I find them very relaxing, and I'm fascinated
by the full ecosystem located on a cruise ship. That said, I do not particularly want to go on
myself, but I like watching them. I like living vicariously.
Me too. I've discussed watching videos starring my hall pass that is impossible, 1987 specific
Kathie Lee Gifford. It really sold me on the notion of a Carnival cruise then. I don't
particularly want to do one now. Mike, I have a prediction coming into this. I think you're
going to become a cruise guy. I think you're going to do a Disney cruise and then be so
in on it. As I was driving here, I said, I'm probably going to do one of these in the next
five years. Or 10 years. Let's say 10.
Because they do leave from Southern California. There is Southern California.
A Disney one?
Yeah.
I don't know. I wonder if I'll be a cruise guy. It's still not something that I'm excited
to become. I think there was a will in my... I had a will to become a haunt guy in some ways,
to conquer something, to watch scary movies. I don't really feel like I'm not excited to
become a cruise guy like I was to be a haunt guy.
Sure. It's not something you're aspiring to.
But I'm not saying I won't be that. I'm just saying I don't have quite the energy there.
Sure. But I could just see you on the other side going, and all the meals are paid for.
Sure, that sounds expensive when you go in, but then you get all the food for free.
The drinks are out on, but I could see you just doing this.
That sounds like this guy, though, too.
It does sound like me. Although I have to say, I've watched some ordinary
adventures cruise ship videos. It seems like there's a lot of add-ons.
Oh, I'm sure. Disney, of course.
A lot more add-ons. Certainly for...
Now, that really sounds like Jason.
Certainly for alcohol, but there are some... And you're paying cheaper, like,
you know, entrees. But there are some restaurants where you're charging into the room.
I would still, I think, rather go to do the Star Trek cruise than I would a Disney cruise.
I think that's fair.
Oh, my God. I shouldn't say this, but I have to now.
Armand Shimmerman is teaching a class on Shakespeare in Glendale.
I have to take it, I think.
Oh, hell yes.
You're going to go take a Shakespearean acting class just to be around Armand Shimmerman.
I think I have to. I got a call there. He's like, here's the phone number for the theater. Call it.
Have you ever had any desire to do or learn Shakespeare before?
Never.
So you're going to go, and then whatever, what do you anticipate the class, like, assignments,
or what are you going to end up doing?
I don't know. I have to, like, memorize shit? Like, I have to memorize Shakespearean dialogue?
Hamlet? Or with the apostrophe. There's no V.
Yeah, you have to get it pretty word perfect, and then you have to get the rhythm and then
trying to put it in modern delivery. Some friends have done Shakespeare. I think it's very fascinating.
Right, and it would be very fascinating to do with Armand specifically.
Yeah, except for all the parts where he isn't there, where you will be bored to tears and
stressed out because, as Jason said, there's a lot to figure out, and there are stakes in you pulling
it off perfectly because you don't want Armand Shimmerman yelling at you.
I don't want that. No, I want to please him more than anything.
What character is he again?
He's Quark.
Yeah, but he's also on Buffy and he's been on a lot of stuff.
Now, do I have to say quark like that, not quark, because then you'll yell at me for
pronouncing it wrong?
That's less of a thing, but he's Quark. He had the bar on Deep Space Nine, which they had in Vegas,
and they're doing a Star Trek, the Universal, for this weird fan thing in the spring,
and they're going to have some sort of immersive experience.
Oh, these Horror Nights, Adjacent, Fan Nights, Star Trek Nights, Dungeons & Dragons Nights,
and Back to the Future.
Yeah, so I wonder if they put up a Quarks bar at Universal.
I was confused by that. Is each one its own night or is it all at once?
I think it's all at once, but let's get back to the topic.
Oh, okay. Thank you. Very good.
Sorry, sorry.
I just want to give you room to stretch.
Not your fault, my fault, Jason.
No, no. In terms of crew's stuff, here's things that I didn't know, because these will be basics
if listeners have been on these things. I didn't know that they have what they call
the only Disney attraction at sea, the Aquamouse.
It's like a water slide that's more complicated, that has kind of launches, that goes up and down,
and that has screens in a long tunnel, and they've started utilizing these
to tell little stories a little bit, even though the ride isn't just to slide through tubes.
But they do little, there's custom, it's those newer Disney or the newer Mickey animation
made for cruise ship tunnels, specifically, that imply that you're doing like a bobsled run
or whatever. So that's interesting. This is the ship that has the Avengers quantum encounter,
the dining experience where Paul Rudd filmed specific stuff for this.
They only see on the Wish. They got a Star Wars hyperspace lounge, which is no Quarks bar,
it's not bad, I saw a couple photos of it.
And then what they have is a, well it seems like they've also done,
they've programmed Halloween stuff, because what I saw is that there's like an adults,
I think adults only thing, I could be wrong, but there's something called,
they did something called Oogie Boogie's Villainous Nightmare, and that has like,
it's like a night, it's a scary nightclub, and then there's like characters who lead you into it
to go to this Oogie Boogie bash at sea, and a guy named Vex with two Xs leads you along and says,
I am a chaser of dreams and nightmares. So we got original IP, ship only, you get to meet Vex,
and then once you get into that dance party, it's stuff like this, it's these characters on
screens portrayed by actors in some makeup, maybe not movie quality makeup, but something.
So there's that, but then what you've got is a lounge, I guess more of a theater area called
Luna, and that's where this thing happens, it boasts this giant LED screen that you can do a
lot of stuff with, and this is one of the big attractions, they, I can't tell if they still
have it, this might have been a seasonal, brief Halloween only, but I could be wrong,
maybe they are doing it this year. They love mashing up the villains around Halloween,
I watched a live stream from the first night of the Oogie Boogie bash, and like so many villains
in the parade, you go on the tree trails, you meet different villains and stuff.
Right, right. Well that's, as a kid and as an adult man, the mashup of the villains has always
been very exciting to me, whether it's just the sing along song tape on the lawn of the haunted
mansion in Disneyland or anything else, that's always been very exciting, and they're doing
of course the Villains Land in Florida, which is like, in some ways I was thinking about this,
this is the only, this is almost the only way you get something like a little surprising or original
is now having the villains in different contexts than just their own movies.
Yeah, which they seem to be a lot, that's something they seem to be open to and that they flirted
with with stuff like Villains Game Night, and yeah, I mean it's a good time to be talking
about this with Villains Land, whatever it's going to be called on the horizon,
is to start thinking about, well what is it like when all the villains get together,
because it sounds crazy and scary, but there's something a little more tortured about it than
what we're getting at Epic Universe, where the universal monsters who all feel part of the same
world are together. Frankenstein and Dracula, the moment the wolf man, all right that makes it,
there'd be some place where they all are. With Disney characters, it's like here's queens from
like pastoral Europe, and then there's a modern car driving puppy murderer in the fashion scene,
right, and then there's a lion, and then there's a big octopus, and then there's a chauvinistic
guy who's like a little too aggro. Yeah, yeah, it's just kind of a guy, yeah, he's got just a
little too proud of himself, right, and has a big musket, and then there's like, and then there's a
priest who sniffs hair, and then there's like the, not the devil, but the king of the underwears,
like the manifestation of evil. I mean it's, look it's interesting as you add it all up,
but I'm a little curious what Villains Land is going to be, how do you justify getting the car
driving fashionista together really lion? Yeah, they're gonna, that's, that is fun in a way to
try to figure out what this like, like the narrative, because they will come up with I think a
narrative to put all the villains together. I'm assuming the biggie ticket will have all the
villains on it in some way. Are you assuming that? I wouldn't, my bet would be that it's kind of like,
that they'd silo the worlds a little bit, because like they aren't, wait a minute, wait a minute,
you're, because you're going off of, remind me, the epic universe ticket, or whatever they call it,
is, is a combo of monsters. Yes, it's all of them. The Frankenstein experiment,
Monsters Unchained, the Frankenstein experiment, I believe is the full name.
So I'm just going from the art of villains, which is just one piece, but there appears to be some
sort of Maleficent roller coaster, and then there's something in the distance, and they don't really
even suggest what it is, but what would you want from a land with an e-ticket with all the villains,
you would want to ride with all the villains on it. But doesn't it not feel like something
Disney does other than, I guess there's things where the heroes get together, although Mickey
and the gang feel like one thing, and if a villain, I don't know, I kind of don't think they're going
to do it, but doesn't feel like Disney does. They silo the heroes, I think, more than the villains.
Sure. Like the villains, I feel like there's a lot more wiggle room, and especially on the cruise
ship, that again, seems like its own ecosystem. Well yeah, the rules are different. International
waters. Anything goes. I just think, what would you want from an e-ticket dark ride in the villain's
land, other than having all the villains? I'll bet, we could bet some money, I'll bet money that
it's some sort of dark ride with all the villains represented somehow. I will go against that. Yeah,
I think they'll keep them siloed. I just don't see what it would be then. What would the big villain's
thing be? It's like, I don't know, it's just an Ursula thing, or just a Evil Queen thing. I'll bet
a hundred dollars. A Jafar thing. I'll bet a hundred dollars that it's an e-ticket. I don't care about it,
I'll do twenty. Okay, we're betting twenty dollars. I don't think it's a combo of, now is that e-ticket,
this doesn't, I have to protect myself in case they say, it's the villain's carousel, where they are
all together, I don't want to go. Well, I assume they'll be, unless the thing like drastically
changes from just the art, which the art could be early, because some of the other art we don't
know, it's different than maybe where they're placing certain things, who knows. But if it
seems like it's pretty much a similar aesthetic, and like there's a coaster here, and then there's
an e-ticket, that's some sort of dark ride. Sure. Yeah, within reach. We know what we're talking about.
I think it has to have a lot of the villains. But the villain's wheel, a dreadfully dreary
ferris wheel where one car is 80s, that doesn't count. Okay, that doesn't count. But yes,
the d or e-ticket dark ride in Villain's Land, where like at least three different villains
of different types of stories interact at the very least. I really never thought about it.
Do you care enough to get in on that? I don't know. I saw someone speculating that like,
it looks like there's two roller coasters. I was like, I don't think they'll be two roller coasters.
I don't know if that would make any sense. I do think one of them will be Maleficent,
and they'll have the dragon. That's in the art. Yeah, that's in the art.
On the coaster area. But that's what you want from Villain's Land. What I want is a ride to see all
the villains. I want to see Chernobog hanging out with Scar. I want to see, you know, who is the
villain of Oliver and Company. There's kind of a bunch. They're all kind of just like lightly mean
humans. Yeah, do you want like Rattigan yelling at you? I would love Rattigan. I don't think it's
happening either. But yes, I want to see them all teaming up. What's the Pocahontas one? Is he like
Rally? Oh, the purple man. What is his name? Why can't I think of it? Is he a real man who existed?
That's a good question, too. I don't know. Probably. But also, you know, you could say
John Smith is the villain of Pocahontas in real life. Yes, yeah. You could say it's everyone
together who made the movie. But yeah, I think that's happening. Okay, yeah. All right. Well,
bet that'll pay off, maybe. We agreed two grand. But I don't think we'd be wise to take the bet
that within the land there will be a game show that is kooky and has a joke where all of the
characters. So yeah, this is, it's a Hollywood Squares, but it's all villains. We get a big,
were we all watching the same video? I feel like I only found one. Okay, so there's one, there's,
we're all going off of one piece of camcorder footage that I think was filming one of those,
the family probably of one of the contestants. Right. But so as said in the topic suggestion,
there's a, there's a live host and live contestants, but then it's all triggering
of video elements. So there's a lot of prerecorded stuff and there's an interactivity to it because
it responds and plays off the audience suggestions. But mostly this gets this kind of eerie screen
situation. Yeah. Oogie Boogie is the announcer. Then we start getting villains out. And who do
we get? We get, we got Kronk. So that's, that's the most like physically off guy. That's like a
cousin Greg's kind of like lanky guy doing like a little bit of a horror thing. And then Yzma. So
we got a pair from Emperors New Groove. Cruella De Vil. This is another where the, you know,
sometimes you have like, you have like evil queens with dark magic. And then you have
three ladies who are mean to one of their stepdaughter of the family. You have Drizella,
Anastasia, and Lady Tremaine. I never think about that character's name. Lady Tremaine.
I want to give me that Lady Tremaine coaster. I want to go imagine we're like in one of her
devilish nightmares. And the coaster goes through the, the track is in the shape of her hair,
the two big buns. I would love to see like online discourse of like,
guys, I love being part of the Disney fandom, but the toxic Lady Tremaine fans are starting to get
a little too much. It's got to be there somewhere. If you dig. Kind of related. I saw. I'm sick of
the Tremaniacs. I saw a take on Twitter because in the, the Marvel comics currently Storm of the
X-Men is getting her own solo series and she's joining the Avengers. And I saw someone go like,
finally Storm will get away from the toxic X-Men fans. And I went, what is this? This is what does
that even mean? What does this mean? Like, I don't know. I don't know. I hate to tell that person if
it's a female character in a movie, toxic fandom will find the character. Yeah. No, there's no
escaping it. Yeah. There's no escaping. It is a fictional female character in any form of media,
really. So yeah, Lady Tremaine's there. I'm quaking now. I can't, I want to get out of Luna.
I was scared of Lady Tremaine. She's so mean as a kid. I was just like, I don't like, she scares me.
No. She didn't have any powers. And of course that would, that would cause her to have the
most toxic fandom. Cause she was a mean lady. She was mean lady. Maybe you're right. I don't,
we'll look for it. We'll look for this fandom that exists. Go ahead. Get in the comments. Start
yelling at us. Jason, would you say you were attracted to Lady Tremaine in any way? I know,
Michael, don't be ridiculous. Okay. I'm a Drizella boy. Okay. You're more of a Drizella.
Got it. Yeah. No, I was afraid of all of these characters and not attracted to any of them.
I believe you. Maleficent's boy is, I really learned that it's Maleficent and I'm Maleficent
from the red squiggle under my Google doc notes. I'll fix that one forever now. And then Center
Square, Hades. Um, now Hades is present. We're going to touch on something else in this episode
a little bit, but the, uh, this is Hades as Center Square completely plays into the Paul Lind
right. Uh, mode of Center Square of kind of like showbiz, like the pizzazzy guy. They definitely
lean away from, I mean, I get, I don't know, it's in the spirit of the James Woods portrayal in that
James Woods was like a sleazy agent, fast talker, but they definitely go a lot more like, Hey,
Hey, you know, we're almost more in Green Goblin territory. Um, but just like, yo, yeah. Fun, fun
host. Hello. Which I wonder, I mean, I love it because it's like kind of a, it's like an affront
to James Woods. I don't think he would be happy with this portrayal. Right. So they're sticking
it to him on some level, I guess. Um, which puts him in it. I feel like there is a lot of demand
for Hades and Hercules. Yes. And he's at the different like show, like nighttime parties
at boogie boogie bash or whatever, like Hades. And he has like a light up hair now. I feel like
they have a good costume for him. The hair effect is really cool. Maybe they did that before. I just,
I think it's, I think it's paint and then they changed the lighting and then, so the hair,
but I'm not, I saw like a tick tock of it or something. Yeah. I was trying to figure it out
Hades and Dr. Doofenshmirtz are the new. Oh, well he's scared. Well, he's been before,
but now they have this weird nightmare version of him facially, uh, where it's like prosthetics
and it looks scary. That was our assessment. And then Jason seems to be like, I love it. I'm kind
of into it. I kind of, I mean, like, I think, uh, translating 2d animation to the 3d real world,
I kind of like taking a big, weird swing. I think is what appeals to me. It's scary. I mean,
I'm not against it being there. It is. I just, it is scary. It looked to me like if they made a,
uh, a gritty horror reboot of Sesame street, that's how they would portray Bert.
It looks like a horror point. Yeah. Yeah. I'm just, I think I was happy to see Phineas and
Ferb get some love. You're always hearing bluey this cocoa melon that you forgot. You are.
We've forgotten the roots. You were a Phineas and Ferb guy. I am. Well, cause I, when I went
to Disney where I'm like 2012 Perry, the platypus was everywhere. And I'm like, what is this? Who
is this guy? But you didn't know what it was until then. Yeah. I didn't know. And I came back. I
watched it. I was like, I like this show. It was fun. You got into Phineas and Ferb late. Yeah. A
late bloomer with Phineas and Ferb. I've never seen an episode. It's fun. You should see if your
daughter likes it. Sure. She likes a lot of stuff. Yeah. She likes bluey. She'd love a madam puppet.
She might love madam. Uh, so the, uh, the, the gangs together and now it becomes a, uh, the answering
of Disney trivia off, which, and all this reminded me how terrible I would be at this. Yeah. Once
they got to, what's the name of the Raven in Sleeping Beauty? You got me. Yeah. I wouldn't have
known. Yeah. Yeah. I do not know. Um, I was proud to not, look, I know a lot of Arcania, but there's
gotta be, my, my brain has to not have room for some things. Yeah. And it's not like Disney parks
trivia, which we would do better. No, that's all I think. Although I mean, we know some stuff about
the movies. It's just that it's like, who is the like old man that owns the big thunder mountain
railroad and part of his T bullion? Like that's type of stuff we could, we could get, but yeah.
Yeah. But that's not what they're doing here. Name, name, uh, Timon's friend. Um, uh,
Ron. What? Ron and Timon. I think it's Ron. I think it's Ron. Um, I, I don't know. I was like,
I might be growing on the idea of growing on a cruise, but I'm like, I don't think I'd want to
play games. No. Like I don't want to do trivia. I, I'm sure there's a way that you don't have to do
that, but if there's that point where like, what is there to do now? And that's one of the things
and the other is go sit in your room. I mean, there's bar, there's always bars and for me,
there would always be bars. I think it's like, Oh, I don't want to do pirates. No, thank you.
Like, yeah, I don't want to dress like a pirate. I want to party with the gorn. I want to see
old character actors, like cover bands, and I want to, um, swing with other Star Trek couples,
Mike, which is what you do on a Star Trek. That's allowed. Yes. You look for the upside down. It's
not a pineapple on that ship. It's like an upside down enterprise, you know? Yeah. Or, uh,
Romulan ale bottle that's empty or something. Nice. Nice. Yeah. It sounds like you've already
made up your mind. I will. If the Star Trek crews left from California, it would be easier. Where
does it leave from? I think it's Florida, the one we talked about at least. Oh yeah. That's
well, next year's going to Miami, uh, Belize city. Um, yeah. But you're, wait a minute. You got,
you got Mulgrew, you got Frakes. I mean, I'm sure you, I'm sure it's too late at this point. I think
it's too late for this, this round, but yeah. Yeah. Um, all right. We'll start, start making
the case for 26. Um, so yeah, well, you actually, you know, we're sort of what you were saying,
Jason, about, uh, the, that Phineas and Ferb character that we, it is like weird physicalizing
of Hades, especially has kind of a fiddler from Bible man. Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh yeah. It's all like
face paint and glopped on prosthetics. And I for one was happy to see characters presented in not
such a brand managed kind of way. Yes. Sure. It's kind of strange and cheesy. I don't know if this
is the answer either, but I kind of love that they're like, yeah, just put it, I don't know,
put some on actors, do it like a play. Yeah. And I, yeah, the only, the only thing is like,
I just, yeah, I wish they were live because it would be much more of a fun show. I think we'll
get to talking about that. But yes, I, I do like that you can, you felt a little bit less like,
oh, they only can only say something from the movie in this in the same way that Deadpool at
California adventure has been saying stuff where you go, wow, the, did this get past some people
at the part of the company? So yeah, it's been, I can't believe how on board all of us are with
this so far. I am honestly a little disappointed because it doesn't seem like they did a ton of
Halloween stuff at Avengers campus. Oh, well, I think they should have had Deadpool take over
the place. I don't know. Maybe that's coming. I don't know. I guess it's Halloween. Well,
we're doing this in the past, so I don't know. We'll see if something has emerged. I know he's
more of an anti-hero than a villain, but like Deadpool takes over. That could be a fun daytime
thing. Sure. What do you, what do you think he like puts decorations on? What do you mean? What
do you think? Oh, some decorations, some fake graffiti. He's going to spray paint Avengers.
Yeah. Okay. Well, draw up a for Halloween. Yeah. Draw up a proposal. Like some streamers and like
carve pumpkins with the Deadpool symbol in them. So far, Jason is suggesting kind of like a
church rec room takeover. Maybe some punch could be there. Like a hell house. Like, oh, that's a
deeper thing. You know what? You know what? Here, how about this? And maybe this is sort of what
you're after. It would be like Stitch in the magic kingdom. That's exactly it. So he TPs Avengers,
like he puts toilet paper all over the Avengers headquarters or whatever the hell it's called
or pim test kitchen. He like makes it look like shit is what I'm saying. He paints a sign on the
like building. He's like, when is this thing opening? Yeah, sure. Okay. All right. That's,
that's a level. Okay. Let me add to this. He dresses up like other characters too. So he's
in his Deadpool outfit, but then he has like Loki's helmet on. That's good. He's Loki as well or
something. So it's a Halloween takeover. That's good. Yeah. That's not bad. Chains himself to the
wall to get red car trolley saved. That's right. Yeah. So we got to talk about that in another
episode. I'm upset. We can't do it. So what you end up with here because like it's, it's nine
characters who have to be represented and only one is answering and interacting for the most part to
all of these answers. You could tell that I was just like, Oh, they had to film like a lot of
Lady Tremaine, just like sitting there kind of looking around, not like scratching her nose,
but just sitting blinking, just the amount of shooting just for, for there to be nothing in
the space. I wonder if it loops at like 10 minutes or something. Yeah, maybe. Probably. I would think.
Yeah. Well, there's a lot of resets because one character takes over the whole screen and then
get smells that kind of like wipes it. But nonetheless, so much, a lot of, it must've been
like a, just a very awkwardly silence shoot. Yeah. Yes, for sure. And then, I don't know, in terms
of like any like moments in this or a actors that we liked, is there anything that jumped out?
I mean, you can't go wrong with Gaston in general. Oh, I forgot Gaston when I was saying all the names.
Right. Like he's just, I, we've talked about, we did an episode on it. I like,
I like the different interpretations. It's a fun character to do. And this guy is also pretty fun.
So he adds a quote, they forget what they ask him about your five year anniversary. What is an
appropriate gift? And they, cause it would be wood. It's the wood anniversary. Apparently we've
talked about this recently. We've learned about diamond and platinum in regards to
paper. We learned that you made up platinum anniversary entirely. That was never anything
Disney was talking about. Yeah. We didn't really touch on that as much. They never said platinum
anniversary. No, but that is the official traditional 70. But that is what it would be called if they
were going to call the diamond in the 60 on the 60th in Disneyland. But yeah, he, he answers like
with, he's going to give Bell a wooden something with horns on it or whatever.
Well, he actually, they say what we do for an anniversary. And I think it's pretty good joke.
He says, what is an anniversary? And then there's a pause for like a laugh break. Yeah. You're right.
Sorry. Yeah. And it, it, uh, the laugh, like the audience does not react, but I was like,
I actually think that's a pretty solid joke. You got to think about, yeah, that he's never had a
relationship enough for there to be an anniversary. Right. Well, the jokes said by the people
prerecorded don't land. Sure. In this, maybe there was some audience. Yeah. Yeah. The, the
hosts jokes and the comments from like the kids will get laughs. Yeah. But the actual video is
such an awkward, like it's, it's a combination of the jokes are okay mixed with the timing of it
all. Even I think this is well done technically seemingly. Yeah. And even that, even the best
version of it is just awkward and laggy. It is impressive. There is about a one or two second
pause from like asking the villain. And then you can tell the tech person is triggering an option,
but there is a slight pause and that's, it just kind of makes my skin crawl.
Yeah. You there and know that this is, oh, come on, don't pause for too long.
Yeah. So it's, I had to watch it a couple of times. I'm like, okay, are they in a studio
somewhere on the ship? No, I did briefly. I'm like, wait a minute. No, I thought like very polite of
you to think that live feeds. I, but then yeah, obviously I'm like, wait, they would have to have
nine different backgrounds, nine different cameras feet. And I'm like, that's ridiculous. And like,
I don't think cruise ships, they're not really wasting space on sound stages, you know?
So wait, your thought was to make it so they could have different backgrounds. They would have like
little rooms elsewhere on the ship and they would be recording it. Well, they would be in one room.
Maybe they would have nine different dreams. It quickly fell apart. Okay. Because then why
wouldn't they just be out there? Right. Right. That's the question. Well, that's, that was the
other thing with the camcorder footage. I was like, is this a set? Cause these are villains that
the other thing we were going to mention today are in that show. So I was like, okay, I could see
they have the costumes for a show. It would make sense to use the actors here too. But that's a
different, that's a different ship, my friend. That's where that falls apart. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
This is very trusting, I feel like of Hollywood Magic on Jason's part. Right. Yeah. You're very
sweet. I was trying to figure out if I was producing this, what are all the options? It's
like, okay, live feed, live actors, prerecorded video options, and someone is triggering them.
Yeah. The main concern would be getting the show off at five o'clock so you could be asleep by six.
Well, yeah. Well, some of these kids, who knows what time their bedtime is on the ship? Who knows
if they've had a nap? Cast a wider net if you, you know, the earlier you do it. You put the kids to bed
and then the parents can go to the pirate night, you know? Well, no way they're doing villains night,
pirate night on the same night. Come on now. You don't think they split the ship? Half pirates,
half villains? No, I think the whole like pirate day takes scenes to take over the whole ship.
Okay. I don't know. I'm a Disney wish. You live it up. You go high octane, anything's possible.
You know what seems fun to me? You pick one of the ports, you don't get off the ship. So then you have
full rain over all the amenities on the ship. Okay. So I think what he's saying is, you know,
sometimes these ships will dock somewhere and you would get off and have a day at an island or
something. But you can also stay on the ship. Jason's saying if you stay on the ship that day,
instead of going and exploring, you have more, you can run, like, because everybody leaves the ship,
he's saying, or a lot of people do. So you will have more room on the ship, I suppose. Well,
there's less lines. Less of a line at the buffet that day. Restaurants, buffets, waterslides,
you know? Yeah. I guess that's a good strategy. That's fucking miserable though. You're going to
not get off. Well, it depends on how long that ship, how long it's the cruises. It depends. I
mean, regular cruisers are like, eh, we pulled into Nassau. We've seen Nassau before. We're just
going to have a relaxing day on the ship. We've seen the bugs at Castaway Cay or whatever.
At Lighthouse Point. Lighthouse Point. At Lookalke. It is so long. I can't remember the name of
whatever that is either. Disney opened a new, like, part, it's part of an island. People live
on the island. They fixed the bug problem though. Did they fix the bug problem? I think so. Disney
opened a new thing and there was a big bug problem. It was a big problem. You remember though,
there was like, there was a buffet and like, there was bugs covering the food in the buffet.
I think it's Lighthouse Point at Lookalke. It's so long. I will take your word for that.
I don't remember. And it was filled with bugs. It was very spread out. You should have stayed
on the boat in that situation. Should have stayed on the boat. And gotten on that waterslide faster.
Yeah. There's the aqua mouse and then one ship has the aqua duck.
Okay. Like aqua duck. And you got that thing to yourself if you don't, if you can see.
You want to be so blase about Nassau that you don't, we've seen Nassau. But so, you know,
whatever. This thing seems like fine. You passed 20 minutes watching this. They were gearing up
for another round, which was not filmed. And I was like, sounds fine to me. I think one gave me
the idea. I said it already, but like, I think this would be so fun if it was nine live performers.
Sure. I think this would kill every night versus this where it dies. But I really think the idea
is good. And I'm sure at one point they had the idea of just having it be live performers and they
were like, yeah, but we can save a lot of money if we pay everybody $200. And that's it. We just
have it. Well, I don't, I don't know if there, there may have been something else on the ship
with actors. This might've been like, you know, there are the, you know, especially the Disney
ships tend to have theaters, but maybe they were like, yeah, we got to figure out something for
this big screen. And it's limited if it's like a Halloween specific thing or a limited time thing.
This might've been meant to be just a brief thing. But I guess you get more of the fun with the thing
that we stumbled into while looking into this, because watch this, this is fine. Then YouTube
starts recommending other cruise ship things. And there's some channel and I forget the name,
apologies, but there is a channel that has like pro shot versions of tons of the productions on
the ships, which might provide future content for us in some way. We might've run into that before
with, uh, with Kevin Perch for a long time ago, but what, but that led us to something related.
And I would have to say superior. And that is a, another cruise ship show that was performed on
the Disney magic and the Disney dream. And this is called villains tonight. Uh, villains tonight
is a actual full theatrical production. Uh, that does get all of the villains together. Um,
I was going to say not all at once, although, but then the finale, they're all together,
but it is this like original story that is, that is a little, that's tied together by Hades,
primarily that takes you to see all of the villains and they all perform their iconic
villain songs, if not other songs that are fun surprises. You could do that. And that could be
the ride really, if not, they think about it. That's the narrative and they all sing their songs.
Hades taking a trip to see if he can fill up the evil ometer. Yeah, pain and panic doing
with very much reminded me of like kids in the hall style characters.
Hell yeah.
I feel like they're kind of doing like.
Are you saying the evil ones?
They're just like Simon and Hiccubus.
Yeah. I think, yeah, that was one.
Yeah. Uh, yeah. Uh, so this, again, we're back to, we're back to a Hades who's like
glop ton makeup and funny plastic hair. Uh, again, they've really decided on this particular
Hades characterization, which is fun. And I think what we, when I, what I was like,
I was just like, let me skim through this and see if this is worth talking about. And I landed,
cause I didn't know anything about it. I didn't know what it was. And I didn't know until I landed
on a certain point that there was topical comedy involved. And I was just like, is this worth
talking about on the show? Let me just skim here. And I literally landed on Hades saying, uh,
I make Hannibal Lecter look like Paula Dean. All right, you're going in, you're in. And this is
full context here. He's then once I backed up and I saw the rest of what he's saying,
he's trying to prove how evil he is with these topical jokes. And there's a little run of them.
One is I make Lord Voldemort look like Hello Kitty, which does you grown at, but I was also like,
I could see Trevor Noah making that joke about Trump five years ago.
It is on the level. Yeah. That's completely, that would work. That would be in the,
that would get a lot. Uh, but then right after that, I make Hannibal Lecter look like Paula
Dean. Right. And this really knocked me back for a few reasons. One Trump has been mentioning
Hannibal Lecter nonstop. Right. Uh, so that was weird. Then it's, it, you're watching this joke.
I don't know when this was performed, but hearing that in 2024, it's such a riddle because Hannibal
Lecter, okay, that's evil. Okay. But Paula Dean, now we know some not very good things about it,
which was not true then. So it makes you now have to like, you have to like get out paper and do
kind of an SAT analogy thing. Like, so what are they saying? Hannibal Lecter. Okay. But if Paula
Dean is bad, so what does, so what does that make Hades look like? He's just somebody who's a racist
or somebody specifically, but then Hannibal Lecter was very charming as well. I don't know
what he's saying here. Yeah. It's, it's a real riddle. If it was, if that same joke was done with
a barefoot Contessa, you would understand. Yeah. Yeah. You would have to change it now.
History has made this joke a very strange joke. It's a real weird math problem now. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, I think Jane and I were able to figure out when exactly, like pinpoint when exactly this
was from. I was doing that, that game the whole time. Cause I'm like,
I parrot, I, they say that like the new iPad. So when is, I kind of remember, and then there's
like a lot of this like Lindsay Lohan stuff somewhere. Okay. I think I sort of, but when,
what did you pin it to? So, uh, in the description of the YouTube video, it says it was taped off
in room TV in 2015. Oh, but in terms of the actual content, there is a single ladies joke.
Oh, that's the biggest data. That's the, that's the tell because he says nice two-year-old reference.
Oh, so that means this production is from 2010. Okay. That's what I, yeah. I remember
iPad was putting it there for me kind of, because I remember there was a funnier dive
video where Pee Wee got an iPad. It was right before I started working there, which is 2010.
That's the, the, the peripheral clues I have to date stamp that specific era sing. Also,
a lot of these things we're talking about are all prime California venture genie stuff. Yeah.
He did. They were probably like, I wonder if they were like emailing areas back and forth.
Maybe. Yeah. Here's the genie and Hades. Hades and the genie. Yeah. Here's what
for this one. This has been working at the California adventure show. You should try it.
Yeah. Yeah. There's, I mean, in terms of like, yeah, what else we're dealing with, I guess,
this is, I mean, the show is fine and the performances are, but like, you know what
we're about. We're, we're, I'm just writing down references. Yeah. Like, all right. Hey, welcome
everybody. Hey, not quite a Jonas Brothers welcome, but all right. Elsewhere in that I make such and
such look like such and such the one after the Paula Dean one is, uh, I make, uh, I'm just going
to say Lindsay Lohan and let you guys write your own joke, which is not that then you didn't make
a joke. So I don't know if that counts. I also later, first of all, how dare Disney betray her
like that. And now the money that she made them and then Howard make it fun around the cruise ship.
And then later, here's one of the biggest mysteries to solve. I don't know if you guys
clock this one too. Uh, so Lindsay Lohan's brought up again. She just got me the nicest necklace.
Then there's a trickle of laughter. And then he says, now work everybody. Uh, everybody get that.
That's going to get it. Okay. Let's, uh, um, which I don't mind that kind of that delivery or
construct, but I, I was like, I don't, I don't know. I was, I'm not going to Google it. I'm
going to ask if you guys know, do you understand Lindsay Lohan just got Hades the nicest necklace?
Did, did she shoplift? Yes. Jane, Jane clock that she remembered the story. Uh, Lindsay Lohan,
uh, was stealing at some point. Okay. Got it. Okay. So that's, and how did that play? I wonder
if you were sitting in your room watching this in 2015. Wait, hold on a second. Jason, hold on.
Lindsay Lohan is sentenced to jail over necklace stuff. May 12th, 2011. Oh, well, oh, interesting.
Well, wait a minute. Well, but when did it happen? When did the, all right, she faced the judge
in February, 2011. There's a surveillance tape that was shown by the jeweler. This video,
this was on ABC news in March. Hmm. So it seems like it could have happened a year prior. I think
this is an early 2011 story is where this is where I'm seeing all of the articles about it.
Hmm. Huh. So that could have been more off the cuff. The single ladies, like reference
and he could have been referring to the iPad too. Hmm. Like that was the new iPad. And also
maybe they were not that specific about any of this stuff. Right. That's also something that
factors in. Yeah. When they said two years, they meant three years. Right. Uh, I also feel like
they would just do all the single Hades today still. Yeah, of course. That would work. Yeah,
that would work. Yeah. That's an interesting little hmm. Hmm. That, um, there's another moment
there. They're talking about villains, like crossover stuff. Hook and Smee and all the crew
of their ship saying like, yo ho, a pirate's life for me. Yeah. Uh, but then when Hook steps away,
the crew sings a rockin' version and Jane very dryly. Yeah, rockin' version. Like she was falling
asleep. She went, that's a Jonas Brothers version from Disney Mania, I think. And like,
Ben was dead asleep. So that sounds right. Okay. Uh. So Jonas Brothers did a rock and roll version
of yo ho, yo ho, a pirate's life for me. Yeah, I think Disney Mania was like rock and roll versions
of the songs. Okay. Got it. Yeah. And again, I think that's how the Jonas Brothers thought of
themselves as a real rock and roll kind of band. Rock and roll band, yeah. They were, yeah. They
were like the stray cats, you know. Yeah, that's, you know, we're kind of trying to do a modern
stray cats thing. That's kind of our deal. I just got recommended a full stray cats concert on
YouTube and I zoomed through it a little bit. This is all right. Within five years, Mike's a big cruise
guy and a big stray cats guy. Yeah. And honestly, Scott, I went back to all those old episodes
where we talked shit about Setzer and I deleted every bit of that because that was an affront
to some of the finest music I ever made. Him keeping the spirit, the rockabilly spirit alive.
Yeah. Information warfare in favor of the stray cats. Deleting the past.
Delete the past to save the future of rockabilly.
So what else reference wise? Cruella walks on to Yeah, Usher's Yeah. That's definitely more than
two years old. Geez, pick up a Shakeweight. There's another good one. Genie for sure,
Shakeweight jokes in California. Like there's so many overlaps with that California Adventure
show. Shakeweight for sure. There's a joke at some point about like Disney making a sequel
that's not directed DVD. Boy, there's a joke from the past. Yeah. Now the now the they're promoting
there was going to be a Moana show that got turned into a movie. Yeah. You know, straight to DVDs
these days. Yeah. DVDs whatsoever. Yeah. That's why this video is villains tonight is really beyond
portals that take you to different parts of the underworld. It's a portal back to, I guess,
2011. Right. A time machine. Which also where also there was different connotations to like,
hey, you're fired. Trump can do it. So can I. I do it with better hair. It's just apprentice stuff.
Yeah. It's just apprentice references. Simpler time. Yeah. Yeah. Wait, who does Haiti say that?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Mm hmm. Of course. That's a yeah. Makes sense. Mm hmm. So let's see. Oh,
the show turns into a villain talk show called Hot Talk where Chades hosts Arizona and says,
because if evil exists anywhere, it's in daytime talk. I mean, have you seen the view?
It's not that that would work. A lot of that. That's the thing with a lot of these, like,
I think they would just do for a cruise ship. I think you'd do the same Trump joke because like
that's what's Trump is very politicized, but you could still do. I think hair is still okay.
I think he might be a joke. Yeah. Yeah. JD Vance might, uh, you know, the media wants to tell you
that this guy's hair is weird. It's not weird. It's not weird. Their hair is weird. Wall's hair
is weird. There's not enough of it. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. And then like a very normal laugh.
JD Vance would be very ha ha ha ha ha. Hello. Ha. I like the show, you know, some singing stuff,
you know, it all makes sense. Uh, uh, yeah. Uh, you know, he would end the tyranny of the
searing humor of villains tonight. Uh, but you could still do the same view joke. You'd still
do all the single Hades. Yeah. Yeah. I think Shake Weight's still getting a laugh, even though
Shake Weight isn't anything anyone thinks about now. Right. A lot of this stuff is evergreen. I
think there has not been a replacement mechanism that's very popular that feels like jerking off
unless I'm forgetting one. I don't think there's been any sort of jerking off. What happened to
innovation? Where is our nude jerk off simulator that airs on QVC? Yeah. And nothing has caught
fire like the Shake Weight. No, no. I mean, there might, there has to be something, but yeah, it's
not, it's not penetrated this. So the consciousness of the world, like the Shake Weight. No pun
intended. No pun intended, actually. I did mean it. Oh, you did? Yeah. Um, there's also some back
story. This is some of the, if we're talking about combining villains in this Villain's Land way,
you get a little bit of mythology and a little bit of new storytelling, that being that the
Snow White Queen and Hades hooked up on Castaway Key. Right. So you get Castaway Key reference,
which we like. That's a real obscure Disney, you know, Disney cruise joke. Um, so then that's,
that's a little bawdy, you know, for a cruise ship kind of a thing, you know? They don't,
you wouldn't think that they would say that on the cruise. They'd have to keep things PG.
Yeah. Are you, are you trying to give them credit or are you offended? That's what I understand by
that too. I think in all the times of, and that's a little, you're trying to like, you're dancing on
the line. Yeah. Did they, did they like snorkel together or like stand in the hamburger hot dog
line together? Like. You're interested in the non-hookup parts. You're interested in what the
rest of the date was. I'm interested in the mechanics of the hookup. Like, unless they got
a private cabana, there's not a ton of privacy on the island, I feel like. I'm going to say this.
If they, and I'm going to get a little bawdy here, Mike. Uh oh. If they, if the hooking up involved
any going down, I hope Hades was careful about that hair. He's got fire for hair. You've got to
be careful with that specific act. Yeah. Can Hades change the temperature of his hair though? I sure
hope so. Or this guy's never getting laid. You would assume he could. I mean, it changes color
and definitely, I mean, it definitely changes like size and volume of fire, but I hope that he could
turn it. Or is it like eternal flame and he can't ever. It's all the same. He dies if you shut it
off. So that curses him to never have oral sex. Does she have a level of invulnerability?
The queen? The queen? Yeah. I don't think she's got anything that protects you from having a
literal fire crotch. That's not what I meant. That's more of a carnival cruise line joke,
fire crotch. Also Hades, he's a villain. He's not maybe such a giving lover. He might not even be
interested in doing that. That's true. When you're dealing in villain sex, that's villainous to not,
to not be reciprocal. These are a lot of people who are worried about their own pleasure only.
Right. He's selfish. Where does that leave you? Do all the villains just kind of like jerk themselves
off and just watch each other? I don't know. This is a whole world of people who might not never
like commingle physically. What if Gaston and Lady Tremaine hooked up? What would that look
like? Gaston's not giving, he's very selfish. It'd be beautiful hair wise, that much we know.
Certainly if they procreated it, it would be the greatest hair. The child would have great hair.
By the way, I was looking up Drizella image search and there are websites. Drizella nude
image search. AI generator, make real life person hook up with Drizella. Upload Jason Sheridan
photo and make me, make Jason kiss Drizella. But like on the Disney Wiki, she is listed as Drizella
Tremaine, which yeah, I guess that would be her last name if Lady Tremaine is her mother. Drizella
Sheridan. Draw it on a notebook. A notebook for a high school class. Drizella Sheridan. XO, XO.
Why do you think Drizella as opposed to Anastasia? What's that? I don't know. For Jason you mean?
Yeah, if you're looking at the two, what makes you pick Drizella? The name? I think you like
the name better, right? I think I like the name. Yeah. Well Anastasia, was the other one named
Anastasia? I believe so. Well that just makes me think of the other animated film. Well that's
hardly her fault. That came years after the fact. She didn't ask for that. I think maybe I have to
give Anastasia some attention after that comment. Scott is an Anastasia guy and Jason's a Drizella
guy. AI prompt. Scott or Anastasia Gairdner. XO, XO. Hart on notebook. High school notebook.
The only thing going in that notebook besides notes is the Stussy S, okay? The what? That you
draw the three line, you connect the S. Oh, that's what that's called? I thought it was called. Well
there's a big discussion about whether you call because I've run into people who call that the
cool S, not the Stussy S. Well it is definitely the cool S. I see it as cool S on Wikipedia,
but it can be called. At some point I was taught that cool S is the proper, that technically it's
not the logo of Stussy. Although even though growing up I exclusively called it. Stussy actually,
the logo is like handwritten. It says cool S, universal S, Stussy S, the super S, the pointy S,
the banksy S, the surfer's S, and the graffiti S. Wikipedia has all those names listed. I mean
they all seem apropos. So I guess you can call it a lot of different things. I'm glad, I'm actually
glad that you consider Stussy in the running because I feel like people have said that's not
a fair thing to call it, but look it's in the, you could see why the mix-up would occur. Yeah,
of course. It's in the zeitgeist. It's in the ether. Yeah, in dealing with cool S's.
It's in the zeitgeist, yeah. Anyways, what else do we not say? Well I like, I will say like yeah,
this production itself looks like it has some money involved. There's different backdrops,
there's different, like the costumes are pretty good. Well I think there were probably high caliber
Broadway level productions on many of these ships and maybe it's our duty to check them out now.
Actually I would pose to the listener what are interesting ones of these that we need to
pursue because clearly a lot are on this one particular channel. The Ursula tentacles are
awesome. I mean I know the front ones are probably just string, but somehow the
back tentacles, she turns around and those are moving too and I'm like how is she triggering
those? Yeah. That's cool. So I wish the budget of the Hollywood Square show was this, like at this
level because I think that would have improved the show. I think that would have made that show a lot
better. Well no regrets because one led us to the other. That's true. You know, the villain's game
night was the path to lead us to this and to further you down the path of being a cruise person. Do we
say Project Cruel was a show sort of they did in the show? We have not talked about Project Cruel.
Yeah I think it's like Project Runway is the idea. Oh okay. Yes there were Project Runways.
Is that a Cruella De Vil kind of stuff? Yes. She changed his outfits. Yes. So yeah that's another
topical and again they have the like logo. They made a logo for Project Cruel and they did a whole
thing but this is and I've said this before and I don't want the eventual Villain's Land e-ticket
to be this. That's not my pitch for it but this is the only area where you will now get some sort
of original story. Going forward everything has to be IP. Everything has to be like kind of a book
report of a movie but the only way we get to have any fun now is if you mash up existing characters
into certain lands. So I feel like the villains could the Villain's Land be the last?
This is our last chance. A last sort of like oh it's a kind of a surprising like narrative.
I mean I guess Avengers will see that's a new story at least. So if these if they don't if we
don't do a topical parody show a late topical parody show with all the villains like for example
they all vacation at the same evil resort the Black Lotus. Right. If they don't do the live stage
parody the Black Lotus. Yeah. It's a sexy getaway that provides ample hookup opportunities but also
betrayal opportunities. Right. If there's not this in the park then what do we get? Right it's and
it's because you look at everything else Zootopia, Tangled, Frozen, Pan all that stuff is like all
the characters from those movies are in the ride and I'm sure. Book report ride. Book report ride
but you're not going to get like a little surprise like this is the only zone I feel like left where
you can get little little surprises. We take what we can get now because there's just will never be
in a completely original ride or land ever again. The thing I've been thinking about and like looking
into is that a lot of these after hours the after hours parties I haven't really gone to
but the more and more I read about them. You mean like Oogie Boogie Bash at Disneyland. Like Oogie
Boogie Bash. Yeah. Or like so like. After hours parties. You threw me off for a second. That is
what they call it. Yeah which after hours parties. Which after hours party are you going to? But like
the like you went to a flashback one. Yeah the 80s one. Like an 80s night. Yeah. So
that is where I think stuff is getting interesting. There's like unique characters
wait times are a lot shorter. There's an Oogie Boogie Bash obviously there's free candy. Well
there's street trails. There's street trails. There's a villains parade. Let's say there's
horsemen. There's free candy for how much admission? What 180 dollars? Yeah 100 bucks or something.
More 100 bucks. Free candy but. But. It's in the cost of the ticket. So that's what he would be
saying. It's really the best value. You're not finding a better way to get candy for cheap.
And if you really. Going to Anaheim booking a ticket five months in advance. And you spend your
whole time doing tree trails. Yeah you spend and I saw someone go like all right I filled up my
bag but I have an empty backpack. So I'm dumping the candy there and filling the bag again. And
that's just good sense. We got to get you next year. We got to go next year. We got to see how
much treats how many treats you can get. I am set on going next year. All right good yeah. But what
my main point is like wait this the interesting stuff at the parks might be isolated at these
after hour parties. Like extra characters. Yeah when we say interesting we mean Judge Doom will
be there or something. Yeah Judge Doom will be there. And I agree I agree with you. It's just
putting it in context of what I'm talking about. There might be that you know that's where you get
yeah Judge Doom doing a dance to a three-year-old Doja Cat song. Right yeah. That's what we mean
by interesting. But a lot of what has been siloed at the after hours parties it's like they should
be doing this every day at the park. This should be default park experience. It would be nice if
you could see Max in his power line outfit. Yes. At the regular day time. Max in his power line
outfit like. It's funny these are the stakes of what. You guys have both been doing political
you've both been like pounding the sides of your and I say this you're pointing and like hitting
the chair you know in a debate fashion and all this is in service of Max and his power line outfit.
Yes. Well we want look we want we want innovation. We want interesting surprises when we go to these
parks. We don't want just your your standard big six characters. We want to see fun around every
corner and for us that means seeing the great mouse detective in a place where you would normally
only see Mickey. I don't know. I I might be stressed out by big great mouse detective. What.
You say that. Like it's like six feet tall. He's not going to be tiny. Yeah I know. You'll be
stressed out by him. I just it might be like the big muppets. Like. Oh it wouldn't be like the big
muppets. Wait a minute. Jason the entire history of Disneyland is centered around a mouse character
made big. Why is this a new premise. He's a cipher. Mickey Mouse can be anything. But there's
plenty of other mice. There's so there's the Cinderella mice. There's ample examples of big
mice in the park. And you draw the line now at great mouse detective. It might be big. I don't
know. Big Beasel might stress. I don't know. Would you be mad if the aristocats have suits
and they're much bigger than normal cats. I think I've been trying. I think that's been around long
enough. It's that it's new. What. You have to have been. You have to have known about something.
I have to have been acclimated. Yeah. There's got to be a great mouse detective walk around
suit somewhere. Somewhere. Yeah I would think. But you creeped out by the idea of it. I don't
know. I'd have to give it some thought. Well OK. Yeah you think sleep on it I guess. But still.
Jason Jason has a bag full of free very efficiently gotten tootsie pops and he he comes
and he comes. I don't. You just said Basil not Basil. Fuck off. I hate. We're not so different.
It's got to you if you need to remember it's to to tootsie. Goodbye. That's a good way to remember.
Yeah. You guys are right. Tootsie is a world of death. What is he even saying.
Language is Scott even speaking right now. Did you go into German for a second. Tootsie is cute
though. All right. Well here I'll change it to Twizzlers motherfuckers. You've found a corner
with a bag full of Twizzlers. You see a slightly tall great mouse detective throw the bag and go
running. Yeah. That's right. He's a good guy. A big rat again would I think I'd be more OK with
because he's mean and scary. But he's little too. He's also little. It doesn't. But he's big. But
he's bigger than the rest of them. I don't understand what you're saying. I don't get it.
But I believe I believe in your heart. You are afraid of it. So I will respect your
feelings even though I don't understand them. Let me just say that. I'm trying to understand
them myself. Well the next time you're talking to a therapist maybe this is what you focus on
to try to figure it out. Just a just a billable hour. Are you OK with Big Fievel.
That was really weird. Well I met Big Fievel. We've showed the picture of me meeting Big Fievel.
You seemed fine with it. Yeah I'm OK with that. OK. So therapy session. I guess you know what I
think I'm ready to get into is I have a thing about big mouse costumes that are new. If I grew
up with it I'm fine with it. But if there was a new one hypothetically I it's it's my biggest fear.
Yeah. So you saw a great mouse. No I thought about seeing a great mouse detective. And it sent me
into a spiral. I think because a lot of the shots in the movie emphasize that they are little
and London is happening around. I still I I know I understood the word you said. It still doesn't
quite make sense to me. But I I again I respect what you're saying. But I would like to I would
like to see a big mouse detective. Basil. His name is Basil. Excuse me. Yeah. Basil. Basil. All
right. Did we talk about what I forget. Did we talk about the right topics today. I believe we
did as far as I know. OK I think we did. I think if you were doing a checklist then we covered
everything on the check. Mike's a cruise guy. I'm going to be a cruise guy eventually. I have a lot
of weird boundaries about character size. Deadpool should take over Avengers campus at Halloween.
And Drizella should take over you sexually. Look I don't want to speak out of turn but I will let
Drizella ruin my life. I've been saying Druzella I think since Drizella. It's more like Drizella.
We've all been saying everything weird and wrong. That's what we're finding. And that
podcasting folks. There's a lot of characters we don't know. We know Barnabas T. Bullion.
We don't know Drizella. Drizella. We don't know. That's the difference. It's the ride versus the
movies. We're ride guys. We're the ride guys. No we're not the ride guys. That's an official
universal. That's an official universal thing. Yeah and it pisses me off. We are the ride guys.
Those guys aren't the ride guys. No they're not. No. And that's when if we said this on air what
Tony Baxter called us the ride guys once. And if he says it. Because I think people are still
confused by podcast the ride. I think that's still a confusing title for people. Every once in a while
yes. There's still confusion about it. Why do they write podcasts here? There's not confusion
if you're listening because that means that you survived well what in this case is haunt cast the
fright. Oh yeah. The cemetery gate. If you want to grave dig even deeper join us on our
RIP tier crypt three where you get one more boonus episode for just three more bones a month. That
one was on purpose guys. I know. I said boonus not as a mistake. Are we good? Yeah I think we're fine.
You were good.