they did the mash they did the podcast mash the podcast mash it was a modest
smash a modest mesh three guys ramble for cash the podcast mash they disagreed
about the flash it's uh hey what's up uh here on haunt cast the fright the
cemetery gate I'm Scott Boris Gerdner joined by Mike Boris Carlson I wrote
the full names out even though I know your names I was like the Boris is gonna
trip me up and then I wrote Mike Boris Sheridan what the wrong fuck it's Jason
Boris Sheridan yeah Jesus I don't know it's look there's a lot to think about
about there's the established spooky names which I've departed from and we're
doing these putting Boris in places Boris isn't usually I'm a mess I'm
your ramble your nightmare your biggest nightmare is a scientist combines Jason
and I in a lab and like a horrible experiment and then you have to deal
with both of our annoying stuff at when one person that's so that's what's I
think happening season a one-stop shop isn't the easier to do one person yeah
harder with two then like then somebody talking about coupons and apps where you
get medical results it can't become a conversation it stays in one body right
so actually a mad scientist could do me a lot of good okay well then you should
find the mad scientist to do it to combine Jason and I just like down the
middle I guess makes the most sense well in the modern way to find two of us if
we did down the middle then there's two yeah there's a Jason Carlson and Michael
Sheridan no that's what I know that's what you really don't want that's like
in there is my father's actual name Wow Oh Michael Sheridan okay this monster
exists in reality yeah I bet mad scientists are fairly easy to find
because I think in the modern world if you want a mad scientist just find
anyone who Joe Rogan talks to as a regular doctor or scientist he had a mad
scientist construct in a lab that orange shirt he was wearing in the
special yeah with the the boob sweat stains the dude I mean that's that story
told me before star recording that was crazy so you you're telling me you were
working in the lab late one night and your eyes held an eerie sight that's
fucking crazy bro I mean were you on mescaline or something like what's up
ayahuasca that is I mean that's that's I'm sure happened verbatim that's
happened yeah yeah so far there's a lot of hours of it there's no and he has a
lot of like free thinkers on there's no way that he hasn't encountered a real
life mad scientist who saw a real monster so that's just great you know
cuz like I mean those monsters should come out here cuz like in Texas you can
do what the fuck you want like you know like nobody's gonna tell you you know
mash this way or mash that way like in Texas you do what the fucking ever man
RFK jr. is definitely gonna have a story in the next couple days about yeah I
was at a monster party and yeah I killed a Dracula I threw it in my trunk and then I
had to go to a steakhouse I had to go to Peter Lugar's for a dinner and then
people like reporters would be like well it looks like from forensic evidence he
wore the Dracula's skull like a mask at dinner and people are trying to figure
out what's going on and he's like no I didn't wear the mask I didn't wear the
skull like a mask that didn't happen and actually some DNA tests run and were
run and what he assesses as a Dracula was actually a 12 year old girl just
walking by in the forest who didn't do anything he had a wild past it was a lot
going on he used to hang out with Epstein look and Cosby and Weinstein and the
wolf man and the creature from the Black Lagoon these are just people he would
meet in New York it was New York City that's just in a party at the Black
Lagoon and I was introduced to this guy and what's his name creature I didn't
know the guy didn't spend a lot of time with him but it's my story and what can
I say Woody Allen invited him to the Black Lagoon one night because they was
hanging out with Woody Allen in New York as you do and then shit got out of
control pretty sure if you go in the Black Lagoon you are guaranteed a brain
worm so that at least would explain something that's right yeah true a worm
crawled up Kennedy's brain so we're talking monster mash today although I
will let me please emphasize the plural that this is this is a monster mash is
because much like the recent episode football shuffles there's one primary
one that we know about but it is a genre there are multiple things in this
genre yeah and and we're gonna talk about it here on the haunt cast to me
this feels like an inevitable episode just given kind of our pop cultural
interests and leanings and especially because it feels like the kind of thing
this hasn't literally happened but it feels like within the month there could
be a party going on and I leave a mash if you will and I go to the bathroom and
when I come back I find Mike like pointing at Justin Michael or somebody
and saying like Bobby Boris Pickett is good and I'm like how did this start and
you and Justin's like I don't know I didn't bring him up at all yeah no I
haven't I haven't said anything for the last 10 minutes I'm like my hands are
like choking Justin I'm like he's good Bobby Boris Pickett is good you you
didn't even say hello you just immediately started screaming the whole
room could hear it's super kicking everyone in the room don't take your
anger out Shawn Michaels yes well I will say this I think three or four years
ago I have called this shot on the show oh did you mash specific but just the
genre well I remember some discussion of like a monster mash related issue am I
making that is that what you're talking about yes and I think I made a mistake
on that and I think I've already apologized for it but I incorrectly
thought that the monster mash was recorded before Bobby Boris Pickett that
was completely wrong I was talking about Don Hinson and the rig of morticians and
they had a cover I believe it was in 1964 and there was something that was
listed wrong as far as dates so I apologize if I haven't apologized for
that before but so but that was a discussion of how well I was digging
through all like old Halloween music I was
music from past Halloween's that was I think like 2020 pandemic era driving
through haunts and stuff I think that was we were I remember listening to this
stuff in the car uh-huh so I think it's this is four years you're blaming the
pandemic for it yes a dig into into the mash genre well and for my incorrectly
reporting the original monster mash yeah and it was a time of a lot of fake news
and right not being able to trust sources and that's why a Joe Rogan is
needed to kind of make you question you're listening that's Dr. Fauci was
working in the Wuhan lab late one night there are labs and warehouse outside San
Bernardino or whatever the kovat comic-con kovat comic I saw it exists I
don't know anything else about it though did you get it someone it's someone got
like a kovat no no the comic book they were hanging out there normally a
comic-con there are the Westboro Baptist Church like repent you're going to hell
protesters this time there were kovat truthers talking about labs in
California and giving out a comic you should have guy didn't realize you were
giving out a comic I would have read that I tried to get it I thought it was
grass so I was you thought you were grabbing whatever someone hands of me
and it turned out to be the entertainment weekly you couldn't tell
the truth people from the entertainment I wanted to get the comic from the woman
cosplaying as the character from the comic but didn't work out well a comic
is a car you'll grab whatever you have free comics and you didn't realize till
page 13 it was a kovat truth or yeah hey wait a minute Reynolds said they had a
lot of fun making Deadpool this isn't cove it I think the character dr.
Fright she might be a stand-in for someone in our real world it is fun
though it sounds like they made it fun if that's the case which I appreciate
making history fun you gotta you know yeah you sneak the vegetables in to give
to the kids yeah it's gotta be so all right so monster mesh and pretty there
have been previous monster mesh controversies but well what we'll do we
can start with the the original the one that changed the game yeah you know fan
out and see what else is is in this world but that of course requires us to
start with the monster match the by Bobby Boris picket who so wait 62 is the
song is that is that correct which it feels to me like it is slowly becoming
and this will only become more the case as you know sands wash over some of
history yeah I feel like there will be a point in time where like pre Beatles 64
there are only five songs and anyone remembers or talks about and one of
those is the monster mash I think it hung in there yeah well especially like
of a rock and roll genre mm-hmm cuz like you'll get your classical pieces it'll
stick around whatever no that's different yeah like you're Dean Martin
stuff and we'll still have owed to joy but then yeah also besides that although
that's fine monster mash wipeout owed to joy I say yeah that's I like it better
uh-huh yeah I know what I've listened to more but there are yes there are a lot
of pre Boris Bobby picket mashes well okay so where do we go do we fan out do
we yeah I think go here and then we'll maybe go back in time we can go but we
can use this as the arrival point and we can go back in time and forward in time
yeah all the way to 2005 right as far as I can tell the most recent mash yeah
yeah that Bobby himself participated in but so yeah even when we were kids this
was a pretty fundamental piece I think it's buoyed by being one of the only
Halloween songs still in all this time yes we've talked about before you go to
that you walk around a neighborhood in trick-or-treat season and you hear you
know we try to loop in like sweet dreams are made of this or whatever but
like all right well just because it's like you know man-eater we're deciding
man-eater is a Halloween song but it's a bit of a stretch in terms of pure
actual meant to be Halloween songs it's sort of this and thriller and look
thrillers dicey or at this point so I Bobby Boris picket bite at his time beat
Michael Jackson yeah I mean it's a it's an amazing story especially given that
the guy was he's a veteran he fought in the Korean War he what it's something I
didn't know about this kid because you hear that voice which is like a creepy
guy and a very like lived in Boris Karloff kind of voice and I think as a
kid and maybe even until recently I thought this was just like an old weird
guy I think he was I thought he was a Vincent Price kind of person so when you
see a photo of him and he's just kind of like a sharp blonde he looks like
Jan and Dean he's just like kind of a clean cut could have been in the wonders
and the thing you do wonders he's like an actor as well he I think he was just
like figure trying to figure something out mm-hmm yeah anything anything that
could we a I think he had like a fine career he'd pop up on things I forget if
these are before or after the mash but he was on Beverly Hillbillies he was on
Petticoat Junction he he dated Cloris Leachman pretty cool yeah yeah good the
Diane Cannon yeah who went on to marry Cary Grant you know not long after wow
I was this guy was the Hollywood elite yeah I as a kid anytime anybody was like
doing some sort of like Halloween based I don't know music or TV you would think
that they were maybe like oh they're from like hell they came up from hell
Ozzy Osbourne as well and you hear Ozzy Osbourne talk about figuring out the
gimmick for black Sabbath and it was just like well like some people like
this like devil worship type stuff so we may as well let's try that as far as our
gimmick yeah it's not like they were so into it before they just were like ah
this is might be a fun gimmick Alice Cooper yeah yeah sure yeah seeming that
pretty like mild-mannered guy just kind of like golfer yes my grandfather got
on my dad's side golfed with him one time he came home like hey you know I got
paired with today you're a day son you're into the rock and roll you know
this guy Alice Cooper you ever heard him like what the fuck you golfed with Alice
Cooper today I think recently I've heard Alice Cooper say he golfs seven days a
week I think he's and Alice Cooper showed up on like the Mickey Mouse clubhouse
yesterday when my daughter was watching like a doll like a goofy looking Alice
Cooper shows up with a top hat boys by him well so yeah he rolled this character
rolls on the screen and I go Alice Cooper and then I look it up and 2019 is
like yeah Alice Cooper does voice on the Mickey Mouse I forget then I forgot the
name of the character right now there's one for the dads yeah for the dads of
the dance yeah yeah the older grandpa son for grandpa yeah that's where I'm
glad Marilyn Manson walks the walk and talks the talk he is he plays an evil
guy and is an evil guy yeah finally somebody who's not this namby-pamby
yeah Alice Cooper probably goes to the GOP convention but it's not as aggressive
yeah I guess I'm sure he's like lightly bad yeah in the way you some that age
not as far as I know as bad as Marilyn Manson sure yes yeah um but anyway he
like Bobby Ross Pickett sings in bands and in his in a little like nightclub
show he does he did this impression and gave somebody the idea of like maybe we
could get something out of this and do a little novelty single yeah maybe sell
5,000 copies and that's the ultimate dream of this which it's so bizarre
that it's now like it yeah it will be it will dethrone truly some classical
composers yeah will be much less remembered than right the monster mesh
yeah I mean when I see a picture of her I see a video of him doing it it feels
very much like when I see Frank Gorshin doing an impression of somebody there's
this there's like I don't know if you ripped Frank Gorshin off I just like it
feels go it feels like the impressions of the time for some weird reason I
don't even know I can articulate what I'm talking about well isn't it even in
some respects is this song and he doing this voice not more iconic than Boris
Karloff himself yeah yeah this point it's more around you're more like a you
know like a three-year-old is gonna hear this and maybe never see a Boris Karloff
performance yeah probably I mean there's Simpson voices and like I guess Wren from
like that's Peter Laurie's voice but like do most people our age know Peter
Laurie's voice or they know what Wren sounds like hmm so there is like that
weird thing where people are doing impressions of famous stars and I'm
wondering what the breakdown of people who know what that voice is actually
from mm-hmm so yeah you're probably right yeah well this is why we're here
to teach the history and the Vegas terms that are wrong and we don't actually
know yeah so let's get into it the Laurie cast with Jason Sheridan I'm here to go
through the Laurie biography as I know both Wren and Peter Laurie is that a
dream solo I mean you just talking old character actors yeah yeah yeah mm-hmm
six hours long and it's just you just do you'll go and you'll go and like get
lunch and leave the mic on and stuff crunch crunch crunch right like so it's
not like a continuous I stopped talking about the Maltese Falcon our hours and
hours ago and you'll wander in the room you be like oh it's still on and you sit
down you go a couple other thoughts I had during lunch then you just kind of
go for more thoughts on M on Fritz Lang's M so you should put it on yeah
it's a podcast it'll take up your whole day and if you sync it up yeah you can
take a lunch break as Jason does yeah that'll help you get through the work
day it's like hey I'm here with you I know this email job sucks but we'll get
through it together you're not having lunch alone you're having lunch with
somebody who's also not talking right on you can hear them crunching with their
mouth that's good idea but anyways so they put this song together and just
here you know to jump out of history I don't know how much need there is to
play the song itself very famous I think we know it to our audience I
assume yeah but here what I will do is just play I'll play my favorite zone of
it here there's a little snippet
a functional yeah not a funny lyric never really thought about Dracula's son
before and now it's all I'm gonna think about all day yeah yeah is he in any
media is there anything you can watch there a son of Dracula movie I'm sure
there is possibly maybe a famous one but but that just makes me picture of like
mild-mannered son who's learning how to be a vampire right although it could
also be you know they're like eternal so they're so you know Dracula's son could
be 700 years old Dracula's adult son yeah yeah I think this analysis is way
more than they did when they were writing the song yeah yeah yeah well
definitely because they wrote the song in half an hour yeah I think that's
literally true this was knocked out and surprised me like so many of you know
that's what they say that's what that's what McCartney says yeah Brian Wilson
says that God only knows all the masterpieces God only knows in Monster
Mesh there is a Beach Boys connection by the way that in early television
performances or at least in one Bobby was backed up by the Beach Boys the like
less nationally famous speed here's a photo of Boris making a face and
there's Brian Wilson next to him that's cool other Beach Boy David Marks Beach
Boys did a pretty inessential cover of this they would do it live but it would
lead to some good like I mean they like lit it scary and Mike Love made scary
faces and that's good all spooked or like did all of their problems throughout
there a lot like mental health issues and and Mike Love's general
cantankerousness was it just because they were too scared from the song the
song freaked them out well I think about it they mainly did surfing songs before
this and then that was maybe the first veering into into darker territory it's
like the musical equivalent of a bad LSD trip so yeah the monster meant that
their encounter with Boris Pickett maybe they never recovered from I was gonna
say I think I mentioned this on the show before but a couple years ago Bruce
Springsteen and the E Street Band did a cover of Monster Mesh and did like kind
of a ska or like a reggae version of it and in the middle of it Bruce just goes
this is terrible so funny because it wasn't really working I don't know why
they did it like that but in the middle he's wow terrible geez that the
confidence is there any history of anything like that of Bruce Springsteen
being never non confident not that I've seen within its three-hour sets because
Bruce is like this ridiculous I'm not gonna be scared of a Dracula or
Frankenstein that's silly yeah he didn't like their asses what were you
saying oh well I was gonna say the thing I only just learned the view of the
stuff about the backing singers oh yeah yeah yeah there's crazy people on it the
blossoms they were like an in-demand like backing vocalist group mm-hmm they
included Darlene love Darlene love is on yes it's a stacked lineup Leon Russell's
on it the drummer of the ventures is on it it was a pretty yeah the Krip Kicker
five is actually well that's if you okay hang on the Krip Kicker five is the
they're the vocal group in the Sun so right but then there's a whole wait and
isn't the band also named separately technically yeah there's it's confusing
to me and then I think he had a different like band later but the but the
whole thing there's actually like a strange thing with all of it that I'm
stealing this observation from other sources from some article and somebody
pointed out in a tweet a long time ago but if you think about it the this is
the song is kind of a predecessor to tenacious D's tribute that it's not the
greatest song in the world it's just a tribute right it is the same thing here
because it's a song about encountering monsters doing the monster mash but that
but it's about that what we know is the monster mash is not what they did it was
also called the monster mash but if you think about it we don't know what they
were doing and playing or what the Krip Kicker five sounds like right at least
they're you know we're hearing humans who might have stolen that name yeah yeah
yeah it's a song about a song we will never hear that's a good point it's one
of the headier pieces of art of the century I think about it yeah there was
some way to know yeah you know it's like how great blues songs were lost
because nobody brought the bad scratchy microphone to play but yeah there were
no field recordings of the monster mash so we have no idea it might have been a
thousand times better than what within this song that is something that should
haunt you if you were a big monster mash fan like us yeah yeah what you will
never know what the when the mummy was banging on a bone xylophone you will
never know how good that sounded yeah how good how crisp the individual tones
of the different sized bones were yeah whoo it's gonna keep me up there's
something if we're analyzing why we like this there's definitely that that just a
bunch of monsters all playing playing a band together it's just inherently it's
so it's so fun it's a monster like they've survived a long time these same
monsters they're reborn all the time sometimes it works sometimes it doesn't
mm-hmm oftentimes it doesn't I would say sometimes they get a new member a
Carmilla creeper type well you're right the monster cereals of course you're
talking about all right right yeah she's back she's back this fall oh the
monster cereals are starting to come back oh okay that's good but it is like
cuz Halloween is so even though probably Christmas is everybody's favorite
Halloween as a kid is very exciting and mm-hmm I don't know there's just
something about Halloween that is super fun if it's the candy or the costumes
but yes this song you imagine the most fun party of your life and it's with
Frankenstein mm-hmm and the mummy is it almost is it one of the first
iterations of monsters being cute does it open up the genre that like they take
a little break from the terror like when is what's like Abbott and Costello meet
Frankenstein what year is that like oh that's probably before it's got to be
before aren't they kind of scary in it because they like jumping each other's
arms and stuff yeah and they're scared of him and stuff but that's they were
doing some comedy stuff with monsters 1948 is when they met Frankenstein and I
also like that when you Google this that Google is like you mean Abbott
Elementary no no I don't mean something from the last five years I'm looking for
a 1948 computer have you not learned the kind of things I look up whose computer
do you think you are five years well I was this is what I was trying to do and
I didn't have a good answer for when the first monster party anything existed I
don't know but I found previous monster party songs okay well that's let's go
backwards then yeah all right so you what you've done is proven that the
concepts did not necessarily come from Bobby Orr's pick right and I didn't I
don't know that maybe there's an oral history somebody can point me in the
direction but it was still like strange enough that in fact when Darlene Love
was at like you know she would just like hear about gigs from producers and
somebody's like oh you know can you come in we're doing a Halloween song and
she was like a Halloween song that sounds stupid never knowing it would be
one of the biggest yeah singles of her career although no not associated with
her really and Halloween wasn't Halloween wasn't as big of a deal back
then either you don't think so that's something I don't really know is like
the fully like how when does Halloween become right what we know is I mean yeah
I imagine the Monster Mash supercharged it I would I think that I don't know do
you think it's a straight line from 50s and 60s or is at any point in there does
it does Halloween get way more popular just one year I don't know it's good
question I wonder if just like and did it get way less popular oh wait no it
when was Kennedy shot 64 so what month it was 63 but what month November
November okay so it's in there before I bet it was a very I bet 63 it was a very
joyous Halloween and 64 everybody brought down a little bit maybe people
did not want to think about death no no even though even though it was November
65 would be a bummer at 65 okay by your logic the next Halloween in 65 would be
okay we shot 63 was he not didn't you say it was November 63 I'm confused
doesn't do this we have to settle on which Halloween was sad I think it was
in 1964 maybe 65 was a little bit sad still yeah I'm confused I'm trying to
load up Bert Convy's Monster Hop while I'm doing this too so you know do you
think there was ever the theory that Kennedy was that there was a there was
an errant Dracula or wolf man who was Billy's part of it he does say there
was a wolf man on that for many decades you've been ignoring the wolf right so
somebody was shooting a silver bullet at the wolf man I wasn't it's that's what's
so oral about yeah Oswald was a good man he was trying to kill a wolf man who was
trying to kill Kennedy but then the kid then the motorcade got in the way his
name is Lee Harvey Oswald Van Helsing people don't know that the name was too
long everyone got exhausted like how I'm back I don't have it in me to name those
last two names yeah so okay I so yeah I don't have a definitive answer what the
first monster party happened but 1958 Bert Convy who I mean in reality it
might have been in like the you know in the 1600 right the actual party if we're
talking the real party but when was it first acknowledged on wax right I don't
know but this is 1958 it is called the monster hop by Bert Convy who hosted
game shows and stuff oh right match game yes yes so you're a song really yep 19th
that's what it says 58
that surely felt like the monster mash from an alternate reality that's what
there's so many monster mashes that's what I was like oh my god and then
afterward everybody was doing a fake monster mash too that's called a monster
hop by Bert Convy this has to be part of the inspiration for the Lewin Davis like
hey mr. Kennedy oh oh you know I think this novelty song there's a market for
some song and knockout and real musicians do it yeah this is a bill
doggett monster party 1959 I'm gonna say I give credit to any who represent
Frank it's beyond Frankenstein Dracula and Wolfman because yeah that's look
that's who I think of but those are the core I'll give bonus points to this guy
if he names beyond that bill dog it don't dog it
that gives us time to start dancing there are not a lot of lyrics in this
the place an unrelated song so it's like an instrumental and then it's like
what if I just a song interrupts that doesn't have the same meter or have
anything to do with the song that's currently playing yeah no that's it's
not as good as the the monster no I'm like a convie's winning for me so far but
still like that's I mean those are the base of the funniest too as far but like
that just yeah we'll go we'll move on but just to prove like this is not Bobby
Boris Pickett perfected it mm-hmm but the idea was out there I think the what
he brought to the party was alliteration I think that my well
monster hop is a fun term I think monster mash there's a right cleanliness
to it and just mash in general because now where did that come from was there a
lot of were people calling things mashes yeah that's a good question is it
related to the mashed potato maybe is that why yeah maybe is the monster mash
a dance or is it the party I think it's the most I think it's the dance monster
mash is the dance right it's not we did the mash we did the monster they did it
yeah maybe at the monster bash right you go to a monster bash to do the monster
mash you don't attend a monster mash mm-hmm right right all right so we're
getting around we're getting our dictionary a real quick a guy I brought
up years ago to 1960 sorry I forgot about this Zachary the great Zachary
this is a horror show yeah a bunch of things like a lot of these guys are like
they did radio for a while they did this like this was Bobby was big he was like
a kid I don't remember the channel but he was like a yeah LA DJ for but like
that 1960 is spook along with Zachary and this is an album I actually kind of
like in general and there's many songs but there's nothing there's nothing
about a party but just even musically I'm like the song ring-a-ding orangutan
huh similar to a monster mash that's all so I just just for funsies I'm playing
so it's in the spirit of it I think too it's a wild song really yeah
arrangement wise I like it yeah yeah it feels like some effort maybe was put
into it yeah yeah the only one that I caught that I kind of like actually that
I would recommend genuinely for your Halloween playlist if we're doing here
we're covering the ones we sort of actually dig this guy this is on called
beware by Bill Buchanan I heard this on a playlist by this guy Mayor Hawthorne I
like a lot who's trying to do all Halloween music and this this is this I
just think is pretty good yeah yeah beware by Bill Buchanan
yeah like this yeah this is just isn't that like leader of the pack story song
kind of you can count on it any odd time yeah a lot of just cool to me it is like
that's got a good vibe yeah yeah yeah that's cool I feel like there's a joke
there too of not like Pennsylvania 65,000 Transylvania 259 yeah I assume
yeah I don't quite understand what that it but I you know it feels like a
reference phone numbers they used to like have a word in there oh right yes
yeah yeah well what's the movie that's called something like that is
Transylvania 65 oh yeah yeah whatever not important but anyways so clearly this
was this did become like a thriving genre kind of capitalizing on the you
know like like the B movies of the era and you know probably all leading to
Monster Mash rising to the top but then it's kind of I think for this guy
especially like well what else do I do are there other things in this world in
this monster world that I can get up to and Mike you were comparing Halloween to
Christmas in terms of holiday fun and he thought why don't I bring some of
that Halloween fun over to Christmas so not too long after Monster Mash was the
follow-up Monsters Holiday
you didn't need to put them in a castle to know that's that's that's too
tortured of a rhyme I don't think the monsters all live in castles hmm they
shouldn't castles are where like the rich gentry live right right not they
storm the castle yeah I mean I guess no yeah Dracula lives in a castle yeah yeah
yeah and he I guess then he and all right so it's his castle and he invites
over because everybody else Frankenstein may be created in a
castle depending hmm he's created in a lab sometimes like a Frankenstein but
Wolfman that doesn't have to have a castle yeah creature mummy is in a tomb
of some kind you know Phantom of Opera is an opera yeah yeah he's not there
Hunchback's in Notre Dame tower but I guess that I know if you're going through
who's gonna host I mean it's look it's not Wolfman yeah not everybody's you're
not gonna although maybe there's something fun and grimy about going to
the cave I'll fit in you know it's like sure when you know when the party's all
happening in kind of a small kitchen and yeah yeah yeah yeah but Dracula has the
room for entertaining absolutely yeah he has a lot I'm sure and then secret
slides and all that shit yeah all right anyway
themselves a new play. They planned to rob Santa's slave. They were making a list and checking it twice. Frankenstein wanted a shiny new trike. A new chain went up.
this one definitely it just doesn't have the heat and no like some of the other
monster songs it so quickly devolves into spoken word yeah with some music in
the background yeah yeah just saying lists which that we got two tough rhymes
right away Frankenstein wanted a shiny new trike. Trike? I mean I guess there's
trikes for adults but you call it yeah it's called a recumbent bicycle or
something that's a strike he's gonna break a trike. What's funny to me
about this is this is on the first this is on a Monster Mash album. Oh yes the
original Monster Mash by Bobby boys picking in the Crip Kickers. Oh that's
right it's Crip Kickers are his band Crip Kicker 5 is the monster band who
will never hear. Right but so usually I feel like so like okay we got a hit
next album we're gonna just repeat it yeah we're gonna twist again next
summer yeah we're gonna try that we're gonna try to do it again there are
multiple attempts on the same album as Monster Mash to repeat this the the
future success of Monster Mash. Listen there's this song there's like 24 songs
on this album and they're all monster songs 16 and some of it like there's a
song called Monster Mash Party which I won't even play that's just the same
exact the thing as you're hearing now with less lyrics like almost about him
like cleaning up at the part or something like there's just so few ideas. These monsters made such a mess. Not quite that. They spilled the Mountain Dew. Everyone get a bag and start cleaning up. This is your responsibility too.
It's just like they were already out of ideas is what I'm saying.
When you listen to the actual Monster Mash. No there because like what do you
establish with Monster Mash is a song with like five verses and a lot of lyrics
that's where that spoken word gets you is now you got a jam it full of details
yeah but how many more do you have left you've used all the good monsters right
used all the good party stuff yeah we got Slim Pickens after I was I had the
same arc with this where I'm like I'm gonna go through the full album and most
of the album was insufferable yeah yeah I mean there's one called a Transylvania
twist which is mythology from the first Monster Mash because the Dracula says
whatever happened to my Transylvania twist so now we get to hear that yeah so there's
some interesting lore I guess here and there but a lot of it is really bad and
just a copy of Monster Mash only worse. What was anyone's feeling about the
werewolf Watusi? Well I like the name of it so that's gonna be elevated just in
general yeah let me let me do a second yeah can you play a little of that
that's interesting Lawrence Wolfe approved yeah but I just think he's doing like a
Dracula voice for a werewolf so I he didn't really change it up much but he's
Bobby Boris singing as the character right but it's it's just a little I
think he should have established you wanted him to sing like a wolf man? A different musical identity for each monster to switch it up a
little Jason the wolf man singing would be really hard to listen to probably
because he howls and stuff. Wolfman Jack was always howling on the radio. Didn't sing though.
Wasn't a good point. Yeah yeah. Wolfman singing? Wait wasn't somebody in this era
didn't somebody have kind of a wolf vibe persona or what was the deal with that
whoever did I put a spell on you that has that's kind of like a howling monster sort of if you count that as a
Halloween song I guess you could yeah but I some people have howled certainly
people have howled on record before yeah I'm just saying a purely as a wolf man that would be
yeah who sings a song dead man's Party it's a dead man it's a boingo boingo okay yeah that is roped in I'd say in the Halloween
that's a spooky yeah it's a Halloween song yeah yeah yeah I don't know I mean
you're look you're right for variety Jason but he is at that he established he
He is a vampire kind of guy, is he?
Yeah.
What was Boris Karloff, mainly?
He was, wasn't he Frankenstein, too?
Wasn't he Two Monsters?
Or am I mixing up?
I forget, I gotta go through,
I think they're all on Peacock, he was Frankenstein,
Bela Lugosi was Dracula.
Right, right, right.
That's right, yes.
These were all things I certainly had to know
as a Universal Tour Guide that was out of my brain
as soon as I stopped doing this stuff.
I know Bela Lugosi because of Ed Wood.
Yes.
I know that.
And I've seen some of these as well, but.
Bela Lugosi, hey!
But yeah, I like Ed Wood a lot.
It was, I just remember deep into tours,
because you go to the monster area,
I just remember that was a zone
where I would say these words, don't mean anything to me,
I just don't care about these movies that much,
and I'm like, it's right where I'm getting tired,
especially on a tour that's not going well,
and just trying to use,
how much tour guide energy can you muster up
in the Court of Miracles?
Bela Lugosi, Boris Karla, and like not,
if I don't have it there,
then the next 20 minutes are gonna be really rough.
Then I'm just excited to get into that mummy's tomb
where I don't gotta say shit,
except for I get like a full minute breath,
I could take a nap in there and it's dark,
and then I just have to wake back up to go,
Whoopi Goldberg, oh no, watch out for scarabs!
That's a good break, yeah.
A full minute, though, where you don't gotta do shit?
Yeah.
And you gotta know nobody's watching you, either.
They're watching the, yeah,
even the people who are in the row in front of me,
or they're not cognizant there's a human being there.
They don't wanna make eye contact.
Can nap against that window as long as I,
oh yeah, that's so uncomfortable.
Playing Tetris on the flip phone, you know.
I remember one time,
I may have said this on the show before,
that like somebody just like,
not only was reading in the front car in front of me,
but just like put it up at eye level,
like took it up from their lap to just block their face,
and I had the best view of somebody,
and they were reading that book.
What was that book that Oprah featured,
and then it turned out to all be a lie?
And they had to go on and apologize.
James something?
Yeah, yeah.
James Fry.
A million little pieces?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, something like that.
Yes, after all that had,
after it had been determined that the book was fake,
somebody was just reading that right in front of me,
blocking their eyes to not experience King Kong.
That's funny.
I don't wanna see King Kong,
I wanna read the book, The Fabulous Droid.
How much money did you pay to come here and read?
Let alone that the book is a lie.
Anyways.
I wanna give Zachary Lee's album credit,
because there's different things on it,
and this Monster Mash is just like going to the well already,
that's what I wanted to say.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
Oh, so you heard that full album,
and there's already a variety in the,
yeah, yeah, well, look, there's a repetition for sure,
and it's not helped by,
then he's, when he's kinda like back a couple years later,
when there's like a full,
a full true reset to a new thing.
Right.
It's not enough of a reset.
Here, he is after a big introduction by Dick Clark,
performing presumably on American Bandstand, Monster Swim.
Yeah.
I mean, his voice, and back in 62,
the trip kickers and I brought the Monster Mash to you.
But now it's a different day, and Mashie is a gray,
and the lights grow dim, we now do the Monster Swim.
Same beat.
All you would be, Monsters.
Yeah, yeah.
I like that he's doing this in front of like
a big weird octopus.
Yeah.
Paper mache looking octopus, so I like that.
Let me see if I can get to the chorus.
Not so loud.
We can't do the monkey or even the dog.
Same piano, and basically, somebody else.
We can't do the monkey.
It's a cool side smash.
It's bigger than the mash.
Oh man.
It's the most wishful thinking.
Bigger than the mash.
That's like the, like, it's a little while ago now,
but Trump doing like, and Biden might come back,
you know what he might do?
He's gonna come back, he's gonna try to take it,
and then I'll be debating him again.
Wouldn't that be something?
It's bigger than the first debate.
Oh, it's like, I just heard a thing about Trump
doing the like, the Congressional Medal of Honor.
It's better than the Presidential Medal of Freedom.
Oh yeah, yeah, that was funny.
I, yeah, it's very sad.
It's also like, you know,
when the career is just clearly on the down slide
a little bit, like we're sort of seeing it,
you know, Katy Perry had a rough year.
Yeah.
She did the song, was it, it's Woman's World.
Yes.
I haven't heard it, I just know it didn't really work,
but if somewhere in there, if she like,
I don't know what the song sounds like,
but it's like, woman's world, it's bigger than firework.
Ha ha ha.
Step aside last Friday night.
There was a video like released where she had to be like,
this is a, like weeks later after it came out,
she was like, this is a parody of like 10 year old,
like kind of rah rah, generic feminist sort of,
like she, you're like, she's explaining what the song is,
like weeks later, and it was like,
this isn't really helping this song.
Songs don't usually require a little story.
Which is what Bobby did at the start.
Hey, remember the other song?
You know me. You love the other song.
I know the beat, I know there's been a seismic shift
in pop music since the last time you saw me,
but do the Beatles do songs about monsters?
I'm timeless like the monsters.
Oh man, yeah, there's so much,
I'm sure there was like an argument
or who, like putting it together like,
people aren't gonna fucking remember this, okay?
This is a shitty song from a decade ago.
We had to remind them this was a thing.
This needs a scroll.
This needs a last time on.
This is a song that needs.
People don't know.
If you had a skip intro button on the song.
Jog your memory.
Yes, when Beatles release a new album,
at the start of the album, they should remind people
what other songs they had in case they forgot.
Hey, it's us, the Beatles.
We told you that she loves you,
but now we're back with a brand new bag.
All about holding your hand.
And just a reminder, it's not spelled like the bug.
There's an A in there.
You know what I'm realizing?
Don't forget about the A.
John Lennon does it in Glass Onion, I think, right?
Oh, you're right.
I told you about Strawberry Fields.
Yeah.
The place you thought. Wow.
That was definitely following the footsteps.
Yes, we were very into Bobby Boris Pickett at the time.
John thought that people forgot about Strawberry Fields,
so he wanted to remind them in Glass Onion
on the White Album.
You think they'll know we told them
about the fool on the hill?
They'd probably like the update
that he's living there still.
Yeah, he did it.
The walrus was Paul, he says, in that song.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
So John did it, yeah.
John did it, too.
I apologize to Bobby and the estate.
He paved the way for a lot of, yeah.
Well, and embraced genres, as we'll see.
I have no desire to play the song,
but somewhere in that album that there's the title
Rabian the Fiendage Idol.
That's what that requires Katy Perry-esque,
because you have to know about Fabian,
and that he was a teenage idol,
and I don't know much about Fabian,
just know that name.
I'm like, okay, I think I get it.
Rabian?
Is it rabies?
I don't know, I don't know, I guess.
This is kind of like, I know the big picture.
Like, Teen Beach Party, Universal Monster,
I haven't really gone back
and watched each individual movie.
Yeah, well, if you wanna combine them,
I think one of the best mystery science theater movies
is one called Horror at Party Beach.
And I'm trying to remember if that's the one.
There's one where when the monster shows up,
it looks like he has a mouthful of hot dogs.
Like, the first, of course you don't see him
for an hour and 10 minutes,
and then when he shows up, you're like,
he just has a big, he has like 16 hot dogs
jammed in his mouth.
Well, if he went to Party Beach,
that's a thing you have to do, I'm assuming.
That's like, it's a little competition.
Yeah, it's competition.
If you wanna cut it at this beach party,
you fit 16 of these bad boys in there.
It researched, like just researching
or looking through all this stuff,
I was just like, this is a 30-hour series
if you wanted it to be.
There's so much stuff that is,
even just in the time it was recorded,
not even going to the 2005 era.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, I know.
I was disappointed by how many,
I assumed that there would be a lot more
that give you crazy mythology, you know?
I, because what I want is like story songs.
I want like, and he was returning from the blood bank
and he slipped.
They did the bloody twist.
Yeah.
They slipped on the blood.
Nothing's that funny.
Yeah, no, nothing is that funny.
But like, there's just,
there's so many like imitators too.
Oh, I forgot to even mention this,
Lon Chaney Jr. recorded Monster Holiday.
He covered it?
In 1964.
Geez, wow.
And then that other band you were saying
covered Monster Mash.
A lot of Monster Mash covers certainly over the years.
Yes, but then-
What was the band,
what was the scary band name of that?
Don Hinson and the Rigor Morticians.
The Rigor Morticians.
But then they-
And they don't have any originals?
They did have originals
that were rip-offs of the Monster Man.
Yeah.
Lon Chaney Jr., I think from,
I think I remember this.
There's a You Must Remember This series
on the Universal Monster Movies.
And I think the stuff about Lon Chaney Jr. is
he was a massive pain in the ass.
I forget the details, but it's like-
But not in the fun way.
Oh yeah, he was a real fail son
and like took over for his father
and like he sucked.
They have a song, Don Hinson,
I forget if I listen to this even,
called The Monster Dance Party, 1964.
You audition it here.
["The Monster Dance Party," by Don Hinson and the Rigor Morticians plays.]
Oh, I think this might be an instrumental.
Okay, I'm thinking of a different-
Instrumentals are dead to me.
Fake, it's a fake.
There is one here.
I think I even played it.
She's making something 10 minutes,
used Frankenstein as a surfboard.
Monsters, surf party.
This is called riboflavin-flavored,
non-carbonated, polyunsaturated blood.
If this doesn't have lyrics,
I'm storming out of the room.
It does.
["The Monster Dance Party," by Don Hinson and the Rigor Morticians plays.]
It sounds like Beware.
When the moon arises in the western sky,
and the vampires are out on strife.
Exactly.
At times they have trouble finding necks to bite.
That's why I concocted my new delight.
My riboflavin-flavored, non-carbonated, polyunsaturated blood.
Riboflavin-flavored,
non-carbonated,
polyunsaturated blood.
All right.
Beaver, let's step this down.
We need a take two.
Girls, I apologize.
You seem very nice,
but you're gonna have to sing better than that.
No.
All right.
Let's not even finish that one.
Just some constructive criticism.
You all sound like shit.
So let's go back in the studio and do it again,
but good this time.
We're doing it on purpose.
We're trying to sound like ghouls.
That's the idea. No, no.
Don't give me that shit.
They're shrieking, not singing.
It's justified.
Mike, I feel like that unlocked a memory
where I was at one of your apartments
and you have played the riboflavin song for me before.
I may have played that on this show before.
Around this, in the same episode
where we were talking about this four years ago.
Also, I have heard you go to bat for Zach or late
a number of times.
I listened to that Zach or late on the first time
like 10 years ago.
So you have certainly heard Ring a Ding,
Orangutan for many years at this point because of me.
I'm a man in my 30s, young, free, unencumbered.
Could just listen to Ring a Ding, Orangutan all night.
I think they have a G at the end,
even though it is Orangutan in the real.
So I think they misspelled it.
Soupy Sails has a song called
My Baby's Got a Crush on Frankenstein.
Can I just say, has Soupy Sails ever come up
on the show before?
I think a little bit.
Soupy Sails is like novel, or he had this kid,
it was like a kid's show, but adults liked it.
And I like it because he had this monster
in Fang who was only represented by a hand.
And I just love any good guttural yelling.
So I love when he like,
it was like something my dad found so funny.
So I found it so funny too.
And my wife, Erin hates this shit.
If I ever put a clip on her, if I ever go,
she says, stop it, stop it.
She has such an aversion to Soupy Sails.
If she's listening, she's gonna be so upset.
Oh, I'm sorry, Soupy's on here.
Just tell her not to listen to this part.
What is this?
Is there a, is Fang on it?
That's, I don't even real, I don't remember.
Let me see.
It's, I'm just, I think this is from like 66, maybe.
Let's see if Fang is on.
["Fang Is On It"]
Ah!
My baby's got a crush on Frankenstein.
She thinks that monster is divine.
She says I'd be her vampire.
He's actually singing.
If I had a stiff and jerky walk.
If I'd always grunt instead of talk.
If I had his look, she wouldn't balk.
At loving me, a no serene.
And then here comes the monster mash-a-woos.
That old vampire's spectacular.
To use my baby's own vernacular.
His cool, cold blooded, icy stare.
His shiny, patent leather hair.
The way his bat wings fly.
I don't like this part.
No, I don't either.
I don't like this fail.
He, he lost, boy, he had us in, he lost us.
I clocked it because of the ah-woos parts.
Like every single person making these
in the wake of Bobby Warren's picket,
there's like at least two elements.
They were like, we have to steal two elements.
It has to be there, like that little drum fill,
that just general drum sound of the time,
the ah-woos, or the chord progression exactly.
Or the topic.
Everybody was really afraid to just fully do a new thing.
That's why I'm like going through these last nine numbers
like this is, there's so much.
I can't believe there's so much.
I can't either.
Scott, just go back.
The soupy sale, Aaron hating soupy sales,
it does remind me, I am picturing you and your son,
and like Aaron's out of the house,
and like my dad used to,
when I wasn't supposed to watch South Park or the Simpsons,
and then my dad just going, just go in the play room,
and just close the door and turn it down.
You don't mind, it's fine, you know?
But you doing that to your son,
and like, all right, mom's out of the house,
put soupy sales on.
Don't tell her, just be cool about it.
Don't make fang voices.
Yeah, I'm the same.
A formative, important memory that makes my mom so mad
when I bring it up was my dad,
because my dad wanted to watch Beavis and Butt-Head.
He can't watch it without, and then nodding,
he's like, all right, come in, come in, slide,
and then remote in hands, like ready to change
if she walks in.
That's really funny.
Very important.
Too much local news scaring,
or Tipper Gore in the news scaring,
and it's like, what did you think I was gonna do
if I watched Simpsons and South Park?
Yeah, all this shit, the only thing that actually scarred me
was when I watched like a 2020 with all of my family there
about a father who killed his own kids,
and then I said, dad, are you gonna kill me?
And I ran out of the room.
You know, the local news is where you should take it,
that's where the real dark stuff is.
What do you think was more traumatic,
me watching some adult cartoons with some cursing,
or like the Little League fathers,
like foaming at the mouse, screaming at each other.
That was scary.
In real, like 10 feet away, and it's like,
I don't care, we lose, that's fine,
I just wanna get the free soda and a hot dog.
Is this happening as much these days
as it was when we were kids?
Because it happened all the time,
and I only played Little League stuff for a short time.
But yes, dads flipping out during games
happened what felt like fairly regularly.
I mean, are they just soothed
by being able to sit in the bleachers
and like, you know, look at stuff on their phone?
Porn out.
Yeah, porn out.
File away.
I didn't know what you were going to,
either you were gonna say vaping or something,
maybe vaping calmed them down.
Probably vaping, you know?
For us, that'll be, you know, like.
Listening to a mash of some kind.
Yeah, yeah, really.
It's like, okay, I'll calm down with, you know,
there's a song, what song did Bobby Boris Pickett do?
And okay, in 65, he did the Monster Hullabaloo.
Okay, phew, all right, I don't have to get mad
at the other dads.
I'm jumping around all over here.
There was a Rankin and Bass stop motion movie
in the 67 or something called Mad Monster Party.
Oh, yeah, I've never seen that.
I know that DVD cover very well,
but.
And there's like a James Bond ripoff song,
sung as the theme of it, called Mad Monster Party.
Ah.
That I guess I'll just play now.
Sure.
I appreciate them at least going with a different genre.
So I appreciate them at least going
with a different genre.
One.
Now, a word.
Deary.
Shit.
It's party time.
Okay.
You know, it's not the best song in the world,
but it's kinda cool. It's about a party in it,
but in a different way.
All right. So.
Hey, sure.
There's that.
Yeah.
So much.
There's a lot.
I mean, like, look, we don't have to,
if you got something in the pocket you like,
by all means throw it in,
but we could move through the rest of the forest.
Yeah, let's do that.
Yeah.
Discography.
Because he's a little quiet,
other than that the song never really goes away,
and I don't think he's one of these guys
who gets like screwed over.
I think there might've been a time
where he was not as well represented,
and he got with a new guy who helped him figure out
how to license this thing correctly,
and maybe, and I think he made his own version
that he didn't know whatever company on.
Right.
Well, yeah.
I have an excerpt from Wikipedia about how he gets.
All right.
When we turn things over to Wikipedia.
I know.
It was just so like confusing.
I had to like, I had to screen grab it.
In 1989, Stuart Hirsch began managing Pickett,
and upon learning Pickett did not own
the master recording of Monster Mash,
the pair in 1993 recorded a perfect copy
of the original Monster Mash
that they then used to undercut
the owners of the track Universal.
Monster Mash. Monster Mash.
Boris' verse.
Bobby Boris' verse.
Bobby's verse.
I wrote down Bobby's verse.
Sure.
It is Taylor's version much earlier.
She did it in the wake of Bobby Boris doing it.
She copied Bobby Boris' Pickett.
Yeah.
And then, if only he were around to do, you know,
blank space Bobby's version.
But a blank space, baby.
All right, Judy.
In blood.
So that's in the 90s.
Should we jump back to the monster rap?
Yeah, so, you know, the mash is still going.
The mash will just shart for no reason.
It hit number 10 in August 73.
What?
Not even at Halloween, so, like, I don't know.
It just kept going, but he's pretty quiet,
I'd say mostly, until we get into,
where do I even start?
I don't know.
All right, I'll just pick a random spot.
In 1985, it was Monster Rap.
["Monster Rap"]
Ha ha ha.
Still working in the lab late these nights
with eyes grown used to any science.
I created a monster who could dance and walk,
but I couldn't teach him how to talk.
My faithful assistant, that hunchback fool
who wastes his time in DJ school,
said, as you get in, don't be a cop.
You're the monster rap.
Shock the body, shock the body, body,
shock the body, shock the body, body,
shock the body, shock the body, body, shock.
Ah!
What do we think?
I like shock the body.
I kind of like the shock the body part too, honey.
It's different, he's not just saying monster rap.
Right, it's different.
I give him that, and I kind of like it,
of like, I kind of like it, I don't know.
Can I jump ahead in that song to,
there's a line, I just gotta play this one line.
Let me make sure this is all queued up,
because this has been haunting me, fittingly.
The monster rap haunts Jason.
Yeah.
Well.
I've given you a voice, now rap for daddy.
Like, oh man, that's out there,
that's out there with the unpleasant,
some of the most unpleasants,
I don't know why that just gave me the chills.
That sounds like the kind of shit you guys would say,
and then you're like, what?
What's weird about it?
Take me pop, daddy, what's weird about that?
What's weird about that?
Maybe that's why it's giving me the chills,
I'm seeing myself reflected back to me.
Dark mirror image.
Gazing to the abyss, long enough, the abyss gazes back.
And then when he then he raps, and then he's like,
now I'm this, and he's like Wolfman Jack, weirdly.
Right, yeah, yeah.
So he does do a character there, that's what you wanted,
you said it on the first album.
Might not be him.
Oh yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's him.
Maybe not.
He might have the ability to do that.
Shook the body, he went to DJ school.
DJ school.
The question is, how many things do you punify,
at what point does it get confusing?
Yeah, is it 85?
Is that right?
85, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's pretty early even for an old white guy
to try hip hop or try rapping.
It's not so, yeah, people did it way later, I would say,
and acted as if it was.
I mean, it's three years before the Beach Boys got there.
Yeah, there's much shittier cash-ins.
Where does this fall along with that John Wayne one?
Do you know about the John Wayne rapping duke?
Oh wow.
Somebody, that's a novelty record
that was actually really popular, the rapping duke.
Really?
It's 84.
Yeah, it's a guy rapping as John Wayne.
Okay.
But it was like kind of, wow,
the guy who did it opened for Bobby Brown
and Stevie Wonder actually was.
Oh wow, rapping Rodney's 83, nevermind, I take back my.
Rodney got there in 83?
That's what this says, yeah.
That's crazy to me.
I thought that was late 80s.
Wow, geez.
Wow, rapping Rodney, 83.
Damn.
Nevermind, I give credit to Rodney
for being an old white guy getting to a new genre.
Rodney, yeah, we're not saying
that any of these guys invented rap,
but did Rodney Dangerfield invent
shitty white guy cash-in comedy rap?
Right.
That's a good question.
Yeah, I got in there first.
He did it before rapping duke.
If Rodney was alive, he would have gone on stage
at that Kendrick show at SoFi,
where the Crips and Bloods were shaking hands
and he did the Drake song so many times.
So he, like a 105-year-old Rodney Dangerfield
on stage with Kendrick.
I'm burying the beef with Rodney Dangerfield.
It wouldn't have been Dr. Dre doing that intro line,
the I see dead people,
it would have been Rodney Dangerfield.
Right, in a hospital bed.
I see dead people, it's me and my wife's thankful,
something like that.
A woman who was 117 just passed away.
I think she was the oldest person alive,
so it could have happened.
The oldest person alive to remember
the references we make on the show.
I think there's been a couple of times
where we've blown by a couple first name
or Frank Gorshin mentions and not said who that is,
which is always a good thing too.
Because you can't always, if you...
If you're listening to this show,
I understand at this point you have to do
a lot of Googling unless you've been listening for a while.
Or you don't, or don't care.
Or your life goes on normal without ever knowing
what that name was that we said.
It's true.
I like that the deeper, that the B side of the single
of Rappin' Rodney, wait sorry, one side is Rodney Rappin',
then Rappin' Rodney, then Rodney continues Rappin'.
Ha ha ha ha.
Wow, and he did it with the guys who wrote The Breaks
with Kurtis Blow.
Rodney's working with real, he got good writers.
Wow.
I don't think, we have not been nominated for a Grammy.
Rappin' Rodney is a fundamental song apparently.
I guess.
I actually, yeah, I'm not an expert on Rappin' Rodney,
but it seems like a thing I should be an expert on.
Yeah, yeah.
You're disappointing everybody.
Who would assume that you are?
Mike, I have another memory of you're sitting
in your old apartment and we tried one night
to watch Caddyshack 2.
Yeah, we tried getting through Caddyshack 2,
but yeah, that was unwatchable.
It took me about 10, 15 minutes of Jackie Mason
walking around a construction site
and we're like, yeah, let's turn this off.
Did Jackie Mason ever rap?
Yep, looks like he did.
King, King, that was fast.
King of deli rap.
Oh, that sounds good.
Might be good.
In that apartment, we also did successfully watch
movie 43, is that what it's called?
Oh jeez.
Did we?
Yeah, it was rough.
I don't have a memory of that.
Yeah.
Yikes.
You may have just gotten in there without me
and watched it.
I'm breaking into Mike's apartment,
which is always 95 degrees for sun rising out.
Let's not skip past the Jason is giving you shade
for the heat in your apartment.
How many years later?
How many years are we talking?
No, it's not shade.
14?
I think it's just, it's fair.
It's a fair assessment.
Yes, it was hot.
It was really hot.
It was hard to get it to cool down.
It was old building.
Yeah, it wasn't my fall.
I mean, I guess it could have gotten.
No, it wasn't.
Now this is, now imagine this.
If the bright mad scientist could just make
that conversation happen inside one head.
Yeah, discussions. Oh yeah,
men with two brains style.
Arguing then with itself about which apartment.
No, it was more like 96.
No, 94 is what it was.
It never went above 94.
The heat may have given you brain damage
so you don't remember the cinematic spectacle
that is the movie 43.
Yeah.
I don't think we watched that there.
Pretty sure, cause it was Jackman
with the balls on his chin, right?
Maybe.
Yeah, but that has nothing to do with where you watched it.
Jackman had balls on his chin
regardless of where it was viewed.
Okay.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Fine, let's back to silly monster songs.
Enough with bad sketch comedy movies.
Yeah, let's jump ahead to,
well, I guess it bears mentioning that in 1995
there was Monster Mash, the movie.
Oh yeah.
Also called Frankenstein Sings, the movie.
This was written by Alex Sokolow and Joel Cohen,
the Joel Cohen, these guys who were some of the many
writer-created writers of the first Toy Story.
And that's the Joel Cohen that the name confusion
led to Bill Murray being in Garfield.
He thought he was working with the Cohen brothers.
Two Garfields.
Yeah, two Garfields.
I still think that's a lie.
Yeah, maybe he's covering his tracks.
Yeah, that's well, the name's not spelled the same way.
I have, look, I don't, I just need,
I don't have to say more about it.
Jimmy JJ Walker's in it.
John Casir is in it, the Crip Keeper.
Yeah, yeah. The end.
That's one of those you poke around,
like any fun material for the show?
Nope, nope, not worth wading through it.
Maybe an Edgemont who would've sat through this,
but not here.
Yeah, in the old days.
Madness.
But then, and then he's kind of quiet until 2004
where there's kind of a dual set of songs.
I'll start with the first one.
He somehow got roped into doing
politically char-issue charged music.
And I, this one's about deforestation.
And they all are accompanied by kind of like
Newgrounds type flash animation in which you'll see,
you know, our old pals Dubya and Condi and Chaney.
So just imagine that.
So this is Monster Slash.
Hiking in the forest, late to one night.
When our eyes beheld an eerie sight,
our president appeared and began to frown.
Then he and his friends cut the forest down.
He did the slash.
They did the forest slash.
Slash.
It was brutally brash.
Public opinion was mash.
He did the slash.
And they did it for the cash.
The lobbyist.
Okay, this is so much a piece with the next one
that I'll just go straight into it.
One year later, he did climate mash.
We were hiking past the white ice.
When our eyes beheld an eerie sight,
the president appeared with folks very strange.
The zombies and vampires of global climate change.
It's not global warming, say your ill company, the cycles.
Our math tells us it's natural weather cycles.
These claims from industry heavies
let the president rest behind his own protective levies.
They're doing the climate mash.
Oh yeah.
All right.
The science is bad.
Climate mash.
Solutions are tried.
And they do it for the cash.
For the cash.
All the sound effects, by the way,
are like George W. Bush is a vampire
and he's sucking what's labeled as oil ale from a can
or at some point he, right at the end there he,
which movie is the dancer pour all the water maniac?
Oh, we've done this.
We've gone over this on the show.
I know, we forgot.
Is it Slash Dancer or is it the other one?
That, I don't know, whichever it is.
I think it's Slash Dancer.
Okay, so that George W. Bush does that with oil.
Can I just get ahead of it?
Is there a song about the deficit or the national debt?
Like the capital steps, does he sing about?
That's more of a conservative thing though,
being worried about the deficit.
He seems like he's on the left here.
Which is good.
It's true.
And you know, look, we should have listened to him.
If we'd all listened to climate mash back then,
we'd be in a better place today.
And that's 2005, right?
2005.
Yeah, he actually, you know,
and he did it before An Inconvenient Truth.
So he was actually a head of,
he's again a pioneer in many ways.
This is, when I hear both of these songs,
what I picture is Harry Shearer laughing up a storm.
This is like, you know, he does entire,
in like classic Simpsons, he'd probably like
do all the dialogue and never crack a smile.
But then he listens to the climate mash and he's like,
ah, ha ha ha, good falling.
Book him for Lace Show.
He probably was on it, right?
Yeah, maybe, yeah, yeah.
There's 40 years of Lace Show to go through for us, I think.
Harry Shearer's show.
Is he still doing it?
Probably.
Yeah, way less listeners than we have.
He's doing it to no one.
The microphone hasn't been plugged in for years.
You know what, it's not the same thing,
but it reminds me of like during the Bush administration
when all of a sudden Burt Bacharach was like,
I'm putting out a protest album.
Oh, I remember that.
Who are these people that are destroying our lives?
Yeah, you know, like, I appreciate the sentiment, Burt,
but we needed this.
Really early, I wasn't still at Funny or Die,
but I would like go visit and somebody's,
I'm like, what are you guys working on?
And then the most miserable, somebody's like,
been miserably working on graphics for hours
of Tom Green's Trump rap called Do the Donald.
Do the Donald, do the Donald Trump.
My skin is orange and I didn't say nothing but lies.
I'm like, man, you were funny once, what happened?
You're right, you're not wrong.
I don't like Trump either, but Jesus.
I appreciate the effort, sir.
Everyone always roasts the pantsuit anthem,
but they don't, that never gets mentioned.
Yeah, yeah, well, it was like, you know,
because the pantsuit anthem was closer to the election.
It's like, you remember the Oscar movies
that come out in December, it was in the season.
Yeah, but yeah, go check out Donald, Do the Donald.
Now, speaking of sketches in Funny or Die and such,
I don't think you can do this episode
and not mention two incredible sketches
based on Monster Mash and all this stuff.
Mr. Show's Monster Party's Factor Fiction,
which has so many perfectly accurate,
fantastic equivalents of this song.
And then, of course, our pal, Nick Weiger's
immortal monster fuck once voted the number one thing
on Comedy Bang Bang ever, and I can't argue,
that's really funny, it's very, very funny.
I didn't realize also, I never appreciated
that the guy, his voice, or his character he plays in it,
who did the original song, I think is called Leo Carpazzi
and the actual co-writer of the song is Lenny Capizzi.
So I never knew that he was nodding
to the non-vocal writer of the song.
So detail, I didn't appreciate Weiger, it's so great.
What else though?
I mean, that takes you through the,
you know what's funny is that, I mean,
I think, look, politically, regardless of whether
you like the songs, I think Bobby Boris Pick is a good guy.
He had this whole arc where he reunited with his daughter,
a daughter he didn't even know about, way late in life,
and they got to reconnect before he passed away.
He had a struggle with leukemia, which sounds very sad,
but he got to have this relationship,
and she was so delighted.
She's like, oh, I remember when I got to tell my kids,
you know who Grandpa is?
He did the monster mash.
That's wonderful.
That's pretty fun.
He was very well regarded, apparently,
and then even when he came down with leukemia,
he started doing blood transfusions,
and then the agent would call him, how's it going?
And he'd say, Stu, there's nothing like fresh blood.
He like monsterified, he was still doing it.
Yeah.
So I don't know, I'm glad there's a guy we can celebrate
and not go into some like, oh, but then he's saying,
oh, he did this, oh, he would've hated the McGovern mash.
Yeah.
Wait, was that the right, no, I should be,
no, Mondale's what I should be saying.
Walter Mondale.
I mean, he could've done a McGovern mash.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, a song about how Mondale was,
he'll only win Minnesota.
I think I've said this on the show before,
a friend of mine, or I guess he's,
we're recording these out of order,
he's been on the show at this point, Justin Donaldson.
His dad was a pop star in the 70s
and toured with Bobby Boris Pickett, here and there.
And my favorite thing is that it was very cheap
to get Bobby any other month but October.
But in October, if you were booking Bobby,
it was the price shot up.
I don't know the air details.
Can I interest you in the St. Patrick's mash?
If you wanted to book Bobby to do Monster Mash in March,
pretty cheap.
Everyone's having a wonderful day.
We're all saluting the hero MLK.
That was like 500 bucks.
He was the opposite of a monster.
Like, yeah, people are confused by that.
Well, it was cheap, it didn't cost.
But October, you're paying up to get Bobby
to do an appearance, which I love it.
Like Homer investing in pumpkin and being mad in November.
I believe Justin directed the video for the Monsterfuck.
Yes, that's right.
The original Monster Mash, I believe that's correct.
A really good video, too.
Here's where my mind started going,
is if he did pass away, unfortunately,
but yeah, I started wondering what genres
he would capitalize on and try to bring Monsters into.
There's nothing as totally new as rap today,
but I was trying to think what sort of the era
that Boris might nod to.
And what popped into my head was monster trap.
And I was like, all right, what's a low impact?
How do I get my head around trap music
as much as Bobby Boris Pickett would?
Whatever, yeah.
And I went on YouTube and just looked up free trap beats
and I found free DaBaby Type Beat Bounce
produced by Phantom.
Thank you, Phantom.
And okay, this is my poorly researched jammed out attempt
at the monster trap.
I need some like, ooh, remember when I did the rap?
Well, now I'm back with something new.
In the lab, late one night, eyes beheld,
eerie sights, monster rose from his nap,
started doing monster trap, monster trap,
monster, monster trap, monster trap, monster, monster trap.
Frankenstein, Dracula, Dracula, Frankenstein,
Frankenstein, Dracula, Wolfman, Wolfman, Wolfman.
That's it.
That's great.
That was great.
That was really good.
It sounds good to me, you got some birds in there.
Yeah, yeah, that's the same.
If it's not accurate, it's as accurate as he would have been.
I mean, and that's my best shot at it,
but it's also very possible that you listen
to the song, the 2024 song, Monster Trap,
and it just goes, I was working in the lab.
That's more effort than he would have put in.
Yeah, they did the trap.
It was some, it was some genuine trap.
There's a, there's a Nicki Minaj song
called Bees in the Trap that that sounds like.
Oh yeah, it does.
Bees in the trap, bees in the trap, monsters in the trap.
Relatively, I learned just like my Googling,
do you mean Abbott Elementary,
earlier I was Googling monster rap and they're like,
do you mean Nicki Minaj's verse?
Oh, from Monster.
No, no, I do not.
That's from the last 20 years.
Have you not learned anything from my history?
I am looking up the 1985 Knowledge Single Monster Rap.
Stupid AI, getting wrong shit again.
Gotta log into DuckDuckGo to get like some clean results.
They know, if I go to Ask Jeeves,
they know I'm looking for Bobby Boris Pickett.
Yeah.
That's where my kind is accepted.
Pure, pure search.
Anyway, too bad he can't be around to do Monster Trap.
He should have been on,
well no, when he died somewhat recently,
like 10 years, 10 years, 15.
Yeah, maybe.
Was he a live monster is what,
from my beautiful Dark Toasted Finish from 12,
14 years ago?
Well, could Bobby have been on that track is what I'm saying.
Was it possible?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Bobby Boris Pickett remix.
You got like what, Rick Ross, Jay-Z, Kanye, Nicki Minaj,
Bobby Boris.
Here we go, about to drop some mad science for 2010.
Get rid of the Rick Ross intro for Monster
and put Bobby Boris on it.
That should have been the thing.
A no good blood sucker.
Yeah.
Well, if only, I mean, that's a remix,
waiting to be done, I would say.
Seems like Kanye's fallen victim
to some mad scientists lately, hasn't he?
Oh God, the story gets weirder and sadder.
Yeah, yeah.
I was working in the lab with my nitrous tank.
My dentist was there in Dracula and Frankenstein.
And I hooked Ye up to my electrodes.
Oh God.
His jack dentist.
Tap to dentist.
Bobby died in 2007.
Jack is the wolf man.
Oh, so he never.
So he wouldn't have been able to do it.
Yeah, yeah.
You could see though, Kanye, I don't know,
with his like eclectic hirings and you know,
there's like spoken word parts on that album.
Yeah, he could have like, yeah.
Yeah, well, yeah, there's a lot of collaborations,
at least in the old days.
Yeah.
I mean, it's now I guess too, but.
And he never called up the originator.
Yeah.
One of the great early rappers.
Right, 85.
He should have had Rodney on the track.
He should have had Bobby.
When is the, yes.
Hey, have you guys heard this new like hit single
with Bobby Boor's Pickett and Rodney Dangerfield?
Rodney died in 2004.
So College Dropout is around then, right?
He kind of passed the baton.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, February 10th, 2004.
So yeah, Rodney's like last thing.
Goodbye, Rodney.
Hello, Kanye.
Sampling, welcome back.
Sampling rapping Rodney.
Has anyone done that?
Anyone done it so.
Well, the John Wayne one is famous because he,
because Notorious B.I.G. does reference.
Remember rapping Duke to Har to Har.
Never thought hip hop would take it this far.
So he did do a reference to one of these novelty songs,
but did anyone give a nod to?
Right. Yeah.
I don't know.
And has Monster Mash been sampled?
I mean, that's a funny, that's a thing to look up.
Was it sampled in that weird like
Munster's Fall Out Boy song or am I misremembering?
Not so.
I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
Munster's Fall Out Boy.
I do like that song.
You do?
Yeah, I like the Munster sample.
She wanna dance like Uma Thurman.
It's called Uma Thurman, yeah.
Well, it was, oh wait.
Well, what whosampled.com is showing me is that it was
covered and remixed by Carmella Creeper.
There you go.
To bring it all back around.
There you go, Jay.
She's a DJ.
She is a DJ.
Oh, she's been to DJ school.
Well, I hope this is a fun trip into a genre.
If we missed anything.
We missed a lot of things.
Okay, okay.
Well, let us know.
Yeah, if you care to hear about more
or do you want more old man novelty rap
or does that sound abhorrent to you?
Should we lock that in a tomb and not resuscitate it?
But otherwise, I think you survived.
Hauntcast, The Fright, The Cemetery Gate.
If you want to grave dig even deeper,
join us on our RIP tier, Crypt 3,
where you get one more boonus episode
for just three more bones a month.