FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following haunt cast may contain
Fly Pods
Lemons vs. Limes
Gene Kelly's final feline role
and spooky talk about a dead pharmacy
All that plus, Adam Sass returns to talk
Universal's Horror Makeup Show
on today's Haunt Cast the Fright
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright, a ghoulish scream park podcast
hosted by three men who are very scared of getting zapped by the host busters
My name is Spiky Snarlgun
Joining me as always is
The Gare Wolf
Okay, great
And?
Jack'll scare it in
Great, yeah
So we're all here today, we're all very scared
We're scared and scary today
And you're saying that the host busters are people who bust hosts, that being us
Right
And if we were to get trapped into some sort of little machine that sucks hosts inside of it
First of all, uncomfortable for all of us
We're long past social distancing, but to be all three trapped in a tiny box sounds tough
Second of all, when do we get out of there and how do we do the show once we've been busted?
Well, I guess we would go into some sort of a host containment unit
We would get out of the tiny trap and then we would go into a bigger like kind of hell zone
Which is where the hosts go, so I suppose maybe that would offer more room
And then we could do our show from in there
A realm of entirely podcast hosts, that sounds to me like heaven
Yeah, everybody
Everyone's idea
So many digressions
Wow
So many half-remembered facts and anecdotes
Well, you're technically in a box, you're technically in everybody's phones
So you're, you know, you are in the box already
We're in the trap
You're already in the trap
It's a trap
Yeah, this whole thing is a trap
This whole podcast, don't tell anyone
Don't tell anybody
You know those podcasts that ride guys?
This whole thing has been set up as a trap
I never get tired of that guy when he floats by my, when they do the memes
I love seeing the merch man
I stop every time for the merch man
Yeah
I'm lost, I'm officially lost
Oh, the M&I Shyamalan trap
Oh, I see, okay
The new film
The trailer has been played in a lot of places and they play this one segment every time
Where he's like explaining to Josh Hartnett, the serial killer, that they're trapping a serial killer
Yes, it's a man explaining the, a character within the movie explaining the premise of the movie
Okay, have we spoiled, we should have spoiled an alert I guess
No, that's in the trailers
No, this is the trailer money shot
Is it really?
Yeah
No, and on Twitter, the new meme is, since traps come out, is that they have a screenshot of the merch man
And they're just recapping different movies and he's like, oh, you know, you know, and then just, they'll fill in the blank
You know, they'll pitch a new thing, they'll be like, hey, you know, and it's all a trap
Yeah
Wow, okay, well, thank goodness
I didn't want to ruin this movie three months after it came out
Get back on Twitter
It's been out for a little bit
But maybe some memes have been spoiled
That's true, yeah
Do memes need spoiler alerts?
Maybe
We're getting to that place socially
Let's introduce this ghost voice that just entered
Our special ghost
Our special ghost today
Returning to Hauntcast this Friday, he's the author of LGBTQYA books and an old character actor, name enthusiast
Ladies and gentlemen, Adam Sass is back
Hello, hello, and for Hauntcast, I am Adamian the Exorcass
Wow, that's cool
That sounds like a real character
Yeah, yeah, we're going to concentrate all the devil energy over here
Okay
As I usually do
That could help us get out of the trap
Although we're still
Having the devil involved?
An exorcist, I just think
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Somehow
That's right
You're right
Well, I'm like a Beetlejuice type who's like, yes, I'm the Damian part, that's the devil part, but I'm also helping out
Okay, yeah, yeah, sort of
Like a Dexter
Dexter or Beetlejuice, which are similar characters now that I just realized that
Well, yeah, I hadn't thought about that
So like if Beetlejuice, if it was, you were Beetlejuice, but the way he was helping was, I'm trying to remember who played Mel Cooley on the Dick Van Dyke show
And you said Richard Deacon, that would be your Beetlejuice's function
That's right, exactly, yeah, I'm the Beetlejuice for old character actors from Nick at Night era
Right
Yeah, mid-90s
Very helpful though
Yeah, yeah, needed
Very needed
There's an unmet need, yes
Yes, more of those, we need more old Dexter names
Yes, so yeah, thank you for coming back, thank you for joining the haunt cast again
I'm happy to be a regular haunt cast ghoulie
Yeah, it's a very fun space to be in
And today we are talking about something very near and dear to your heart, I would say
Currently called the Universal Orlando's Horror Makeup Show
That's right, and this is, so like I'm, you know, last time I was here to talk to Murder, Shrew, at Mystery Theatre
And I'm, for whatever remaining OG Universal Orlando things you all have left, I'm like, I don't know, I feel like I'm scavenging for those
You're stalking them, yeah, picking the bones
This one's definitely more Halloween horror appropriate than the Murder, Shrew, the Murder, Shrew one was, you know, I think that was still appropriate
But now we're like
It was really, you suggested it, but I think I rounded it up into Halloween not really knowing the contents of the show
Knowing that the word Murder was in it and thinking, well, that'll be good for a tiny amount of research
Well, shit, sorry on the books, let's not, but this is way more, this is like a year round thing that does have scary moments, scary clips and all that
So now we can really get into my horror bona fides here, you know, with that
So this is something that like, yeah, I loved this show and it's, I think, you know, it's been several different iterations
But this has been around from the get-go, this has lasted
As something that's been around from the get-go, we get to do something that we also did last time
Which is, you know, we can only build these things up so much
But you need somebody with a true presence and a strong voice to tell you what the attraction's all about
And that means I get to consult one of the great texts, the Magic of the Movies video with John Forsythe
And I think once you hear this clip, you'll understand why it needed to be played
Because we're never going to explain the attraction as succinctly as John Forsythe does
The darkness is the deepest. These are the elements of our most enduring type of storytelling and entertainment
Universal gained the reputation as Hollywood's home of horror in the 20s and early 30s
Bela Lugosi, Dracula, Boris Karloff, Frankenstein
Was that a scary crow that they piped in or was that just a regular crow hanging out during the shoot?
It was just some guy circling John Forsythe, sensing his time was approaching
The Grim Reaper was so good!
Sounds good, but white hair!
He seems to be kind of getting through that sentence a little bit
That does seem like the opening of Universal Orlando was so fraught with troubles
Like Jaws didn't work, King Kong kept breaking down
It would be apropos if they were like, also there's a murder of crows haunting this park
We cannot clear out the crows, they're a protected species, we had to leave their habitat there
Well Spielberg has the big film strip and he's got the scissors and he's about to cut and then he just hears
And he just throws them off and he's like, oh shit, okay
It grabs his hat
It reveals that Spielberg's been bald the whole time
What?
Thank you for bringing back my guy John Forsythe
I hope you're sitting down
I did rewatch the entire making of the movies ahead of this
Because I can't just watch a little clip, I had to watch a little thing
I'm in love with John Forsythe's line readings
I know we're in this age of like, that sounds like Chad GPT wrote that
This script was written by a human being and it does sense
It was an early version of AI wrote a lot of these sentences because they're so clunky
And the way this Magic of the Movies opens, he says something, I'm going to paraphrase
I had it written down but I lost it
He's just describing the act of going to the movies
In the most rudimentary ways
The filmmakers of yesteryear entranced our minds and imaginations
In the same way that our bodies were entranced by the popcorn and soft drinks
He hits the syllables weird
And it just sounds like it was Chad GPT wrote it
And you're having an AI voiceover guy read it
But no, it was the Magic of Forsythe that came organically from him
It's so highfalutin and what does any of it mean
In that clip I just played, does that actually
He got to horror but we didn't quite get to the show
He does a little bit later
But the weird past tense
Lovers and heroes lit up our days
But villains and spooks haunted our nights
Why is it past tense?
I got news for you John, there's still movies now
They're still making them
It feels like someone
Like if he came in now I'd be like
He's eulogizing movies
He's eulogizing the way we kind of do movies
Because movies are in this kind of flux period right now
But I think definitely back in 1990
When movies were just in their absolute prime
Just everything, even just the 17th movie at the box office
Just some beloved thing that you just watched on HBO all the time
I love this genre of YouTube video
Where it's like people buy movie tickets in 1997
And like one weekend the movies that are playing
It's like blockbuster after blockbuster after blockbuster at one time
Oh I mean every time I'm listening to Plank Check and they do the box office game
I'm just like God, what a week
What a week that was
And they all did immensely well
It's like wow, number nine is great
Oh to be in a theater seeing Mr. Wrong now
It is funny to think that John Forsythe is talking like very poetically
About a show that will eventually have clips of the lost world and the frighteners
Yeah our greatest days are ahead of us
Van Helsing is coming
That's my favorite part is that the most recent movies
A lot of them are like kind of duds
And we're going to get into this
But like it is one of those things where I wonder how many days the show has
I mean I hope it's continuing
I hope it's like a well attended show
But it's just like we don't really do makeup a lot
Not as much
We're kind of doing
I was researching best makeup winners, Oscar winners
And you're just sort of seeing the last 10 years are really defined by
We're going to make
The defining makeup of the last 10 years really has just been like
We're going to make Charlize Theron look like Megyn Kelly
Which wasn't saying
Which wasn't, I looked very spookily correct
But then it's really just defined by
Like we're really just makeup now is just we're doing
Really iffy fat suits now
Like that seems to be what makeup is doing
Like a lot of the best makeup actors
I think there was like the year the whale one was just like it was that
And then Colin Farrell doing that and the penguin and Batman
Like there was just
I think that was that year
There was like three of the four or five best makeup actors were like
Yes that was overweight makeup you were putting on
And it just seems like I'm like we're not really in the Rick Baker glory days right now
Of like you know because it does seem to be more defined by like digital manipulation
Hopefully it is maybe
You know maybe it's just one or two swinging back
But I saw an interview with Michael Keaton about Beetlejuice Beetlejuice
And they eat him and Tim Burton were kind of like as much practical stuff as we can
As little CG as we can
And I think that's from the reviews that are starting to pour in or just like yes, correct
Yeah
Like that worked and it's just the tactile and you can feel it
And I think that's I think that's another reason why like it's just horror is so fun
Is because you're just it'll kind of kind of feel like it feels like it feels like that's still a good haven for makeup
It still feels like that's a good place to get lots of good practical effects
Like everybody who's doing horror seems to like be really like kind of you know both feet deep in on
You know doing things practically doing things in this way
We're like we're going to try to invent these new mechanisms for blood splatter and this sorts of things
And it still does feel relevant
That's why I'm like I hope it continues because I do think there is still this really strong avenue for makeup
It still works as a show to see in a theme park
And it's not you know how it's maybe if it's less appealing to see other you know a special effects show or even like
Go look at backlog sets because of how much is done digitally at this point
There is still really crazy makeup in movies all the time and it like and it's still physical and tactile
And you can like it's yeah, I don't know and with the blood and everything
It's just it is a good thing to do in front of an audience in a theme park setting
I guess just the the basic cliff notes to say about this is that this is a show
It's been going since opening day of Universal Florida
And the the basic thing I guess is that you are going to see a demonstration in a makeup lab
But also like a creature effects lab
Where there's it's I guess it's it's one guy is more or girl is more hosty and the other performer is more the experts in the
Makeup or blood and guts and gore area and together they give you a demonstration person in suit and then person in
Hawaiian get up
And the while a lot has changed about the show over the years that basic
Construct is stayed and the you know where they they do it is stayed and with that. It's kind of interesting. I think
Definitely saw places pointing out maybe the only
universal opening day attraction besides ET adventure and
That still remains and then if you add it up and somebody correct me if I'm wrong is this not the final in all of
Orlando show that is about how movies are made unless you count Indiana Jones
Stunt spectacular you're still that component of we're shooting this but it's a little bit more you get lost in the
You know in Indies world in the stunt, but but in terms of like here is a specific as there's no animation tour
There's no special effects stages. Right? There's no here's how Foley works. Yeah, Disney or Universal
This is the kind of last man standing. I think like so much
Horror keeping people in theaters
Horror is keeping
How how do they do that kind of around you know, because I think like a lot of times with digital
I'm not like a I'm not a huge digital hater
But like there is an element that takes the mystery out of cuz you're just like oh, I'm sure you know a computer did that
I know there's like a more sophisticated answer to that
But I think for the masses you do end up in a situation where there's less curiosity cuz you're like
I'm sure somebody just did a thing on a computer and it's fine. And there is not that sort of deeper level of like
Here's how that gets done and then this is what that's like
I wonder if there's a compelling theme park show based around
computer like a graphics or something. Yeah, could you do like a
Admittedly insultingly remedial version where you're like dudes doing like, okay. Yes. Here's how you you know, here's how someone who's
You know, here's how you do like a mocap. They're gonna do like a mocap room
There's gotta be some mocap and volume definitely yeah themselves more than my past iterations of
Yeah, cuz usually it's just a montage with all the different stages like you see a gray
Mummy and then you see another mummy with a little more detail and it is always the mummy still
Yeah, it's still kind of got set on when we show people how computer characters are made. It will always be
actor Arnold Voslue
And look, you don't have to tell me I love Arnold Voslue
Let's get them all back for number four, you know, we we brought Brendan Frazier's come back Stephen Summers needs to have his
Do you know the story about how he like?
Lived in a house that that was apparently like people say was cursed
No, like Britney Spears own it owned it. I
Heard yeah, yeah through all this stuff and then he bought it and then had like these movie like
all his movies were hits and then he did Van Helsing and it was kind of
Barely broke even and then he he just got stuck doing he blamed the box office bomb on the house
People were saying okay sounds kind of fun though to just be like Van Helsing was you know, if you didn't like it
My house goes well, I made it so how would it be good? How was it gonna work?
Universal has treated I feel like universe. I was treated Van Helsing
In the Peter Jackson King Kong. It's like the biggest
21st century there there's they're still contractually obligated to speak like that
I feel like they're they send some yeah
They send some Faustian deal back then just just be like well in perpetuity you have to speak about it as if it
Yeah, yeah, and I I saw a King Kong when it opened that when you're a Christmas
I think I've seen half of Van Helsing on TNT. They know drama
But I I've seen this show a lot
So you're saying it's better because you've seen it
Oh this? Well I can vouch for it personally. You're the taste maker so you're like I am yeah
You're like well if I haven't seen it, it's not really close to you know, it's not
Van Helsing is worth half a watch. Van Helsing equals Olivia Rodriguez
You've only seen the first half of Van Helsing
I've seen 25 minutes of Van Helsing and I've seen all of this 25 minute show a number of times
Listen, if you've only seen the first half of Van Helsing, you've missed the best part, which is for an entire generation
There's a whole like there's a whole like werewolf thing at the end of Van Helsing that like all of the like
Monster lovers on Twitter are just like that was my root when I was like young like there was like
Yeah fucking like stuck in their heads and they're just you're like cuz it's just like this
It's just like it's like a ripped guy with like a werewolf head on it
So it's just like it's and it's just it like stuck for a lot of people
So yeah, you missed out on that second half man. I gotta fire a peacock
Where I would assume it would be but it is probably not listen peacock is like got everything low-key
Peacock and to be you're sad that's I'm telling you all you need is peacock and to be like you and you've got all of
cinema covered
To be has I gotta go home and watch cuz I just discovered to be has cats don't dance, which is gene
I
Was reading about the Emperor's new groove
Okay, and I started reading about the director and it says he briefly left it left Disney to direct cats don't dance
Credited as Gene Kelly's final film role. Yep, cuz he is the choreographer
Okay
The
Character is kind of inspired by him and I'm like I didn't know this
I thought it was just about like a slick looking cat. So now I have to go watch this cuz I love Kelly
So when you see Danny t cat
Really seeing Gene Kelly for the last time but he didn't motion capture it. I don't think I don't think they were there yet
Doing any choreography for the penguin named Pudge I
Don't know cat says cats don't dance. There's no word on if Pudge dances. We don't know penguins dance
They do there is I don't like you have to promise me you won't talk about something else for 20 minutes
But I want to tell you quickly Don Knott's is in this movie
He has TW turtle an erotic superstitious turtle. You said neurotic not erotic, right?
Yeah
The word was that Don Knott's like got around there's a ladies man, you've heard this I assume yes, okay
I'm watching you for those listening my warning for those listening. I said it at all
So I was listening when he Mike Mike heard that he did a Don Knott's esque reaction
Some yeah
Like really yeah early style and I really do hope you get off on a tangent on this because it was Mike it has been
On my it's on my like bucket list to not just now that I've been on
Podcasts to ride to be part of a false start episode
Really I was like I really hope I throw this into such a disarray
So yeah, it's a way to buy yourself a second episode. That's true. That's true. Look, you know, we can go down my different watch lists
I gotta get the cats. Don't dance. I gotta finally watch cool world
To be has
Okay, these are all
Do the full start for you
Advertisements in the comic books of the time and they loomed so large. Mm-hmm
You for a year you look you've been 18 and over for a long time
It's been legal for you to see many many years
I think the thing to be scared of is it sucking?
Well, that's a good thing about a lot of 80s and late 80s 90s animated stuff about 70 minutes long
So not a huge investment sure sure. Well now the test for you with anything is does it pass the Helsing?
Do you make it
I mean look, I don't I don't want to date it
But I we have a few days with nothing to do
Need to get my rest so I could fire up Van Helsing can fire up cast
Don't dance. You don't want to date it. You have a few days with nothing to do
Like saying what holidays are coming up because we're recording recording a little early
So how would you saying you have nothing to do like people would know because Jason's they all know Jason's schedule
Famously packed schedule. We've already kind of discussed Beetlejuice Beetlejuice is a movie that is about to open. So
What will cause Jason to have to leave the factory that eats his days and nights when he's not doing the fuck
Just just know if you're tucking in with some of these movies with to be and you put on the second half of events up
Then Helsing just be prepared for something to awaken in you
Know as at the end, you know by the second half, you know, but no one's ever prepared
Here's my pitch you get the volume which is the big like fake screen
It's a screen they shoot the Mandalorian on it with like very ultra detailed backgrounds
You bring dad up you put the motion capture suit on dad and then you cycle through funny scenarios on
Stage and everyone eats it up
This is a perfect recipe for a theme park show and modern version of what we like and what we miss listen
You guys are fathers here. So you just I don't want you to go the rest of your you know, you know
Your fatherhood while you're while your kids are in the house, you know and not get humiliated at a theme park
That's your that's a rite of passage. We were all promised right growing up. Yeah
I think everybody was moved by Tim Walz's son saying that's my dad
Well, we're since there's no chance of us becoming vice president or a vice presidential nominee
We're waited that moment will come when we're on stage wearing a feather bella
With the other big theme park show participatory group
Members of giant Brazilian tour groups who have English as a second language
Okay, that was the one show I watched
Oh this of the makeup show right over the audience loved it
They're telling the show that there was a giant Brazilian tour group. I was she I think she alluded to
Yeah, and she was like
English was her second language, right?
the hosts were
speaking they were using that as
Like well spelled me a bad name for you and then they you know cut into her what I love about the horror makeup
show is that there are
You could just type that into YouTube and none of us will see the same episode. Oh, yeah
Yeah, and we've come across things and recently we're like we're just watching one person's home movie of this, huh this case
There's a ton of recent ones and then I don't remember what year I I think you know, probably like 91 or 93
Oh, yeah, hopefully we can all bring different jokes to we can all just recite very dry Lee different jokes from our performances to each other
I did read
This is one of Universal's official website, but a few years ago on this blog discover universal
There was a long profile of two actors
That have been doing this show forever and they've been doing lots of shows in Orlando
Summer ILO and Robin Kelly and they talk about doing this show and I would change over the years and now like if they're coming in
And they're working together
Sometimes a rock-paper-scissors for who's gonna be those and who's gonna be the effects expert?
Wow, and it's really fun. They know it so well they can just they can flip it easily and also yeah
Well to that end it seems like a show in which improv is allowed and encouraged and included
Yes, which I don't think is the case with a ton of these things especially things shows where there's sort of like tight brand management
But there isn't with this because they're talking about universal horror in general
Yeah, and it sort of is its own IP within just you know
All that has to happen is a guy and a Hawaiian shirt has to be very passionate about Jack Pierce or whatever
Beyond that you could sort of you could sort of do what you want Lon Chaney man of a thousand faces and that's
Because the original iteration of this was called the Phantom of the Opera horror makeup show
Yes, so this would that was the first the first time this clunky name was clunky
Was they were and it opened where you went into this opening room
You know much like you kind of did in all them in the murderous row on the Hitchcock one
Was you went into this pre-show room probably what they wrapped up the next thing and then this one was there was a guy
Dressed as Phantom of the Opera, you know original Lon Chaney Phantom of the Opera and he had a mask on and then he did a little
Ah, you know kind of while they had like a room full of props and posters and whatnot and then he kind of did his
Spooky intro and I'm not sure if they do that
That was also the big ending of the show was not Eddie the werewolf it was the fly
Chamber and that's the one I remember because that would the fly chamber which
You know at no offense to Eddie the werewolf
But they you know, the fly chamber thing was like so impressive because like you're they had
The Hawaiian shirt guy like would go in the one of the pods and
You know and you know everyone be like no don't get in the pod
You'll turn into a fly and then and then he appears in the next one
Really?
It's somebody else who's already got you know
Sort of halfway to fly makeup applied in the Hawaiian shirt and I think that might be why
They had that guy in the Hawaiian shirt cuz they're like, oh, I remember that's the the shirt
That's the same shirt the guys wear
Quickly you could recognize me like oh my god, it's the same person
but it's a very recognizable shirt and then he comes out and then he
Goes back. This is not this is not proper fly world building
But this is how they did this in the show
You can't just go back in and go go back in one came out half fly went into the other pod came out full
beast fly
And then he's like get back in there and then came out normal at the other one
So you just needed to kind of crisscross if it were that easy
Yeah, that would have solved all of the film's problem. Davis would not need to be so terrorized
Yeah, saw the movie and you know what? Honestly, there should be more David Cronenberg representation at the park
Let's get a videodrome
Horror night scanners house. Oh my god, that would be scary. Yeah. Well, I think let's let's get an infinity pool
into
Just in general, there's just like a body horror sort of thing and it's really like interesting how because the original and I I'm sorry
I'm gonna I'm gonna if everybody remembers the last one. I'm
Mr. I only remember in 1982 and I don't recall anything else
There you go, so I'm just like so they had the fly and then they had the American Royal from London change
Oh heads as part of this as well
Yeah, I think they still lean on those pretty heavily because they're still very impressive and they're at the Academy Museum now still too
You know, so they're they're kind of all over the place, which is an interesting demonstration that that is not it's like it's it's not prosthetics
It's like although it's related to prosthetics and Rick Baker did it
But they're like that there's two steps of molds based on the actor's head one that is getting somewhat more
Wolfified and one that's all the one that has the mechanisms to make the face stretch like crazy
Which is also it's all interesting to watch too because you're like, what's the same?
It's also the thriller thing on I forgot John Landis did this too
So John Landis made that movie and then two years later Michael Jackson said will you just do the same thing for me?
Correct and then it kind of that sort of lives. I'd say higher up in pop culture
Then right movie. That's just a strange like hey you good job me too. It's one of those things where
So like I love American Werewolf on London, I think it's a it's a it's a it's fascinating that
That that
That that's like that's such a like hyper
Toxically straight guy
You know made a very fun
fascinating
Zippy sometimes accidentally queer
Movie, but it came from such a rat bastard
Like I love that movie so much but they're like, oh you're like a landis guy and I'm just like no every other movie
No, I think this is
Yeah, and I think this one of those things where that's a movie that's kind of lived on they still use it in a lot
Of clip shows they use it. It's a horror staple. It's really really great
It is a movie that I think like
Like Zemeckis with death becomes or he just accidentally stumbled onto like gold with that and a lot of it is the makeup
I think that's Rick Baker's movie to me
Like it's I think these are a lot that landis, you know did or whatever like that
But like I think the the power of that is really Rick Baker who like looms large over this show
Horror makeup show and and you know film makeup horror makeup in general
Did he consult on it maybe I think he may have at least like hey probably I think they talked to him and he said
Yeah, I got these meccanus. I think he like personally donated the American werewolf stuff
I believe yeah, because it was it was it mean because you had the to change your heads which are which are you know?
President because that whole sequence took
The week to shoot I mean and then it's like a few minutes of the movie and each like I think day was like
Two or three shots like it was truly like it just truly like this laborious thing that like everyone involved with now
It was just like oh, I wouldn't do it the same way
but it's like it's the thing everybody remembers about the movie, but
but like I he must have consulted on this because a lot of like his
Mentees and mentors are kind of in that there is this sort of like the more I've been was investigating this the more I was like
Like you know, cuz he was mentored by Dick Smith who did a lot of
The stuff that gets featured in this he did the exorcist
and
This dick Smith did a ton of stuff and and then he mentored Rob Botten who did the howling at the same time
So like there's a lot of just like passing this knowledge down
I would say through the generations, but really through 15 years
15 years they just very right a lot of them were like 70s and 80s when there really was a lot of this like horror like
You know revolutionary doing that kind of stuff where you could really the production code was over and you can really just go gnarly
on a lot of these effects
But yeah
one of the one of the movies that gets brought up a lot in in
The original version that I remember really scaring me was something is a movie that like not a lot of people talk about now is
Ghost story, which was 1981. Oh, yes. I watched that a couple years ago and read the book
Yeah, it's um, it's a Peter Straub
Yeah book and it got made into this movie with like a slew of like
Golden age of it like Fred Astaire is in it. Oh, wow. I've never seen this Fred Astaire
Melvin Douglas like Douglas Fairbanks jr. Melvin Doug. Yeah
yeah, and like there's like a whole bunch of that era guys who are like 80 when they made this movie when
Like 81 and it's just about them being haunted by this young woman that they killed killed
When they were teenagers, they accidentally killed and the whole thing was just like there was like a I can't remember what it was
But it's like it's a really freaky movie. I rate highly recommend it. It's um
Really nuts if you're if you're if you're down to watch like a horror movie, you're never seen it's 81
But it featured so prominently in this show
Because they brought out the the ghost woman because it's this sort of this rotting ghost skeleton woman
Oh, that's from the okay. Okay, we sort of have sort of a half decaying face
Yes, yeah, because she's they accidentally like oh she they've they're struggling and she fought
I remember what it is, but like it's one of those accidentals grapple grapple grapple. Oh, no accidentally dead. What do we do?
We have we have bright futures ahead of us. We're young men
We gotta
Put her in the car and drown the car and they do that and then oh she wasn't really dead
And so she like drowns in the car and remember like they showed the clip of that in this show
I remember being you know, like just very little watching this and just being and she's just and it's
If I'm pronouncing her name wrong Alice Krieg who's Borg Queen? Yeah, who's in Silent Hill just who's horror queen? Yeah
And she's like a very young woman in this movie
But she's extremely they very early on she was able to tap into I am a sinister person I am a sinister presence and
So like she's very sweet, but you she very easily taps into that sinister energy got an intense look. Yes
yes, and
Yeah, and I just remember like the way she's like pounding on the window of the cars
The cars sinks beneath the dark lake and it just was like it just stuck with me
So even when I knew we were gonna be doing this episode, I was like the first image popped in my head was like
Oh the lady in the car
With you. Yeah, which I feel like became like a trope and cut the cars thinking like
maybe like
It became a thing where it's like, oh, I don't know what that is originally from
Maybe it's just that clip is in where she's like almost
Yeah, she's banging on the windows maybe it's a lot of those AFI specials or something it
Jumped like, you know, so like yeah
The AFI peppers where it was like, oh the hundred scariest movements in movie history and they did that around like
2002 and so it's like you get a lot of nice 80s 70s that way but can I can I just say really quick?
I'm looking at Alice Kriegs Wikipedia and it's like a it's a big list of you know
Great films and things that I basically I'm looking at blue links meaning I haven't clicked on it and there's only one
purple that I have clicked on and that is
The TV movie dynasty the making of a guilty pleasure
She plays Joan Collins, I believe and I have like, okay
So I've only clicked on this and why I've never watched dynasty. I've pursued
What is up with a TV movie just about the making of dynasty which wouldn't be
The first time I've watched a full making of bad TV movie about a show. I've never seen I
Just like a good hammy represent
unauthorized
like
There's the real person's threatening legal action. Yeah. Yeah, so wrong
Yeah that they may be have to change characters names because it was so not close
Actually recently there were fun like there was a
Did the cheapest cheapo of saved by the bell and full house and a lot of good ones of Mork and Mindy way in
The past but then I looked and then I'm like, oh, well, you know what this is what I forgot which ties it together
Is that John Forsythe was on dynasty? So he's portrayed
Okay. Oh, I think I maybe I got to see this somebody playing John Forsythe
And Alice Cree and somebody as Heather Locklear. All right, this is going in my queue
To report back because like I feel like I'm gonna have a high level of expectation for who's playing Forsythe
Oh, yeah, I'm like, no you need to get that rhythm right Bartholomew. John
You had a big pop hit in Australia
Bartholomew Johns hit someone from from Australia. It's very funny
I was trying to figure out the connection because when you played the John Forsythe clip earlier
I searched him and one of the second or third suggestions was John Forsythe Joan Collins. Okay. Oh, okay
Yeah, yes. Yeah
Force that got around. Yeah. No, he was and I don't I feel like it's one of those things where like I have a question
About him, but I don't want to know I want him to live as a legend in my mind
I'm like, yeah, I feel like it was like he seems like a Shakespeare guy
But I like thinking of him as a guy who was like never really touched Shakespeare, but he just acted
He carried himself with the gravitas
Yeah, I mainly did introductions for rides and stuff
Mm-hmm. Let me can I back up and play something from let me go back to the magic of the movies nice
Uh a little bit more where he introduces it and then you get a little of this Phantom of the Opera thing, too
Oh, yeah, this is it's not gonna play to the listener super well
But we'll talk about what what happens here of the best-known classics of all time
the secrets of metamorphosis from human to horror are
Excitingly revealed
So this the lamp is is tearing up
You should learn secrets of makeup and effects, which I have chosen to allow
These secrets of the craft are for you and for no others should you choose to ignore this warning
I
Have you now you will learn the history of
Of our Rick Baker's secrets were passed on from he who hath done the makeup for the godfather
Do this at once or you will be mine forever
I'm in love with the no more no less
He's you will not learn how to be a best boy or a grip unless you will only learn makeup
Yes, like if we were if we are somehow given a subpar show, he will descend upon the hosts as well
Yeah, give me a lesser show to be on them for me. I'm just sitting there
I'm trying to learn like you told me Phantom
But also you I think what you couldn't really hear is that the Phantom is revealed by bursting through
Like a poster, yeah, and there's I've saw footage of that
Right in front of it. Yeah. Yeah
But a much darker scarier iteration of that which would have it does scare like I
This is it's a pretty big character a pretty big creepy face
And then I'm also logistically like why they had to print a new one of those posters for every single show
They probably did this like I don't know at least seven times a day the printing costs alone of this production
I don't know. I don't know if I remember him jumping through that thing
I think maybe like he could be one of those like it could be like a Disney thing where they're like
All right
We're really gonna wail on this for the first three months and then it's gonna seriously Peter. Oh, yeah
Well, it's also unclear to me I don't know exactly when it became
Because he John Forsythe said the other name
There was this Phantom of the Opera pre-show that didn't really
Seemingly affect the main show and then at some point it was renamed the great big clunky title
The gory gruesome and grotesque horror makeup. Yeah, I was so when you were with it for safe clip was playing
I was like wait
He's using the language that it eventually gets changed to if you just riffed to that they named it
The universal parks
Copywriters room like had two warring time and there was just a team of gory gruesome grotesque and there was a team of no
We got a brand manage this Phantom of the Opera
All those 90s 80s kids love Phantom of the Opera
Weber musicals out
You know and they're don't they'll get fooled into it and then I think they were they kind of split the diff and like snuck though
The terminology might have been phantom after the rename
But yeah, the pre-show doesn't really
Other than you just have to like sit in there and wait like you're trying to have fun with your Hawaiian shirt guy
But you're like, oh is the Phantom gonna give me if he sees me yawn?
Am I getting yanked out of the ceiling? Do I have to go live in the rafters with him now?
That's so funny that almost it's so funny that a lot of the opening day attractions a universal have this like
We have to make it fun and theatrical that being said it's about making things
Right, we have to figure out both ways and they was a constant adjustment until it's all just been gone as far as showing
You how to make anything. Well, they were also like you did the early making of universal stuff
There's so much of like alright, we can't be Disney. We got to go against it. We're gonna be a little edgier
We're gonna be a little
bawdier
Just to clarify and I
Only because I saw this on that universal profile this attraction apparently opened
Two weeks after the grand opening so opening month
Take it away from them opening day
Cutting the chandelier is falling
What the hell was anyone doing opening day because jaws
Didn't work the job wasn't there yet. The King Kong is breaking. There's a murder of crows menacing everyone
We're my was my gang at murder. She wrote mystery theater. Just holding it down preventing a riot from happening
Yeah, they're like, all right, keep it up, you know stretch it out, you know, just this is on our show
Let's do the best damn Foley effects demonstration anybody ever go along the ADR section
We really got a take another, you know socket wrench to King Kong
we got the shot of everyone walking down the main entryway and
Yeah, murder. She wrote and Hannah Barbera holding down the fort. Yeah, Fred Flintstone arm-in-arm with Robert Yurick. Yeah
Shots we need were they giving out refunds these the first few weeks months to imagine I wonder
I don't know. I've never seen any like language that suggests that but you would think people would have been furious
I feel like I I feel like in lieu of a refund. I would have preferred to just watch
Spielberg get visibly more distressed in the park. I don't know if he was visible to the park gas
I don't know why that was happening. But yeah, I feel like if he if he was in a sort of a
So if he was just pilloried in the middle of like Mel's dying in
Just being like my my rivalry with Eisner. I can't
Without a hitch
it takes a few decades to get from like
Chaos of opening day to like huh that Mel's die inside for hard nights. It's pretty clever
What if we put it on magnets and t-shirts? Okay, and that's what's happening this year. Yeah
33 it took the hard nights 33 before they're like maybe we should sell merch of that Mel's dying it die inside everyone likes
It's great. Yeah, it's great. I it's I don't know. They're they're like, you know
We always make fun of a Disney being like fucking 10 years
Ten ten years and ten steps behind everything being like slow adopters and you know Universal's faster
But they're like five years and five steps behind. Yes, so yeah nowhere close to you know, they're they're better and they're better
Yeah, is it possible that the experience of opening day?
Universal made it more pressing for Spielberg to make a movie about an amusement park where everything's breaking
Existed already, but he's like something about the book story is speaking to me, right?
Yeah, yeah, I think that you might be on to something because he might have been sweating to the same degree as Samuel L. Jackson
Yeah, Richard Attenborough when he does the like damn like he was not getting the line
Right and Spielberg was like no do it the way I did it
Everything broke it all happened. Yeah
I'm giving you a line reading. I don't care that you're one of the most well-established
I'm just telling you you might hear my avatar. I don't know what this is like
It's possible that opening day he cut the ribbon
They ushered him on ET or maybe they did ET the day before maybe cut the ribbon
Went to the VIP lounge for diet coke and then left. Yeah, maybe he didn't know about the chaos
And they and Spielberg they stopped him right before the green planet and they let him get off because he was too scared
He was just going to the green planet
Intimacy of hearing ET say his name, right? It's too personal right he is scared of teakley
Yes
No
Friends to how he got off at the top of the Jurassic Park that yeah
It was like I knew he got off at some yeah
No, we're nice and deep within many levels of reference
Buried in references. Yeah. Yeah. He also would not go in the edit bay for the BFG. He was terrified
I
G
He's frankly to be in 2g
This I did not go to Universal Orlando when I was young we were at Disney family until in my late teens
Unfortunately, I have never seen the Orlando show in person
But you guys by the way you and not so tangent here, but you and Jason have more we were a blank family
Yes, and I've ever heard I don't think my family had any declarations about what kind of that's the way to be
This is giving me because like my family went to both
but I don't think we ever had like it I feel like when you say stuff like that it gives me the impression that like
Universal was suggested and then like your father angrily was like no
Now look at me look at your mother you see your eyes in her do you see your face in me?
Know that we are I am a Disney man, and you will be a Disney man like me
Well, these are very big. It's very funny when it boils when it's a family. It's like we don't go to I hop
We're Denny's family. You know I feel like you'll bust out of nowhere. You'll go like we were all lemons family
I was taking a walk mother
I was taking a walk, and I bet there's some neighbors had lime sitting out in a basket
Your mom just crushes it in her hand throws it back in your face
Lime sting I occasionally I never remember. It's funny you say that I never remember having lines in the house
But you know we always had in the house the plastic
Lemon filled with lemon juice. Oh yeah sure
Fortified and just laughs forever mm-hmm that was legit
Yeah, that was the most seasoning or plate that was like that was
lemon juice my ice water
I've never been again. I've never been young let me
Hey, here's a tip for a natural spring in your step lemon juice and ice water. This is a clip of you at 11 years old
Like I came here because I heard you had video games. Yeah, I go
Lemonade stand and you're like sorry you're misunderstood it is lemon juice in ice water
It's none of this
What are you getting lemonade mixes so expensive these days the country times on the top shelf that's for the fancy
That's not for the riff-raff here on the street just to squeeze that's all the flavor you need
I know if it's bedtime it can just have some orange seltzer from path mark. You know
Is path mark a local
Pathmark I think got absorbed by one of the company shop right is still around that grocery store
Do you want to shop right in Illinois would have been Dominic's probably that sort of thing or like a dual osco?
Yeah, I don't know where they is I wonder if they were as big as Dominic's was as far as grocery stores in the Midwest
But maybe maybe that is the same
There was a place called far more in the Midwest for a while where I would rent video games and we would get
prescriptions filled
So there were multiple things you could do at a far more
Aid like you go there and you'd get your little square ice cream and you could rent DuckTales on Nintendo
They often would have it that was in
The way wins had a big video store
Never seen that before interesting grocery store with rentals. I don't think I ever even
Considered going to Universal when I was a child. I don't think we don't go there
So I was never a thing I asked to do
So I it's weird to even think about cuz I like the way like your religion is handed out to you
Yeah, right. Well, I guess I'm dizzy
I'm a Disney and right and then I think spider-man opened at Islands of Adventure
Oh and that drew you and I said well if we're going there we should go to spider-man, right?
It was like, oh, okay. Yeah, so we can go to we can go to Universal then so that was not but there was no protest
It just needed to be vocalized. I think yeah
No, there wasn't so it's it's interesting to think about in hindsight
And I've said this many times before when I would see stuff about Disneyland when I was a kid. I'd say oh, well
That's interesting. I'll never go there. I only go to our land. We go to Orlando
Why would I ever go to Disneyland in California? It's too far. Yeah, so I yeah
But that being said this would have scared the shit out of me. I was so scared by me
I mean, I liked Star Trek the next generation and makeup and weird stuff
But it was so I was so scared of all of it says genuine. This says like this says jump scares. Yeah
When you meet the Hawaiian shirt guy he comes out just brandishing a gun
Yeah, at least in task versions of it like where's my I don't remember the name
But he cut it like all right, and here's this guy bang bang bang charging at the audience. Yeah
Yeah, nowadays it comes out with a knife in his chest like a bloody knife. Oh, okay
I remember seeing like pamphlets or ads or something where like this show before I had seen it where it was like
Someone getting there like arm cut it like oh your arms getting cut open
I just was like so like I just thought it was real
It's dead too old to be thinking it was real, but I was like, oh they cut somebody open
I don't know about that
But like and this is one of those things where I feel like it like and like you mentioned with the spider-man
Bringing you into universal. It's sort of like that moment in the in like the the rock star biopic where they're like
What's the strange white powder? Oh, it's interesting. What's you know, it's like all the ominous like oh, it starts. Yes
That's what brought me into horror. I still don't like they they still do that
Put your knife in the arm Trek and I know it's fake
I know it slides up and it fits and it's dull and everything but that rocking back and forth with the fake
I hate it the magic of the movie
It creates me out
Eddie comes alive for the fly
Transformation in the previous iteration so much of pro wrestling watching it over the last few decades has gotten me prepared for
Starting to watch horror movies in the last six seven years
Yeah, just because of the amount of blood sometimes you'll see
Last year there was a match where one wrestler drank another wrestlers blood for real in the ring and it's really gross
But there was part of me going that's awesome
Some level like I have it's a full transformation for me from like
Yeah, so like oh, okay. Yeah gross gross me out something
Yeah for you you'd say no to us a lemon squeezed in ice water say a glass of blood
Speaking of nasty little freaks this picture of Lon Cheney with his makeup kit is like a universal go-to
In footage. Yeah, I mean devious in it
Yeah, anybody like I get like he rocks
But like there's like anybody who was like that into a thing before it was a big thing is just a little freak
Like you're like, oh, you're just this little freak and it was like you pioneered it
But it was like it's just cuz he liked doing it
He like, you know, it was just this this whole thing and I and I love I love I love little freaks
Being a little freak about my own stuff and I support everyone's little freedom
I love this story is the anecdotes again
They get recycled so much in like making of rides or specials about how many like
Four hours in the makeup chair to become a Frankenstein eight hours become the moment like I love that stuff
I love a good like when it was like Rebecca Romaine during Mystique where it was just like yes, she
Hated it
Like 12, it was some insane amount of like it was like it was like all day in the chair and then like we'll shoot for
An hour of right like ha ha to Wolverine and then then we're done it
See you tomorrow and she like doesn't say much in those movies
No, so it's like it's just a full-body makeup job
Yeah, and then I mean she's prominently just shown in the movie
Like what am I doing here? Well, but it like it's her not speaking in those things like ended up working because it like created
Like this sort of nice or a mystique if you will sure
that
Made it all the weirder with that when Jennifer Lawrence was doing it and she has like whole soliloquies wearing the same makeup
You're just like just talking too much. This is too much person. This is too much emoting for yeah for this level of
All-body bluetude and also not how mystique looks in the comics
Her legs are out but it's like yeah, like a loincloth long loincloth covering like a sort of a Greek goddess sort of white
Yeah, wrap skull belt buckle the skull belt buckle. Yeah
Have as much makeup if they just replicated that yeah
The I like those stories of makeup like Jim Carrey Grinch where he had to have like some sort of CIA
torture specialist that could train they trained him how to
Deal with getting all this stuff put on his face
Like I would need but I've done a little of I had to do this thing for Conan where they put
Two and a half hours of makeup on me and it gets you get weird you can get really like claustrophobic and it's an interesting
Thing it's on you it's on your body. Yeah sticky. It's like it's like merging with you
Yes, and you can't take take it. Can I take it off for an hour real quick? Like no you can't like no
I think that was one of the things going back to American World from Lyndon, which gets featured in this is
I think what they did for that actor was they started with the full makeup and then they just backtracked it
So like every day after that was a little less so they do like we're gonna start with the worst
And then after that we're gonna like, you know, cuz it's you know progressing so then they like kind of did a little less
So I think they started with the full, you know applique and then they just sort of like started cutting it away
Like trimming it down. So it was like, okay if you're having a panic about it, like it's gonna be a little less each day
that's the worst part has got to be the
you know, cuz there's something like it's like you're saying Jason there's something neat about like four hours to become but then like
Less glamorous how long it takes to get all this shit off
so then like and at least when you're getting the makeup on then like you're watching it build and you're watching craftsmen do their
Thing and then you get to come out on the set and everybody's like wow
Look at you and you go roar and then you get to act for a little bit
But then if it takes three hours to take it off and your reward is just like alright, go to bed now
Come back at 530. Yeah, and you're I think that's the part that isn't said enough
Just rip you could hurt yourself you just start ripping it out
Yeah, and sometimes you're dealing with mechanisms that have to you know, stay in good shape for the rest of it
Yeah, really expensive stuff that they've like processed and they and I think they did something like that. Yeah
Yeah, I wonder if you could nap during that if you're like Jack Nicholson
I think nap during Joker makeup from according to Michael Keaton. Yeah, he was fault, right?
I feel like he was calling the shots though
I wonder if like he was so one because the story was that he wouldn't work if there was a Laker game the night
Before that's right. Yeah, like there was stuff built in his contract. So he could he called the shots of how things would work
That's funny. I know there I guess you know
I know he had like the map like the crazy meh, but it's what I flashed to was just the version where he just
I'm taking a goddamn nap. All right, 20 minutes in the chair. I'm bored to tears
some of the
Those big outfits or makeup like you can't even take a drink like they have to give you a straw for water
or
soda or like sometimes it's like I
Add a smoothie for lunch because I can't take this thing off. Well, you know Star Trek
actors also I think about cuz
You know whether it's war for its quark or its neelix from Voyager you get on you're like
I got cast on a Star Trek show. This is gonna run for years
Also, I have to get there four hours early every day for seven years
Yeah, and have this makeup on me and like if I ever want to come back
I have to get the makeup so like it's like a weird like blessing curse. Yeah
We're yeah, I'm sure they I think as they go they like figure out ways to cut down on time
But still it's so many hours
it's just funny how like counterintuitive it is because you brought up Nicholson's Joker and I just like how far we've gone from like
All right, I'm gonna nap in this makeup and I'm gonna you're gonna work around my Laker schedule to like anyone doing the Joker now
It's just like we had a psychiatrist on set because I went too close to the edge
Institutionalized my you know, I didn't speak to my wife for three years
Male pig fetuses to people it is real like have you tried acting dusty?
Yes
And it's just like you'd think
It would make more sense if it's like listen, he went to the edge
He was in that chair for eight hours sure
But now it's like there's less makeup but more madness behind the scenes
Yeah, now the joker maybe just gets a little smear, but then you turn you turn your brain into a smear
Yeah
I think probably like that
I think maybe it is just because like once you've spent that many hours in the chair and you're getting like all that stuff put
You start to just get really real and you're like, this is all right
Let's just shoot this and I'm not gonna pretend to be like I'm actually the man
Who was it in in the robber patents in Batman?
There's the like is it a deleted scene or a bear is a very key
So he might be did I say you wanted you I used to I thought I said Keegan I know it's a key
I think it's no, it's a yeah. I don't know. I'm sorry. It's it's mr. Barry. Okay, mr. Barry
Okay
Yeah, yeah, but he's very clean he's like his
Filmography is like really grown. So it's like he could very well be queuing up for like an intense Joker performance
Everyone will play the Joker in the next there will be more jokers in our lifetime than we even imagine now someone in this room
We'll play the joke someone in this room will play Joker. Not who we think five years
I
It's like it's one of those thing I feel like if it's this point if you were cast as the Joker and
You do like like if I was gonna play the Joker, I'd feel a lot of pressure to be like, yeah
I I don't know. I you know, I you know, I you know and just sort of act mad
but like, you know, and because I'm like, that's what everyone's expecting they're gonna if I if I say anything less than like I
Was I was someone called, you know, someone did a 5150 on me or something like that
Like I liked it like anything less than that people be like, oh, it's not as intense of a yeah performance. It's just a silly
Nicholson esque, right? Well, I think in the wake of the ledger Joker
Everyone's felt the need to go a certain rain road with it and I have yet to see somebody take
But yeah, that's about being the joke
But he was like he was not acting that way on
Just like skateboarding on set like it was just like that's what people away but from other reasons
It's not like war was like, yeah that tortured him or something. But then people are like, I don't know
He's yes skateboarding on set and like he's maybe not as it in one video
You realize he was really all he really had to do was transform into Tom Waits
Well, yes the Tom Waits voice comparison that crazy. Yeah. Yeah, I've seen it. No, I love it
I'm like it's it. I'm just like yeah, that's what people should just just be like
Yeah, some some weird old dick cabin interview if somebody don't people don't remember and just like do that bit
I really don't know. I heard I've certainly familiar with his music, but I didn't know how much Tom Waits licked his lips
Maybe in the way that like filmmaking is some people are trying to swing it back to
Shooting on film and more practical makeup
Maybe we need the next Joker to be like I just showed up and I was this silly goose
Yeah, you know, I just drove Batman nuts like yeah, it was fun. I'm not gonna shave my mustache paint over it
Yeah, all right. Well, I think Jason's auditioning
We were recording the other day and I was just starting to like, you know, feel it like a silly
I was just being a little silly
For instance the other day I was feeling like a silly little I was a so could I not be the Joker?
I was like
Wrapping up. I'm just feeling like silly goose
This this Joker takes the podcast conversations in chaotic direction
And to fight the chaos, let me say let's talk about some more things in this show
Yeah, hey look you get your yeah, you get your your like cleaver in the arm
Yes
the hole for the
It's it's you know what a lot of blood in this for a year-round show that kids are at and there's moments where they
Have to say hey, maybe kids close your eyes
They used to do a thing and this must have gone, you know due to sensitivity to gun violence
But that I didn't know that in the early iteration that they would bring out just a head
On a table that could talk and they would shoot the head and in front of like a really clean white
Backdrop right just to show you how squibs work. It was a different time 2007
Now they make it a thing where the head can still talk they don't they don't perfectly right reenact William H
Macy and boogie nights
Listen it's chunky is we can do a like yeah
I let's expand this out of the horror genre and do like make up these squib effects for you know that sort of those
Here's how we did the elevator sequence and drive
just explode
They do also I think it's one of the early ones it must be I can't imagine that today
They would be cutting a woman's arm and then say she's a bleeder
Well, we watched the one of the 91 ones and they brought a woman on stage and they went take off your clothes and
She was just like Jesus Christ
Yeah, they were just
Figuring it out back then I guess it was sort of an early iteration of like the
Bill and Ted like where they're just like, yeah, we're gonna get a little
We're gonna get you know, calm down mother I think you just said your Joker's catchphrase
Well, I don't want anyone to feel uncomfortable but the Joker doesn't care about that because he's a little naughty naughty
Discomforting you
Is your does your Joker dress up in a little sailor suit as well
He got well, I think he would have a lot of outfits. Okay. Good. Yeah much like Duffy
Yeah, he's kind of like a twisted Duffy
Duffy the Disney bear. Yeah, I think your Joker should do a lot of like
sort of
25 year dated sort of like like we're sort of like all those are kind of pushing the line
They're a little iffy sort of theme park jokes. Oh, you're just like, oh, I'm sitting here. I'm a little uncomfortable with this
It's a little gawdier than Deadpool's story time where he tells jokes that
elicit probably the reaction from the crowd of like Deadpool
Come on Deadpool. No
That's why you just you say like I think you would say hey, all right lay lady take off your clothes. Naughty Naughty
Naughty Naughty undercuts it. Yeah
We're all invited in on the joke
Right, yeah, just just remember at my core. I'm just a silly goose
Sorry apologies, I didn't mean it at the end of the day look look at me think silly goose
You're in a net upside down of said City Hall Batman's like, oh, we got you now. You're like, I'm just a silly goose
Yeah, I'm just a little guy. You gotta let me go
Yeah, we can get James Gunn to listen to this
I think maybe for his bad because there's gonna be two versions of Batman in case everybody didn't know
There will be a Matt Reeves Batman and a different James Gunn produced Batman
He's producing both of them secondly, but maybe Joker for that more
gunified Batman some it recently sometimes you've been telling me stuff that I know
Is accurate but I'm like, are you making a joke because I'm like, oh, I hadn't heard the James
Gunn bad the James Gunn
DC you whatever that it's called now
DC you well the DC you was the whatever was before old one whatever the James Gunn a verse of DC
When he did that video like here's what to expect. It was very if you've seen it the mr
Show pre-taped call-in show. Oh, it was just a lot of no, this isn't Batman
There's we'll have a Batman but the Batman is gonna be that's part of DC
World right and then that's a joker, but it's they will have a joker
But it's not joker and it's and there was a whole lot of explaining
There's a lot of like listen, we don't care doesn't sing only that joker sings. That's prestige joker
That's joker. Right and so there was a lot of caveats of like listen, we're building something but
We are not putting all of our chips on this. We still need these
Moneymakers to continue right right. So anyway, he'll listen hopefully as much explanation as Jason
What you're a you know current ones how this shows different, you know, what's a I remember this area
I feel like I don't know if I did jokes like this is a tour guide
but like I know that like there seems to be a top a topical slot that where you refer to somebody as a
Monster and then you say a currently famous person
Hmm, and I think this is a tougher area these days because we're not gonna do the thing where we bring up somebody who's having trouble
Yeah, we call them a monster so it leads to a pretty inexplicable version of this in one that I saw from this year
Which is like they make all of the you know, here's all the universals great monsters Frankenstein Dracula
Taylor Swift and Travis Kelsey
And I think the audience is confused because like they're pretty well regarded, right? Yeah, they're
In the media a lot, but I don't feel like annoying and overexposed. It's a weird
I don't think anybody knows what to do. Right? Yeah, it's not like Paris Hilton in 2006. Yeah
Went for 2019 and I believe they showed bride of Frankenstein. They were like Lady Gaga and then Frankenstein Bradley Cooper
Bradley the star is born
Was pretty recent and then of course there was some Kardashian jokes and the more Reese, you know, because they don't want to get into like
You know or they could just go broad. They could just be like the monster
That presidential camp, you know candidate you don't like
That's as close as you could sit you certainly can't you can't use gender specifics you get that gives you clues that that
That actor or director or producer that we don't hire anymore, right?
You know the one I'm talking about
He was in the absent of Deadpool 3 but he's in one and two
You call in threats to amtrak you don't get in movies anymore
It's the monster the the the the person who's on the it ends with us press tour. You don't like
Whichever one you don't like
Did he write during the strike I think he wrote it before the strike
Yeah, that is I want yeah cuz that was such an easy cut and dry thing 15 years ago
Whichever like young lady was struggling
Yeah, right at her. Yep, and it would get a big reaction, but that doesn't yeah
We were a little more like oh, yeah, maybe not anymore
the show did come back like after the park opened in 2020 and
You know, obviously they were wearing face shields and masks and stuff
But I think the thing that is pretty funny is all the heads of the monsters having surgical masks on
Oh, that is cute. That is cute. Great. Yeah
it's
That I wonder I was gonna say you said it's what it was, Florida in 2020
So I don't know that everybody was wearing a mask
If I was performing in that show I'd be like, well, hey someone in this room's got a mask
I think the theme parks had mandates longer than
Yeah, that makes sense
They were playing a game of chicken. Yeah for sure where it was just like yes
We're thinking yes that they were they were doing that for a while and then it was just very clear that it just was like
Oh, we're gonna lose people. It's just fine. It's fine. Yeah, just put the let's put the you know, the the sanitizer stations
Looks nice
but yeah, you know like it's it's a it's a actual demonstration of
makeup to show and you get a lot of like
Clip reels that pay tribute to Universal's legacy and show actually
Genuinely upsetting and scary stuff which leaves a mark when you're a kid and that spirit that all has kind of remained the same
But like the set pieces have changed in and out and it used to be it used to build up to this fly thing
but now it builds up to the sequence where there is a
big werewolf that is
supposed to be a
mocap controlled
But after a while it's revealed that that's a person in a suit once they break free and then they do a big genuine
Scare of the audience we've talked about this before because they had this same they brought the same thing to the special effects
Stages, which we talked about with Carl Tart forever go
So we're we're back to Eddie unless there's a different name. I don't recall
Though you're controlling the werewolf gag
Scared the shit out of me when I first saw it in the 2000s
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and apparently it scared somebody so badly in 2002. She fell off the stage
I was just gonna bet you that the incident the incident. Yes, and it no longer does something
So she fell off the stage and broke her leg
And obviously they probably paid her out the ass
But the big change in the show is the audience volunteer gets back to their seat
And then Eddie comes to life
Got it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, you don't something doesn't charge at you while you're on an elevated
Do some like
Yeah, then yeah, it did seem to be yeah
Like a plug it was a it was a it was a definitely like a like a Kelsey Grammer type fall
Where it was like really like it was a it was like, oh stop the show. Oh, yes. Yes. Yeah
Right I
I looked up this show because because I feel like this show practically
It's also a good place to cool down 25 minutes in the dark in the air conditioning
This is brought up a lot online
it's also a good place to hide out from the rain in either the
Entrance lobby or the exterior the show
But I
I also was a thing. I like to look up for these off the more off the beaten path
Attractions is what is the old merch being sold on eBay and I only found two things
I found this kind of ugly postcard
With like a man and a very very good show time
Go story ghoul
And then this limited edition pin of the marquee
Except the marquee says universal instead of Pantages
Which drives me nuts. I don't do we say that this is you go inside a replica of the Pantages theater
No for this show, which is a good replica
I went online and looked and the Pantages I didn't realize it was such a
Complicated design because usually has so many banners on it. Now. Is it does it still say Pantages?
I know in the foresight video it said Pantages, but like is this is this like something that they had to lose at some point?
Maybe yeah, I think in reality. Oh just for merch over selling it and got it
The picture in the app still says Pantages great
Okay, so what's the one look at the description in the app too?
The current description
Okay, take a close. Look at what goes into and oozes out of some of Hollywood's strangest creatures
Hmm oozes out of yeah, not exactly a good description
Yeah, it doesn't like puss
15 minutes of puss play
Yeah, but I'll tell you one thing you you're you're given for side to run for his money for for the for the descriptor there
You know, I you could do some voiceover stuff. Oh, yeah, they do it
I thought let's do a new magic of the movies hosted and let's get you, you know hosted by Jason Sherman by the Joker by
Jason Joker
Brothers they universal they have relationship with the the Harry Potter. That's right
They always say is the universal gonna buy Warner Brothers or another studio or they always do say that
They always be saying that listen. I let's let's let's keep mashing these
Companies together until we're left with
We all definitely have jobs for one cool company it'll be great for everyone's jobs
Wow get my picture under the smile
Nice to see you know that that that Florida gets a Pantages is nice that we don't have to hog
The Pantages a place that we all are at all the time
Nary a weekend that I'm not hanging out at the Pantages theater. Yeah a great area just yeah
A lot of like yes, I'm in, Los Angeles
Yeah, yeah programs a lot of their shows at the former Kodak theater where the Oscars are
I would every saw Margaritaville. I know exactly where to park if you told me to go there right now
I would know exactly where to leave my car. No time wasted and no getting tricked into 30 unnecessary dollars
I remember this also here's a role like universal detail that I that there was the little they had little stands
That you could put your camera on and then there'd be a matte painting a mini matte painting
on top like that you could practically use with your camera and in this case because it's just kind of like the bottom part of
The Pantay, but they with the magic of matte paintings. You could put your camera there and then make it look like there's a giant grand
Marquis and back truck they did that on that you could take a picture of the back of the future ride and it looked like there was a
Space shuttle rocket. Oh, right right on top. Yeah, these were I love these they didn't work very well
You would get them back and like yeah with my bad like disposable film camera and not work at all
But I sure liked learning about how matte paintings worked
Oh, it was a thrill to put your disposable camera on that thing. Yeah, and it would not
Cut off all the crap around it, but it was cool. It was fun. Yes
Did you do you guys have have the photos still somewhere?
So I remember having a disposable roll where I took a lot of pictures of the Triceratops encounter
At islands of adventure and so if you want to see some very some dark dark
Photos that you could maybe a forensics expert could make out there is a fake baby Triceratops
Yeah, I could post though. Those will be that all the likes will be flying when we get those on the socials
Something about like this show that I really really appreciate and I love that it's still around is that I think you know
I love horror and
Universal has just never really lost track of like that's where their bread and butter is that it's just like even through every
Up and down that they have had as a studio
film studio and as a park
That they are leaning into that and they go and we're gonna start to get that again soon with the epic universe
Where they're finally doing something horror related. So like this was sort of this was their horror event even before they did
Horror nights, you know, they did horror nights. They're gonna do this Vegas horror thing
And then the epic universe thing
So I just I'm happy to see them continually reinvest in this and you're getting a lot of it's a way to like keep an older
Thing around and keep it newer
Which I'm I'm always happy when either parks can do that, right?
And it's not yeah
Cuz it's not a big there's not a big hit movie franchise right now for them
Even though that's what they eventually want back there. So it's good that they're still keeping it alive like this
They're starting to do we will we will see
But they're starting to do because they're starting to do the Universal Monsters because they did invisible man with Elizabeth Moss
And then they are about to next year do wolf man again. They're doing that with Christopher Abbott and
The same director is invisible man
So like they find these sort of interesting ways to make these classic monsters sort of relevant and you know
Make it feel urgent and not like, you know, kind of we're doing this again
So and I did a little investigation on lights. We don't really know a lot yet about this new wolf man one
But there is a whole
Practical makeup effects team listed on IMDB. So it does seem like we're doing some practical stuff there
You know, I know cuz I know that was something that Rick Baker fought a lot on on the Benicio del Toro wolf man
That was 2010
Was he did a big stuff with creature design?
But then they decided to opt for digital for the transformation it and it really was this half-and-half and it really was sort
Of the beginning and the end of his retirement where he was just like I feel like everyone's moving away from what I want to do
But hopefully like he said Jason that we're moving back into that
We'll probably be the guy from the show doing the make the Hawaiian shirt guys probably working on the wolf man
Oh, yeah, yeah when there aren't audiences in there. I don't know another audience
Slow down wolf man work the name of this
The character the host character is officially named Alex Ross
Which is also a big paint comic book painter. Yeah, so that's that always confused me
Okay, like I was like, wait a minute. Is this a reference like
The
It was the the Batman and Superman one. I'm not a kingdom come
Kingdom come it was the it was like one was like the Superman peace and then one was like Batman war
Yeah, it was like 90s or something
Yeah, I don't think I think that's not related
Generic name and it Alex can be
Gender-neutral there are a lot more that profile was like yeah, this show used to be all men and there are a lot more women
Doing it in the mix, but you can see it's nice because they said like yeah, there's a lot of fans of this show
They brought us gifts
They someone made little rubber duckies of the hosts and the makeup artists and they put them on one of the shelves
In the stage and it's it's nice. So there's super fans of the characters in the show
Wow, I think so. Yeah, but not the actual performers. No, there are of the performers. Oh, okay
Really? Oh, yeah, they probably like who memorized. I like this one. I like this Alex in particular. Oh, yeah
She when she worked up at the Frog choir she would talk about there were regulars
there were super fans there were regular photographers who would send pictures and
So I'm nervous about all of these people you're describing but
Enjoy that they exist. Yeah, but there's a dinner party where we are all there maybe
Not so much or maybe I don't know
That would be very interesting look as long as they don't call me late for dinner, that's all I'm saying
Aphorisms for the 1950s getting people on board. I like the idea that potentially your Joker never does anything illegal
You're just kind of a rascal
He seems to be appealing to the silent generation
Disturbing the peace and then we're like, what can we book him for?
Alfred there's a really annoying guy out there. I gotta stop him
He says ain't I a stinker a lot
Bothers me, but I'd be sad if he wasn't around like I'd like him
Yeah, he's interesting something about it. Yeah, it's fascinating. Yeah kill him
He didn't put a banana at a tailpipe like Beverly Hills cop, but he left some bananas by the rear wheel
Yeah for someone else doing a note that just said naughty naughty, so now he's writing it down
It's a lot like a lot like the original little rascal
I
All in one all rolled into one less crimes than hygiene
he drew a
Crack on my windshield and there was no crack. I was very upset for about 20 seconds
Pencil and he just rub it off
Smudge there I can't get the smudge. Yeah
Anything else about the show before we wind it down. It's hey, I don't know. It's it's it's fun
It illuminates great the great work of the great universal makeup artists
Names are said clips are shown. I
Have not seen
What clip exactly but I'm very curious. I went back and was looking for it and didn't see it in the list of movies
Featured in the show. It does list Mulholland Drive and I'm very curious
What oh the the the like homeless person behind the the dumpster that would be my guess that is
One of the scariest moments in film. Yes, it
Scared the hell out of me when I rented that DVD from blockbuster and I turn around if I rewatch that movie
Yeah, I know I'm telling you this so that is that is actually my number one favorite movie of all time
And I saw it in theaters when it was first out
And I'm gonna be I'm gonna be a little Jason Cheridan right now and I'd be like so it was two weeks after 9-eleven and
The national mood was we don't want to go it's hard to go back to the movies
But you know, we need we were starting to get back
We had Brittany Murphy don't say a word that movie was out there and then we were slowly getting the whore
Yeah, I'll never tell you know exactly said that we got we were starting to get people back in the theater
So this was like it was like my first movie after being like I'm freaked out. I don't want to go anywhere
and I was a I was a I was a
Freshman in film school. So I was like it was like like a month after I just like left Illinois and went to California
And so I was just like out on my own and I was just like, oh, I'm nervous
I'm this Midwest kid and I don't like I'm just I'm the world is frightening and I just went and I was like
I'm gonna chill out with and I never heard of David Lynch before too
So I was just like, I don't know this movie seems to be getting some good, you know reviews and it got a you know
I got a good, you know had a good showing at Cannes and I'll go see this movie
Maybe it's about a fun drive to the canyon like I'll see a Hollywood
Rod racing through Mulholland Drive. You see a movie about you know, you know, just kind of crazy people who make the movies and
I was not prepared. I was I was in the theater alone and I
And then the guy steps out from behind the the dumpster. I had the same
Heart attack the guy in the movie does yeah
like I'm truly like I was like and I was just like and I was just like a lynch guy from from that point on like
it was a it was it was my whole thing, but
No, I would say my my thing about
About makeup that I was like while I was researching for this was
You know, this seemed to be coming at you know, during the big hate heyday of makeup effects
Because it was you know, there was there was always kind of makeup effects
But they were really like getting into this artistry level and they had I
Think there was so the best makeup Oscar was I created in 1981 for Whirlpool London and then but that really started because of an outcry
After Eraserhead didn't really get you know
Because it was supposed to be there was this it was sort of like the Dark Knight how the Dark Knight led to there being
Ten potential movies now for Best Picture
This was Eraserhead was sort of that
Of that time where there was such and like oh we need to like give this movie something and we need to like really
acknowledge the makeup effects are kind of
going where they need to go and
And then from then on they they started the the best makeup Oscar which which ran pretty pretty like oh my god
You know is pretty run by like horror and big things like the Grinch one and that sort of things
But then now last ten years, you know post
Benicio Wolf, man, there's been like a tapering it has been a lot of like oh they recreated that that famous historical person
they write, you know, you know
that sort of thing so it's I I
I really do hope my makeup effects kind of do come back and into into a big vogue that there's
little freaks out there who are experimenting with like new ways to do things and you know, you know, you know new
maybe not even horror but just like kind of just like new ways to kind of you know make a person look like you know
Something but I I I really love makeup for the innovation that it continues to bring to film because I think that's something that's still
We can't really quite digitally recreate yet. Yeah. Yeah right on. Well, yeah urging makeup artists out there
Pursue your dreams and step one get a Hawaiian shirt. Yes
No one will take you seriously in that business unless you do I guess with that I can say wait a Damien
The exorcist as you survived haunt cast the fright
Happy to do it. Absolutely. Oh great. And
Congratulations, and let's exit through the through the crypt shop. Is there anything you'd like to plug? Yes, I would so for you
No, but talk a lot about horror. I have a you know, I'm on the last episode
I talked about I have a my horror book your lonely nights are over which is a slasher which is scream meets clueless
That is that is out that is still out in stores review go
My newest book curse boys and broken hearts is a romance because I like to go back and forth between I started
I my first book was a horror then I did a romance then horror romance. So
I they all seem like they're from the same universe for me everybody is
When I write them both they they seem to be like the characters all feel like this is life and death and just in the horror
it really actually is and
So in my romances
Which a lot of folks have said are just as stressful if not more stressful than my thrillers my suspense ones
Because we have we have you know, sort of characters behaving badly naughty
but in this one curse boys and broken hearts it is set at a
Vineyard it is it's at a winery
where this young man believes that he is
he has been cursed to always lose any boyfriend he gets after a few weeks and
He goes back to his family's bed and breakfast vineyard to help them get the house back up on its feet
it's old family house that's kind of in disrepair and
When he is there he has to work with this local gardener who turns out to be
An ex of his from long ago. And so they have this oh, we got to work together, but we hate each other
Energy, so it's a very very back and forth back and forth
Silver-tongued romance and I had a lot of fun writing it
I just enjoy when characters can be sort of mean to each other in a very intimate way
I think it's a very queer experience thing, but I think it's just fun to write
It's a lot. It's very up my wheelhouse. So curse boys and broken hearts is
Available now, but before I go I have one. I have a little surprise for
So yes, so so I am so I am a Los Angelino, but I am you know
I think we can still you know, I just recently moved to the Palm Springs area
So and I have brought I have come bearing gifts for everyone here
From because I have moved. I didn't realize this at the time. I have moved next door to
Coutino
Coutino, so I live next to the burgeoning site of a story living by Disney development
I drive, you know, I drive past
Where people will eventually live their Disney story?
When I'm on my way to Planet Fitness
Whoa, I guess that could be part of their story to your planet fitness written
So I so I went in there specifically just because I knew I was coming on here and I was like well
I can't just not talk about that. I just drove in from Coutino. You can't just leave it alone
So I did walk in there and so there it's you know, it's it is real
That I did I wanted to confirm that it was real
There's a lot of holes in dirt. It's happening. I believe yes. It is like like we learned to d20 right now
There's there's no blue sky. There's there is it is shovel ready
And they have you know, depending on when this episode releases, I believe there will be
You can take a tour of model homes right now. So I would I don't know
I'm not telling you all what to do. It sounds like depending. It's they're not gonna be the haunted
They're not gonna make you they're not gonna make it a haunt where you do tour haunted
We don't know we don't know if they did a poltergeist s like clearing of headstones, but no bodies to build this land
There's like a ghost story. Yeah, so I think hey if you read Adam's book read ghost story the novel
My father was right. It is the scariest book ever written. Very scary. Yes exactly. So that that's the homework of this
So Cotino I brought in so I've driven they have a
community sales site, so I have a community site plan to share with everybody and it is
Homes you could see the Cotino Bay Cotino Bay it is all around beautiful Cotino Bay and
I feel like I would I could get into this if they had like a really retro like
70s sort of like, you know, how like 1971 Disney World was very like and you know, it was very focused on like
Usually paragliding. Yeah
Yeah, you know, you know, you know, they're like, yeah, there's a theme park
But really you're here to paraglide and have a mustard aspic dinner
Like I feel like yes, so so there's around Cotino Bay
Future development future town center, but I went to the sales studio
There's two people there who could not have been nicer and I feel really bad because they did fit
To them because I said I was I was scouting on behalf of my my boss
So I could get a little more information. They would be a little friendlier to me for these two hours
Well, I'm getting some I would like some physical info because they did not want to give me anything physical because they wanted really
Wanted me to go on the website and I was like, well my my boss is a little more tactile and I didn't want to say
I was going on a podcast to goof on them
But because they couldn't have been nicer
There's just two they were out there in the middle of the desert and like that like a true like they were like wait
I was like a waiting for Godot thing because there's no one there
I walked in and they were like they did that like thing. They were like, yes a
Customers like they just lept to like their feet and I was like, oh, I'm yes. I'm here to you know
I wore a thick mustache and everything but
I've been looking for a place to story live. Do you think you know me?
And I don't know if I'm feel like I'm living my best story
My life can kind of come and go but so there is a community site plan and I have this for everybody here
They have made
Story living by Disney bookmarks. So this is very apt for me
So because the sleeves say mark the next chapter in the story of your life
So there is all of these different bookmarks different
Some have little desert flowers cacti on there and then mark the most expensive chapter of your life
Yeah, this should be said that I did not move into a similar boondoggle in the desert
I moved into just a regular it was a it was a new home that might as well have been Cotino
It's just an eighth of the price. It's the same neighborhood
It's sure we're not your and it's got a community. It's it's we just don't call the pool Cotino Bay
I guess we don't have a man-made lake, but you know in the desert
I like calling just just a dress up where you live calling your pool of Bay
Quick tip in the Bay. Yeah, so we've got these we've got a gecko here a lizard next chapter best chapter
Got some others that your next chapter beckons and just an oh and this one is for
Asteria, which is I think a new difference not Cotino. It's a different. Oh, there's a different. There's a it's a different area
I think it's in a wooded area because this is an owl that just says discover. What's next hard to keep track of not?
Asteria because Cotino is not a stereo hard to keep track. Yeah, these different places to live stories
But now I will leave these all with you and so my god. Thank you too
Did we say that this is the a bunch of houses that Disney is owns in the desert?
I kind of said it's yes. They're out. Yeah, they're in like what it Palm Springs area, but like Rancho
Rancho Mirage. Yeah, so it's like
Everything in that area is five minutes away. I mean after after you leave
LA you're so used to just like I mean it's closer than Burbank is to
Pasadena. Yeah, right. They're all in a big area. Oh and Cathedral City and exactly exactly
There's a Disney's most exciting, you know, we can focus a little too much on the rides in the parks
But the most exciting thing Disney is doing is are all these houses. They seem to exclusively be
Advertising it in Los Angeles at upscale Caruso shopping center
Universal in this game Universal should build some houses in the
The first one to theme them actually because like I'm telling I it's the theming out there is
nice desert place
It's it's not really themed. Well, what if they built the psycho house out in desert?
I would be I would you move it up and it was comfortable inside put my house on the market
I would I would leave they have a 30 psycho houses in a row
Well, one Street is psycho house one Street is Elliott's house from ET
Back to the future you get that. Yeah, that's the town square too with the clock tower
You live your clock tower life, right? Yeah, they should I think pay tribute to the aforementioned in this episode
an
Actor who they reference a lot and a lot of their special effects discussion, you know
But the backbone is built around this guy. Why not call their housing development Voslou?
Waiting for there's a psycho house waiting for you at Voslou
You could just yeah, welcome to Voslou that would work
115 degrees
That is something I will confirm that it is it is presently
Voslou will be built in Death Valley or it's even hotter
It'll be built it will take advantage of the record-breaking hottest site ever recorded on earth
Yes, so that's you know, because Disney has Rancho Mirage covered
So yeah, this was got to go to death Valley and they're the horror company. Yeah
Yeah, Shrek's house will be built in Death Valley. Yes
You do original psycho house then you could do Vince Vaughn psycho
Alternate them very similar and Voslou Bay is Shrek's
And you know what they call the people who do landscaping and fumigating the company is called the scorpion king
Listen I'm too into this now
Okay, now we're gonna get a Cabot Cove out there. We're gonna get an amity out there
All the bad they rebuild the back lot where there's room in the desert, right?
Oh my god, and they put a real shark in there
Think of ways to get more real estate square footage for rides at Universal Hollywood what they do
Destroy the back line, right? Yeah, move it to the desert. Yeah. Yeah, I live in old Mexico recreated
I live next to the flash flood
Crucial that's how I shower. I just stand away for the flash flood every day
There's all just gets to a place of recreating the Salton Sea
A brand-new environmental disaster brought to you by Universal Pictures
This was the one because I did to make sure I wasn't repeating anything. I listened to the story living episode from 2022
I'm telling you. I'm like, that's what I really your pandemic brains. No, it was from 2022
It was an hour
So it was very I had it like listen I had an hour on the road
I had an hour on the road
So I listened to it and you did bring up that with the the word they like they just the desert said no
You're saying one of us repeated a story in this podcast
That's how we our story living we live our stories by saying them
Adam thank you for being here and from bringing us gifts from the Holy Land of Latino much appreciated
Hey as for us for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the cemetery gate or get one more
Boonest episode on our RIP tier crypt three. You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride name not scarified
Hey, happy Halloween season. We got a little bit more to go. But for now watch out for little scamps and silly gooses
naughty naughty
Forever
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Bohm Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts
Please visit forever dog podcasts calm and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us
Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook