FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following haunt cast may contain
Scrim Talk,
A Hall of Ill Presidents,
Hypothetical Robert Downey Jr. accents,
and
Pat Sajak,
The Actor?
Yep, we're still doing this.
It's Haunted Mansion 7 on today's haunt cast,
The Fright!
All right, everyone.
Cappy!
Cappy, yes.
Oh, you knew it.
Cappy Lewis!
You definitely, you were ready to go on that.
Okay, okay, all right.
Now Jason, be honest, were you ready to say Cappy?
Because it seemed like nobody was on the same page as me just then.
Well, I was ready to say my favorite track, Umbrella Man.
Wow!
You've just spun around your iPad with a photo of Umbrella Man.
You have been getting happy with Cappy all year.
It turns out you're the most listened to artist now.
Yeah, recently-
Yeah, Cappy Lewis!
Right, and recently played on my Apple Music is, well, where is he?
He's on there somewhere.
Cappy, I was listening to him on the way over.
Wow.
Yes!
Oh, in the most recent, okay, okay.
Look, I took that delay as, which was an in-person delay.
We're not doing this over Zoom.
No, yeah.
I took it as a sign that we did not remember the assignment from last year, but I'm ready
to pounce on that stuff.
I know, I understand.
I'm worried, but I guess I shouldn't be, because last year you guys fulfilled the assignment
and then some, the yearly assignment that we leave here on these Haunted Mansion episodes,
and I'm thrilled with that.
Maybe we should listen to one of these really briefly, but for now, let me officially say,
welcome to Hauntcast the Fright with three grim grinning hosts who in high school rarely
came out to socialize.
I'm the garewolf over there is-
I forgot my name already and I can't pull it up.
Jason, then, great.
Go, Jackal Scarridan.
Jackal Scarridan.
I'll find it later.
Uh-huh.
Mike Capison.
Capison, yeah.
I guess it's going to have to be for now.
Because he plays the trumpet.
Well, great.
Well, here we are.
Spiky Snarlgun.
Okay, great.
It rolls off the tongue.
I don't know how you could have gotten that.
Perfect.
Yeah, it's perfect.
It's a perfect name.
You're just so excited to talk about this graveyard jamboree and all the many ghosts.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah, and that's what we're here to do this year, and it's also, I mean, this
is more for me than for you guys.
This year is kind of a year of picking up the pieces for me, and we're still grappling
with what happened last year.
Last year, we did the Haunted Mansion live on stage at Dynasty Typewriter, and at the
end of the show, I'm just going to get ahead of it.
There was an unfortunate incident that I take 100% responsibility for.
I acted as if it was possible to finish the Haunted Mansion entirely within 30 seconds.
I conveyed this via a video, and then I danced around like a fool.
I made an ass out of you and me in doing so, and the year has just, it's been a tough one,
and it's brought me to this point where I have a lot of regrets about what happened,
about the toxic display in which I embarrassed myself.
I say myself, but I feel like it was a different me.
I've done a lot of work, and I don't think that's the same me that you're getting today.
I don't want to go so far as to say that this was a Michael Richards-esque incident, because
I didn't say anything as hateful as that, but the spirit was hateful.
I think the spirit was in just as bad of a place.
Jump in.
Don't pile on me, because I've been trying, or do.
If you need to work through things about what I did, then feel free.
Obviously, at the live show, I sat on stage and just dryly went,
It's not funny, for a while, and then everyone was laughing more because I was doing that,
and then my fury was sated by the many different types of candy they have backstage at Dynasty Typewriter.
We sat with some candy, and we talked it over, and we realized maybe that was not the venue.
Obviously, they were laughing because they associate me with comedy and with physical comedy,
even though they shouldn't, but they knew they were witnessing a grim display.
What I'm able to cop to now and admit to today more fully is that at the time,
I was grappling with an addiction to speed.
Not the drug speed, I mean with speeding through topics,
which is an energy I feel like I've brought to the show even in non-Halloween episodes.
That's true, yeah.
That unfortunate spirit of trying to move things along
and make sure that they aren't too dry or cumbersome or whatever, but that's not me now.
This is a new me. This is a changed me, as you guys know.
You've seen it probably less in the episodes and more, hopefully, in my personal life,
and we've talked through these things.
Yeah, and I appreciate the work you've done.
Thank you, thank you. Personal work, a lot of personal work.
I canceled myself, and now I'm back to hopefully un-cancel myself,
but that's up to the audience, ultimately,
because if I could paraphrase the film Ferris Bueller,
what I've realized is the haunted mansion moves pretty fast,
and if you don't stop and look around once in a while, you might miss it.
We're not going to be in here forever. We're not going to be in the graveyard forever.
We're not going to be in the ride forever, so what am I doing trying to rush through?
We're going to look back on these times as the greatest times in our lives.
We're going to look back on a haunted mansion series that was mostly done in our 30s,
but by next year, all of us will be 40.
That's true.
Not just one of us, and it's also not the new me to call out the one of us who is 40 currently.
Thank you, yeah. I appreciate that, too.
Jason, you should say thank you, too, so that nobody's sure which one it is.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for doing that, for obscuring what the actual truth is.
I think that should throw everybody off the trail.
Wow.
But anyway, what I'm excited about is that this is going to be the first,
after a lot of haunted mansion episodes, this is going to be the first one with a reflective Scott,
a subdued Scott, a serene Scott.
Any of the adjectives that were applied to Trump by New York Times editorials after the shooting,
you could apply all of those to me.
I am changed Scott, and as such, here's what I want to do.
We are taking our time. There is no rush.
And in fact, any role that I've ever taken on of being the person setting the pace in these episodes,
my hands are off the steering wheel.
This is entirely on you two guys at this point.
I do want to make sure this is not an act and there's not a minotaur about to burst into this room.
It's changed Scott, yes.
Old Scott consorted with nefarious minotaur types.
But that was last Halloween and then again in January or so.
But that's a long time ago.
As with Donald Trump, who was a completely changed man within two days, which stuck.
As you're hearing this, we're so much deeper into an election site.
We spent so many weeks cozying up to the changed, subdued, non-polarizing Trump.
And it's the same thing.
Even if the minotaur had happened two days ago, that's a different man.
So relax everybody. That's what this is going to be about, is relaxing.
It's up to you. We don't need to leave the graveyard.
My hands are nowhere near the steering wheel.
I'm in the second back seat.
I couldn't reach it even if I had a gripping pole.
Let's let Jason steer the ship today, I think.
That's my preference.
I feel like you've always been a little bit of a moderate in this effort.
You've found common ground with both of us.
Jason has been the primary one saying, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
And actually, I think if anything, today I'm going to be the one saying, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
Asking for more details, making sure that we really enjoy this time together.
Because we're not going to have it forever.
Wow. That's very profound.
I'm taking a lot of work to get there.
You know what? You know what I'll say is this is perfect because I want to talk about a couple things that aren't where we left off.
They are back. They're going back.
Because I just went on the Haunted Mansion.
It is Haunted Mansion Holiday, of course.
We don't even have a plan for how to do it or when to do it.
We don't know how this factors into this yearly series.
Right. So Haunted Mansion Holiday just went on a couple days ago.
And I want to praise the original mansion.
We're not haters of Haunted Mansion Holiday.
We're like a general Disney fan who wishes it was just a little shorter of a window for Haunted Mansion Holiday.
Even this time around, it's been that since July.
Something like that.
Strange. I love the Halloween season I want to spread, but it feels weird, does it not?
Yes. And this occurred to me as I was going through Pirates, funny enough.
That section where they took away the mist and the hologram.
I was going through there and that is maybe my new favorite part of Pirates is that dark tunnel.
Because it's mood. It's like serene but scary.
And as soon as I started Haunted Mansion Holiday and it's like,
that Jack was here and then blah, blah, blah.
I was like, the mood is gone.
The complete first part of the Haunted Mansion with the mood and the still and the somewhat,
there's the ghost hosts but there's silence.
And you really kind of melt into the scariness of it.
That's gone.
And I really appreciated the regular Haunted Mansion for it setting a mood,
which is missing in our modern film, our modern TV, a lot of rides.
They want to pummel you with things, dialogue.
This is what change Scott has been saying. Everything is so fast paced.
Why are we doing it? What are we gunning for the destination and not enjoying the journey?
Exactly.
It's funny you say this because it's a thing I've been thinking about lately,
going through the big book, going through the Jason Searle coffee table book
and seeing clips of Haunted Mansion Holiday.
As we must do, old Scott would have said,
why are we slavish to reading this one book and repeating what we see in it
page by page every year?
Why do we just copy the work of Jason Searle and put it in a different form?
But change Scott would never say that.
That's not fair. We also look at do muggies a lot.
And Wikipedia. No insult to Wikipedia.
And Wikipedia. I haven't gotten to the Fox Nolte book, but once again I've been told it's very good.
The Haunted Mansion, stuff that came after the movie,
the Haunted Mansion, the popular consciousness and derivatives of the movie.
The movie is a lot more grotesque, I feel like.
Which movie are you talking about?
Nightmare Before Christmas.
Oh, not a Haunted Mansion movie. I see.
The actual stop motion one is a lot more eerie.
Yeah, for sure.
I feel like then the kind of whimsy of the, you know, Haunted Mansion holiday.
There's whimsy, but it's a little bit more messed up.
It's a little bit more off kilter. Yes, that's true.
It's almost like they took the energy of the delivering presence sequence and made it entirely that.
There's not the, yes, the more foreboding. Yeah, that's a little of a slower movie, actually.
There's not a lot of the insane doctor scientist character in the ride.
In fact, I don't think there's any of him in the ride.
I also wish when they built it, I don't know if this is a Bob Gurr thing,
they should have built it so that the ride could only go a certain speed.
Because they moved that thing so fast, and they still were doing that up until a couple years ago at regular mansion.
That thing is motoring through the Haunted Mansion.
Those doom buggies should be going slow, slow, slow.
And they should have prevented it from happening in the early days, is what I'm saying.
It should barely be a ride. What is the slowest it could possibly move and still technically be a ride?
Yes, so I was like, ah, this is going too fast, and the movie is gone.
There should be individual people pushing each doom buggy, because how fast could a person make those moves?
That's the speed. It's a very belabored, back-breaking pace for one person to push.
Yes, so that, yes, I appreciated the original mansion in a different way when I was on it.
I also want to say this. Last year, I was hoping that we could do a whole section on the new Haunted Mansion queue and gift shop.
That's right.
I kept saying this in the live show.
We did.
People were excited about it.
Scream Beatles-esque shriek every time the notion of discussing the new queue, the new landscaping gift shop.
They had recently shown art, I think last year, I mean, of this.
And it was like, oh, they're really doing the graveyard up outside, and they're going to be a little gift shop.
And of course, foolishly, I'm a foolish mortal.
I thought, oh, this will be built in a year. This is just a change in the line around, and they're building a little shop for the merchandise.
No, wrong. They just went vertical on the gift shop.
There's literally steel beams I saw three days ago.
Finally, it's just like four beams and like a roof outline.
And I went, this is just starting now?
So, I mean, it's almost like believing hypothetically that if the Disney company comes out on a stage and tells you that everything that a lot of plans they've announced are all going to be wrapped up in five years.
It's almost like believing that completely with no hedging of bets.
That's true.
Well, that's why they want you to do dreams and wishes and magic.
Yeah.
So, like, get them into the fantasy because the reality is going to be construction walls for a decade.
They should say, yeah, wishes, imagination, and then believe us.
They should say, like, believe us. They should slip it in and there's like little presentations.
They might say it subtly if you listen, if you crank up that sound. We're hearing it subliminally.
Believe us.
I know. Well, that also is what, you know, because it changed me who wants to take his time with this.
Yeah.
I was looking forward to that cue so much.
And it's why I have to institute the policy of just taking our time in the graveyard because I want to be talking about each bush.
You understand?
You know how much I want to change me wants to be here talking about the height and width and depth of every bush and what kind of what kind of bush they are.
And then the full history of how long has that bush been grown in America?
Yeah.
If at all. Maybe we discover they're foreign bushes.
Yeah, I think.
Brought here for the first time.
Right. We could have done a little, like, we could have, like, taken a little piece off each bush and then taken into a forensics lab and figured out exactly which bush, where each bush is from.
Oh, kind of an ancestry.
Yeah.
Yeah, for plant life.
Jason knows a bush.
You know a bush guy probably that could do that?
Yeah, I could probably get in touch with a bush guy.
Okay, because they could.
Yeah, they could date the leaf, the leaf that you give them.
Yeah, I'm sure they could figure out a lot of things about the leaf and then we could do a whole leaf episode.
Yeah.
But not, we can't now.
We can't because it's not built.
And I'm sure they're still moving headstones.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
So there's a virtual queue going on at the Haunted Mansion right now in the year 22.
If you're listening to this in the far future, it's 2024.
There's a virtual queue for Haunted Mansion holiday.
And it's just a mess.
Really?
Yeah.
That's the only way you can do Haunted Mansion right now.
Oh, God.
You have to get in either at the 7 a.m. or in the noon slot, you have to get a reservation.
That's the only time.
Okay.
So everything's more complicated, more expensive, and the whole resort is the construction site.
Yes.
And there's only a little bit on the lawn you can walk through.
And then the line goes fastish, but it extends out all the way almost into like Pirates,
the virtual queue line.
So it's a big mess.
So it's still, yeah, you pay a lot of money.
It's tough to get reservations and impossible to get annual passes to get into the Disneyland
that still has the issue of the Pirates crowds and the Haunted Mansion crowds just like bash
and bash.
Yeah.
Like a giant West Side Story gang fight.
Yes.
And yes, the logic of not completing the queue for the Halloween season to me, I don't know.
How much money did they save for not finishing?
And it's like they weren't thinking about us.
Well, they certainly weren't thinking about us.
And they never do.
And that's what we complain all the time.
No.
They never think about us.
Yeah.
We weren't at D23 front row cheering daddy on.
Well, they also knew that we would have been there, that they would have said, all right,
new Stark flight test attraction.
Boo!
What's up with the queue?
What's up with the new garden?
What kind of bushes are you using?
Josh, what kind of bushes are you using?
There should be a world.
If you didn't see D23, they did this presentation with the Stark flight where it was Bob Iger
and then they revealed it was Robert Downey Jr. next to him.
In that world, there should be a third reveal that Jason is next to the two of them in the
Stark flight lab vehicle.
And I got a notepad in my reporter fedora with the press thing in it.
And I'm like, are you here as Tony Stark or is Victor Von Doom?
The people want to know.
Yes, then it would have been a video in this instance, not a photo.
Yeah.
You would have said that in real life.
I mean, I could have held up what I was asking him.
Is he going to have trouble keeping the parts straight in his head?
If Disneyland is asking him to return to Tony Stark, a role he's probably long forgotten
how to play because he is so in Von Doom mode.
And he's been, you know, that amount of money that he's making, that means you are getting
a what, an 80 million dollar performance.
You said 80 million last time.
I under guessed before.
And I think it's at least a high rate, at least a hundred.
Great.
And so he's putting he's he's putting a hundred million dollars worth of effort into his Von
Doom.
Yeah, yeah.
And then and then Disney's asking him to go the other way and also be this character that's
that's dead to him.
It's ash to him.
How is he going to do that?
We can only ask so much of this one man.
I think maybe they should, you know, see all the different variants of Tony Stark and
maybe one of them's like a whimsical 18th century, you know, scientists who can talk
to the animals.
Oh, smart.
Yeah.
Now, this is another one of those where it passed me.
You might have tried to move past Doolittle very quickly, but I feel like my new spirit
should be, whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down, guys.
Tell me something else about Doolittle.
I don't know.
Let's let's let's milk this tangent a little bit.
Let's talk Doolittle.
I think you know everything there is to know about Doolittle.
You know, but it's OK, because let me see.
He can talk to the animals, squawk to the animals.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
It's OK to be scared.
Oh, that's right.
And then there's the like French horn in the butt at the end.
Oh, yeah.
That's but that's really what you need to know.
To fart.
Spoiler alert.
Yeah.
So that's the finish.
That's the finish of the movie.
So there isn't much more to say about that.
But I'm hoping for an accent for Vig for Von Doom.
That's what I'm hoping for.
Oh, yes.
I am really hoping for an accent from Robert.
Yeah.
Make him Welsh or something.
It is.
Well, now that we're OK, tangents are all right.
I am hoping I'm hoping that there's no like connection to Tony Stark.
He just like kind of looks like the guy, which to me is a funny decision.
Because everyone's going to be like, well, what you look like.
And they're like, no, no, I'm not him.
And then that's it.
I can't imagine that's what they're going to do.
We'll see.
But to me, that's a funny narrative choice of like everybody's going, oh, my God, you're
the guy.
And he's like, I'm not.
I am a different guy.
And then you're like, OK, and then we'll fight him.
And you're from Transylvania is the idea.
He should do like a Darth Vader thing where his underlings go like, you know, you look
like and he just vaporizes them.
Maybe.
Yeah.
And it's a little gag.
It's a funny little bit.
I what I think I what I think will happen.
And this is I'll make a big prediction now, because what is this?
Twenty twenty six is the first one or twenty twenty five?
I can't remember.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Twenty twenty six.
But we will still be weak when it comes out.
We might potentially still be in the graveyard.
So I want to make a prediction that Victor because they said he will be Victor Von Doom.
My prediction is that it's a variant Tony Stark that was kidnapped by like my
mama Von Doom when he was little and then raised as Victor.
But he actually he was Tony Stark and he has good inside of him.
Yeah.
And at the very end of like Secret Wars, he flips and does something heroic and either
he dies or he lives.
And Iron Man 4 happens a year later.
I mean, I think whatever the solution is that gets the most movies in him back together.
So I think he will be related to Tony Stark, but we'll see.
Yeah, yeah.
That's my guess.
Can change Scott say no, no, no.
Slow down really quick.
And just can I just ask for you guys to just name five Marvel comic artists off the top
of your head?
Just say five names really.
And don't you say anything.
Sure.
Back and forth.
However you want to do it.
Again, your hands are on the wheel.
Say five names and don't add any jokes or do anything funny.
Well, in the history of Joe Manarera, Andy and Adam Kubert.
Yeah.
Well, that's two.
So we're moving a little faster.
Slow down.
Herb shrimp.
OK, good.
Wow.
Mike.
It's not herb shrimp.
You're not.
You're not just thinking about herb shrimp.
No, I'm not.
So something you can get at a restaurant.
No.
I'll say Mike Waringo.
Rest in peace.
Great.
Wow.
Mike Waringo.
Peace and love.
He would sign Ringo as his signature.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah, he would.
Yeah.
Jason, you want to?
Oh, OK.
Wasn't that five?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, that was five.
Sorry, sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
But again, at any point in the episode, if you want to just say the name of an artist,
feel free.
Great.
Thank you.
And with that, Jason, you're steering.
Yeah.
I'm not even sure exactly where we start.
I think it's up to you to plan us in that mansion and take us on a ride.
Well, I was pleasantly surprised to find out in the live show, I did mention the Garret
Ticker Gravedigger lit with real lighting, UV lighting, all other ghosts lit with black
light to distinguish.
So I did cover that in the live show.
Great.
And I made a note that, hey, look, I was surprised.
What we didn't cover is the giant scrim with the ghosts flying up in the sky.
Yes, very good.
Yeah.
Very good thing to catch.
It is an old, like, magician technique known as the magic lantern.
So yeah, when you're leaving the attic and your doom buggy is tipping over and you look
over and there's ghosts flying out of the graveyard, that's what Jason's talking about.
Yes.
And it is a very cool effect.
Every trick, when you look into it, it's just like, ah, it's some old magician thing.
Yes.
It's some old 100-year-old trick.
It doesn't like, other than like maybe those new, like, the beast effect in Japan and other
things, which maybe those are still old magician tricks and we just don't know how they work.
They might be based in some way.
Most things, you go, ah, it's Pepper's ghost.
Most things are like, oh yeah, Houdini did that 100 years ago.
Yeah.
Houdini made it up.
Pepper really, we owe everything to Pepper, ultimately.
Sure.
When I hear Pepper, I think of Robert Downey Jr., because you go, Pepper?
That'll be...
That was the character.
I thought you were saying that once he's finally free of the $100 million burden, that then
he'll make a movie where he's Pepper.
Oh, that's good too.
You get to find out how he made the ghost.
So yes, because he'll say then, because he says Pepper Potts is the name of Gwyneth Paltrow's
character in the Iron Man movies, and he says Pepper a lot.
So it'll be a similar thing to like Michael Douglas in Ant-Man saying Scott, with Behind
the Candelabra.
Oh yeah, right.
Where he calls...
R.I.P. Scott Thorson.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for the memories.
Thanks for the movie.
Yes.
So hopefully he will make a Pepper's ghost, or he'll be Houdini in total.
Well, what needs to happen is he plays Pepper, and at the end, he posts credits, he meets
Hugh Jackman prestige, and he meets Ed Norton illusionist.
Oh wow.
And he's back in his shared universe again.
Of old moustache.
Ed Norton.
Of old magicians.
Yeah, magicians or just guys who have a lot of mirrors.
And then they can recruit the name here, Etienne Gaspard Robertson, who kind of was famous
for his magic lantern illusions, a trickery made famous by a Belgian magician, Etienne
Gaspard Robertson, in shows in which he would project ghosts onto gauze, which was thin
enough to see through and masked by smoke.
That's from doing buggies.
So that's another old magician.
I think part of the appeal, part of what makes the Houdini Mansion special is you just layer
trick on top of trick on top of trick, and it adds to the unease and the spookiness.
Now, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's slow down.
I don't mean to put you on the spot, but can you just find a list of 10 French names and
say them all please?
Any French names?
Wait, hold on.
He's Belgian.
Oh, sorry.
Belgian.
Belgian names.
Thank you.
I do not know where to start.
I do know that name is pronounced Etienne, I think.
Okay.
I don't know off the top of my head.
Next year maybe we'll start with the list of 10 Belgian names.
Any name.
Any Belgian.
They could just be regular people living in Belgium today, you could make them up, wherever
you want to get your Belgians is fair game.
This will be a real test because usually we say the assignment at the end of the last episode,
you listen to the last episode before you start and you go, oh, that's right.
So now this one we'll have to remember, it comes at like a half hour into the episode,
not at the end.
Well, and mainly Jason.
Jason, we're getting off easier.
Jason has to say 10 Belgian names.
Yeah.
Okay.
As long as it's clear, I was just happy that the Cappy thing was simple because I didn't
finish last year's episode until about eight o'clock class and I was listening and I was
like, I hope I don't have to scramble to acquire something.
Oh yes.
Oh no, I forgot.
I was sent on a mission.
I have to find, there's a map.
Time is the perfect target open until.
Can I?
Wait, wait.
They sent me into the sea.
I have to go, I have to take an old map and then it like connects to a part of a broken
watch and I have to put them together and then fuse them somehow and then magic's going
to shoot out of that.
And I have to have that at the top of this fucking podcast.
Honey, do we have any Pacific ocean water sitting around?
It's the only way to activate the magic watch.
Cappy also is the name of Mario's cap in Mario Odyssey.
So that is like, we have to get a sentient cap with eyes and wear it.
Oh yeah.
Listen, before the next episode, get a cap and bring it to life.
Bring it to life, yeah.
So.
Then we're all like, what do we, oh god, the only solution I could think, because I don't
know any magic, the only solution I can think of is to masturbate into this hat.
That's how you bring it to life.
That's the only way to bring it to life is to give it living beings to like bless it
with living organisms.
And the only ones we can produce are sperm.
We've made life happen.
That's ultimately sort of that way.
Yeah, sure.
Can I say something serious about the scrim?
Yeah.
As a kid, especially, I think when you look over to the graveyard, the scrim like takes
away even you wanting to look at the ceiling to notice how big, like I feel like it's a
good trick to move your eye to prevent you from like going, oh, we're still in a room.
It really makes you, helps make you feel like you're in like outside, basically in outside.
You're in outside.
And it's still like, you're like, oh, look at that.
It's still like such a good trick and it still looks good.
And the scrim itself is like hazy, like you can tell it's a scrim, but also it makes it
look like it's foggy out there.
Yeah.
Like you can tell, oh, there's something going on there, but it kind of just looks like it's
fog or haze.
It might be like the entirety of the atmosphere throughout the ride, but especially this part
of the ride is the use of scrims.
Yeah.
Scrims are the secret weapon of the Haunted Mansion.
Now, there is a story, and I don't remember if it's this part of the scrim, but I saw,
it might be closer to singing bus, but according to the book More Mouse Tales, there was a
grad night one year where some teens trampled the graveyard, got out of, somehow removed
the safety bar, got out and destroyed the scrim among other things.
This happened, this must have been by the, when that book was published, that must have
been early 90s.
And I'm thankful I didn't know about that before.
It might have made me not want to talk about the Haunted Mansion at all.
How upsetting.
Too painful of a memory.
Yeah.
Too upsetting.
Yes.
Teens, if they knew the history of Etienne and all of that, they wouldn't have dared
touch those screens.
This is why we need more magic education in schools.
That's, yeah, that's true.
We do need a whole hour of magic.
I'd like that as a parent.
If you guys had high school and then had magic class.
Magic 101.
Yeah.
That's true.
That's funny, because that's what people thought the toadins would do for Mr. Toad.
They thought, oh, people are going to steal the Mr. Toad cars or destroy the ride.
Not realizing that if you're a Disney fan, if you're enough of a Disney fan to be posting
a word about it online, that means you are so scared of ruining anything.
Right.
You would never, you would never go near any of these precious items made by the coats
and the henches of the world.
There are a lot of people online currently upset about the Rivers of America closure
and they post every day about what's going away.
Yeah.
Now, I am scared of some of them.
That's a new, that's a different-
Not all some.
Some are a new breed.
Well, if you say, I like the water and I like the boat and I don't want them to go away,
of course.
We agree with that.
Yeah.
When you say, Disney is destroying our heritage or Disney hates America.
Disney hates America is my favorite one.
Then perhaps we're on a different side, we're on a different viewpoint.
Something deeper is going on.
I like the water and then also what, this is, again, I'm glad you gave me permission
to talk-
Good.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ultimately, and I see this in a lot of spheres, fan spheres, people upset for corporations
making various decisions, ultimately, a lot of these decisions are made because of capitalism
and how corporations are continuing to just try to maximize profits out of every square
inch of land or every IP.
They're trying to, well, there's no IP on Rivers of America, we should just shove cars
there.
That's water.
That's a runaway capitalism decision, that's not a hating America decision, but it's funny
because the people that are the most pro-America and are worried about the history of America,
they don't want to put those two and two together and realize that the capitalism is really
what is making Disney decide to replace their beloved river with cars.
That's what I would say, but no, it's like Disney hates Benjamin Franklin and all he
did for the country.
Disney doesn't give a shit about Benjamin Franklin, that's true, but you are not tying
these two decisions together, you're finding scapegoats and this happens everywhere, it
happens in Star Wars, it happens everywhere.
Well, I mean, it's tough to talk about hating America because in a few, in mere days, we
might elect two people who hate America, their names are Kamala Harris and Tim Walz, we need
to do everything we can to make sure it doesn't happen.
The two biggest America haters might be steering the ship in days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's tense.
It's always tense doing these.
I know.
Elections right around the corner.
Of course.
But let's, Jason, feel, you don't have to steer us anywhere, but if you want.
Oh.
Hmm.
No, I wasn't prepared for that, were you?
Well, no, I was just thinking, well, let's, we talked about scrims a little, I don't think,
I'm sure I learned this fact at some point and forgot it, but there are more, I guess
there are technically scrims throughout the graveyard party, you know, dividing all the
ghosts, all the little scenes that are going on, I think to prevent light bleed and also
to help the illusion of making it look like the graveyard just goes on forever.
Yes, there's like depth, like messes with your depth of field a little bit, your vision.
Yeah.
It does lead, and I've said this, I don't know if I've said this on a Haunted Mansion
episode, it does lead to like, kind of like squinting to try to make out some of these
ghosts.
And I think some of that is good, but then you see Hapox Ghost, which is a new animatronic,
and you go, could they replace all of these with this figure, this type of figure?
And would it ruin it?
Would all those ghosts being clear ruin it in some level?
Or could you have a couple close like that and then keep it as is for the rest of them
or the farther away ones?
I don't think it would bother anybody if there were some bright ghosts.
I don't think so, but maybe you want the bright ghosts up front, but then would that distract
from the less bright ghosts in the back?
You want a crisp loot player.
You like one.
Well, I just, you get a little spoiled by how crisp the Hapox Ghost is, because it's
such a new robot and it looks like a ghost, but you get so close to him.
And then you're led into a room full of non-crisp ghosts.
Yeah, uncrisp, non-crisp ghosts is what you're viewing for the rest of the time.
And it's fun because it gives you, they're ghostly, but you're like, I bet there's some
features on these faces that I would enjoy looking at.
They're whimsical characters.
Or they're not.
Or the scrims hide that they never made any features.
That's true too.
The scrim could be hiding the lack of features.
A real question that is going to dictate how long we're in the graveyard is, how much do
we care or like any of these specific graveyard ghosts?
Or is it just about the atmosphere and that there are a bunch of them?
But are there are there individual ghosts as we assess the scene that are like, well,
that we have to really give some love to?
Well, there are flowers.
There's definitely ones that deserve that are doing fun stuff.
And there's also ones that you just discover because there's so many like the ghosts on
a bike and stuff like things that you go, oh, maybe I didn't notice that for the first
10 years of going.
So I don't know that I have a specific favorite one that deserves its own episode, but we
can definitely like list some other favorites, different effects, because really what it
is, is there more effects or what they're doing versus they're actually like, oh, that's
character suggests a fun guy like the middle pirate who's singing on Pirates of the Caribbean.
When you get to that barn, that guy is great.
That guy deserves maybe his own episode.
I don't know. You're talking about it.
And he you've thought of it.
You just went on it and you thought middle pirate is its own thing.
Well, right. And because he's the one who, if you catch the right part of the song, stop
singing the yo ho, yo ho.
And he starts going like one pirate sings this funny little background like warble.
Yeah. And I'm like, that gives him his own little unique thing.
Yeah. So but I you don't get that from all these ghosts.
You can't tell who's singing what necessarily.
You can't tell who's like you can't tell what their faces look like.
That middle pirate's burned into my brain.
I know his face. I wake up thinking about him sometimes.
You do. I didn't know the relationship you have with the middle pirate.
Lindsay actually one who pointed him out.
She's like, oh, I like this guy because he's saying he does that little singing part.
Now, anyone feel free to to say, hey, wait, wait for your turn.
We get back in the order.
But when you talk about that crazy musical improv, that is apparently a thing with the
opera singers who are towards the end of the graveyard scene that this via an interview
with Buddy Baker put the music together.
Now I don't have the name. The last name is Norman, but I didn't cover the first name.
But there is the female opera singer who they brought in had like perfectly trained on
the melody that she was given and could nail it in this very studious way.
And then during the recording, Buddy Baker said, you're this character is supposed to
be a nut. So just ad lib all over the place.
And then and but it was she was kind of resistant to it because she knew it one way, not
willing to depart and improvise.
But then she ultimately did do this very wild, much like that pirate, which is sort of what
people like about this sequence, that it's a bunch of crazy nonsense.
Yeah. The full name, Lou Lee, Jean Norman, Lou Lee.
Yeah. Soprano, Lou Lee, Jean Norman and tenor Bill Reeve.
OK. Now, is this good license to just talk for a while about our feelings about the series,
The Sopranos? Jason, what do you think?
Oh, it's been a while. I do think about restarting it recently.
Yeah, I would like to. I don't have any time.
But when I do, when I will have time, I would like to rewatch.
Sure. Great. I watched it.
These are some excellent sopranos.
I liked it. Great.
Polly Walnuts is a funny guy.
Rest in peace.
He's in the Haunted Mansion.
He was a real mobster. Did you know?
Pio Mai is one of the hazy horses.
Maybe you can see.
Wrestler Tommy Dreamer is his kids are in The Sopranos is that little kids.
Really? Yeah, they're in the car.
Lin-Manuel Miranda is in The Sopranos as a bellhop.
Yeah. Will Arnett in The Sopranos as well.
FBI agent. This is very good.
Have you seen The Sopranos?
Some. I haven't finished it.
I know I should. That's a bad thing to admit.
That's all right. I've liked it.
I've seen it. I'm not mad.
This is great. We got a list of names.
We got a list of names. This is wonderful.
I feel. Can I admit this?
I feel like we're being set up.
I feel like something's coming.
Oh, what do you mean?
The axe is going to drop. I know that about an hour ago.
The hammer is going to come down.
Here, I'm trying to make you guys relax,
but at this point, it's a boy who cried,
well, you're just so. Too good to be true, I think.
Something's happening. I don't know how.
I don't know. I'm trying to think what could.
No, it's so good that it is true.
I've changed. I've changed, Scott, and I'm allowing it.
And let me throw one more in.
If you guys want to take any time in this episode
to talk about any complaints that you have
about the internal messaging system
of a health care app that you're using,
take as much time as you want.
10 minutes, 15 minutes.
I want to hear everything that's not functional about it.
What's good about it?
I have thoughts about that, but I'll save it for later.
Okay.
Look, the health care system is broken in this country.
I hate to go. I went off on capitalism
a couple of minutes ago.
Look at this. I cut Mike loose, and suddenly we're getting.
You're tearing down all the pillars of our society.
Doesn't make sense. I think you hate this country
as much as Tim Walz does.
I don't know about that. He hates the country a lot.
He really is very of it.
Now, you talk about he's the one running the long.
I'm saying I'm making you guys nervous.
I'm nervous about this guy pretending I'm a football guy.
Running the middle, I eat chili.
Fuck you. I'm on to you. I'm on to you, man.
Jason probably has some gripes with him
just about the different state fair meats he eats
and his feelings on that,
because he's such a folksy guy goes to those state fairs,
and he has certain types of meat.
And he has not come out with his stance on pork rolls.
There's meat he's been mentioning,
and I go, I've never heard of that before,
and maybe Jason knows.
Governor Walz, did you eat the deep-fried ranch
in the Minnesota state fair or not?
That would be, if we could get you, yeah,
maybe to question him before the election,
you could do a little sit down with him.
Yeah, on all meats interview.
I think that's an interview they wouldn't hide from.
Can I say, sometimes you look at pictures
of the graveyard scene,
and it doesn't look like it does
when you're on the ride live.
This is just a photo from mice chat,
and it's like, the effect is really cool.
It looks kind of almost neon in a way
that this doesn't look like the mansion
when you're on it.
I think it's hard to photograph.
This is a very difficult thing to photograph.
Is that even a, did somebody take that while writing it,
or is that a pose for a photo?
I don't know, but it's almost like
it gives it a different vibe.
I don't know that I necessarily need the vibe
to be more neon,
but you can definitely make out the faces easier.
Well, and then if you photograph with the lights on,
this photo of two of the goofy band members,
it's like, oh, they're all kind of baby blue and cream,
because that paint has to show up.
Can you show me that photo again?
I want to see what it's baby blue and cream.
I mean, sky blue, I guess.
That could be, yeah, no, I guess,
I see what you're saying.
Baby blue and cream is just a phrase
that seems like it'd be your album or something.
Yeah, yeah, it's a bit of a trick Princeton released.
Jason Sheridan, baby blue and cream.
Yeah, I covered the Neil Young track,
baby blue and cream.
It's a Neil Young.
I was thinking more like a jazz thing,
but it's a Neil Young.
Kind of a cappy kind of song.
It's more of a cappy thing.
I guess it's more of a cappy thing.
This guy I really like, and maybe I missed his name,
Jason, help me out if you know it,
he's sort of sitting in the casket,
and he's got a little cup of tea,
and he's a little guy, and I don't know,
he just like, he's got kind of like a little grin
on his face, and I don't even really know.
He just almost looks like a rankin' and bass elf.
He looks like the heat miser or the snow miser or whatever.
And I really like him.
He's got a top hat on.
He looks like, shoot, the guy from Laughin'
who's in Wedding Crashers.
This is great, this is exactly what I want to be.
If last-minute cast members are being discussed,
Shane Scott is so happy.
And if Mike has taken a bunch of time
to not talk and look him up,
this is a, oh, old me would have been so frustrated.
Thank God he's dead.
Thank God he's gone.
What is this name?
In fact, let's all not say anything
until the name comes up.
He's so great, and I can't think of his name,
but he's a funny.
You can't think of the name of a great guy from Laughin'?
You can't think of the extended cast of Wedding Crashers.
You know what, for years and years,
I can never remember who did Piglet's Voice,
who was on the Bob Newhart Show.
John Fielder, and finally I remember it now.
I've remembered it so often now
that my daughter's watching so much poo.
But Henry Gilbert, Gibson,
Henry Gibson is my indicator.
No, Henry Gilbert's our friend.
Henry Gilbert's the guy who's been on our show.
We just talked at the Simpsons show.
But no, Henry Gibson is the guy I'm thinking of.
He looks like Henry Gibson to me,
which makes me happy.
Jane and I just ran into Trap.
We saw Trap and-
Whoa, whoa, slow down.
Via what service?
What streamer did you rent it from?
I had a credit on Amazon.
How much of a credit?
I'm tired of you speeding through this, Jason.
Six dollars.
Good, wow, that's a big credit.
So I rented it on Prime.
We're watching the opening credits,
and the name comes up, Hayley Mills.
Oh yeah.
And she is an older FBI profiler in the movie.
This, by the way, we're gonna be,
this is gonna be, and this is more of an old Scott complaint,
this October series is gonna be so full of discussion
of the months old film Trap.
That is true.
Several episodes now.
But that's an old me thing, I'm sorry Jason.
I think it's probably out at theaters by this point,
so it's reasonable to rent it, you know?
Yeah.
Anyway.
It was reasonable to rent it.
We were like, is that parent Trap Hayley Mills?
And sure enough, it was.
That's her, yeah.
Yeah.
She's back, she was at D23, she was singing the songs,
the old Let's Get Together.
Let's Get Together?
Yeah.
So she's back, Hayley Mills is back.
This is the kind of thing old Scott would not have stopped
to smell the roses, we wouldn't have landed at points
like Hayley Mills is back.
I feel like you're gonna kill us by then or something.
I don't understand, here I'm coming at you
with nothing but kindness.
You're gonna attack, like physically attack us
to end this episode.
You're acting as if I've wired the building,
and when I take a convenient bathroom break,
that that is when the building will implode.
There's like checkoffs.
And layers of bricks will crush you both.
This is more stressful than a Lady Raven concert
that turned out to entirely be a trap.
This is like checkoffs.
Yes, this is, I have not trapped you, this is no trap.
I've tried to say this joke three times already.
And people are gonna be hearing me,
I'm gonna do it again.
It's like checkoffs niceness or something.
It's like the niceness is like lingering
and like when is it gonna,
no checkoffs, it doesn't really make sense.
It's not a really good joke.
I shouldn't have said it, I'm gonna edit it out.
No, this is like, this could be like Shakespeare,
Shakespeare Bob, I was gonna say say Shakespeare Bob.
This is the famous Simpsons character.
Sideshow Bob, when he's nice in the one with,
Sideshow Cecil.
Yeah.
And he actually is nice.
There'll be a shoot, yeah.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see, Jason, just stay on your toes, Jason.
For once, I'm not trying to kill you.
Stay on your toes.
Keep your eyes open, Jason.
Get off your toes, kick up your feet.
Don't even worry about what your little toesies are doing.
All right, okay.
And this is, how great does it feel?
Because at this pace, I don't think there's,
I'd be shocked if we got done with the graveyard today.
It felt right, which, yeah.
I don't think we've talked about like two things.
Which is what James Scott is all about.
My little guy we talked about.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Well, who else are we talking about?
Jason, you got a character?
Well, there's cats and owls in the graveyard.
They make noise that kinda adds to the sonic symphony
going around.
So the meows and stuff in their hoots.
The meows and the hoots, yeah.
Now, are those ghost cats and ghost owls
or are those living cats and living owls?
That's a good question.
I think they're living.
I think they're living as well.
Scott, what do you think?
The pictures that I'm looking at,
they seem to be lit with just like regular lighting.
Right.
I'm seeing photos of just graveyard cats.
Yeah, I think we're dealing with just regular cats.
Right, cause they have the pet cemetery in the queue,
but I think those animals are alive.
Yes.
So, that's good.
There's a lot of tea drinking happening in the graveyard.
With a floating teapot.
Yes, there's a lot of tea drinking.
I think these characters are drinking more cocktails.
There's characters at a little table here.
These are more like circular,
almost like a glass you would have the Carthay Manhattan in.
You know what they kind of look like?
They're gloatini's.
They do look a lot like gloatini's.
It's like a drink I would have at the Tron Electronica
Festival, whatever it's called.
Not a festival, but it should be a festival.
It should be a touring festival.
It should be early.
It should replace Coachella.
But yeah, these guys are all having spots of tea.
This is like a bigger cup here.
So, it's like people are having different types of parties
in the graveyard.
Everyone's not having a sort of unified party.
Everyone's having their own little gatherings
and it leads to this one sort of
grim grinning ghost sequence.
But all, appropriately you say that
because it's all like the music track.
It all kind of ties together.
There's like the one bass track of grim grinning ghosts
and there's all the weird instruments
just as there are like.
Yeah, there's the music.
There's the instrumental and then there's the singing bus.
Slow down, slow down.
We're not at the bus.
Old Scott might say the singing bus
would be an interesting thing to talk about this year,
but no pressure.
We'll get there.
Slow down.
You ain't racing yet.
Yeah, I'm giving a slight suggestion.
That's the kind of thing that you should.
I'm not opposed to going there.
It's up to Jason, really.
It's Jason.
Sure, yeah.
Well, what would you like to talk about
before we discuss the singing bus?
Well, you ain't racing yet reminds me.
I hope with the new cars coming next to Haunted Mansion,
I hope you get a made or fart.
I hope you can hear made or farting
from the Haunted Mansion line.
That's all I'll say.
That'd be a nice thing to add to the atmosphere, absolutely.
Yeah.
Do you think that, look, that is on topic
because the proposal right now
is moving cars to Rivers of America,
but that is right by a Haunted Mansion in Florida.
Well, I mean, folks might say that we are keeping,
listeners, in all this time,
we have never discussed the Disney World Haunted Mansion.
Right.
It's not, it's related.
It's related.
There's an offhanded comment here and there.
There's an offhanded comment here.
We make offhanded comments once in a while.
Once in a while.
But it hasn't been a fully dedicated
Disney World Haunted Mansion yet,
and which has different things,
the Escher Room and various different things,
and I don't know.
What are you turning into?
I don't know.
Look, we have a lot to talk about
because they just threw the hat box ghost in there,
sort of willy-nilly.
Oh, that's happened now?
Yeah, he's just hanging out in one of the early rooms.
But yes, there's gonna be like cars racing
in front of the Haunted Mansion,
which I guess they'll try to.
You always say this, but do we,
we're all acting as if Disney doesn't.
Sure, we don't know the,
we don't know how they'll hide it.
It's probably a tree line.
We don't know how it'll hide,
but it does feel like you'll hear.
Because that's a point of view I've seen,
is just like, you know, loud exhaust pumping cars
ruining the Haunted Mansion.
I hope it's not exhaust.
You're a professional Disney blogger or whatever.
You think they're not gonna do anything
to make this a pleasant area transition.
I would think so.
And I don't think the cars pump exhaust either, but.
Should we make, I mean, we could make bets,
because we'd love to bet now.
We could make bets.
Will you be able to hear,
I wanna say made or farting, but maybe we expand it.
Will you be able to hear any of the cars
from the queue of the Haunted Mansion in Florida?
I don't think so.
Should we bet?
You think, no.
I think they will try to soften it,
but I think you'll hear people screaming,
which actually might fit for a Haunted Mansion.
Okay.
Also, like though, you think about it,
you said earlier they're not making the connection.
That is capitalism.
Like a big, fast car next to a dilapidated old building
is very American.
You mean like it's actually more American
if there's cars next to a Haunted Mansion?
If there's big nasty cars zooming by
the regal old mansion next to the Colonial Street.
Actually, if they could use gasoline
and they could make the whole thing stink.
You want them to make it like Autopia from the 1950s.
Yeah, like a freeway built next to a historical landmark.
I see what you're saying.
So the one thing is like a protected landmark,
but because the 10 feet over isn't,
America will throw cars there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Maybe like, maybe it's time to flip Liberty Square.
Like maybe it's time to make it Little Vegas.
Maybe it's time to put up some neon and stuff.
Put some slot machines in it?
Oh yeah.
That's the one thing this world is missing.
Some progressive slots.
Here's what I, okay, I will bet $5
that you will be able to hear some car noises
from zooming around in the distance.
I don't know if they'll be farts.
I hope they are, but at least zooms.
And then I believe within 25 years
there will be a slot machine on the grounds of Disney World.
So this one we gotta hold on to for 25 years.
This is gonna be a long time, yeah.
But I do believe. 25 years,
which is when probably we will make it
to the Disney World Haunted Mansion
and how it's different.
I'm gonna be a full Benjamin Button baby at that point.
What?
I age backwards.
Is this the reveal that you, oh no.
Yeah, I age backwards.
God, we've all been trying to place our finger on
like why is Jason somehow,
he's the one who knows about like what songs
from the last three years are,
but also he's from the 1800s.
That's why you've been Benjamin Butting the whole time.
Benjamin Butting.
I shortened it.
Jason is Benjamin Butt, not Benjamin Button.
That's just a little nickname
he picked up along the way.
That's why I want me here to fart.
It feels homey to me.
Benjamin, call him Benjamin Butt from now on, folks.
That's what he'd like to be referred to
now that he's revealed it here.
This is now, what I'm, it's not like I,
look, talking about ghosts,
I haven't fully exercised old Scott.
You know, he's in me somewhere.
And I just have to tell you that he's,
I am receiving these vibrations reminding me
that talking about the singing bus might be fun this year.
But again, I can, it's on me to suppress those.
I can push those down.
We do not have to listen to that guy.
Shove those down, please.
That asshole.
Old Scott, I have to agree with you
because there's a lot of good names to be said.
Wow.
Oh yeah, please, yeah, give us the good names.
Okay, we're talking about the singing bus.
I haven't talked about the ghost island.
Oh yeah, please.
I always forget this there,
but the executioner and his victim.
Oh yeah.
That's a pretty good visual gag.
Okay.
So isn't that after the singing bus?
We really, I throw it to you guys
and the whole, the order situation.
I thought it was you who were adherent
to the moving through it in order scenario.
And now it's all willy nilly now that you're in charge.
It's a cocktail party.
Well, that's what happens.
Remember, you're looking around.
Like, this might be the most,
is this the busiest in a good way,
I guess, some of the big pirate scenes.
I guess so, yeah.
That you're very much looking around.
Well, there's all the presidents.
I guess they're all blinking and coughing and shit.
This is, yeah.
They are coughing.
They're all ill.
I wish the olive fries,
I wish they all coughed in a manner appropriate
to the ailments of their time.
Now that would plus up that, right?
If you could watch them all die
the way that they actually died,
it'd be dark for some of them, but.
The one getting the cherries,
eating the too many cherries
and getting beef bullion shoved up his butt.
Who died of cherries?
One of them, one of them ate.
The president died of cherries.
Like he ate too many cherries
or he was prescribed them.
The president ate too many cherries and died?
Is that right?
There is a president, there's a thing.
I think one of the presidents who was shot
got a bunch of liquor and bullion shoved up his butt.
Zachary Taylor, what I'm reading is,
let me find cherries.
For 4th of July, it was a big outdoor celebration
and he was very tired.
Hot and tired, he drank iced water
and consumed large quantities of cherries and other fruits.
He suffered severe stomach pains for the next five days.
This is very much like Jason and the bananas.
This is why it's good that Jason's careful with the bananas
because he could die in five days.
I love ice water too, oh no.
Jason's a big supporter of ice water in general.
Yeah, we did just learn that, yes.
Lemon and ice water.
Diagnosed to suffering from cholera morbus
by his physicians, Taylor ate slivers of ice for relief
until his body began rejecting fluids.
And then five days later he said,
I have always done my duty, I am ready to die.
And he died. My God.
It's kind of out of nowhere, so there you go, wow.
There was a president cherries death.
But I think that's different than beef bullion
being shoved up your butt.
Well, if you're shot, what are they gonna do?
Could all, okay, there's been so much talk of,
if I want to mention, of all the presidents going away.
Instead, could they just add each president
holding a bloody rag and they hold it up and cough
a couple times during the show?
Because that would plus it up
and then give it a little more realism.
That would be amazing, yeah.
So they all, and then they look, they examine the rag.
Yeah, they have to look at it.
It looks stricken.
Can I say something about the band?
I know we're going, oh, we're jumping all around.
And I will say we kind of talked about the band last year,
but that's an old Scott thing, he's still in me.
And I don't know, maybe I'm forgetting
if we actually address this.
What's funny to me about the band
is the band looks like they're made up
of different time periods.
They're not all uniform.
So they maybe all didn't die at the same time.
They didn't know each other when they were living.
It looks like there's one guy from the Civil War
playing, I think, drums.
Then there's just a guy in his pajamas
playing that long horn.
I really like the idea that all these guys came together
to form a band in the afterlife.
Yeah. Yeah.
No DJs, though.
There's nobody who's died recently.
That would be a very good addition.
They should, yeah, this would be a good way to,
yeah, just to keep modding.
He doesn't have to do much,
but you throw a little bit of scratching in there.
Right.
Because assuredly, there's, I don't know for a fact,
but I bet hundreds of DJs die every year.
I pay tribute.
Let's look at the census.
Let's look at and see what the grade is.
So you want a ghost with a ghostly MacBook Pro
in front of them.
In the back, yes, in the back.
And I guess it maybe would ruin the flow
to like all of a sudden change it,
like change the Grim Gritting Ghost song to like dubstep,
but it would be what that DJ might do.
Or I guess you could even just add in a few scratches
like a Limp Bizkit track.
Well, yeah, you just add some random ones here and there
because they had so many tracks
and they were like cherry picking.
Yeah.
Zachary.
Careful.
Careful, Zachary.
They're cherry picking what to use
and then recording tracks in reverse
and then flipping them so they were correct.
But sounded a little off, you know.
We should not, they should not put in the ghost
of any of the members of LMFAO,
who we, as we have learned a lot,
they're not dead.
They're not dead, yeah.
As Jason questioned.
Yeah, yeah.
If we open for this.
He said not dead, yeah,
but I guess that is technically true.
We all have to go at a certain point.
So singing bus, singing bus.
Oh, sorry, he's in me.
I have to shove him down.
Singing bus, singing bus.
Shit, fuck.
You guys, that's the threat.
It's not current, Scott.
It's that old Scott might come back
and take over the episode.
Oh, no.
Just get down there.
No, guys, please, talk about something
that has nothing to do with the Haunted Mansion, fast.
Well, you know, at the very last LMFAO show,
they both said, I've done my duty
and I'm ready to die.
You've now switched.
Now your theory is that they have both died.
Well, they said that in unison.
It was crazy.
You can't find the video online.
It's illegal.
We were sexy and we knew it.
I think somebody online figured out
what you were confusing it with, though, right?
Wasn't it somebody from Migos died?
The somebody from the group Migos died.
I remember someone from Migos dying separately.
And there was like an uncle connection in that,
like there is an LMFAO.
It's an uncle nephew band, the rare uncle nephew band.
Well, that's funny that you're not just taking this
and going, yes, that's what I meant.
I mean, I'll take the, I forgot about the uncle.
I think he's still convinced
that somebody in LMFAO was dead.
I think he does not want to admit he's wrong.
He's like still, he already, he declared both of them dead.
It's there's now that now it's two.
The numbers are climbing.
He's going to declare that three of them are dead
and there aren't even three members.
Trying to get something a little more hip
and current in the Haunted Mansion.
Mike was trying to get the Jared Leto ghost in there.
Now they're docking his pay on this Tron movie.
So Haunted Mansion did so poorly.
Yes.
So you were, wait, we were going to read names,
but do you want to, you're holding off on the names?
Is that what you're doing?
Oh, I mean, I think we'd cover the party.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
The graveyard band.
Wow.
I think we could get to the bus,
sign stuff on the bus.
Oh my God.
All right, wow.
We're going to talk about the singing bus in this episode.
You know what?
Hold on, hold on.
I want to make a point in general.
Fuck you Michael.
Michael, I'll kill you in the end.
Shit, fuck.
And I've seen a lot of people make.
Old Scott, be careful.
I know, I'm trying, I'm trying to get through it,
but like this is such, this is to me,
this is the quintessential scene, the graveyard scene,
the pirates setting the town on fire.
This is the stuff you think about
when it's like foundational Disney ride stuff.
And this is what they don't want to do as much anymore
because it's all IP stuff and it's all like single scenes
and they point you in a direction of some action happening
versus just floating you into the room full of,
or floating you, yeah, floating both ways works,
into a bunch of robots and you pick where you're looking.
That's what, you're going to decide what you want to see.
And I feel like we're not getting as much of that anymore
and it's really hard, especially when it's movie stuff,
because they just want to show you the famous scene
from X whatever movie their ride is based on.
So I mourn the loss of sort of these party scenes
because I feel like this is such an important thing.
This is such a fun thing.
And I think it's good to reflect and focus
on what ambiently is bad today,
instead of talking about the thing we like
that is in the graveyard scene
that we could be talking about at any second.
But I think it's good what you're doing.
Thank you.
I don't know that I'm feeling
your sympathetic vibrations correctly.
I'm feeling vibrations.
You heard the words I said.
I didn't hear the words,
but I don't know that I felt them.
I don't know that I felt the sympathetic vibrations.
Yeah, I want to get all of the negative
feelings that you have out before we can say
the five funny names of the singing bus.
Okay, all right, all right.
Jason, you want to say the names of the singing ones?
Sure.
Well, Scott, you're so excited.
I feel like you should say,
do you want to say the bus names or the actor names?
We can split them.
Yeah, let's split them.
Let's split them, yeah.
I don't know.
Do we know the order?
But I don't actually know if it's a left to right order.
I mean, I know which one is the broken one.
Throw me whatever.
Why don't you say these names and I'll say the actor.
Okay, I'm going from left.
Rolo Rumkin.
Yeah, that's Vern Rowe.
Great.
Uncle Theodore.
That's the great Thurl Ravenscroft.
Of course, yeah.
Cousin Al.
Well, I'm seeing it as cousin Algernon.
Algernon?
Flowers for Algernon, of course, the story.
I know where that name from.
Chuck Schrader.
Ned Nubb.
Ned Nubb, J. Meyer.
And let's get this out of the way.
Ned Nubb is not Nine Numb.
Right, from Star Wars.
How do you say if it's N-U-N-B?
Nyan Numb is always what I've said,
but I actually was calling him Neon Numb for years and years,
and I've heard Nyan recently.
Ned Nubb is a real precursor to that.
Yes, for sure.
And finally, Phineas Pock.
Now, I'm seeing it as a Phineas P-Pock.
I'm getting a middle initial in there.
This is why it's good that we consulted
several different websites.
Ned Nubb, by the way, J. Meyer.
I said that, but sure.
That's an old Scott thing.
Why didn't I?
Oh, god.
I'm still getting used to it, guys.
Irish tenor, saying at the Golden Wars shoes.
Old Scott would also say he didn't even
say the name of Phineas P-Pock, which is Bob Ebrite.
But that's, again, that's a, you know,
it's like I'm still breaking in these shoes.
Well, we're trying something new.
We're sharing the names.
We're doing it on our feet.
We're finding it live.
Yeah, we're doing it live.
Yeah.
Dwayne, you were saying J. Meyer is what now?
He was an Irish tenor, saying, for many years,
at the Golden Wars, he wrote a few years.
Tor a lor a lai.
No, let's, all right, so we just jumped right
into those names.
But let's say a couple things, bigger picture
about the singing busts.
One is, and I don't think I realized until last year
when I did this research, foolishly,
that you are looking at the faces of who is singing
the song, that these were not actors hired later
to pantomime.
And I remember putting that together
as I became a fan of Thurl Ravenscroft,
the rich baritone voice who is throughout all these rides
that we love.
And once I clocked what he looks like,
I'm like, oh, that's him.
That is him on the bus singing.
So I wonder if that's true of all of them.
And in fact, it is.
They think they, I don't know if this was coordinated
or if they recorded the vocals and then realized,
hey, these are five weird looking guys.
They all kind of look like ghosts as it is.
Why go hire five other people?
Let's get, but that gets you into a different place
than Madame Leota, a character from 2021 or so
on this series, who that is one face
and then a different voice dubbing, correct?
Right, yes.
So yeah, you are looking at the faces
of these odd singers that is who's doing it.
And the second fact, that of course answers.
And I think if you're listening to this show,
this one's not true, but this is very urban legend
that not one of these five men is Walt Disney.
Yeah.
Something that a lot of people believe for many years
that he snuck in there.
As a kid, I thought it was,
because I think Thurl specifically,
because he's got the mustache.
That's who people think it is.
And that's who I always is up until,
I'm sure, my early 20s or later.
I don't know, I was too old to learn.
I needed to know that before.
But it seems like, it just looks like an old man.
But we're all still improving and bettering ourselves
and turning new leads.
So I'm admitting, I'm comfortable now admitting that,
that I didn't know. That at what age, 29 perhaps,
or even in your 30s. It's too old,
too old to learn that Thurl was not Walt Disney.
But yes, it would make, it feels very, I don't know,
it felt right, it felt so right.
So I understand why so many thousands
and millions of people think that.
Thurl, I used to mistakenly think that was the ghost host.
That's Paul Fries. What?
Paul Fries. Yeah.
Thurl's other, but then I did it again with Thurl.
That's a fact we haven't said since 2020, at least.
Maybe 2019 even.
So I can't blame him. Probably, yeah.
Thurl's other big career notes,
Tony the Tiger. Of course, of course, yes.
And sings the You're a Mean One, Mr. Grinch.
Again, doesn't narrate, narrator.
Old Scott, I'm sorry, New Scott is not gonna allow you
to say we've discussed all of this many times.
Not on my watch.
All right, I apologize.
But no, this is me thing. Shut your mouth, Michael.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, that was mean of New Scott.
This is me thing.
I used to think Thurl was the singer and the narrator,
but the narrator of The Grinch is Bella Lugosi, right?
Boris Karloff, isn't it?
Boris Karloff.
I'm confused.
Borlows Karloff.
Inspiration for Bobby Boris Pickett,
who we discussed in the Monster Mash episode.
Yes, we've been threatening Thurl episode in general
for years, and we should do it.
You know, it doesn't feel like,
I don't think this one's a threat.
There's episodes that are certain, you know,
Jay Leno acting career might be a threat.
Jay Leno's wrestling career,
which we still haven't made it to,
that one's a threat, sure.
But Thurl Ravenscroft, I think, will be a joy,
because this is a wonderful man, a man of faith,
I think a big presence in like Orange County churches.
I think that's where he started singing in churches,
and then got all career out of it,
because the voice was so unusual.
And this quality that nobody had,
I don't know who, you know, you hear that like,
all right, this actor, this current actor
has taken over all the Paul Freeze parts, or whatever.
I don't know who's doing any of these Thurls.
I mean, clearly there's people doing Tony the Tiger today,
but, you know, there's a,
I just don't think they make them like that.
I don't think voices can get as deep as that anymore.
It does feel like that, doesn't it?
They're that guy from Boyz II Men.
Maybe, yeah.
If they ever have to re-record any of this,
they gotta get that guy.
There is something, yes, that feels very unique
to like the generation of like voice actors.
A true opera singer, also.
That's in my notes, yeah.
Yeah, that'll help.
But yes, they're all...
In their appearance, too.
Doesn't it, now, if you find,
and I don't think this is true,
if you found out that all five of these guys
were Walt's best drinking buddies,
and that when they filmed this,
all of them were 35 years old,
I would believe it.
Yes.
The apocryphal story I heard about
is that they cast all these guys for singing,
and then they were emoting so much
when they were singing,
and they're like, let's just film them, too,
and that's how it ended up.
Of course, they could only emote
with their mouths and eyes,
because they were in such intense,
okay, don't move, they put them in a brace,
so they captured them correctly,
so it would match the projection correctly.
It's really creepy, in general.
I think that adds to the creepiness
that they had to just keep the head still.
The Phantom Five, I don't know if we officially said
the name of the band.
Well, there was discussion last year
of whether this is the Phantom Five
or the other band is the Phantom Five.
No, I think it's these.
See, I saw it with the other, I don't know.
It's where I get mad, where old Scott would get mad
about the hazy, half-thought-out mythology
in which everyone is named Phineas or something,
but new Scott recognizes this is great.
It's figured out wonderfully,
and it was part of the design
that nobody knows which one is the Phantom Five.
Oh, yeah.
But I think the effect is fantastic.
I think it's great that it's not perfect.
Because now we know, obviously,
they can projection map in this precision way,
and they do so much of this in the parks now,
but I like that it doesn't feel like these busts
are perfect to the centimeter exactly,
the faces and noses and cheeks of these guys.
And I think it adds to sort of an eerie feeling
whenever you see them.
That was gonna be my question.
Do you wanna keep the effect as is,
or would you sign off on an upgrade for these?
Because it looks, yeah, it looks weird,
and I don't, it's not at all like the weird bride
at this point with the projection face.
It doesn't stick out like that, where it's like tired,
but it does, I feel like, oh yeah,
you could really nail this now,
probably with the same footage.
I think don't nail it.
I think it's, yeah, and also you'd never wanna take away,
the real problem would be, and this,
I don't think they would do this,
but you don't want them to ever make it modern people.
There's something about this where you can,
even with digital projection,
which at some point it was updated,
you can just feel that these were just odd,
interesting, craggy face guys filmed in the 1960s
on 60s film, and I'm glad that retained
in the digital plus up.
Other than just maintaining visibility and brightness,
I don't want anything to happen to these bus.
Right, here, maybe I'll save this for the end.
I'll save it for the end, actually.
Okay.
But I was, yeah, looking at these and going,
yeah, I wonder, would it take it away?
Because it's interesting when we talk about upgrading
any of these old rides, because they've upgraded them
in little ways over the years,
but sometimes you're thinking,
when you see Hatbox Ghosts, you go,
oh, wow, they could really plus this thing up
in a crazy new way, but if it was all Hatbox Ghosts
level stuff, would some of the magic be gone?
Would it feel weird?
I kind of was like, maybe these bus could be upgraded,
and that would be cool,
and you could do some effects with it,
but I don't know, will it?
What do you want them to do?
I guess they could disappear and go different places.
I don't know, like you could,
like you could do Hatbox Ghost type effects with them.
I don't know.
But.
I don't want any of them to not be visible to me
in that part.
I want to see all five of these weird faces.
You could have them switch faces.
You could have, like that might be interesting.
I don't know.
But would some of the modern stuff,
would it not age well,
and would it get rid of some of the magic?
I mean, I think the different eras of technology
throughout the mansion,
in addition to the 100 or 200 year old magician techniques,
I think it all kind of adds to the weirdness.
It does, but some things age worse than others.
That's true.
The Bride effect aged worse.
I'm confident that Hatbox Ghost will look great in 20 years.
I could be wrong, but I think that will look good.
Yeah, as long as it's not married
to the technology of the era too much.
Right.
Some of the stuff that came out of Pirates was, I'd say.
Right, okay.
The other thought I'm having, I'm gonna save till the end.
Okay.
Got it, all right.
I wanna put you guys on your heels now, or your toes.
Keep on your toes.
He's gonna throw in whatever you say.
It might be so controversial.
It brings old Scott out.
It is gonna be a little controversial.
I just keep rocking back and forth
between my heels and toes, and I'm tired.
Well, so I'm sorry, but that's just-
You're getting your steps in while you're still here.
I am getting my steps in.
Who's gonna get you?
Scott or me?
I'm working.
I got lots of stretches I'm doing these days, so.
Now, we just named the people who,
the first set of actors who played
the part of the singing busts,
but we have to acknowledge who else
has played these five roles.
Oh, sure.
And I'm talking about when the singing busts do a cameo
in the fairly recent film Muppet Haunted Mansion.
There is an appearance from the singing busts,
and they pulled out all the stops.
For these iconic parts,
they got the five biggest stars in Hollywood
who all fit together as naturally as the Rat Pack.
They are all thick as thieves.
They make so much sense together,
and I'll kind of do this with a leisurely pace
so that the listener can shout them out with me
in your car or on a walk or wherever you are.
Henry Gibson.
No, all right, the five who are the Muppet Haunted Mansion
singing busts, and I know it's obvious, but here we go.
Skye Jackson from the Disney Channel show Jesse.
Canadian video game journalist Jeff Keighley.
Pat Sajak.
Justina Machado from One Day at a Time.
And Craig Robinson.
Phew, okay, you know, it just had to be said.
That's just fan service.
I mean, I know we all, we all know that.
We recognized them as soon as we saw them,
and they make so.
I don't believe they could be in the same room
with each other anymore.
Well, it finally proves they aren't all the same person,
you know?
So Michael Janet Jackson thing.
Like, can there really be two stars
as big and electric as that?
Why, no.
Pat Sajak is different than Jeff Keighley.
The natural, this is the, it's the most natural set
of first people offered.
Clearly, if you've, I've never seen more of a group
of first, first offers in my life.
And I'm so glad we have this Sajak now,
that he's stepped down.
Right, right.
So all we, the only, you know,
we used to have him every day,
and now we only have him on Halloween.
I think he's acting in a play,
but that's not permanent.
Pat Sajak is acting in a play?
I could be crazy, but I feel like I saw him,
Pat Sajak Theater plays, Google that.
So he's no longer Pat Sajak, he's Play Sajak.
New Scott, change Scott, that brought a tear to his eye.
That was so wonderful and so perfect.
Oh, that tear looks like a drop of blood
that will make you burst up.
Oh, he's ripening her act with it, yeah.
I'm still grappling with it.
There are ghosts inside me.
They are scrunching my organs
and making me bleed in surprising ways.
It appears that he is in something.
Wait, what the hell?
He's in, the play is a play of Columbo.
This is a, in Hawaii.
Pat Sajak, just retired, boy.
Well, it wasn't said in the title.
Is he playing Columbo or is he the killer?
No, I believe he is the, I think he's the killer.
The play is, this is so,
what layers unveiling themselves like a Columbo mystery.
This is happening in Hawaii.
It is called Prescription Murder
with Pat Sajak and Joe Moore,
the original Columbo mystery thriller
by the William Lincoln Richard Levinson,
the creators of the show.
This is a live on stage Columbo in Hawaii
and whoever Joe Moore is,
Pat Sajak's longtime buddy is Columbo.
So you can, it says buy ticket, just one.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna wanna bring my whole family to this.
Don't tell me I can only buy one.
When is this, oh, well buy, you know what?
This is gonna be applicable even way after this comes out.
Buy these now.
This is happening in summer 2025.
You can right now buy a ticket to go to Hawaii.
Well, that's a separate ticket.
You can go to Hawaii and see Pat Sajak
play the Columbo murderer at 2 p.m. on a Saturday in August.
Wow.
Prescription Murder is the pilot.
It was the first Columbo,
so I think it's an adaptation of that.
Do we know who was, is that what,
which actor, is that the I Spy actor who I can't remember?
Do we know who the murderer was in that?
It's Gene Berry, Catherine Justice.
It's the one where Columbo looks very young
because Peter, I just read this yesterday.
Peter Falk was 39 filming the pilot,
and when he filmed the final one
of that first run of Columbo, he was not yet 50.
Wow, wow.
So we, next year, Jason, wait, I don't know,
two of us, bleep that, two of us will be older
than Columbo when he started.
That's wild.
On the topic of the merger
of longtime television personalities in theater,
there's something that I wanna head towards,
but in order to do that,
I think we have to talk a little bit about the song itself,
Grim Grinning Ghosts, because if we're talking singing bus,
you know, this is finally,
it's not until this part of the attraction, correct,
that we hear the lyrics of the song Grim Grinning Ghosts.
We've heard, obviously, instrumental themes the whole time
for many years as we've been talking, but now.
Yeah, slower versions.
Yes, sturgy versions, and we even, and last year,
we talked about our kinda like
hoppin' graveyard jamboree version,
but now we are to the lyrics.
First of all, general feelings about the song
and the song with, I mean, it feels like
we must have sort of talked about it before,
but are we, and there's probably some broader conversation
of best theme park original songs ever,
but do we put this in the top five?
Do we put it in the top two?
How do we feel about Grim Grinning Ghosts?
Yeah, I think top five for sure is fine.
It's hard, cause like, stuff like Tiki Room,
I really, I enjoy a lot of that music,
but it's like, is that even,
has that penetrated the culture
like Grim Grinning Ghosts says?
I don't think so.
So it's like, I have to kind of also give it credit
for probably being pretty, like well known
amongst regular folk.
People that don't go to the parks all the time.
Sure, sure.
Once in a while maybe.
Yes, yeah.
Yeah, do we, do lyrics jump out in anyone?
Is there a part that you like?
Is there a turn of phrase?
Because I always liked it, you know,
we certainly talked several times
about the creepy performance by the very wet Maleficent
from the Disney sing-along tape,
which is, you know, was at the time
the best way to experience the song
outside of being on the ride itself.
And with the lyrics on screen and the, you know,
I forget if it was a bouncing pumpkin
that let you follow along with the lyrics,
I liked it as a, like, you know,
little snooty like to learn kid,
because I'm like, these are words I do not know.
Oh yeah.
These are big old words
and I want to know what they mean.
And they have to get real clever with the etherealize
and that's all of a vocabulary word
that I had to learn just because I like theme parks
and I'm nine years old.
Yeah, it's, it does make you,
it's like watching Star Trek when I was younger,
when I would just like, they would say instead of like,
to make a human, they would say procreate.
And I was like, ooh, and I remember I used the word procreate
in my like sixth grade and recess once.
And I was like, oh, look who's Mr. Smarty Pants.
He learned his word from Star Trek.
And you still, that's what you still call it today.
Procreation.
Yeah, that's the only reason you would participate
in the act, which makes you very uncomfortable.
I participated in procreation.
That relieves the entire thing
is you start calling it sex and there's a tawdry association.
No.
When you're doing it to have a daughter
and then close up shop.
Clinical, yes, clinical.
And it takes all the, all the grossness out of it.
It's just, it feels so functional.
Yeah.
And that's what it should be.
Sexual stuff should be functional.
You gotta done it.
Hopefully there weren't so many tries
that you had to participate in gross sex
more than you wanted to.
I've done it once to make a kid.
And then the other urges, I just do a little prayer
and those go away.
That's the hell, that's what I do.
Pray them away.
Little prayer, sing like a fun, funky song
like God bless America or my country.
A funky song?
A fun, funky song.
Yeah, or my country tis of thee.
You give it up for America.
Those are funky, I suppose.
Yeah, anything that's not the Star Spangled Banner
is a little funky.
Well, it lets people kind of improvise
and have a little too much fun.
Yeah.
Those songs keep you on track.
The song I like a lot because of like the call and response.
Like there's like different voices in the song.
So you'll get like,
Like it's up and down.
Yeah.
And like that always feels like a fun.
High highs, low lows.
Yeah.
It's Greek and the tombstone, it's one of the best,
most iconic, thorough voiceovers.
Yes, and it feels, I think that element also adds
to the party feeling.
Cause even if you're not thinking about it consciously,
there are so many like voices popping in and out
that it feels like, oh wow, there's like,
there's so many variations.
So I think that's helping give you the party feel
is the way they recorded that.
Very different personalities of ghosts
you feel just within the ones who were singing.
There's like, it's like almost like queen backup vocals
or something where.
That's true.
And with kind of like weird effects on them
and echoes and what have, wow.
Yeah.
It is kind of a,
but maybe there's no Bohemian Rhapsody without.
Stop being dumb.
Like stuff for somebody to love or like,
it is similar in the like,
oh, there's like kind of interesting background singers
or little parts that are different from the main vocal.
I kind of, you know, I will never,
now I will like think of queen the next time I go on this.
You're not incorrect.
Yeah, yeah.
So think of queen when you're on this.
It's kind of the original queen.
Yeah, and if Disney hadn't fully sold the queen catalog,
there would be a chance they would put queen on the ride
just because it's an IP they own.
But it's not gonna happen.
It's kind of a good idea to do like a live,
like just to experiment,
to do like a live Wizard of Oz Pink Floyd kind of situation.
The Bohemian Rhapsody takeover of.
Oh wow, yeah.
Let's see if you sync up to Bohemian Rhapsody.
Right.
Maybe you'd have to do some other.
You have to put in like some of the,
you have to put in like the intro of Flash Gordon.
Oh yeah.
To cover some of the early part.
So you could score each room with different queen,
but I imagine it's Bohemian Rhapsody in the end.
A full, I mean this is a good idea,
like a full like rock and roller coaster
that is part dark ride that goes along with a famous song
like Bohemian Rhapsody would be actually pretty cool.
I mean we obviously got it with Knights in White Sadden.
Yeah, that's the pinnacle right now.
That song we can sing every word of.
Don't even.
Oh yeah.
Even I won't make you guys do an impromptu
Knights in White Sadden.
Right.
But it's almost, did they do,
did Dark Dark Park have a Bohemian,
oh it was a Bohemian Rhapsody firework show is what it was.
But yeah, some song that Disney owns
that's like a top 10 rock radio hit
that everybody knows potentially could be cool.
I don't know if that'll happen,
but it is an interesting idea I think.
Well you know they're clamor,
they're gonna strike, if Epic Universe is a big success,
Disney's gonna strike back
and get an exclusive deal with The Weeknd.
They're gonna steal The Weeknd
from his Universal Association.
Right, right.
In turn, and what?
What's up for grabs?
Hey, you know what?
Song wise or other artists?
Or ride wise, you know.
You turn living with the land
into blinding lights, the ride.
Okay, yeah.
Starboy, what could that be?
I don't know, anything.
The restaurant. The Space Mountain, yeah.
The Space Mountain, yeah, Starboy.
That would be good actually.
And then take all of those,
take those theaters where they don't do much of anything
anymore, the movie theaters,
and just play episodes of The Idol.
Don't be a crowd pleaser.
Yeah, yeah, a couple of edits here and there I suppose.
But yeah.
Just check IDs at the door.
For time, right?
For time, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just to get audiences in and out.
In terms of Grim Grin and Ghost lyrics,
I always loved Spooks Come Out for a swinging wake.
Because I knew with swinging,
like when I was a kid, I think I learned what a wake was,
and then later on I heard that lyric
in Haunted Mansion, and I'm like,
oh, because they're all dead,
because they're, yeah, they're deceased
and they're having a party.
I thought you were heading towards
that you like the use of swinging,
because it's an area you've always been interested in.
Oh, well, just academically.
Again, it's a studious, it's more about the way
people intermingle. Sociologically, you know.
Thought experiment more than anything.
It's interesting how people do that, isn't it?
It's a thought, you know, thought exercise.
Creepy creeps with eerie eyes, yeah?
Yeah.
Because there's two, the alliteration twice,
the alliteration there, that's good.
These are wonderfully dense lyrics,
but don't feel overdone.
I think that maybe the funniest thing
about the lyrics to me is that now that, you know,
in talking about the narrative of the ride six years ago,
we probably last discussed the notion of segueing
from dark and spooky to fun and funny,
and the lyrics are clearly where they are getting,
you can feel a note given at some point of like,
you gotta represent both, because here's where we get
these kind of bet hedging lyrics about,
it's silly spooks and they pretend to terrorize.
Right, right, right.
Yes.
Was there a first pass which went more all in
on the terrorizing?
Yeah, because the pirates.
They murder you and terrorize.
Pirates are doing the bad things on the pirates,
but this one, it feels like they're making sure,
you know, these ghosts are not going to hurt you.
But there's no agreement with you and the pirates.
They may hurt you.
So that is a difference between the two.
Obviously the ghosts, like this could be anyone
from any walk of life, pirates have, you know,
dedicated themselves to a certain lifestyle.
So I do think that I guess that there is a difference
in just the clientele of the ride, but.
One of them might really hurt you by busting out a guitar
and doing some covers with Jeff Beck.
That's the biggest threat of how one of them could hurt you.
He's played with so many people.
I just got recommended like him and Gene Simmons
out of makeup doing what, rock and roll all night
or something.
Gene is trying to get him to sing with him
and he keeps like not paying attention.
I don't know where they are.
I don't know how old this video is.
America's ancient rock stars are trying the best they can
to rehabilitate Johnny Depp.
I know they are, all of them.
Yes, every single one.
I've seen him with every old guy over a certain,
like 65 or something.
They're all hanging out and they're doing their best.
They're doing their best to get him back.
But yeah, this is a fun party.
I almost wish that the ride vehicle would kind of
bump up and down.
I want it to have, I guess like a low rider, a car.
Because it's such a little jaunty little song
and I'm like, I want to kind of,
I bop naturally I feel like to it.
I don't know if you guys bop naturally
when you're hearing Grim Grinning Goose.
The listener can't see this,
but can you, what is bopping to you?
Like a little like this, like I'm bopping up and down.
A little bit like, it makes you want,
so I wonder if there, like a newer version you could like,
kind of the vehicle, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
You'd feel like that bass,
because that bass, like that stand up,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Like that really just makes you want to move.
Bass makes you want to bop, yeah.
Makes you want to bop.
So you don't want to provide your own bopping.
You want some of the vehicle to be doing the bopping for you.
Right, and as you know, I like a ride vehicle
to fuck me up a little bit.
And this is just still too smooth maybe.
And I want to bop a little during the Grim Grinning.
So you want it to go way slower,
but also fuck you up.
Yeah, well then this, I don't really want it to jostle me
like Transformers or anything.
I just, you know, if it could dance,
if the ride vehicle could dance a little bit,
you want to have a swinging wake when you hear this song.
And Pirates is a very much, oh, it's a fun song to sing,
but it does not make you want to move
like Grim Grinning Ghosts.
Grim Grinning Ghosts makes you want to move.
It's jaunty, it fits with the more whimsical Mark Davis
kind of second half of the ride.
Yeah, yes, so I guess that's a plus up.
I want the ride vehicle to dance a little bit.
Okay, so notes, beginning of the ride,
you move so slowly you aren't even sure that you're moving
by the end up and down.
Up and down like a low rider, yeah.
If it gets to get you close to your head
hitting the top of the thing.
Yeah, now they've done things where like you could,
there was like you could eat dinner in one of the rooms,
you pay like a grand or something.
I really want the ride vehicle to stop here
and you can get out and dance.
You are jealous of those teenagers causing a ruckus.
Well, I'm jealous of, well, no, I'm not jealous
of their like desecration of the room,
but if I was a teenager in the 90s,
I would have gotten out and just danced.
They would have had to pull me away
because I was like skinking or something like a ska,
like a ska concert.
Going to town like that extra mighty, mighty Boston's guy.
I've been like the yo, Boston's guy.
In this bumping, do you foresee them installing
a totally new ride system or are they retrofitting
the existing one? That's a good question.
I think you, could you install a seat
that bumps up and down, just a seat,
although where your head hit then
because it like is too elevated.
Probably.
I think I'll get Bob Gurr on the line
and I think Bob could figure it out.
Bob figured everything else out
and Walt would tell him, well, here's what we need.
Here's what you got to do.
And he would just figure it out
because he's an engineer and he knows what he's doing.
So I'll say, Bob, make these seats dance.
Well, what I would do if I were you would say,
because he's not, I don't know if he's going to listen to you,
my Carlson, a guy he's never heard of,
but if you say, Bob, it's Walt from beyond the grave.
I forgot one thing.
I had one last wish.
That is for the seats to Bob.
Okay. Get on it.
Oh, yep, yep, got it, skip.
Well, I'll do that. What are you doing here, Bob?
Ghost Walt called me.
I'll put a bust, I'll put like a bust outside his house
and I'll project my face onto it.
Oh, that's good.
And then I'll tell him to make it Bob.
But again, as in the spirit of the song,
you're only pretending to terrorize.
Yeah, of course.
Your hope is not to scare the hell
out of elderly man, Bob Gurr.
Yes, of course.
You're just trying to provoke some more great work
from this great man.
Of course.
And this is another room.
And I know I was, I often, I've said this on the,
hold on a minute, on the Small World episode
that I didn't like that you could sort of see
that you're in a big room.
And you guys, I think you guys convinced me on that
now that I've been on Small World a lot recently.
I do like that it's kind of like boxy
and you see the, like you don't need the illusion
that you're in some other place.
Cause Small World is all, it's little dolls.
Like that's kind of almost like you're in a big toy box
or something or you're in a big doll house on Small World.
But Haunted Mansion, I really like
that it feels pretty outside.
Like you do feel like you're outside in the scene.
Yeah, no visible ceiling, yeah.
Which you don't on the Jack Skellington version.
You can, it's lit up very, what is the word?
It's brighter.
It's brighter, that's what I meant to say.
Did you mean to say it's so weird?
No, I was just, couldn't think of a good word
and then Jason said it so then I did like a big moose voice.
It's brighter.
Yeah, that's what I meant to say.
And yeah, as a kid I would always like,
I would look for it, I remember.
I would look for like, this has to be a room,
but like sometimes you couldn't see it.
Oh, so you'd be on a night, maybe you are outside.
Here's something I didn't know.
Grim Grinning Ghost comes from a Shakespeare poem,
Venus and Adonis?
It does indeed and this brings me to a point
that kind of influenced by where this series is gone,
where Haunt Cast the Fright this year has gone.
I would say that Shakespeare has not come up on the show
terribly much over the years,
but it has in this series because,
and this was a second gate thing,
so let me fill in anybody who is not subscribed to that
and you should be, patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Nice.
Yep, fit it in there.
But Reese, in one of these other episodes,
there was discussion of Shakespeare because
Mike here was giving some consideration
to taking private Shakespeare classes and why?
Because he's suddenly interested in the,
not private, but a small,
a small limited time Shakespeare class.
Was this to broaden his horizons as an actor?
Well, possibly, you'd have to ask Mike,
but one of the things influencing this notion
was the teacher and would you like to tell us
who the teacher of the class,
you happen to be considering taking?
I thought about it last night.
I really, I forgot to even look into it.
I think it is too late for you now, this round.
But Armand Shimmerman who played Quark on Deep Space Nine,
Star Trek Deep Space Nine in Glendale
said he was teaching a Shakespeare class
at a theater up there.
I went looking into this, it definitely stuck with me
and I found his Twitter in which he just posts
the phone number to call to sign up for the class.
I love that.
This is at the Antaeus Theater Company in Glendale,
which, and in my case, as an aspiring Shakespeare fan,
had you heard of Antaeus before?
Mm-hmm.
Of course.
Oh yeah, I know.
You thought, well, you moved here
and you were like, huh, UCB or Antaeus?
Antaeus or UCB?
Yeah, yeah.
This class, and it is now too late for you to have done it,
but this would have been $425 for six weeks.
Sure.
A small price to pay to spend time around the actor
who played Quark.
That's a pretty fair price.
That's like UCB.
Yeah, that's cheaper than UCB.
It is, and for sort of a higher, all right,
but I thought it'd be valuable to read to you
what you would have been signing up for,
because I don't know if you read the synopsis.
Of what would have been asked of you
if you were to spend six weeks learning Shakespeare
to be around Quark.
Don't have the time right now, but you're going on.
Uh, so, Armand Shimmerman,
the esteemed Shakespearean scholar and teacher,
offers a six week class at the Antaeus Theater.
He is looking for new people,
so far you qualify, you're new,
interested in learning more about Elizabethan rhetoric.
You with it so far?
I hear you, I'm understanding the language you're saying.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, and you, I don't, you would,
I think you could stand to know more
about Elizabethan rhetoric, as far as I could tell.
Which he considers the Rosetta Stone
to not only understand the playwright's language,
but also acquiring techniques for communicating
arcane language to a modern audience.
This is exactly what Jason said would be required,
that it's not just learning the text,
but it's how to update the language,
which is a little obtuse, and modernize it.
And I thought I had some very good teachers in high school,
and, but I feel like there was not enough context
when we covered Shakespeare.
It was just kind of like, learn this, but don't,
like, it can feel very stiff if you're on about, like, the.
Yeah, here's the plot, here's the kind of stiff language.
It made more sense when I watched, like,
there's an Orson Welles Hamlet, there's also,
which I really do love this movie,
the Ethan Hawke modern Hamlet.
Oh, okay.
Julia Stiles, and Bill Murray,
and, like, a bunch of other actors.
Right, right.
Well, this is, again, this is why you signed up
for the Shimmerman course at Antaeus,
is to learn about Elizabethan rhetoric,
which is the Rosetta Stone to unlock all of it.
And that's what it's about,
not about getting to look at cork for several hours
for six weeks.
And also, you're gonna get his insights
into Elizabethan culture, medieval history, religion.
That sounds interesting.
What are some things you've always been interested in
on this show?
Well, I'd love to get into all of it.
It sounds interesting.
Maybe it wasn't something that previously
I've ever expressed interest in, but, but.
Given the right, you know, it makes sense.
You're into a music artist, and he delves into this genre.
Suddenly you wanna go down the path of this genre
and find out more.
And it's, yeah, hey, if, look, I'm a fan of his work,
his cork, maybe I do wanna learn about medieval history.
Right, maybe I wanna know that.
Maybe in a different life, or a different one,
different decade of our lives,
Jason and I would have taken this together.
Wow.
Do you think you would have agreed to this?
Ah, I think I would try.
If I paid for it, I paid for it.
Huh?
If I paid for it.
I mean, that certainly would have been
the icing on the cake, but I would have gone with you.
Look, I need a wingman.
Are you, like, wait to go on dates?
No, no, no, to get me in with Armand Shimmerman.
I think he's gonna be able to tell
I haven't even seen the Ethan Hawking.
The real problem.
I need somebody who knows 1% of a Shakespeare to join me.
The real problem is I would have had to work so hard at this.
It would have taken so much extra time out of it,
and I don't wanna disappoint him.
So, ultimately, I can't, unless I have the time to devote
to practicing Shakespeare.
But you could, you know, you just, like,
well, I don't know, you're more engaged.
I'm still picturing you with a little baby.
That's not what you have.
You're engaged with your daughter.
It's hard, you can't exactly be like,
all right, I'm feeding her in one hand,
and then in the other, I am learning about
what religions were thriving in the Elizabethan era.
Yes, exactly.
It's not quite that, but, you know,
there's still a limited amount of time.
And going, first of all, it seems hilarious,
me underprepared or trying to cram in the car on the way
into Armand Shimmerman's Shakespeare class.
You're eating Taco Bell in one hand,
you're trying to, you're, like, up on the dash.
You have, like, a really tiny type.
Your entire dashboard is taken up with a full soliloquy
you have to go do in six minutes.
I'm eating, shoving a Crunchwrap in my mouth,
and I'm trying to, like, memorize words I don't know,
like, words that are unfamiliar.
What has?
And then I'm just, like, I start crying.
I'm like, I'm gonna disappoint Clark.
Clark's gonna be so upset with me.
You see, I don't know the show.
Would Quark be, if he was upset,
is he a character who was upset a lot?
No, not really.
I mean, he was the bartender, essentially.
He's a Ferengi, and he's always kind of, like,
up to something, and, like, he's, you know,
I think he's ultimately a good guy,
but he, you know, he's up to some mischief,
and he's up to, like, deals, and he's bartering and stuff.
So he's not, like, he wouldn't be upset,
like, he wouldn't be upset in the way
I am worried Armand would be,
because just looking at Armand's Twitter and the posting,
I feel like Armand would be somebody who would call me over
and be like, Michael, I am so disappointed in you.
What you have done here today is a disgrace to the theater
and to William Shakespeare, and I don't say that lightly.
I've been teaching for over four or five decades,
and I just think that, quite frankly,
you should quit acting, in general.
Like, I feel like he's very, he takes care of-
Shakespearean or not.
The tweets.
I don't, I've never banned anyone from the Antaeus before.
There are no faces, do not admit this man,
but you will be the first.
We will make room at the box office door,
and your face will be the first plastered,
shamefully, on that wall.
But you don't think- I despise you.
There's room to fail and to soar in this class.
No, what?
No.
No, acting class, I hear you meant to-
We got a lot of work to do before he soars.
When you brought this up, I think the timeline,
if you had signed up for it, I think it had been like,
maybe it's two weeks before the first class,
and then you've only got a week in between,
in which you're very busy, you've got a lot going on,
and I think, yeah, I just don't think the time to soar
and to learn this complex language is gonna be there.
But I'm sure he would've been given a monologue
or a poem or something to practice.
I don't think you had to come in prepared.
Well, on each class you do, I'm sure.
By the time of week two, I'd imagine.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Mike would get away for a little bit
just doing kind of the free, like, what brought you here?
You would have to lie your way through that,
but that's acting.
That'd be, if you could get through the opening
where you kind of imply that you're interested
in Elizabethan culture,
and never say the word quark or Ferengi.
If you could survive that test,
maybe you could soar in the rest.
And then he would, like, mention an episode
or something where he had to do some of this
or some other character had to do some of this,
and I'd go, oh, excuse me, what,
were you on Star Trek, Deep Space Nine?
Oh, okay.
Oh, under the makeup, they under the,
you were one of the, what do they call those guys?
So you were swinging way too far in the other,
you're like, you're swinging between extremes.
This is the kind, maybe this is the kind of note
that Armin would give, is that you can't run,
every performance, including lying to an actor
you want to be around,
instead of just going to meet them at a Q&A,
the character has to be based in reality.
You know, this is a sort of comical deception
present in Shakespeare's comedies.
All right, well, you would have thrived in this class.
I think I would have loved this class.
You gotta say, well, maybe, well, you could still do it,
and then you just gotta like, you know, I don't know,
be there as some sort of like, Jason Helper,
you have to act like, oh, yes, he's my young ward.
I never go anywhere without my man servant, Michael.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
And he was mentioning he's aware
of some of your television work.
Did you fit in any television work in your time?
So he, am I his ward or his man?
No, I'm your ward.
No, no, you have to do Shakespeare.
Okay.
And as part of the plan, you have to pay for it
just to keep up,
because the name on the credit card,
it has to be Jason Helper.
It's gotta match, the three-digit code, too.
If you wanna pay him back later, fine,
but I think probably Jason just should pay the $425,
but then, yeah, you have to learn all the Shakespeare,
and Mike gets to hang out,
deal with your bags and personal effects,
and then you get to watch all of the classes
and stare at Armand Schimmerman for six weeks.
Look, I think if Jonathan Frakes was teaching a class,
it would be much more of an easy vibe,
where it'd be like,
Mr. Frakes, I didn't do any of the homework.
Ah, it's all right, don't worry about it.
Does the class wanna go out and get a steak
and I'll tell old TV stories?
Like, that's maybe more what I'm looking for.
But the seriousness, the passion,
which clearly are from that bio
that Armand has for Shakespeare,
but this is where, why I brought all of this up,
is that he's gonna do other sessions of this.
This will be a possibility for you in the future,
and I figured at some point,
saying grim grinning ghosts in context,
that was gonna happen anyway,
and it occurred to me this morning,
why not have Mike read it
and give you the opportunity to prove
your potential prowess as a Shakespearean actor,
which could then flesh out the entire illusion
of you just wanting to be around cork for a while.
Oh my God.
Oh, I truly thought this was going to end with me
having to read this poem.
You know what's funny?
I was my, again, this was in my notes from last year,
and I was like, probably I'll hand it to Jason,
and that'll be something.
And then I was like, wait a minute, no.
Jason is not the aspiring Shakespearean actor,
it is Michael.
No, and much like the class,
I've been sitting here reading it over and over.
In preparation?
Yeah, because that's how I dress.
Now you're like, this is what Scott's leading to.
This is what that weird tone's all about.
No, no, no.
This is how I prepare for acting class.
I end shows and stuff, I beat stuff into the ground
till it's meaningless to me.
But I can do it.
All the spurks.
By instinct.
It's also hard to know even what you would,
what a voice do I affect for Grim Grinning Ghosts
and a Shakespearean.
Yeah, I don't know.
And you have a question when you arrive at it,
which is kind of in the middle of the stanza
from Venus and Adonis,
that do you kind of blow past it?
Do you not act like it's the name of a song
that you like from a ride that you like?
Or do you really hit it?
It's really up to you, but I think this is,
if you ever had to point, if Armin got you in a corner
and said, you don't care about Shakespeare, do you?
And you'd say, sir, I have nothing but respect for you,
but you're incorrect.
I, in fact, have performed Shakespeare in an audio medium.
I will produce this tape for you if you wish.
Flavor, style.
I also like, one of my favorite things
is so many people on Star Trek
are very accomplished actors.
Yeah, right.
And they do know all this stuff
and they can recite their favorite passage
or maybe a whole play or whatever.
And then you're cut and they're like,
hey, you want some Romulan ale?
Give it to me, I'll get you.
And like Patrick Stewart, very accomplished.
Mr. J. Todd, the Romulans, what do they want?
And you're like, I worked so hard.
But pronouncing Romulan and Ferengi correctly
is kind of like saying some of the
Shakespeare terminology correctly.
So I leave it to you now to regale us.
So this is Shakespeare.
Yes, this is part of, it's one of his early poems,
Venus and Adonis, that happens to have a phrase
that we know and have talked about in this episode.
Here now, Shakespeare aspiring Elizabethan actor.
Could I do it like Quark?
Yeah, I think it's up to you.
Hard-favored tyrant.
It's totally your call.
No, hard-favored tyrant, ugly, eager, lean,
hateful divorce of love.
Thus chides she death, grim grinning ghost.
Earth's worm, what dost thou mean?
To stifle beauty and to stealth his breath?
Who, when he lived, his breath and beauty set?
Gloss on the rose, smell to the violet.
That's a cold read, folks.
And then what do you, if you, I mean,
Jason, feel free to do this, but you could,
does anybody feel like they could do what Armin,
or actually what Quark would say in response to that?
Can you do a Quark?
I cannot do a Quark.
Also, is that the, that's the second A from the poem?
I don't know, some of it.
It's part of it.
You might say I did a little Control-F
to find the word grim.
Oh, sure.
Got it from there.
What do you think he would think?
Who cares?
Bunch of nonsense, that is.
I can't do a good Quark.
I really should have a better Quark impression.
It's pretty good.
Give yourself some credit.
No, I don't want to give myself credit.
Wow, well, I don't know.
Did you think it was moving?
I thought it had a lot of range.
Like the song, there was some low and some high.
It had dynamic spikes.
I thought it was pretty good.
Maybe you could sell your way into doing this class.
Yeah, I would love, if he does it again, we'll see.
If he does it again, I mean, look,
it's good to test yourself sometimes.
And yeah, maybe, is it helpful to test yourself
when you're around somebody who was on one of the Star Treks
from the 1990s?
Yes, that's extra good.
It puts the heat on you.
You really want to perform.
Now what'll happen is that some podcast,
The Ride Superfan, is gonna keep an eye on the classes
at the Antaeus Theater.
They're gonna pretend they're interested in Shakespeare
just to be around you.
So then we got a class, we got a little chain
where there's Armin up on stage,
and then you're staring like a wide-eyed puppy at him.
And then right next to you is some guy
who doesn't want to admit, I'm assuming guy,
who doesn't want to admit.
Yeah, let's be honest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Doesn't want to admit that he knows you
from podcasts, The Ride.
Yes, I'm the Shakespeare, I've always loved Shakespeare.
Yeah, I love that guy.
Oh, do you love a podcast?
Shakespeare Bob.
Oh, I see you on Star Trek?
I don't know.
This is wild.
I'm learning stuff.
Geez, I'm so blinded by my love of Shakespeare.
This hypothetical person has taken every,
there's so many Star Trek classes at this point.
LeVar Burns teaching a class in there,
and like Marina Surtis is teaching a class.
Scott Bakula has one from Star Trek Enterprise.
Oh, I love Bakula.
Bakula, Avery Brooks is materialized,
he's teaching a class.
Yeah, so every year.
Are these all in LA?
This is a joke.
Oh, okay.
I truly thought you were tracking all of the acting classes
from Star Trek. I wish it was just the Star Trek theater
teaching acting classes all from the cast.
I think you could find it.
Well, like, I mean, I follow these people on Twitter,
but I don't know that any of them are teaching acting classes
other than Armin right now.
To sleep, to sleep, a chance to dream.
Look, I will take an acting class
from anyone who was on Star,
I mean, there's still a couple original.
George Takei acting class, forget about it.
Shatner, Walter Koenig, come on, the three.
This is the chance that you have.
Unless some of these other people start classes,
and I just thought, you gotta follow your dream now
while this one is present.
Well, your dream is just mere miles away at the Antaeus.
I hope I got you closer to being here.
Thank you, yeah, I appreciate that.
Look, the media landscape, popular culture
is always shifting, but the theater is eternal.
Much like the Haunted Mansion.
This guy, yeah, this guy needs to take
Shakespeare classes, I think.
I mean, yeah, I think you excel the most.
He's the one who randomly in some episodes said,
we tread these boards as a defense
when you said something we didn't understand.
We tread these boards.
I said something equally archaic, yeah.
When somebody, he throws Shakespeare at you.
That doesn't sound like me at all.
He throws Shakespeare at you when he's cornered.
He's the weirdest dick when he gets nervous,
he gets Shakespearean.
He throws Shakespeare at you.
Well, that's all something, do you wanna close out,
you had this controversial idea.
Well, I don't know if we should do it next year
or the year after.
We did an episode recently about fixing Tomorrowland,
and I said, we gotta do more of this.
And I think we should do the same exercise
where we each take different assignments
and we talk about the Haunted Mansion.
Some of, and I don't know if we figure it out later,
but walk through the Haunted Mansion
and what do you change, what do you keep the same,
what do you fix, what don't you fix,
what do you make worse?
Now, I think old me would have been on edge about this
because what you've just described
is an excuse to go all the way backwards
and do everything again, even though I'm not sure
we are out of the graveyard now.
We're not, necessarily. It doesn't seem like we are.
But new me, changed Scott is touched by this idea.
Oh, great.
I think that as, now that I'm backed into a corner,
yeah, let's, now I know I didn't have any ideas
about how to change the bus,
which I think are great as they are.
I welcome this.
I say, let's go all the way back.
Next year, when we have, now that we're taking our time,
let's go through, let's look at every hedge.
Let's go through the gift shop and let's talk,
why not talk about every single item again
and point to it and say change or keep it?
Maybe, because there will be,
I think the queue will be ready next year
and the gift shop will be ready next year.
Maybe we could do queue, gift shop,
and then hitchhiking ghosts and the moving walkways.
Finish it out and then the following year.
Changed me is into this declaration.
We go through, just because it's a tidier way to do it.
Then we go through and we each maybe figure out
a different assignment.
Budget, we each have a different budget.
Then we go through the Haunted Mansion
and propose our different changes to it.
Sure, sure.
We'll do another version of this sometime
in the next 12 months.
Not Haunted Mansion related, because I enjoy the exercise.
But, 2026 is fixing Haunted Mansion.
So we have now delayed doing,
presumably, the Disney World one.
Yes, delayed.
We've delayed doing Phantom Manor.
Yes, we've delayed it.
This all gets delayed.
Delayed nightmare.
We haven't talked about if Phantom Manor
is technically a separate thing
that we could do elsewhere in October.
We'll talk about that in 2026.
We'll do a lot of planning and how this will work.
Great, well, Changed Me cannot wait for this excuse
to go all the way back through and do it all again.
Now, I can't promise that I'm not gonna change again.
We'll see.
Two years is a lot of time.
It is, yeah.
I just hope you dab that blood coming out of your eye,
like the tears are.
It's a lot of them, and it's a real steady stream now.
You'll have seen it, Robert.
I'm better, I'm improved.
There's increased blood flow in my head.
I want it to be coming out of me.
This doesn't indicate any rage
that I've been suppressing unhealthily
for this entire interminable episode.
You'll have seen if Robert Downey Jr.
is doing an accent or not by then, by 2026.
So you could be different.
You'll be different.
Maybe I'll be talking like that accent.
Maybe we all will.
Oh, $100 million to do like a Boris Batonov voice.
I hope that is what it is, yeah.
I hope.
I think he doesn't know.
He'll be talking like Rodney Dangerfield.
Wow, he took it.
Boy, actors take inspiration from the weirdest places.
It's Dr. Doom, it's like Rodney.
Dr. Doom does not get any respect.
He kinda doesn't, though.
He doesn't get any respect, that's true.
So, yeah, we'll see.
Yeah, that's what fuels the character,
and we can't wait to meet him.
Well, a lot happening in 2026.
A lot happening in 2025, in which Mike,
without even me pressing at all,
with my hands off the wheel approach,
you've now committed to finishing
The Haunted Mansion next year.
That's wild.
The episode-
Jason Sheridan has not said anything in protest,
therefore he signs off, and as soon as I say,
you survived haunt cast the Fright,
that closes the door, at which point
there would have been,
we would have been able to get protest from Jason.
What I would like to say is,
that episode could be five hours long.
So, well, Change Me usually likes to get these done
in a tiny amount of time.
That could be a double episode of time.
But Change Me has nothing but time.
Nothing but time.
I don't have anything else going on.
Time enough at last, you know.
Is that Shakespeare?
That's Twilight Zone.
A lot of Shakespeare stuff.
All right, well, I guess, for now,
you survived haunt cast the Fright,
and when we push, I guess, confusingly,
some of the graveyard, not even sure what's left.
We'll find out next year.
Into next year, yeah, but wow.
This is the first single room
that will have taken three calendar years to get out of.
And you know what, the more we extend it, why not?
Because I don't, you know,
now it's become such a tradition that I really love,
is that, you know, getting to post these,
wondering what the world in America
will be like a year from now.
I hope we do so many more Haunted Mansion episodes
that happen to come, you know, within 10 days
of Donald Trump potentially being the president again.
Because this guy is, you know,
he's gonna live till he's 110,
and they're gonna run him until he's 110,
no matter what happens.
So you think we have, like, our Haunted Mansion
and Trump election season gonna meet
at least three more times?
It depends on us and it depends on him.
It could be three, it could be seven.
That's true, we don't know.
So it's all ahead of us.
Everything's ahead of us.
Dr. Doom is ahead of us in more trouble.
Well, it's what I see now,
and it's why I've taken this relaxed attitude.
I'm so happy, I look forward to the future
and to just chilling out and hanging out with you guys.
For three booness episodes every month,
check out podcasts throughout the cemetery gate,
or get one more booness episode on our IP tier, Crypt 3.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And boy, it's just nice to exit this thing
in a relaxing, non-concerning,
Old Scott returning, Old Scott returning.
Oh no!
The Ghost House Warrior returns to remind us
of Hitchhiker Ghost, who we soon meet,
Ezra Bean for Mr. Phineas Bluff,
and gods, I'm finishing it!
What funny names!
All right, all right.
In a series of various,
I don't know, all of us,
we have our two muggies,
and we see a smuggler like Brian,
who tells us to hurry back.
It's finished, it's done, now you're mine.
Okay, okay.
Jim Lee drew X-Men.
You're bleeding, I don't put up with names anymore.
Frank Quietly, new X-Men.
Time to bleed, fellows.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com,
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.