FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcasts may contain
surprising sheet cakes,
eye contact disagreements,
evil little laughter,
and trivia questions about Walt Disney World drainage situations.
All that plus, Jessica McKenna returns to talk about the Disneyland app
on today's podcast, The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
a theme park podcast whose lore is as hard to navigate as the Disneyland app.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hi! Yes, very difficult to navigate both.
Yes.
We have a lot of unnecessary animations that really slows everything down
and heats your phone up.
Yeah. I was thinking about, I actually was thinking about this.
This joke must have come from the fact that I was listening to Doughboys earlier today.
And I was like, yeah, they don't throw out as many weird references
that must confuse a new listener.
We're like, there's like, yeah, it's a theme park podcast,
but they talk about Grandpa Munster a lot.
And there's lore about Grandpa Munster that they are talking about.
What do they mean? I just want to hear about The Ride.
I just want to hear like, does it go fast or slow?
Tell me if it goes fast or slow and if they like it.
Let me ask you a question.
Is this integrated marketing for Doughboys?
Is this like on the office when they would talk about their new HP computer?
So you think I'm advertising for Doughboys right now covertly?
Yeah, yeah.
But trying to make it seamless?
For our friends. Yeah, yeah.
I wish it was doing that because they would be paying us, right?
That's how it works.
Correct. That's how integrated marketing works.
I guess, no, it's not.
I'm just giving them a free plug and saying their show is funny.
Let's bring in our guest from the off-book podcast.
I can barely say it because it's so good.
It's Jess McKenna is back on the show.
It's been ages, Jess. How are you?
Yeah, Jess, welcome back.
Oh, thank you so much for having me.
I have a lot of opinions about Doughboys.
Oh, go ahead, please.
No, I don't.
Love Doughboys.
It's good.
Today we do have a very important topic.
Yeah.
And I'm not saying that facetiously.
No.
This is a topic that, so Scott is gone.
This is an episode that we've been calling it Scott Free.
Here I am getting off.
Scott is on hiatus.
Yes, you're getting off Scott Free.
We've been getting off Scott Free for a few weeks now,
being little rascals, talking about all sorts of off-topic things.
Exactly. You get it.
Oh, yeah.
I don't even need to explain it more.
No, no, no.
We do have a little giggle that happens,
a fiendish little giggle that happens.
But people probably will see the title of this episode and think,
oh, this is Mike and Jason getting away with something
they've wanted to talk about for a long time,
and Scott has been stopping it.
That is not the case.
Not true.
This is a guest-suggested topic.
Yeah.
Disneyland app.
I pitched this.
You pitched this.
Yeah, I think we talked a couple, like two months ago maybe.
And boy, I was so excited because Scott would be here if he was not on hiatus.
He would be doing the episode with us.
But that gave us the license to do it.
And now people are going to think that we're doing something.
This is not like a recess appointment when Congress is gone
and we just get to force something through.
Topical.
We're at friends, Mike.
I love talking about recess appointments,
even not during the hellish few weeks of politics that we're going through right now.
I'm a big recess appointment joke maker.
I make this reference a lot.
All right.
So I just want to be on the record for liking that joke.
So yeah, you texted and I said, is there anything you want to talk about?
And you said, Disneyland app.
It was like the first thing.
And my heart swelled.
I was so excited about it because, boy, have I want to talk about this app forever.
And we've talked about it in little like pieces,
but finally we're going to dedicate three, four, five hours,
however long it goes to talking about the Disneyland app.
So yeah, Jess, tell us why this was your choice.
OK, so I think, you know, we share.
I love theme parks and I love Disneyland.
And I love giving people in my life a positive experience at Disneyland.
Yes.
I take that role very seriously.
I grew up 15 minutes from Disneyland.
I can hear the fireworks from my childhood home.
I like grew up with an annual pass, you know, used to go a ton.
And I've watched like, you know, if people come here from not growing up here
or they only got to go to like Disney twice in their whole growing up,
whether world or land, and they don't have the like dexterity of knowledge
that someone who's gone a bunch has. Right.
So it falls on you to be the leader because, you know, you have the ability.
But what I have found is that the app is just like I just end up feeling
so like handcuffed to this like completely joyless experience with
because you were saying when you get the goods, it feels amazing.
Yeah.
So it's like a double edged sword because obviously it's created like a certain ease
because before the app, I was also the person in the party who'd be like,
give me all your tickets.
I'm going to sprint to Big Thunder to get us fast passes.
You're not going to move through the crowd as well as I will on my own.
You guys take your time in the trail line.
Meet me like meet me back at Star Tours.
I'll one person getting back through the lines, not the end of the world.
Go get in line for Star Tours.
I'm going to sprint over to get fast passes for Big Thunder.
You know, I would gamify it that way.
And that was a little more exciting.
Maybe that was also age, like maybe I was like 17 showing like cousins
from out of town around or something like that felt exciting or like my first summer
back from college, my college boyfriend came out and I was like,
you're not going to believe how well I know my way around here.
And that, you know, there's a certain pride in being able to do that.
Pride and be able to be a good guide for disneyland.
People are like, oh, it's going to be so crowded.
It's going to be so tough.
And you're like, hey, I got you.
I'm going to minimize the negatives and optimize the positives.
But I think just like everything else in our society, we fall into this like
faux trap of maximum optimization that is depriving me of the joy.
Not to mention that I'm here with my nephews and niece wanting to make glorious
memories and I have to have my face down in a phone literally the entire day.
Yes, yes.
That all that rings a lot.
Very true to me.
I still feel like on some level I'm the hero of the group and I still feel like
I went with family a couple of weeks ago and Rise of the Resistance had been
closed and all of a sudden we saw it was open and like we now have our daughter
with us, but she can't obviously go on that.
She's not old enough yet.
But I just start yelling at the family.
Go, go Rise of the Resistance open now.
I'll stay behind.
I'll watch her.
Don't worry.
You haven't done it yet.
So like I'm still, I feel like I get my like hero moments here and there in the
park, but I've always felt like I wanted to be the ambassador because how many
times did you run into somebody go, why do you go that often?
Yeah, totally.
And you go, go with me.
Yes, you haven't gone with me.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Because like I don't know what it is.
My sister like didn't get bit by the bug.
Like my mom was a great theme park mom.
This was back when like the only navigation you had to decide was which way you
started the circle.
Are you going down mainstream?
You starting left?
You starting right?
You know, like that was the big decision.
And then you worked through the park.
However, however you want it.
I would choose chaos back then.
Really?
Watch.
Well, I would go to, I would like, all right, we're going to tomorrow land and
then we're going to cross the hub and go to adventure land.
That's totally reasonable.
Just trying to hit.
You're trying.
Exactly.
You're like, can we sprint to Space Mountain and try to get it and then start our
circle the other way?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Totally.
And my brother and his wife love, love it.
They going once like in a February break with my brother, his wife and their
three kids and my mom, they have gone to world a bunch.
Yeah.
My sister-in-law was, that's the only time I've gone where I felt like I had a
partner in the app where she like knew how to navigate it too.
This was also right.
Coming out of COVID where you literally couldn't get food without the app.
Like, yeah.
Yeah.
So that was also a dark time where you'd be like, seriously, I just want a
skewer from Bangle Barbecue and the next opening is three 20.
Yeah.
And I can't just like walk up and get a skewer.
Remember this?
That was a dark, a dark time.
One of the darkest parts of the pandemic.
Yes.
Was I just couldn't get a skewer at Bangle Barbecue.
And not to mention you couldn't sit anywhere around there.
Yes, right.
You had to kind of roam.
You had to roam.
The most annoying thing was going out to cast members and go like, hey, I'm a
little early, but can I get my skewer?
But they were probably more annoyed by me banging on pots and pans when they
delivered the skewer to thank them.
They let you bring pots and pans into Disneyland.
Yeah.
If it's to thank essential workers.
Yeah, of course.
Which I still do every day.
My neighbors hate me.
And they're all essential workers.
Yeah.
They're like, I worked the most insane double shift and you are waking me up.
Yes, please stop.
Please stop.
Yeah, that has gone back down a little bit, which that part's OK.
Yeah.
The fact that you can maybe pre-order food or I still find the reservation
game extremely hard to crack.
Like everything's always gone by the time I've bought tickets.
Like in terms of if I wanted to reserve it, like a sit down restaurant.
But then, like, I'll just walk up and they'll be like, yeah, we can get you
into Oga's Cantina.
Like I feel like they can always get me into Oga's Cantina.
Right.
You can. Yes.
That is something that happens a lot where you look at it and it says you can
come back in six hours or you can ask a person.
But then what I've noticed lately is that if you sometimes like refresh, you
can get different times.
Like there's a couple of different places in Disneyland where you can just
add yourself to the wait list right there in the app.
Right.
If you're close enough.
Yes, you have to be close.
You have to be inside and you have to be close.
But if you refresh it, sometimes the time will change because some other people
will have their time in like their cart essentially on the map.
So then they'll let it go.
And all of a sudden it was 60 minutes.
Now it's 15 minutes.
So then that's another element that I just started picking up on recently.
Another element to checking that both satisfies my brain, but also makes me
have a worse time.
Right.
So because you're looking at your phone.
I mean, I think I always bring up is there was a time at Disney World and I
would guess it's between like 2010 to 2014 and they were really trying to get
people off their phones.
You know, the iPhones are starting to get like mass adopted.
Android's coming out.
The first few Android phones are out.
And so they're like, all right, we'll put little games in the queues for people
to play.
We'll put games or statues with plaques and like an interactive stuff.
And by 2014, they're like, no app.
Use phone.
Yeah.
There's so many.
I don't know.
I guess they were like people get these animals get so bored in this cage that we
need to do something to entertain them.
So they tried having like exterior things to have fun with and that didn't seem to
work.
And then they did the phone thing.
And then it was like there was that space mountain game you would play and you
could get to the front of the line if you won.
I don't even remember.
But it was the worst game you've ever played in your life on your phone.
And like it took up the whole time.
Yes.
In line.
And meanwhile, most people in line, if they're like in a big family group,
they're just playing like heads up.
Yes.
Everybody's playing till still there was a time when I feel like I saw every
other four people, but now it's like still pretty popular.
Yeah.
But that is more fun than at least you're engaged with everybody.
But this was some like game where I'm like flying a rocket and I'm trying.
I don't even remember what it was.
My favorite was when I was like in second grade and Indiana Jones came out and I
would just, you know, wait in a two and a half hour line as like an eight year
old.
And that was just the reality of the situation.
And they gave us these AT&T sponsored decoder cards.
The decoder cards.
Yeah.
And that was like pretty fun to be like, yeah, yeah.
This message says drink water.
It's above a water fountain.
That's funny.
You know, like that's the other part is like taking my nephews and nephews
and niece, if they have to wait for 20 minutes, they're like, oh, this line.
And I want to just like scream.
Yeah.
Because I'm like, I, well, your parents have spent so much additional money to
keep you from having to wait in a line, you know, and, and I'm not their parent,
but I'm like close enough to be like, Hey, absolutely no complaining.
This is a very expensive day and people are working really hard to make sure you
have a good time.
And they'll be like, right, right, right, right.
But how much longer?
Like, so they'll catch themselves on tone or like, right, we can't complain,
but they still don't internalize the Disneyland used to be.
Right.
You had to wait in so many long lines and you were lucky if you got on.
Seven, seven, right?
Like I can now curate a day for them where they get on 15 rides, you know,
get to repeat.
You have such knowledge and ability.
Eight year rides.
Yeah.
That they don't even realize how good they have.
No, they don't.
And this is my daughter doesn't know this.
She's two years old, but she doesn't understand that daddy's giving her a
better situation than a lot of these kids with parents that don't know shit.
Right.
Well, that's the other thing is, is like the knowledge gap keeps getting bigger
and bigger.
And like, there's these cottage industries about like, okay, you're not
good at it.
I'll make an itinerary for you.
And like, yes, right.
Right.
And just the, and then not to mention the financial bummer of like, okay,
so now you're just assuming that everyone has to have a smartphone.
Like, yeah.
And you're rewarding people who have more money, who can buy a $20 front of
the line ticket for rise of resistance for part six, spend 120 more dollars to
get to the front.
I mean, the like bummer capitalism side of it is like pretty tough versus
like everyone used to get a fast pass.
And as long as you could work them correctly, you'd get two or three a day.
Yes.
And it would help take the edge off the absolute longest lines, give you a
couple of breezes.
And then you spent all of the time in between that waiting in lines.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's everything of course is being done because the, the, the like
business people are just trying to figure out the right configuration to
steal as much money out of everybody.
And all it's doing, it's like, it's meant to confuse and steal, I guess it's
meant to confuse and like vacuum money out of your pocket.
And it continued, like it's continuing.
There was like talk of like, oh, maybe the reservations will go away in like
Florida to some degree.
They've gone away.
Disneyland still has the reservations for like, for just even getting in the
park.
And now, now of course there's like a $400 tier of fast pass that is like that
just gets you on every ride, which honestly in some ways that is a better
insult.
It's better in some ways because like it's a lot of money.
It's too much money to spend if you're already spending money.
And it's just like, you don't have to look at your phone all day.
Yes, exactly.
Like you're paying for the freedom of, of not having to think so hard about
this.
Right.
But like, if you buy just regular lightning lane and you're surfing your
phone all day, which is what I do.
I feel like I'm in like Mission Impossible.
I feel like I'm Simon Pegg.
I'm Benji in Mission Impossible.
I'm on my phone.
I'm doing it the whole day and I'm, I get dopamine hits from it, but then
everybody else gets to enjoy it.
So you just, I justify my disengaging from the group.
Disney does have the entity working against you.
The villain from the last movie.
I know the entity.
I know the Mission Impossible lore.
We all know the entity, the very, very understandable villain of Mission
Impossible seven part one.
It was like part one, but now it's not going to be called part one.
It's going to be called, it's just going to erase that.
It's going to be retroactively.
Good.
Yes, but the entity, but Disney's entity is shitty too though.
It's a bottom of the ocean.
It's a nuclear submarine at the bottom of the ocean, but it's also video
art at a weird European party.
It was a club.
It is a club as well.
Yeah.
The entity is a club, which I like that part a lot.
They're the greatest movies on the planet Earth.
They're my favorite movies.
Just to address a couple of things that have come up.
Jess, you'll be happy to know that today, Lightning Lane for
Riser is actually $27.
Good, good, good.
The other thing is that first off, I've had this app open for about
maybe like 45 minutes and I think it's already taken my phone from 90%
to 74% and the other thing I was going to say, oh, the reservation.
So the park reservations, there is a button in the app.
It's buried in a spot and it says park reservations.
When you click on it, it opens a browser window.
You can't just build that into the app.
Jason, this is one of the things that I am upset with this thing every day.
You don't have, it takes you to like GoDisney.com, which is a thing we've
threatened to do an episode about forever, is that Disney bought Go.com
like 20 plus years ago and all of its infrastructure is built on Go.com.
Some bizarre thing, some useless Michael.
It was an Eisner purchase, right?
It was an Eisner purchase.
One of his rare elves.
Flawless except for GoDisney and then Mickey's Kitchen.
I went to Go.com and it's just a rich text website to links to all the
different Disney departments.
That's amazing.
And then Disney also, if you want to use a gift card, you have to go to
DisneyGiftCard.com, plug in and then plug that into your app.
I mean, the way that they don't talk is like this past summer when I
played captain for my sister and her three kids, she got those tickets
through like a family friend connection who has a Club 33 membership.
So he gifted us tickets, okay?
I had to, there was no way for me, a human, to take that reservation
and import it to an app.
Oh, right, right, right.
I had to, which meant like, if I didn't know any better, I was going to
I would have just shown up that day with these tickets and then not been
able to access anything.
I think you can do it at retcon once you're in the park, but it meant I
couldn't make any reservations.
I had to get them to merge this with, I don't know, I had to talk to a human.
A human had to do it for me.
And they were like, can you give me the receipt for this purchase?
I was like, they're Club 33 gift tickets.
And they're like, okay, let me like backdoor this time one, and like, you
know, had to create a fake reservation, something for me to even be able to
use the app because those things don't talk well to each other.
I've had difficulties before where it's like, if I bought a ticket, you know,
like me and I bought me and my husband's tickets and then my brother bought his
families, but actually I want to run the app all day.
Merging the reservations is not as intuitive as you think.
I had to eventually scan their physical tickets to put it all in one app
interface so that you can, because you're not just going to get Lightning Lane
for two of you, you want to get it for the whole party.
You know what I mean?
And I've had like tons of like running into weird corners there where it ends
up taking you to your Safari browser.
It's like not within the app.
And you're like, this should all be in the app.
If you're making me use the app, it should all be in the app.
I had to update for an annual pass monthly payment.
I had to update my credit card, which you have to do by calling.
That's crazy.
Or to change it on the internet.
Like it's crazy.
Like it feels like if Ethan Hunt was up against the entity, but the entity was
dumb and bad and like shitty and it would like just fuck up once around.
It was built on 30 year old software.
Well, the day that I went this past summer was the day that they switched from
Genie Plus to calling it all Lightning Lane.
So, but it was still like that meant it made it some of the reservations in
lead up kind of confusing.
Cause you'd be like, well, my Genie's telling me to do this.
And they're like, just so you know, Genie won't be here tomorrow.
Or like Genie will still be here, but like it's not called Genie Plus anymore.
But the tipboard I find to be like a such a patronizing interface.
Like the tipboard is so.
Oh yeah.
Cause that's the, they were plugging the idea that, oh my God, Genie Plus
you'll pay for, but Genie regular will tell you what to do.
Yes.
He'll give you all kinds of tips, which will be like, have you thought about
getting a balloon?
Like it's so stupid.
Or they're like, are you aware of a topia?
And you're like, yeah, I'm aware of a topia.
Like if everything else is broken, all right, a topia.
Like.
Yeah.
It was acting like the AI would just like direct you to like things with no
line and like it would like glide you across your day.
Or, but it's like everybody, I don't know.
And maybe they don't, but I'm like, everybody has this base level of
information.
Don't they?
Most people do by this point, like the Genie Plus, the tipboard, and then it
wouldn't be where your things were.
You'd have to click on the other.
You know what I mean?
Like the tipboard versus like your itinerary would not be like, they
wouldn't be talking to each other.
So wouldn't be like, why don't you recommend for me a snack after big
thunder, knowing I'm going to be on big thunder about two 30.
Why don't you be like, Hey, you know, you can just get fries right here at
this walk.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like the tipboard wasn't actually tipping me anything good.
No, it would be like, check out this ride or this or this parade or this
show.
And it's like, I already did those things.
I just didn't tell you I did those things.
Exactly.
Or you could tell me like trivia, or you can tell me like interesting things
to do in line, or you could tell me a lot of things that would enrich my
experience.
But what you don't need to tell me is like, have you thought about booking a
princess encounter?
I'm like, no, I haven't.
And I don't want to.
I'm already here.
The best is when they would direct you to like ready-made Apple music or
Spotify playlists.
And it's like, I can search that.
And when I'm home, I'm here now.
I'm here now.
Exactly.
Or like it didn't ever, if you really want to like do my tip board, you
should know that I have a park hopper and you should be telling me, Hey, now
is a great time crowd wise to switch parks, save things.
You like to come back later to this park.
Why not make it a sandwich type day?
You know, like stuff like that.
Although I know that was for strict for a while where you had to only switch.
There's still kind of a thing.
Like at 11 AM is when you're allowed to switch.
You can't switch.
You get arrested.
But you can switch back, right?
Yes, you can.
Yeah.
Can I just mention, cause you said the phrase and you haven't, I don't think
you've said the phrase.
And since we did a country bear jamboree, you said, you just said, I'm here
now, which was your famous song.
I'm here now.
And we did the country bear jamboree.
So if anyone thought I was not being sincere on the country bear, on the
actual jamboree.
Yeah.
And if you end that lore, we need to, we need to maintain that.
Yeah, we do.
Yes, we do.
That's lore.
Yeah.
This has been kind of lore free so far, as far as the writers concerned.
That's our version of the Disneyland app.
It's like, okay, so this is lore for an episode of another podcast that we
made an appearance on.
It was kind of tangentially related to our country bear jamboree.
It's a pretty good episode.
It was very fun.
It was a blast to do.
I laugh at that song you did.
Like every six months I listen to it.
Okay.
Cause here's, here's what I bring to the table for musical improv that a lot of
people don't bring.
And that is a panic.
Oh, everybody brings that.
Yeah.
That's the eternal flame.
It read as a character, but you were the most, were like, I don't know if I can
do this.
And then yours was like the most harried, like, but that energy was very good.
It was thematically correct.
Yeah.
For the country bear.
I feel like there are just seven prompts to what you're describing with Jeannie
Plus where they would just like rotate them.
It was, I'm sorry.
There's probably a dog here on that or something.
That's all right.
But yeah.
So do you want to go like, go, I don't want, cause there's some stuff in the
app I'll say I like.
Sure.
Like, you know, yeah.
I mean, we could go through, like, if you just go on the app, isn't that
listeners, if you have the app, open it up, I suppose.
Cause we'll, we'll, we'll go through it.
Cause I don't want it to be, cause this could easily descend into just, uh,
making fun of the app.
And like, you know, I want to, I want to both sides of the app.
Oh, I don't have, I don't, I need the upgrade.
How long do you think it'll take me?
I don't know.
It's probably on the network, whatever your network is.
Um, but I mean, you can see my, my phone.
It's not like we have to be.
Um, but yeah, they give you like the first things that the first thing you see
when you open up the app is that they're trying to sell you the lightning lanes.
Right.
It's either the $36 one, which is the multi pass or just the premiere,
which is the $400 upcharge.
Which my girlfriend thought.
It's $400 on top.
Yes.
$400 on top.
She thought it was all included.
I was like, no, no, that's on top.
400 per person.
Per person, not per party.
Yes.
Right.
So it's 400 per person.
That is inconscionable.
Did I say that word right?
I think you said inconscionable.
You probably meant unconscionable.
Yeah.
It's that.
It's yeah.
It's so yeah.
$400 for today and the next few days.
Uh, it's a person.
Yeah.
That's so horrific.
So depending on how many people you have, it might make more sense to get like a guide,
which is still, I forget how much that is.
And that's very expensive, but it might make more sense.
I forget.
Um, but yeah, that's, that's if you don't want to work, that's the no effort choice.
And it depends because like, is the effort on a 12 hour Disney day when you're taking
a friend from out of town and you want to give them the best day, how much actual physical
labor and effort am I putting in?
How much is my time worth?
Is it $200?
Is it 300?
Like, I don't know.
It's hard to tell.
Yeah.
I mean, it really comes down to group size because that, if it's just you and your friend,
that's still $800.
Yes.
Like, so that's not-
I mean, I'm never going to do that.
That's not worth it to me.
Unless I like win the lottery, I don't think I'm ever going to do that.
Okay.
So today's plans, the icon next to it is still a genie.
So-
Yeah.
We really ran the character genie through the mud for this thing.
Because we talked about this, we did an episode a couple of years ago and we were talking
about how like, why are you tying a beloved character to this failed part of your app?
Yeah.
It's also like, he's free.
He's free and now-
And now you're basically putting him back.
Back in the lamp.
You're putting him back in the lamp and that's not right.
No, it wasn't right.
And now I guess he's free again or he's dead.
I'm not sure.
Pretty easy going day right now at the old D-Land 20.
Yeah.
I'm seeing some short lines.
Now that's a thing I like.
Yes.
I like opening up the app and seeing what the waits are and imagining I'm there enjoying
a light line.
Yes.
Obviously the map and like wait time, that part's great.
Like that's easy.
I cannot believe it's $400 a person.
That is so nuts.
Showtimes.
Okay.
Virtual queue.
I've not been able to successfully get in a virtual queue.
Really?
I always was just fast passing or paying for, or I guess lightning lane.
They're not, nothing is called a fast pass anymore.
Right.
There's no fast pass anymore.
It depends.
Virtual queue right now is easy to get for Haunted Mansion Holiday, which you still have
to get a virtual queue.
You cannot join a regular line because the queue is still under construction and the
gift shop is under construction, but that's pretty easy to get.
I finally got on a Tiana preview because I have the magic key, but that took four different
tries, four different day tries.
What'd you think?
I haven't said, oh, are we saving?
I like it.
Okay.
I'll say that.
I said I like it, but I'll.
The early T was not enough drama to the story.
Well, I will give a little hint of my feelings is that if I have one complaint is there's
not, there's no tension in the spot where you go up.
Let's have a, that's what I had heard.
There's not like a, that moment used to be terrible.
Bunny is tied up.
This is very scary.
This is like, and those vultures and the tension under the clip going up, very scary.
And you know what?
We're saying it.
We're not giving our kids enough scares.
I said this last week.
This is a common thing because like Snow White scary adventure, which they changed to Snow
White's enchanted, whatever enchanted wish.
I don't know what it's called.
I like the new version of the ride, the dark ride, but they did take away a lot of the
scare stuff.
So I do feel like we got to scare these kids.
These kids should be scared a little more, even though I was afraid of everything as
a kid.
But look at the man I am now.
Look what it made me.
Oh, I wrote thunder.
I wrote a Matterhorn till I was like 12 with my eyes closed because the Yeti scared me,
but I still wrote it.
Right.
It didn't keep me off the ride and I didn't look into his eyes on Indiana Jones till I
was like 21.
Mara's eyes?
Look into my eyes.
It is your destiny.
You had a blue moon before you looked into the eyes.
I just put my eyes down.
I just say, I'm not looking at that guy.
Do you still look into Mara's eyes now?
No, I do.
Or is there part of you that still is a little weird about it?
No, I look into his eyes.
I know it's just for play.
Now I know.
But sometimes it's fun to play along.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Sometimes it's fun.
Jason, do you look into Mara's eyes?
Sometimes.
But not always.
Sometimes I'll just look at the other doors and then I get to look into the eyes but not
be scared.
Mara, the big Mara, not the little Maras.
It's the Maras above the door that you get in trouble.
No, big Mara.
No, big Mara already.
Indy is already out, isn't he?
No, that's after Mara.
Okay.
Oh my God, Jason.
It's over the door you're not supposed to look.
No, it's inside.
Don't look into Mara's eyes inside.
Am I crazy?
It's right before you go through the doors.
It's right at the beginning.
Yeah.
It's the big Mara head.
Yeah, yeah.
He's saying though, you know how there's three doors and they used to rotate, which was cool,
but it was the same track, obviously.
But then when you go in and see the giant Mara, that's why it's hard to not look at Mara.
Yeah, I would just look down.
Okay.
So you always thought it was the little Mara eyes?
I thought it was the little Mara eyes because you're seeing the different-
You know what we got to do now?
Indiana Jones episode two.
Well, we've been teasing it for years.
And we've got to do it soon because apparently there's been a miscommunication here about
what it is, so we have to do a second episode.
Now I'm calling it, I'm calling our shot now.
Let me just say, Haunted Mansion Holiday, no more virtual queues left, no more stand,
no standby line, no lighting lanes available.
Well, it's 4 o'clock, so-
I guess so.
But you can comfortably, the thing is, the virtual queue, you have to get up at like
7 a.m. and do it in Disneyland, which is just sucks.
Yeah.
Okay.
So you can do virtual queue before you get there.
You have to be on property.
So right now, again, Scott is getting a piercing headache just from us talking about it far
away.
He's like, ah, he's like clutching his body.
Because he has so many thoughts or he doesn't want to talk about it?
Because he doesn't want to talk about it.
He doesn't want to talk about it.
He gets physically ill when we start going-
Because it's too stressful?
Yes.
He hates any of this.
He, I've seen him get, I was working on figuring out a problem with the app.
I saw he physically got up and walked away.
He's so like app averse and talking about all this stuff.
He doesn't like any of it.
So I'm just imagining now he knows that what we're doing to his podcast right now is talking
about this and he's having a physical reaction.
So virtual queue, generally speaking, 7 a.m. you get up and you get that one if you're
not in the park.
And then there generally will be a noon chance as well.
Right.
And sometimes even a further three or four.
I remember this when Rise was like, when you could first go back, COVID had to be a California
resident.
They had the like, at 7 a.m. you have a chance and at noon you have a chance to get in a
virtual queue for Rise or WebSlinger.
Yes.
WebSlinger.
Not good.
Disappointing.
Okay.
I've said it a hundred times.
If you want to make a ride based on Spider-Man, well, what's the thing you want to do with
Spider-Man?
Fly.
Suffer.
Oh, fly.
You want to get like broken up with on the ride or something.
Yeah.
You want to disappoint him.
I want to have the moment where I go, oh no, my scientific mentor is the villain.
Yeah, right.
You want a revelation of some kind.
But the way down the list is shoot your webs like bullets.
And it's just not good.
It doesn't work.
It does.
It's too hard.
Yeah.
The Spider-Man ride in Islands of Adventure, way better.
The best.
Jason's favorite ride of all time.
My favorite.
It's really good.
Yeah.
It's still really good.
I hope it lasts because it's gone now in Japan.
So there's one more left and I don't know.
We'll see.
A Rise of the Resistance type Spider-Man, I mean, obviously Rise is a massive footprint,
but the movement is like the Spider-Man Islands of Adventure ride leveled up where you're in
a thing.
Now, I don't really like a 3D component, but it works pretty good.
Yeah.
And you're moving around.
It's almost like a similar movement feel to Rise, right?
Well, yeah.
It's just that that ride system, like Spider-Man Transformers, and the way I put it is that
that ride system fucks you up more, which I like.
I feel like Rise of the Resistance, I have a few complaints about it, and one of them
is that it doesn't feel like you're getting jostled enough because it's so smooth.
It is smooth, but the drops.
Yeah, the drop stuff is cool.
I didn't mean like when you're getting shot.
The drop to give the sensation of flight and swing, I think, would be awesome.
Yeah.
Man, I think Rise is maybe perfect.
I don't know.
I've said it on the show before, but I have a couple problems.
We don't need to re-litigate it.
Yeah, in general.
It's just I wish the ride vehicle messed you up because my body doesn't feel like it's
under attack like it does on Indiana Jones or Transformers.
I think I still get it from the stop starts, like when you're going in between the cannons,
stop start, stop start.
Well, that's the best.
Yeah, it's my favorite one, but those don't work anymore.
What do you mean?
The cannons don't work.
They're stuck.
They're not moving because they're so big.
I think both coasts, the cannons have stopped working.
They're so heavy and they did move with such force.
Apparently, they shook the foundation when they were a little off once.
I don't know that it's never coming back, but I've seen people say it's never coming
back to working.
I don't know.
Well, hopefully that's wrong, but we'll see.
But those don't work.
That is my favorite room because that feels like a crazy thing.
Yeah.
And it feels dangerous.
It was very startling the first time.
And the drop is great.
At the end, you mean when you go, yeah, yeah, that's a fun.
Yeah.
It locks into a different ride system.
I just it's so smooth.
That Wi-Fi controlled thing is so smooth.
I just like Indiana Jones.
You come out of it and you go like, ah, my neck messed up.
But I want that.
I want my neck to be messed up.
See, I don't want my neck to be messed.
No, I love Indy.
Indy, I love.
But like all of the, there's basically half of Universal I can't ride.
It just makes me too sick.
There's so much stuff that's 3D.
Yes.
Yeah.
I had the talking about Rise of the Resistance.
I had the like, go, go.
You haven't done it.
My dad and brother came out to visit last fall.
And we were down in Disney World end of 2021.
And any time we tried to do Rise, it was down.
Yes.
And I had done it out here right opening day.
And I felt so bad for them because it was like, I mean, it was chaotic.
It was chaotic down there in 2021.
So it was like, you know, under a little more understandable.
But I'm like, you have to get on this.
Yeah.
This is amazing.
You had to get on this for you're out here now.
Yeah.
It should be working a little better.
I took two friends around last April.
And I really fucked them up at the beginning of the day in a way that they basically couldn't recover,
which was that I was like, we can get into Oga's Cantina.
It's the only place you can get alcohol on the Disneyland side.
We did this right as we entered the park at 8 a.m.
And I was like, let's get a fun, blue, funky cocktail.
Super fun.
I love the Cantina.
I have a great time every time I go there.
And then I took them on Smuggler's Run and they basically didn't function.
You know, the like combination of two alcoholic drinks on like near empty stomachs early in the morning
and a very like herky jerky, hard to track visually ride.
So the day was ruined in some ways in many ways.
Yeah.
And this goes to the like pressure of being the leader.
We still had a great day.
I like didn't push anybody to go any faster than they needed to.
I was like, I've been here a million times.
Like there's nothing that I need to do.
If you don't want to go at this pace, we can let's go like walk around and do something different, you know, mix it up.
But at the end of the day, like one of them made like a completely innocuous comment and I like completely snapped at them.
I was like, I was like, you have no idea the pressure I've been under all day.
Actually, I can tell you exactly what I said.
I said, oh, man, I just feel like at this point you understand why getting a hotel would be fun because I would just love to get some honk shoes right now.
Oh, yeah.
What do you think I mean when I say that?
That's some a little nap, a little sleep.
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
They were like some honk shoes.
I was like, yeah, yeah, some Z's, some sleep.
That's what it honk shoe.
It's a cartoon way to describe.
Like a looney tune.
Yes.
Like if they're not imagining sawing wood, they're imagining snoozing.
Exactly.
And then I laughed good naturely.
I was like, I guess that's not as clear cut as I and my one friend said, yeah, she's explaining it like we're the dumb ones.
And I was like, the implication there is that I'm dumb and I have just navigated an entire day for you.
So actually what I did is I went quiet for like 20 minutes and then the drive.
I was like, I have to be honest.
That really hurt my feelings.
I have to speak truthfully to you, my two college friends in our late thirties right now.
I didn't appreciate that after a day of navigating your day through the park.
And part of me blames the fricking app.
Like it blames the like the pressure to navigate and optimize every moment.
Yeah.
Means like even when people are grateful, you're going to feel like I can tell you who had the least fun today.
It was me, like the mom who doesn't get to eat a hot meal in 20 years.
You know, that's how I feel at Disneyland because of the damn app.
The app heightens the like right before like happy hour, like the 3 p.m.
to 5 p.m. like drag where like everyone's trying to eat or take a rest or like get on a ride.
And they're trying to push through if they're not resting.
And it makes me also like I've always been like a land Disneyland lover because of growing up in Southern California.
And I haven't ever done like a big proper world trip like my brother and sister in law have.
And I was like, you know, this also is putting into sharp relief the difference between being people who vacation at Disney versus people who visit Disney in their regular life.
Right.
Because if you're vacationing there and you're going to multiple parks each day, you maybe aren't you maybe don't need to pedal to the metal each of the parks each day, especially depending on like the age of your kids.
You could be like we are going to go back to the hotel and take a nap.
Yes, we literally can do that.
And it can be part of our design.
If you're visiting as a day tripper, you're like you have to suck every moment.
And the more money you spend, the more you feel like you have to do that.
Yes.
And it's but like you said, when it hits, it hits.
Well, that's the thing.
When you pull it off, you go, thank God the app is here because I could fix this for us while we all stand in line.
Well, we're all having a little break to have a churro.
I can get ahead of this.
And that's the best part of the day with my nephews and niece was when we saw a bunch of ducklings.
Right.
Well, that's always the stuff.
Weird little stuff is usually what's the best.
That being said, though, in Disney World, and I said this, I think I'm sure on the podcast, when I pulled a frozen fast pass a couple like whenever we were there a year ago, that it goes those go fast.
So you got to be checking, checking, checking, checking.
And it took me an hour.
I was on it for an hour and I pulled it and I may as well have gotten this Pulp Fiction adrenaline shot in my heart.
Like, oh, my God, I was so excited and I got it.
And then I was the hero of the day.
And that's the evil of the app because you do get addicted a little bit to the thrill of the chase.
The artificial scarcity.
Well, I mean, I guess it's artificial in some ways.
But yes, you do.
Yes, there's there's that's the thing that keeps you coming back to the app, unfortunately, because I wish I could just say, no, don't worry.
Like, obviously, if we're taking a two year old, we're not doing we're not going hard.
We're not doing we're waiting to see poo and Tigger.
Yeah, that's the thrill.
So that's fine. But if a person comes in from out of town, we're doing it.
And I'm both like, oh, man, I'm going to be on my phone the whole time.
But then I'm like, I'm going to be on my phone the whole time.
Yes. No, I listen.
I agree. And I've been that person for countless groups for years.
Right. Do you think and I'm not this isn't a challenge.
I feel like I would I could challenge somebody with my abilities.
If we had a contest at Disneyland to see who could get the optimize the app the most.
And you don't have to take me up on this.
But we've talked about this before, where I wanted to when we thought Jeannie would actually be an AI that told you what to do.
I was ready to compete against it. Man versus machine.
Absolutely. But it's nothing.
I well, because and I thought when it was first announced, they were essentially going to give people some access to their crowd monitoring software.
Like not the whole thing. Well, they can.
Yeah. Smart enough to tell you like, oh, this this land's really bad.
Maybe try this land. Yeah. Sure.
And that's not really what it was. Yeah.
But I do wonder, like, what percent what percentile am I in?
This feels like a sport to me now.
I feel like you're well, I mean, there's so many blogs and like things and people who are really good at it.
I'm sure you're still in like the top five percent.
Thank you for saying that. God bless you.
Because, like, I feel like I have once I'm there, I feel like I can intuit it because I also have I have some like internal metronomes of where I think crowds are going.
Where I think a parade or a lull or the little kids need a break.
Now's the time or hey, this time is going to be hard.
Save a big ride for your last ride of the day if you really didn't get it.
All that like stuff that's just internal clock stuff.
I feel like I do that.
And then the app adds to it right where it gives me access to more more lightning lanes where I'm not sprinting around the park anymore.
But I don't feel like like I didn't know the virtual queue thing because like when I tried it, when it was covid rules, I remember being really rigid about it and then like striking out and being able to do the noon one, like not getting the early one.
Right. Being able to do the noon one.
And then we got on a rise and it broke.
Right. And then we got tickets to come back to go on rise later in the day.
You know, like so I would still put myself only maybe in the top.
I don't often meet somebody who seems to have a very similar feeling to me about it.
Like it's not a common thing where I run into somebody who like hates and loves the app as well because they feel so important, like not important, but like feel like I have to be in charge.
I have to take control of the of the day.
So could we have a podcast about like invitational where we invite anybody who wants to see if they like whoever gets the most rides during the day off of the lightning lane, whatever the thirty two dollar one wins or something like was there.
There's got to be a way to structure that and then like have people far and wide across the land.
Anyone who thinks they can compete against me.
I love it.
Challenge me and I'll say I will beat you.
I will take you down.
The best thing would be also to go when it's like terrible.
Yes, you have to go on a summer day.
You have to go during spring break.
You have to go like, you know, you have to go a really, really like intense, intense day.
Yeah, whatever the worst day of the year is like Super Bowl Sunday is kind of bad.
Usually now people don't watch Super Bowl.
They go to Disneyland because I feel like that's the that's where I appreciate the app is like, you know, that's just the time of year that my sister and her family can come visit is the summer.
And I'm like, when we were growing up, we would never go in the summer.
You know, that's when the that's when the out of town rubes go.
We're going on like a Tuesday in March when it's drizzling.
And so that is where I really do appreciate the app because I remember going one like lead up to Christmas time and it was like you couldn't walk.
And then you're like, man, it really is hard to have fun.
Like you could try to have a good attitude and keep your expectations managed.
But like when you really can't even navigate basic spaces because it's so crowded, it's very, very hard.
And so to be able to throw a little money at the problem, if you're really if you're with family or friends who really it is a scarcity thing, they're only going to go once every couple of years.
Then you're like, OK, I can throw money at this problem and try to like make a better day.
Whereas I'd be facing a really horrible day otherwise, you know, like I've seen the toughest insurmountable crowds.
Yes, yes.
I mean, that makes so much sense, because obviously if somebody can only travel on this day, so we have to go that day.
So we have to do it.
And that always again, I feel like I would get a little more excited being like, oh, it's going to be bad.
Let's see what we can do.
Let's see what we can squeeze out of this tough.
It felt like because, yeah, a lot of people are like, oh, we got to go.
My mom especially was like, oh, is it going to be crowded?
And I'm like, doesn't matter.
I get I get really cocky, I guess, when we start talking about this.
But yeah, because I because it's given me a sense, finally given me a sense of control in my life in a lot of ways, I guess.
Because, you know, you can provide at least a certain minimum of a day now.
You can get like, hey, we might not get on everything.
We might have to wait in a couple of long lines.
A couple of the lunches like might be, you know, your experience walking around Main Street at certain times might be a little more crowded than you thought.
But basically, I can give you a good day, which is different.
Did you know you said this earlier?
Did you know you can like drink at a couple of different places around New Orleans Square now in Disneyland?
No.
Because I didn't realize you can drink a beer.
Where was I?
Would you tell me?
You weren't with me, but I texted you.
I.
The one right, the Terrace.
Is it Riverbell Terrace?
Riverbell Terrace.
I had like a little vegetable thing with some like tomato sauce on it.
I had a big beer.
I'm watching the Mark Twain go around and they went, well, this is interesting.
Interesting.
Yeah, because for the longest time it was only Club 33.
Yes.
And then Ogas Cantina.
Yeah.
I mean, which is hilarious because on California Adventure, you can get alcohol every foot.
It's so funny.
Well, right.
And you could go.
Everywhere you walk.
It's just like, here's more alcohol for you.
Right.
Because that's why it doesn't make any sense.
I honestly, if they were like, you know what?
It's all dry.
We don't want it.
That evil alcohol should be here.
I go fine.
That's your.
But I can walk a hundred feet.
Yeah.
And drink as much as I want.
California Adventure is.
So I hesitate to.
I don't want to like, I am going to Disneyland and I am going in a group with a guide for
the first time.
Oh yeah.
I've done this once.
And I am a little bit like, is this going to break me forever?
Now obviously it won't because I have my own nostalgia, my own love, my own dedication
to the park, but I'm about to experience absolutely no resistance to a day.
Like no lines.
Everything is like, I won't be in charge, which would be like incredible, but it's only
for a few hours, you know?
So it's like, I think we get the guide for like three or four hours maybe.
Yeah.
And then I'm like, literally what happens after that?
Will we have tickets?
Will we even use the app?
Because like we wouldn't have used the app prior.
Like should I start getting lightning lanes for the five or six o'clock hour because we're
not going to have a guide anymore.
You know what I mean?
Maybe.
Yeah.
Or I think that the group that I'm with won't care.
We will have written everything under the sun.
They might also give you a few complimentary for when the guide's done.
That's probably what will happen.
That would be choice because it's also kind of big.
It's like eight or nine people, which is like, that's my other question is, has the app made
you more or less strict about group size?
As far as inviting people along?
I mean, obviously you take what you take when it's like your family or friends who want
to go.
Like I've always been like, oh, four to six is like ideal.
I mean, two is a fucking blast, but like it was nice.
Yeah.
But four to six.
You're still you're having fun.
It's reasonable to navigate.
Yeah.
I mean, a big group obviously is a heart is harder.
I've never put any restrictions on it because like again, I when we bring the two year old,
it's not like we do this.
So I haven't yet tried to do the whole family optimization day.
I haven't done that yet because that's like imagine the scarcity then.
Like you really are going to get 10 fast passes, lightning lanes all at once.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Where you have to keep checking.
And it's harder because because of course, when they run out, you still can get them,
but there's only there's not going to be a there's a worse chance of getting seven versus
two.
Right.
Yeah.
So that's the difference.
Even numbers are the thing that I'm like, oh, two or four.
It's going to be easier.
Yes.
We had a group.
I remember going when I went in the summer as a party of five, but my youngest nephew
is only was at the time four and a half.
And so there was a couple of dining reservations where I just like tried to make them for a
party of four and be like, you're going to you're going to turn us away with this little
kid.
And then they wouldn't because they were like, yes, just like one more little kid.
Right.
Yeah.
It's not like you showed up with four other adults.
Exactly.
But it's crazy if I went on the reservations before like trying for dining reservations,
the amount of things that were open for parties of four and not for five.
And you're like, man, that's one more seat.
That's so crazy.
That's a little that's a little sneak.
I do.
Yeah.
Because if you go, I can't get a reservation five, but I can get one for four.
And then you just do like a little, can I add a child to this?
Yeah.
I well, for years, that was a thing I loved was like, you would just call a phone number
and you talk to a human and they'd be like, OK, well, it's a little full for lunch.
Do you mind eating at like a late lunch, three or four?
And like, no, that's no problem.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, great.
And now it's just in the like, it's near impossible to get like a Blue Bayou reservation.
Right.
Mm hmm.
But you can still go and ask.
Yes.
Mitch went and asked once.
Scott and the Doughboys.
Yeah.
Mitch Magic.
The Mitch Magic.
He showed up and just asked politely.
Mitch just showed up and asked.
And it worked for Mitch.
The ultimate hack that I used to be able to pull back in my day.
So when I was in middle school, I had an annual pass.
And but you would also you could.
This is back when fast passes were done by barcode on your physical ticket.
Yeah.
And so you could when you were just checking into the park, you could be like, oh, can
I have a physical ticket?
Because I like it.
Right.
Yeah.
They would give you a physical ticket.
And I did this a couple of times with just one other friend.
So we're a party of two.
And that meant we had double fast pass abilities.
Oh, right.
Right.
Each had.
Two barcodes.
Yeah.
So we could be like, use our annual pass barcode for Space Mountain.
Right.
It gives you the window when your next one's available.
Use your other ticket.
And no one cared about two 13 year old girls pulling this.
Did you feel were you scared doing it or were you just like elated because I would be both
elated and scared.
I think at 13.
I think I was scared.
One time we tried to like really overreach and be like, I bet we could also additionally
go up to lines and be like, I have a fast pass, but she dropped hers.
Yes.
Yeah.
And that felt a little more like bald faced lying in a way that felt a little worse.
So we only tried that once because the guy was like, OK, but that's something that they
can avoid now with everything being on an app.
You know, you used to really be able to be like, yeah, you wanted me to keep track all
these little papers.
Oh, it's one of these little papers.
I'm sorry.
And they'd be like, you're right.
Like, it's kind of a lot to keep track of all these little papers.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, and you just make it look like you're about to burst into tears.
Yes.
No cast member wants to deal with that.
Because what's it matter?
One more person in the fast pass.
Yeah, whatever.
Like, who cares?
It doesn't matter.
They created the name fast.
I mean, I assume Michael Eisner, it came to him in a dream, like everything else, everything
good that he made.
And then they got rid of this IP.
That's their IP.
And they're not using it.
We all just want to call it fast pass.
Let's pitch a TV show called Fast Pass.
I would love to.
There's so much Disney Parks IP they haven't pitched.
Dude, I think, Zach and I tell you this, that we tried in just like a general meeting with
Disney to be like, we love Disneyland, anything that, you know, and they won't tell you what's
in development.
They're like, if you can guess it, we can confirm or deny.
We're like, can we have a list of rides that aren't currently being developed?
And they were like, no.
And we were like, OK.
Big Thunder Mountain.
They're like, already being developed.
We were like, Tiki Room.
We were like, Matterhorn.
They're like, already being developed.
And we're like, but it can't go the other way.
You can't tell us what's open.
They're like, no.
Well, if memory serves me correct, I was a week away from going on a Zoom with you and
Zach about Country Bears, and they canceled it.
Yes.
They were like, never mind.
Wait.
Never mind.
Like they discovered someone working at it in a closet somewhere.
Probably.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it was like, oh, yeah, never mind.
I was asked about rights for a movie.
I was like, who has these rights?
It's a 20th century Fox movie that is now also Disney, you know, because they've merged
or whatever.
And it was funny.
People we know have the rights.
Which is always like a funny situation.
I'd be like, I wonder if they still care about this.
And like, should I just email them and be like, you still care about this?
Yeah.
Which I might, but.
Yeah, it's worth a shot.
The amount of stuff, though, that they were, I've said this recently too, the amount of
stuff where it's like, oh, this is in development and then you never hear about it is like,
how much money have they spent on every single property to not make it?
So much.
So much money.
So also I think that they, I don't know that there is Matterhorn anymore, but Expedition
Everest, which might be is in development and that might be too similar, you know, like
now.
You think it would be.
Yeah.
So it might be like that, that one out.
Hey, this just remind me.
I've not yet been on the Mickey train.
Yeah.
And I hear great things.
I'm a big fan.
It's great.
I'm excited.
That'll be.
It's rare that I have something new at the park.
Yes.
And the queue is amazing too.
Like there's, there's like artifacts from cartoons that are now in real life, of course.
And I, there's one from Lonesome Ghosts, which is like my favorite.
And then I saw this thing.
I won't, I don't know if I'm spoiling it.
Like I saw this thing from the cartoon and I was like, that's cool.
I got so excited.
I have basically not even ventured into that section since Toontown.
Like do you, do you, do you guys remember when Toontown for, well, I don't know your.
I didn't go when it, I was in, I never went to season until I was in my early twenties.
Okay.
Same.
We're Disney World boys.
Right.
So when Toontown first opened and you will, you could wait in like a mammoth line to go
through Mickey's house and it was like crazy.
And Goofy's house was just a bounce house, which was pretty fun.
And then they had this, they had this thing that I absolutely loved, which was just like
a topiary garden, but the topiaries were bouncy.
Oh, that's cool.
And they got rid of it.
But that was like one of the only things it would be like, Oh, if you have a bunch of
little kids Toontown is fun.
And there were like a couple good restaurants in there would be like, Hey, go have lunch
and your little kids can run around things that are actually more like a playground that
from like being cooped up waiting in lines.
Yeah.
There is less.
I guess there's still some stuff like that.
There's one in California Adventure that's like, well, Grizzly challenge trail.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I, these are two, we are big fans of the challenge trail and just before I had a child,
but now especially having a two year old wants to run around.
Yeah.
I'm in Toontown a lot now.
I mean, it's good that we need these, we need these third spaces.
We need.
It's not just about work.
We need more third spaces.
In Disney.
The back of Toontown now with fake grass and fake rocks is where we usually go and let
my daughter run around and pick up leaves and run them to grandpa.
Great.
And then as soon as like Pete shows up or Daisy, I pick her up, we go over there and
we meet the characters.
Cause that's like a really easy spot to, there's not a long line cause they just kind of pop
in and out.
It's a dead end.
Yeah.
People aren't venturing back there that much.
Like Goofy just came out and we walked up on his porch and Goofy's like, like this will
come on up here.
And like we were first in line.
That's great.
And we hit like four characters within like 10 minutes.
It was great.
So, and, and I would say even Toontown though, with the new changes they've made to it, it's
like, it's even, it's, it's more, obviously there's a big ride you want to go on now,
but I feel like there's enough for parents and children now.
Whereas if I didn't have a kid, I would be going back there a lot more because before
that Roger Rabbit once in a while, but that's not your prime.
No, no, no.
And I'm really not, it's, it's also the dead endness of it.
Like I'm basically not even venturing to that section of the park unless I'm going
on holiday small world.
Yeah, sure.
I'm not even going past Matterhorn on that depth of plane, you know, I'm cutting it off
like right there.
That used to be me.
You know?
35 minute wait for Runaway We're All Away, not too bad.
It's not that bad.
Yes.
And they play little music versions of like Eye to Eye from Goofy Movie.
Ooh baby.
There's a lot of good parody posters in the queue.
Yeah.
It's easily one of the best rides.
I'm excited.
It's, it's, you don't, you don't get a new one that often.
Yeah.
Yes.
Not often.
Um, so yeah, go back, especially with a kid.
Um, but can we?
Sorry, I just had, no, I just had a quick memory of going this summer where we, my littlest
nephew who is now five, but was like, you know, not five yet, but he's very tall for
his age and he, so he can go on almost everything, but he's scared because he's a little guy.
So we were like, let's just take him anyway and maybe it'll be okay because you never
know.
That's how I got treated.
Cause I was the youngest of not only like my immediate family, but also like the cousins
we would go with, they would just kind of be like, you have to go cause like no one
wants to wait with you and like, that's the way of it.
As soon as you're tall enough, you have to go on it.
You have, I never got to like sit out for being scared ever.
And so it's very much like, I don't know, maybe you'll like it once you're on it.
Maybe you like it once you're on it.
And they would not, they made us take him off because he was so big.
Oh no.
We're on which ride again?
On guardians, which maybe he wasn't too scared for, but he was okay.
You mean calving before it started.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
They didn't stop the ride.
No, no, no.
He was okay in the queue and his brother was like, I'm going to be so proud of you buddy.
And he was like, okay.
And he thought Rocket was cute.
So we're like, he might be okay.
He had done a lot better on rides than when he'd got like a year before he was scared
of, just at universal, he was scared of life of pets, but he had done so much better.
It wasn't like first ride of the day.
I was like, I don't know.
It's kind of a toss-up because like also guardians, it's shocking, but it's funny.
And it's not that long, but they wouldn't let us keep them on.
They won't let you make, make kids go on rides.
I've seen parents make kids go on it though.
I've seen it a couple of times, but the cast members were like, he can't go on it.
I wonder if it's cause like it's been too many times.
Yeah, maybe so.
We're just sort of like, I think he'll be, there's at least like a fight knowing him
and his personality.
There's a fighting chance that he like loves this.
This is like a coin toss for how he's behaved on the rides so far today where he's like
get scared in the queue.
And then he's like, that was really fun.
Right.
And he's five.
Now he's five.
Yeah.
I have a two year old who is three inches away from being able to go on space mountain,
big thunder.
She's in like 95th percentile of height.
It's really, it's really tricky.
Cause you're like, I don't know, you can go, you know, like last year, a year and a half
ago I took him on, we put him on smuggler's run and he was like horrified and I was like,
I'm sorry.
I forget that he's like littler cause he's so tall for his age that I'm like, I don't
know if you can go on it.
You can go on it.
That one's confusing too cause it's kind of a video game and kids like video games.
Yeah.
But he didn't like he's, you're in an isolated seat.
Oh yeah.
Cause no one's next to you.
I think that's the scariest part cause like I remember being scared, but my mom would hold
on to me and I was like, okay, my fear is not deep.
Right.
It is like, it's right in the fun zone of like, it's a thrill ride, you know, it would
get me a little flashlight.
I could point up my feet if I got scared in the dark.
That's nice.
Yeah.
That's very sweet.
I didn't know that.
Oh, I swear I've talked about this before.
You probably did.
I, I.
Do you shine that at Mara?
Huh?
Do you shine it at Mara?
Do you still have it?
No.
Well, first off I was three years old.
It was 1988.
You don't keep that flashlight on you still to this day?
I still have it somewhere at my mom's.
But yeah, I was terrified.
They took me on Pirates of the Caribbean.
I screamed my head off purely because of the dark.
And when we're in the gift shop, they're like, well, just get them a little key chain flashlight.
And then they got me that.
We went on again.
If I got scared, I would just shine at my feet and I was fine.
That's brilliant.
Yeah.
That is smart.
Forever.
When I was like an adolescent, I would just ride Alien Counter Florida over and over again.
And that's, that was a terrifying ride.
Did you use the flashlight?
No, I just knew all the beats.
I just knew everything that was coming.
Yeah.
I like the idea of somebody ruining the experience by shining a flashlight in Alien and Counter
because it would be so.
I, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, now it's just ruining the experience when you go to sit down restaurants at Disney
and Boomers are just shining their giant Android phone and you read the menu.
And it's like, what do your parents do?
Surely they figured it out.
You know?
Yeah.
I don't know.
My daughter is just getting scared of stuff.
She was not scared the first time we took her and now she's starting to get scared of
stuff.
So I don't think we're going to force a two and a half year old on Space Mountain.
That would probably be too much.
No, no, no.
But Guardians.
Well, I think she, I think maybe she has to be like five inches away from Guardians.
She loves getting thrown around though.
She likes Mater's junkyard jamboree.
So she likes that, but I think dark and loud is a problem.
Yeah.
You never know.
Well, because you can only treat people how you'd like to be treated and I have only positive
memories of being forced on rides.
My mom and my aunt and my cousins and my siblings were always right.
The ride ended and I was like, I'm so glad I did that.
That was so fun.
I never walked away from a ride being like, I can't believe you made me go on that that
was terrifying ever.
So I've, it's been, I've had a couple tricky moments where I'm like, Oh, I get to do the
same thing.
I get to be like, don't worry buddy, be brave.
It's all fine.
You're going to be safe.
Mama and I are going to hold you.
Like I can do all the same things and they might not have the same experience because
not everyone's the same kid.
And I've had my other nephew, Dez freaked out on the Radiator Springs ride when I, and
I was like, you're going to love it, man.
When this rides over, you're going to love it.
He did not.
And I was like, I don't know.
I don't know what to do about that.
I guess I violated your trust.
Yeah.
You scarred them for life.
When my girlfriend and I first started dating in 2019, the Jurassic World redo of Jurassic
Park ride opened at Universal and we had gone to a press event for it and I was like, Oh,
we should go.
She was working at Universal at the time.
So I went to go see her.
She was doing the frog course in Harry Potter and we were just walking around the park and
doing some stuff.
And I was like, Oh, we should go to Jurassic World.
It's awesome.
And she was still like, we'd only been dating a couple of months.
And so she was trying to like doing the play it cool thing you do with your friends and
had not fully explained to me that she's terrified of things hanging above her and she's terrified
I believe it's robots in it's called submechanophobia and it's like animatronics in water submerged
in water and that ride has both.
And so she was like freaking out the whole ride.
I'm like, okay, it's good.
It's not that good.
What's going on?
And she's like, no, I was legitimately scared.
I was like, Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's tricky with little kids when you want to get them to like try something new and
be a little bit brave when you're like trying to read between the lines, you know, you're
just like, that's why we had warmed them up on lots of safer rides and trying to gauge
like especially when you're not going that often, you're like, who knows the growth that's
happening in a year and a half in your like ability to handle these rides.
Even trickier with 29 year olds where you're like, are you fucking with me?
What's going on?
Yeah, I will.
I guess I'm going to have to err on the side of caution going forward.
Sadly, you know what?
That's great.
It's just like you always want to give like that tiny bit of push of like, yeah, are you
nervous or are you scared?
You know, she can't say a full like complete sentence.
So I guess I should give her a little bit more time.
Yes, yes, yes.
Definitely don't be don't be like me and don't forget that height does not equal maturity.
I was shocked, though, because I was like, oh, looking at Disneyland website and you're
like, oh, she can go on almost everything.
There's like seven or eight things she can't go on.
Oh, and she can go on those and like when she's two and a half or three, that's wild.
Yeah, I was like, oh, she'll be like nine.
Right. When she can go on Guardians.
Yeah. No, not the case.
Yeah. DJ can go on everything except for in credit coaster.
But that doesn't mean he should.
But that's like tough to remember because like I'm just going by like as soon as I was
tall enough, I went on everything.
And I was a little tall for my age, but not I guess I just forget he's really tall for
his age. You're just like completely swayed by short.
You're like, whoops. It's confusing.
It doesn't make sense.
On the app, there is something that says, are you a Disney parks trivia whiz?
Oh, which I was like, oh, that might be interesting to play.
So I said, let me just click playing.
I don't want to spoil the questions yet.
But I hit play and then it takes you to a different app.
It doesn't have it takes you to the play.
It takes you to the Disney play app.
And that's where you then play guys.
It says at home fun.
And then you play in one player and then you select a category.
Random Walt Disney World characters, Disneyland, film, TV, history.
I mean, we could pick Disneyland just for the hell of it and then say, start playing.
We can play as a group.
In what year did the original Disneyland Park in California retire ticket books from use?
Oh, an interesting question.
Do we know the answer to this?
I'm going to guess like it's well, there's choices.
Two thousand eighty two, nineteen eighty two, nineteen fifty nine, nineteen seventy six.
I was going to guess the 70s.
I'm going to guess it's I think it's either seventy six or eighty two.
And that would be my guess.
I think it's eighty two.
That's a it is nineteen eighty two.
Yes. So that's fun.
But again, it's another where you're like, why isn't that just not in the app?
Yeah. And that's how it works.
If you want to do like all that Galaxy's Edge stuff that I don't find fun at all.
Yes. Where you just have to go around and like click things and stuff.
And it's like I understand the idea is maybe fun, but in actual execution,
it's not so fun.
Well, the one thing have you messed around with play up at all?
No, that's how much they're doing to play up.
Are you using it?
I do like and I think it was Avery Monson, a cutie sin on this.
But like Esmeralda, the fortune teller on the Main Street Penny Arcade.
So it's normally 50 cents to get a fortune told.
But if you use the app at it, you can do it for free.
That is a pretty good.
You get a little car, you get a little souvenir.
So it gives you a fortune on one side and then like a chapter based story on the other.
I don't like that chapter three or four.
I don't hate some of the stuff in here or anything.
It's just how confusing it is to get to it.
But like there's the Gifts of Mara.
There's like so many different like little games and stuff you can play,
which is like cool.
But I don't know.
There's something about it that isn't isn't the best.
I don't know. I guess it's just they should just within the app.
They should just have heads up with Disney categories.
Yeah, I'm surprised they didn't like buy heads up.
Do we know who owns heads up?
Can we pitch on a heads up show or a movie like Ellen DeGeneres?
Maybe she said she come up with it.
I think there was like some sort of Ellen tie in maybe.
I don't know. But you should just have games for.
Yeah, games for lines.
Right. Like I remember trying to do like the QR,
like the code stuff in Galaxy's Edge when I first went, it was just nothing.
It is Ellen. You're right. Yeah, she played it on her show.
Yeah. Wow.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Ellen owns heads up. Yeah. Wow.
OK, so she's the one who's going to pitch the movie, I guess.
Yeah, probably. Heads up movie.
Yeah, it's big IP heads up the game.
I mean, that is what they think.
That is what companies think.
I know. You're such dummies.
I clicked on that trivia thing and I selected the random trivia option.
And just even if you're not a big Walt Disney World person,
you might get this one. True or false?
Well, it's fun to splash about Epcot in the rain.
You can always take shelter beneath spaceship Earth
if you don't want to get wet. True or false?
Why? Yeah, I mean, yeah, because there's like an overhang.
So I would say true. Yeah.
What did you write these questions?
I don't that that one was so odd because it's like you look at a picture
of space where there's clearly room underneath it. Yeah.
Fun fact, did you know, despite the seemingly round shape of Spaceship Earth,
the water that runs down the structure during a rainstorm
gets drained by a specially designed system? OK.
Well, these are facts that you would learn about.
This is the type of dry fact you learn on podcast the rise.
Yeah. Are there more drainage based?
Oh, that's about the dapper tans.
Well, I want to know about drainage.
Keep reading, see if there's more drainage stuff.
I want to point out something on the app.
So there's different like there's a pull down menu.
You can go on the map and see attractions.
You can see like character stuff.
And the character stuff is pretty helpful to know where you can meet a character,
because like if you have kids and you want to you want to do that dining,
blah, blah, blah. But you go to guest services.
And then there's a list of different things you can like.
Where's an ATM? Excuse me.
Where's an ATM? Where's a baby care center?
And all of it looks pretty standard.
And then I get to the one thing on there that says cakes at Disneyland Resort.
And I go, wait, what? Cakes.
Then it says cakes at Disneyland Resort celebrate birthdays,
anniversaries, a honeymoon or even the even the every day with a specialty cake
find on the map.
And there's only one location at the Disneyland Hotel in the Goofy's kitchen.
And I guess you could just go and get a cake, Jason.
Did you know about this? I knew there was no, I knew there's like
if it's a birthday, you can get stuff sent to the room.
Well, sure. Yeah, there's room service and things like that.
You could get. But on the app, it's just cake orders.
So you can just get a full like sheet cake at the Disneyland Hotel.
And I guess eat it out in the pool by Trader Sam's.
I like the filter for spa and recreation.
Yes, yes. And there's which is just about pools.
It's mostly about pools.
There's obviously a spot grand Californian.
But yes, there's there's that.
Most everything else, yes, like is is basically, you know,
like there's a thing called this is travel insurance
and there's no locations to get that.
So I guess you used to be able to buy travel insurance for your vacation.
You don't see travel insurance in category.
Oh, it's a guest services. Yeah, yeah.
So you can get strolled like it says you were stroller, like service animals.
Yeah, bottle filling stations. There we go.
And they have a bunch of new bottle filling stations and they are themed.
Yeah, they are nice like Pooh Bear.
It's like kind of looks like it's a honey pot or something.
I like that. We're good.
That's pretty good.
Hand sanitizer locations, in-room celebrations, locker rentals. OK.
Yeah, but I was just in the designated smoking areas.
Those are gone, but it's still on the app.
So they haven't updated the app to tell you you can't smoke anywhere anymore
because it used to be used to be a couple of places.
At least you could do it.
So that stuff is interesting because I never really looked at that before.
I mean, there's the you can find all the restrooms on the app.
Unlock your room door with the Disneyland app.
Yes, I have not tried that.
I haven't stayed there since they added that feature.
But that's pretty standard with most hotels, I feel like these days.
But I also like how they name some of the restrooms, too, like, you know,
Tomorrowland station restrooms.
But then this one, I like Wetzel's Pretzels restrooms.
So it's Wetzel's Pretzels.
Obviously, it's I don't know actually what that restroom is, but
that must be in downtown. It is. Yes.
But which can I say, I hate that,
that if you look for just dining reservations, they'll include
downtown Disney in your options. Yeah, you should.
Have to like select like I'm just saying,
I'm imagining that as a trap for someone who doesn't know better.
Who's like, oh, right, right. Oh, oh, amazing.
We can eat at this jazz kitchen.
That must be in New Orleans Square.
Ralph Brennan must be a character, a Disney movie character.
Yeah, no, that's a downtown Disney.
That's a mile and a half away. Yeah, just walk out of the park.
Ralph Brennan is one of the rescuers, right?
Yeah, that was some of the mouses.
That was a mouse name, Ralph Brennan.
That's what that's what bums me out is like, yeah, is like
trying to imagine like a well-intentioned family
who doesn't know a thousand things about this already,
trying to navigate this extremely expensive day with high expectations
from their children and getting trapped eating at Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen.
Well, we had a lovely meal, Ralph Brennan's.
I will say that in like 2019. It's delicious.
I used to eat there before or after seeing a show at the House of Blues
that used to be there when I was a teen.
Which concerts did you see at House of Blues?
Vlogging Molly, one of my first concerts when I was 15. Wow.
Yeah, I saw them there twice, actually. Wow.
Is that how many concerts do you think you've seen there? Four.
It was also like where my we had our
choir banquet there, I believe my freshman year.
At the House of Blues. Nice. Wow.
And the House of Blues moved. Yeah.
But it's still kind of an anaheim, but it's like over by that other thing
called the Grove, the Garden Walk. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Which I was just spent a lot of time in the other day.
And it's weird. Yeah. Why? Why were you there?
Because I was trying a new parking trick.
I was trying a different parking hack.
And then I which works, by the way, I mentioned this on our Patreon
that if you park at that Garden Walk
and you go get something from Starbucks or the restaurant Huckleberries,
if you have like a pancake at Huckleberries, there's a mysterious
phone number that you text your receipt and your validation,
whatever parking ticket you got when you came into the parking garage.
If you text both of those to a mysterious number, they will just text back
validated and then it's only eighteen dollars for the day.
And I trusted it out and it worked.
But it's a pretty good hack, but it's a strange mall.
It's very, very weird.
There's a magician I've never heard of's club there.
And he's got like a whole lounge going on.
And I promised this on the Patreon, but I'll promise to this on the main feed.
There's going to be content coming about this Anaheim Garden Walk.
Content coming. Yeah.
Prepare for content because it's coming from a mall near Disneyland.
As a Disneyland person, I don't mind us learning lessons from Disney World.
Like, are magic bands going to really take off?
You know, like, will there be things that we really love?
But it's just sort of to me like it there's they're different, you know,
so everything like builds up around Anaheim that feels like it's chasing or
it's just like that's a wildly different massive compound
with a totally different infrastructure site, like amount and scale of hotels.
Yeah. And I kind of want Anaheim to just like chill out sometimes.
Yeah. Well, it's a different it's a different culture there.
It's a whole different it's everything is different.
They have you can get a magic band now at Disneyland.
And I would say I like magic band a lot.
Won't be doing Florida and I still like it, but I don't have a desire to get it here.
I don't know why that is.
I think it's because it's not multiple.
It's not multiple day.
Like the like the idea that you're going to do four parks over four days.
It's a big trip.
It just feels different than like it was complimentary.
Well, that was a nice thing.
Yes, I didn't buy one charge, but at least if you're like doing a big trip,
you're like, OK, yeah, my own one does work still in Orlando for now.
Oh, OK.
All right. I think actually I have a purple one.
I have like a standard purple one and then a gray one.
But yeah, I don't have any desire to do it out here.
I don't know. I didn't think that would be me.
I thought, man, as soon as they come to Disneyland, I'm going to be a guy
with a thing like a little charm on it as Apple Pay to anyway.
You're making me use the app.
My phone's out all the time.
And now I'm sure we all do this when we go.
You have to have some sort of charging cube.
Well, yes. And we've talked about this.
There was a whole the fuel, the fuel rods and the lawsuit that ensued
when they tried to change the terms of the deal.
And then they'd go back on that.
But I don't even know if they have those in the park anymore after the lawsuit.
I bought one last year.
But now that I'm thinking about it, I don't know if I saw it.
But yes, you have to have that.
My phone died. I said this on the second gate.
I said this. My phone died when I was there and I had to text
everybody for my computer at award wieners.
So I just had to tell Lindsay, look, my phone is dead.
My computer is still alive and I'm at award wieners right now.
And I'm eating film strip fries.
And I'll be home soon.
She said, I love you, baby.
I love you so much.
She got riled up and she was so excited to hear all that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's that's just like that's a real reality is that it really drains.
Yes. Oh, yeah. No, it's pretty.
And the fuel rod has not really changed in the fuel rod.
Gives you 15 percent charge.
The fuel rod is a big scam.
And they're they're really bad.
And there's better.
You have to bring your own little brick or something, or just, I guess,
keep turning your phone on and off.
But that's not that practical thing.
I when my family was visiting, I kept like, if we split up,
I kept texting my dad, like, oh, we're here.
Just look at the map in the app.
And he's like, I hate this.
Like any time would explain mobile ordering the app or stuff.
Like I would just see the blood.
Like, yeah, and he has been going to Disney World since the 70s.
I know that's how I had that moment with my mom, where she was like
she was the amazing captain for years.
And now her knowledge is almost obsolete.
Like, it's so sad to be like, oh, yeah, my mom has a good attitude.
She's like, oh, great. Love it.
But, you know, there used to be a time where she would at least be like,
well, I think we should go, you know, she's like, I don't know.
You got to take it.
Because like the learning curve is way too steep to expect her to understand.
And they train people like FastPass for like 20 plus years.
And like they train people like, oh, do this.
Eat it this time. Go this time.
And so much of that is defunct.
And I bought the Lightning Lane multipass for four of us
when my family was visiting and they were only here for a few days.
And they're like, oh, thank God you did that the day we were at Disneyland Park.
And I was like, yeah, but the trade off was one hundred and twenty dollars.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So they thank you. Yes.
Like, oh, yeah, you want.
That's what I want after one of these days.
My like sister, like the one time that I took a strike.
She she like bought me a hat.
They pay for my. Yeah.
Like they're paying for if any of those up charges that I'm doing
to help navigate the day for their children, they're paying for it.
And I'm like, hey, just so you know, I'm I'm spending this money on this thing.
And they're like, yeah, whatever. Thank you.
They were paying for a lot.
But this we ran into a thing where you like, oh, I got park hoppers to everyone.
I was like, well, I think my magic might still be active.
But I was the one who made all the park reservations.
So if I deleted the one ticket, everyone's reservations would go.
And I'm like, I guess because I'm just using the park hopper.
This doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
We're merging. Reservations is not intuitive.
You maybe could have called someone to have them do it for you, but maybe not.
Yeah. But you're just on the phone for five or ten minutes.
Just going representative, representative.
Yeah. When Apple buys Disney in the next few years, they'll probably fix all of this.
I'm assuming I would assume maybe they won't.
Maybe it'll be worse.
But like, it doesn't feel like Disney has any incentive to like,
it's going to be still like kind of pieced together.
It's funny, this changes every few years because years and years ago
it was Disney will buy Apple and now it's Apple buying.
Well, everything's there's going to be two companies going forward
and it's going to be helped by the political situation.
Exxon Chipotle.
Just as Parks and Rec.
And Comcast Apple.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's let's brainstorm real quick on our way out here.
What what do we want from the app?
What do we what would we like?
I mean, obviously, we're not getting what we want in the sense that like
at this point, Lightning Lane going away would be awesome.
Just let's let's playing field.
Let's level it. Let's even it out.
Yeah, I would accept that.
Like, fine, great.
We all have the same shot, but they're not going to do that.
So what do you want from the app?
What do you want to streamline everything?
Basically, thirty six dollars a person to me is not a crazy upcharge.
Yeah, what I would like to be included in that payment
would be that I can pre book more things.
Yeah, the fact that like you're you've paid for this money,
but it is still relying on your effort on day effort.
Right. Is the downside for me.
So like even if it was piecemeal where it's like, OK, you've paid for it.
Pre book four. Right.
And then day of you're going to get whatever more you can.
You can go, you know, you can garner whatever.
But like it would be great to know those like certain times of day.
We're like, OK, I'm going to get like two really big rides
in the beginning of the day to give us a great start.
And then let me get us to during the three to five, like dreariness
to like give us another like boost of energy or something.
We'll take a nice long lunch.
I think if I could do
if that money got me a little bit more right the time ahead,
I would like that.
And I want the app to have weight.
I don't want the tip.
The two toggles I don't like.
What do you oh, oh, oh, as far as going back and forth from
like the like whatever portal, we should say that they're like
they'll say like enter the virtual queue and then there'll be like a port.
Like there's different words for like clicking on buttons.
And sometimes it'll be like enter the magic key portal.
And then some things will just be a virtual queue.
So there's different names for just clicking to get to another page.
Like, OK, so this is my welcome, but it's not the home.
Yeah. Which doesn't make any sense.
And then like today's plans, the tipboard versus my day.
Right. I don't like that.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Like this this toggle is a bummer to me.
So I just want it to be my day, which is my itinerary.
Right. That has tips like maybe a genie icon on that page.
I could I could click on. Right.
That's like, hey, we noticed you have a gap here
and you're going to be in this part of the park.
Here's the two or three things that are nearest.
Here's the best snack to get over there. Yeah. Yeah.
You know, like going back and forth.
I've watched cast members have to explain this to people. Right.
Because then you go back to the tipboard and that's where it shows you
current wait times.
It's just not good.
It's not simple.
There's a little more.
Yeah. A little more intuitiveness. Yeah. Yeah.
I want yes, because like in Disney World, you can pre book
or at least you could at some point, like book three ahead of time
and then do it yourself.
So it would be nice if you could do like six, because then I would feel OK.
Because it is it is a thing where you pay thirty two dollars
and you could end up like doing three in one day if you're not on top of it.
Or you could do 15. Yes.
So that's the problem.
And it's like in some ways you were like, OK, there could be an extra tier.
That's fifty dollars where I get six.
But it's like we can't do that.
I don't want to do that.
And but it's but it's fighting my instincts.
Or or like if you if you book, maybe you get rewarded
for like having a reservation further out or whatever.
Like, hey, if you if you book Lightning Lane two weeks before your visit,
you get five. Yeah.
Because that's probably going to benefit the planners anyway.
Yeah. I don't know.
Just give us a few that we get to pre book, because then that takes the like
that takes the anxiety down a little bit where you're like,
OK, I have some footholds.
I know they're going to get on Space Mountain.
Thank the Lord.
Like, I don't have to like, you know, reinvent the wheel.
Yeah. I am like this is I guess this is the silly park maybe.
You know, so you get you're you're getting you're getting rewarded
for purchasing a park hopper. Yeah.
So you pay for Lightning Lane.
You get three pre books per park that you have a ticket to.
Yeah. Yeah.
And this is a big part of the vacation experience in Florida.
Like, oh, you've got like 60 days out or 45 days out.
You can pre book some fast passes. Yes.
And then when you use them, then you can get more. Yes.
And then COVID, they use COVID to like, all right, we're getting rid of that,
at least for the free level.
It might not forget whether it's back a little bit.
Yeah, I've got a couple of things. Sure. Go ahead.
One thing that I find very stressful with virtual queues is
it kind of doesn't account for your location, despite
you have to have location services on.
So it's like Sunday, if you book at 7 a.m., you could end up
being like your virtual queues at 830 or not.
And it's like, oh, we live in Los Angeles.
It could take 90 minutes or two hours to get down there at park.
That's impossible.
So like if there was something in there where it's like, OK,
you've got a virtual queues spot and when you get within like a mile,
we'll assign you your time.
That would be great.
The other thing is that a thing we kind of learned in Florida,
because we had different ticket types and we were trying to get everyone
in everyone else's phone so you could try for the virtual queue
for the Guardians Galaxy roller coaster.
We learned this and someone eventually described it to us as like
that is a fail safe.
But there is a QR code in the app.
And if everyone scans everyone else's app
or everyone else's digital ticket, then you're all on everyone's phones.
And I would like more things, more fail safes.
Yeah. More fail safes.
More idiot proofing, you know. OK.
Because it took us a while of trying to get all our tickets together.
Yes, that was when Scott got up and he was upset.
QR codes.
He was upset with too much too much app talk, which right now
he's probably like in a hospital right now.
The doctor's like, what's wrong with this man? His head is swollen.
We can't tell. He's just screaming out in pain.
He's like, people are being naughty on my podcast.
Being a little naughty. Yeah.
He sent a picture a little while ago and I can't talk about what it is.
I'll talk about what it is.
I saw the photo as well.
And we'll show it to you.
Really, really, really good.
Well, it'll be brought up eventually.
Here's the thing.
I was like, I got to kind of some suggestions, but I'm like,
Disney's going the way of every other business
where they're just trying to suck as much money out of me.
And nothing is ever going to get better.
And here's a solution, I think, to the problem we're having.
And it's not a great solution, but it is a solution.
I believe there should be a group of checkers.
I believe I'm a checker.
This is a self-described checker.
And there's a lot of people out there that are checkers.
You're a checker as well.
I think there should be a pool of checkers.
And we sign up for slots to help other checkers on their Disneyland Day.
So basically, say someone say you're going Thursday
and I'll say and I'll say I'm going Wednesday.
You will check for me on Wednesday from home.
And then I will check from you, check from home for you on the Thursday.
So I will get to enjoy a full, great day.
But there's a person like Mission Impossible.
There's a man and there's a man in the chair.
There's a man in the van, a man in the chair searching for you.
Now, that's going to take up a day.
But it's not you still get some work done in between.
But that is going to take care of the problem looking at your phone.
So if you exchange days, I'm serious, if you want to do this, I'll do this.
As long as I don't have if I'm have like somewhat of a free day,
we could exchange checking.
This is like people who vote swap.
This is like people vote swap.
And it's yes, it's called man in the van is good.
I like that. That's that's a clean title for it.
But if all the checkers band together, we could only have to pay thirty two dollars.
Don't have to do the four hundred.
Yes. And then from remote, because you can do it from home.
If you gave me your log in, I can log in and still check.
It doesn't matter. But the virtual queue, you'd I'd still have to be like,
hey, Mike, get in the virtual queue.
It's open because it's based on location, right?
You know what? If you gave me your login for your app
and you were in the park, I bet I could still pull it at noon at seven a.m.
It would still be I would have to.
It could be anybody could do it. Right.
Well, the thing I haven't tried is like
do pay like setting up a VPN
and and picking like an Anaheim tricking it.
Well, that's thinking you're in an Anaheim signing on from Anaheim.
But it's smart enough.
I wonder if it would have to be in the grounds or if it just thinks Anaheim
in general. Right.
Because I ran into this even trying to like show up
for an August cantina where they're like, we can tell you're not close enough.
Like, you know, the dining stuff, even the dining stuff.
They're like, you're not close enough to check in.
Like, I'm like, I got us a reservation.
We it took us longer to get from parking.
And I'm like, oh, no, no, no.
And it's like, hey, go ahead and check in for your dining reservation.
And they're like, you can't check in yet.
You're not close enough.
And I was like in downtown Disney.
You know, I was like very, very close.
McDonald's tried to do this to me when I ordered a nice coffee
and I wanted it waiting for me at the counter when I got there.
But they said, you're not close.
And then there was an extra prompt on McDonald's app where you can say,
yes, I am close. OK.
So but it's not like that at Disney, I don't think. Yeah.
I mean, again, it was fine.
I don't know why every single time I can get into August Cantina.
Does no one want to go there?
It's not a big. Well, it's always crowded when I've been in there.
But I don't know. It's not as it's not as it's really fun.
Do you ever do the fuzzy tauntaun? Which one's that?
That's the one that numbs your mouth.
Oh, because that's Szechuan in it.
Yeah, I think that's what it is. It's in the foam.
And I got one a couple of weeks ago and I took like
I kind of was like being so funny.
I was being like funny.
And I took like a bite of kind of the foam.
And there was so much Szechuan or whatever in there that I just coughed.
I just had a hacking cough immediately.
I just like sprayed.
I was like so embarrassed because it's so close quarters in there.
Yeah, that's my friend.
And it was fine. But I didn't get it on anybody.
But like, I was like so funny.
I was being funny because I was taking a big bite of the foam.
This is huge. You can get a beer at the.
Yes, and a couple of other places as well.
You can get it at a carnation on Main Street, I believe, as well.
You can get like a cocktail at Carnation now.
This is huge for me.
This is a big deal. That's a big deal for me.
It's a limited menu because I enjoy drinking at California Adventure.
There are some great places to get drinks over there.
Well, yes, we are big Carthay, Manhattan guys.
Of course, this is this is what's converted many a person
that we probably all we have in common where I've people.
I don't know. I go, well, come down.
We'll do the day.
And my general thing is midday, you go to the Carthay Lounge.
You have a Manhattan. Yeah.
In my younger years, you might have two. Yeah.
But at least you have one.
And then you come out of there and you're like, I did that with my two friends
who got motion sick.
I was like, let's go take a long break at Carthay.
It was great. Yes.
It's that's a real energizer, like reenergizer.
Yeah. So anyway, I mean, yeah, there's good.
Look, there's good things about the app, but it's complicated.
And they're trying.
It feels like they're trying to actively make everything feel bad.
They're trying to make us feel bad. Yeah.
And it would be nice if they could at least just simplify
some of this stupid stuff in the app.
If it was easier, you would have an easier time making an argument
to your group being like, hey, someone else want to take the next turn.
But I couldn't imagine I couldn't imagine asking my sister to do that.
No. You know, we'd lose valuable time.
Well, I was going to say, don't trust.
Don't trust her. I wouldn't trust my sister to do it.
She wouldn't know because she doesn't she doesn't go enough.
Like that was the one time my sister-in-law
and it was an issue where our reservations was hard to merge.
We had to go get someone to help us to do it.
I think we ended up scanning something, but it was still weird
and not as easy as it should be. Right.
But we were trying before when we were like, well, we just have to find
some sort of bandaid for the solution.
We were simul booking, you know? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So anyway, it's nice to have a partner in the fight, but it's still
solidarity only takes you so far.
I mean, two people, two alphas can't exist in a group as well.
So you have to understand, I think.
And then she's bringing her like, you know, in Orlando, it's like this.
And I'm like, listen, I appreciate that.
It's great. But like you're in land now. Right.
Put some respect on its name.
You're the top dog in lands. Yeah.
You're an alpha. You're an alpha checker like I am. Yeah.
And there's there's I don't know.
It would be interesting. Let's pull the audience.
Who out there are alpha checkers of the group?
And what what do we think the percentage of those type of people are?
And beta checkers.
What do you think you're bringing to the table?
And how can I support the beta checker? I think. Oh, for sure.
He knows how to do it to wander around and look at the landscaping.
But you know how to do it.
If I know how to do it, if I went down in a Disneyland day
and I said, I can't and I'm going to be at the like first date or whatever.
Jason, I need you to take care, like, take care of it.
You would be able to do it.
I think I have looked up stuff like I used to have your ticket.
But you will say you will let me be an alpha checker on a day.
Yo, absolutely. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But Scott, we wouldn't.
He doesn't want any part of it.
He would kind of reluctantly do it.
But like, yeah, you're a beta checker and then he's whatever.
Give me another letter in Greek.
Yeah, yeah. Delta.
He's a delta checker.
It's pretty far down. That's so.
Yeah. Anyway, we'll let us know.
We'll post a poll on whatever social media.
I don't know what social media to use.
Also, this is a big debate going on.
It's the whole thing of like, do we stay on the thing with the guy?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do we stay on the thing with the guy?
I don't know. I left the thing before the guy.
I've been off the thing with the guy with the guy for like,
I think, like five years.
Wow, really? Yeah.
So I'm a other guy is also.
I heard the other guy isn't good either.
He's not good either.
But right now, he's a little less bad.
And also the the actual like
discourse is a little less bad.
Yeah, for now. For now.
Because everything gets bad, too.
How do you spend much of your day mad about things out of your control?
Well, then I fell into like I did get on threads a little bit.
Oh, threads.
Which is still pretty bad.
But it's very echo chamber in a different way.
You know, which is, you know, different.
But no, I had gotten sort of post 2016
and then maybe a couple more years after that,
I had whittled it back down to just Instagram to try to to try to be like,
it's impossible to be a comedian right now and not have a social media.
But I can limit how many I have so that I'm not spending that much time on them.
Sure. I like looking at the pretty picture.
Yes. So in my like good moments, I'm I'm only on Instagram
and I try to put a timer on it.
OK. Well, we'll talk.
I'll figure it out.
See, I'm just not against I'm against being on my phone in general, which is why.
Yeah. Like good for you.
I'm trying and they're making it hard.
Anytime I go to anything that wants me to have an every single unique airline,
I have to have their app every day.
Like I just reject that they all need to be apps.
You know, like, yeah, but they really do make it easier.
It sucks. Yeah.
Yeah. If there was just like a magic band for all airlines.
Yeah. With a little plane on it.
I just want to be able to log in, get my ticket on a browser window
and then upload it to my Apple Wallet.
Yeah, that's what you mostly can do.
But a lot of times they're like,
but don't you want the American Airlines proprietary app?
Yeah. She's like, no, I don't need this shit.
I tried because you can technically get your airline ticket on the Apple Watch.
And I tried it one like they saw me going to do it.
And I swear I heard a like they're like, it's not kind of OK.
It on the fifth try worked.
I think in the next 10 years, like it will.
There will be some like, I don't know if it'll be like the guy.
The guy invented the thing in the in your neural link or whatever.
I don't know if it'll be that.
But there will be like something like it's a chip in your like wrist
and everything's just in the chip wrist.
Not for me. Yeah.
But you're going to it's mandatory.
Damn it. Yeah. OK.
I guess for me, that's going to be.
Yeah. The chip app is going to be intolerable.
I don't think I knew this about myself, like as a young person.
But I'm like, I have no tech like design.
I'm not an early adult. I'm basically a Luddite.
I will do what I have to do.
But I'm like, no, I don't want that.
I don't want any of that.
Well, it will be a law.
So it will be a law.
There'll be a law in the next four years.
In the next four years, they're going to get to chip law.
There'll be a chip law.
What about the chips act?
Unrelated. Different.
All right. Well, thank you, Jess McKenna.
You've survived podcasts to ride app talk.
Boy, it feels good to be naughty, doesn't it?
Talking about apps like this.
Please exit to the gift shop. Plug away.
What do you got going on?
You know, you can still always listen to off book podcasts,
even though we don't do weekly studio apps.
We got some new live apps that are up and we're touring.
So you can check those dates out.
There's a link in my bio at Jess, Jess McKenna on Instagram.
The one I'm on or off book on any socials.
Yeah. Yeah. Come come see off book live.
It's fun. Yeah, it's great.
So, yeah, go. Yeah. Instagram.
Jess, Jess McKenna. Yeah.
And is there an off book as well?
And there is. Yeah. OK.
I mean, like, OK. Yeah.
Yeah. So go check that out.
As for us, we're on the stuff with the guy at podcast, the ride.
And we're on Instagram at podcast, the ride, but patron dot com slash podcast.
The ride. There's more app talk this month as well.
Different things. Jason and I are really spreading our wings out here. Yeah.
And getting rowdy with it.
Crazy. Yeah, it's just agreeing.
And it sounded like a judgment.
And honestly, in the last few weeks, there's been app talk as far as phone
apps and appetizer talk as Jason started talking about chili's appetizer
and cheese planks and how there's something going viral where people do a cheese
pull, you know, at the cheese.
If you are, she's not on social media as much, but Jason was informing me
because he's the one who checks in the most that the teens are going.
Teens or just people in general are going wild.
I lost track of all the age group.
They're doing a cheese pull.
So it's like a phenomenon going on where they do a cheese pull
with like a cheese plank at a chili's.
Well, the cheese pull is kind of agnostic to anywhere.
Jason was using the term cheese plank to describe a mozzarella stick.
I kept hearing it on TikTok because the chili's mozzarella
sticks are kind of like rectangles as opposed to round, cylindrical.
Yeah. And so it's just how good of a pull you can get.
Yeah. You got to ask this guy.
But you get a good pull.
But I never thought those were that good.
So I guess I have to revisit.
You have to revisit and we have to get you to go viral.
Yep. I guess so.
Yeah. So we're going to Chili's.
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog News by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.