Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate where today we will attempt to go 20,000 tangents
below the topic.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me Skipper, first mate Jason Sheridan.
I like that.
I'm Skipper and first mate?
I know those are actually, as I said it, those are two different positions on the ship.
Well, it must have worked very hard to earn two simultaneous positions.
Or somebody died at sea and you have to do two jobs now.
Oh, well that sounds like a downgrade.
Although you know Scott isn't here, he's not died.
He's, they were doing this Scott free of course.
He is lost at sea.
Scott could potentially be on our podcast submarine.
He is maybe the Skipper or first mate, so you're going to have to take his job today
too.
His, yeah, his submersible is still stuck deep underwater, has not been saved by Atlantean
magic yet.
No, it hasn't.
So I'm still doing just one job.
I'm just like the engineer or something, but you're going to have to be two jobs today.
You're Gilligan and Skipper today.
Oh, shit.
You're both.
Self in the head with a hat.
If you screw up, you can, he's actually doing it.
We are not recording video here.
I was just testing.
You braced for impact too.
Like you were going to get hit with a lead pipe.
Yeah.
Like, oh, you're like grimace.
Like, was it really something?
Let's bring our guest in.
You know him.
He's a, he's been on podcast ride.
I don't want to say he's, a friend of his has been on podcast the ride recently.
A friend who is a monstrous type friend, um, but it's not him for sure.
His, he, he's friends with the Minotaur is what I'm saying, but he, that's not him.
That's just a buddy of his.
So that's the closest he's been to being on podcast to ride lately.
Right.
But he himself, uh, has been on a number of times.
Yes.
He himself has been, I'm just saying when like the, that's the last time I think when
I see the Minotaur, I think of him because of how good their friendship is.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So that's the only reason I brought that up instead of just mentioning one of the times
he was on the show with the episode about the, uh, Ronto raps.
Of course we did, uh, um, but Matt Mazzani is back.
He's here.
He is not with his friend today though.
I don't think.
No, no, I don't think, I don't think he's going to show up.
He's, he's more of a professional acquaintance like with, when you, when you're friends with
the Minotaur, it's always a little bit business.
You know what I mean?
Like, like you could be friends, but it's, it's like, you know, you're always trying
to do Minotaur-y things, get people lost in mazes, things like that.
Well, that's, and you net, he always wants a ride.
He hates driving.
Oh yeah.
But then you're like, I gotta pick him up at the maze.
Oh, it's gonna take so much time.
We're going to miss Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice.
Ironically, parking at the maze, so easy to find, so convenient.
Oh, sure.
But, but getting to the maze is-
Getting to his unit in the maze is-
Yeah.
It's like one of those condo situations.
And it's like, he's like maze, uh, one 24 and a half.
And then like the, the three quarter ones, it's confusing.
I can't.
Yeah.
He's a real user.
This Minotaur.
I think he's a great guy.
I don't know if-
Are you sure?
I don't know if you want to start running him down.
And then he starts coming back.
He just sounds aggressive and he sounds like a real pain in the ass and he sounds like
somebody you wouldn't want to associate with.
That's all.
I want to know if Mike's about to start calling people users regularly.
I don't think I've ever heard it.
I don't think, I'm hoping he starts going on about fake friends soon.
Fake ass friends.
Oh, the haters are out too for Mike Carlson.
Well, the Minotaur tried to be my fake ass friend by the end of the episode, but he wasn't.
He was just trying to be like, buddy, up to me at that point.
I think he thought he, he probably went too far.
He felt he went too far.
And then he was trying to be my fake ass friends.
I don't, I don't want to say you're talking a big game cause the Minotaur is not here,
but you know-
Well, whatever.
Yeah.
Would you say that, would you say that to the Minotaur's face?
Cause that actually kind of makes you a fake ass friend if you wouldn't say it to his face.
Well, look, when you're in times of struggle, you will say things to get out of that struggle.
So I feel like I was in the right.
You'll delete a deals Twitter and then bring it back.
That's what I said.
For spite.
I brought up that whole, I brought up contract law on that episode.
If we remember.
That's right.
Sure.
I often cite contract law on podcast the ride.
But here, look, we're not here to talk about the mythical beast, the great beast itself.
Great guy.
We're here to talk.
Who's that?
It seems like a bit of a user.
That's a good soft insult by the like, you know, you heard about that guy, he's a bit
of a user.
Yeah.
A bit of a user.
We can all write down a piece of paper, a person we know who's a user.
I'm not saying we all have the same person, but I'm saying we all, somebody comes to your
mind when you think of user-
Scott, Scott, right?
Scott Geerner?
Scott Geerner.
Yeah, yeah.
He's no user.
Well, we all wrote it down and flipped it over at the same time.
I wrote my own name down.
I didn't understand the prompt.
Well, you know what you got to do now?
Hit yourself in the head with your own head.
Don't do it.
You could just do it, Jason.
You could just do it on the mic and pretend.
No, because you would go on a whole tangent that I didn't hit myself.
You could do it like this.
You could just take your hand, put it near the mic and hit like this or something.
Okay.
Because you could like foley it.
Foley or like sound effects.
Yeah.
No, people like the authenticity.
That's why they tune in to podcasts for the authenticity.
But he looks like he's in such pain before he does it.
I did actually whack my ear kind of bad that time.
Yeah, no, it makes me like worried about him if he keeps hitting himself in the head.
That's a beautiful hat, by the way, the Grand Californian hat.
Is that is that an old hat?
Is that a newish hat?
It's about a year old.
I got it.
My dad and brother came out to visit and I got it when they were out.
And that's the hat that he will use to concuss himself on today's episode.
Well, it's a solid hat.
That's why I thought it might have been like a retro.
It's got like a retro nice earth tone.
It's a spa hat.
Can you tilt that down for me?
It's the hotel.
It's the hotel and spa.
Hotel and spa.
I think it's just in the logo.
It's just the name.
It's in the spa, which it's very expensive, but I do want to do that one of these days
is the three of us go down to the Grand Californian Hotel at Disneyland and do spa stuff.
I'm a spa guy now.
I love spas now.
Yes, I do it once every three years, but when I do it, I love it.
You get the robe.
You sit there with a bunch of strangers while you wait for something to happen, like a massage,
not something weird.
It's not like an orgy.
I don't know why I said it like that.
You know what I'm saying?
There's like a comments room.
If you want something to happen, Michael, you just got to make it happen.
I'm just saying you wait for whatever service.
Excuse me?
What was the service?
Well, you pick one color handkerchief, put it in your banter pocket.
You sit naked with a robe on, you sit with a bunch of strangers, and you wait for something
to happen.
Generally, a service that you've paid for in advance.
At the legal spa.
Right.
And everything I said is how you would describe it.
Nothing I said there is too weird.
Sure.
Yeah.
People would understand that.
But you're twirling your mustache as you're saying it, which people don't get on the audio,
so it is a little.
Yes.
And I'm not going to do it.
Well, I'm miming it.
And unlike Jason, I'm going to mime here.
You can hear it.
Ew.
It's an ASMR mustache twirl.
That's right.
So if anybody in the audience likes that.
Anyway, we will do spa stuff eventually on this show.
Sure.
A very wet episode that'll be.
Well, we're not going to record it in the spa, I don't think.
Why not?
I feel like that might be.
They might not like that.
This is the protest for authenticity.
You'd record in a spa, right?
Yeah, I would consider it.
Oh, bull.
You didn't want to record at CityWalk.
You thought we would get arrested.
Well, look, that was before all the vloggers and Instagrammers had like just buckets of
equipment nowadays at theme parks.
So I thought it would look unusual.
But he flipped out when we suggested it like years ago.
Well, hold on.
That was texting.
I feel like you're reading a lot into that.
Did you use all caps or an exclamation point?
No.
Is that counterpoint?
You're wrong.
Yes, it is.
That's one of the famous.
I don't think there was any punctuation.
Counterpoint, you are wrong.
It was the very early days of the podcast.
You were feistier back then, I think.
Oh, I was feistier.
So now you're ready to go tape a microphone to your chest and get a massage.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, I don't want.
I just don't want any, you know, fire.
Our guest today made a short film, which we'll talk about at the end of this episode.
Yeah, sure.
Fire does come into play.
What a good segue.
I would not want anything like that going on.
No, we are anti-fire on this show, if that's what you're saying.
We don't want fires to happen.
Yeah, fire bad.
A bunch of Frankensteins in that way.
Right.
Nobody likes fire.
There's a roaring fire and there's chestnuts nearby.
Just like at the Grand California.
Is there a fireplace at the Grand?
There is a fireplace.
I've never been to the Grand California.
You've got to walk through.
You've got to do yourself a favorite walk through.
You can get a drink at the bar, drink in the big lobby.
Okay.
Yeah, it's funny because I love the show.
I've been listening to the show for many years.
I enjoy it.
Thank you.
And I'm a theme park fan, but I don't, the hotels are something I've just never touched
and never got into.
I don't know how to engage in them without the, because I can't stay at the Grand California
now.
Here's the thing.
What is it, like $900 a day or something?
Well, yes, don't do that.
It's too much, too expensive now.
If Scott were here, he would say, look, we got a topic to talk about, but Scott is not
here.
Yeah.
Why don't we talk a little hotel?
I'll talk some hotel, I guess.
Do you want to get a little naughty?
20,000 tangents under the sink.
I think we could get a little naughty.
And what is Nemo's ship, but a very fancy hotel for sailors?
You know, they call Nemo's ship the Naughty List.
That's the ship that we're driving today.
You should hit him on the head with your hat, actually, for that one.
Unfortunately, my arms are far too short to accomplish that.
We are driving the Naughty List today.
That's what we're doing.
Not the Naughty List.
Not Santa's Naughty List, the Naughty List, a naughty little ship that Captain Nemo pilots
under the sea.
No, wait, we're in a separate submersible from the Naughty List itself.
No, I'm talking about podcasts as an entity, we're in the Naughty List.
This is a very Naughty List vibe.
I do like the Naughty List vibe here.
This room, we're alone, we're away from the oceans, no laws, Captain Nemo can run around
and do what he wants.
We can talk hotels.
Yeah, it's cold as shit, you know?
It's cold.
It's a little damp for some reason.
Why is it damp?
I walked in here as damp, Carl.
Well, because I have a humidifier going for my dry sinuses.
See, he loves fire.
He's always tempting electrical devices by it.
Yes, that's true.
The only reason I wanted a quick talk hotel is maybe not quick, is I just did around a
hotel hanging out.
I just went alone, by the way, in the middle of the afternoon.
I checked out the new Pixar Pier Hotel, I checked out Grand Californian, you sit, you
have a little drink.
I went to Disneyland Hotel and there's something called the Broken Spell Lounge.
It's the same exact lounge that the steakhouse had.
It's got darker carpet, though.
Oh, that's fun.
Disneyland is so expensive and they continue to turn the heat up on everybody who wants
to go, but if you're down in Anaheim, here's what I think you should do if you want to
do a day, an afternoon or a night.
There's a little trick, a parking trick that I have recently been hip to on some Instagram.
You go to the Garden Walk, which is the mall, the Anaheim Garden Walk, which is right by
there.
It's where they have the bubblegum shrimp and they have a restaurant called Huckleberry's,
which looks like the Knott's Berry Farm logo.
And you go there, you can go to the Starbucks or the Huckleberry's.
There's a phone number that you text your receipt to and then you've gotten a parking
pass from parking at the Garden Walk.
You text that and your receipt to this number, a strange number, and then in a couple hours
they will say, validated, and the parking will be $18 for the whole day, which is much
better than the $35 you'd use at Disneyland or whatever.
Yeah.
So you go down, you do that, maybe you wander the Garden Walk, which is one of the strangest
places I've ever gone.
It's a very odd outdoor mall with a bunch of strange things, magicians you've never
heard of have their own place there.
And look, I don't want to say we're going to do a lot of content on this area, but we're
going to do a lot of content on this area eventually.
You were sending pictures and I was like, wow, the Garden Walk has gotten even weirder.
Yes.
I think that's correct.
But it's a very, it's like 10 minute walk, eight minute walk, so you get to park for
under 20 bucks.
And if you want to do the whole day there, you can.
You just want to wander the hotels, wander the Grand Californian.
There's a couple of different places.
You can go get a drink outside by the pool.
You can go get a drink.
There's a little indoor spot there too, and there's a couple of restaurants.
So talk to me like, just because I'm a very, like a very neophyte when it comes to the
Disney hotels.
You go to Garden Walk.
What are the hotels that you go to?
You go to Grand California.
I've heard of that one.
Never been.
Well, okay.
So there's three Disney hotels.
There's Grand Californian.
There's Disneyland Hotel.
There are place hotels, that's what it's called, which used to be called Paradise Pier Hotel.
Yes, and a number of names before that.
Yeah, so there's three Disney-owned hotels.
Now there are plenty of other hotels to enjoy in Anaheim as well, on Harbor Boulevard and
other places, and I recommend going to those, but I'm just giving you the core.
If you want to do three Disney hotels, you go to Trader Sam's right by the Disneyland
Hotel, and you can make a full nice afternoon of just kind of going and hanging out, doing
some work there.
I might do that.
I got some time coming up in a week or two, and I usually fill it with like, I go to the
art museum.
I go to the Hammer.
I go to LACMA.
I go to all these other places, but it sounds like this is a better way to spend an afternoon
than trying to enrich myself.
A hundred percent.
I'm being completely sincere.
Take a computer, go park for 18 bucks, and then wander the grounds.
The music's playing.
You're still getting some of the vibes.
It's like somebody's doing drugs in another room, and the smoke is coming in, and you're
still getting the smoke of the actual theme parks.
You're still getting the theming.
You're still getting a lot of it, and you will be happier.
It will make you happier to be there and working and wandering around, and you can still sniff
the magic.
You can still sniff a little magic while you're down there.
While you sniff some magic while you're waiting for a service at the spa.
I get what you're saying, pal.
Well, depending on what you ordered.
That's right.
What hotel would you recommend?
What's the big hotel experience that I should do that you find the best?
I think the outdoor restaurant at the Grand California is really great, drink and food-wise.
There's a bar there, and you can just sit at the bar.
It's only a few years old.
The current iteration is only a few years old.
Now, you can get the full menu at the quick service restaurant, but you don't get less
of the vibe, you know.
Got it.
Okay.
This sounds good.
This is good.
I think this is a good tangent.
I think I'm going to go do this.
Yeah.
It's honestly so much fun.
I haven't done it in a while because I have a child, and there's responsibilities now.
But you know what?
I didn't have to watch her that day, so dad got to get a little work done down in Anaheim.
Daddy's day out.
It was daddy's day out.
Daddy's had a real daddy's weekend.
He went to a concert alone yesterday.
I'm really stepping out again for the first time in a few years.
What concert did you see?
LCD Sound System.
How is that?
How was that?
Fantastic.
Are you a big fan?
Yeah.
I don't know if I like them or not.
I listen to them.
I do listen to them.
Okay.
But I don't know if I like them.
You seem skeptical.
I am skeptical.
It feels good to be naughty on this and talk LCD Sound System.
I do feel naughty.
Let's talk a little LCD Sound System.
What do you feel about it?
It's one where it's like I heard the singles for years.
I think I only ever really listened to one album because someone burned it for me.
The Dancers of Clean one?
Is that the one?
The one with all your friends.
Okay.
All my friends.
Yeah.
So that's how much I know.
It's like all my friends.
All my friends are at the Grand California.
That one?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I feel like, I think of LCD Sound System as like I learned about this band when I moved
to Los Angeles and it was around my Los Angeles friends.
Yeah.
Six, seven.
I think of this very much as like young 20s just moved to LA.
I remember they did a big hoopla about breaking up.
Yeah.
That's right.
They did a fake breakup in a Madison Square Garden Residency.
And then they got packed together and have sold tickets thanks to the help of American
Express.
Oh, sick.
Sick.
That's a good credit card.
It's a great card.
Yeah.
Great card.
Is the card good?
Yeah.
Do you like American Express?
I only have ever had one American Express.
It's funny you say that because coming up soon on Podcasts to Ride Club 3, I am going
to be doing an episode on credit card.
Jason and I will be doing a credit card point episode.
Oh boy.
The people demanded it.
The people voted on six topics and by far there's no narrow win or anything in this
election.
That's right.
It was credit card points by like 10 percentage points and that's out of six choices.
It's crazy actually in hindsight how smooth that election went by the way.
That's crazy.
Oh really?
I thought it'd be kind of a little nutty, but it was just like chill and everybody liked
the results and it was good.
We knew by the afternoon election day before the polls even closed.
Yeah.
And then the loser came out and was like, wow, I lost a fair fight.
This is really fun.
And it was chill.
That's kind of nice.
The lines were longer for ice cream at the end of the night because everyone's like,
well, I think we earned this.
We're recording this Monday, November 4th.
Just to time stamp it.
You do kind of have to time stamp it.
You know that's the joke.
But I do think you have to say we have no idea.
We don't.
By the way, I do love all these tangents.
I'm imagining Scott right now with his little steam coming out of his damn ears listening
to this.
He's popping his AirPods out right now.
Yeah.
They're fried.
They're fried using recording equipment in a hotel spa.
That's right.
But no, LCD, I think especially if you go live, it's not a fish situation where I don't
think it translates to the record, but like live really.
I think the difference from somebody who might think they're OK to somebody who really likes
them is like dance music where there's a lot of repetition, but that's kind of the point.
You want to just be vibing on the groove for nine minutes.
If you like to vibe on a groove for nine minutes straight, that's more maybe your band.
The same groove will be just repeating for like three minutes with little changes, percussion
changes, synth changes.
And that's especially if you go and you have, if dad has a couple drinks and he's alone
and just vibing on the floor like a cool older man, like on the on the standing.
I thought you meant like you've like fell down and somebody did fall down.
Oh, no. I got to the concert and I immediately saw there was an EMT there in the back with
a like a board or whatever we call it, the stretcher or whatever.
Yeah. And I go, oh, God, what dad is going to need this by the end of the night?
No, man. And it was that I was a young lady.
Oh, no. I was like immediately.
I was like, oh, God, somebody hit the deck and then they ran over.
I think she was probably died.
They're all dehydrated from what the drugs they're doing.
Oh, I went to go see the new pornographers that the will turn one time and everyone was
lining up outside because you get to the will turn a little early.
You can just stand on the floor area.
So everyone was getting there early.
So and this like teenager was just walking up, joined the line and just like face planted
like on the concrete and just stood up, just covered in blood.
Oh, no. And it didn't.
They didn't like stumble or I don't know what was going on with them.
But it was just very shocking to see.
Well, it's like we know this from like professional wrestling fandom.
You get the right spot up in the head like that head.
Blood will just come out super thin.
Yeah. Looks good. Good color on that kid.
Yep. Made a few bucks that day, I'm sure.
Yeah. That's the angle's green.
You know what I mean? Sold the angle for sure.
That's right. But yeah, anyway.
Look, this naughty list will take us on tangents.
We're not even thinking about right now or today's episode.
But we are ostensibly here to talk about 20,000 leagues under the sea at Tokyo,
Disney or Tokyo, Disney, sea specific baby, which is half day trip.
You get all the Tokyo, Disney, sea you need.
No, I'm sure I'm on your side.
I do like the more I think about it, I would do I would do a day and a half.
I'd do two days at Tokyo, Disney, sea, I think I've grown there.
Disneyland. I think I said this before.
I almost would skip Disneyland and in Tokyo, skip it.
Yes, it's not offensive to do that.
Although I would say now I'd probably have to go
because I couldn't skip the Beauty and the Beast ride.
I'd have to see that thing.
That's true. There's a couple of things.
And like the Monsters Inc ride is really good.
But Beauty and the Beast is I didn't love that Monsters Inc ride.
Loved Honey Hunt.
Well, yes, didn't.
I like that a lot better than monster.
But I do like the Monsters Inc.
Yeah, I didn't.
I didn't. I didn't.
I don't remember it. I went on it.
Now hold a flag. You shine a flashlight on things.
You like shine a light on the monsters.
I know it's fun.
Again, it's not in the League of Poo or anything.
No, Poo is great.
Yeah, Poo is amazing.
And then Beauty and the Beast looks amazing.
And then they're going to have like a brand new Space Mountain in a year or two.
What are they doing to the Space Mountain?
They demolished it.
Like not a refurbish.
No, they're building it from the ground.
That's crazy.
They set it on fire and the whole thing burned up.
Oh, boy. They're building a new one.
Yeah, that's cool.
I mean, well, maybe I do.
I got to go back to Disneyland.
Oh, yeah. So I was just like, especially if you go in a year or two,
it's like you got to go at least at least a half day at Tokyo Disney.
Yeah, like a day and a half to Tokyo.
You have to do two full days, which you shouldn't.
You should do three or four.
We've established on this show.
Yep. If you're doing to your half day at Disneyland,
Tokyo, Disney and then half day,
Disney and then the full day at Disney.
Yeah, because you got to do a full day at Universal Osaka.
That was a big surprise for me. It's far.
It's it's a different trip.
But if you if you I know you want to get to Japan, you're talking about it.
You want to do it at some point if it happened.
No. Yeah.
But if you don't don't skip Universal, Universal is a great choice.
Because they still have Jaws.
The Jaws are so fun.
My friend Jaws again.
Jason's friend Jaws.
The Amity boat tours with the grenade launcher, you know.
It's so good. And that was so that's why.
And that's why I went because I wanted to do it.
I heard about it.
The even the it's because the Jungle Cruise ish where somebody's like talking.
But even like the guy speaking Japanese, I got all the jokes
because it's just the rhythm of jokes.
It was just and like he shoots the thing and that blows up the gas.
He actually shoots the gas gas with the grenade launcher and it blows up.
And he like does this like take to the audience.
He's like, oh, sorry.
Basically, it's like it's so funny.
It made me laugh so hard.
I didn't do I know I'm mad at myself.
I keep floating.
I'm like, we celebrate Christmas.
Disney to like the family.
And I think everybody's looking at me like, no, we're not doing that.
I'm like, it would be fun.
I still think it holds.
I think it's cheaper to take a trip to Tokyo and go to Disney
and Disneyland than it would be to do two days at the Grand Californian.
Oh, yeah. 100 percent.
It would be. Yeah.
So maybe we all go to Christmas at Tokyo.
Well, you get the cave seat pockets.
Oh, that's a tradition.
Yes. In Japan.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, yes, this is this.
I feel like this ride is a little bit even overlooked in the
when you're hearing about how great Tokyo Disney is.
Yeah, because it is really a sleeper.
Awesome ride is that sleeper.
But you know what I'm saying?
It's like if you go down the list, like Journey to the Center of the Earth,
Sinbad, which is just my favorite is my favorite ride in both parks.
It's my favorite Disney ride.
And I that doesn't make that.
I wouldn't argue with that at all.
Yeah. That is so how much I love it.
That is how much our hearts swelled.
And it's everybody who does it. Yeah.
Also, we haven't had anybody who we were like, oh, go on Sinbad.
They were like, that sucks.
Everybody kind of comes back like teary eyed.
I mean, like that plucky little Sinbad, I mean, so nice.
I I'm really freaking out if I if I told this story on the on the Bronto
rap episode, but I tell you about my Sinbad thing with where I did it three times
for the Sinbad ride today.
I don't know. Well, real quick, there's a dark ride
that's kind of small worldish in Tokyo, Disney, DisneySea.
And I didn't know anything about it before we went on.
It's got an original Alan Menken song, which I think is like
the second best song Alan Menken's ever written.
It's incredible. Part of their part of your world. Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, go ahead.
So so I did the ride because I heard about it.
I loved it. Just a great ride.
And then I and I but the other thing that's great is even in Tokyo,
it is you see short line.
I just went right to the back of the line. So short went right in.
Do it again. And one of the one of the women, one of the employees,
they're, you know, Japanese.
And she goes, she looks at me, she goes like going again.
And I go, yeah. And she goes, wait, wait.
And as my boat's going, she goes, wait, wait.
I see her in the back there.
And I go, oh, what was that?
I do the whole right again.
And I come around to go exit.
And she comes up and she goes, no, no, stay, stay on the boat, stay on the boat.
And then she hands me this little pamphlet.
Now, I've been traveling in Japan solo.
I did. I did like a week and I was exhausted, jet lagged.
And like I was, you know, like you don't get to share a lot of stuff with people.
You know, traveling solo, so you chat with strangers.
But, you know, you're in Japan.
I don't speak Japanese.
And so I, you know, I started to have all these Cuban connection moments.
And she goes, wait, wait, stay on the boat.
She hands me this this this pamphlet.
And it's the it's the Sinbad song translated to English.
And she goes, so you can sing along.
And my eyes started watering up and I was like, oh my God.
And it was like, great.
And I sat there with my little thing and I sung along with the song.
And wow, it was that Sinbad is the best.
I'm serious. I got like a little chills.
Yeah, that's how much that's the Disney thing.
Right. That's what you want.
It's a great version.
Alan Menken performs it.
There's a YouTube from the D23 at Tokyo they had a couple of years ago.
And he performs it in English.
And there's just people in the audience just like weeping.
It's impossible not to.
Yeah, possible not to.
It was it's crazy.
It's crazy what just that song does.
The ride itself is amazing or great.
But that song is what takes it to this next level.
Yeah. But yeah.
So so you can lose that like 20,000 leagues is so amazing.
Yes. When you talk about
there's so much good stuff there.
But yeah, this ride, this ride would be like a top three ride
in another domestic park, probably.
Yeah. Like it's that good.
Well, you know what?
It fits for me in terms of like like if I do a Disneyland trip
and this is like a California guy, I've got to go.
I get to go to Disneyland more than other people do. Right.
Like if you're if you go once, you got to do Space Mountain.
You got to do Pirates. You got to do Haunted Mansion.
Like those are probably the big three.
If you're in the main park.
Yeah. The main part.
And I like throw Indiana Jones in there because I love it.
Indiana Jones.
I think if you're like Johnny never, never went to Disney,
I think those are the three you got to kind of do to say you've done Disney.
And but then I I think that like if I do a Disneyland day, I do have like
I got to do either Pirates or Haunted Mansion.
That's kind of on the list.
Maybe not both, but I got to do one of those.
And then I got to do like Big Thunder because I like it.
And I'll do Rise of the Resistance now because that's great.
But I always have to do at least one dark ride.
Like it's usually Mr. Toad or Peter Pan.
Yeah. Or one of those things.
And I think that 20,000 Leagues at Tokyo Disney is like kind of like
it's a must do dark ride.
It's just kind of like it's a break from everything else.
It's low key.
It's got mood for days.
It is like, you know, yeah, it's it's so vibey.
It's so vibey.
Watching the a few videos of before this, the sets are incredible.
Yeah, like and the the area itself, I mean, so much kinetic energy
with the boat going through the mountain and the Nautilus is parked there
and all these walkways like it's amazing.
Like I don't if I went to you to see see tomorrow, I'm like, oh, I want to see
the classic Disney seat.
Like there's this new Fantasy Springs area with Tangled and Frozen and Peter Pan rides.
And I'm like, it's kind of a pain in the ass to get into, as with any new theme
park product nowadays, it's a pain in the ass for the first three to six to 12 months.
Yeah. And I'm like, I think I'm more excited to go to the best theme park in the world.
Like, I still haven't experienced that.
Yeah. Before I get to all the new rides at it, you know, I think when I was there,
they just opened the new version of Soarin and that was just like a four hour line.
I'm like, I don't know.
I've got Soarin, huh?
I'm sure this new Soarin is great for this stuff.
But their new line, the new line, the new queue is better.
I'm sure. Oh, at land or at sea.
At sea. OK. Or wherever it is.
Yeah, it's at sea. Yeah.
But like Toy Story, Midway Mania, I would take a picture with Big Woody
head that you enter it through. Yeah, we didn't do that.
But I don't need to do that.
I've done that in multiple parks at this point.
Yeah. But you need to see Harrison High Tower's statues of bosomy women.
Well, of course. In the queue of the Tower of Terror.
Tower of Terror is also really good.
That's Disney Sea and that's a real, that's the one I wouldn't pass up on.
That's an original story.
Like, I would have to see that.
There's also a magic trick on that one that I truly don't understand.
Like, I see, I think I know what you're talking about.
It's the idol. Yeah.
Pre-show. And it's a thing that like when I was like watching it
and this thing disappears and I'm like, I was like,
there's no misdirection. You're looking right at it.
There's lights shining and stuff like that.
But it's you don't feel it drop or go anywhere.
It's just right. That's great.
Somebody online, I think, slowed it down.
And I think it really what it is is just it shoots down so fast.
Yeah. And it's kind of in the dark and there's like a little flash.
Yeah. It's all timed out perfectly.
But I'll say this about the twenty thousand leagues,
the entrance and the entrance area.
When I was there's another this is another my my my Disney stories.
When I was like when I did that, see, is like when I walked in,
you know, they don't have the castle, they have the volcano.
When you walk in, it's kind of a big thing.
And it is like a great entrance.
You walk through, you're like, wow.
And I was like, wow.
And there's like a Japanese woman left.
And she's like her eyes were open.
She's like, wow. And I'm like, and I looked at her and I go,
we made eye contact. I was like, it's good.
And she looks at me, she goes, it's good.
We like high fived and we ran all these moments with strangers.
I had was so great to there.
That's a really we have.
I think we were getting on this ride toward the end of our trip.
And I think a cast member was like, what's your favorite ride here?
And I think we said Sinbad.
And she was like, that's my favorite, too.
Oh, like you do get little like moments like that.
Yeah. It's pure, pure feelings of what I mean.
Do you guys I mean, you guys have been more recently than I have.
Do you feel like the cast members at Disneyland in California?
Do they still have that kind of like warm?
They're really excited to be there.
That that extra kind of I kind of think that the cast members are part of like
the Disney charm to me.
I think they're above and beyond.
Well, here's what I'll say.
I like a couple of years ago when I get in that kind of love at Six Flags.
Let's just say that.
No, the different kind of love flags.
You can not even spot love, you know, not even a transactional thing.
Yeah, you'll get vape love.
You can see a lot of people making out in the lines, but that's not love.
Well, it could be love.
It could be love.
They don't lead to love.
Do you see the version of love? Yeah.
Well, teenage love is a version of love.
Teenage love is a they're very they're very much in love.
They just don't know. They don't know they're not yet.
That makes it so pure.
That's what makes it so pure.
A couple of years ago, when they would do Guardians of the Galaxy,
the the tower, the Halloween overlay,
Mitch, God, Monsters After Dark, I can't remember anything.
Monsters After Dark, they would do
like a bit where the clothes were tattered on the employees.
And the first year or two, they would have employees do a bit.
We're like, oh, my God, you got to get out of here or whatever.
Or like somebody pretended he was like a monster inside the skin costume,
basically, where it's like, oh, hello, baby.
I'm just a regular human or something.
They were doing all these fun bits.
And then I did it this year and I was like, yes, seatbelts.
Where's the seat like tug on the yellow strap?
So I do feel like maybe I haven't seen a lot of fun.
Theatrical employees lately. Yeah.
And on one hand, I'm like, I miss seeing more like a goofy person
at the Haunted Mansion trying to scare little kids. Yeah.
But then you're also like, are they making enough money to really
have to put in the energy? Yeah, that's the thing is, I do feel
I don't want to be like, this isn't up to my standards.
But that is incumbent on Disney to pay them enough that I like that job.
And because obviously, it's like the type of job that if you're
in your 20s and you like Disney and you got paid decent,
what a great job that must be. Yeah.
Yeah, I think the rise of resistance still has the yes.
Those guys do a good job being scary resistance or empire people.
Oh, my God. I can't even think of that.
Well, there's the resistance and the first order, the first order.
Of course, the first order is a lot different than the original.
Yeah. You remember when Luke was like, we've got to fight the first order.
I forgot about that.
Star Wars four, which is a lot different.
Yes. And and that change paid off big time.
I was so mad at my dad that he showed me Star Wars four first when I was a kid.
Why would he show me Star Wars?
You should have waited until the other one.
Yeah. Like, I don't know what my dad was thinking when he showed me Star Wars.
Very foolish.
Yeah. So so this one, or did I cut you off in another story?
No, no, I was I was I was I was just to say, like, when you see the volcano
and, you know, like in Disneyland, you could go inside the cat.
You see the cats, you go inside, but it's not that impressive.
But when you go inside the volcano
and you see the Nemo land, the 20,000 Leaves of the Sea land, mysterious island.
Yes. Yes.
It's crazy. It's such a great reveal.
And there must be some forced perspective
because it feels so much bigger than it should be.
Would you like to turn a corner and you're just like, what?
And you're looking down into this thing.
And there is potato churros there.
Oh, yeah. I didn't try them.
With a line of ketchup inside the churro.
Oh, Jason, what do you think?
I like that. Like the sound of that.
Pre let me ask you this, though, with other things
where you would use like a pump ketchup after the after you got your food.
Would you do you like being able to distribute the amount of ketchup or
like would you take a hot dog where they gave you a little ketchup?
Or would you try to do your own?
Well, I would, because I'll tell you what those pumps are impossible
to make a straight line with.
If you're making a puddle of ketchup for French fries,
that's one thing.
But inevitably, you try to get the pump going.
And like the first spot you hit is going to have a glob of ketchup
before you get a line.
But this question can be for everyone.
Would it be offensive, though, if they were to put ketchup on everything,
not just on like a churro or some specialty item?
If you were to go to Disney and they were to put the ketchup on,
would you try to go, well, give me extra so I could dip?
Or would you be fine with it?
Whatever they decided.
I think I'd be fine with it.
I mean, I've always liked ketchup.
I was always a big ketchup kid.
But I mean, are you like a dipper?
Do you like a ton of ketchup?
Would you like be upset that you weren't getting like a ton?
Like, oh, I see what you're saying.
Yeah, sorry.
No, I don't think so. OK.
I hear what you're saying.
It's so funny that we would order like we would order
the loaded fries with like sauce and stuff on it.
And we would take it as it comes.
I go, this is how it is.
But if you're saying it's a little different with ketchup,
it is a little different.
We expect to like customize our ketchup.
I'm shocked he said that because my first reaction was like
like a little side of ketchup, just in case I need to use it up a little bit.
Well, this is a local thing.
But if you guys have been to Walt's, right?
The pinball bar here. Yeah.
They do a hot dog there and they do an incredible ketchup job.
They'll pre ketchup the thing.
And oh, interesting.
It's a little swizzle.
And it's a talk about straight line.
It's like a perfect swizzle.
The lines are all the same size.
No globiness. It's just like it's incredible.
And I love that hot dog for getting my ketchup like that.
It's interesting. All right.
Well, I'll try that.
But yeah, I I did just go to award wieners.
My phone died at award wieners.
I got on my computer and I texted Lindsey.
My phone died.
I'm on my on my computer at award wieners.
You have a picture of the text.
But I got Jason's favorite film strip fries.
I do like those fries.
And they're like they're not like film strip fry.
What is a film?
It's like a little moon or something.
It looks like a moon or like fry.
But the fries are a different shape.
Kind of. Yeah.
They're almost like crisps or something.
Kind of like a potato wedge.
Oh, like a little half moon.
Kind of. Yeah.
And they're like they're good freezer fries.
That's almost what I.
But I'm like, oh, Jason's kind of like, look,
have I given him some some of the business for saying
he likes film strip fries from award wieners? Sure.
But I was eating them and I went, well,
there is something to these film strip fries.
I have to give it to them.
They're good.
I have to limit them.
Fries are one of the things that I am like,
they say salad or fries.
I just force myself to do salad nowadays.
Force, yeah.
I'll just go crazy.
You grab your own arm and start squeezing it.
Go and say salad, say salad, say salad.
Well, I sometimes like I work.
I go to Jamie and say, do you want one of us get fries?
One of us get salad and we share like.
And then you eat all the fries, she eats all the salad.
I know how that I know.
I know that game goes well.
But also, like, I really only want like four or five fries.
Like, I don't want a lot of fries.
Usually too greasy.
Make me too bloated on that.
I can't get on board with that.
I want a ton of fries.
I'm finally doctors of water is kind of trying to get my diet and water
and like up the fruits and vegetables and like cut back on sugar,
because that's like my one vice.
Getting your diet or that's like asking Sampson to cut his hair.
That's your power, Jason.
And right after we bought all those bags of day after Halloween.
Oh, I think we have like four or five, four or five.
Does that mean eight? Huh?
Does that mean eight? No, it was four.
It was buy one, get one free on some of the bags.
And we bought four bags.
And then the next day I was like, I don't want those Reese's bats.
So it sounds like it's more than four.
No, I think it's five.
Oh, it's five. OK, OK. Yeah.
And what were they?
Um, I think it was a bag of fun sized Kit Kats.
OK, maybe two bags of like, you know, sugar skull Reese's,
which I was disappointed because they're tiny.
Yeah, they're shaped like Calaveras day Azucar, the Mexican day,
the dead sugar skulls.
Are they like the size of like a little the little gold foil cups?
They're like the size of like if you get a like candy cane
or a teddy bear shaped one at Christmas.
So thick, but small. Yes. OK.
And then a bag of bats, which I was a bag of bats of Reese's bats.
So you have three bags of Reese's.
I think so. Yeah.
Dude, I lost track.
No, I've lost track. I'm trying to think.
I know what candy we had. Yeah.
We had one bag of Reese's.
And they were like some pumpkin shape, I think, whatever,
which always when they're different shapes,
they're almost better than a regular cup.
They are for sure better.
For some reason, I think it's the distribution of peanut butter
and chocolate or whatever.
Yes. You try that if you're at a gas station, the caramel cup,
the caramel Reese's cup. I haven't tried that.
I haven't tried that. It's a it's a crazy variant.
It's nuts. Yeah, OK.
Caramel and Reese's just like you don't think they go together.
But of course it does. It's all sugar.
Of course it goes together.
But I do. I do agree. I love shapes.
I do love the shapes. Did you say all of them?
Was there a missing one?
That's four. Right.
Or did you say I there's three Reese's and then there's one.
I think the Reese's sugar skulls who buy one get one free
and then just a markdown bag of Kit Kats.
So Kit Kats, bats and two bags of sugar skulls.
That's four. So that's four. Yeah.
OK. Yeah.
Well, if you go home and you find an extra one, we'll tweet a picture.
OK. To show everyone. Yes.
So that's the thing that's wild.
You've said that before. You only want four fries.
I want the five guys where the bag is spilling over with fries.
Well, I kind of either want four.
I want them overflowing in a dirty paper bag.
I love the the CEO of five guys is like it's like a psychological trick.
What they do, you know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah, where they overload the fries in the cup.
And then there's a bunch in the bag.
So you're like, oh, my God, look what I got away with.
Like, look at the extra I got.
And it's a trick they do to make you feel you've gotten more.
And it works every time, right?
Even though it's one simple trick
to keep me coming back to five guys, guess what?
It worked. Even though it's 19, tricks wouldn't fool people.
The price of those burgers, even though it's like $19 to go to five.
I know. Mysterious Island is the name of this place.
And I Volcania Lagoon is the name of the water.
Well, that's great.
That's great. In between, like in the volcano.
So, yeah, we were talking about like you see a volcano in the distance.
And yes, you assume it's just a facade or something.
And then, you know, you can go inside the volcano, essentially.
And it's a pretty expansive space.
There's a bunch of water there.
There's a bunch of different things.
And then there's like three different exits.
So you can go into different parts of Disney Sea from there.
Yeah, it's a hub. It's a little mini hub. Right.
And I actually did not put you guys in the spot,
but I did watch this kind of interest.
I watched the 1954 20,000 Leagues before this episode.
Oh, yeah. Have you guys watched that recently?
I think we watched it when we did the original 20,000 Leagues
episode six years ago. OK.
But I haven't seen it. James Mason.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's what it sounds like to me.
Yeah. Objectively not Indian.
Like he was often portrayed as. Yes.
But he's but that the the mysterious island,
it is like a lot like the movie,
because I watched a ride through after I watched the movie.
And it is like they they really recreated it in a really cool way.
Like, you know, if you're a fan of that movie and I don't know
kind of why you would. I don't know if I love that movie.
I don't know if I.
There's things about it that are cool, but I don't know that I loved it.
Yeah, like, but there's plenty like the sets and stuff.
Yeah, the sets are amazing.
The underwater sets are great. I like that song.
Sure. You can't remember it now, but I know there's that.
It's about like he's kissing a shark and sailor song. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Kirk Douglas is kind of insane in that movie. Yes.
He kisses a seal.
Everybody kiss or the seal kisses everybody. Right.
Which is all pretty cool.
That's one of those things. Yeah, that's awesome.
You can't act with you can't.
We're too woke for having seal actors now, dude.
Like you used to be CGI seals and CGI seal kisses.
Yeah, no, there was like one.
There was one take where Kirk Douglas was getting a kiss from the seal
and the seal like nipped at him and it looked kind of dangerous.
And then he was like, whoa, and kind of got back into it.
But like that made that like, yeah, that's if you're drunk and hang out.
That's the danger. Yeah. You know, magic magic.
They should have real seal kisses at Disney.
The behind the scenes of one of the older Bond movies
where like Roger Moore and his stunt double are running across alligator heads.
Yes. Yeah, there was a stunt double doing that.
Yeah, I but there is behind the scene footage
where like one of the gators almost kissing.
Oh, yeah. Oh, it's insane. Yeah.
That must be like an act that people used to do in alligator farms.
Like you could run across alligators. Oh, I'm sure.
Because that's like not something that I think that somebody can create
whole cloth and be like, oh, well, what if he just ran across alligators?
Like like like a fucking cartoon? No.
Like that has to be like a thing that like, oh, I used to see this act
where they did alligator running or whatever. They look like rocks, right?
Yeah, I don't think so.
Oh, they look like rocks. Let's just do it.
Things were better back then.
I was when I go.
It's one of those things that I get why you don't do it.
But there is a movie.
Whenever I do a movie podcast, I will always try to get people
to do a thing called Kung Fu Kids 2. Have you ever watched this movie?
No, it's on YouTube and a very low res thing.
But I watch it like every year now because I just love it.
I used to watch it as a kid.
I had a VHS of it and just ran it through.
But it's it's a it's like a Hong Kong
Kung Fu movie starring children with the children doing their own stunts.
And it is unbelievable. Like it's they're so good.
Yeah, very, very good.
But there's like a like a 10 year old and they're doing the thing
where they they slide him across the table and he's like busting through glass
and he gets thrown off.
And and then like, well, and the other stunt performers
take worse bumps than they do.
It's it's great, man. It's a great movie.
But it's one of those things they go like, of course,
I would never want to have kids done that or do that's awful.
It's bad. You can't do it. It's dangerous. It's terrible.
But I'm so glad this is here.
I'm so glad we have this.
Well, the kids, they were OK.
Maybe they were they didn't get hurt.
I mean, they got hurt. I'm sure they got hurt.
I'm sure they got live. Yeah.
Of course, they got hurt.
This isn't three ninjas where they like cut away at the last moment.
Yes. And I think three ninjas was a remake of Kung Fu kids.
Oh, really? Because it's it's three kids.
It's three kids and they live with their grandfather.
Their grandfather trained them.
And I only watched Kung Fu kids who I've never seen Kung Fu kids one.
But we only had the VHS of Kung Fu kids to Kung Fu kids.
Yeah. Wow.
The grandpa and the grandma have a fight on soda cans.
They put soda cans on the ground and they have to balance on top of soda cans.
And the first one to touch the ground loses the duel. Really?
And they fight over the custody of the kids.
This sounds good. It's a good movie, dude.
All right. All right. I'll watch it. I'll watch it.
Yeah. Kung Fu kids. Wow. Yeah. Two, two.
All right. So that's nineteen thousand nine hundred ninety three tangents.
We're close to already getting. Yeah, we're in. Yeah.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
Well, I should bring up like a big element of this ride
where, you know, Disney has done so many water dark rides,
multiple submarine rides that are always a pain in the ass to operate.
And this one they solved by just making a dark ride,
albeit a suspended dark ride, and just putting water and bubbles in the windows.
And it works.
It reminds me of the like, I think, now debunked
story of like NASA spent all this money developing a pain pen
that can write in space. Cosmonauts just use a pencil.
Yeah, like it's like, oh, they lapped us so easily on this one.
It's like, no, you don't build a water ride.
You you build the magic trick.
Yeah, it works so good.
I mean, even if you're I'm sure you're watching the ride through videos
and it looks good, like you just forget.
But even you're in the middle thing,
because also like what you're not getting from a ride through videos,
the sound is amazing.
Like the bubbles like all surround you.
Everybody has different ports to look out of.
And unlike what's that?
I guess it's Nemo and friends now, the one in the that used to be
the the orange submarines that are in next to Matterhorn.
What's that? Yeah.
Finding what is the official name?
I just always call it the Finding Nemo subs.
Oh, yeah. I don't know what the official name is.
It used to be called. Why don't I? Why can't I pull that?
Oh, it's I think it's the submarine.
The original name was Submarine Voyage.
So now I think the new name is Submarine Voyage with Nemo and friends.
Well, the but those that ride, I went there maybe five or six years ago.
I remember I had good memories of it.
But I went one time at Disneyland trip when I was a kid.
And I remember the scary dragon thing, the underwater crazy eyes.
The sea serpent is like like scared me.
But it like sticks in my craw.
But I loved it.
So I'm like, oh, I'm going to go like it was like twenty eighteen.
I'm going to go on the right.
And I am a big fella.
But I had a crunch and crunched down and I couldn't even see out the port.
And I was claustrophobic.
It was a horrible experience.
I yeah, James Claude claustrophobic.
And I'm just not navigating that mobility wise these days.
So I'm like, but the twenty thousand leagues at Disney see.
Yes. It's like a little claustrophobic, a little tiny.
But you just walk in.
It's just a normal little contraption.
You walk in.
Yeah. It's a little box and it feels great because there's a lot of room between the seats
because I think every seat, there's a seat on the left on the port and the starboard side.
Yeah. Pardon me.
And then there's aft and rear.
I only know these from crossword puzzles, not from being salty at all.
Oh, OK.
But but but but you could fit two people on a seat per window.
So it's only six people in this big box and it feels spacious.
It's tall enough when you're sitting down.
It's like it's and the windows are huge because they're not worried about actual water coming in.
So it is a comfortable ride.
It's sweet. And you get to toggle the searchlights.
Yes. Spotlight, which to me, I'm like, there's all this stuff about interaction and gamification.
And I'm like, kind of want to just do that spotlight.
Yeah. Well, I mean, that's here's the big trick on it, too, is because it is like talk about dark.
It is actually a dark ride.
Yes. You don't see everything that's in that set.
And you can really kind of only see what your flashlight's hitting.
And so you are shining that flashlight around, trying to find the stuff that you want to see,
because once you take it off the octopus, like you can hardly see the octopus.
And that creates like a sense of like underwater adventure.
It's fun. It's it's and it's just a light.
Yes. And it's just so much like you can do the limitations any time you go on the actual subs
in Disneyland or Disney when it was open at Disney World.
Like you can't see very much on those because like they like just just a tiny little window.
Like this is like the best of both worlds to make you feel like, oh, my gosh, we're in this little
vehicle that is like really doing something.
But the window is big enough and you can actually see cool stuff.
And you get a sense of the scope and scale because that's what you don't get on like Nemo.
It's like you look looking even though you're looking into like show scenes and water.
Yeah. Everything looks like you're looking at a tiny little like elf village or something,
a little like Keebler elf village.
Everything feels so small to me on that on the Nemo subs.
Yeah. This is just the scope and scale of it is so impressive and is what they were going for when
they built those old subs.
Yeah. And like I said, it's just it's just it's just one simple trick.
Just bubbles in the window and the sound effects.
And you're and you're because I'm a big underwater head.
I love being under. Yes.
I found that out about myself.
If I if I if there's like a thing and I can scuba dive, I will scuba or I will like snorkel.
I will snorkel for like three hours without putting taking my butt out of the water.
Right. See, I just like being up high.
So suspended rides where the arm is above you and there's stuff underneath you immediately
appealing to me. You could go on this ride.
I get my water fix. You get your suspension fix.
Yeah. It's a good ride.
It's underrated. It's a good ride.
It's underrated. I do think it's a dizzy sea is like so many top ticket items that this
thing is lost in shuffle and big sets.
A lot of creatures, some nasty little freaks that help you out at the end.
They're nice. They're not.
They're not freaks. They're not bad.
No, I don't know what the freaks are from.
I'm trying to figure that out.
I think they're original.
I think they're I think it's supposed to be Atlantis.
Yes, it's supposed to be Atlantis.
They're little freaks from Atlantis.
Yeah, Atlantis freaks will like kind of like undersea alien type character.
They're not aliens, but yeah, they're like magical little sprites or something like kind of.
And they save you as Nemo and crew are debating.
Like, have we tried all the tricks?
Are we letting this volunteer crew eat shit or are we letting them die?
I went back and kind of zoomed through our original 20,000 Leagues episode and Scott had not
been on the ride yet, but he watched a video.
I insisted on not watching it and I like plugged my ears when people were giving details.
Yeah, but he said that it reminded him of ET and yeah, it does.
Like some of the like colors and the the sets and or whatever the show scenes like I can see that.
And then there's little aliens kind of at the end.
Well, this this is where I'm going to be because I just don't I didn't see those little freaks
during the Disney movie rewatch.
I was like I was kind of expecting.
Yeah, I don't think they're in the movie.
No, he talks about going to Atlantis and he talks about like he's got like a magical
like Iron Man, Ark Hart or whatever.
Yeah, that runs the ship.
It's like a magic MacGuffin of an engine.
But he does he doesn't he doesn't we don't see the little freaks in the movie,
which have been fun to see them.
Yeah, I'm sure they'd have been like Disney animated and been real cool.
But but these I this this is where I'm going to be tough but fair on 20,000 Leagues.
I think that once you get the giant squid,
well, it is the high point of that ride and you don't need the little freak section.
Here's but that's I think that's a dark ride thing.
The pacing on dark rides are a little funny.
Like the big thing is always in the middle and then there's like a slow ramp out.
Yeah, I felt this.
Sorry. What are you saying?
Oh, I was just going to say for if anyone wants to once to watch video,
but follow the narration, the channel LMG Vids has a subtitled video.
Yeah, with the English translation of what Nemo and crew is saying.
Yeah, so so you go through all these different show scenes
and then the climax action wise is the big squid.
Yeah, and I felt the same way the first time we went on it.
I felt like, OK, here it is.
And you're going to end with a big like, oh, my God, we're about to get fucked up.
Yeah, because the ride doesn't fuck you up.
No, it keeps you very gentle.
And it's because I was wondering if like we're going to get hit with a tentacle or something.
And like we don't really shake us.
I don't even think you have seatbelts on the ride.
No, these little like leather booth kind of things are like little chairs,
like a bench, I guess, which is nice and casual.
A blush bench. It's soft. It's comfortable.
It's a plush soft bench. Sounds pretty good.
Huh? Yeah.
So I but I was like, OK, here we go.
We're going to get a little we're going to get a big jolt or something.
And it's not it's nothing crazy at all.
And then it ends with these little magic Atlantis freaks.
And it sounded like I was about to choke up from tears.
And that's not why my voice said that.
It was Sinbad I was going to choke up and not these little freaks.
When you see that giant and he's playing the little violin, it's so good.
It is. Yeah, it is really good.
That giant is so good.
I would tear up at the giant almost every ride.
Yes. After that first ride, we did it like three more times.
And the giant room is a part of the song that happens on the Sinbad ride
where I start to tear like I would tear up again.
Yeah. Yeah.
But so the end of the 20,000 leagues, there's just this like you're kind of
all of a sudden like spotting a couple of these little Atlantis aliens freaks.
And they're like in the first you see them in the distance and they're poking out.
And then they get closer and closer and then they save you.
Yes. And at first, I agreed.
I felt like, well, that was it.
We need to end with a big drop.
We need to end with something.
The place blows up and we like shoot out something.
We shoot out a whale's blowhole from blue sky off the top of my head.
Sure. We got to do something like that.
But then the second time and then was like watching it on YouTube.
I really like that.
It's different that it ends on kind of a sweet, nice thing.
Yeah, because it does defy the expectations of a regular ride.
And I've said this before on the show.
I like moments of empathy, intimacy.
I like little beats in rides that are not just all action.
I could see three PO says we've just joined the rebel alliance
in the middle of star tours because it feels totally different.
So I think I've come in, especially in my older age,
I've come to appreciate a ride ending this way.
That is not just a conventional conventional like fireworks display.
I like that.
Like, who are these characters?
Oh my God, are they friend or foe?
Ah, they are friend.
They're saving us.
They've say like there's an I feel like there's a nice thing about it now.
And I think that anyone who goes on it now can think about it.
We don't need to end in a big explosion.
A ride can defy your expectations.
Yeah, I like rides have like an epilogue because I think about the
I think like the even like the Little Mermaid Dark Ride or whatever has the
you have the Ursula's there.
That's a whole.
And then I know this whole thing, but then it's like it's a lot.
The ending is like Ursula's in the middle, like the only scary part.
And then it's all soft.
It's like the kiss the girl song.
And then it's like she's in the distance.
She's dying in the distance.
Ursula is.
Yes, that's right.
In like shadow.
The shadow in the distance is like she's been stabbed in the chest.
Very much a and the kids were rescued by, oh, let's say Mo.
Yes.
And so that that one almost feels like and this is a discussion for a future episode of
that almost feels like the modern Walt Disney Company not wanting to scare people anymore.
Yeah.
And that's again, we're going to have there'll be a future episode
where we talk more about that because I do think like.
About scares in particular.
Scares or just sort of more intense things, because I think that in the recent years
they've wanted to reduce stuff that will make kids go a little like.
And I so like I think that's what happened with the Ursula thing.
Yeah.
I think because I mean, you're not going to have her, I guess, get stabbed,
but there should be like a climax if you're trying to just retell the story,
which is what that ride is.
Yeah, yeah, you could have you could just have her threatening the the.
Sure.
The boat and then like a boat cuts her off.
Just know you don't even see what happens.
But it's just like, you know, at least her threatening the boat.
But that is a scary scene in the movie.
Yes.
Which is cool.
Like it would be a cool way like there would be a cool way to recreate it on the ride somehow.
I think, you know, because I was talking about the sea serpent in that thing.
That's like for my childhood memories of going to Disneyland, I was probably like
eight or nine, you know, from Alaska.
So a trip to Disneyland was like this is like the one time we're going to do it, kids.
Like it wasn't like it wasn't like I know you guys were from
places you could drive to Disneyland, so you guys could do it every couple of years or.
Or a quick flight.
Oh, yeah.
But like Alaska is like it's no it was no small thing for us to get down there.
So but that's literally one of the few things I remember is that sea serpent and his crazy eyes
and that scared me.
Yeah.
But that's the thing I remember.
So you do need I think you need scary things on these rides.
And then that sea serpent was sold at a dirty abandoned sports authority in Sherman Oaks.
And I saw it and like my hackles went up.
I didn't have like a little like I had a physical reaction when I saw the thing.
And I was like, it's not so scary.
But then I imagined its eyes twirling.
I was like, yeah, but I wish they would almost like I know it's kind of the end of the ride
is a surprise that you see these little creatures, but I also wish they would like
market them a little more like I want to see them out there a little.
Have them hidden in the land.
Because you do get some of the Tokyo Disney specific characters in plush and toys.
And maybe I maybe I just haven't seen it.
If somebody knows if they do make these little Atlantis freaks, let me know in a toy.
Well, the fact that we're calling them freaks is like they should have a name.
They should be a little more branded than just letting us.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
That's like a vacuum of power that they're giving us.
Well, not knowing if they're friend or foe is like Nemo himself.
I feel like a lot of those stories, be it 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea or
Leave Extraordinary Gentlemen, no one knows where they stand with Nemo.
This is what I want to get into.
I want to get into this Nemo character.
I was watching this movie and I'm saying to myself, and this is why like 20,000 Leagues
isn't as big as like Wizard of Oz or like these big, big stories that people really like.
Or even something that's old enough to say now like Indiana Jones.
We all understand Indiana Jones.
He's like this dopey but heroic guy who's in over his head, but he somehow makes it
through through his grit and his courage and maybe being a little stupid.
But something about this character is very compelling and he will be compelling for
a hundred years.
Nemo, I don't get.
I was watching the James Mason one and the whole thing with Nemo,
it has the trappings of a good character.
He's this outsider.
He goes to the sea to have his own rules.
And he's going to do things his way.
He's kind of like an anti-capitalist, anti-colonist because he came from like,
as a mining slave was his like origin story.
He was like a slave in a mine and they killed his wife and kid and he escaped and then got
this big ship and now he's going to like take down all these British ships and it's like,
this is all cool.
But there's not been a 20,000 Leagues that's made gangbusters since the 54 one.
Yeah. I mean, I feel like the main things I know about Nemo,
mostly from Alan Moore in the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen comics,
has an autolist hates the British.
Like, and that I think obviously gets likely stripped away in the way a lot of those Disney
live action movies, certainly the old ones, like when they would have to simplify it for like,
you know, a family audience, an American audience,
like some of the weird stuff for the more meaner stuff gets taken out.
Are you, are you saying though that Captain Nemo is so hard to read, it's hard to like,
get like dig into him in a way.
It's hard to either root for him.
It's hard to like, it's hard to know what to feel.
Yeah. He's like, is he a baby face or is he heel?
Right. Wrestling terminology.
Yes.
You want to know.
I think he's a tweener.
He's your classic tweener.
Classic tweener.
Yeah.
Because like in the second League of Extraordinary Gentlemen book,
when they fight the aliens from the War of the Worlds,
Nemo at the end gets so pissed because they kill the aliens using germ warfare.
And Nemo's like, what do you mean you have this?
I'm not, I've got to be a part of this.
And he like sails away.
Yeah.
And then I think later books his daughter kind of takes over.
Yeah. He's like a good pirate.
Like again, in the 18th century, 19th century, I'm really bad at that.
But it's like, I never, when you say centuries, I never get the numbers right.
I always jump back into one.
I'm not going to get into my own insecurities about saying what century it is.
But yeah, like I want to, like I think Nemo has a lot.
I'm just surprised there hasn't been,
I guess League of Extraordinary Gentlemen is the most common recent one.
But even that was, the 90s did Alan Moore write that?
I think early 2000s, that kind of bad Sean Connery's retirement movie.
The movie I have not seen.
With Tom Sawyer is like a secret agent.
Yeah.
Like there are some, they take some big swings on like,
ah, Dorian Gray uses his anti-aging powers.
And I was like, no, I think this is one where he was right to turn down the rights money
or give it to Kevin O'Neal.
Then there's the, the, the, the safari guy, Alan.
Alan Quartermaine.
Quartermaine.
Yeah. We love Alan Quartermaine.
There was a David Fincher attempt, right?
At 20,000 leagues, maybe for Disney a couple of years ago, 10 years ago, 15 years ago.
And then it fell apart.
Maybe Brad Pitt talking about being in it.
I don't know who he was, but who he was going to be.
I mean, I think he was going to be the guy playing the turtle,
the turtle guitar kissing a seal.
That'd be a great role for Brad Pitt.
David Fincher would have wanted to use a real seal.
And they would have had to do 200 takes.
So good.
Oh, man.
That's how he does it.
That he would have gone through so many seals.
That right.
That's true.
Well, and he had to keep this, put the seal in its place.
He would, when they switched to digital, he'd be screaming out,
delete those last 10 takes.
It's a power play.
Yeah, of course.
So I don't know.
Maybe somebody will make Nemo popular one day.
Because I would, all this just to come around to say is like,
boy, would this ride do great in Disneyland.
Oh, well, sure.
Or even, like, how come this is not cross state side?
Other than Nemo's not that popular.
Nemo's not that popular.
I do wonder if, because like, the ride system is not,
I don't think, quite the same.
There was an idea to do Little Mermaid with something
that was kind of hanging from the ceiling
to make you feel like you were underwater.
And that they went with the thing that is the thing now,
clamshell on the ground, like Haunted Mansion, basically.
When he said it like that, it's so unromantic.
Yeah.
Well, what else is it?
It's a clam shell on the ground.
It's an omnimover.
I guess omnimover sounds more romantic.
But, you know, you can watch the ride through
of the hypothetical cool version online.
It was on a DVD like 20 years ago or something,
but it's online and it would kind of bob you through the ride.
And that's Tony Baxter's big thing is he was like,
that would have been better because that's actually
the transformative experience of going under the water.
Right.
That's actually giving you some extra feeling of specialness.
Like bobbing around.
Bobbing around.
You don't want to bob around.
But it's not quite the same thing here.
But I am surprised that they haven't used it
for something else.
I'm surprised they haven't figured out another ride,
stateside, to do something like this.
Underwater would be, I guess, helpful.
But you could do like a space ride or something.
You could do space.
It'd be an interesting way to do like,
I'm trying to think of like going through
like an abandoned space station,
but that's like too horror themed or something.
Well, yeah.
I mean, unless it's like they're cute aliens,
unless it's like Stitch is up there.
Or Mars Nines Moms is up there.
There's not enough good.
I'm trying to think of another undersea property.
Treasure Planet is up there.
Oh, we could do Treasure Planet.
Atlantis the Lost Empire.
Yeah.
I also like, I think it's fine to just do like,
as far as kids know, 20,000 Leagues on the Sea
is just like Thunder Mountain.
Thunder Mountain, I mean, I know.
Well, that's another long-
I know they're not making anything without IP.
Yeah, that's a long thing, yeah.
But yes, they're not going to do like a new like space time.
You could go to the Gungan Kingdom.
Yes, of course.
With Jar Jar Binks.
Yes, I would love to do that.
Bosnaz, yeah.
So yeah, I guess, I mean,
I guess there hasn't been an obvious choice
to use this ride system or technology.
But yeah, it's so cool.
And I don't know, there's really no, I don't know.
There's no Pixar, like, because Pixar's,
the new stuff is like what's going to happen.
Like Coco is going to be a boat ride
in California Adventure.
I mean, that's the obvious thing is you've got to
just replace the submarine Nemo thing with this.
Well, yeah, but that's not, probably not a room.
Yeah, but it's got to be a big showroom, this thing.
Well, I don't know.
It's-
I think it's somewhat big.
I don't know.
Look, do you want me to break out the Google Maps?
Because I will.
Oh, boy.
If you overhead Google Maps.
But it might be still hard because it's so,
the mysterious island is so big,
I might not be able to know where the actual showroom is.
And it's like halfway underground,
like it's under the side of the volcano.
You know what?
Here, talk amongst yourselves.
I'm going to look at the Google Maps.
Let me ask you this.
You're a seasoned vet of parks.
How well do you know geography of the park?
Like in terms of, when I, I'll say this,
in my experience, when I go to Disneyland or any Disney,
I don't know where I am or what the layout is in my head.
Like, I can't understand.
Like, I just walk and I know that,
like, oh, if we're at Haunted Mansion,
that means we're near Pirates.
That means we're near Big Thunder.
Like, I can kind of do the, the point to point,
but I couldn't like,
if you asked me to draw a map of Disneyland right now,
it would be so crazy.
Jason, here's him, Jason.
I think I know more than most,
but also I tried to not ruin the magic for myself.
Like, I still, like when you're on the parking lot tram
and you're, you're going,
and someone goes that show,
that's the Haunted Mansion show building.
I went, no, it's not.
No, that's a mansion in New Orleans.
Quite like I, I don't, I don't know.
I, you know, I think I can tell more
when they're doing big projects.
And you can see through clearings,
you can see through construction sites.
So I think I can navigate the park pretty well in my sleep.
Think I could find it.
Cause I mean, it, I mean, it's very famously the hub.
And then the left is the, the frontier land.
And then adventure land.
And then right is tomorrow land.
Yeah. I, so I get that sense of it,
but once I'm there, like I, I don't know where the,
I mean, that's part of their job, I guess.
I don't know what the show buildings look like.
I don't know how, like how far it extends out,
like the geography of it.
Like just an overhead map.
But like, if I looked at this Google map
that you're pulling up.
He has been very into Google maps and satellite maps lately.
Because it is fun to like, if you,
if you block out a chunk of like, oh,
this new project takes up X number of acres.
That's the number of acres they have to play with.
Yeah.
When they say they're going to do a new ride
and they don't tell you where,
it's fun to look around the map
and see where there's space available.
Yeah.
And plug in, you go, okay, this ride seems like
it's going to be this big, this new land.
Like, whereas the big thing right now
is where Avatar is going to go in California Adventure.
And people are saying,
I wasn't believing them for a while
that it was going to replace Hollywood Land
in California Adventure.
Yeah.
And then I started looking at the map and I go,
man, if they're really just going to use what they've got,
it's got to go in Hollywood Land.
It's where there's space.
It's where there's the most space.
Yeah.
And you can cut into the esplanade.
You can trim some of that.
I've heard rumors all their name.
You know what I'm thinking about?
I've heard some rumors, I don't even want to,
I don't even want to give any oxygen to them
that maybe that won't happen.
Who knows?
We'll see.
But it's fun to expect.
I can't tell what's a show building on an overhead
from this mysterious island and volcano.
Because is this in Journey to the Center of the Earth
share, like, show billing?
Like, is it?
I don't know because I don't know if they go both,
go down at the same time like the Avatar situation in Florida.
Yeah, when you, when you are in the,
was it Volcano Lagoon?
Volcanic, Volcania Lagoon?
Volcania, Volcania Lagoon.
Volcania Lagoon.
You can see a piece of the Journey to the Center of the Earth
car going through like a break in it.
So you see a little bit of it.
It's like test track.
Yeah, they're very close in that way.
But it is like, Nemo is like under the volcano.
So you can't really tell what the, because it's all,
it's got to be all underground.
I want to unplug, but it's like, that's 20,000 leaks here.
And that's Journey over here.
So I'm guessing that Journey show building is kind of
under the actual peak of the volcano.
Yeah.
That's more where that ride is.
And then it goes all the way around here.
And then 20,000 leaks is like this, I guess.
Because it's completely hidden.
It's interesting because Tokyo Disney Sea is like on Tokyo Bay.
It's on the bay.
And they do have earthquakes in Japan.
They sure do.
So like, I don't, I don't know that I would build
things on top of each other.
I don't know that I would put my magical stuff like stacked up.
I think there's something, and this is me.
I am not a geologist.
But I do think there's certain like bays
that are very protected from earthquakes.
In terms of, in terms of like the wave, the snobbing efforts,
like the wave would go past the bay
and then like around the corner kind of.
If it's like built out like a big island.
I think Tokyo Bay is a very protected bay.
Tomorrow, Tokyo paper, it's going to say,
Matt Mazzani says Tokyo Bay is safe.
Yeah.
No threat at all.
Dig, baby, dig.
I'm going to be stuck on that water topi ride
and a little auto thing just flying around.
Then all of a sudden the waves are going to just take me
and I would be just like floating through Tokyo on the water topi.
American geologist, Matt Mazzani on Podcast Arrived says SCZ.
As I was saying that, I realized like,
wait, I follow a bunch of like food YouTube channels
based in Japan and they're always like,
we went to this quiet little cafe.
You went to the ninth floor of a common office building
that opened directly into a cafe.
And I was like, oh, okay, I guess there is a culture
of building things on top of each other in Japan.
I don't think they're on top of each other.
Maybe just that last stretch is to some degree.
But once you think about the bay, I was saying,
oh, it's probably underground,
but how could you make something underground if you're on a bay?
You're going to get into the ocean.
Then Nemo becomes real and that's no fun.
That's a good question.
Maybe, I mean, this place is so special and magical.
Maybe there is some like trickery.
I'm not even like, yeah, they built on top of it or.
Yeah, or like the first part of the car ride
is like very far out or something like that.
It's, I mean, I think ultimately like think about Nemo is like,
I think the biggest piece about it is that it's
in Disney Sea, it does give you a sense of adventure
because you have to go down into the lagoon.
And I remember being kind of a trek and it's all that is like part of the ride in a way
you get your potato churro and you're walking down there.
And then you then you go on this thing and the ride is great.
Then you exit off into a totally different part of the park.
It does feel like a bit of an adventure in a way that not a lot of Disney stuff
like has that same thing.
I think maybe Haunted Mansion to me feels a little interesting
because you go to the New Orleans Square,
you go in and you kind of come out a different way in a certain way.
Right.
The ride is part of your journey through the park, which is a cool thing.
Yes, I think that it's not because Tower of Terror in Florida
obviously has the cooler room.
That's the fifth, fourth dimension room.
Fifth dimension.
Fifth dimension, whatever.
When the elevator car lurches forward, some people always say,
okay, well, the reason that tower is so good is because that extra room
because that an elevator is doing something you've never seen it do before.
There's a lot of truth to that.
That's why the California Adventure Version, which didn't have that,
is less successful, was less popular.
But the placement of that ride in California, I feel like also really hurt it
because when it was Tower of Terror, even though it's still a fun, good ride,
there was just something about it kind of being in this sort of boring
Hollywood land area, which we would just never go and do it.
And in hindsight, I'm like, oh, even a B-plus Tower of Terror
is worth going on more than I did go on it.
But in Florida, it's at the end of this long street.
It's set back.
You kind of walk up to get to it.
There is something that makes the tower there more special
just because of the way you get to it, the way you have to walk up
and the way it's presented in the park.
And Guardians, I think I like it better than Tower.
And it doesn't need that because that's not the vibe of it.
Even though it would be cool if it was in a big, crazy Marvel city,
which I guess if it's Avatar, that's not going to be the case
because we always thought they were going to build out a fun Marvel,
New York or California high-rise around it.
You build the Baxter Building next to the Guardians Tower.
That always made sense to me, but maybe it's Avatar, who knows, whatever.
But I do think that what you're saying is right.
And just the idea that you have to walk far to a volcano
and then there's different levels to the volcano when you're inside.
And then it's tucked in over here.
And it gives your brain a sense of, oh, I went on this little journey
and now I'm going to get to do this thing that's just a little secret.
It's like a little secret I get to do, even though it's one of the rides in the park.
Very expensive.
There's not good, clear signage.
It's not like this way to the ride or anything.
It does feel like you're kind of discovering things.
There are ride signs.
But I do feel like I wandered into it.
I do feel like I was walking and I go, there's a line down there.
Is that a thing?
And then you kind of go down.
Yeah, that is fun.
I think Cars Land does a great job.
I mean, the walking into Cars Land, walking past all the shops, down to Radiator Springs,
like all that stuff.
By the way, do people still like doing ride talk on this show?
Should we be talking about a TV special from the 70s right now?
If you want to get me started, we could.
We like to talk about rides sometimes.
Yeah, this deep ride theory.
Is that what people are still into here anymore?
Sure.
They like deep ride theory somewhat, but what they like more, credit card points.
Credit card points are good.
Hearing points.
And I will say this on the show right now.
I would like to make the Club 3 not just about credit card points, but all points in general.
App points, reward points.
Scott is falling out of his chair, wherever he is right now.
His brain is hurting so bad, it's pressing on his skull.
As if Marmaduke himself jumped on his lap.
He's got so much on his plate.
He can't handle a big old dog.
We told him not to get that big old dog.
Jason also just declared off Mike, Marmaduke month on the main feed.
Marmaduke May next year.
Reviewing all the Marmadukes and also all the Clifford movies.
Yeah, all the adaptations.
I don't know why we're doing.
Oh, is Clifford having something to do with Marmaduke?
Yeah, he's big.
But Clifford is a giant.
Marmaduke's just a regular sized big dog.
Well, you're distinguishing between massive and big dog.
Yes, I am.
So I'm just saying.
So this is May is big dog month, not Marmaduke month.
Well, I don't know.
You can have Balto.
I'm just blue skying.
Yeah, Balto's on the table.
No bad answers when you're blue skying.
Marmaduke month also includes other big dogs.
Other large dogs.
And that's May Tobin's big dog.
Oh, he's so big.
But he's a regular sized German Shepherd.
I know, but he's a handful.
Or German Shepherd.
No, no, he's a what?
He's a great date.
Or no, he's a-
No, that's Marmaduke.
He's a St. Bernard.
Come on, guys.
Act like you know your dog breeds.
Marmaduke, well, we'll have to brush up before Marmaduke May happens.
We both, we're studying before the night before the test is.
Listen, on a cosmic scale, Clifford is as big as Beethoven.
You know what I mean?
No, I don't know what you mean.
If you think about in terms of planets and universes on a cosmic scale,
they're very close in size.
Yes, that's true.
A lot of things on a cosmic scale are all sort of relative in size.
Yeah.
I mean, us and like a skyscraper in some ways-
Very close in size.
Close in size.
On a cosmic scale.
I mean, you're right.
What you said is correct, so I can't really dispute any further.
This is the type of talk you want on Marmaduke May.
Marmaduke May.
Opening up a fourth gate for this.
It's a dog door.
But the dogs are big, so it's really just a regular door.
It's a gate.
It's a gate for Clifford.
The doggy door.
Will Big Dog Month have a talk of Big Dog T-shirts?
Oh, of course.
I jumped the gun.
I got so excited.
I forgot I have to buy Jason a Big Johnson T-shirt for Christmas this year.
Big Dog is not as bawdy as the Big Johnson brand of shirts.
Yeah.
Write them hard, leave them wet.
That whole thing.
I'll get Jason a pack of three of some of those.
Man, I should keep a mouth shut.
But we should plug ears.
Jason, we should make some Big Jason T-shirts.
Like some Big Jason, like some puns and stuff in there.
And he's having some half moon fries or whatever the film is.
Film strip fries.
Well, it's film strip, half moon.
I'm showing my butt.
And I'll say something like strip him down, crunch him up.
Show your butt.
Big Jason T's.
Big Jason T's is a good idea.
You could have that one for free, fellas.
We'll give you some shirts.
You're going to be mad when Jason's in charge of the empire
and he's making like $10 million a year from selling things on like the boardwalk.
I'll be Winklevoss looking at all these Big Jason T's.
There is going to be like a way too long Netflix documentary.
Like the Von Tutsch doc.
If you were going to create Big Jason T's,
you would have created Big Jason T's is what you'd tell me.
All based on Jason's stories.
So it would be like, oh, my Airbnb bed is wet.
And then he'd be like, he's like soaked.
But it's really just about him finding a wet bed.
It's not anything dirty, but it could be interpreted in some ways.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
And it's certainly a call to anyone who wants to just draw these for free.
Right now to make us some Big Jason shirts.
Body or not?
It doesn't have to be body.
No, I like t-shirts a little body.
All right.
Just at least one body one for one.
Sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, there's a lot.
Look, we just set out a pretty aggressive 2025 schedule here
with Marmaduke May and a new line of t-shirts coming soon on Podcast The Ride.
So it's very exciting.
Universal is building a new theme bar.
But we've got Big Jason tees over a year.
Easier to get into.
Marissa Strickland, Jason Sheridan and I did improv under the name Leisure Suit Jason once.
Oh.
Leisure Suit Larry.
So he's certainly been in this avenue.
His character has certainly pivoted to being a little pervert.
Yeah, I would say a little pervert.
I'd say an impish lech.
An impish lech, okay.
Yeah, that's a little more class to him.
You don't need to go full Myrtle Beach on the Big Jason shirt.
That's right.
He could be looking over his glasses at a lady in a bikini and she's putting too much
sauce on the fries and it's like different.
Then I'm like, oh, I have to run.
I have the early dinner reservation at the fish house.
I mean, these are all just, anything I'm about to pitch probably could appeal.
You could pitch it to Archie for a Jughead story.
There's like a lady in a bikini and she's putting mustard on her hot dog and she's
squirting it so much that it's getting off the hot dog or something and Jason's diving
with a little cup to try to save the ketchup from hitting the sand.
Oh, like a dipping sauce cup.
Yes.
Because I've got a hot dog waiting for mustard.
Or you could have a different hot dog also catching.
Catching with another hot dog.
Right, that's pretty good.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So you get a little bawdiness, but he's, Big Jason is not worried about the lady.
He's more worried about the mustard or ketchup.
Yeah, no ketchup left behind.
Right.
Something like that.
You know, like it's not body, but it's like makes you feel uneasy.
By the way, the shirts are also very patriotic.
These are, it's a lot of flags.
There's a lot of salutes.
Well, I, you know, people think it's patriotic, but it's really tricolor printing.
It's a lot cheaper and a lot more affordable than full spectrum printing.
Full spectrum colors.
Is there, there has to be like a Big Johnson shirt that's extremely patriotic.
That's like my boner as at half mast or something.
Like there has to be some combination of these ideas or my boner is at full mast.
There has to be like.
Flying the flag today.
And like some like patriotic pervert wears it on 4th of July.
Yeah, there, there, there has to be some like Big Johnson shirt where he like.
On the day that Osama bin Laden got shot or something like that amongst yourself.
I mean, I'll take a look here.
Yeah.
There's a shirt that says love it or leave it.
And he's pointing out his boner.
That's right.
Yeah.
Like American flag board shorts.
Yeah, that's great.
That's great.
There's a big John Cena announcing the Osama bin Laden off to a permanent end.
There's a big Johnson shirt that just says, I stand with Texas.
And he's got, he's just like the guy's on there with a lady in a bathing suit.
I mean, I was misremembering big Johnson.
Big Johnson is a little bit of a Jason share.
Like a Jason Sheridan type.
He is like, shh, we're going to get sued.
No, when we start our own.
Big Jason's are totally different.
I'm sure the owner of big Johnson is a reasonable man who understands.
Who understands.
You don't know if he's a man.
That's true.
You know what?
I do know.
Let me assume on this one.
I would been a rent check.
I rent check that he's a man.
Oh man.
Well, big Johnson used to be so wholesome.
He used to just be about the politics.
These big Johnson shirts.
It was about, it was about being just horny, regular misogyny.
This is what Joe Brandon has done to this country.
Who?
The president, Joe Brandon.
Oh, I forgot about that guy.
Yeah, you forgot about let's go Brandon.
Oh, Joe Brandon.
The president, technically, as we record this.
Technically, he is the president.
After he's fighting kids, he's calling people garbage.
And then whatever he's doing.
He said Trump needed, guys like Trump, you need to bite him in the ass.
Or no, you want to smack him in the ass.
Yeah, yeah.
Did he spank or smack him in the ass?
Yeah, whatever.
I don't know.
He spacks.
I don't, I don't, I'm not mad at him for fighting the baby.
I don't know what's going to happen, you guys.
I don't know what's going to happen.
That's what I'm going to say.
It's fine to like.
48 hours, 24 hours.
I understand wanting to nibble like, like the air that there.
I get that.
I do.
Still photo belies that the video, everyone was laughing and having fun.
That's right.
They also like Photoshop, his eyebrows like tilted down.
So he looked angry and, you know, like he was trying to eat the baby.
Come on, guys.
Sure.
But you know what?
By the time everybody's listening to this, nobody even remembers that.
No, it's all lost.
Everybody remembers how smooth the election went and how easy the.
Monday, November 4th, 5, 13 PM is the timestamp for this moment right now.
All SNL cast members practicing different set songs at the piano.
We don't know.
There's a lot of uncertainty.
Yes.
So let's, okay, let me look through some notes here because there,
there was an actual English translation of the ride because the narration is in Japanese.
And it's not like it's an, it's amazing or anything,
but it's interesting Nemo.
Nemo is talking to the crew and he says volunteer crew.
So that's the idea of the ride is that you're all volunteers.
You're not actually sailors or whatever.
Yeah.
He says, this is Captain Nemo.
Welcome to the magnificent underwater world in this mysterious ocean.
There may be highly developed intelligent beings.
Your mission is to solve that mystery.
So it's translation, but that's a lot of pressure for volunteers.
So there is, it does feel like, because I, this didn't,
this wasn't conveyed to me just by going on the ride is that he,
he knows they're out there.
He's looking, Nemo is looking for these little guys, these little aliens.
Well, that does help our, that does help our, our case in terms of like,
why after the Kraken or after the squid, do you see these guys?
It was like, oh, that's what we, we got past the squid to get those guys.
That's the goal.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I've said this before.
I would, I want rides, do a ride where like you make me cry the whole time.
Yeah.
You know, I want to
feel something and you're a man in his forties, you know,
there's a lot of pent up stuff in there and you need songs.
You need LCD sound system songs.
You need movies.
You need things, you need Sinbad, a wholesome Sinbad ride to make you
as a, you know, get it out because we need to get it out.
We don't always get it out.
Yeah.
You know, and these things get it out for us.
I watched, I watched Interstellar yesterday and that scene where he like leaves his kid
and he's like, he's crying as he's driving away and she's like, oh, they're all zooming in.
Oh man.
It still gets me.
The, the, that Hans, that's good.
You need that shit.
You need the shit to make it all cry.
Isn't it weird?
I've thought about this recently.
Isn't it weird that that are, we've developed as humans to the point where we almost need
like a McCann, we need somebody to take it and take it from us.
They take it out of us.
Yeah.
It's not just like, cause you use so much stuff happens during the day that you just
don't process.
Yeah.
There's so much awful shit happening in the world that you just like zoom by.
Sometimes you go, I cannot process what I just saw on Twitter.
Like I cannot process some horrible thing I just saw on Twitter.
So it just goes in there.
It just goes in there.
And then you're watching karate kids too.
Karate boys too.
And something sweet too.
And you, maybe there's a sweet moment and you like start crying and it is sweet, but
you know, it's a movie and really what you're crying about is you saw something horrible
a week ago or you felt so sad a week ago and you never processed it.
Well, it's a weird thing.
This, this body we have, this mind we have.
Once again, on a cosmic level, we are in uncharted territories as humans.
We're supposed to like die at age 32 or whatever.
Like sure.
So like our, like that we're operating now in our, in our age, we're like,
well, we got to figure some stuff out.
We didn't, we didn't have our biology is like, we didn't have plans for these kinds
of emotions.
So we got to get things like Sinbad that to make us cry, to make our heads work right.
Well, that, that's it.
We desperately need these rides guys.
That's a joke that goes around squittering down there.
Then it was just like, we all know too much about each other.
Yeah.
That's true too.
Like, you know, I get mad at how someone chews gum or like, how do you eat?
You eat fish and chips with your hands?
Americans?
Like that was a real thing I saw a few days ago and I got stupid or just from reading.
Oh man.
You didn't cry about that though.
No, I didn't.
I cried about all the people like going like, no, you must be in Mayfield, England.
If you're using your hands, you have to use a four.
And I'm like, the fuck's eating fish and chips with a fucking nut?
Like Jason is consistently on different parts of the internet than me.
I always will say that.
I'm like, I don't know.
I'm fairly ill online, but he's yeah.
He, he, I didn't see any of this.
Fish and chips, Twitter, man.
That's a whole nother thing.
I'm not in there.
It's not in my algorithm.
Everybody asks like, oh, why are we, why, how are you still on Twitter and all this
stuff?
And I'm like, yeah, but fish and chips hasn't, hasn't gotten the threads.
Fish and chips, Twitter hasn't.
That's a big day.
I'm on the like, uh, uh, what was it?
I saw people go and like, oh, Chapparone is going to be so mad at Bow and Yang for
doing that moodang bit.
And it's like, they know each other.
They're like on record as being friends.
I know every word in that sentence.
I know I'm sad.
I know that every word, uh, is there a big Johnson shirt that says fish and chicks?
Fish and chicks.
Yeah.
What do we think?
Oh, and if not, that's a big, that would be a big sexy.
Yes.
Oh, nice.
I think it is.
I think big Johnson does have fishing shirts.
So I think he's fishing and it's like, uh, it's going to be a union Jack flag in an
American flag that's bigger.
And then it's going to be like fish and chips.
I'll take with extra malt vinegar or something like that.
Do you like malt vinegar on your fish and chips?
Um, I added a little.
I'm a tartar sauce.
I'm a cocktail and tartar sauce.
I like cocktail, but I'm a big malt vinegar head when I, when I do all that stuff.
I do love it.
There's no big Johnson shirt, but somebody has started their own shirt line called fish
and chicks.
Oh, free plug for them.
Wow.
Hopefully they don't have a weird Trump assassination.
My mom, my mom is a great fisherman.
She's a fantastic angler.
Yeah, she, she caught a lot of King salmon.
Uh, her and her friend used to like literally before work, they'd have, they'd have work
at like eight in the morning and they'd be at the river at five in the morning, catching
salmon downtown.
And then they would like pack them up and then go to work.
It was crazy.
She got really obsessed with it for a while, probably at my age and I'm not as cool as
my mom at my age.
So, um,
Well, talking about different types of the internet, a thing that I had been thinking
about, um, lately, Matt, have you encountered the phrase, the rot economy, exit trans rot
economy?
No, I have not about basically just everything is getting shittier and shittier and doesn't
work and more expensive.
And sometimes I feel that way about theme park, uh, uh, theme park rides or theme park
stuff, especially domestic Disney parks.
I'm like, this just keeps getting more and more expensive and everyone keeps posting
photos of like themed lights that are broken or the giant half a billion dollar ride is
down for half the day.
Yeah.
And I was thinking about that for 20,000 leaks because I'm like, this is such a cool ride
and I bet it runs like clockwork.
Yeah.
Everything seems so simple.
I mean, I mean that you even compared to like Disneyland and I've only been to animal kingdom
and Disney world, but like Disney, see when you walk in, even like Disney, Disney, Tokyo,
Disneyland, you just know they're in another league in terms of the care they put in that
park.
It's, it's not.
And I say about Disney, see, it's like, oh, it's like Disneyland.
If they had more money, like you could just feel it in every way, shape, and form.
But I do, I mean, I do have this thing where my brother was like, he goes, I think I come
out to LA, we should go to Disneyland.
I'm kind of like, I don't know, man.
I don't know if like that would be worth your while at this point.
Cause it's a $500 fast pass.
Is that true?
That exists.
Yeah.
That's like a full.
You don't have to do it.
Like you don't have to.
It's like a full day, like.
Front of the line.
Front of the line for everything.
But from the line in quotes, like how many people have bought individual lightning blades
or how many people bought the day pass?
Yeah.
And it becomes like a money proposition.
I think when I did my first time ever in my life was like 2019, I bought a Disney pass
and I think it was $900.
And I was like, this makes sense.
I'm going to go.
And I think I went maybe, maybe 10, 12 times.
Like I had a great year.
It was fun.
And I was like, great.
It was worth it to me.
Free parking.
At that level.
Yep.
Exactly.
And, and, and I had a great time with it.
And I've been kept on wanting to get, oh, I need to get another fast.
But what's the, what if I want to get a pass right now, what does it cost?
Not the same level of pass.
Yeah.
What's the pass that I, that we have that we just went up or I have,
it was like 400 bucks, 450.
I have the worst pass.
Okay.
Now the second, second to worst pass.
And then just went up a hundred bucks.
So I think you can get it for like 500 or 550.
And those are with like blackout dates and not a lot of them.
Yeah.
And not big, but you can have that $18 parking if you text that strange number
and I'll give you the number.
I'll tech, I'll share a contact with you.
Oh man.
Strange city walk garden.
Excuse me.
Garden walk number.
You're going to wake up with your bit of bathtub full of ice with that number, dude.
Yeah.
But with the, I have saved $12 from parking.
That's a good point.
I get the $12 on the counter there.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, if, if, if those deals are so important to you and you're willing to go
through them, even if you're, even if you're a little bit afraid of a giant horned gentleman
who's trying to get you to really connect and not be so connected to deals like that.
A giant horned gentleman, like a big Jason.
That's right.
No, no, not a, not a horny gentleman.
Oh, okay.
Not a big horny gentleman.
Okay.
That actually there, we're, we're trying to, they're not little, like not pervert.
It was like a big horny gentleman.
I like that.
Like that feels like, that feels like, that feels like stately.
Yeah.
Like a Bustopher Jones and cats.
I always have fancied myself more as a skimbles shanks, the railway cat, but I'll take it.
Skimbles shanksy.
I'm so, I'm, I'm, I'm here to air my grievances and we're on, uh, uh, tangent
19,800, Scott free.
I'm so mad at the James Corden casting and cats.
I love cats.
And then his take on it was like crazy.
It's in the fucking text.
He goes in the song.
He goes, I'm Bustopher Jones.
I'm not skin and bones.
In fact, I'm incredibly fat.
And he's like very proud to be a fat cat.
And then like later, James Corden does this improv.
He's like, Oh, don't make fun of my weight.
I'm so sensitive about my weight.
It's like, no, you were literally singing about your
The whole song is about how Bustopher Jones gets to eat so much garbage that
he's a big cat, which is a point of virtue in the cat world.
And James Corden doesn't understand the character and the script that he read.
He is lousy in that movie.
Wow.
Uh, Jason, what do you feel?
I've never seen cats, the play.
I've heard the songs.
Well, uh, me and my lady friend saw it, um, like opening month on animals.
And, uh, uh, yeah, it was, uh, uh, certainly it's a trip.
Sounds like he's punting on answering this.
Oh, it's not.
I mean, it's not good.
I have the nipples and the hands and I, yeah, I don't.
Do you feel like you have a good, like, does everybody embody the action?
You knew the characters of the cast before seeing the movie.
There's a lot of great, like Jen Rodson is great.
She's great.
And, um, so my whole story, let's get into it guys.
Scott's not here.
I can get into this.
Right.
My whole story with cats is like, I was in, I was writing for the WWE is in
Connecticut.
I would go to New York all the time just for fun on the weekend.
Right.
And I would just do a lotteries for Broadway shows, try to go see a show.
And I would get, I got cats.
I'm like, oh, well, I'll go see cats.
I'll go see cats.
And I saw it and I went to work on Monday and I was like, oh, I saw cats this
weekend.
How was that?
I'm like, ah, man, it was stupid.
That's a dumb show.
It's just like a bunch of cats come out, they're singing their names and I'm
telling them about it.
I'm talking about it at the table and then one of my friends goes, Hey, you
know, you've been talking about cats for about 35 minutes.
Do you think maybe you like the show?
And I go, ah, maybe I do.
And then I listened to the, the soundtrack at home and then I would go
into New York and I would just do the lottery and I saw cats four more times
in New York.
Wow.
I loved it.
At that point, I love the show.
I'm into the show and I was so excited about the movie and I do think the
movie pulled almost everything off except for Bustopher Jones is a big miss.
Interesting.
And Skimbleshanks, I'll also say Skimbleshanks is better in the movie than
I think the stage performances.
That was quite a inspired look and feel and what was going on?
As we learned with Starlight Express, trains, not the easiest thing to do on
stage, but that's it.
Starlight Express is running somewhere in the world right now.
So what do I know?
I'd like to watch.
I'd like to see it.
I haven't seen Starlight Express.
Yeah.
But you should see the movie.
Okay.
I mean, you got a kid and at some point they need to watch love that will scare
her.
Oh, yeah.
It's a good scare because that's the other thing.
Talk about the good scares.
In the beginning of Cats, the music's very creepy.
It's like, it's like really spooky.
Yeah.
And as that music's playing, the lights are off and then the cats walk up the
aisles and like I said, I always try to sit on the aisle and like I was like
looking at a cat across the way.
Then I turn around, there was like a cat right in my face.
It goes, does that thing?
Oh, it's so good.
It just scares the shit out of you.
It's so fun.
I would like to be scared by a cat on Broadway.
Yeah, it's great.
Okay.
Then they're also like, you can look at them and they're a bunch of like
good looking folks in tight clothes, but they're cats.
Oh, there's a horny element to it.
There's a little horny element.
It's very understated.
Now I'm getting to it.
Now I'm getting to the heart of what's going on here.
Like, and it's not like the animals.
The cat ladies.
Oh, it's, I'm attracted to the ladies portraying the cat.
I don't know.
It's, it's, it's, it's very titillating.
It's very fun.
It's a very exciting show.
God, I didn't know that.
I mean, I guess it makes sense because like, I know there's like a whole
community of people that like are very attracted to the thundercats.
Yes.
And they've, the cats always felt very thundercats to me.
Very thundercats in the, especially the face design.
Facially.
Yes.
And I, I'm a big Zubili Zoo fan from our childhood.
I, do you know, are you familiar with Zubili Zoo?
I don't know if I know Zubili Zoo.
Ben Verene.
They were very much dressed like cats.
Well, you know, well, we'll do a little Zubili Zoo on the way out.
Let's, let's do a little bit more about the ride.
The gray ride that we all love.
The color palette.
We are doing a fair job of some hardcore ride theory talk mixed with some good tangents, guys.
The color palette on the ride, just like the bright greens and then all of a sudden
there'll be like a splash of like neon orange.
Like you get the, each room has its own like color profile.
Yeah.
And makes everything so memorable.
I don't really want this, but part of me is almost like, man,
I'd love to like look at this, not in this ride vehicle.
Yes.
And I think it would take away some of the illusion of how big it is, obviously.
But sometimes I'm just like, man, the colors in here are so cool.
Yeah.
I would just like to see it unobstructed.
I have a weird aversion slash desire to doing that in pirates specifically.
I would like love to see the ceiling of pirates because I never look up.
I never want to look up.
I never want to try to find it.
Yeah.
Because that room, the room with the ships at the beginning is so massive to me.
I just don't like, I truly feel outside, but I know I've gone underground and it's a great illusion.
But like if pirates ever stopped and the lights were on, I'd be kind of like.
Well, there's something creepy about it.
Yeah.
But it would like break my heart.
But also it's like, I can't explain it, but it's like I want to see it,
but I know it would ruin the ride for me.
Yeah.
I mean, I understand that.
I mean, I think a lot of it, even when you see like pictures of haunted mansion,
lights on, ride vehicle is stuck.
You look at some of the sets and you go, this looks like garbage.
This looks like everything looks cheap.
Everything looks small.
Like, is it, was it really worth it to get a peek behind the curtain in this aspect?
I think with the robots on pirates, even when the lights are on,
you'd still find a bunch of cool shit to see.
Yeah.
Then you'd see like some of the guys don't have bottom halves.
Some of them are just tops.
There would be weird stuff and it would be creepy, but interesting.
Yeah.
But yeah, I don't know.
Maybe I wouldn't want to be out of the ride vehicle to see some of the stuff,
but I don't know.
It's just the colors are so cool.
The other cool thing about it is when you walk in, that's very earth tone,
very, we forgot to mention this is a very steampunk thing.
Well, yeah, although Jules Verne aesthetic.
Yeah.
This is, I was looking, I don't know if you've found anything,
I can't find who was the project lead or something on this ride.
I didn't really come across that.
And we know Tony Baxter is Mr. Jules Verne and he tried to put a bunch of Jules-
I think there's a whole generation of Imagineers that Jules Verne just lodged
so much in their minds and I think clearly there's been so many adaptations of Jules Verne
and H.G. Wells, but Jules Verne especially works well for like police making.
Well, yeah, and it feels somewhat timeless, not somewhat, but I guess timeless at this point.
But there's, yeah, there were many different attempts to put a bunch of Jules Verne shit
in the back of Disneyland and it's in its own like port, I write port Disney,
like there have been so many Jules Verne concepts lying around Imagineering over the years.
So it wouldn't shock me if a lot of Tony or whoever was involved in this,
but I was wondering, yeah, who did anyone have like the real vision for this?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, Jules Verne, the Jules Verne look in this thing is very much like the Venn diagram of like
Adventureland and Frontierland. It's got like a little bit of like fantasy and a little bit of
like rustic exploration and stuff like that. So it makes sense that 20,000 Leagues is a Disney thing
and that's why I'm surprised there's nothing in the park that's, in the LA park that's like this.
Right. There's a, I forget which specific scene, but when they do electricity on the ride,
it looks so good. It's so fun. It's like just this like, it looks just like little ribbon
lighting or whatever you would call it. Like whatever I use to light my toy shelves.
I think it's projection lightning.
Do you think that's what it is?
I think so. Cause I, cause I don't see, cause I think when you do the ride through,
like it's on the tentacles, like it's, it's how you get away from the squid.
You know what? You're probably right. I'm looking at it right now.
Yeah.
Yeah. I think you're right.
I thought it was black light. I thought it was a physical safety.
Illusion if we're all arguing. I think you're on, I think you're closer to what it is.
The other cool thing about that is watching the movie, there's a scene. It's, it's,
it is the most regrettable scene in the movie is where there's a bunch of, they go to an island,
there's a bunch of cannibals that chase them. It's, it's sure it's not great in modern day,
but they get them up, they all hop on the ship and they get them off the ship by doing electric
shock on the ship. And that effect is like, I think on purpose, the ride effect of the
lightning is the same effect they use. And it's like the same color. It's the same shape.
It's the same squiggle of the lightning. I think it's like an intentional homage to like
how the novelist protects itself by like overcharging itself, but it's cool.
It looks, I think you're right. It almost looks like laser lights that aren't in a straight line.
Yeah. There's something.
Yeah.
I don't know. Maybe there's some very simple explanation for what that is.
I wonder if that was the timing on the novel, 20,000 Leagues, was electricity still very new
and modern? Oh, I don't know.
Like, cause I w we watched around Halloween. We watched Halloween three season, The Witch,
which is not a good movie on a lot of levels, but there is some interesting stuff in it. And it,
there are some obsessions of America at the time, the advent of closed circuit TV,
divorce, the rise of divorce, like commercials, like television commercials and stuff.
So every now and then popular obsessions, I feel like make their way into media.
Yeah.
And I feel like the rise of electricity around the turn of the century kind of like
really affected a lot of people's brains. Well, I think there is also something with the,
I think there's something very like nuclear bomb about Nemo, because the whole thing is
the ship engine is like this magical power source that nobody knows. And you can't even look at it
without like a huge blast shield in front of your face. And then the spoiler, Volcania Island or
Volcania Lagoon blows up at the end. And it's a very like, it's a practical effect, but they
really have rigged the explosive to look like a mushroom cloud. I think they are playing like this
is like, Captain Nemo has harnessed this power that is like a nuclear bomb. In fact, to the point
of, I'm kind of surprised slash maybe we should save this, Godzilla versus Captain Nemo would be
like a great thing, like set it in the fifties and like do something like that. But like maybe
Nemo's power is the guy that unearthed Godzilla. Godzilla is 70 years old as of yesterday.
Yes. Happy birthday to Godzilla.
Happy birthday, Godzilla.
30 years until the public domain for Godzilla.
Holy shit. That's going to be great.
We're all going to make a Godzilla movie at that point.
All these gods, all these monsters and Dick Tracy,
they're eventually going to clash in the blood and honey universe.
I mean, you're actually, you're probably right that Dick Tracy won't get brought into blood and
honey. So we got to beat that Dick Tracy out. Yeah.
Yeah. What year did this ride get made actually?
This was an opening day.
2001.
Attraction. 2001.
Yeah. And the projection, the lighting projection on stuff where you project onto things, is that-
Projection mapping, they call it?
The projection mapping, yeah. When was that effect like kind of popularized? Like what was the-
Well, they've been doing a version of it for decades, but there's like a more, I'm assuming
there's like a more modern version of it that they've been doing for the last decade or couple
decades at this point. Cause like they do so many projection mapping shows on the castle.
Yeah.
And I feel like, I feel like it was all of a sudden, like everything was projection mapping
and it was like, oh, wow, cool. They can do a lot of cool stuff. And then it kind of got boring to
me. I'm like, oh, everything's projection mapping. And now I'm seeing more projection mapping and
there's stuff like in, I think Paris, maybe that they do on the tower of terror there.
And then they have like a Marvel drone show in addition to the mapping they do.
Oh, that's cool.
And now I'm like, okay, maybe I'm back into the projection mapping.
Cause like that's like half box ghost is like a projection map face.
No, I think, uh, yeah, that's complicated. It's like a real head that they,
I think there's a projection in his, we are still not sure exactly, but it's not like pretty
projected. I don't think from far away or anything. Like, like, I mean, an old school version of
projection mapping are the singing busts. Right, right. It was just a film, but that's just,
that's from decades ago. Um, but I'm not sure. I feel like we tried to figure out what the illusion
was on the cat box goes up. So I forgot any of the speculation. Cause I think we read different
like ideas of what it could be. I think there is like an official Disney video of them setting it
up. And I think one thing they alluded to was a tiny projector inside the hat box.
Huh? Like projecting, but small. Yeah, kind of.
Yeah, I forget. It was in whatever we talked about was interesting
man years ago, but they, especially with the one at mansion, they do try to keep, so there is a
certain cave fade to some of the stuff. Right. They want to, they want to, they don't want to
show all their behind the scenes. It's all a pepper's ghost. If you have a question,
you go a pepper's ghost. Oh, is the, is the last Atlantean a pepper's ghost? I, I, I couldn't
remember the ride. And I also couldn't tell from the ride vehicle. Cause there's a little more
complicated. Um, and it wasn't quite, it was 2001. I wouldn't be surprised with peppers because it
couldn't do the, uh, the, who's the, the, the, the shaman priestess from, uh, avatar, the shaman
of song. That's the, you know, that's, they're showing their, their brushstrokes there.
That you're talking about this guy. Yeah. This one is like waving goodbye. Yeah. Uh, but no,
you just get, it just kind of goes, the lights turn off, I think. Okay. So he's just, he's just
in a little box waving at us. But these are like, we really probably didn't even do a good job
describing. They're almost like, like seahorse people. Yeah. And they look like they're about
what? Three, four feet tall. Maybe this one's actually bigger. Maybe it's like four foot tall.
Yeah. They're, they're a little, they're little people. They got fit and they got kind of
thin hands. I'm trying to think what the, who's the, they look like Navi adjacent, but they're
not fully Navi. Well, that's the ride vehicle to use their way of water ride. Well, that's good.
But the rumor is, is they're using the pirate Shanghai boat technology to do this new water ride.
Right. Okay. Because then you can do like these big screen, like theater rooms with,
with stuff where you go underwater. And then a Tolkien can swim by and be like, yeah, yeah.
But like, yeah, a little, like more of like even like a small, I don't know, d ticket,
avatar, a little sub here. That's funny. Cause, but I think the, the Navi adventure is already
filling that hole. Like if they didn't. Well, they're there, but I'm going to California
adventure. Yeah. Like a way of water dark ride. Yeah. It's water. Cause like the main e-ticket
is going to be way of water dark, not dark ride, but like, well, I guess kind of, but like an
e-ticket dark ride. Yeah. With like a dynamic ride system. Cause if you do the Nemo ride
now, you just add it. Cause one thing about the Nemo ride right now, the 20,000 leagues under
the sea is that you don't have a ton of animatronics. There's some. Yeah. There's the,
there's the squid. And then there's a few of those guys are kind of like really simple ones.
But if you started having those like shaman of song level animatronics, like you could make
an incredible squid on this new one, you know? Yes. So I think that, I don't know. I think there's,
I wouldn't be against in the middle of the ride, the squid fucking you up. Yes. Like I wouldn't
mind getting jostled. I don't know if the ride system could handle it. Maybe you'd have to alter
it. I mean, it feels easy. Like there's going to be a hanging ride. Isn't that the Donkey Kong
ride is going to hang and then. No, it's a mine cart. So you're on the ground. You're thinking,
I think of the element of the ride that there's an extra little bar that's going to make it like
that's going to be hidden. So when you jump track, it's going to look like you're flying.
You're on a fake track, right? You're elevated. It's not hanging. You're elevated. The car is
right. Right. Right. And they can't seem to get it to work in Japan. It has, it's behind. See,
that's, that's just been the running thing. I feel like last few years of like, it's a technological
Marvel. It works every other day, but it's like, we need to run this thing every day. Harry Potter
won't open with Epic Universe. Oh God. And look, we got to book, we got to book our live shows that
weekend. Now we got to get it up. We got to get in gear and we got to get down there to celebrate.
But as I'm like, Oh, if everything's not going to be open, I don't know. Man. I was at, I was
talking to a person who works in the theme parks and actually was like designing rides on the more
creative level, but also works with the engineers and stuff. And I was very curious about like,
like I've been talking about, like I'm a big guy and I, there's some rides I cannot get on
universal. Yeah. Yeah. Especially universal. And I'm like, why is universal? Why would life of pets,
which is a dark ride, why would they not accommodate somebody like, if you tell me
like the Harry Potter arm thing, okay, there's probably an engineering issue, something. Okay.
I like, I'll buy that safety issue. Fine. I'll buy flips people up and, okay, let's go with your pets
goes three and a half miles an hour. And also it's literally like, you could just do one bench seat
out of anything. Like why not? And I was like, why would they not have them? Like, Oh, it's they,
we definitely could. I think it would save like four days of prep. And so that saves them like
$200,000. So they think that's not worth it. It's just like, it's purely in a money issue.
Cause I was like, is there an engineering thing I don't know about? And they're like, no, no,
it's just like, if you have to make a design a new seat, that's just going to cost another
two weeks of work or something like that. And it's just like, it's, it's crazy. Like,
how it feels like it should be so easy to accommodate that.
Especially because theme parks as tourism destinations go out of their way to advertise
accessibility. Right, right, right. Now Disney would like, you know, sick people or non-mobile
people or people with issues to jump through a lot of hoops to get that access ability. But that's
another thing entirely, but it's like, yeah, why wouldn't they, if they're so high on, on doing
this on it's for everyone ages eight to 80, blah, blah, blah. Why would they not?
Yeah. Disney's better. Disney's better. Universal's awful. Like they're bad for at least,
at least side stuff. I mean, like, I'm not sure about everything else, but I could get on most
rides at Disney. The, the, the avatar ride, the, the writing, the guys, uh, the guys,
if you want to ride some guys, um, the mighty guys, the mighty guys, the mighty guys. Yeah. Uh,
that, that one is like literally the, just like my, my calves were just a little too big to like
strap me in so close. And I told that guy's like, motherfucker kicked that thing into my leg. I
don't care. I want to, I want to ride these guys. Uh, yeah. But, uh, but Universal's just like,
so insanely weird on like, that's like, it said life of pets. There's zero reason I
shouldn't get on life. I don't even want to go on like a little box that's going on a track.
Yeah. Well, and even, uh, even Mario Kart, which is one, uh, I would say this, thank goodness.
Universal, they, they, they, with Mario Kart, they decided to hit, they hid the test one.
Oh, right. Right. Oh, I know. But then now you can like go into like a little,
you run a little thing, you test out, but the Mario Kart is like, I heard that it's not size
accessible. Okay, cool. I bet I'm going to try anyways. I get on it and I bring the lap bar down
and like, it's down. It's around my legs and it just doesn't click. And I'm like, why does it,
they just, there's like a gear with like clicks and just make two more clicks and I'd 100% fit
on this motherfucker. You almost feel like adding insults, injury or something. Like,
yeah, just like to cut, like, I don't know. It felt like there was a guy laughing somewhere.
Ha ha ha. Yeah. Like I could have done it, but we didn't. It's like, I couldn't, these two widgets
cost us $350,000. So now you and everybody else like you doesn't get to ride this ride.
It is insult injury. We already live in America and have to eat poison every day.
Come on. I know. I feel like, yeah, I've also just feel like Universal's ride vehicles are
uncomfortable in general. Right. It also just feels like there's like some like sick pervert
designing the like seats, not a pervert in a sexual way. Mr. Comcast is like torture device
seats. Yeah. Cause like, look, I've talked about it at length on this show, the mummy ride,
which like makes my genitals fly into my body somewhat, like the way the, which the seat is
angled up and you're just like sitting on it. I don't know why my genitals retreat on that.
It sucks. I don't know. Like I know I'm a tall guy and maybe that's part of it, but yeah, but,
but they're, they're, they're riding vehicles, presumably for human beings. And we are all human
beings with different shapes and sizes and ways to get around. And it's like, uh, we, and we're,
we're literally talking about parts. I don't mean to get into this, uh, this accessibility thing on
this 20,000 leagues. This is a tangent that feels a little heavy, but, uh, this is what drove Captain
Nemo to go under the sea and attack ships. I'm going to go, I'm going to get in my own little
Nautilus and start just bombing universal. So I can get on secret life of pets,
audio bombs on this podcast. That's right. Like, like old, old Captain Nemo, my pal.
Then they say Nemo, cause you keep calling him Nemo, which is what they say.
No, I, this is why I imagine James Mason says it because Captain Nemo, I just, he's,
he's not Indian, which is bad, but he has a very pleasant voice, which is good.
So I don't know how to deal with that. Yeah, I understand that. Um, I dunno,
is there anything else we want to shout out about the ride before we go? I don't know. It's,
it's hard sometimes cause you're like, ah, the ride is great. You should go on the ride
and that's podcast ride sometimes.
Check it out.
Let me ask you this. So, so you haven't gone to Disney Sea yet, Jason. Let me just start throwing
these out to you. So let's say it's end of the day and whatever imaginary trip has happened,
you could go on one more ride and it's, uh, it's either 20,000 leagues under the sea or,
and I'm going to give you a few ors and you tell me whether you're going to go on
20,000 leagues or this ride. Okay. Does that make sense? Like you have to make it
Just from like afar, my assessment from afar. Just from, just from your assessment from afar
or reputation or just what you heard on this podcast? Re-rides or first time riding?
Uh, uh, first time riding. Oh, okay. Yeah. Like so, so you basically have to make a hard choice.
Got it. So it's like between this, between 20,000 leagues and tower of terror.
Oh, tower of terror. Uh, this and Soren. Uh, this.
Okay. 20,000 leagues or the Indiana Jones roller coaster. Oh, this is okay. I've, I've,
I don't know, but they're easy. These can be easy questions. What, what, what, what,
what do you think would be a harder choice? Oh, 20,000 leagues or water topia.
Oh, I only know a little about water topia. Oh man. So I'm probably have to do this. I want to
see this or eating a steak at Magellan's, the restaurant, the sea headquarters society
of explorers and adventures. That's tough, but I feel like there's better steak likely to be at.
There's better steak, uh, in the rest of Tokyo. That's right. It's a great steak. I, yeah,
I'm curious. I do think the hardest coin toss for me having done both is this versus water topia.
Yeah. Water topia. I like a lot. It looks pretty cool. Oh, it's cool. Yeah. It's also like a unique
ride to me. It's just like, I've never seen anything quite like it. I guess like the dancing
cars in, um, in cars land, Luigi's little dance or whatever. Uh, God, I, I, I'm going to get
raked over the coast. I don't know a single ride name. Uh, I called it Luigi's little dance.
You kept calling secret life of pets, life of pets. Well, it's not very secret.
He's watched all the films. He's watched all the Louis CK. That's true. Yeah. Just the first one.
Just the funniest dog. Just, he just, yeah, he just licks himself in front of other dogs and people
don't like that. Yeah. Uh, but, uh, but water topia is so cool. And I actually, I actually water,
cause the thing about water topia is he said, Hey, let's shout out the last thing about 20,000 leagues.
I'm going to go on a water topia tangent is like, it's right on the Bay and it's almost like an
infinity pool type thing. And you could kind of like see out into the Bay. And I was doing
water topia during sunset, like in Tokyo Bay. It was amazing. That was like one of my highlights
of the trip besides sin bad. Uh, but, but 20,000 leagues, I think it's kind of technically a better
ride, but, but water topia is just kind of a neat little sum bitch. You know, I think that's a thing
that always appealed to me about theme parks in general. It's like, it's just kind of like a thing
that evokes a lot of feelings and thoughts and you can't do it anywhere else. So sometimes when
they just make, as it's called, sometimes the book report version of the movie, it's like, well,
this feels a little less special. You know, if it's not a transformative ride, it feels less special.
You know what? I will also, what's unique about this is that it's a little box, like very rarely
are you going to go on a ride vehicle that's an actual box that they put you in. Generally it's
open air on some level. I can't, I mean, can you think of anything other than the other subs
where you're in a box or in a actual first thing I think of is, is a state fair ride called the
Gravitron. Oh sure. The Gravitron. Yeah. But I love the Gravitron for being that because it's the,
it's like you're in the park, you're outside all day and you're in the, the one time you go inside
and there's like disco lights and. Yeah, no, it's great. But like there's no dark ride where
it's a box, even with a window. Just secret life bets. It's a literal box. Well, but it's open.
I mean, you're right. It is a literal box. Well, this is, it is funny. This is a unique ride system
compared to the other subs where it, you do walk into it and it's not as claustrophobic,
but like submarines in general, it's a little claustrophobic. Sure. A little bit. You're right
up on that glass. But yeah, if you got, I mean, this is like, this is like the most potentially
depending, cause they'll put a couple other couples with you, but this is the most intimate
ride vehicle. This is very like. If you were to go in alone or in Jason's case,
go in with a couple other swinging couples. Sure. This is the most intimate. What is this,
Lord? This is not something to even say. The Jason's a swinger? Yeah. No, no, no, no.
Yeah. You're like, we're going to wait for the car with the upside down pineapple. With the
upside down. We've talked about that. That's a joke on the show. But no, it's, it is interesting
being in there. Cause like, you do feel like we're like in our own little little pod. This is a,
this is a ride for smooching. If you're going to sneak a ride for smooching. Can you flick
these spotlights off? Yeah, you could just turn them off. Right, right. No, cause like each bench
is like a pair. So if you, if even if you don't have to look at them, even with the other two,
even if it was like strangers in the car with you, you could, you could be like, give your back to
them. It's like, yep. You don't need to see what they're doing. Yeah. Cause they're not pointing.
You're not looking at them and it's dark in there. Probably the sexiest Disney ride. Probably. And
we talked about this. So the second sexiest is when you're in the Haunted Mansion and you're
leaning back to go into the graveyard and the thing tilts you down. Dude, I do kind of think
Haunted Mansion is the same thing. I'd like anything. It's like, I didn't get to go there
as like a teen, but I do think of like, when I was a teenager, theme parks were always like sexy
to me because you can go there and meet girls and you could like take a date there and you could
always like sneak off and then smooch. Yeah. And then I think that a Disney does a great job
and it's good that they do of keeping that out of the parks. But then once in a while, Haunted
Mansion, 20, those things are the same. You go to Tokyo Disney, you get a little bowl. Everybody
puts their room keys in a bowl before you get on the ride. Well, you better make sure you get
one out because I think some of those hotels are the style where you put your room key on to turn
the light on. That's right. And then you swap couples on the benches. That's right. If you
really like whine a swing, if you really want to play. And you're literally swinging from the top.
This is the swingiest ride in Disney for sure. That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying.
So there's another feather in its cap. That's another good thing about this ride. Another nice
thing, cool cast member uniforms, which are based on the movie. They're the little blue sailor
uniforms with some purples and teals in there. It's a cool get up. Yes. That's the ultimate
thing about it is I think everything that you do here brings you into that world. And even before
the ride happens, I do think it's transformative. Next level immersive. Yeah. And that's the epic
universe. They're promising it and that's what we want. That's what we keep saying over and over
again. You can find it 20,000 leagues under the dang sea. Yep. Well, there it is. Matt Mazani,
you've survived podcast the ride. Wow. The second gate, I guess. Do we say that? Does Scott say the
second gate when he says it? No, he doesn't say that. I can't remember. I've only heard him say it
hundreds of times. I honestly didn't remember which stream this was going on. Well, that's
the whole thing. We need to have a big meeting, Jason and I. We have big plans going on. Not
just Marmaduke May and big Jason tees, but we have big plans this month. We have to do a big
credit card episode. There's going to be a whole bunch of elements that he isn't even aware of
that are going to be happening during this credit card episode. Oh, wow. You don't have to be
involved in anything. I'm bringing extra things in. Oh, okay. Because we're going to do it up.
We're going to do credit card episode points. I'm very curious to hear an update because you
had not talked about credit card points in quite a while. So I'm curious to see where you're at.
Well, that's going to be part of my credit card point journey because the listeners voted for
this. It's not like I suggested doing this recently. Have you guys gotten more server space for the
extra traffic for this episode, the credit card episode? Well, we should. What you're saying is
a good piece of advice. You don't want people to go to download it and they can't get it because
the servers are overloaded. The servers have been crashed. Yeah. From, yeah. So like that DJ
Khaled album. What's going to be interesting too is I have to make sure my bank account
can hold all the money. That's right. From what we're going to get when everyone signs
up for this credit card point episode. Because we've never checked the capacity of that bank
account. Right. We don't know. Yeah. We don't know. This money's just shooting in when they
hear this riveting episode. But no, there's a lot of, we have a lot of fun plans and we're
going to talk about it soon off mic. Oh boy. Yeah. It's not about, it's about church. It's
about big dogs. Beautiful. Many versions of big dogs. And yeah, anyway, Mavisani exit through
the gift shop. Yeah. Plug away. You've got a cool short that you've recently made. Yeah. I
shot a short film last year. We've been running it through the festival circuit and now it is out
online. It's called Big Brothers. Starring Mike Mitchell, a friend of the pod, I believe. Very,
yes. Very good friend. Yes. Then Eddie Pepitone and Jesse Klein and Winston Carter and Leroy
Patterson. It's a great cast and it's on Omeleto, which is a YouTube channel that does a bunch of
short films. So O-M-E-L-E-T-O. Check that out. I wrote and directed it. It's a blast. It's a,
it's a, I don't know, we've got some pro wrestling fans. It's got some pro wrestling stuff. It's a
comedy. It's fun. It's a five brothers go to fix their mother's house. And after she dies
and the dad shows up and it's a big brouhaha, but. And you take a bump in the movie. I take a big
bump in the movie. Yeah. Oh yeah. You gotta, you gotta see me. You take a stunt. Do you think it's
a more severe stunt than those kids took? No. Okay. Those kids. I'm telling you, when you watch
Kung Fu Kids 2, you're going to be like, well, that's like, that's the inspiration. You watch
Kung Fu Kids 2 and say, I want to be a Kung Fu kid. I want to fall off a ladder through a table
for fun. And it was fun. But the moment before was extremely scary. I bet. I was like, it's all
really good. But then you're up there and you're like, well, this is fucking high. Yeah. Wow.
Yeah. So yeah, I was actually afraid of breaking the location too. Cause it was like an old house
built in the 1800s. And I was like, well, I just go through the floors into the basement. We'll see.
Sure. Hey, director taking the bump himself, not making other actors do it. You got it. You can't.
Hey, that's what the great Vince McMahon would do. Okay. What? What do you mean?
What do you mean? I was trying to pay a compliment. We should time since we're recording this in
November, uh, 2022, before anything bad happened with Vince McMahon. In 22, I knew Vince was a good
guy. That's for sure. A good man. A good man with good beliefs and good practices. Uh, so yes,
anyway, check that out. We'll probably, yeah, we'll post the link. Um, and then yeah, hopefully,
uh, we'll have you back on to, uh, unveil the line of shirts.
Hell yeah. Um, and we'll maybe, I, I don't want to say a Minotaur should be a spokesman for it or
being featured, but we'll see. Maybe it, maybe it'll happen. Yeah. Well, I, for your sake, I hope the
Minotaur doesn't show up, especially during that credit card episode. That's not, but that would
be very scary. We can't tell the Minotaur when we're doing it. Oh yeah. One of the things I'm going
to bring is an ax. That's smart. Kill a Minotaur if he comes during the credit card episode. Yeah,
you can try. That'll be fun. All right. Well, I'll try.