Forever!
Dog!
Warning, the following podcast may contain a clumsy ballerina,
big beers,
a horse with a bright smile,
and an elderly clown's wedding ring.
All this plus Bethapel joins us to talk Tivoli Gardens on today's podcast,
The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, or as it's called today, Podcast Turin.
I'm Jason Chardon, joined as always by Carlson.
I'm here, and I'm not Danish at all, but I will try to pronounce some of the words and embarrass myself, I'm afraid.
Oh, I'm going to 100% guarantee I'm going to be mispronouncing stuff left and right.
On a recent episode, I called the actor Barry Keoghan, Barry Keegan.
I thought it was Barry Keo.
So I'm just saying, recently I felt like I've been doing a bad job pronouncing a lot of things,
including this poor actor's name who I'm mistreating with my knowledge, my lack of knowledge.
So prepare for it is what I'm selling the audience today, to get mad at me and to be upset with me.
Especially our Danish listeners.
Yeah. Well, welcome to our Danish listeners.
We're talking about the historic Tivoli Gardens today, among other attractions in Denmark and around the world.
I guess today, I didn't even ask what credit she'd like.
She's a writer on the sexualized college girls, the former artist director of the UCB theater.
It's Bethapel. Hi, Beth.
Hello.
Are those credits right? Were those good?
Those were both accurate.
OK, cool.
Yeah. OK.
And I like that you've had so many sex lives of college girls writers on this podcast.
We have, yes. Well, you and Matt Orberton.
That's right. This is a test.
I've been going back and forth. Justin Noble, we've been emailing.
Oh, he still has not gone on.
He has not, because I think I initially emailed him a year went by and he emailed me back saying, I'm so sorry.
He's a very busy man.
I'm sure he is. And then we were just trying to pinpoint and then we just got.
So, Justin, we'll have you on soon.
Eventually.
So Scott Garner, not here today. He's out on assignment.
But we're so happy to have you here.
Yes, I'm thrilled to be here.
You pitched these topics to me, the Denmark topics.
But before we get to that, we have covered Las Vegas attractions in the past.
Themed casinos, former theme parks in Vegas.
Yeah.
But one of the blank spots is that we haven't covered is the Excalibur Hotel, the very themed Excalibur Hotel.
And I wanted you to ask you if you would tell the story.
You have a very specific Excalibur experience.
I do, but it might not be as much Excalibur related as you think it is.
Really?
Possibly.
Oh, OK.
Because you mean about getting married?
Yes.
I didn't get married there.
You didn't get married there?
No.
But I did stay there for two nights.
Oh, OK.
So can you tell us about the pillows?
Can you tell us about the blankets?
Because that could be interesting.
No, I don't remember those.
But I eloped to Vegas to do an Elvis wedding because it was not possible to get a marriage license in the correct amount of time to then do a city hall marriage during COVID.
And it was just easier to drive to Vegas and quickly get married there.
And I was in a hurry to get married.
I was like, I got to do this now.
So we stayed at the Excalibur in deep, deep, deep COVID because that was one of the hotels you could stay at where you could get the limo package to take you to the chapel where we got married.
OK, that's good.
That's a connection to the Excalibur.
That is the connection.
Yeah, which we chose this chapel because we had randomly seen on Instagram that David Harbour and Lily Allen got married there.
And we were like, that looks fun.
Not really a fan per se of either of them, but they did get married at the same place.
And then so we did that.
We stayed at the Excalibur.
It was like the we thought it would be a cheap, cheesy place to stay.
And it was.
It was.
And it really was.
And we had to we had brought like champagne with us.
We had to request a refrigerator and they brought it on like an AV cart that like a TV would have been brought in on and like, you know, a middle school class.
And it just was so loud.
We eventually had to unplug it.
The fridge.
Yeah.
It was like a mini fridge on an AV cart that made so much noise.
So I would say the Excalibur has maybe seen better days.
Yeah.
My experience there has always been losing at the penny slots and very bad vibes.
Well, the vibes during Covid were especially bad.
I would say maybe worse than ever.
Yeah.
Did you have your wedding meal at the Dix last resort in Excalibur?
Most of the restaurants were closed when we were there.
So we went to a restaurant called Tommy Bahamas.
Whoa.
Yeah.
And then we went to the yard house.
There was like not a lot of places that we could eat.
Tommy Bahamas.
We've talked about this on the show as a clothing brand.
I didn't know it was you could.
Yes.
You can also eat a place where they'll serve you a hamburger as well.
I couldn't believe it.
I was like, why is there dinner at Tommy Bahamas?
But it was just a restaurant.
And we wore bride and groom masks.
And the purpose was give us free things.
And it totally worked.
Smart.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I wish masks were still a little more normalized so that we could lie.
Oh, yeah.
Like any sort of occasion you could put on a mask and sort of get birthdays.
Birthdays.
Right.
Anniversary.
Morning.
In morning.
Yeah.
R.I.P.
Grandma.
Yes.
Give me a free Mai Tai at Tommy Bahamas.
My grandma died.
Free Tropical Monterellas sticks.
What do they do at Dick's Last Resort when they're like trying to mourn, like help you mourn?
Do they still call you gay but then also say, I'm so sorry for your loss?
Like they have to keep in character and what the tradition of Dick's is, which is just to call you gay.
Yeah.
But then, yeah, they have to show some sort of respect for whoever you lost.
Absolutely.
This is really a side note, but I worked at Ed DeBevix in high school.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so I'm no stranger to a place where you're supposed to kind of razz the customers.
Are you from Chicago?
No, they open in Ed DeBevix in Denver.
Really?
Yeah.
And I worked there for like a couple months, weeks maybe.
And they brought in a specialist from the Beverly Hills Ed DeBevix to try to rehabilitate the restaurant and like teach the waiters like how to perform and stuff.
And then I showed up to work one day and it was closed forever.
And they didn't tell you ahead of time.
They did not tell me.
I just showed up for my shift and there was like a sign on the door that was like closed forever.
That is like apropos with the vibe of Ed DeBevix.
It's like, fuck you, we're closed.
It was on theme for sure.
Did the sign say, fuck you, we're closed or something or no?
No.
I didn't say fuck you.
It would say like screw you probably.
Screw you.
Yeah.
Yeah, it did.
It said screw you, we're closed.
Wow.
Okay.
Were you expecting like she was going to say we got married on the top of the Excalibur?
Yeah.
I don't know why I could tell that you thought something different happened at the Excalibur, but I knew it was not right.
Dressed as a king and queen on the top with like an inflatable dragon or something.
We took pictures.
Yeah.
Well, you had posted on Instagram ages ago.
And I'm like, I guess they have a wedding chapel with an Elvis inside the Excalibur.
No.
I think I just saw the details and mushed it together.
Now, this is one of it does cover one of our favorite like vacation topics, which is a bunch of crazy pain in the ass shit like a giant loud refrigerator on a high school AV cart.
Yeah.
And a limo from Excalibur to the Elvis wedding chapel.
And the limo was disgusting.
And there were open beers in it when we got in it from the previous people.
And the limo driver was very mean to us.
Like very similar to Ed DeBevix.
Yeah, it was an Ed DeBevix style limo ride.
Wow. Yeah.
Are you sure they were just not opening the beers like to be polite so you didn't you could just get in and have a sip of cold one?
I didn't test it because again, it was October of 2020.
So whether or not it was just a polite beer too risky.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, yes.
So we do recommend the limo service from the Excalibur in general or perhaps not.
I think if you are getting married at a chapel in Vegas, your standards are such and I include myself in this.
I'm allowed to say this that it does that you don't you're not you don't care that much about the classiness of your fair enough.
Fair enough. Okay.
Well, let's look into if there is any sort.
I don't even know if there's a wedding chapels in the main strip hotels.
I feel like there's not.
I've never seen one.
No big own stuff on buying like MGM Grant and stuff.
I don't think so.
I think you would that would be a different wedding experience than that.
Yes.
That would be like shut like it down.
Like that would be very expensive.
I feel like you get the full king and queen ceremony at the Excalibur.
Even David Harbour and Lily Allen couldn't afford that.
Right.
And they're rich and they're rich.
Yeah.
Rich with friends and money.
Well, great.
Well, I'm glad we cleared that up.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you sooner.
You actively, I feel like, did not tell me.
I forgot you even mentioned it.
And then as soon as you brought it up just now, I was like, oh, there's been a misunderstanding.
Look, it's all gravy.
I mean, the story was worth it.
I can tell you're mad at me, but we'll work it out later.
He's furious.
I can tell.
I'm like the Hulk.
I'm always angry.
To be fair, Jason will say, well, I have a big story about a hotel.
And then it'll be like, the story is that the sheets weren't on the bed or something.
And that'll be it.
So like, this is actually, this is right in the zone of what he is interested in.
Oh, great.
Okay.
Yeah.
But now hold on a minute.
If the sheets were not on the bed and I checked into a hotel room, that would be very unusual.
It would be unusual, but it's not like, oh my God, an amazing story.
Well, it depends on, you know, you've only said the beginning of it.
I'd like to hear the middle and the end.
I just told the story though that Jason's like, that is exciting.
What you're talking about is exciting.
So I should have stepped it down.
There was a time when you went to an Airbnb in San Diego and the sheets were wet.
Oh, yes.
The sheets were wet and there were dabs of hand lotion.
And I was like, I don't think I want to stay here.
How did you know it was hand lotion?
He tasted it.
I think I saw the bottle sitting out.
Okay.
And the guy had also said like, oh, you're my second Airbnb guest.
The first was last night.
And he's like, yeah, sorry, man.
I just threw the comforter in the wash and I put it on the bed and I'm like, I feel like you buy a second set.
Yeah.
My first guest was last night.
It was Buffalo Bill.
He greased himself up.
He got in the bed.
He put the lotion in the bed.
I mean, he also was very late giving me the keys.
And instead of meeting in the lobby, he pulled up a giant SUV on a street corner and kind of toss them to me.
And I was like, this is not this is not a great experience already.
One star.
All right.
Well, we'll we'll we'll think about this and we'll remember Jason.
You know what?
We should do an episode on your top five hotel stories.
Here's my Excalibur story.
Oh, wait.
We're doing more Excalibur content?
Now I know why this came up.
Well, no, because the one time I went there was when I kept doing the My Vegas.
There's these games you can play on your phone and earn like rewards like free nights or free play.
And I had racked up a lot and I just kept cashing in free play.
And I got to the Excalibur and there was a long line for the players club.
And we were in line.
There was a much older woman with long braided purple and blonde hair making out with a much younger man in line.
Like full on teenagers in line at a theme park making out.
And so we're in this long line and we get up to the window and they're like, you have cashed in too much free play.
You cannot claim this.
I don't understand how an app and what is happening.
It's an app you play at a casino.
No, you play it at home.
It's like slot machine games you play on your phone.
And then it gives you like a free appetizer or free twenty five dollars in slot play.
I see. So then you go to the place where you got the free thing.
And then you have to activate it at the counter.
OK, is that the story? Is the story finished?
Yeah, that's it.
And that was at Excalibur.
Yeah.
I just want you to recalibrate.
It just smelled like cigarettes everywhere.
I want you to recalibrate what you think is interesting now going forward on the podcast.
Because what Jason just told us his Excalibur story was that he was in line to cash in app points.
And he saw a lady kissing a man.
Like nasty.
And that was the story.
Like nasty kissing and she had interesting colored hair.
Right. But she didn't like go, hey, Jason, join us or something.
It was just like we saw people kissing.
So I just like going forward.
That's the bar is what I'm saying.
This is summer twenty twenty one.
So still very weird vibes in Vegas.
Yeah.
But I had racked up so many points because I was sitting.
I was sitting at home during twenty twenty.
Just playing these Vegas games.
Where were you trying to use the points?
A restaurant?
No, I was trying to use trying to use slot play.
I was trying to use Excalibur.
You were in line for a slot machine?
Huh?
If Scott were here, he would be so upset by now that we were talking about an app.
He would be screaming at Jason right now.
Stop talking about points.
I am taking advantage of his absence.
All right.
OK.
I'll ask further questions.
I had already cashed in free play Luxor, Bellagio and New York, New York.
And they said you can only do three casinos.
They cut him off like a bartender.
They cut me off.
I understand.
They cut him off from his free points via an app.
He did win like a hundred dollars at Luxor.
So it wasn't always not lost.
It's like if a mom was it's like if a mom was couponing too much and she went to a Ralphs
and they were like, Lady, look, you're cut off.
No more deals for you right now.
Yeah.
You're too good at this.
And then she saw a woman and a man kissing and then told all her friends about it.
It was nasty.
It was a May, December expression of love, Jason.
I know it was weird.
There was nothing.
Do you don't know what ages they were?
I could have been 25 and 60.
That's Madonna's dating a young man right now.
Cher is dating a 30 year old.
You're 77 years old.
Are you going to say Cher is inappropriate?
No.
One of our national treasures.
She is a national treasure.
Better not.
Look, we all got through 2020 in our own ways.
Some of us were playing flash games on our phone.
Some of us were like quickly eloping to Vegas.
That's right.
Out of boredom, out of necessity love.
Beth, did you get made out of boredom?
I was like, God, I'm bored.
I got to get married.
I got to get the fuck out of LA.
It was a good diversion.
Absolutely.
If you're bored, I recommend eloping to Vegas.
Yeah.
I think our listeners, yeah, if you're bored right now, turn this episode off and head
to the Excalibur.
Drive.
Well, you can't get married there.
Well, I did get the limo deal.
Yeah.
I want you to have your experience.
To get the limo deal.
Yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Well, let's get on the plane at Harry Reid International and fly to Denmark.
That used to be McCarran Airport.
They changed Harry Reid after he passed.
Yeah.
The Vegas airport.
Senator Harry Reid.
Senator, yeah.
You were in Denmark.
Yes.
And you would text me that you're like, have you done episodes on Tivoli Gardens?
Yeah.
And the other place that you all seem more excited about is a park called Bakken.
I would say I'm equally excited about both of them.
Oh, equally excited.
Okay.
Tell us about Bakken.
So Bakken, I mean, you tell me about it.
Bakken is the oldest amusement park in the world.
Yes.
And they tell themselves it's the oldest amusement park in the world.
Tivoli Gardens, I saw conflicting reports that it is the second oldest theme park in
the world or...
Third, I think.
Third after a park in Vienna.
Yes.
Austria is number two.
Yeah.
I haven't, I've only seen the third, the version where it's the third.
I have seen, I don't know.
I don't know if Tivoli is trying to keep this narrative going that they're the second.
I feel like it might be somewhere on their website that they're claiming this.
Oh.
But I don't know.
I didn't see any sort of write-up about a controversy.
Well, I did carbon date some items that I found at each amusement park.
Great.
And I'll let you know when the results come back.
Thank you.
Yeah.
We would appreciate that.
That's what our listeners want, is more carbon dating on this show to really be factual.
I, you know, honestly, that's not too far off because Bakken was established in 1583.
1583.
And I believe there was, like, we had to go to the king and get permission.
Right.
To make this an amusement area.
You had to get permission from the king to do most things though in 1583, I would assume.
You couldn't just go and get married in Vegas without the consent of the king.
Well, sure.
He's got to arrange the dirty limousine to him.
Well, the king did officiate my wedding.
Oh, okay.
Oh, right.
The king.
The King Elvis Presley.
Right, of course.
Yeah, it was by permission of the king that the guy built Tivoli Gardens.
Right.
Oh, Bakken.
Oh, and Tivoli Gardens.
And Tivoli Gardens.
I think both, yes.
Both had permission of their.
Yeah.
Yes.
Royalty.
But yeah, Bakken, a spring, freshwater spring was discovered and it seemed like entertainment
kind of sprung up around that.
Oh, cool.
Didn't know that.
Yeah.
Yeah, so Bakken, I love amusement parks and theme parks of all kinds.
And Bakken was like a 45 minute train ride outside of Copenhagen when we were there.
So I was like, let's go to Bakken.
And it's weird because it's a combination of like really old looking things and buildings
the Demon Clown Puro.
Puro, yes.
Which is like a whole thing, like a nightmare, Commedia del Arte mascot.
Like absolutely a terrifying, every image of Puro at Bakken and Tivoli Gardens was a
different kind of scary clown nightmare.
Yeah.
You could say he almost has like a nun's, what do you call it, a habit?
Habit.
On his head.
Yeah.
On his outfit.
Like it almost looks religious.
And then he has big like poof, white poofs on the front of his big jacket.
Yeah.
Giant eye, like dark eyebrows.
Yes.
In a lot of images and then like white face paint.
Right.
Yeah.
He is scary.
We're covering this when Scott's not here because he would just be screaming.
Is he scared of clowns?
He doesn't care for them.
Yeah.
He would really hate Puro.
There's a lot of Puro.
There's cartoon Puro and this other mascot, this moose mascot.
Oh yeah.
Well, we didn't see the moose.
Is that a Bakken or Tivoli?
That's Bakken.
Yeah.
So Bakken has like that kind of old school stuff, but the rides are like new-ish and
they look like they're from like a traveling fair kind of.
Like they're the kind of rides you would expect if you were like driving through Iowa and
you were like, oh, there's a fair here.
Right.
So it's just like, it's like one loop of rides.
There's a fun house that was pretty cool.
That was kind of like a little bit like the fun house in Greece at the end of Greece,
which is my measure of a fun house.
Right.
But otherwise it's just like one loop and you get like, we kind of got like bamboozled
into getting like a full pass, which was like really expensive.
It's like you can ride as many rides as you want.
Although we were then told that I think you could only go on a ride like there was like
a limit of like 40 times.
You could only go 40 times a day?
Yeah.
Ride with your best 40 times or something.
They just paid you as Americans and like, we know you're going to get excessive.
So only 40 times.
Okay.
Yeah, exactly.
They were like, we know your type.
But I did immediately get motion sickness, which I've never gotten before.
But Bakken took me down so hard that I only went on maybe like four rides before I then
just had to like sit and watch my husband go on rides without me.
He didn't care.
He was like, I'm going on the rides.
What ride took you down?
Great question.
So do you know the kind of ride where you're in like your own little like airplane kind
of thing and you control the wings and you can flip upside down?
Yes.
Have you seen the video of the woman who went and have you talked about her on the pod?
I know what you're talking about.
She went to the Mall of America and she would go every day and ride the like Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles version of this ride.
And she was like, I've gotten up to a hundred flips.
She was just like obsessed with it.
She was like, one time the ride stopped and I kept flipping.
They told me not to do that anymore.
She is amazing.
So we had seen that and my husband was like, I want to go on.
This is a ride like that and I want to try to flip.
Right.
So I was like, let's go.
And although I was not trying to flip myself, you like use your like body weight to shift
from side to side and you put one wing up and one wing down and you just try to like,
it's like a competition.
There's like a leaderboard.
How many who got the most flips?
Oh, I didn't realize there was like a competition aspect to it.
So this is a thing where it like it spins around, but then also your individual like
cars or whatever spins in like a circular motion.
Yeah.
So it's like, it just goes around on an axis like the like regular, like an airplane ride,
like a Dumbo ride or whatever.
And then, yeah, you can spin upside down, flip upside down.
So I was not trying to flip because I'm not a daredevil, but I was watching my husband
try to flip.
And because I was looking to the side for the entire ride, my brain's equilibrium got
really messed up.
So I got off that ride and I was like, I feel weird.
And then I rode a ride called Polyp that was like an octopus ride that was very spinny.
And I got off that and I was like, that's it for me.
In general, I try to avoid polyps of all types.
Yeah.
Polyps are never good, it turns out.
There's never a positive polyp.
Yeah.
Bakken, it's very unfortunate that you got the like unlimited ride, because Bakken is
unique.
You see this in a lot of older parks where admission is free.
Yeah.
And then you pay per ride.
That's right.
Or you just buy a full day pass.
And then ride four rides.
But there are weird, I watched some videos, there are weird nasty machines in the queue
for like ATMs or like you can buy the single ride ticket.
But many of them are like cash or coins only.
Yeah.
It was kind of overwhelming.
And it's also like every single person in Scandinavia speaks English.
Like it's of course a shameful thing to be an American there and speak no other languages.
Yeah.
Until we got to Bakken and the woman at the ticket counter, suddenly she doesn't know.
Oh yeah, yeah.
She can't answer a single question about whether or not we should get the all day pass.
Very convenient.
She was like, I don't understand what you're saying.
So she's like, I don't want to call you a mark, but she maybe saw you as a mark perhaps.
She looked at us, she saw a couple of Commedia del Arte clowns.
And she said, I'm going to get, yeah, she was like a teenager.
She didn't care.
Right.
But the other thing that was really weird and fun and interesting was we were there
during graduation time.
And do you know about Danish teens when they graduate?
I think I've seen some TikToks.
Jason, list everything you know about Danish teens.
Well, I think it's in Danish teens, but do they just get really hammered and just go crazy?
That's one thing they do.
Okay.
Yeah.
So he's partly right.
Do you know one other thing about them from TikTok?
No, I'm excited and afraid to hear about it.
They wear little caps.
They wear special little caps for like a week all around town that look kind of like train
conductor caps, like decorated with their name and embroidered and stuff.
So we were at Bakken with a ton of teens in like captain hats.
Whoa.
Now I'm interested.
Wow.
So yeah, truly like little like, yeah, like I'm trying to think of an example of a character
that like a skipper from Gilligan's Island hats.
If that helps.
Yes, that does help.
A 50 year old show.
Does that help?
Wait, what's his hat?
It's like a captain hat.
He wears the captain hat.
So do the captain's hats worn by the teens, do they like style each of them differently
or are they all sort of the same?
They are similar.
They're different colors, but otherwise they look pretty much the same except they have
names embroidered and the teens wear them everywhere with no real sense of irony it
seems.
Right.
And there were like, like, you know, 18 year old boys or whatever.
And they were playing like park games, like the game where you throw the ball on a little
trampoline.
Have you seen that?
I don't think so.
What do you mean?
You bounce the ball.
You bounce the ball on a trampoline and then the person across from you has to like slam
it back onto the trampoline and it bounces around.
Okay.
And they're tiny trampolines or a big one?
It's a tiny trampoline.
Okay.
Anyway, so these guys were wearing, you know, teens wear big giant like Jankos now basically.
Yes.
So it's these teenage boys in big giant jeans, shirtless, captain hats on.
Shirtless?
Captain hats on.
Wow, really?
Yes.
And do you know is this just like they've done this for hundreds of years or is this
a newer teen trend?
This is an old school tradition in Denmark and they wear their captain hats, they go
around and they get super drunk.
And shirtless?
Well, the shirtless thing was it was like hot and they were in the park.
So maybe that's just a Danish thing in general.
Well, it's a teenage thing like teenage boy thing.
Didn't you used to go slam a ball on a trampoline shirtless in the park when you were a teenager?
I don't know.
Maybe we slammed the ball, not on a trampoline, but somewhere.
We slammed balls somewhere.
But I wasn't looking to be shirtless a lot when I was a teen.
Scandinavian people are fit, outdoorsy.
Right, that's true.
Shirtless.
And in general, like a higher quality of life from this, from all the polls.
Yeah, exactly.
Happy, satisfied.
Yeah.
37 hour work week from what I understand.
Yeah, and it was the summer.
So like the sun's out all, you know, never goes down and all of that.
Yeah, it gets dark very late there.
Yes.
Yeah.
We never saw full dark while we were awake.
Like it's just like blackout curtains and you go to bed.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Interesting.
I think Jason wore like a captain's hat regularly for years.
That's not a joke.
I just need to buy him one, I think, to make it happen.
Wait, I have one.
That's true, you do.
But that's more of like a bit captain's hat.
I want like a nice fitted one for you.
Yeah, these are nice.
They're nice.
It sounds because they're embroidered.
Yeah, they're like high end.
Yeah.
At first I was imagining like, you know that thing, like colleges, freshmen all had to
wear little beanies.
What?
You know, I thought this was like a new thing.
Like jughead?
At colleges, like back in the like early 20th century, the freshmen all had to wear these
little like beanie caps.
But like jughead caps with a little crown?
Like with the propeller?
Yeah.
What do you, which?
No propeller, but kind of similar.
Like it would just be like cover the top of their head.
Are you thinking of like a Yanaka?
It's similar to, I'm familiar with a Yanaka.
It is slightly bigger, but similar size wise.
Got it.
It's like imagine a baseball cap and it was shrunk down to like a third of its size.
And it was, and I think it was just a way to like identify who you could rag on.
Yeah.
Like the freshmen were all Ed DeVex customers.
I really want to fact check this, but now is not the time.
I mean, I'm sure it was individual at each college.
I just remember it's a guy had a display case of historical like, I think it dates back
to the time when it's like sit on top of a flagpole cram got as many people into a phone booth.
Wasn't that the 60s?
Huh?
I think some of that tradition carried on to the 60s.
Wait, what?
The phone booth thing?
Yeah.
Wasn't that more of like a 60s thing?
I don't know.
I don't know when the phone booth thing was.
I don't even know what the phone booth thing is.
People would try this before television and the internet.
People would try to cram at a phone booth.
Okay.
As many people as they can fit in a phone booth.
I am going to fact check when telephone phone booth stuff started at colleges.
That's a good idea.
Okay.
Because I need to know that.
Yeah.
So Danish teens, shirtless, embroidered captain's hats.
In the park.
And they're hammered.
Hammered.
Are they polite or are they rowdy?
They were neither nor.
They were just like there.
Okay.
We didn't interact with them.
I did keep thinking like are we going to get bullied by these teens?
Yeah.
But they seemed to be weirdly unconcerned with us.
They weren't like clocking us.
They weren't clocking me with my head and my lap from motion sickness waiting for my
husband to get off a roller coaster.
So we just all minded our own business.
Oh, okay.
But that was one very kind of unique and interesting thing about when we were specifically at Bakken.
And another thing was one of the roller coasters my husband went on after I could no longer
go on a roller coaster, there's like a tunnel you go into and the roller coaster was not
themed.
However, when you got to this tunnel, there was a naked, above it, a naked woman and it
was as though you were going into her vagina.
Okay.
Hmm.
So.
He said when they got there, the teens behind him yelled pussy.
So he gets off the roller coaster.
He was like, I know you feel really sick and you want to leave.
I need to go on again to get a video.
It is very interesting to see.
Yeah.
Because it seems like the rest of the roller coaster, there's nothing else.
It wasn't themed.
It's just that.
Yeah.
It was just a roller coaster.
So happy to share that video with you if it's of interest.
We could put that on social media.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
Like, is it, I actually do, I miss this.
Is it like a, just sort of a cartoon version of this or is it just sort of to like, is
it like an abstraction of what it is?
Of a vagina?
Of going into the vagina.
Yeah.
Well.
Is it detailed?
I guess is really what I'm asking.
The tunnel is not adorned.
Okay.
It's a tunnel.
Right.
It's just, you understand it to be a woman's vagina because of the like cutout, like the
wooden art cutout above it.
Okay.
Which is like a painting of a naked woman.
With her legs open.
It's pretty graphic.
That's what we're getting at.
It's cartoon.
It's a caricature.
It's a photorealistic depiction.
It's like a health science like health book or something.
Yeah.
I wouldn't say that.
It's whatever you want to picture.
Okay.
When you picture riding a roller coaster into a vagina.
Which I assume when you both close your eyes to go to sleep at night.
That's kind of-
Well, that's how I fall asleep.
Yeah, yeah.
You visualize that.
It's like counting sheep for you.
You sent me a photo of Falken.
Yes.
And I'm trying to, oh, okay, it downloaded.
It's kind of like, it's a horse with a lot of teeth.
I don't know.
I don't know how else to describe it.
It's a painting of that.
Yeah.
Okay.
It feels like it should be said.
Did you say a horse with a lot of teeth?
That's right.
Well, you'll see why.
A toothy horse is what you're talking about?
He's smiling big.
Okay.
Yeah, he's smiling big.
I'm just going to send it to you.
Do you know what the words next to it translate to?
I do not.
Did you look it up?
I did not.
I forgot there were words.
I was just picturing the horse.
Yeah.
There was a lot of-
That was a nightmare one night.
I was trying to ride my favorite roller coaster,
but then I kept thinking about the tooth horse.
It's the last thing you want to see in a vagina.
Yeah.
So in this, do you know, I'd actually missed it.
How old is this ride?
Do you know offhand?
Or is this, this has been here for a while.
The woman, we're still talking about the woman.
We're still talking about the woman.
I don't know.
Well, the woman is of age.
Okay.
None of the rides, I thought we would go
and it would be like that exhibit about,
with the vintage amusement park stuff
that was just in LA or maybe still is.
Oh, the art exhibit that Drake, yeah.
Yeah.
Luna Luna.
I thought it would be like quaint,
like old, you know, cogs and things,
but it was new.
The rides felt very new.
Right.
Yeah.
Because some of the ones,
at least in Tivoli Gardens,
there's like a hundred years,
a hundred year old ride there.
Yes.
But yeah, so I mean,
this is another thing I'll check.
I'm checking on beanies.
I'm checking on the foam booth stuffing
and I'll check on the age of this ride.
I sent you the tooth horse.
Oh, thank you.
I have not seen it yet.
I turned my texts off on my computer,
but I'll take a look at this right now
and I will react live.
Oh, wow.
That is a toothy horse.
Whoa.
It's just a lot of teeth.
It's like a human mouth's worth of teeth.
Yeah.
It's like he got veneers or something.
It's a horse with veneers.
To find Danish tradition.
Yeah, the words next to it say veneer horse,
if you translate them.
That's partly why people have such a,
like a happy experience living in Denmark
is because the horses smile at them so broadly.
Even the horses have beautiful smiles in Denmark.
Yeah, and that cheers everybody up.
Yeah, exactly.
That makes you feel good.
Yeah, throw a little captain's hat on that horse.
Oh, shit.
That would be amazing.
Yeah.
This is scary though.
This is frightening.
Yeah, the art, a lot of it was like a little bit,
especially of the clown,
was like just a little bit freaky.
How often did you see that clown walking around?
Never, not once.
Oh, okay.
I took a picture of his little house
where it's like you would do a meet and greet
and it was shuttered.
I mean, not to the...
There's a little stage where he does
Little Comedienne Del Arte.
Yeah, that was not in session when we were there, sadly.
I have some sad news about the horse photo.
Oh, Jason.
No, I mean, I guess it's boring news.
The translation of the words is entrance to the stables.
Oh, why is that sad?
Well, because I thought it'd be weirder.
Like veneer horse with veneers.
Yeah, veneer horse here.
Come smile with the horse or something,
like smile with him.
I didn't even know there were stables.
That's fun.
There aren't anymore, I don't think.
I can't tell if it was literal
or if it was just like a little doodle or something.
Well, it is kind of a park.
You know, Bakken is a park as well
that you could just walk around
and it's pretty much like Tivoli Gardens.
So probably at a point.
I mean, there were stables everywhere, I assume.
Bakken, it seems like the gist
of reading about it, watching videos.
A lot of people go there to hang out.
There's a lot of restaurants.
There's a lot of green space.
And for the amusement park element,
they build up because they can't really expand out.
Right, yeah.
That sounds accurate.
There's a lot of different levels.
Yeah.
I think there is some nature restrictions.
It's protected area, so they can't really just expand.
Yeah, nor should they.
It's fine.
Yeah.
It's enough.
Yeah, it's enough.
People like it.
How was the food?
Did you eat there at all?
We had some gigantic beers.
There was a...
The candy selection was incredible.
My favorite candy is a filled rope,
like a licorice rope, but it has sugar kind of inside it.
Okay, yeah, but not like a nerd's rope?
No.
Okay.
That's a covered rope.
Okay, yeah, it's more like a jelly-filled donut,
but it's a rope.
Yeah, and they had a lot of options of that.
In general, I thought that the merch and food situation
at both parks was not good.
Okay.
Oh.
Well, Tivoli has all these fancy restaurants
that you could go to.
Okay.
But it wasn't Disneyland where you could casually go get...
A burger.
Yeah, or a big turkey leg.
Maybe they did have that, and I just missed it.
Okay.
But yeah, so we didn't eat much yet, and also I was dying.
Oh, I did have some really good fries
to try to curb my motion sickness.
Did it work?
No, no, it was just time.
Okay, okay.
It just needed time, maybe some water.
Fries does seem safer than a schnitzel with gravy.
Yeah, exactly.
Like settle it down with some mackerel snacks.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a picture on the website of what looks like a teen
with partial clown face paint.
Did you see any of that going on?
No, no.
Like a face painter or anything, no?
No, also all of the rides that we have videos of,
there was no one there.
That was the other crazy thing.
Yeah.
Never a wait.
Often they would operate the ride
with one or two people on it.
Right.
So I don't know why.
And school had just gotten out, you said.
It's the high season there when we were there, end of June,
but it just wasn't, it wasn't really,
maybe that's the version of like crowded that it gets
or something, but we didn't, there weren't like
the extra things like Pierrot wasn't there doing
his performances and his meet and greets
and we didn't see anyone doing like face painting and stuff.
So you didn't consider it like, all right,
I'm motion sickness, I can't do more rides.
I may as well get a full Pierrot face.
No, I didn't think about that.
But if I hadn't, I think the motion sickness
was taking up a lot of my brain space.
So if I had it to do over again,
I would have gotten my face painted like Pierrot for sure.
Did your husband Dave consider getting a full Pierrot face?
He was busy getting, he was really focused
on that vagina roller coaster.
So we both kind of had our own things going on.
Right.
Yeah.
Maybe Pierrot wasn't there and the people
didn't want to come because he wasn't around.
That's true, maybe they had heard
he wouldn't be there that day.
Right, this elderly clown.
He wasn't here.
The upsetting clown, they heard he wasn't there
so the Americans are like, oh thank God he's not there.
But the Dutch or the Danish.
Like this picture of him, he's an old man clown.
He looks like he's hanging out by a garbage
or like a ball wash at like a putting green or something.
Like I can't tell, it's like a little basket
with a little hole on the top.
I don't know what it's for.
Is he pulling something out of it?
Yeah, maybe he's doing like some scarf trick or something.
Oh God.
But yeah, he looks a little feeble
but he's giving a thumbs up and he appears to be married.
So he's got a ring on the ring.
I'm guessing he doesn't necessarily have to be married.
Do you think potentially he's married to the stage?
Do you think he has a formal ceremony?
Is there a Mrs. Pierrot?
Yes, it's the stage.
Yeah, it's the boards.
He's devoted his life to performing.
And yeah, he had an official ceremony.
I wonder if clowning in the style
that has become what LA people think of clowning
will make its way over and take over.
And suddenly instead of Pierrot, it's like Natalie Palamides.
Taking a dump.
Doing a fringe festival-esque performance
by taking a dump as she famously does on stage.
Is that what she does?
I haven't seen one of these shows.
No, she does eat raw eggs sometimes
and she hatches eggs and lays eggs.
That was just that one show about eggs.
That was just the one show.
Yeah.
So sometimes she wrestles audience members
in the Nate show.
Yeah, she was partially naked wrestling.
Anyway, I'd like to see maybe her...
I would like to see Pierrot partially naked
playing eggs on stage at this park.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I don't know.
Maybe clowning's passed him by at this point.
Maybe.
If he changes.
But maybe, yeah, I don't know.
I would think he would be there if he's the mascot,
so I hope nothing's wrong with him.
Yeah, it must have just been an off day for him.
Maybe he accidentally looked to the side on the flippy ride.
Oh, yeah.
He had to take some time.
He had to try to eat some fries and calm down.
Yeah, exactly.
So overall, did your husband like all of the rides?
Or was he just sort of, he wanted to get it done?
No, no.
He loved.
We both had a blast on all the rides we did,
and he went on a couple more than once,
and that's how he found out that there is a limit.
Right.
Even with the unlimited pass.
Careful.
You're at two or three.
You can't get to 40.
Exactly.
And there was a...
They scan a barcode.
So it is like keeping track.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Because you would think it would be old school,
but I guess these are...
It's very updated, and that was,
although it was really fun,
that was like the most disappointing.
I thought it would be like quaint and old school,
and it was not that.
Yeah.
Right.
So yeah, it's almost like too modern.
You would want it to be like more rickety.
Well, that is the trade-off is like the rides felt safe.
That's true.
For the most part.
Uh-huh.
But yeah, I kind of wanted them to be really rusty,
rickety, built 100 years ago.
I feel like if it's like a flat ride that doesn't spin you,
I would want it to be as old as possible.
Yeah.
If you're not going to lose your life if it malfunctions.
So yeah, I get that.
That makes sense to me, but yeah.
Because looking even like there's a big duck ride
that looks like a family thing where you spin it,
like the teacups Disneyland.
Yeah.
But the duck looks too new for me.
Yeah, it's all very snazzy and like, yeah.
Even like the carnival, you know, throw a thing or whatever.
Some of those are like older, but yeah.
Yeah, you would want, yeah, you would want like the duck
to be falling apart more, I think.
You would want his like beak to be falling a little better.
Yeah, there was an amusement park growing up in Denver
that's still there, I assume called Lakeside.
And it was like the alternative to the nice amusement park.
It was like the cheap, bad amusement park
and everything was falling apart and that was kind of its charm.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, there is a fine line though between a bad park
because sometimes it's good that it's falling apart
and then sometimes it's like depressing.
Yes.
Yeah, you got to hit it in its sweet spot
while it's on its way to becoming a depressing place.
Yes, right.
And like Six Flags is like their mission statement
was to always make it a little depressing.
Yeah.
But it doesn't, I don't think it ever had a,
not, I shouldn't say this.
Their mission statement.
It's always, depending on,
some of the parks were like acquired later.
So some of the parks actually started with some quaintness.
Yes.
And then they got sad.
But then some of them I think were just built
whole cloth as Six Flags.
And I feel like those maybe lack the old school charm.
Well, that is the good park in Denver was called Elitch Gardens.
Oh, yes, of course.
Oh, well, yeah, I just made that connection.
I've got some bad news because Scott went there.
Scott just went to Elitch Gardens.
He just went to Elitch Gardens.
You know, it became then a Six Flags.
Yes, it was a Six Flags briefly.
And then it unbecame a Six Flags.
Yeah.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, it's kind of, it just seems to be in disrepair.
It sounds depressing.
Oh no, that was the good one.
I know.
I was afraid that's what you were going to say.
It just seems like there was a lot of stuff down
when he was there.
Yeah.
And there was a lot of like preteen group,
like tour groups, like middle school, high school.
Yes.
Groups and I think trying to navigate them all.
Half the park is down.
That's fair.
They have a four year old with them.
And it just kind of was like a little overwhelming.
I see.
Well.
They have a Meow Wolf dark ride.
Meow Wolf was.
At Elitch's now?
Yeah.
At Elitch Garden.
Meow Wolf was given a full rein to redo a dark ride.
Great.
That looks kind of cool.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Maybe Lakeside's the place to go now.
The formerly bad one.
Who knows?
Oh, it could be.
Real quick, did you play this game that appears to be shooting water at somebody holding their
nose in a bathtub?
We played a shooting water game.
I can't remember if it was that one.
Okay.
Yeah.
Because I'm trying to figure out what the narrative of the game is because it's like
a person with different colored hair.
All the people have different colored hair.
One's orange or red.
One's green.
One's purple.
Are those not bath caps?
Oh, maybe they.
I don't know.
They look almost like a part, but maybe they are bath caps.
That's not in focus on this photo.
So perhaps not.
But then they're holding their nose and you're shooting.
I'm trying to figure out.
Are you trying to wash them fast?
Maybe you're trying to fill up the bath.
Maybe you're, but they've covered their, their lower half is covered in bubbles.
Yeah.
So they've already done some of it, but I wonder if you're trying to, I don't know if
there's like holes in their feet.
I don't know if you're trying to wash their feet and wash their chest and then wash their
hands.
Well, they represent the start of the school years.
So you graduate and you wear the little caps and you get drunk and then you're saying you're
washing a bunch of teams before they start the school year.
Well, they are shirtless like the teens I saw.
Right.
So.
Okay.
So this is like wash a teen for their first day of school.
Wash a teen for their first day of school.
Yeah.
That's what you're saying.
And then you're given a puree.
You're given a stuffed puree and you had to pass it on.
Oh my God.
And it's cursed.
It's alive.
Yeah.
It's a prize.
It's also cursed.
It's cursed.
Cursed clown.
Lots of fine Danish traditions.
Yeah.
Well, let's talk Tivoli Garden.
This is a historic park.
Yes.
It was a wonderful time because I'm like, what are the odds someone just got back from
Tivoli, the park that Walt Disney visited multiple times and heavily influenced like
Disneyland.
Heavily influenced.
Well, he apparently took a trip there with Art Linklater, the television broadcaster.
And Art would just catch him like scribbling down notes.
Yeah.
He would ask Art, like, what do you think about this?
What do you think about this idea?
Because he was like stealing ideas from Tivoli.
Yeah.
He was like the bad guy from Bring It On.
Very similar.
Yeah.
He was like, you know, like a Perot type.
He saw Perot and he said, I could learn a lot from that scary clown.
Yeah.
And it is like, it totally lives up to that.
Like, it's like clear.
There's just a lot of clear influence.
Although, I guess I don't know what rides were built when.
So, I don't know like what he saw.
I think it seemed like the things that sat with him are like very family friendly.
Yeah.
Good customer service.
The ambiance and the landscaping are very beautiful because it is like a gardens.
It is a public space.
You have to pay a nominal like $20 to get in.
Something like that.
Yeah.
I thought you could walk around and not ride any rides.
I thought it was Bakken rules.
And so, I did get in a bit of a tiff with the ticket taker.
Oh, wow.
I think it's like $20 to get in and then like 20 or 30 for like unlimited rides.
Yeah.
Which was not an issue for me because I continued to have motion sickness.
Oh, no.
Whoa, no.
So, it was a walk around situation for me.
But there's a lot of stuff.
There's like the NIMH Hotel, N-I-M-B, which on the outside looks kind of like the Taj Mahal.
And to me was like clearly a potential inspiration for the It's a Small World building from the outside.
But then there's this amazing dark ride called the flying suitcase.
Trunk?
Yeah.
Trunk or suitcase is how it translates.
And the inside of that seems to have maybe been the inspiration for the It's a Small World slash the haunted mansion, et cetera.
Yeah.
It is like a weird mashup of the two like styles to see.
Yes.
You would think that was like a big ripoff or something or like.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, I have the sign outside the flying trunk.
It says a fairy tale journey.
And it says, here you will meet numbskull Jack, Thumbelina, the top and the ball, the soldier and the dog with the eyes as big as teacups.
The Ice Kingdom to the north with the Snow Queen and the Robber Girl.
That's all one.
Yeah.
The Little Mermaid and her sisters in the Kingdom of the Sea King.
We all know that.
Right.
The Emperor of China with the artificial nightingale.
Again, I don't know about the translation on this, but this is in English.
Like this wasn't translated.
The Princess and the Pea and many more in Hans Christian Andersen's wonderful fairy tale world.
It is like it's a lot of Hans Christian Andersen stories in one like condensed into one ride.
Yes.
Hans Christian Andersen himself was apparently so taken by Tivoli Gardens.
It inspired that story, the nightingale.
So Tivoli was opened.
It's much more modern.
It was opened in 1843.
Much more modern.
It's brand new practically.
It's 180 something years old.
But yeah, that ride.
It's like, want to feel young?
Yeah.
But there's a lot of just like this drooping tree is covered in lights at night.
It's very beautiful.
Yeah.
Although it seems like it doesn't get dark till two in the morning.
Yeah, we didn't get to experience darkness there.
But yeah, it's stunning.
It's beautiful.
It's like even the carousels are like the most beautiful, elaborate, ornate things.
Yeah.
Everything is just like really, really pretty.
There's like a lake that was like part of like the moat originally.
Yeah.
The city.
It's just really nice.
And there's swan boats and stuff.
Yeah.
So there is an adorned haunted house that you can walk through.
Did you do via vendetta?
We did not.
Wait, is that like a fun house or a haunted?
No, it's like a haunt.
That must be during Halloween or is it year round?
I couldn't tell.
It seemed like it might be.
I think it's in addition to whatever ticket.
You have to pay another fee for that.
I don't think that was running when we were there.
I think it might be seasonal because they have like Halloween and Christmas stuff too
that I think would be very fun.
But we didn't see that.
From what is video, it's a vibes park to me.
It just feels like that's the draw is like just how scenic it is and being there,
especially if you can be there during the nighttime.
Yeah.
It's not a rides park if that's kind of what you're saying.
That's what I'm saying.
It is a vibes park.
It's like there's also the best thing we saw by far was there's this theater
and it's like a giant outdoor, it's a proscenium stage and then an outdoor seating area
with like, there's like some chairs I guess you could reserve,
but then there's just like a hill where people are just watching.
And the theater is like in the style of almost like a Chinese palace, like the proscenium.
So beautiful.
And then the curtain is like a big peacock.
Feathers.
Yeah.
And it opens like a peacock's feathers would go down.
I guess I know what you mean.
I don't know how else to say it.
It takes like a number of people to operate it.
I think they may have it automated now.
Oh, do they?
Okay.
To me, it didn't look man-operated, person-operated.
It looked more mechanical or something.
But yeah, it's really beautiful and ornate.
And then there's a show that we saw called Clumsy Hans.
That's great.
That's a ballet, like a pantomimey, like almost like Commedia del Arte ballet
about a guy named Clumsy Hans.
And there was just a huge crowd just watching like a gentle ballet.
Wow.
Yeah.
It looks like they put up shows like this all the time.
It's been like a hundred and what 80 years.
But is Clumsy Hans, is that Hans Christian Andersen?
Is he Clumsy or is it just that's a guy's name?
I think that's just a guy's name.
Okay.
It's like Clumsy John.
Interesting.
And are his eyes as big as teacups or are they normal?
We were kind of far away, but his, you know, it's more his clumsiness.
It's his defining feature more so than big eyes.
Fair enough.
But he, like his like dad is wants his brothers to marry a princess
and he's going to like take them on horses and then Clumsy Hans wants to go too
and dad's like, I don't want you to meet the princess.
And then Clumsy Hans has to ride a goat.
Does he do it well?
Because he seems he's clumsy.
So well, here's the twist.
Clumsy Hans is only clumsy in that.
I mean, he's the person who played Clumsy Hans was like a great ballet dancer.
Right.
But he kind of like tumbles in a graceful way.
Okay.
But it's still clear ballet like graceful ballet.
He's not taking like hard Chevy Chase style falls.
Yeah.
I was going to say Chris Farley.
He's not like falling through a coffee table or whatever.
He falls, but he rolls out of it probably in a beautiful way.
Yeah.
And the fall is like it's like West Side Story dancing fight, fight dancing, you know,
where you're like, no one's really they're just like dancing.
Right.
So Clumsy Hans is maybe like a nickname he created to like pretend he's like faux humble
or something because he sounds like he's very graceful.
Hans is very graceful actually.
Other people are the ones calling him Clumsy Hans.
But I guess he I didn't delve too deep into it.
Maybe he is perpetuating that to be like, right.
I'm just clumsy.
And oh my God, did I just do a perfect pirouette?
Okay, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Clumsy Hans.
Is the goat cantankerous?
They're fickle creatures.
The goat is a two dimensional painted goat head on a stick.
Okay.
All right.
So does he ride it just like a little hobby horse?
That's right.
All right.
Really go either way, you know, with one of those.
You mean it could be friendly or not?
Well, I'm saying you could really eat shit or you could just go about your business.
That's right.
Yeah.
But he has full control over the goat character because of just the simpleness of that of
that apparatus.
Yeah.
Is Clumsy Hans, is he good looking?
Like, is he also just like I picture him hot.
Yeah.
Clumsy Hans has like a kind of a boyish good, good looks.
Not like a manly, like his brothers were more like manly, hot.
Okay.
Like brooding, whatever, princes.
And then he's kind of like a boyish.
He might be hot for American standards, but by Danish standards, he's not quite.
They're looking for like a more tough guy or something.
I don't know.
You don't think that's right?
He's trying to figure it out in a picture.
He's trying to figure out how fuckable Hans is in addition to being clumsy.
I would say if you saw Hans in Vegas with an older woman.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Come on.
You would think this is going to be a good story later.
Okay.
Got it.
Now I know what he looks like.
A boyish charm.
Got it.
Well, that's, yeah.
We oftentimes lament the fact that Disneyland and Disney seems to be going away from a lot
of live entertainment.
Oh, is it?
Well, just like they closed shows and there's an empty, the Hyperion theater in California
Adventure has been empty for a while and that used to have a big elaborate Aladdin show
and a Frozen show.
I think it's going to get demolished for Avatar in the next five years.
And there's other examples of live entertainment being cut, which is very important.
Well, yeah.
To me in these parks.
I'm curious what you think.
I was with someone at Disneyland recently that has a conspiracy theory about the fireworks.
Oh, can we hear it?
So, no.
Next question.
Got it.
All right.
Oh, okay.
So when I was there, they canceled the fireworks because of quote unquote wind.
Right, right.
Yeah.
We could not detect any wind.
We're looking at the trees.
We're not seeing the trees blowing enough that fireworks couldn't happen.
Right.
And he is like, goes there quite a bit, this person I was with.
And he's like, the fireworks are always canceled these days.
And then we looked up how much it costs to do a fireworks show.
And he's like, they're just trying to save money by pretending it's the wind.
I would believe that.
It's the theory.
I believe it.
Yeah.
Usually when I've seen them cancel it, it feels like it's windy.
But yeah, I would believe that.
Yeah.
There's a lot.
There could be a lot of costs, like downing live shows or running it a lot less sporadically,
canceling fireworks, closing restaurants before the park closes.
There's lots of ways to nickel and dime.
It's the Disneyland version of saying the ice cream machine is broken at a McDonald's.
Exactly.
It's exactly that.
And I look, I know there's articles about those being hard to fix.
You've sent them to me listeners and I don't care.
I still don't believe it.
That was like a new thing.
I feel like that just came out.
Yes.
Like some article about ice cream machines.
Yeah.
Some sort of impossible contract and impossible.
Like one company makes machines and only they can service them.
Jason believes this a lot.
And I think it's wrong.
This feels like Big Donald's planting kind of a news story.
Yes.
With their power.
I agree.
Yeah.
So I don't believe it either.
But yeah, the big attraction that's like clearly a Disneyland thing is the big rollercoaster
that looks, it's like a mountain.
It looks like the Matterhorn.
Yeah.
And it like towers above everything else.
And it's just, you can see it from a lot of parts of Copenhagen because, or downtown,
it's like this Tivoli is in the middle of Copenhagen.
In the middle of Copenhagen.
And you can just see like basically the Matterhorn.
It's very cool.
But it's like, that's clearly where Disney got that idea.
Wait, I'm confused.
Is that the one with the person that operates it on the car?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
A hand cart.
Handbrake.
There's a brake.
This is very rare.
There's only a few left in the world, but the roller coasters were right in the middle
of the roller coasters.
A guy operates a handbrake.
And I saw videos where he's like standing up and waving.
Yes, that's what I saw, yes.
Yeah.
Which seems like, I don't know if I like it better that there's a human being doing it.
I don't think I do.
I don't like it at all.
Yeah, I don't think, right?
No.
Because like what if he forgets?
Okay.
I just mean like a computer is just going to do it unless something like a virus happens.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's terrifying.
You would think, yeah, because there's literally like an old train, like a big crank, like
an old train.
There's not like a coal section where he's putting coal into an engine, but.
It's crazy.
I wonder if there's videos where he has like one ear pod in.
Like if he's listening to a podcast.
He's listening to a murder podcast.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then he gets so excited he forgets to break the thing.
Because the climax of the podcast happens and he gets, yeah, he just gets distracted.
I wonder what the worst thing that would happen if he doesn't do the break right would be.
I mean, it would go sailing off the track, I'm assuming.
The whole thing.
It's the only one thing that could happen.
Yeah, right.
It would have to go, yeah.
Or, I mean, maybe the worst thing is just you go around again.
Maybe, actually, now that I think about it.
He has to break it though at certain points in the roller.
It's not just to end it at the end.
Okay, yeah.
So yeah, it's throughout.
Throughout.
Yeah.
Every roller coaster at Disneyland, and imagine there's the guy on it who has to, every time there's a turn or something where they have to slow down, he has to hit a button or pull a lever.
That should be like the highest pay, they should make like baseball player salaries to do that.
Yes, I agree.
Like you have many people's lives in your hands.
Yes.
Yeah.
Like every roller coaster has a conductor.
Every roller coaster has a person.
Imagine if that was on the vagina roller coaster and the guy had to focus.
Well, he'd get distracted.
Yeah.
Dead man's curve.
You know?
That's what I call my vagina.
Yeah, it's so scary.
I think I would want one on Big Thunder at Disneyland.
Not a vagina, a conductor.
Really?
That would be fun.
Because he could dress up like an old prospector, he'd have a big hat and a big beard, and then he could say stuff while the ride was going on.
You get like a live performer aspect.
I'm serious.
Yeah.
Like a performer aspect to Big Thunder.
But you want someone going like, hold on tight, folks.
Yeah, I want him to give me the business while the roller coaster is happening.
Yeah.
Like roast me gently.
That would be fun.
Yeah.
Little Ed DeBevix style roasting.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, the live performances are like the most special thing for sure.
We also went to an open-air museum in Stockholm that had like the greatest musical I've ever seen in my life.
Really?
It was set in the 50s.
I mean, in like a campy way.
Yeah.
And it was just about a guy whose job gave him a washing machine as like a reward for doing a good job at work, and his family being confused in the 50s about what the washing machine is.
And like his wife worrying that if she used the washing machine, she would have too much time on her hands to think about other things.
It's like very existential.
Wow.
There's a whole song about the man not being able to find his hat.
He's a hat man and he needs to find his hat.
That sounds good.
It was honestly so good.
We were like actually laughing.
The performers were great.
And it was just in the middle of this like random like reenactmenty kind of open-air museum in Stockholm.
So that kind of stuff is very special.
Yeah.
Looking through, that was the stuff even just the Tivoli like made excited to be more than just the old ride that seems like it could fly off a track.
And will.
And might.
Yeah.
Well, although that one's been around for like 100 years, so I guess they're all experts at it.
I don't know if this happened.
I don't know what day of the week you were there.
I'm excited by something at Tivoli called Friday Rock.
We were not there for Friday Rock.
What's Friday Rock?
Friday Rock seems to be some sort of a concert series where you will get rock and roll.
One of my favorite music genres.
But what I was most excited is they have tribute bands like Billy Joel, the piano man from New York.
A tribute to Billy Joel.
And it looks like it also has some sort of a narrative about his career.
Like they're doing a little story about like Billy Joel like starting out.
A jukebox musical.
That's what it seems.
I could not find a video of it.
So I don't know.
That's cool.
And it seems like maybe it only happens at Tivoli.
They have the names of some of the performers and I looked those up and that didn't seem to be.
We did see a list of names of performers.
Yeah.
But we weren't there for any of the performances.
The piano man from New York tells the musical story of Billy Joel's life and career about ups and downs and how a boy from the Bronx who would have preferred to be a professional boxer instead went on to become the world's most powerful.
He became the world's most popular piano man with album sales of over 150 million copies and with hits such as Uptown Girl, Just the Way You Are, Tell Her About It, Honesty, New York State of Mind and of course the signature song Piano Man.
Wow.
So you get like a full bio of Billy Joel if you go to Friday Rock.
They have a Tina Turner show as well.
I don't know if I would trust them.
You don't think in Denmark that's a safe trip?
I'm just wondering how they would cast that.
You know, it's a good question.
I did not see a video and maybe there's a reason why.
Yeah, they're like phones down.
That's like, I see, I think Hamilton is starting to be done by high schools, including some high schools in the Midwest and I think, I think I see an issue.
Listen, I was in the Wiz in high school.
This has come up before.
He sang a lot of Wiz in high school.
He's on down the road in like middle school chorus.
Yeah.
And like spiritual, like wade in the water.
Yes.
Yeah.
And yeah, looking back, I'm like, well, this spirit was correct, you know, like exposing us to new things.
But it is very funny to look back on.
I know.
Yeah, Hamilton taking on that role now is very special.
They list like this Friday Rocks.
They like in their history, they have like sort of a history on the website of different moments and they added Friday Rock.
Like this was a big deal.
1997.
I got to go back.
And then you have to go back and they list, they list like the first performers, the first few performers, including Danish rappers.
Den Gale Pose, I guess.
And I did look up what Den Gale Pose is.
Big hit was.
And this is the vibe of them.
They are all in like straight jackets.
Yeah.
Which honestly, I don't know that the music really sounds like, but like it sounds like this.
Wait for the Danish rapping rock and roll.
Yeah, we're rocking now.
So that's like one of the first groups that played Friday Rock.
Wow.
Imagine you get to watch Clumsy Hans, the ballet, and then go over to the bandstand and listen to that.
Right.
That would be a perfect Friday.
I didn't understand a lick of that.
But you understood the vibe of it.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
You felt it.
I have a couple more Walt Disney things.
OK, great.
Yeah.
One, there's this picture.
So if you go on a Disney cruise that as a port stops in Copenhagen.
Oh.
As a, you know, day on land.
Yeah.
I'm losing the word.
I can't think of the words right now.
I don't know what the cruise ship calls it.
A day on the land?
It's a port.
It's like, oh, we're stopping here and we're stopping here.
I think you have to pay to get off the ship.
Off the Disney cruise?
I think so.
I think there's an upcharge if you want to go and do their like Tivoli Gardens day.
Like a shore day or something?
There is the Tivoli Gardens packet.
It's like you get, you get driven to Tivoli Gardens.
You get the ride thing.
I think you get a tour and like lunch and a beer.
Yeah.
So, but on that page where they were talking about the Tivoli option,
there's this picture,
Walt Disney wearing a bearskin hat in Tivoli Gardens while a drummer boy stands by.
And it's about what you'd think it would be.
It's a big hat.
Oh, yeah.
And he's smiling.
It's huge.
It's like a Buckingham Palace guard hat.
Yeah.
And then the drummer boy, is he, is he seated at a full drum kit?
No, he's got like the drum they wear.
Oh, to like be in a parade, in a marching band or whatever.
Okay.
And he, I believe they, I believe these two are members of the Tivoli Boys' Guard.
Yes.
Which is like a long, they've had this forever.
It's just a bunch of boys that are like a marching band.
Yeah.
And it seems like some sort of a grand tradition.
And I, did you see the Tivoli Boys' Guard?
We did not see the Tivoli Boys' Guard.
However, the changing of the guard in Copenhagen, I'm like trying to, you don't want to mistake
the, the Stockholm and the Copenhagen change.
Yeah, yeah.
If the guard people would come for me.
Right.
So fast.
But, so the one in Copenhagen is pretty young people and they march every day, like a long
ways through the city.
Okay.
It's like the biggest waste of time.
They seem kind of proud to be doing it, but it's like, why are you all doing?
Like it's so antiquated, but it is just this grand tradition.
So they love to march in formation from place to place and have it be like a daily tradition.
Interesting.
So they're like passing an Apple store and each and them.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's through like the shopping district of Copenhagen.
Well, then you can be like, hey, sorry, I was like getting back from lunch.
The marching was going on.
I got stuck by the changing of the guard.
Yeah.
Interesting.
I mean, Disneyland still has marching band.
Yeah.
There is still like a hold over like feeling of like the people want to see people march
and play their instruments.
It feels sinister.
Well, that's the way I put it.
Yes.
Say they enjoy the music.
They want to hear brass.
Yes.
They want to hear a big brass version of, I just can't wait to be king or something.
Yeah, right.
But yeah, the Tivoli boy.
I don't know.
I should have looked up like what age you have to leave the Tivoli boys guard because like
it feels like you can't be an older man.
Right.
And be in the boys guard anymore.
There's just a guy like every day shaving his like five o'clock shot.
Please let me stay.
They force him out and he's like shell shocked PTSD.
Yeah.
So he just goes and joins the French Foreign League.
There's that one place in Paris you can just show up and knock on the door and join the
French Foreign Legion.
Yeah.
There's like a gateway right from the boys guard into that.
It's a straight line.
Yeah.
Another Disney connection.
The founder of Tivoli Gardens, George Carstensen said in 1844, Tivoli will never, so to speak,
be finished.
And then a hundred plus years later, Walt Disney says Disneyland will never be complete.
It will continue to grow as long as there is imagination left in the world.
Whoa.
So sort of stole it.
Yeah.
He did steal it.
I wonder if it's it's definitely true of Disneyland.
Yeah.
They're always tweaking that.
They're always doing something.
Yeah.
They're always up to no good.
They're always keeping all the fireworks to themselves.
I do wonder if they're like renovate like I don't know Tivoli felt done or something
like but it is in the middle of the city.
So there's kind of only so I guess they could like redo things.
Somewhat recently they added a little bit, but it's like I think real estate is hard
to come by.
So yes, it's not.
There's not an easy way to expand it.
Yeah.
You're going to run into like a monument pretty fast.
Yes.
You can't do anything about it.
It is.
I think it's called.
It's called Demon.
Yes.
Which is like a B&M full on like metal roller coaster.
It's a roller coaster manufacturer.
So that is there next to like the beautiful pagoda and the pond or lake or whatever.
Yeah.
It's part of a whole like like Asian style.
There's like Midway games, but it's like like Asian like it's just like this beautifully
themed lanterns and like dragons and stuff.
And then there's like an old west themed part like a vaguely old west part too.
Yeah.
Can I say something about George Carstensen?
And I don't want to get off on a whole thing here.
And maybe this is just because the glasses are similar.
But Jason, do you resemble George Carstensen?
I think there's a picture of you.
There's a picture of him with glass.
You used to have small glasses.
I think that's what I'm responding to.
I don't think you look like him necessarily, but there is like a high school photo of you
that I've seen where I do think you resemble Tivoli Gardens founder George Carstensen.
Do you see what I'm saying?
At least I'm not saying this is an exact situation.
I unfortunately see what you're saying.
OK, there's I think I think it's mostly glasses.
You never had your hair like this.
No.
Oh, dude, did you?
Not on purpose, but I think 2011, 2012, I let my hair.
I just let my hair grow.
And it kind of feathered.
It kind of curled at the ends.
Right.
So I think there's an old photo that just there's a and I think really what it is is not even necessarily features.
It's more the vibe of the photo.
I was going to say it's the vibe.
It's the vibe of the photo and the glasses.
Yeah.
And I think we've got to put the pictures next to each other.
You have kind of the vibe of a Danish man who died at age 44 in 1857.
Thank you so much.
You're so welcome.
I did.
But he created he created magic.
He's the reason we have Disneyland in the current condition.
You know what? I'll take it.
And I looked I looked for bad stuff about him and I didn't find it because I usually when we do this, you're like, OK, what did he do?
Yeah.
But I don't there was I maybe I didn't dig deep enough, but it seemed like he served in the military.
He started this. He went to the king.
He got permission for this.
All above board.
And then 44 he died of pneumonia.
Yeah.
But yes, that's that's there's we'll we'll post this online and you can tell us.
We need a picture.
Yeah.
Side by side.
We'll do a side by side.
I was looking some of this park was destroyed during World War Two.
Yeah.
Because.
Well, it's old enough because I was like, wait, did either of the wars affect the Nazis?
Sure enough.
Denmark said we're not getting involved.
They were probably taken over by the Nazis.
They're too close to Germany.
They're they're right.
But up against Germany.
Right.
But then they were attacked because they were Nazi territory.
Yes.
Doesn't seem like a damage was great.
They were close for like two weeks.
It just burned down like one roller coaster or something or one.
Yeah.
One building.
Quickly rebuilt and reopened.
Yeah.
I was like, that two weeks is nothing.
Well, one fun thing about Copenhagen.
And this is not really about Tivoli, but is and it wasn't Nazis in general.
But every building in Copenhagen has burned down like multiple times.
And I don't know if this is true.
But we went on like a tour and our tour guide said that it was a combination of like it's cold.
You know, it's cold and dark.
You have to like have a fire going at all times.
It's cold and dark.
People are drinking a lot and the water is frozen so they can't like put out the fires.
Right.
And so it wasn't a Nazi thing in that way.
But at Tivoli, it was a Nazi thing.
So one way or another, a building in Copenhagen is going to burn down and be rebuilt at least once.
The talk of old rides was making me think about the early, early days of Coney Island.
And some of the original Coney Island stuff is you were really taking your life in your hands.
We're not 100 percent on the physics of like sending someone upside down.
And some of that stuff is not around anymore just because they would just constantly burn down in Coney Island.
There was just so many cheapy slapdash haunted houses or shoot the shoots or rollercoaster, whatever.
Like it's a miracle the cyclone has survived.
Well, the cyclone is so painful to ride.
I hear that.
I threw my back out so badly on the cyclone.
And when I was in New York before I went to Scandinavia, we went to Coney Island.
We were like, should we take our lives into our hands and go on the cyclone?
And we're like, no, we have like a two week trip ahead of us.
Let's not throw our back out today.
But it's the most painful ride I've ever been on.
Wow.
Yeah.
Geez.
It seems like you love amusement parks, but they really have not been treating you well.
I think I'm just a weak, feeble, easily rattled person maybe.
Okay.
So you have to like toughen up before you go to your next one?
Yeah.
I'm going to need to go into some training, some combat training.
Okay.
Before I go back.
Can I real quick?
Back to Carstensen.
Just real quick.
He obtained a five year charter to Create Tivoli by telling King Christian that when
the people are amusing themselves, they do not think about politics.
So that was his big sales pitch is that they're not going to hassle you, King, if they're
on a little ride or if they're seeing like fun lights.
Yeah.
I guess he's right.
So I feel I don't know that he was like helping the King do anything nefarious, but it kind
of seems like he could have been.
Yeah.
Throw them on the polyp.
Right.
They'll never think about anything ever again.
They won't notice you stealing from them.
Yeah.
If they're eating a big churro or whatever version of that they had a hundred years ago,
180 years ago.
Let me ask, because obviously we talked about Perot and being the mascot of Bakken.
Did you meet Rasmus Klump and his friends?
I thought you might ask about Rasmus Klump and his friends.
I knew it would come to this.
I knew Rasmus would weasel his little way in here.
And no, but we saw little sculptures of them and took a lot of pictures in like kind of
the kids area in the Rasmus Klump area.
And it's adorable.
Yeah.
The other thing we saw over there and I don't know when it was built and I was like trying
to figure it out is, you know, like Monstro the whale.
Yes.
And there's like there's like a similar looking thing at Tivoli Gardens.
Oh.
And you go inside the mouth.
It's a little like souvenir store.
So it's not a ride.
Right.
Present day.
And I don't know how it started, but it is a giant whale where you it looks the same
as just a different color.
And you go in the mouth.
So that could be a similar theft.
It could be, although I guess it's also the story from the story.
Pinocchio.
Yeah.
But I thought that was interesting.
That was near Rasmus Klump.
Oh, okay.
And the merchandise in the whale's mouth did not live up to your expectations.
No, the merch was quite weak.
A lot of it was just general like Danish like national merch.
Okay.
I wouldn't need to ever buy Lego like they're really into Legos, of course.
Oh, yeah.
And like just like a tie with like the Danish flag on it and stuff.
So I wanted some kitschier.
Yeah.
I really wanted kitschy Bakken merch, but that did simply did not exist.
What would your dream merch have been from either place?
Oh, that's a good question.
Maybe like a t-shirt with like a poorly translated maybe a t-shirt with the Hans Christian Andersen
spiel on it from the Flying Trunk Ride.
Okay.
Or like, yeah, I like a thing that's like specific to one ride.
Yeah.
I agree.
Maybe some socks with like the whale on it or I don't know.
There's a lot of options, merchandising options that they're not tapping into.
Yeah.
Would you have bought a clumsy Han action figure?
I would have bought a clumsy Hans anything.
I would have I would have stocked up.
I would have bought a second suitcase to get home with just clumsy Han stuff in it.
Wow.
I would have bought a series of plush like a plush Hans.
A plush Hans.
Yeah.
The hobby or a hobby goat he rides.
The goat.
That's a no brainer.
Goat on a stick.
That's an easy thing to make.
Oh, that's your carry on.
Yeah.
You ride that thing onto the plane.
I would have gotten a second seat for my goat on a stick.
Yeah.
If they had been selling that.
The International Flight.
It's fine.
You can afford it.
Yeah, who cares?
Who cares?
You should.
And do you think anyone's actively pitching a clumsy Hans TV show in America?
Does who owns that?
Do they own the IP of clumsy clumsy Hans?
It must be.
Well, the government maybe owns it.
Is it a Hans Christian Andersen?
That's a good question.
It might be public domain at this point.
Clumsy Hans.
It might be you.
This might be on you to pitch this.
Well, yeah, you should pitch it.
But I.
I'm going to buy it real quick.
So you have to pay me.
Yeah, we should.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Hans Christian Andersen.
Clumsy Hans.
It is one of his stories.
That's interesting.
And he named him Hans.
Right.
So I wonder if he felt he was clumsy.
But then that makes a lot more sense because he's actually thinks he's like cool.
So he's right.
Oh, this guy's so clumsy.
I'm so clumsy.
I'm so quirky.
It's probably darker in the fairy tale, though, right?
Like he probably died of.
He killed a bunch of people.
Consumption or killed people.
Yeah.
Oh, his clumsiness.
Clumsy Hans.
Let the slaughter.
It's a short story for children by Danish author Hans Christian Andersen.
It was first published as part of an anthology stories, 1855, public domain.
Oh, baby.
You're going to have competing pitches in this room for Clumsy Hans going forward
so we can do some.
Jason will do like a horror movie version like those Winnie the Pooh,
like those Winnie the Pooh ones.
And then there's the Steamboat Willie, of course, now coming out
direct to DV like he's a killer and Mickey.
Oh, my God.
Wait, is that real?
Yeah, it is real.
A killer Steamboat Willie.
Yeah, just Steamboat Willie.
He just is in the public domain.
I see.
But not the other Mickey's.
Oh, not yet.
But why is he a killer?
That didn't.
Why is he a murderer?
Sorry.
Because people are just like running with the public domain.
Like, what if it was fucked up?
Cool.
Yeah, yeah.
So you can do that with Clumsy Hans.
OK, that's good to know.
I have more Rasmus Klump stuff.
Would you have bought a plush of Klump?
No, because it's just a bear.
Oh, OK.
I didn't go through all 80 of the books,
but on the website, it says,
learn more about Pele Pelican,
Pingo Penguin and all the other good friends.
Discover who Rasmus Klump's ship is named after,
what Skeeg Sea Lion's most prized possession is
and who loves playing cards, but hates losing.
Wait, so Rasmus Klump is a gambler?
Well, we don't know.
We don't know.
There's mysteries.
It could be Pingo.
It could be Pele.
It could be Skag.
Skank?
It could be Skank.
It could be Pingo.
Wow.
So these are there's a series of books.
Yeah, I think they're a beloved series of children's books.
They're comic strips, I see.
Oh, OK.
They don't use speech balloons.
Oh, interesting.
It can be classified as a text comic.
And it was created.
It was 1951 when it started.
So that is not public domain yet.
Well, I have to say,
Rasmus Klump was, to me, reminiscent of the like cartoons and mascots at Knotts.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
That like bearer family and then like the like naughty
foxes or whatever that are trying to steal their boys and berry pies.
Yes. Yes.
It felt that a little bit to me.
Without the naughty foxes.
The berry, the berry tales bears.
The boys. Yeah, there's boys and berries and girls and berries.
Girls and berries. Yes.
And what's that?
We all know.
So maybe Mr. Knotts also paid a visit.
Oh, Walter. Walter Knotts.
Yeah. Walter Knotts, actually.
Knotts. Yeah.
It's the apostrophe is right.
Before the S. Right.
Yeah. Yeah.
I that's a good did Walter Knotts ever visit Tivoli Gardens
because Walter also stole from Knotts. Yeah.
So I wonder if Walter also did some theft.
That's interesting.
Like later passed on some proprietary information to both of them, perhaps.
Yeah, that's a good question. Yeah.
We'll have to look into that.
There's a lot of things I got to look into now after this episode.
So the wonders of Europe, of Scandinavia.
I don't know anything about world history, but I do want to know more
about Rasmus Klump and his friends.
That is a priority.
Nasty, weird friends.
One of them likes to gamble.
But you have to read all the books to find out who it is or look at the books.
There's never words.
No, there is. Yeah, it says there are words.
It seems like a lot of captions, but not word bubbles.
Not word bubbles. The words are underneath underneath the pictures.
They're underneath the cards. I've read the books.
Look, the books.
Look, I don't there's I don't know what else to describe it.
But the book picture of the books, I go, oh, there's got to be something bad in here.
Like it's old school, like cartoon stuff where I just started immediately going,
oh, those feel like there's going to be something inappropriate
or racist in one of these. Almost certainly.
Yeah. 1951. Yeah. Yeah.
Some children smoking cigarettes.
Maybe they're fine. Maybe I'm maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I'm thinking something bad about Rasmus Klump.
Those like all the tin tin books.
Yeah. There's some rough stuff.
Yeah, I'm sure there's bad stuff.
Jason will read all these books and report back to us.
Shit. You could you could read them so fast.
It would only take you like three years to read all of these children's books.
Oh, man, Jason, I don't want to say again that you might resemble a character,
but this picture of Rasmus Klump looking at all these pancakes.
That really gives me a Jason vibe right there.
Yeah. So kind of like you.
And he's got like a he's got like a knit cap on and no shirt.
Yeah. But he's like a freshman.
Rasmus has a cap.
Yeah, he has a freshman cap on.
He's wearing I have answered to the freshman cap question that I will say at the end.
He's wearing a Mike, Mike Nesmith from the Monkeys hat.
That's again, a reference that's older than Gilligan's Island.
Yeah. But yeah, he's I mean, he's fun looking.
So it's a shame you didn't see him in person.
Yeah, I feel like also the need to say that I didn't just go to theme parks.
I did so much highbrow stuff.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All the museums I've sure looked at from the inside.
Was this trip anything specific you were going for or?
It was no, no, just just for fun.
Just visiting Europe.
Just visiting a part of Europe I hadn't been to.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
What is and if you're uncomfortable saying that's OK.
But what was the percentage of theme parks to actual museums and historical sites?
I went to only two theme parks total.
OK. And it was Bakken and Tivoli.
One day each.
One, not even a full day.
OK. Half a day.
OK. Tops each because they're little, which is nice.
Right. It's not like Disneyland or Disney World.
That's better than when we when Lindsay and I went to Japan.
And it was like half Disney, half Japan.
Yeah, that would be a concern for me.
Yeah, I would have to build in many extra days.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, we went to it.
Well, I guess going to Sanrio Pearl and in my mind counts.
That's like a museum.
There's a museum. Right.
Yes, exactly.
And there was only half day.
So that was fine.
Yeah, we were we was a more shameful visit in a lot of ways and what you're describing.
OK, good. Yeah, I feel great about myself.
Yeah, because also Disney, it being I mean, on one hand, you have Tokyo Disney
Sea, which is the best theme park in the world, supposedly even it is.
I mean, it's amazing. I haven't been to every park.
But then on the other hand, you're going to like an American Disney park
in another country. Yeah.
And even though they're very proud of it, I'm just saying it's not like
I went to see the sights and the culture. Right.
As much. Yeah, it's yeah.
You did fine is what I'm saying.
OK, well, I hope you're going to do some introspection about your
his choices. Yeah.
That's what this podcast is for in general.
He's saying out loud what I've done.
Yeah. And reckoning with it.
And Jason, what have you done?
Oh, very little comparatively.
Oh, OK. I have not been to Japan.
Did you have and you did bring notes.
Did we hit all of your notes, by the way?
Oh, well, that's just because it's a lot of Danish words and stuff.
I think we did pretty good pronunciation wise.
I wouldn't agree with that. Oh, OK.
Maybe I'm just at least maybe I'm not thinking quality.
Maybe I'm just thinking quantity.
Those Danish rappers, I know I did a bad job naming them.
There's no way that was right.
No, I've already forgotten what I said.
But I think you both leapt in with fearlessness.
Oh, like a clumsy Hans.
I'm proud of you both.
Thank you. Wow.
That's rare that a guest says that about.
Oh, you know what?
The main ride, I think, at Tivoli that we haven't talked about,
like the big other than like the mountain
coaster that you can see is the star flyer.
That's like the thing you would picture,
which is the swings that swing around, you know,
and you know what I'm talking about.
I kind of don't.
Yeah, like the big swing ride.
Yeah, big swing ride where, you know, you have a little seats
and you're outside. Oh, swing.
OK, I I was pictured.
No, I was pictured.
I was trying to remember which ride you got ill on.
And I thought it was similar.
But actual swings, actual little one seat.
Yeah, I like those.
It's humongous. It's so tall.
Right. It looks scary to me.
Yeah, I did.
I didn't go on it again due to my lingering motion sickness.
But it looked even if I had been able to,
it might have been too scary, too high.
Because I get very stressed when my legs are dangling.
Yeah. And especially if it feels like you're on
this like a rickety piece of metal hanging from a chain.
Yes. Thank you.
Hanging from like old chains is like dirty, old, dirty, old Tivoli chains.
I mean, Disneyland has one of the California
Adventures got something like that.
And we did it a couple of years ago and I hadn't done it for a while.
And I was like, I'm scared.
Was it scary? Yes. Yeah.
Like I'm flying right out into the water or on the pavement.
This goes like twice as high as anyone's in America.
It is high. Isn't that insane?
I want to ride this right now.
Really? I like to be up high.
I like to be very high.
You want to jump off the stratosphere?
Well, the more.
OK, I do.
You declared that. I'm not lying.
Can your app points get you there?
Oh, no, it's actually a different owner.
It's not an MGM.
OK, all of them.
All the big Caesars has their own app.
MGM has her own.
This is complicated.
The more I've learned about the stratosphere, the more it seems like.
Real Excalibur vibes, like seen better days.
Yeah, you know, yeah.
So you're saying it's not a professional jumping off the hotel.
So I'm a little more trepidations about jumping off.
You know, bungee jumping? No.
But you want to.
I would consider it.
Well, that's the same as isn't it the same?
I know. I'm just saying I just it makes me nervous
learning about the stratosphere.
What element of the stratosphere, though, make you nervous?
Stuff being broken or closed so much.
An Elitch Gardens vibe.
So you're saying like a like a bar closes down on the stratosphere
and that makes you doubt the quality of the safety, safety running.
I think just overall.
So I look into it more.
Yeah, I also.
I would need to get contacts to do it.
This is what he's been saying for years.
I've been saying that this is an excuse for why he hasn't done it for years.
I'm blind as a bat without my glasses.
OK, so I would want to see everything.
Right. Because you have like a panoramic view of the city
and the surrounding area.
You know what it looks like. Come on.
But I want to see what I'm falling towards, too.
I have a new theory.
You don't actually want to do it.
I think this contact thing is a sneaky little excuse
to have a big, big talk.
The contact is not a make or break thing.
Oh, OK. OK. The safety.
I just think I feel like they close the rides a lot or like there's issues.
Like, it just makes me a little more nervous than I was a few years ago.
Would you have done the Tom Cruise end of Olympics stunt
where he kind of like ziplined down from the top of like
whatever arena they were in or stadium stadium?
Yeah, that seemed like pretty casual for him.
Yeah. I'm wondering if he wanted it to be more hardcore.
Well, in what way? He didn't stand on the Hollywood sign.
Like that was cool. Yeah.
Yeah, but that's not as crazy as ziplining from the top of a stadium.
That looked kind of fun. It did look fun.
We did. Would you go on or did you go on?
It probably doesn't exist anymore.
The New Jersey Six Flags, the like what was it called?
The Kunda Ka or whatever.
Kingda Ka is still I haven't gone on it because every time I went there,
it was closed, often broken.
It's kind of a logistically difficult ride.
It would often like shoot up and not make it all the way up.
Which it's it's built in to like slide back.
So, oh, good. I think that means it's working.
Right. Built to not work.
Yeah, it's built to occasionally work.
They should have somebody on the ride all at all times, though,
to like a guy with a little lever.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I we we talked, I think, with Dan Klein about that years ago.
Yeah. And I cannot remember if he successfully got on,
but it wasn't from a lack of trying. Yeah.
But I haven't been there.
I think I was there when it was open and was just down.
It just wasn't running.
So but I would totally do that. Oh, would you?
But it was down.
Very convenient, very convenient.
Very convenient.
He lost his glasses before, too.
So you can see where he was going.
He wanted to see all of that big specific part of New Jersey.
The parking lot in New Jersey.
And then, yeah.
I have the answer for the beanies.
Oh, good.
100 years ago, according to OSU, I forget what, actually,
the, where am I in, the Lantern, which is some sort of college website.
Who cares what it is?
That is probably the college newspaper.
The cap tradition began in 1912 and its looks changed throughout its lifetime at OSU.
But this is what they look like.
And it's going to load.
These are the caps.
That is a beanie.
Yeah, it's a little beanie.
Like what character on Fat Albert wore one of these?
I forget. One of them did.
Yes. I forget which one it is.
I mean, it's literally the thing that would have a propeller, but it just doesn't.
Exactly. Yeah.
And then Foam Booth Stuffing was most prominent in the 1950s.
But it fizzled out by 1959.
So that was the heyday when people would stuff as many people into a Foam Booth as possible.
And sorry, were the hats so you could know who to look down upon and make fun of?
I believe so.
I don't know. I think this is a, this was actually a good thing.
I don't think it was like a, like a dunce cap.
The hats were a good thing?
Like they would say, like, we're proud of you for being here.
We're proud of you for getting it.
Well, you know what?
This says freshmen men were required to wear beanies.
So perhaps if there was a rude upperclassman, they would make fun of the freshmen.
Carry my books. Yeah.
So perhaps, yeah, you could spot like a newbie that way.
OK. But I don't know.
Those don't lie.
Like this, I mean, I guess beanies were happening during Foam Booth Stuffing.
So I wonder why it fell out of favor, Foam Booth Stuffing.
I just the Wikipedia says it fizzled in 1959.
I guess it just fizzled.
I mean, maybe it was like we did an episode on Tunnel of Loves,
which like still occupy such a big place and like TV and movies.
But they fizzled out around the 50s because public displays of affection and car culture
just kind of you didn't have to go to a carnival and sit a dark boat ride to make out.
Now you can be in line at a casino. Right.
For all to see.
They really should have.
The policy was to wear masks at the time.
So I don't know why they were doing that.
They were in love. That's why they were doing it.
They were like Angelina Jolie and Billy Bob Thornton.
You remember how all over they were all over each other?
They were. Oh, who could forget?
OK, real.
The Foam Booth Stuffing was referred to one of the all time great fads
by the Bridgeport Post, and it but it had become regarded as passe
by the end of 1959.
It was akin to the meteoric rise and fall to the earlier fads of flagpole
sitting, goldfish swallowing and panty raids and to the later fad of streaking
while still practiced contemporarily and has not again achieved the social currency
it had in the late 1950s. Wow.
So this really makes it sound like it was a big deal to cram a bunch of people
into a foam booth. And then there was just one day a guy was like,
who wants to get in the foam booth?
And they were like, please.
Yeah, and they laughed at him. Hans.
Yeah. So 1959.
I like this just another example of, like, the flattening of history.
And it's like, yeah, caps were in the 1910s and 20s.
And then flagpole sitting was in the 50s.
Yeah. But in my mind, you flattened history.
Yeah, I flattened it.
And in my mind, it's just like, oh, the past.
Yeah. You must not have had your glasses on when you were
describing those historical goldfish swallowing 40s.
Swallowed goldfish before every episode for good luck.
I feel like shit by the end of every episode, too.
Because the thing is still alive for the first 15 minutes or so.
Oh, no. You're swallowing it alive.
So, yeah, anyway, we'll put up that George Carstensen
photo with Jason and we'll check out the tooth horse and the tooth horse.
Yeah, maybe you pick someone you think looks like the tooth horse
and put up a side by side.
Oh, good. Yeah.
Who has a lot like a big toothy smile? Yeah.
That's a good question.
When you don't like probably. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, we'll think about our enemies and think about who looks like the horse.
Do we have what else? Do we have anything else?
Anything else? Say goodbye from your lovely trip? No.
OK, well, then I'll go ahead and say, Beth, you survived podcast, the ride.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Do you have anything you'd like to plug? Oh, no.
OK. Well, I don't know what I would plug.
You can plug somebody else's thing.
I mean, anything.
A Sex Lives of College Girls is back.
It's back in November.
Yes. Watch season three of The Sex Lives of College Girls.
Watch. I just watched Pop Star Academy, which I thought was a pretty good
reality show.
That's just the thing you like. Yeah, that's right.
But yeah, watch The Sex Lives of College Girls season three in November.
OK, great. Yeah.
And as for us, you'll find us at podcast, the ride or
Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
If you want to do more, if you want to get there's that Elitch Gardens
episode behind the paywall.
If you want to go back and listen to that and all the somewhat depressing antics
that happened that day, I won't elaborate on what happened to Scott.
But we're on all the socials at podcast, the ride.
And yeah, look for the comparison photos soon.
And if you have any video from the piano man from New York,
I would like to see what a Danish Billy Joel show looks like.
So please send it my way.
You know, the email, I assume podcast, the ride at Gmail dot com.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com.
And subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.