Welcome to PodcastsAride, the Second Gate where today you've all been accepted to a
very special academy.
The Second Gate School for Gifted Youngsters, I'm Jason Sheridan, here with me the Sean
Cassidy to my Emma Frost, Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm a headmaster I suppose you would call me?
A head, yeah, headmaster and I'm head administrator.
Are those real titles from the film we watched or are you assuming?
No, they are real titles from the film, I just can't remember who was which.
It's okay, there's probably a few things I can't remember from the film but I will get
to those eventually.
I do want to say of course today's episode is Scott Free, what would you call it?
Our new branding, that's what it is.
Our new branding, yes, the jubilee to our Frost and Cassidy is not here today.
Right and he's, I don't want to speak for him but I will and say that he is thrilled
to not be wallowing in the slop of Marvel Universe films and continuity and characters,
I believe that.
So we are getting away with something today, Scott Free, by talking about the characters
of Generation X.
Yeah, we're talking the 1996 television pilot that became a TV movie, Generation X, starring
a guy from Cold Case, James Vanderbeek's ex-wife and a woman from some soap operas.
Should we say also though, today, the reason we're, not that we couldn't do this any other
day but the reason we're doing this is because this is your birthday shot.
Yes, it's my birthday shot, we're a little late on this Halloween haunt season, butts
up against my October 4th birthday.
But hey, better late than never, you know.
Right, so we are finally honoring you and celebrating your birthday by watching this
made-for-TV movie and talking about it today.
Yes, now this movie, I saw it when it aired in February 1996 and in a way that, you know,
I think I've described this before but like as a kid growing up, like TV special events
like one-off movies or magic specials kind of gave me that little bit of a rush that
theme parks did, like, oh my God, it's a special thing, it doesn't happen that often, this
is so exciting.
I have to schedule the week around, like I have to make sure we, like, homework is done,
dinner is eaten.
Right, so the novelty of a made-for-TV movie or a one-off special, we've talked about,
you know, breaking the magician's code, we've talked about, beyond belief, fact or fiction
was an actual series but this type of even Fox specific genre of alien autopsy specials
or an actual just made-for-TV movie like these Marvel movies that they made in the 90s including
Nick Fury played by David Hasselhoff, that's something Scott would be happy to be on, I
think, talking about that type of a Marvel property or today's topic of Generation X
which was sort of an X-Men offshoot property.
So you were saying that this is something you would get just as hyped for as going to
Islands of Adventure.
Yeah, a little bit, closer to methadone than the heroine that is Islands of Adventure but
like...
Well, yeah, fair enough, fair enough, the drug wasn't as strong with these movies.
Not as strong and this especially was very exciting because the Generation X comic came
out in 1994 and it sort of like, kind of, after like Jim Lee left the X-Men, we're going
to get very granular here, it sort of made a big impact, I think, not just because of
the hologram foil cover that was very common in the 90s but it was like, it looked different
from everything else, it was a bunch of new characters and what we've talked about before,
it's kids at a boarding school, it's teenager next generation of X-Men and they live at
the school and there is like a biodome that is their danger room and that's very exciting
and my dear friend Jubilee was kind of leading the charge so it was just, it hit at just
the right time that comic and then this movie hit even more so.
So it's 1994, this comic book Generation X comes out and as you were saying, it's a mix
of old characters and new characters, Banshee and the White Queen are sort of the leaders
of it, they have been in other X-Men comics before, Jubilee, of course, has been on the
X-Men but now she's in a whole new crop of teenage heroes and they're trying to do like
teen X-Men now, it's not your father's X-Men, these are the new kids, it's sort of probably
in the same vein as Beverly Hills 90210, there's a 90s wave of teen stuff and I almost feel
like this is kind of in the wake of all of it happening and if, I mean, how old are you
at 94? How old am I, 10? You're what, 9?
Nine, yeah, so then like 11 in 96? I went back and read the first Generation X issue
in the Marvel Unlimited app the other day and it is, there's a few things going on to
compare and contrast it with this movie. One, the first issue of the comic is setting up
a lot of threads to pay off in this series and two, it kind of, like I said, it doesn't,
the artist is Chris Bockelo who would go on to draw X-Men and Spider-Man, draw a lot
of stuff but the inker is this guy Mark Buckingham and Mark Buckingham and Chris Bockelo were
just doing a ton of work on Vertigo in the 90s, especially early mid 90s and so this
book really didn't look like a lot of the other X-Men comics of the time, the sort
of like hulking, you know, lots of muscles, lots of pouches. It looked a little weirder
and that was very exciting to me.
Okay, now let me give you a counter, not that you're wrong, you are right about all the
things you just said. For me, it looked a little too weird and it was something a little
bit too much. I don't think, I was so totally on board with the teens, I think the teens
kind of scared me and I was like, well where are my favorites? Where's Gambit? Where's
Iceman? Where's Rogue? Where's Beast? They're not here? I don't know, maybe this comic is
not for me. So I stayed away from the comic book of Generation X. I didn't dislike it
but I think that the weirder art and the teens specifically were a little off-putting because
again, you're nine, I'm ten. It's not like we were teens yet. We were not teens.
No, but I think at that point I had already had the logic problem of like, all the X-Men
seem like they're in their 20s or 30s. Why are they living at a school? So this kind
of solved that of like, oh these are teenagers at a school.
It makes sense and the things would go on different comic book runs when I got a little
older and more comfortable with teens. That would happen where I would say, okay great,
Grant Morrison introduced a bunch of young X-Men in his new X-Men run. Great, I'm comfortable
with these teens. I'm comfortable with, maybe even some of them are not even teens. Like
Quentin Quire, even though he's a bad guy, comfortable with him. Beak, the X-Man Beak,
who just kind of has a beak and he has like wings and stuff, very comfortable with him.
You go on another Chris Boccolo, Jason Aaron run, Wolverine and the X-Men, which is almost
like a Magic School Bus meets X-Men run, which I love. That's got a bunch of teens. I'm good
with this concept. I think you're right on. I just think I wasn't ready for these new
teens.
Well, I will say I liked it. I think I was a little nervous about the teens and the weird
art style. They scared me, the teens. They scared me and the villain empath, who was
kind of horrific, scared me as well. Yes, scared me too. He was a scary guy. That was
probably why after that first issue, I didn't really read Generation X monthly. I just picked
it up here and there, but I was very happy it was going on. I was also intrigued by like,
oh, Banshee and White Queen, a good guy and a bad guy are the headmasters. Now, it wasn't
until later I learned about Emma Frost's first class of children, the Hellions, which are
oddly enough mentioned in this movie of all the things to keep from the comic.
There are references in this movie. I like the idea of Generation X. It kind of was a
short-lived thing. They haven't brought it back for a long time as far as the title of
the book. Characters have appeared in other things, but that feels so 90s to me. Then
the fact that they very quickly turned around a movie of it was shocking to me at the time
because we were in the desert back then. We weren't living the life now where we get a
Marvel thing every few weeks. Oh yeah, and we're like, ugh, do I have to do this? It's
almost a hassle to try and keep up with it. Of course, some of it's homework. Some of it's
homework. If somebody's asking you, what is all this Deadpool Wolverine continuity? I don't
understand it. You're like, well, there's six things you've got to watch to fully understand
what the TVA is and to understand all the different references. But yes, back then I was
like, oh my God. So I was excited about Generation X on Fox. I love the Fox network. Big fan of Fox
network. It was a little naughty. It was a little naughty. I didn't care for that as much, but we
talked about the specials. We talked about the sort of tone of Fox, mostly because of the Simpsons,
but other stuff too. So I was excited that Fox was dipping their toe in the X-Men universe
and was excited. I think I watched this live. I think I was that excited about it.
Yeah. Now I watched on YouTube. There's a few rips of it on YouTube and I unfortunately,
not until an hour ago, did I find the rip of the live broadcast with the commercials
and live correspondence from Mardi Gras. Fox's Mardi Gras was happening at the same time this
aired, including, I don't know, did you see the first chunk of it? I kind of jumped around,
but I think I know what you're going to reference. So there's different hosts and there's a guy I
recognize. I'm not sure who he is. He was on TV at one point. And then Jimmy Kimmel is there all of
a sudden. Yeah. And then it cuts even more excitingly from Jimmy Kimmel to the House of Blues,
to Jim Belushi in full Blues Brothers outfit. And he is also one of the hosts of Fox's Mardi Gras.
And I just, I fell out of my chair. I was so excited. House of Blues and Jim Belushi
introducing Generation X. I don't remember that happening at the time. That being said,
I don't think as a 10 year old, or excuse me, a 12 year old, I was that excited about Jim Belushi.
No, I don't think so. One thing is certain. This celebration and this made for TV movie
are brought to you by 1-800-COLLECT. Well, that's 1-800-COLLECT logo is everywhere. Let me,
Mike, I'm going to share the screen just to show you a picture and I'll post this online.
This was another thing about this movie that really lived in my mind. And that's this print ad
with all of the teens and Banshee and the White Queen, like they are all giving some attitude.
Yeah. And I just thought this was the coolest thing. This was obviously in a lot of comics
and magazines at the time. It doesn't even look like an ad for a movie or a show. It looks like
it's a nineties print ad for like a clothing store. It looks like.
Yeah. But they are all dressed wildly differently. So I guess it would be
a department store where you can buy all items. This isn't a regular Sears. This would be like,
say Sears started like Sears started trying to do like a store called Sears Extreme or something in
1996. It's like, this is Sears, but it's a little different than a normal Sears. Like the clothing,
a little bit sexier, a little more of the belly will show when you wear a shirt.
Nowadays, if they did like, oh, we're doing an alternate version,
but kind of nodding to our past, the store would probably be called Robox.
Oh, I see. Oh, we're brainstorming like different Sears. Yes. Because like McDonald's has that.
First of all, have we even talked that much about the McDonald's like test stores the,
and what are they called? They're called like, you know what I'm talking about?
The, the like caught the place competing with Panera and Starbucks. Oh, it's Cosmix.
Cosmix. Yeah. So there's like these just specific, like you can get like a little flatbread
sandwich or something, but it's a lot of different drinks. It's almost like Sonic,
where you can have all these different options as far as if you want like boba in there,
if you want different flavors added to your sodas. So like they're testing that out.
So you're saying a Sears kind of like alternative cooler brand would be called Robox because that's
an old school thing. Yeah. Cause it was originally called Sears and Robox. Sears and Robox. I think
it was singular. Don't quote me. Don't these Robox heads come after me? Not Daniel Robox heads,
original Sears and Robox heads. We're getting into Barnes and Nobles territory.
No, it's not that. There's no S on the end of that.
No, that's Barnes and Noble for sure. Yeah. Anyway, Cosmix. We haven't really talked about it
on this show a lot. Again, Scott Free. We're getting away Scott Free talking about the fact
that McDonald's is testing out this store where you just drive through and you can get like
different little like juices in your drinks or little flavor shots in your drinks and they have
different kinds of drinks, different kinds of sugar drinks. And I want Cosmix here so bad.
Why won't they do that? I know they always test it out in the Midwest and maybe I think, maybe I
should have never moved away. Maybe I should not have come to California because I've talked about
this before. Woodfield Mall, they would test out McDonald's pizza. They would test out McDonald's
hot dogs. And that was cool. That was cool as shit to walk into McDonald's and Woodfield, Woodfield
Mall in Schaumburg, Illinois. And all of a sudden they have a new type of food they sell there.
Yeah. It seems very exciting. Like when I ordered pasta, I ordered a big bowl of pasta at the
McDonald's in Orlando. And a cheesesteak. And a fucking cheesesteak. And I was elated. It was
2 a.m. It was after our live show and I took it back to the hotel room and I ate every piece of
both things and passed out for two hours and then got up and went to Tron.
Yeah. My Lyft driver on the way to the show was like, hey, the biggest McDonald's in the
world is over there. And I went, oh. So we drove by so fast. I didn't really see anything. But
yeah, I don't know that we talked about Cosmix a lot on the show. Talked about it a lot in our
text messages. In our private life, yes. In our private life, we've considered it a lot.
So Sears, yeah. Sears should have tried Sears Xtreme in the 90s. A sexier version of Sears.
They could have had Bob Vila, but Bob Vila would wear little shorts instead of his normal jeans.
That's good. Yeah. Some fluorescent clothes. Some black light stuff.
Hunky Bob Vila. A younger, hunkier Bob Vila. I don't know if he has a son. If Bob Vila has a hot
son, I'm not sure. But you could have gotten somebody like that. You could even get an actor
to play hot young Bob Vila. And he's wearing a weird vest like the Generation X cast.
There are a good amount. There are a number of vests.
Oh yeah. It was a very vest-centric decade. So yeah. So this ad you're showing,
it doesn't officially look like something you actually can watch on TV.
Yeah. Everyone is dressed differently. Almost to a point, it was different. Jubilee's kind of a
skater. Monet is kind of the cool girl. She's got a green leather jacket with a bra underneath.
Skin is kind of the nerd. Refrax is kind of a, I don't know, kind of a bleach blonde jock.
Yeah. Skin. So yeah, these characters, Skin, Refrax, Mondo, Jubilee.
Yeah. And Buff.
And Buff. Buff is what young Bob Vila would have been.
All right. We could only hope. Buff, this is a very important distinction. Because I,
as I started to read about this, I was like, I think there were characters in this that were
only for the movie. And I bet it's because of the budget. And sure enough,
that's what the fandom entry also said. Because Refrax and Buff have very manageable powers for
a $4 million made for TV budget. Yes. Because so much of the discourse around movies with
comic book stuff in them at the time was like too expensive. We cannot do an X-Men movie.
There are seven or eight characters and each one of their powers is so expensive,
there would be no way to get this in the budget. Superman, okay, he can fly. He's one guy. Fine.
Batman doesn't even have powers. And then it was like, you're not getting good superhero movies
because the budget doesn't allow it. Yes. And Refrax and Buff especially were stand-ins for the
comic book characters Chamber and Husk. Yes. Chamber is a proper British teenager
who's like from his nose to his chest is just a giant ball of energy.
Chamber scared me. And this is what we're getting at today about Generation X is that I saw Chamber
and I was afraid of him. I was afraid of both of these characters, to be honest with you,
but I was afraid of Chamber. Yeah, both kind of, this phrase gets thrown around a lot,
but like body horror, like Chamber has a big ball of energy. He's almost like a human torch.
He's almost on fire the whole time, but it's only a little part of him. And to me, that makes it
seem scarier than if you were just head to toe flames. Head to toe flames doesn't scare me like
Johnny Storm and the Fantastic Four, but for some reason a little chunk cut out of energy or flames
does scare me. Because he usually has like a turtle neck, kind of like leather collar pulled
up to his nose and he communicates telepathically. And then Husk, who is the younger sister of
Cannonball, Husk's power is she pulls off her skin to reveal either new skin or like
power, like solid metal or fire under, like she just keeps pulling off her skin as needed.
She can rip her face off like the movie Face Off and then there'll be a different type of skin
underneath. And it is unclear to me how, so she can decide what the next layer of skin is going
to be when she rips off her exterior layer? I think different writers have gone different
directions because in the first issue of Generation X, she is very, she's portrayed as very type A.
So she's going for like a 6 a.m. run through the woods and then Jubilees like why are you up so
early? Specifically like you woke me up playing your Bridget Fonda work or your Jane Fonda workout,
not Bridget Fonda. That would be very funny. I don't think Bridget Fonda.
She didn't go into the family business of having a workout tape?
Peter Fonda's workout tape, it's just a lot of like the Family Guy style, like hut, hut, hut, like.
Oh, how about Henry Fonda's workout tape? Now we're talking, or were you thinking,
you were thinking Henry and you said Peter, Peter's Jane's brother.
Henry is Jane's father who's in on Golden Pond. I'm just terrible with names nowadays,
which I was always bad with names, but it's frustrating mixing up.
Well, I just, there was a guy I've gone to wrestling shows with that I looked straight
in the eye and didn't recognize him a couple of days ago. So I'm not like, I'm doing very good.
Yeah. I apologize to Kyle is what I'm saying.
Those wrestling shows are very high. You get, you know, you kind of.
You get so excited you forget the face of a person that's sitting next to you. Yeah.
Yeah. This is all to say that in the first issue of Generation X,
husk goes for an early morning jog and then she tries a trick with her powers where she pulls
off her skin and goes, Oh, well, that worked. It was like taking a hot shower. It pulled off the
sweat and grime. And I'm like, that's pretty clever. I, that's an interesting use of that power.
It seems like a lot of effort though. Instead of just taking a quick shot. I mean, I guess,
I guess the skin could be potentially damaged. Like we do shed our skin as humans, but it takes
a lot longer. So I would think it would make more sense if you were like, it would almost be like
getting an immediate facial, like the skin below this, the other skin would be so like new and
taut and fresh that you would look regenerated. I mean, I'm sure there's been something in one
of the comics where she did that. All right. Maybe I'm wrong, but that's where I would think,
because I guess getting like getting your skin sweaty, I don't think hurts it.
I guess if it's dirty, but I don't know. I'm saying she's experimenting. I understand. She's
experimenting. Yeah. The book and the comic do, they do both go in on the like, you're here to
learn how to harness and experiment with your powers. So that is copacetic with both. I would
like a mutant power that would like sort of secondarily help me appear more youthful as I
age. That would, that would rule. I would be, and I would try to use like, if I had Iceman's power,
I would try to kind of like freeze my face, like Botox style before I went out or something, or
not before. I wouldn't freeze it like it's so I couldn't move, but you'd kind of do a little
something to sort of keep it like taut before going out. Like I would try to, whatever power
I was granted by the universe, I would try to figure out some sort of anti-aging element to it.
Oh yeah. That's fun. It is fun. I don't know if they would all apply. Obviously Wolverine has
healing power, so he just kind of stays younger, youthful looking longer because he's been alive
so long. And Wolverine in the, that early 2010s, Wolverine and the X-Men comic, he is the head
master of a new class, a new Xavier's school. Yes, it's a great, it's a great like comedy
setup of like Wolverine's in charge of this school and wacky stuff's happening and the school is on
top of a living island and they get into all sorts of mischief and it's fun. How, what do you think
minute wise Scott would have said, can we talk about the movie itself yet? Probably about 10
minutes ago. Yeah, I think so. I'm not saying, by the way, I'm not saying we have to get to the
movie. We don't have to get to the movie at all. Hey, we don't have to get to the movie at all.
I'm enjoying a kombucha, health aid kombucha, pink lady apple flavor right here in a can.
So I'm fine. This is your birthday. I'm along for the ride. That's true. I did make a lot of notes
on that. I was surprised that like this was actually pretty well documented. So I will,
it's not a hundred years old or anything. No, no, I just wasn't sure how forgotten it was, but.
Can we start with a question about the movie? We can go into the movie. We can talk about the
movie real quick. We can talk about the movie real long. Do you like this movie? Can I ask that
first? Did you like watching this now in the year 2024? I just want that's my question before we
even start. I have to say, and I have the trailer queued up, so we'll we'll do that next. Sure,
sure. Yeah, because it's a pretty pretty solid captures everything about it in 25, 30 seconds.
I did like it as an adult. I definitely clocked some weird stuff with this movie.
Well, sure. Yeah, really what I'm driving at, because if you were going to give it a
general positive review before this, do you still think that Country Bears movie is that bad?
I am not ready. You're already more positive about this Generation X movie than that Country Bears
movie. Well, now this Generation X movie, I positive childhood memories of the Country Bears
movie. I really only remember trailers of when I was in high school and I was like,
oh, I don't want to see that. That doesn't seem like the Bears at all. Yeah, because in case you
didn't guess, I kind of found this movie boring. It's a little boring, boring and cheap, boring and
90s cheap and not not there's not even as many treats as I would want, whether it be like weird
stuff or a strange performance. I mean, we talk about Matt Fruer, who is great, who I like a lot.
Remember, I have other Fruer thoughts that I want to share, but I was watching this and I at the
time, I didn't love it. I didn't run out the next day and say everybody, oh my gosh, Generation X
was awesome. Maybe I did. Maybe I'm misremembering. I had a weird feeling about it because I was like,
isn't that quite what I want? I was still hopeful that it would become a TV series because I,
look, I was so savvy back then. I knew the biz. I knew that like, you know,
if we get one comic book show on the year, then we get a second one. I knew how that stuff worked.
I was reading Entertainment Weekly, you know, you were too. You knew the biz. So I was not against
it or anything, but I was watching this and going, gosh, the budget. It looks like they gave them no
money to do this. Like for instance, I just watched the pilot of TJ Hooker a few weeks ago.
Okay. And I was like, man, is that watchable? That's not a good show. Okay. There's a few
interesting things in it actually, but man, just Shatner's performance, giving monologues to like
no one in a bar, like just looking off into the distance, monologuing into no one. We're watching
this and we're like, man, maybe TJ Hooker is good. So then compared to this where I'm just like,
okay, this is 90 minutes. So all that to say, I think you owe Country Bears another watch.
Now, I don't think you should watch it with the idea that I really want to like this. I need you
to watch it. And if you come back and you say, I still hate Country Bears, Generation X is a better
movie. That's fine. We talk about it then. Don't do anything to please me. You don't have to please
me. I'm just always interested in when we talk about enjoyment of movies. I always like to rank
it against Country Bears because that was such a contentious episode of Podcast The Ride.
Well, I'll say this. This and Country Bears both share something in common that drove me nuts as a
kid, which was deviating too much from the source material. Yes, sure. Because there's stuff in the
source material that I wanted to see. Like in this, I thought the portrayal of Jubilee was pretty
solid. She's like a teenager. She's a lit, very mouthy. I don't think you get enough of her
powers. She only really uses her powers like probably less than five times. Those are expensive
powers. But they're, they're kind of not. They're, they're kind of just sparks. It depends how you
do them, I guess. It depends on how you do them. The last shot when she's fighting Matt Fruer,
that seems like the expensive Jubilee power use. Yeah. And Jubilee, if you didn't know, sort of has
like, she shoots fireworks out of her hands, basically. She kind of has, I don't know,
I guess they're like, they do hurt if she wants them to. I think she can control how strong they
are. She could just make fireworks appear as if it was a fun party, but I think she also could
hit you with fireworks and that would hurt. Yeah. They're kind of, as a kid, I loved energy blast
powers like Cyclops or Havoc or Jubilee or Bishop. If you could shoot powers out of a part of your
body. Yeah, I love that. Hand, eyes, head, chest. But they're, again, granular. Like each one is
kind of different. Like Cyclops optic glass are concussive. Right. Which means that it's like
getting hit by a bus. It's not like Superman's x-ray vision, which can melt stuff. And this is
so granular. This is so like, and it is very funny to see writers using powers in different
ways. It's kind of one of the fun things. Like in the current like X-Men, they're setting up like
Jubilee kind of, if her power's kind of evolving, like her kind of mastering them down to like a
very certain level, like in the Gale Simone run, which very weird time for X-Men comics.
They've recently relaunched after five years where all the mutants live on a magical island.
And now they're just back to like, they're hunted and feared, even though they saved the whole world.
It's a little bit, it's a soft reboot. It's a reset. It's a soft reboot. It happens all the
time though. Which seems like it was rumored. It was a Kevin Feige request because there's going
to be an X-Men movie in the next 10 years, maybe. Um, I think five within five, five. Okay. I think,
I'm guessing. Let me play the trailer for this generation X movie. I will rewatch country bears
and give it another chance. I've been meaning to do that for the longest time.
Tonight, Fox presents a world premiere motion picture from the creators of the hit comic book
series. The X-Men comes generation X. They've got the power. They've got the technology.
There's a new generation of superheroes and they're coming
to save the world. Get ready for generation X on the Fox Tuesday night movie.
Wow. Wow. That was very exciting. It was very exciting. I mean, there's, there are powers
showcased in that trailer, stretching powers, some energy powers. So like just the idea,
just the idea that like the legitimate entertainment business would acknowledge comics
because I mean, at the time it was just like, oh, I, me and one other kid I know in college,
in high school or in elementary school, read these comics. So we felt very much like a very small
club. Obviously you go to comic conventions, you'd see a lot of other people, but it was like,
almost like you were being like, yes, what you like is cool enough to be on the big stage. Now,
do I kind of wish some of the stuff I liked was back on the small stage? Sometimes I do, not
always, not always, but sometimes you're like, ah, I missed the good old days when everything was
sort of not all of, when all of entertainment wasn't a stuff I liked when I was eight,
which is shocking, which is shocking because I would have never guessed that. But when you're
like, oh yeah, maybe a couple non things I liked when I was eight would be good. Yeah. Now it's
everything. I mean, it, you know, you lose the hunt. The hunt used to be part of the fun,
you know? Sure. Yeah. Hunting stuff down, going to obviously I still go to comic shops plenty.
But yeah, I remember being in second grade, getting really into the X-Men cartoon.
And then later that's like when the baseball season started talking to one of my friends
at like a little league game and he's like, oh yeah, there's all these X-Men comics and
trading cards. You should go to a comic book store and check it out. And somehow my parent,
I like, I either talked to my parents or they, their parents talked to mine and like right
after the game, we went to a comic book store and I bought like X-Men 21 or 22,
which is like a very confusing, it's like the middle of a story arc about how
Psylocke traded bodies with Revanche, who's a ninja. And it wasn't until much later. I was like,
wait, why? So that British lady became an Asian lady? That's odd.
Yes, that is a storyline in X-Men.
And eventually they retconned, they switched that and dealt with the fallout from that in the last
few years. But at the time I was very thrilled and I went all in on X-Men and Marvel trading cards,
went all in on the comics for like eight years or so. I had an X-Men subscription
where it would be sent to me. And I always had one or two friends who were in this.
And as we all got older, they started dropping off and I was like, nope, still good on comics,
still doing this. And then- This is a story of my life.
Yeah, it made new friends, it got me into other comics and expanded.
All these guys watching wrestling in their high school years and going to pay-per-views,
and then all of a sudden things fall off and they're no longer watching week to week.
And I'm still there, baby. I'm still watching. I'm the last man standing when it comes to
liking stuff. And this has happened throughout my entire life. And it's what you're describing now.
And I'm not annoyed by it because I enjoy it, but I just feel like no one has the stamina.
No one has the stamina, brother, when it comes to liking stuff longer than me. That's what I'm
saying. That's fair. That's fair. You've fallen off with comics though, a little bit. Okay, wait,
hold on. Wait, hold on. I have- Now turning it around on you where I'm the stamina boy.
I have a Ninja Turtle comic here. This is the first. All right. This is a special.
I have a bunch of things. I have X-Men 700 sitting here that is a recent comic. I'm not
fully caught up, but I'm just saying that- You're not fully caught up in all fairness. And I am
only up to January 2023 on the Krakoa era of X-Men comics.
All right, there you go. And I look, I'm a father, okay? I am a father who has responsibilities.
We both have other things, yes. As you said, next to three bookshelves of action figures,
your other responsibilities. I'm up on those. I'm up on those. You are up on those. I'm all caught
up. I got all the NECA Turtles. I got the Wrestling Turtles up here. I'm all caught up. So yeah,
so what you're describing is correct because I would also, my whole life I've had the energy of,
hey, come on guys, isn't this exciting? And it just, that's been my life with a lot of things
with stuff that I've liked. And I'm always trying to rally everyone to sort of get on board.
Sure. Yeah, I had fallen off of the AEW a few months ago and then I got back on board and it's
like, wait, every time I watch this, it's good. But when I read about it on the internet, people
are insane. Well, that's a whole, that's a whole nother story. That's a whole like,
I, I, everything. That's a whole nother Scott Free episode. Social media is just
more and more removed from objective reality. I could do specific episodes on everything that
I'm a fan of. I know, I wallow in the dark side secretly on social media. Sure. Yeah. So I know
I know the bad insane discourse for Marvel stuff. I know it for Star Wars stuff. I know it for
wrestling. And it is a fascinating thing. Some people are truly just bad faith instigators.
They're trying to irritate everyone and get clicks. Some people I think are just sort of,
they don't have a context for things. Maybe they're young people and they haven't been
watching a reading or knowing. They don't know a lot about this. They just know one thing. They
know how WWE does things. They know that they like X-Men one way. They don't have a, a vast
knowledge of it. So maybe they're not so informed. I'm giving those people the benefit of that out.
Then you have just like, uh, uh, hateful people, vile, angry people with bad opinions. Uh, and it's
interesting. And I, I wish I didn't pick up the rock to look at all the ants, but that is another
thing that I unfortunately do. You mentioned Matt Frewer. Yes. Uh, let's, let's get into this.
Cause I have a Matt Frewer moment queued up. Please play it first. Play it first. I'll play
it first and we'll talk. Matt Frewer was Max and hopefully one day again is Max Headroom,
which is a character. Did you say something? No, I did not real. I didn't know that.
Oh, well then we, whoa. When I, we were talking before we started recording that we,
but then I had some Frewer stuff now. Okay. Now you know what I'm talking about.
I had Max Headroom queued. I don't really know a lot. I've just seen little clips about that.
This is so PTR coded as people say now online when they see things. And,
and I don't know a ton about Max Headroom either. I know if in case the listener, uh, wasn't, uh,
isn't a hundred years old, like we are, uh, Max Headroom was in the eighties primarily and was,
uh, a character that was like inside the computer almost and looked like those like Duracell family
like characters in a way. So they would basically like in a space ghost coast to coast moment,
like on Letterman, Matt Frewer as Max Headroom would be in the TV. The resolution on the TV
looks kind of poor. It looks glitchy and he would have this full like prosthetic outfit on that
made him look like he was a digital character, like from, I don't know, the eighties was a reboot
style. That's, I guess that's nineties, but like a polygon character. Have you seen Videodrome?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That, that kind of like, uh, haunted TV stage, like interrupting, like we,
like weird, like the characters from the Money for Nothing Dire Straits video. Sure. So, uh,
look it up. You'll understand. It's my birthday shot. So I'm going to call a birth, another shot,
Max Headroom episode coming soon. Yeah, of course. Absolutely. Yeah, yeah. 100%.
Let me share an early. Yeah, go for it. Go for it. Frewer's seat and then we can talk more.
He also reminds me of like Mac Tonight almost. Like there's just this like eighties,
nineties sort of aesthetic of characters. Yeah. Very Mac Tonight coded. Okay.
What are they? Brain waves, Bobby Bird, nothing you'd understand.
Try me. Sorry. It's the next phase in free market mind control. It has to do with the
machine I've been working on. That dream device? No, Bobby Boy, not that dream device. Like I'm some
maladjusted computer nerd who makes some machines so stressed out yuppies can catch some decent
alpha waves. I'm sorry, Russell. Please go on. It's okay, Bob. I completely understand.
I'll start from the beginning. Okay. Okay. So I assume what you're going to say.
I was going to say it's very quirky. It's very quirky and it's very Jim Carrey Riddler.
As soon as I saw this and I haven't watched this in a while, I went,
geez, this is crazy. Did Matt Fruer steal his whole delivery and this character
off of Jim Carrey? Cause like it's a year after Batman Forever. Also, I will say plot wise,
character wise, this is like an evil scientist with a dream machine that steals things from
people's minds, which is what Edward Nigma does in Batman Forever. Jim Carrey is the Riddler.
But then I started going down a rabbit hole online and there are many people that do believe
that Jim Carrey took a lot of his personas from Max Headroom. I'm not saying this definitively,
but you look at Max Headroom, he's on Letterman in the 80s and he has very similar delivery to
this. A lot of specific kind of quirks that Jim Carrey would have and it's hard not to draw
that conclusion. Now Jim Carrey does appear, so I was trying to figure out, okay, when is Jim Carrey
on TV? Jim Carrey is on TV in 1983 on The Tonight Show and it is not like, I will say this, the set
isn't great. He does like some impressions, but he does a lot of like, he takes like 90 seconds to
contort his body to become the impression. It's not my favorite piece of Jim Carrey comedy,
I'll say that. But he wasn't totally a different guy, different performer. It's not like Andrew
Dice Clay when he was doing his other characters before he became Dice. So it's not like it's
totally different, but it doesn't have some of the like kind of specific Jim Carrey stuff you would
see on In Living Color. So there are people online that do believe that Jim Carrey took a lot of his
juice from Max Headroom specifically, from Matt Fruer. Now they're both Canadian, they both do have
just normal like, normal like Canadian voices, because if you're seeing Fruer, now this is,
by the way, in case you couldn't tell, I got so sidetracked from watching this movie
going down this. I was like, yeah, yeah, Generation X, but I need to figure out the situation here,
because I love stuff like this. I like from The Lucy Show, I like hearing that Gail Gordon may
have stolen his whole thing from Frank Nelson, that guy who goes, yes, because he has very similar
voice, very similar delivery. So I got really derailed from watching this movie by looking at
this. And it's interesting, because yes, they have, as I was saying, they have similar voices,
but there are so many little quirky things. And you can hear it in that Generation X clip,
which is why immediately you think, oh, he's just doing an impression of Jim Carrey.
There's so many other things that are so spot on Jim Carrey. And even so, even so much so,
that Matt Fruer does the voice of Lloyd in the Dumb and Dumber cartoon. Oh, boy. See, I didn't
know any of this. So I mean, I was like, I acknowledge that I connected through Jim Carrey,
like I was kind of doing a quirky guy kind of thing. It was the 90s, man. Doing Jim Carrey,
channeling Jim Carrey was what you had to do. I mean, some might say that the guy who plays
Deadpool is still doing it. He's still channeling him. Initially, when I started watching this,
I was just like, oh, yeah, Jim Carrey was was hot at the time. And people wanted a Jim Carrey type
performance. But no, there's a chance at the very least Max Headroom influenced Jim.
I think at the very least, that's that whether you want to accuse Jim of outright stealing
the whole thing for his whole thing. I don't know. I'm not there yet. I would love to do
more of a deep dive and then declare something like that. I think Max Headroom was very influential
for a lot of things and performances. So, OK, we'll put a pin in that and revisit it in the
future. Some of the other actors, I mean, the one thing I was very curious about going back
and looking at was, were these actors and other stuff? And by and large, the answer is yes.
Uh, Jeremy Ratchford, who played Sean Cassidy, Banshee, one of the headmasters,
he started Cold Case for a number of years, like 100 plus episodes of Cold Case. So,
Finola Hughes, I don't think I've ever seen that name before, Finola.
Finola. Isn't that one of Shrek's children?
Oh, maybe it's one of Shrek's children. No, that's Fargo, Furkus, and Felicia, sorry.
Felicia, OK. She was on Charmed for a bunch of episodes. She was on General Hospital.
General Hospital, one at Daytime Emmy for General Hospital.
She was on All My Children, too, I believe. Yeah, she was on a couple of soap operas.
Heather McComb, who plays Jubilee, she went on to be in The Profiler, if you remember The Profiler.
I don't really remember The Profiler. She was on Party of Five as well,
which was another Big Fox hit. And I guess Matt Fruer was a big get for Dr. Russell Tresh,
a normal last name that lots of people have. Russell Tresh is the evil character, the Matt
Fruer character. I think Fruer is the only one who, I'm not saying any, everyone else is,
I'm sure, very talented. Fruer is the only one who pops in my mind. Obviously, he gets to do a big,
fun villain, but that's the only performance that I was like, what is this?
He's kind of giving 110 percent. I think Jeremy Ratchford's Sean Cassidy and Heather McComb's
Jubilee are pretty faithful to the comics. The Emma Frost gets a lot of it, right?
Sure.
But isn't the most... Talking about powers, this movie does a thing that I feel like,
or a lot of superhero stuff used to do when the budget was smaller,
where they try too hard to solve logic and budget problems and create much more complicated logic
problems.
Sure.
Because in this world, mutants all have latent telepathic abilities,
but similarly to the way they don't want to just make refract cyclops, even though he kind of has
laser eyes and wears glasses to block the laser eyes, they don't want to just call the astral
plane that telepaths can access. There's a lot of convoluted stuff about dreams and planting ideas
and dreams. Oh, this is well before Inception, but they kind of go out of their way to establish
another dimension that is mostly, like I said, colored lighting and blackout curtains and
walkways. They also, there is a room full of computers, large computers, and they go...
This looks like the set of a porno when there's always computers.
Silk stockings on USA I felt like had a better budget than some of them. There were USA late
night shows or late night hour longs. Baywatch Nights, I'm sure, had bigger budget for some of
this, but this is the zone of set quality you're getting in a lot of these scenes.
They were specifically like, this is a room full of computers and it's Cerebro,
and it's how we find mutants. Then there is also some dream machines that kind of look like a
cheaper version of Cerebro, but they're different. It's not the same.
Yes. Then they need to do some sort of high tech scan on Jubilee when she gets to this
room you're talking about. They basically put her in what looks like the eye exam you do with the DMV.
You just a little bit of like, she puts her head on it and I'm like,
this isn't the sophisticated equipment of a highly evolved mutant school.
This is just like, oh, what do we have here? Okay. Well, we can go down to the DMV and check
their dumpster. Let's talk about this scene because it's a thing that happens a couple
times in this movie that as an adult, I was like, oh, that's weird. Which is,
they say we need a full body scan, take off your clothes. You know, it's that famous comic scene
where Jubilee takes off her top in front of Emma Frost. This is where I almost
went, am I accidentally watching the porno version of this?
It does. Because that's just a porno setup where you're like, the teacher at the school
is going to stand. It's not even like they go, oh, here, go into this little booth
and here's the like undressing area with your modesty curtain or something and then go do that
and she's even still a little weirded out, which would still be kind of a weird or would be a weird
scene. But Emma Frost stands with her and makes her do it and you're like, this is, I don't know
of a movie that has a more porno setup than this. This is just the start of a porno.
And as Jubilee's mother said a few scenes earlier, Emma Frost looks like a stripper
with all the latex and leather she's wearing. She just dresses very flashy. I think she's actually,
some of the comic depictions of Emma Frost, she shows more skin. So she was actually fairly
modestly dressed, but she does still have like silver boots and stuff. So, but yes, this also,
I was like, huh? But at 11, I was like, oh my God, it's a teenager's back. And I'm like,
well, yes, that made me uncomfortable. Yeah. I was kind of uncomfortable, but I was kind of like,
ooh, Fox, this is naughty. When you were 11? Yeah. I was like, oh my, I was scandalized too.
You were tugging at your collar. I probably ran and hit under a blanket probably.
But, and look, this actress, Heather McComb, married to James Vanderbeek for six years in
the 2000s. So she's probably like 1920 when they're making this movie. They'd already
established that Jubilee was 15. That's insane. And that's not the end of a teenager's back,
although it's much weirder later in the movie. So they've established in the movie that the
character Buff. Buff is a character on the country bears, that name. That's right. Yeah.
Yeah. Go ahead. Sorry. Jubilee's like, oh, I'll come get changed with you. Like they were going
to get changed from bed. And she's like, no, I prefer to get changed alone. And Monet, the
character who's super strong and invincible and knows everything says like, oh, she doesn't let
anyone get changed with her because of her horrible body, which is insane. That was insane
to hear about as an adult. And then at some point they go to town, they go into town and they're at
a cool thrift store and Jubilee walks in on Buff changing. And in my mind, my memory from childhood
was they put some sort of prosthetic or hunchback on Buff. The reality is that there is a cheap
insert shot of a normal muscular person. And then the actress turns around and goes, doesn't anyone
knock? But doesn't cheat enough. So you can kind of see her normal back in the mirror. But don't
worry about it. But I, I swore there was like an insert shot of like, oh, this mutated, super
strong back. Again, no, it's just a normal muscular back. One of the, if I forget which character
like says something like nice beaver to another, like a lot of this stuff, you go, oh God. Now the
Emma Frost thing with the shirt off, that's just like abuse. That's just straight up. That's not
something, that's not something that the group guy character would do. No, you all should leave the room
because it also keeps cutting to skin, Angelo. And he keeps like, oh yeah. Like he kind of gives like a
whoa sort of nod. Yeah. Only teenagers should be allowed to write scripts where teenagers are body
or say insulting things to each other. You know, then it's authentic. Then it's fine.
Cause teenagers are doing it. It feels authentic when Olivia Rodrigo sings about this stuff.
Well, of course it does because she is just recently out of her teens.
And in some cases was still a teen. So it like, it just made a lot more sense. I think again,
there's a couple of logic problems going on, which is I think they were like, okay,
well teens are kind of into each other and lascivious. So it'd be weird if we didn't include
that, but they went a little too far in being very weird about it. The other thing is they make all
the characters really mean to each other so that it makes sense when they like overcome that and
come together and support each other at the end, which you probably didn't need to do that much.
No, because it's unpleasant to watch most of these characters interact. This is where I see
why it's just like not like most of the movies, like not fun and everybody's mean to each other
and they're making a mean comments or lascivious comments. And I'm just like,
don't we want this to be fun? Like you can still have it be fun and have there be some conflict.
And then the characters come together at the end, but this is just like unpleasant,
unpleasant, unpleasant. Okay. They're a team. And you're like, that's not,
that's not what we need to do here. I want to have some fun with the characters.
I was trying to examine like, okay, the stuff that I find weird as an adult,
which I was like intrigued by as a kid, what borrowed into my self-conscious,
like I did think buff was very cute as a kid. And I did end up with a partner who is incredibly
strong. Oh, so you think that's the generation X is because of that? I'm what I, I don't know.
Cause she like throws around Matt for her, like she beats the shit out of them in this.
So you think you became attracted. So you're, you're, you had a thing now because of
generation X. It was a formative time. Maybe. Were you a She-Hulk kid? Did you like she,
cause she was really strong. It's funny to say that I am actually reading one of the
current runs of She-Hulk. Like they're, it's a very, it's a very fun light romantic comedy
where She-Hulk and Jack of Hearts are an item. How strong is she? Like how muscly is she drawn
in the comic? She is very, she's very mousy and then she's very muscly. And I'm like, yeah,
yeah, I think I kind of like both. Okay. She-Hulk kind of, all right. And yeah, so, so I ended,
yeah, I ended up with my own buff. Jean can just throw me around the room. She's fair. Like I said,
she's all muscly. She's very strong. Yeah. Do you have a bench press in the apartment?
We don't have a bench press in the apartment. I mean, we have yoga mats and yoga straps and
I just want to see if she could like bench press you or something. She could bench press you or
something. Well, I, if I like having, were like doing stretches on the ground or like have fallen,
she's like once or twice squeezed me up so hard. I'm like, oh, hey, you're going to pull my arm
out of the socket. Very impressive. So yeah, I mean, that's also probably like, I'm kind of,
you know, made of glass. You know, I'm not that, I, I am a little bit of a never drop the full
roly poly kid, you know, uh, eating corn and I'm still eating corn and taters every day. I just
try to portion size control it a little more. The a hundred year old song, the Bob will song,
roly poly is what Jason's referencing in case you didn't know. So, uh, yeah, I have my own little
buff, little buff in the house. I hope I'm not as crude as refraxes because he's kind of a jerk,
although he says he looks away when his x-ray vision kicks in when they're making out in the
car. Yes. And there's a lot of like x-ray vision. Oh, I could see through your clothes talk and
that's all like, I guess that's sort of par for the course as far as I guess a teenager having
those powers. Cause that's like, it is an intro. There's been plenty of different comic series
that like examine, well, what would a human being actually do if they weren't like a virtuous
person? Yeah. Most human beings aren't a hundred percent virtuous. So, uh, yeah,
you could imagine there'd be some problems that would arise if you gave a bunch of teens powers.
Yes. And, um, did you, what power did you want? What power did you want as a kid?
Oh, I mean, I certainly wanted that energy blast power. I really liked long shots agility,
just how he could flip around. Cause I had just no center of gravity as a kid. I had no balance.
Um, and, oh, what was the other out? But there's nothing you could do practically with the pot,
with the like blasting, like cause there weren't super villains in the real. I'm talking about
like in real world, if you got powers and there weren't super villains around. I think I wanted
shadow cats ability to walk through things. I know what I wanted. I wanted ice man powers.
You wanted ice man. Ice man could kind of turn into a solid piece of ice,
but he could then use his powers to create like ice sleds basically where he could kind of shoot
around very fast on ice that he created almost like he's making his own like slide or roller
coaster in real time. And I was like, Oh, that sounds awesome. I guess I could have just gotten
a power that where I could fly, but there was something about the ice that was very cool
and I wanted. Yes. And then he could go and he could look like a regular human too. But yeah,
the stuff that like does resonate with everybody is just, Oh my God, my body is changing. What is
happening to me? I feel so weird right now. I think, uh, yeah. And that's why as a kid,
I like leave the buff thing. Probably. I was like, that is very relatable. Cause I was like,
I don't know what I, my body is changing. I smell bad, you know,
and the angle, the generator, that's probably what I was afraid of when it comes to generation X
because generation X was leaning into that aspect of all of it. And I think that's probably,
I don't want to speak for Scott Lobdall, the writer, but I'm assuming that was the idea
because the characters weren't like perfect specimens. Like a lot of the X-Men were the
characters look stranger. The powers were weirder. Grant Morrison did the same thing
when he made up a bunch of new beak. It looks like a bird. He's like a half human, half bird.
Those weren't like all like just like perfect asymmetrical face human looking characters with
a little power they could turn on and off. So it makes sense. Yeah. And the beast in his run is
very much kind of has like horse legs and he looks more like beasts from the Disney
beauty and the beast. And that was the thing that became like artists sort of all draw him
differently, but it seems like Morrison had something more in mind because they started
getting into secondary mutations where characters started either heightening their powers or getting
other powers, which this also plays with a little too. I was a little disappointed watching this
and that it starts with like Jubilee is kind of your way in and like Jubilee, Shadow Cat,
other teen characters after them have kind of been your way in. But this very quickly takes a turn
where Angelo's skin is sort of becomes the main focus because he gets obsessed with the dream
machine. Yes, that, yeah, that's true. I mean, I, this was, they were hoping this was going to turn
into a series. So like that's what I understand about it. So it makes sense that it's kind of
ends up being more of an ensemble than it's just like, Oh, Jubilee is the main character.
But yeah, they, they, I think probably also just a hook in at any X-Men comic or cartoon fans. It
was like, well, you know Jubilee is. Yeah. And they're watching the broadcast version with the
commercials. There's X-Men Fox Kids commercials in there. Oh yeah. Sure. So that's bridging the gap.
Yes. If you're a kid, now they're going to, now they're going to bring you into prime time to see
what Fox prime time has to offer all the wonderful programming that you could possibly see. Honestly,
if they're smart with this MCU X-Men movie, just have Jubilee, you know, come into the school and
everyone else is there already, you know. That's what you would do with the Marvel, the new MCU
X-Men you mean? I think it's an approach. I think Jubilee, if you're going to have a audience surrogate
character, have it be Jubilee because everyone who grew up with the X-Men cartoon is like 40 or
something now. So they'll be like, oh yeah, I know my friend from childhood. Yeah. They use
Rogue in the original and the singer, the Brian Singer 2000X, like Rogue was sort of the Jubilee
or the shadow character, the Anna Paquin Rogue. Yeah. She was like the new recruit. That's a
changing body. Like Rogue can't touch anyone, but she has these feelings for Iceman in the movie,
right? Well, and I liked Rogue the best and I've determined now after psychoanalyzing myself that
I think I liked Rogue because she couldn't touch anyone. Okay. Thus making her safe. She was not
going to try to kiss me. Even though I wanted to kiss Rogue, she was not going to kiss me because
she couldn't. Safe. Good. That is my favorite character. So much so that Rogue is sitting on
my shelf up there waving to me. At a safe distance. Hey, Suga. Out of sight, Adamon, baby.
She's way up there. She's way up there. She cannot, she cannot hurt me. She cannot hurt you,
but she can also not love you. Well, she can love me from afar, but it's a comfortable kind of love.
Yeah. At some point in the comics, they figured out the Rogan Gambit touching each other and
they're married now. It's fun. And they're fun. They're like a fun couple together. Sure. They've
done, I think, some short run series under the name Mr. and Mrs. X, which that's cute because
Gambit and Rogue were also like the smart Alex, you know? Sure. There are, in the Generation X comic,
this kind of carries over to the show. There's a lot of characters razzing each other,
but in the comics, it's also a way to get out what their powers are and what their personalities are.
I am looking currently at the schedule, like the Fox schedule for
96, 97 and Beyond Belief Factor Fiction was on the air at this point. This is the Jonathan Freaks.
Right. Where they would film different little short stories and then at the end,
they would tell you if it was a made up thing or if it was actually based on a real spooky story.
That has kind of taken on a life of its own on the internet
the last few years. It's like a meme, right? Yeah. Yeah. And you can find super cuts of
Jonathan Freaks asking like, have you ever read, you can find him be like,
have you ever ridden a bicycle with two seats before?
Have you ever stopped and eaten ice cream? You want to talk about someone giving 110%
Jonathan Freaks and those bumpers are, it's really something. It's very much Rod Serling,
Twilight Zone or I didn't know this. Do you know about the Orson Welles on the BBC?
He hosted like a show where he would introduce an outro. I don't think so. I've seen that Orson
Welles talk show where he's got like Kermit on it or something. Sure. But I have not seen what
you're, I don't think I've seen what you're talking about. Still uncovering Orson Welles.
He did a lot. Get back to the movie. There is a moment that I think the rip I watched must have
been either a master copy or like if they sold it on VHS, because there is some profanity that I
found quite shocking. Yes. I also, I looked at, okay, I looked at both versions. I don't believe
this scene is in the broadcast because they say two fucks and a shit, I think. And I was like,
what? My head spun. I said, what is this? Some Cinemax? What is this? Like what channel? This
was Fox. I was like, there's no way. I was like, I wonder if they bleeped this in the other version,
but no, I don't believe that scene is even in the original Mardi Gras rip with Jim Belushi and
Jimmy Kimmel. You're talking about this scene. They're sitting outside the school skin and jubilee.
Yes. Skin and jubilee. And I only caught the one, but it was very off the cuff. And I was like,
oh, this makes sense. But I didn't expect it. I think there's a couple. I think you were so
blown away by one that you just like your ears filled up. I wouldn't be surprised here. Let's
go to it now. It was like my, my brain was floating in outer space, but with like nothing
to hold onto it. You know what I'm saying? Awesome. Are you fucking nuts? That was the
scariest thing I have ever felt in my entire life. I cosmically shit my fucking pants. I
cosmically shit my fucking pants. So three, there you go. Two F's and a shit. Two F's and a shit.
Yeah. And you were right. No, you were right. I was just like, that first fuck caught me so off
guard. And it is like true to the character. Like Jubilee would square. Jubilee would say she shit
her pants. She fucking shit her pants. Teenager real life Jubilee would say that. Has she ever
in the comics said I'm going to fucking shit my pants? No, cause they are, were comics code rated.
But would they have done the little like expletive like, you know, where they put like symbols in to
say that they were saying an ash swear or something? I think so. Yeah. I think she would.
And now they're what? Rated teen, T from T, whatever Marvel's kooky rating system is. I
feel like that doesn't feel like Jubilee to me. That she fucking shit her pants. I feel like a
a confused, frightened teen probably has a potty mouth. I think she, okay, she wouldn't say I made
in my pants cause that's like a kid's, a little kid says that she, but it doesn't feel right to,
I'm just trying to analyze my own feelings here. Why I don't think that that feels right to Jubilee.
I think she would have said it in like a cooler way. Like she would have talked about shitting her
pants in a cooler way. I'm trying to think like, I like, like, it's like, like I blazed one,
not blazed one out. That's like weed. Okay. I not shot one out. That's weird. Um,
drop the kids at the, I dropped the fucking kids at the pool. I fucking dropped one. I dropped one
off in my pants. No, that's not cool. See, I'm not cool like Jubilee. So I can't even think of
something good. Like she, yeah. What was cool at the time? Rollerblading, like a piece of shit,
rollerbladed out into my pants. Like that's not, I see again, I'm not the guy to think of this cool
teen dialogue. I can't do that. An old boss I used to have, uh, he was a little weird. He, uh,
you say I got a turtle head peeking out. If he was going to the bathroom, he would say that.
That's like the least offensive thing he would say. That's what fat bastard in Austin powers
says. I think. Oh my God. Yeah. I think he was probably your old boss was stealing lines from
fat bastard from gold members spy who shagged me. I don't remember which, which movie I believe
spy who shagged me, but I don't. Okay. That's a little better. If, if someone worked in a quote
from gold member into their repertoire, that would be very strange. I've, but I'll say like,
I love gold and stuff. I will work a gold member quotes into my real life. Yeah, but we're weird.
We're weird. We're, but I guess we're still thinking about the strange Mike Myers character
from 20 years ago. They were cultural phenomenon, gold member to some degree.
Yeah. Not as important as, uh, uh, Dr. Evil in Austin and, uh, Felicity Shagwell, but
gold gold member is like, that's, I feel like the clue to the love guru. Like that's a preview of
love guru Myers. I feel the love guru was that character was supposed to be in one of the Austin
powers movies. He had been thinking about it for so long. So yeah, maybe I remember in college,
um, uh, I used to see stuff on comedy message boards or comedy websites. So like,
Oh, Mike Myers workshop, a new character. And that was like, Oh, New York, they're sold out,
but New York is so far away. Which how long was it from you? Oh, probably good three plus hours.
Oh, wow. And there really wasn't, I guess you could get Ithaca to New York on a greyhound,
but there wasn't any trains anymore to Ithaca. I would, I would travel three hours to see Mike
Myers now, I think. Maybe, maybe. Cause you want to see, you want to see him revive his
gong show character. Tommy Maitland? Yeah, Tommy Maitland. British host of the gong show. Yeah.
But yeah, I, I, for whatever reason, it just seemed aggressive. Jubilee seemed like she had
such a hard edge here with, with her type of swearing. Well, she was generation X. They were
extreme. They were, I understand they were a little bit more, uh, out there. They had a lot more edge
than my average. Yeah. Than my average mutant teen. I get that. This is pre Mad Manic Pixie
dream girl. You know, cool skater girls back in the nineties had an edge. She's almost more like
my so-called life. Like she's almost more. Very so-called life. Yeah. Yeah. It's almost,
that's kind of the vibe to it too. Um, another thing I've never seen and had no interest when
I was a kid, because I wanted to be a child forever and I wasn't interested in the lives
of people who were older, unless they were much, much older, like Henry Fonda level older.
But not if it was Bridget or Laura that could get dangerous. They're very beautiful. Very beautiful.
Yes. Uh, uh, I wonder, yeah, did they sell like, was this common where they would do a scene
with like a couple curses for overseas? I don't know. That's interesting. Maybe. I did a quick,
there's not a ton of trivia. Just if you look at IMDb about this thing. Um, so yeah, I wonder,
obviously they knew that wasn't going to air and I don't recall, like X-Files didn't have just a
bunch of bleeps in it. Like show regular shows on Fox didn't just have a lot of bleeping.
So it must've been filmed for the idea that it could be a theatrical release somewhere,
or it would go somewhere where a country that celebrates the phrase, uh, fucking shitting,
fucking shitting, like it may be in Germany or something. That's a, that's like a popular
teen phrase and they were just trying to appeal to that market. I don't know. I'm speculating here.
I don't know. I have no information really going in on the Germans and their shit love. Um,
they, uh, yeah, I don't know. I must, like you said, they might've just cut this scene.
I think it makes sense without it. I, it starts to not make sense pretty quickly because they,
Angelo helps out Dr. Uh, Trash. Uh, and then he communicates to Jubilee, uh, like help me help.
I mean, I'm stuck. And then Emma Jubilee wakes up Sean and Emma and they get the whole team
together and then transport is layer into the real world or they transport them to the dream.
It's very unclear. It just kind of like is a complicated way to get everyone to go fight
this bad guy who doesn't really seem that powerful. No, his power is his quirkiness.
His power is his silly, uh, vocal delivery and getting the shit beat out of him. And he gets
beat up, surviving a pipe exploding above him. Um, uh, there are some other weird little moments
in that for one, the product placement of the video game virtual fighter. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Fighter is mentioned multiple times. Um, the teen was a virtual fighter. Is that what you're
looking for? Is that the Sega Sega? Yeah, I was just called a virtual fighter. I fucked up.
I think I was not cool, you know? Yeah, it's a virtual fighter. Uh, after refrax and buff make
out the car and he accidentally reveals his x-ray vision, start to act up and she storms away.
Him and Mondo are like, uh, he's like, oh man, what do I do? Mondo says, uh, listen, man,
there's only one thing to do at a time like this. Let's crack a 40 and, and then it cuts to them
at like a soda stall. It's not quite clear. I, I think they just wanted the reference in there.
They weren't drinking like a 40 ounce beer. They were drinking a 40 ounce soda. Yeah. I, oh yeah.
I guess it, I, I, I don't know. I don't think it was that well thought out. Just like it wasn't
well thought out. The toss off line mutants can see subliminal message. What's it was at the end.
I don't even remember this at this point. At this point I'm trying to piece together. I have the
Charlie day meme going with Jim Carrey and Matt Fruer. So I'm forgetting some of the lines toward
the end of this movie. Uh, Matt Fruer is also like a real creep about you. He's like, oh yeah,
he's very lascivious, a pedophile or whatever. Like, yeah, she's very young. Um, he also,
the bad guy there's, I swear they watched, I was looking up who, who did this directed it,
wrote it and it's like, uh, guy who had some writing credits on Cagney and Lacey, some old shows.
Uh, but I swear somebody watched Batman forever right before this because there's even a scene
like we all remember the famous scene when Jim Carrey throws, uh, at Begley junior out a window
in Batman forever. He's his boss, uh, at Wayne, whatever Wayne tech. Uh, there's a scene here
where Matt Fruer, uh, Dr. Tesh, Dr. Tresh, not John Tesh, Dr. Tresh, uh, uh, like tricks a person
into thinking they're in a dream and then throws them out a window at the top of a building.
And it was like, did somebody just say, give me Batman forever? And I know I'm a guy who has
Batman forever on the brain 24 seven, but still it felt just like the Batman forever had just had
cast such a shadow over this movie. Uh, let me just say the director, Jack shoulder, uh,
Jack shoulder, he's from Philadelphia. Uh, he directed a load in the dark, a nightmare on Elm
street to Freddy's revenge and wish master to evil never dies. Does he still working?
I, let me see what his most recent credit was. Both him and the writer had made a lot before.
Could you get an internship with Jack shoulder because of the Philadelphia connection
solely? I think a lot of people have lived in that city, Michael. Um,
well, that would just be a little bit. I mean, obviously you're a fan of his movie. So that
would be another, that would be maybe a stronger connection, but I would just like to see you
working for Jack shoulder for no money. Um, Ed Blake knee is the writer. He directed, uh,
he wrote some episodes at 21 jump street. He also directed a 2000s movie that I very clearly
remember the poster, but I've never seen called gun shy Liam Neeson, Oliver Platt and Sandra Bullock.
Okay. Uh, kind of a powerhouse cast. Oh, budget 14 million box office, three million.
So maybe it's good. I don't know. Yeah, I don't know. It seems like up my alley. Um,
so yeah, I mean, I shoulder Jack shoulder sounds like he could be an X man. Cause like he has
shoulder, a shoulder power or something. He, Jack shoulder would be the one. Maybe that's
whose shoulder they used in that insert shot in the changing room. Oh, maybe he actually,
that's like almost a pseudonym or a nickname because he has such a nice looking shoulder.
And then anytime he does a shot where somebody has to like disrobe, they use his shoulder.
Yeah. Hmm. I was thinking more along the lines of he had like a mutant power of like
his shoulder could grow bigger. One shoulder could grow bigger.
Oh, that's more interesting. It's one shoulder shoulder gets really big,
but like it gets so big. Like you could, if like you could carry a piano on it or something,
like it's, it's not as such a great superhero power, but it is good if you need to like
carry three different garbage bags to the curb at once. You can just set them on his big shoulder.
Very funny scene too, to like communicate the, the teens feel affection or camaraderie with each
other where Mondo and refrax are eating in a fifties diner, a classic meal of hamburger pizza
slice and milkshake and Mondo. A regular Jay Leno, a regular Jay Leno meal. Well, breakfast, lunch
and dinner, you know, uh, Mondo starts having like an across the room eating competition.
The bully kids, uh, push his face into a banana split.
Did that upset you seeing that? I mean, I was mostly trying to figure out what flavors of ice
cream, cause it didn't seem like, it seemed like bright colors, but isn't it usually chocolate,
vanilla strawberry? You're asking me. I'm asking you. I'm asking you as a pro.
I would think you want a Neapolitan lineup. You want something simple, but varied to go
along with the bananas and the crushed pineapple. Okay. I have a pitch for you here. Yeah. Your
mutant power is that your fingers dispense soft serve ice cream. Do I eat the sauce or ice cream?
Yes. And each finger is a different, each finger is a different flavor of soft serve.
And you can, you can, you can use it. Like here's the thing. You can also shoot the soft serve very
fast. So it could be some sort of a defense or weapon. So you could hit somebody in the
face with like a chocolate soft serve stream, but it also is just regular good soft serve.
So you could use it and eat it and, and give it to your guests at a dinner party.
I am a nail biter since I was a kid. So if I could turn that into just
eating soft serve ice cream, it would really help. Although I'd probably,
probably be bad for my arteries. That feels like a mutant power where it's not like not a hundred
percent reliable, uh, offensively. So the character just has a gun for some reason,
like, uh, yeah, backup like cable kind of has telekinesis, but he's got to keep his body together.
So he also has a lot of guns. Right. And your name will be your, your code name is soft serve.
That's pretty good. I don't think we've had a mutant soft serve. Um,
that, which brings me to another point. I think a carrot, uh, uh, a comics creator,
I'm kind of shocked in like 18 years that no character, uh, creator has written in refrax or
buff of just like, you're shocked by that. I think it's probably, there's probably some trademark
copyright stuff, but it's like, if you need a bunch of mutants, I think that no one watched this
or liked it. And that's the reason that those characters haven't appeared anywhere else.
I could be wrong. I like the names, but, uh, it seems like first off, uh, credit to Jubilee
for being the first cursing X-Men on camera. Sorry, Deadpool and Wolverine Jubilee beat you to it.
But like, if they're bringing back all of the filmed Marvel characters in all of these movies,
have the Fox generation X pop up and explain who they are.
It would grind the movie to such a halt to use. You have to explain to the audience who they are.
Well, not if Deadpool's like, check out these guys next.
Okay. So you're going to bring them in just as a gag.
He does like the loony tunes, like when they push the frame, when they push the frame out of view.
Right. Um, yeah. Okay. It's a gag. I think that's, that's okay. I mean, the Nick fear,
uh, Castle of Nick Fury would play well. Which we should, I, I didn't want to do
talk about both those because obviously there was more than enough to talk about
in the world of generation X. I think we should examine that one with Scott.
Cause that one, I think is a little more standalone. He's a Hasselhoff enthusiast.
He's a Hasselhoff connoisseur. Yeah. He's of the three. He knows his Hasselhoff so he can,
he can pull recall. I'm sure other Hasselhoff performances, um, and compare and contrast in a
lot better, more effective way than us. Um, and I haven't seen the Hasselhoff Nick Fury. I did not
watch it. Oh, okay. I was excited about that one. I just Fox's. Isn't there one more? Am I
forgetting one? Like a Fox or is it only two? There's, um, there's a low budget man thing,
like horror movie, but I don't know if that was looped in with this. Hey, by the way,
at the very beginning of the movie, there's a production card for a company called, um,
I think it's new world entertainment. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Did you look that up?
I did look that up and I was shocked to find like they had sold it in the mid eighties,
but that was founded by Roger Corman and his brother. Okay. In the mid eighties, they sold it
for like 16 and a half million dollars. So, uh, I eat, eat, I think it was low budget movies when
they were doing it. And eventually it just kind of became a public, like independent production
company and they had a lot more like legitimate credits to its, to their name. Let me ask you a
question. Uh, did the Craven, the Hunter movie ever come out? Did it come out or is it about
to come out? Uh, it's a very good question. Um, did it come out? I don't, I don't think it did,
but I'm not sure. The movie Craven, the Hunter, the film is coming out December 13th, 2024.
It has not come out. I was right. And this has happened before where you all say the same or
ask a similar question to you, uh, where I go, did that movie come out a year ago or is it coming
out in a year? And yes, we're a month away from Craven. Darren Taylor Johnson is Kick-Ass,
Quicksilver and Craven. Yes. That's racking up. I am, I am interested in a lot of these guys who
are going to end up, a lot of these actors, uh, who will end up playing like 10 different comic
book characters once their career is all said and done. Yeah. And just hoping they end up in a future
Deadpool. They were trying to get Brolin to be Hal Jordan, Green Lantern. And I was like,
oh, is Brolin going to be Cable, Thanos and Green Lantern? I heard Kyle Chandler last.
Oh no, I know. Yeah. They were trying to get him, but they didn't. Kyle Chandler, who I'm a big fan
of. Yeah. He would be perfect as Hal Jordan. Who else could play soft serve other than Jason
Sherwood? Well, only me. Yeah, I am not. I'm offer only on soft serve. I'm not auditioning.
Well, the character has been created on this podcast now, so I don't know. You don't have
to get an offer from anyone but us, I think, unless we sell the character to the X-Men,
which I would like to. Well, that's fine, but I'm not auditioning. I'm demanding. I don't think
you should audition. Original character. No, I think I should get co-creator rights, you know.
Sure. I mean, again, I invented the whole thing, so I really should have the full rights,
but I will give you a 20% stake in soft serve. And we will say that if you buy the rights to
soft serve, you have to play the character. So at the very least, you'll get your big payday there.
I get my scale. Yeah. That is a sort of cutthroat negotiating that who would have been doing it,
Stanley or Roger Corman? Would they have just both been cutthroat to each other?
That's a good question. I don't know how cutthroat Corman was. I mean, Corman seemed like everybody
had nice things to say about him, and Stan, I think, is a little more murky. I don't know
exactly if he had a lawyer doing a lot of it, but early in the day.
Jack Nicholson breaks down in tears in that one Corman documentary talking about how he made his
career. Yes. Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. I think a lot of people got their start with Roger Corman.
Yeah. But I don't know. I don't know the negotiator that he was. I don't know anything
about it. That's none of my business. Well, if you ever are listening to this,
if you ever had to negotiate with Roger Corman when he was still with us, let us know.
Yes, please. And on that note, I'm going to say you survived podcast to ride the second gate.
Jason's birthday shot. Hey, yeah. Oh, yeah. Somebody called somebody pub head in one of
these scenes. Oh, yes. Yeah. And that's I guess that's all in good teen fun, right?
Yeah, there's a lot of good teen fun. You know, there's a lot of mid 90s good teen fun
superimposed with Fox primetime Mardi Gras correspondents. I recommend watching the full
two hour block that as if you were going back in time, because I think that's more of an
interesting experience viewing wise, because then you have the full time machine and you
at least can enjoy because you can I am and I enjoy the cheap aesthetic of this movie. I enjoy
like, oh, this is what these these cheaper movies and TV shows look like at the time.
I enjoy all that stuff. And I enjoy the commercial. So I would recommend if you're interested,
I do I would do that. And then you could scroll around. But if you want to hear Jubilee say that
she fucking shit her pants, you do have to watch the other version without the commercials.
Correct. Yeah. And I I do like this probably did imprint on me, you know, not this specifically,
but this was like of a piece of like sound design, kooky angles, kooky colored lighting,
things I still like. Well, who doesn't like a lot of the things you listed, you know, if you don't
like that, something's wrong with you real quick before we go. And I'm going to put you on the
spot here. And I want you to do it. I'm going to give you maybe 60 seconds to do this. I'm going
to give you 60 seconds. And to play us out, to talk us out, you're going to list the different
flavors that soft serve has coming out of each finger. As far as the powers are concerned,
I guess you could they could switch up. But like a basic wise, what would you think each finger
would be? And tell me when you're ready. And I will give you the 60 seconds on the on the stopwatch.
All right, this is going to be it's going to probably end up being pretty close to
obviously yogurt land out here, but then Coors Brothers soft serve custard, frozen custard back
east. You can get wild with you. OK, are you ready? Yeah, you ready? All right, I hit start.
OK, vanilla chocolate, vanilla chocolate twist, strawberry banana, strawberry banana twist,
coffee, peanut butter.
I don't think you have to do the twist because I think you could you could combine the two fingers
and that would be a twist anyway. So we have to start all over again. All right, chocolate,
vanilla. OK, strawberry banana. Right. Peanut butter, coffee. OK.
Uh, oh, now he's stunned me. OK, make stuff up. Chocolate, chocolate, almond. OK.
Birthday cake. OK, you didn't need 60 seconds. Caramel. OK, good. And
rounding out the list, butterscotch. Butterscotch. Wow. You only need 29
seconds and that was with one restart. OK, that's that's great. I mean, I would have thrown in
did they have like cookie dough soft serve? They have to be able to do that, right?
They I think they've tried. We're like, I feel like I've seen chocolate pudding. Like, I think
it's just variants. That's a doctor. It's like time variance authority, you know, TVA.
An evil doctor, Tresh, would try some sort of abomination like a cookie dough soft serve.
Yes. Anyway, I just confirmed a dental appointment on my phone.