Forever!
Dog!
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a theme park podcast that will not end until we've done a cross-country tour of every state fair where we rank the cute faces on all the blue-ribbon winning pigs.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Scott Garner, who looks very confused and maybe upset.
When you said cute faces, I was like, that are drawn on a pumpkin or on a dessert or something, but then the face is on a pig.
On a real-life living pig, yeah.
Because I guess the normal way to say that would be the pig's faces, but faces on a pig, I think, threw me for a loop.
Well, they're technically on the body of the pig.
There's nothing incorrect about what you said.
There might be a couple extra words in between two thoughts or ideas that maybe threw you off.
Jason, did you understand? Jason Sheridan, did you understand?
I understand.
We're ranking the pig's cute faces.
Yeah, Jason got it.
I got it. I did not get it.
He was right along with me.
There's just something baffling to me about, and do we really, like, the real pigs, do we think their faces are cute?
You don't think pigs are cute?
At a state fair, a bunch of real big pigs run around. I don't know if they are cute. Their faces?
Well, I mean, I actually didn't even think about another, like, cute debate happening on the show, which has happened many times.
Yeah, this is an organic cute debate.
But I do think pigs are cute. Jason, what do you think? Jason Sheridan?
I think they can be. I think at state fairs, they're often tired and sleeping and lying on their side.
That's what I'm thinking.
Well, I was going to say it's very relatable, but look, I'm a side sleeper, you know?
I'm a side sleeper, too. I'm just saying.
Yeah.
I think there was, look, that'll be part of it, though, is, like, will there be, like, an unnaturally cute pig that we'll find across America?
I'm sure there are pigs that are cute. I just think your run-of-the-mill fair pigs, it's cute, isn't it?
So maybe what your issue is-
A grown piglet, maybe?
So maybe you're thinking we want more of, like, some sort of a fancy show pig versus a fair pig.
You're, like, looking for a city pig versus a country pig.
I would think, yes, that if the pig is in some kind of a show, then the cute likelihood is higher.
That's interesting. Are there pig shows? Did Jason, you know?
Well, I think state fairs, that would be the cream of the crop. That would be the show pig, wouldn't it?
You don't think there's, like, a fancy pig show somewhere that takes place in sort of a convention center, like a dog show?
I'd have to look into it. I want to talk out of my ass.
Yeah, you're right. We don't want to spread misinformation.
I think that they keep these things outside or in sort of a, you know, open but covered area.
I don't think we're bringing a bunch of pigs into the Hilton, into the Marina Room.
Well, maybe we should bring pigs into a Hilton.
Fancy pigs, pigs that have more money, high-class pigs that are, like, nines and tens.
You're picturing swine. I'm talking about remarkable, classy pigs.
Nine or tens on the scale, the Bob Guccione whatever scale of attractiveness.
I'm assuming that's the ranking.
Let me say this. I have nothing against pigs. I think pigs are neat.
But I think pure face, cute, this is just what I question.
I don't know. Maybe I have too much cartoon pig on the brain. Maybe that's really what it is.
Because I'm looking at, I saw art of what we're talking about today,
in which Mickey has a cartoon pig nuzzling against him, and this absolutely is cute.
I have no, you know, pig depictions, certainly.
Well, when this comes out, I will try to find pictures of legitimately cute pigs,
post them along with the episode, and then the audience can decide, is the average fair pig cute?
And maybe I'm wrong. I'm happy to be wrong in this instance.
But I guess maybe, yeah, maybe I'm just getting, my brain is clouded with, like, the cartoon three little pigs.
Look, as I Google, I'm seeing cute pigs. I know there's cute pigs. There are.
Well, we're going to do it. We're going to go cross-country and figure it out.
Wow. Lots of things.
Let's bring our guest in. He's a director, he's a writer, and he's a member,
most importantly, of my serious toy collector, Text Chain Chat.
Ah.
This is Justin Donaldson. He's here.
Hello, everybody.
And if you wouldn't mind, I would prefer to do a toy swap live on the air.
Yeah, we can do this. I don't mind.
Because we are going to do one of these right now.
This is something that toy collectors do. They look out for each other, they find toys,
and then they do a trade, and we're going to do this live on the air.
Wow.
This is very exciting.
Okay. So you'd just be doing this somehow.
We would meet up in the middle, usually, wherever we are, we'll meet in the middle,
and I'm going to trade him a NECA belly bomb, which I've talked about.
This is the one you said you wanted to kiss.
I'll send it around if you guys want to take a look at it.
I'm very excited about this.
We talked about kissing this belly bomb on a recent episode.
There's too many sharp teeth to kiss this guy.
Well, you kiss him on his teeth, you know, close the mouth,
because the mouth closes, and you can kind of kiss him on his teeth,
which is a line in a Ryan Adams song, I'm realizing, but I don't have to mention that.
But the teeth, so you're talking about the surface of the teeth,
because I don't want to get near those points.
Well, yes, close the mouth, and then kiss on the sort of enamel of the teeth.
I guess that's not far from what I always say, because I chose, in talking about kissable toys,
I chose a street shark, and they have sharp teeth as well.
Right.
I guess it's, all right, so you close the mouth.
No more objections, sir.
Yeah, it's a very phallic toy, and it's honestly one of the best toys I've ever owned.
I say this with no hyperbole.
It's so incredible.
It's a character I've never had before, and it's so well done.
It's really well done.
Mike, I don't know, I mean, in terms of phallic,
what penises have you seen that get really fat at the end of the shaft?
Well, on a recent episode, I also said there are penises
that are the shapes and sizes of things we can't even imagine.
That's right.
People have stuff going on down there that we don't know,
and I'm just saying, I bet someone's looks kind of like that.
I suppose.
Hopefully not with the eyeball and horns.
His eyeball and horns.
Well, right, hopefully where the head is, it's not an eyeball.
It's just where I start to feel like you, Mr. Prude,
are seeing penises everywhere and in everything.
I've seen many YouTube toy guys mention the phallic nature of this toy also.
He's a pink color.
That's true.
He's got a long neck.
I think the color and the shading and kind of like where he bunches up.
Yes, he bunches up.
That's the most important part about the toy,
is that it bunches up in the right part.
And I think that's where it does it.
Now, that's not why, I swear to God,
that's not why this is one of my favorite toys of all time.
But anyway, I'm trading this to Justin.
Now, Justin has a very exciting toy for me.
He can say it.
This is the Toilet Taxi.
This is a re-release of a classic 80s vehicle,
but with a new figure.
The original didn't come with a figure.
Oh, I see.
You would have had to get this without you bringing your own turtles to the Toilet Taxi.
Right.
Now you can get a Donatello with a helmet and goggles.
But I do have this somewhere, but it's kind of broken,
and they just reissued it, and I'm very excited.
And we've talked about this vehicle on this show before many years ago.
I think at this point, is that the turtle is sitting on an open toilet
while he drives his vehicle around.
So you have to presume that shitting or pissing in it powers the vehicle.
Why do you have to assume that?
You would have to assume.
I think a lot of the vehicles were...
Powered by pissing.
Sewage.
Yeah.
There was a lot.
There was a sewage theme.
They deal in sewage.
They live in sewage.
It definitely seems like a function over form sort of thing.
Yes.
What science allows poop and pee to...
Well, in Back to the Future, Doc dumps a bunch of garbage into the time machine.
So obviously he could have probably picked up a couple...
So it's Mr. Fusion-esque technology.
Yeah, Donatello's the smartest Doc Brown.
Mm-hmm.
He can figure that out.
So this is a live toy swap.
You're seeing it now, how it happens.
So it's very exciting.
Technology that Big Oil is suppressing.
Hold on a second.
Donatello is the smartest Doc Brown?
I think he is.
We're all...
Almost everything you've said we've found problems in.
You've only said like four things.
Donatello created a whole interdimensional travel portal that was in the sewer.
He would bring people through.
I suppose that's true.
That's pretty good.
So I'm just saying that's on par with what Doc Brown did.
And now the toilet taxi is different than the Ghostbusters haunted toilet toy.
Oh, absolutely.
Which you sent to me, and it was one of the fastest purchases I ever made.
Right.
Well, please use the real name of the character, Jason, Fearsome Flush.
Fearsome Flush, excuse me.
Yes, of course.
But yeah, I guess he eats human waste.
Yeah, his tongue is coming out of the bowl.
Right.
And his eyes are on the tank.
Mm-hmm.
So there's many different vintage toilet-based things you can buy now.
It was a big thing in the late 80s, I feel like.
Right.
And yeah, I'm glad to see it's coming back.
Slime, toilet, poop.
It was all the same stuff.
Right.
Because we were embracing gross out for the first time, maybe, the culture.
Uh-huh.
We were experimenting with it.
Well, that was thrilling.
Boxes, two men pulled boxes out, and now you have different boxes.
Two men exchanged boxes.
You both remembered to transport them.
One man gave the other man a toilet, and one man gave the other one a penis.
Eyeballed penis.
That was beautiful.
Yeah.
It was a beautiful thing.
But look, we got a lot to talk about today.
Yes.
We're going to talk Disneyland State Fair, which was another one of these limited-time
events.
I keep wanting to say limited-time magic.
Sure.
Because that's the currency on the island.
Yeah, yeah, why not?
But let's real quick.
This is limited-time, and we'll get into it, but it was on the second gate by now.
You've heard us talk about Blast to the Past, which was a 50s throwback event, and we need
to talk about the State Fair thing they did, and Justin has fond memories of the State
Fair thing.
Yes, thank you.
But don't let that distract from where you're going.
Oh, sure.
I just want to bring up real quick.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff.
Justin is a big Disneyland guy, theme park guy, Orange County guy, and you went a ton
as a kid.
Yeah.
I was born up here in Van Nuys, and we lived in Glendale until the summer between the second
and third grade.
However, I don't know what age you are at that point, so when I was really little, I
was all about Universal, and also because I wanted to be a filmmaker, and back then,
making movies was exciting, and I would go to Universal and see how it was done.
I would go to Universal almost weekly, and then we moved to Orange County, and before
we moved to Orange County, Disneyland was a two or three times a year thing, but then
once we moved to Orange County, it became an all-the-time thing, like Universal when
we lived up here.
Every time there was one of these limited time things, we had to go.
They would sell discount tickets for them at Ralph's, which is the California Kroger.
There was always some sort of deal going on at the same time as these events, and I don't
know if I saw them on television.
Somehow, myself and the family, everyone knew that these events were happening.
They were pretty heavily advertised, seemingly, and with big budget commercials, it was not
like, come on down, this weekend there's a thing.
They were shot filmically, and maybe presented.
Was not the blast of the past, wasn't there a McDonald's ad we talked about with Little
Richard that was a national ad, so yeah, they got the stuff in front of you.
The discount tickets there, so each one of these had a tie-in, so that was a thing with
my parents being like, oh, the other tickets were on sale, blah, blah, blah.
We ended up going to all of these in 87 and 88.
Which was kind of a new breed of, this is sort of an Eisner era invention.
I think we sort of touched on this on the second gate with blast of the past, but I
think there was a time, if you can imagine it, kind of right when Eisner got there, right
before, where it was just accepted, like, well, Disney's busy during the summer and
the holidays, and then we quiet down a little bit.
We even closed the park some days, and Eisner gets in, he's like, what are you doing?
You should be making money in every possible way, from every avenue.
Don't ever close the park down, and like, okay, what's going on here?
You got nothing between summer and winter?
Come up with some stuff, make some things happen, and that's where this particular
event and the others came from.
And it totally worked, I know, at least for us, because we went for our regular Disney
trips, and then we would also go for these special events, and we were there specifically
for the events.
Right, right.
There is a state fair Ralph's commercial on YouTube, and I believe what it was, if you
spent $50 at Ralph's, you would get a free child ticket with purchase of an adult ticket,
and I believe they said, like, a $16 value, and it's like, oh my god.
I know it was nearly 40 years ago at this point, but children's tickets must be ten
times that price at this point, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, they would have to be.
Yeah, easily.
But that's, yeah, and for state fair specifically, like you said, you did Blast to the Past
and other events, but I would assume, like, state fair was your favorite.
Absolutely, like, my favorite and, like, my whole family's favorite.
Like, I remember everyone being very excited the next year that the state fair was coming
back.
Yeah, this one they did twice, 87, 88, yeah, yeah.
The circus, I barely remember.
Like, the only thing I remember from it was the motorcycles in the middle of the hub.
There was, like, a metal ball that had motorcycles crossing each other in the hub.
So they're depicted in the Simpsons movie.
Yes.
These are all these cylinders of death.
And that's, like, all I remember from that, and then Blast to the Past, the main thing
I remember from that was the giveaways.
There were all these, like, 1950s toys, and with every ticket you could exchange for one
of those.
Okay.
So I remember that and the parade, and I think they also had the shooting the guy out of
the cannon, which the state fair also had.
I believe so.
The TV ads for both feature human cannonballs.
Right.
Yeah.
All right, so at a state fair they would have that, and in the 50s they would have that.
In the 50s, human cannonballs were all the rage.
It was the main way people transported themselves sexually.
It was faster.
It was cheaper.
Freeways weren't everywhere yet, so yeah, just getting a cannon.
The state fair felt like so much bigger.
It's crazy how much stuff.
There was so much.
Like, lastly, I was trying to finish up, like, looking all this stuff up, and I kept finding
stuff and watching stuff, and I was like, this is wild how much they had.
It's very park-wide every corner of the park.
Yeah, yeah.
Tons of big produced events.
But if you search Disney state fair, you also get, and this is a different episode, with
the inflatables going around to various actual state fairs in the 96, but that's something
else.
That's something else.
I'll say the names of all the things just to whet the appetite of the audience.
Do we think that's an episode?
Oh, yeah.
If we can't cover that in two minutes.
If we could find a video of it, I believe it's an episode, but I can't find-
Yeah, it's pretty, I think the undocumentation is the-
I found a video about it that had footage, and I found these articles.
I want to see the whole show.
There was Disney Fun Fair Extraordinaire, which Disney had a plan to run these weird
balloon shows at all the state fairs across America.
The Great Inflation Celebration.
Mickey's Inflation Celebration.
Which was a very expensive, very labor-intensive show to set up and perform.
Which they only, I think we all watched this video.
Midway to Main Street made a video about this, but yeah, they tried it at the Washington
State Fair and the Arizona State Fair, and after one, we're like, this doesn't work at
all.
We have to hire so many people.
How are we going to, okay, to set up tons of inflatable shit to do.
All right, so we got a lot.
Let's get as many hands as we can to transport all this stuff.
You all, you're in.
Later, people find out these are non-union workers, IOTC protests.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
All right.
Okay, so we're going to be regulated on this.
You know, how about not?
How about we don't do this?
That's the, how about we deflate the Great Inflation Celebration?
I love that there's just, you keep uncovering Eisner era failures.
So many Eisner era failures.
We still have never talked about, was it called Club Disney or Club Mickey or what?
Club Mickey.
Westlake Village, there's a shopping center that now is, it's a pottery barn.
But whenever I'm there, I remember, oh, that's where there was this weird Disney club thing,
which is different than Disney Quest.
There's, yeah.
That was a Chuck E. Cheese thing?
I think it was sort of Chuck E. Cheese-ish.
I don't know much about it.
Family entertainment center.
Did you ever do that, Justin?
No, like I didn't even know about it.
Most people I don't think knew about any of this stuff.
But it was like constant.
I was a really, like we talk about continuous.
And I was like on top of it, even back then, like I knew the like themed entertainment
news when I was a kid and I had no idea that place.
Justin, you lived in Southern California like all your life.
Did you ever go to, it's a thing I encountered recently and it's a chain.
It's called Boomers.
Oh yeah, well, Boomers.
It's a chain of family entertainment centers and it's still hanging in there despite having
multiple different, like locations are owned by different companies.
Yeah, so Boomers like came in and bought up a bunch of like miniature golf courses and
stuff like that.
And like the, one of my favorite places to go when I was a kid was Bullwinkles.
And Boomers.
Oh yeah, of course.
Yeah, Boomers bought the Bullwinkles in Fountain Valley.
So like I went to Boomers, but they weren't Boomers yet when I went there.
And then like, I remember after high school, they started opening up more miniature golf
course and like bowling places.
So I remember going to Boomers like just out of high school, but it wasn't really a thing
when I was a kid yet.
There were a bunch of like independent miniature golf courses and then Boomers bought them
up and like added other things.
What are the odds that you get into the weeds that you talk to the owners of these places
and discover that Boomers was a cutthroat, terrible pirate organization that like we
had to sell.
We had no choice.
The Boomers wave ruined the right.
It has to be that.
Before Boomers came in, like that Bullwinkles in Fountain Valley was just amazing because
you had the full Bullwinkles with the animatronic and the whole thing, plus you had bumper boats,
which were crazy.
Yeah, it was a very, very fun complex.
Wow.
You need a lot of land to have bumper boats.
Is there a place within 30 miles that you can get in a bumper boat right from here?
Yep, definitely.
Where are they?
I mean, Ventura, I don't know if it's within 30 miles, but golf and stuff in Ventura is
what I flashed to, which is right off the freeway, off the 101, so you can see that
very easily.
And it's on my mind because the Beach Boys filmed a very embarrassing music video there
for a cover of Crocodile Rock, and they're all in the bumper boats and shaking their
hands around, like doing jazz hands, wearing leisure suits and fedoras.
It's one of the worst things you'll ever see.
What year are we talking?
95, 96.
Stamos in it for sure.
Stamos is like a Latin lover.
They have slicked back hair, like dipping girls.
But I think maybe one in the Valencia-ish area too might have, I forget the name of
that.
I think it's the same golf and stuff as from Karate Kid too.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Oh, wow.
Interesting.
Okay.
Oh, and then they moved all the balloons from the state fair to some show in Singapore,
some Disney Fest in Singapore.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I would love if we can get a video of what that balloon show was, a highly produced
balloon show.
Jason's ready to go without the, Jason's putting his foot down.
We're doing it.
We don't need the footage.
It's all the inflatable parade balloon.
It's our guys.
He wants to list the balloons.
It's our guys?
What do you mean?
It's our guys.
He wants to list the balloons.
Tell us what our guys are.
Just that we like the balloon.
We always, I feel like we always speak fondly of the balloons in the parade.
We do love the balloons.
What do you mean by the balloons?
I don't know.
Are you talking about the balloons?
Like the party grub.
Party grub.
But that's not part of this, is it?
This is a different thing.
The video alluded to some of those balloons were in the show.
Ending up.
Okay.
But I don't know which balloons specifically, if it's the mini with the big fruit hat on
or something.
I just found it so strange that you're yelling it's our guys at me and I'm like, what are?
Who are?
They're my guys.
Some people.
If they're my guys, I should know what they are.
If somebody has the video, please send it to, email us and send it to us at JasonSheraton.com.
Did you go to the great inflation celebration?
Yeah.
Did you bounce in luxury?
Be very careful searching that now or you're going to find Mickey going like, oh boy, oh
I'm getting bigger.
I'm about to pop.
What?
Inflation stuff?
Inflation stuff is like a rule.
Is that a sex thing?
Like a rule 35.
I feel like inflation stuff is a sex.
Inflation stuff.
If you feel that, then you know that's true.
You're going to have to just admit it.
Are you into inflation stuff, Jason?
I am not.
No.
I just know.
I'm just an anthropologist, you know.
I'm just curious.
You study that people do this.
But do you think an example of that would be Mickey saying, oh, I'm getting so bald.
Oh, don't put too much hair in there or else I'm going to puff.
We haven't even gotten to the fairest feels yet.
I know, but what is inflation?
What is it?
Like being inflated.
Like being pumped in.
So there's porno or is it like cartoon porno where like a balloon is being inflated and
somebody gets horny because of that?
Like characters get inflated.
Justin, you know what I'm talking about?
No.
All right.
He maybe just invented a thing.
But don't send us this.
He maybe invented a thing.
Maybe that's an invented thing.
I assure you, I am not.
I think maybe you did.
I am not the expert here.
I am just a casual observer.
You're a creator.
You're a young creative who's come up with a new kind of porno.
No, he's not.
Because I've just found a Reddit where people are accusing the series Tiny Toon Adventures
of being a way for the writers to make real their inflation fetishes.
And they're proving this by, you know, like Babs Bunny would get big sometimes.
Like Violet Beauregard or something.
Tiny Toon Adventures was practically the writers barely disguised furry weight gain and inflation fetishes.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, no.
Wow.
Jason, you're really lurking on the dark.
You're looking at the dark part.
You're not allowed to think of a part where a cartoon character blows up real big and
then that's...
That was fun.
That's just fun.
That's not just you trying to write your fetish into...
I think it's just good old fashioned fun.
Like a turn of the century state fair.
Donald puts his mouth on like a...
If you think you're segueing back with that, you're incorrect, Jason.
We're staying on this point.
Good try.
It might continue.
I was going to say like Donald puts his mouth on like a helium tank and he blows up and
he floats.
And he floats away.
That's good fun.
That's for perverts is what this Reddit person is saying.
That's for perverts?
Yes.
The only way you'd ever want to see a cartoon character blow up is to get off on it.
What?
This is awful.
Thank you, Jason, for bringing inflation stuff to our desk today.
I assume you then take the inflated cartoon character and like put it on your dick.
That's what it is?
I guess.
I don't know.
I don't know that that's a part of it.
Jason says it's not and he's an expert on this.
Jason, the inflation stuff expert.
You just look at the thing and inflate it.
He knows.
He's pretending he doesn't know.
It's not my thing.
But he knows.
He clearly knows.
It's not my thing.
Yeah, right.
Bullshit.
The more he says it's not my thing.
I think it's making them real big and occasionally popping.
Oh, it's the popping that's the...
This is what we're missing.
That might be an element.
This is part of it.
This is like how every snowflake is different, you know?
No two snowflakes are the same.
What?
It is?
Yeah, people...
No one has the same exact fetish.
You think different inflatable people like a different element of the inflatable thing.
Yes, exactly.
Some might not care about the popping.
Right.
Some might just like to see it.
No, it's funny.
The popping's not part of it for me.
It's too aggressive.
I agree.
I love the character.
They're my guy.
I don't want to see them pop.
So maybe this is why they had to shut to the state fair thing, the Mickey inflation celebration
down, because people are getting too horny watching the show.
This thing, if I go in there, it has inflation stuff.
Was that Michael Eisner?
No, that was a leering inflation man trying to buy tickets.
I guess my theory is that Eisner wanted to do it because he's an inflation guy.
I don't know.
All right, for this fiscal year, my proposition, inflation stuff.
I'd like to see Pluto get really big.
Not because I want to see him pop, I just want to see him get big.
Make it very clear.
Not into them popping.
I'd just like to see him bigger than normal.
Wow, inflation stuff.
All right, now segue us back.
Now we're ready.
They were inflating a lot of balloons at the state fair promotion, right?
He's upset now.
Maybe.
Huh?
It's unfair to make Justin deal with this.
No, he's all right.
He knows Jason.
He's known Jason a long time.
He's familiar with all his different interests.
Well, where does that lead?
Here, this is a good reset.
Let's watch a commercial for the state fair.
Yes, thank you.
Here we go.
It's not the Ralph Swan, but it's a whole big musical number.
And there's a part, as often with videos, where I'm just going to have to explain it
and the listener won't understand it at first.
But there's one shot that stands out to me.
Oh, the state fair, the Disneyland, state fair's coming.
I know there's something special there for me.
Disneyland brings 50 great state fairs all into one.
It's a whole park full of fun and games with all the ingredients for nonstop surprises,
with daily pig races and a down-home state fair parade.
All this and Disneyland 2 every day.
Oh, the state fair, the Disneyland is something special, something special.
Something special, really special.
Yeah, that's that.
It kind of gives you an overview of the sort of stuff they had
and the vibe and the Americana of it all.
But what's jumped out at me is that the musical number is being led by, I mean, is it Burt?
I guess it's Burt-esque.
He's got the suit on.
Yeah, it's the jolly holiday-type mode of Mary Poppins Burt
with the red and white stripes and the hat.
And then that, if we're saying that's Burt,
then there's a weird part where he is holding a bowl of chili with a ribbon on it.
And he's making a, and steam, only just now have I realized
maybe they're conveying that steam is coming out of the heat.
Yeah, it's hot chili.
And he's making a face like, yeah, yikes, hot, hot chili.
Burt can't, I live in England.
I don't know from spice.
I don't know.
How do you do this?
The food is bland there, yeah.
You put this kind of thing down, you shovel this kind of thing down your mouth, do you?
He also is dressed like Professor Harold Hill from The Music Man.
That's what I think they were going for.
Yeah, that song is the Wells Fargo wagon song from The Music Man.
A number that I don't think Harold Hill is in.
Which upsets you, because it's not accurate.
Well, no, that's the big song.
That's child Ron Howard's big song.
Okay.
I'm just saying, do you like the mixing of Music Man, like iconography?
I do like it.
I feel like a lot of the state fair music is just in the parade, especially.
It's just production numbers of the music played on Main Street nowadays, like the instrumental music.
Yeah, there's different types of state fair things going on.
It's not all sort of in the same Hello Dolly Music Man era.
Unfortunately for Jason, it is not all set in 1906.
Yes.
But a lot is, and I feel like the parade very much so.
That's a big part of it.
Maybe this has something to do with the chili being in the commercial.
But the state fair was the first time that I ever remember food being a big deal at Disneyland.
Seasonal offerings just for the special event, something that's very commonplace now, and they really push.
We do really polished photos.
You've got to come here for these months because you're going to get this thing.
You're right.
This might be the first time that was ever done.
Getting that chili was a thing.
You remember getting the chili.
Oh, very much so.
Oh, really?
Maybe we felt like we had to because of the commercial, but I remember it being a big deal.
It was made out of buffalo meat, which was this mind-blowing thing at the time.
I remember my family discussing if it was actual buffalo.
I feel like it's in the commercial for a reason.
The pies, I remember the pies being a big thing.
I think single-slice pies suddenly were available.
I don't know if it was just one place or all over the park.
Well, they had booths set up, so the areas that wouldn't be really themed like Tomorrowland.
That's a tough thing to marry.
There would be a booth with pies and maybe some carnival games and stuff.
Once again, Jason, this is a time where you could just grab slices of pie handily no matter where you are, even in Tomorrowland.
Well, you've got to wash down your chili with something.
It's funny because a lot of his stuff does look very fun, but also a lot of it is this chintzy, corny shit that Walt hated.
I wouldn't say a lot.
I can't believe Jason's mad at this.
No, I'm not mad at it. I'm just giving the other side.
The other side where it's shit. It's fucking shit. Fuck it.
They did have two Ferris wheels, but the way that they were presented and the places that they were, it felt not obtrusive.
Right, they were on the railroad tracks?
One of the years.
That's part of this, why he's upset. It's because they were blocking the railroad tracks.
It shut down because of Splash Mountain construction.
Oh, they weren't running the train?
At least one of the years.
Interesting. So you would use the train station as a line for a Ferris wheel.
Yeah, that's the one in the front of the park.
So you're looking at the parking lot on that thing. That's on the other side. Interesting.
And then there was one right in front of the castle?
One year, and then the other year it was over by the rivers.
Two Ferris wheels. I saw people online saying that they felt like this was another, in addition to his inflation interests, that Eisner was determined, hell or high water, to get a Ferris wheel into the park somehow.
Two of them he got. So when ultimately California Adventure happens and you have your big permanent Ferris wheel with several names that it's had, people theorize that Eisner really was dying for a Ferris wheel forever.
I think the Ferris wheels were at most of these events. I think they were also at the circus.
Oh, really? I think they were, oh yeah, the circus. I don't think they were a blast to the past, but I can't remember. I can't remember seeing them in any of the videos.
They'd have a big record on it.
Were you ever there when blast to the past with John Bowser Bowman from shenanah?
No, I think I would have remembered that because I was a huge shenanah fan.
Or you. Oh man, we should have had you on the first one too.
We were baffled by it. We didn't understand this guy, his appeal. We watched a special where he's telling us about the blast to the past event and it's full of all these weird monologue jokes.
Remember the lunch ladies? They look like they stink.
I couldn't tell you why, but I remember as a kid watching shenanah and really being drawn to Bowser.
His Charisma Ice pose? I don't know.
Yeah, they picked up some of the Happy Days shine too, I feel like.
And recently I've been watching him out of the character as the host of Hollywood Squares and Match Game. They've been airing that era on Pluto.
Oh right. Yeah, they have a full Hollywood Squares channel. When was he a regular? He wasn't Bowser on it?
No, he was the host of Hollywood Squares and he was out of the Bowser character.
Whoa. Weird. Does he have like a crazy different, like an Englishman or something? Does he have a crazy different voice?
Not quite, but it's definitely like weird. Like I didn't recognize him. So it is a real put on, the voice.
Oh yeah. Like yeah. Huh. Yeah, Bowser was a gimmick.
Yeah, I knew it was a gimmick. I just didn't know how much of a gimmick.
Like I knew they were like a comedy act also in addition to a 50s revival act.
And also they ended up playing Woodstock because Hendrix was like a big fan.
That's why? Yeah. What? Why?
Part of him doing Woodstock was he had to book Sha Na Na.
Is Sha Na Na in the Demetri Martin movie about Woodstock?
Yeah, taking Woodstock. Taking Woodstock.
Well, look it up and see if Sha Na Na is in there.
I'm going to have to ask my mom because I feel like maybe we did that and I forgot.
Because going to Disneyland to see Bowser definitely feels like something I would have done as a kid.
I just don't know how often he was there because he was, yeah, using the promotional material for that.
We might have done a show with some kind too.
Because like Viral was at Knott's all the time in Halloween season.
I feel like Batman was a viral level celebrity.
You know, you could get him down for a few.
I got nothing going on.
Even as a kid though, that whole thing felt like it was trying to capitalize on Back to the Future.
Which I didn't appreciate.
Yeah, suddenly like there's a new angle.
There's a cool current thing with a lot of 50s stuff in it.
Yeah, that's an underrated part of why all that 50s.
Yeah, I didn't even think about that.
This ad for State Fair, we're talking about pies.
This ad is so good and kind of creepy and is so Knott's Berry Farm.
Yeah, well it's very Norman Rockwell.
Here, let's describe some aspects of this.
I have this too.
It's a drawing, but a drawing of Mickey, Minnie, and Goofy as they're suited in park characters.
Yes, and Mickey looks sharp.
Plaid, bandana, denim overalls.
Minnie looks lovely.
Beautiful, yes.
Well, what a bonnet.
And what kind of pattern would you say is on her dress?
I don't know, it looks almost like a picnic, like a cloth that you put on for having a picnic.
Gingham?
Is that what that's called?
A white something, but she's wearing kind of a little dress and a little hat.
And then Goofy is wearing a drum major outfit or a marching band outfit.
He's a music man again.
Yeah, he's got a conductor's wand, and he's got his arms in the air.
And Mickey and Minnie are holding a pie toward the viewer of this ad.
This feels like if you were at Knott's Berry Farm, you'd be pissed that they were infringing on your territory.
Yeah, it's that hominess.
Yeah, how much the whole thing feels like it, and just that the pie is like the thing they're presenting to the...
That's true, yeah, the Disneyland's all about pies for this stretch of time.
I would be furious if I were like, what the hell is this shit?
All we have is pies at Knott's Berry Farm.
They have all the good stuff and the characters, and here they come trying to take our market share.
Yeah, they already stole the idea of doing a teen nightclub, and they plussed it up by being less tolerant.
Right, yes.
To me, this feels like Ruthless Eisner, like kind of a Ruthless Eisner.
That is another thing I remember about this time period, is we always had to get out of there before nighttime because of the teens coming.
To Minneapolis? Wave, interesting. Oh, wow, wow.
Do you remember being interested in going, like, oh, if I was only a little older, I could go to Minneapolis.
Not at all, and I remember my mom making it out to be a very scary thing because teenagers were scary.
So no, we had to get out of there.
There's drugs, there's alcohol, there's inflation stuff, you don't want to go near this.
Don't want to go near it, although now you just give them an iPad, and they were all iPad kids, so you can kind of trick them.
Well, you could just have a couple iPads on you.
Yeah, just some old ones, yeah.
Can I say one more thing about this poster?
I'm stealing this from a Reddit comment, but somebody posted this, nostalgic for this event, and then in the comments somebody said,
boy, Minnie looks like she's seen some shit.
And you've got to look closely to see, but Mickey is definitely, he's looking at us, can't wait to see you, and she just looks like she's trying to hold it together.
Yeah, she's staring into the middle distance or whatever.
Why is she staring here?
She watched, earlier that day, she saw somebody get crushed in the gears of the Ferris wheel.
And then like, I don't know if I can do the photo shoots.
And she's like, you hold it together, okay?
The photographer is coming.
You have to do this in Zara Park.
You put on a brave face.
She saw Michael Eisner kill a buffalo and put it into the chiller.
He likes like Gus Fring style and Breaking Bad sliced the throat.
Come this way.
The buffalo habitat is just a few more steps.
It's just right through this tube.
Minnie, you didn't see anything.
Minnie, you saw nothing.
Shut your mouth.
Keep your mouth shut.
She got splattered by buffalo innards.
Come over here.
I'll wipe the entrails off of your snoot.
Don't talk about this.
Aren't you scared?
Aren't you freaked out by this goof?
Look, I'm here to do a job.
I don't ask questions.
So yeah, this lists the things that you could do there.
And I don't know.
Do you have any recollection of Justin's image?
No.
Yeah, that doesn't jump out at me.
But I would like a poster of this.
This is how much I like this image.
It's really good.
I also like that something I get nostalgic for,
I don't do it as much anymore,
but there was a while where I was buying a lot of like 80s magazines.
I mean, I own a lot of the Disney magazines from them,
but there was like LA Magazine and Orange Coast.
Did you ever have Orange Coast magazine?
Or the events that are happening this week
and listings of every bar and restaurant.
And yeah, I used to buy a lot of, I don't know,
maybe Bea Arthur's on the cover.
You get to see her vacation condo in Corona Del Mar.
But I would buy these magazines.
And something I always liked is like the sheer volume of copy
that like now ads have no words.
And it used to be like, pull up a chair.
I got five paragraphs for you.
But I find it very relaxed.
It really takes me back to the 88
and you're looking at the dense copy.
Right.
There's like four paragraphs, five paragraphs,
four paragraphs here.
Yeah.
The state you want to be in, it says.
And so the idea, they said in that commercial,
but it was like, we're combining the best
of all the state fairs in the country.
50 state fairs rolled into one.
Yeah.
And the different like things would also say like
which state they were from.
And I remember there was either like a sticker
or something from each state.
Yeah, these.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they would sell, did you know that they would sell these?
These are stickers that have like characters on them
and then list like Minnesota and Donald has an ax,
I assume to chop down a tree.
Well, I saw that every, people would get them
when your car parked in a lot that would give you a sticker.
Oh, okay.
There was a different one like each day
to get people to come back to collect the stickers.
Yeah, and then some kids would like stand on Main Street,
like trading them.
Yeah.
Like they were trading.
Like the toy thing they did.
Like an early pin trade.
Right, yep.
Yeah.
That's cool.
I feel like there was something like that
for each one of the events.
Yeah, there was some sort of like collectible element to it.
Oh, and it's too bad that some of these
have Mickey doing things culturally
that he should not be doing.
Wearing clothes that, also there's one, the Texas one,
is it Mickey with a bandana over his face
holding two pistols?
Oh, I'm not seeing that one.
I think he's being like a Yosemite Sam.
They're stealing knots,
now he's stealing Yosemite Sam schtick.
Yeah, I just Googled Disneyland State Fair stickers,
and some are nice.
So like South Dakota, it's a Mount Rushmore
with our characters on it.
And then Wisconsin Mini's got butter urns.
What are butter urns?
A churn?
Yeah, a churn must be in my head,
but it can't be an urn, is it?
Jars, what do you put butter in when it's done?
The whole butter holder?
But both Texas and Wyoming,
Mickey is holding two different types of guns.
Really?
I'm trying to find out.
And then New York, Jason would like the New York one,
where he's like an old time chappy.
He's in a pinstripe suit and a bowler hat.
With like a bowler hat, yeah.
It's a little surprising for California,
he's the Zodiac Killer.
He's got a bag over his head.
Wait, John Wayne, he's the John Wayne Gacy clown?
What the fuck?
A different event I think you're looking at.
Oh, yeah.
In the mid-90s.
Illinois, he's Al Capone?
He's throwing his enemies in a river?
Poor Chippendale.
Oh, for New Jersey, he's the devil impregnating a woman
to create his cursed spawn?
Why is he that?
Jersey Devil?
Jersey Devil.
Oh, okay.
Look, I'm looking at some nice ones.
Goofy's bundled up because he's in Alaska.
Oh, that's nice.
Ship sold in the Georgia peach.
Idaho, Donald's relaxing next to a giant potato,
and he has a big old gut.
He ate a lot of potatoes.
He looks like he's pregnant.
Yeah.
It is an interesting drawing.
Or has he been inflated?
Oh, no.
Inflation stuff.
That's a lateral move to, I believe the term is impreg stuff
with a pregnant Sonic.
I believe.
I'll fool them if I say I'm not sure.
I don't want to seem like I miss you.
I don't want to seem like I'm disrespectful,
but I've definitely seen pregnant Shrek, pregnant Sonic.
And that's a sex thing.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
And is it just you look at it, or is there other stuff?
I don't know.
Don't even have to, yeah.
I don't know the mechanics.
I don't believe you, but we'll go through
because we already did too much on this.
This is like they still do like little stuff sometimes,
but it's like your annual pass holders go out
and they get like maybe a magnet once in a while.
But none of the magnets are Mickey shooting two guns in the air.
None of the magnets are that.
This is the time.
Yeah.
Do you remember having any of these?
Yeah, I think I still have one with Goofy on it.
I'm not sure which one.
There's a Montana Goofy.
It's so lazy.
It's just his big face and he's got a cowboy hat.
I think that's the one I have.
Is that the one?
Wow, wow.
But they couldn't think of an activity.
They couldn't think of like an action that is Montana.
We ran out of time.
Well, he's the governor inspired Yellowstone, you know.
Inspired later season plots.
There's like a lot of stuff online on eBay.
There's like hats that they had, like kind of cowboyish hats.
I did bring my State Fairer 87 button.
Oh.
Wow.
Yeah, there it is.
That looks nice.
There's a good logo, good bold.
Yeah.
Blue ribbons on here.
Like this poster.
Let's see if I can get a bigger version.
And the Ferris wheel square in the middle of the logo.
Wow.
The castle pushed to the side.
Yes.
Get out of here, Matterhorn.
He's never hated a castle.
He wanted to replace it with a Ferris wheel.
The Ferris wheel is given prominence.
It is up there with the castle and the Matterhorn.
It is an equal partner.
Yeah, he was pushing it.
This poster I found, that's like a really well-produced piece of art for this thing.
You can feel the effort that was put into this event.
Yeah, especially I feel like this event, they did a lot of this stuff for the other events,
but this one felt like it had a little bit more than the other stuff.
Yes, I would agree with that.
We haven't even listed yet all the stuff that was there.
So we were talking about the Main Street area was more like Hello Dolly Music Man,
but then over in New Orleans Square there was a bunch of hillbilly nonsense.
And over at Videopolis there were like 80s...
The hillbilly stuff was more like Big Thunder Ranch,
where New Orleans Square was more of the lumberjack stuff.
Rivers of America had guys trying to balance on logs and stuff,
and then they'd fall into the river.
And then log climbing competitions too?
Yeah, it was like a 20-minute to half-hour show that they would do a bunch of times a day on the Rivers of America.
It had the competition between the lumberjacks, but it also had built-in bits and comedy things.
It also had a band that was a different band from the pig races, which we'll get to.
Captain Mike and the Cavalry Band, and I believe they're all dressed like Confederate soldiers.
Good!
Maybe they're Union, I don't know. The footage isn't so good.
But they seem like Confederates to me.
Yeah. You know, all 50 states were represented.
So two families, I think it's the Aikens and the Barkers, maybe?
Yes.
And they were competing for a bag of gold.
So they would send a member of each family to compete in the different events.
One was climbing the big pole, one was out in the rivers running on...
What do you call that?
Log rolling?
Yes, log rolling.
Log rolling, and they would both be on a log, and whoever fell first lost.
And this is wild. This one in particular, I think, is one of the wildest things to me.
You could just see people in the middle of the rivers falling into it off of a log.
Oh yeah, and doing bits on the logs.
I don't know why I remember this.
This must have been one of my earliest exposures to improv comedy.
But I remember we had just had a big earthquake in Norwalk.
And I was watching the Lumberjack show, and the emcee was doing crowd work across the rivers of America.
And he was asking people where they were from, and someone yelled out, Norwalk.
And the guys on the logs did a bit where they acted all shaky because there had just been an earthquake.
And I still remember that to this day, being impressed with that level of crowd work.
And that you could go to Disneyland and hear something referred to that happened this month.
Yeah, a topical joke.
But I feel like that was more common at Disneyland at the time.
And especially the State Fair had so many shows like this.
Because you had that plus the pig racing, plus there was a diving show.
And then there was a show on the train tracks in critter country.
It was bear country at the time.
With robbers and cowboys.
Really? I didn't find that.
So there was stuff all over the place.
The all-star dive show was in front of Small World, I guess.
Which is wild.
The amount of stuff.
But yeah, we've said this many times, a lot of the live performer stuff is what you end up remembering.
Especially if you're a kid.
But I've said this, the stormtroopers hassling people in Tomorrowland is stuff I love.
And I feel like that stuff, it's so much more fun when you get tapped on the shoulder and the stormtroopers are behind you.
That stuff you remember more.
I was definitely more into the shows at Disneyland when I was a little kid than the rides.
I was a scared little kid.
So I didn't love dark rides.
You had this mix of shows with live performers and then you also had America Sings and Country Bears.
And that was the stuff I was always more drawn to.
That's a different perspective.
Yeah, I guess especially then.
It was sort of a more show environment.
It wasn't until Star Tours opened that I actually loved a ride.
Oh wow. Makes sense.
Real quick, I think Scott will be extra.
We're all going to be excited about this.
And maybe you've found this already.
But there's a clip of Miss California from 1988 with the California Secretary of State sort of doing a little speech at Disneyland during State Fair.
I don't know if you found this or not.
And somebody makes an appearance.
A specific version of someone makes an appearance, I believe, during this.
So if it's not cued up, here we go.
Welcome you to this momentous occasion as we honor the state of California.
Welcome to Disneyland.
I'm sure Mickey and Roger will agree it is a pleasure to have you with us.
Right, Roger?
It's me, the wrong one.
It's the wrong, weird Mickey voice.
This is what we're doing.
We are comfortable having Mickey.
Our biggest character sounds like this when you come meet him.
Prime spot for Roger.
You forget Roger Rabbit was on the level as Mickey back then.
They clearly rushed to miss.
That must have been because the movie comes out in 88.
So by the 88 version, they're pushing Roger in the TV ads, in the parades and stuff.
I feel like maybe right before that they mentioned our brand new character.
Welcome our new guy to Disneyland, Roger Rabbit.
They make a big deal out of Roger.
I remember it being a big deal.
I don't feel like, even though that was the beginning of the renaissance of Disney animation,
he wouldn't see new characters in the park that often.
Yeah, it wouldn't be a quick thing like that.
And they went all in pretty quickly too.
Yes.
But now I think they would, it would take three and a half years.
And they try to make that, you got to come back to the park.
I mean, I don't know who it would be now, but that's how long it takes at this point to just get a new suit.
I would love it if they did a poochy kind of character of like our new character.
I think they were maybe like back to our piloting the wishing star from Wish.
And then that didn't really take off.
There's a character that's a gag in Runaway Railway, the little chirpy bird at the end.
Oh, right.
And they sell stuffed animals and that's like, I feel like a joke in that.
What you might miss is like, oh, it's our new character.
Yeah, but they're not pushing the chirpy bird like he's Roger Rabbit.
No, they're not pushing the chirpy bird and the star that you wish on did not really catch on.
Yeah, Sean do type like from Sinbad where it's like a cute character.
And maybe this will maybe it could turn into like a parks fun parks character.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's speaking of like so the original characters, there are I don't know if I should go here first.
Let's let's go back to the cannonball guy because the cannonball guy is a character with a name.
I don't know if you found this. Yes.
Captain Zoom is the name of the guy who would get shot out of a cannon on Main Street.
OK. And was it the same name for each of the events?
I don't know the answer, but there was a whole intro on Main Street with Captain Zoom.
There would be like there's a so you can see here in this in this YouTube video, there's a big banner that says Captain Zoom.
And then a guy would come down the street in the like Burt outfit.
So it's probably like the same whether it's the same actual performer, but it's same character as from your commercial.
OK, yeah. And he would do a little spiel introducing Captain Zoom.
And I don't know that any of this is particularly good, but I'll play it just so.
And the grace of the cosmos, so it's in God's hands now is what he's saying.
The cosmos is feeling graceful today.
And then I find this footage hilarious and scary.
Like he really honest to God shoots himself out of a cannon down Main Street.
And this is happening. Did you see this live? Oh, absolutely.
It's insane. They built the Spider-Man animatronic, you know, that does a less impressive thing in Avengers Canvas.
But they had a human doing this multiple times a day.
And this was like a level up from when he did it during the circus, because for the circus, I think it was over the rivers of America.
And now this is over cement on Main Street.
He could be kept in splat. So this footage is so crazy to me.
I loved this as a kid.
Listeners, you're going to hear a human cannonball.
Oh, fuck. Oh, yeah. Why would you show us that? Oh, yeah.
He exploded like a big bag of blood. Yeah.
I can't finish the episode. I got to go puke.
Come on. Like so mean. Very high.
Yes, it's crazy. And lands in a net. Yeah.
But it was like they're talking about now are like all these different like drone rules and stuff.
They can't fly the drones over the heads of people.
They were shooting guys out of cannon. They were shooting guys out of fucking cannons.
Guys, they can do it. Yeah. Guy's fine. Guy is fine.
He signs his life right away. But a little robot is too is too scary or too dangerous.
So, yeah, Captain Zoom would do this.
And, yeah, I don't know if it was always Captain Zoom or there was a different thing.
I don't know if Disney owns Captain Zoom or this was this guy's gimmick.
I guess we should look into. I would assume Disney owns Captain Zoom.
So they just found a cannonball guy.
Well, yeah, back then, I'm sure it was a lot easier to find a human cannonball than it is today.
It was like it was a family tradition. Maybe people were doing it.
It was it was people's livelihood in the 30s.
And then like they trained their son and their son. Right.
It was a trade. Maybe a daughter. You know what?
Hey, first female. There was a lot of death death defying going on at these events.
Wow. Like, yeah, what else would like?
Was there anything like the high high divers also? Oh, sure. Very scary.
The log climbing. I saw a video of the log climbing with the coming down because you want to pick up speed.
You got to climb up and ring a bell.
So but then if you allow yourself to just kind of essentially free fall down that thing, you can win a little easier.
But that what cost that looks so scary. Yeah. Yeah.
So yeah. And I guess the bike stuff was a little scary, but not as bad. Yeah.
I will say that the I mean, I guess we should talk about it.
There was a goofy suited character that would do like BMX tricks.
Oh, yeah. There was a BMX. I forgot about this because like just not interesting to me.
There was a BMX trick show at Videopolis.
Yeah. This may have come up a little bit when we talked about Videopolis many, many years ago.
I don't I don't really remember. Yeah.
But it was I don't maybe I didn't connect the dots that it was for the state fair because it doesn't have the vibe of the rest of the state fair.
Exactly. I think it's notable for its name.
Wizards of Rad. Wizards of Rad.
And this was during a point in time where I feel like most of the Southern California theme parks had something like this.
Yeah, Nott's had like bike guys. Yeah, Nott's had it and SeaWorld had one.
Oh, wow. Very odd.
Like everyone had like a pre-extreme sports like BMX skateboarding type event or show at some point.
Yeah, it's like that's what kids were into.
So we got to get them. They've got to get the bikes there.
Well, I also what I liked from the show is that the what song are they playing?
Oh, it's You Can Fly, but a new lyric.
But yeah, a rock version of it performed by a live band that was always that had to be there singing the song live.
I don't think they're doing that these days.
No. But yeah, a rockified You Can Fly, you know, like bikes do.
They fly briefly.
And it's long. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a long version of the song.
They solo and they shred.
I'm just going to play the one, the little like lyric amending that I like.
I think it's cute upright.
Let's do the limit. Break out.
I suddenly like this song. I like a Peter Pan song now.
He's also like it's like supposed to be a rock version, but he's very lounge singing.
He's a lounge guy as well.
And like it's so it's a funny mix.
And they're like, you got it.
I'm kind of like Poison Meets Melt Torme.
Right. So they had a Jason thing.
They had a live band there and then a live band at the Rivers of America and at the Pig Races.
So much live music.
Tomorrowland and in Main Street.
So you have five live bands.
I do. I legitimately it's upsetting to me that they don't do this level of live entertainment anymore.
And they'll never go back to what I'm assuming.
I mean, some of this is how would they ever approve any of this now?
But even for something that's like synergistic with a movie, I just think it's never going to happen on this scale ever again.
I mean, I was complaining about Pixar Fest this year not being to the level of Donald's Quacky Duck City in Tokyo.
But this is this blows everything else out of the water as far as stuff you would go like original unique stuff.
And this and it's this kind of thing that is why this podcast remains proudly pro Eisner.
That's right. This thing.
This decision that has been made that he ruined the company.
And I'll look at this. Look what.
Look what happened. Right.
It's just one of the many that there are so many odd things like this.
Not even counting all the new shit he added and then attractions and hotels.
Right. Bob Iger does not approve confusing things.
And that is the problem.
That's right. It may all makes too much sense.
It makes perfect corporate sense.
Michael Eisner, you throw some weirdness at him and go to state fair.
But there's BMX bikes and also there's a hillbilly pig show.
Yeah. OK. That sounds great.
Sign off on it.
This is before PowerPoint presentations, you know, this before you had to present all your ideas with slides.
You would have to verbally do saying you could get verbally.
You think Eisner would have approved the slides in the 1980s.
But there was slides.
Overhead projector.
But that's so expensive.
Yeah. Overhead projector.
Disney couldn't afford some overhead projector.
I feel like these came so fast and furious.
These events like one after the other that they had to even though they were impressive,
they had to be kind of slapped together.
Yeah. Yeah.
In order to happen.
Sure.
They had to be planning the next one as the other one was happening.
Yeah. And then some of these like back blast to blast to the past.
I can remember.
It is kind of not the phrase.
These are both in 88.
But like there's an overlap.
I was reading that.
Yeah.
88 were the two big years.
So like there's stuff constantly happening.
At the same time that you have Star Tours is brand new.
Captain EO is brand new.
More new.
They're building Splash Moon.
What a time.
This was a time.
Yeah.
It was very, very exciting.
I'm so curious what like just your Tony Baxter.
Obviously he's working in Star Tours.
But what did that core top level Imagineer think about some of these events?
Which were seemingly slapped together.
I wonder if they didn't like it.
I wonder if they felt like if it felt.
That's what I'm getting at.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because money was definitely spent.
Yes.
Like money had to have been going here instead of creating new attractions.
Right.
But at the same time, like Scott just said, like we were in this run of big attractions.
Maybe you'd be in support of the theory behind it.
But maybe think some of the execution was gen Z.
That's yeah.
I wonder.
Because yeah.
You don't.
Yeah.
You hear all the big Imagineers talk about the big projects.
But I'm always curious about what like what department did this stuff?
And do they have any input in it whatsoever?
And were they like there's a big Ferris wheel in the middle?
This like I'm assuming some of them weren't pleased with some of the choices.
But I guess it's temporary.
And maybe they didn't care so much.
I don't know.
Well, have we talked about the notion, the theory that's out there that maybe we've said this some episode long ago.
But that the Ferris wheel, I think people really hated the Ferris wheel being in the hub and blocking the castle.
Yeah.
And and then that was not the case the next year.
And I think they even I forget what was there for circus.
They kept these these events.
I think nobody like motorcycles were there for the circus.
Oh, it was motorcycle.
OK.
Well, yeah, I think people thought that was really silly and people in the company.
And the theory is that the partners statue, the Walt and Mickey statue was built as a permanent thing that you can't move so that they can't put a bunch of bullshit.
You can't have sumo suit wrestling for an entire summer in the middle and blocking the castle.
What was funny with these events, though, is it was almost like you weren't there for Disneyland.
Like you were there for the events, like especially like with my family in particular, like my mom had a very specific way that she liked me to experience Disneyland when we went,
which was going down Main Street, crossing the drawbridge, going through the castle.
You had to do it in that order.
Interesting.
Before you do anything else, you had to go over the drawbridge and through that castle.
And then we would do the Fantasyland rides and then we would take the Skyway to Tomorrowland and do America Sings and that stuff and then walk across to Adventureland and then Tom Sawyer's Island and then Bear Country.
Right.
And then get out of there before the teenagers came.
At the end of the day, a mad dash.
Yes.
But for these special events, like that was off the table.
Wow. Oh, then you broke the rules.
It was all about these events.
It was all about getting that like schedule at the beginning of the day with, okay, we're going to see the pig races at this time.
We're going to see the lumberjacks at this time.
We're going to do this, this and that, try the pie, try the chili.
Like so it was almost like we weren't at Disneyland.
That was kind of a secondary thing.
That was fun.
Like when we did that throwback night a couple of years ago, even though that was still like on brand Disney, it is interesting how just changing some of the music and changing a few things about it really does mess with like your normal Disneyland day.
Like I could see all this new stuff just being thrown around and like you go like, well, it's this is a different thing.
They've really, they've really changed.
We were there to experience that, to go to the state fair, to go to the circus, to see the blast to the past stuff.
Thumper's Easter.
You mentioned this before we started recording.
What was Thumper's Easter?
It was like an Easter egg hunt.
And, you know, the Easter bunny was there and it was very lightly themed.
It wasn't like all over the park.
Though I think maybe the Easter egg hunt.
Well, like there was a real physical Easter egg hunt and then a sticker thing.
Is there footage?
I believe that only happened once.
Okay.
And then the other limited time events that I remember going to, which was the only one that I was very disappointed in, was the Disney afternoon.
Oh, really?
Oh, I loved it.
Maybe I was just the right age.
I would like whatever they gave me.
But at the tip, those ride overlays and inflatable stuff.
I like that balloon.
I like those big, it had such a, I mean, my love of like, you know, 80s purples and teals is very influenced by those big inflatable tubes that ran through the small world.
I did love the ride overlays, like the boat overlay with the gummy bears I loved.
But I just remember hearing that they were building Duckburg and I would be able to go to Duckburg.
And when I got there, seeing Duckburg and just being so disappointed.
Yeah.
That wasn't very good.
That was like flats.
Yeah, if you're, I see what you're saying.
You know what?
I was, like the slight age differences make it such that I was not, DuckTales was not my show.
Like the, it's so, the micro micro, like because what it was DuckTales and then Chip and Dale and then Darkwing, like those are so much more my show.
So maybe I wasn't as offended by the lack of inaccurate depiction of Duckburg.
But if DuckTales is your molten core, that makes sense.
I wonder if this is a syndication thing because I watched hours of DuckTales.
And we're like.
I did too.
I just don't, it wasn't like mine.
Oh, well wasn't your, yeah, yeah.
The other ones did come later.
I'd also seen in like magazines what was going on in Orlando with Mickey's birthday.
Oh yeah.
Oh, Mickey's birthday.
Yeah.
And the DuckTale integration there.
It wasn't as good.
It wasn't that good.
I, but to me, like.
It looked.
Just seeing it in the magazine.
It looked great.
And I was expecting something on that level and I felt like it wasn't even on that level.
It was bigger.
I agree.
It's not.
Yeah.
It was kind of chintzy on the general scale, but bigger.
I remember feeling that way.
Seeing it.
Cause I was like the, the idea that you would go see the money bin obviously was very exciting,
but it was not giant.
It was not yet to the, to the correct scale.
I mean, I felt the same way about birthday land when I would see pictures of Toontown
in Disneyland, which I would.
Gotcha.
And I would be like, oh, well that's amazing.
Oh, this is okay.
Like there's a less good.
It's less.
There was also like some of this limited time stuff.
You would wonder why they didn't just keep it.
Like why not keep the cutouts of the gummy bears in the boat ride?
No, sure.
Yeah.
Why are you.
The boat ride was nothing.
De-theming.
That's a ride.
We've never done an episode about motorboat cruise, right?
That's a dry one, I think.
Oh, that.
I'm so mad I didn't get to ride the dry.
That's so funny.
Mike and I are both like.
Boring motorboat cruise.
Jason's like, I know.
It tears me up we haven't done an episode.
Let alone the gummy bears version.
When we do our stressful pitch meetings of what episodes Jason stands.
Oh, at any time there's one where it's like, oh, that's a little dry.
That's a little boring.
I'm like licking my chops.
So I'm like, let me at it.
Let me.
I love the motorboats when I was a kid.
It's a parking lot tram.
It's exciting.
Michael, Scott, Scotrick.
I stand today again and say motorboat cruise should be.
Where did you get Scotrick from?
Why did you dress up my name?
That's your official, that's your legal name.
He's found an overhead projector.
At much expense.
Talking about Thumper's Easter.
I don't know out here on the West Coast.
I mean, I'm assuming it aired everywhere, but I remember growing up.
The Disney Easter parade.
Special was as big as the Disney Christmas parade.
And so we would have to tape it before we went to church or like catch it.
Before we left or whatever.
But and I don't know when that went away, but they would do the full.
You know, parade with the top hats and you know, the Hello Dolly stuff.
Yeah.
So many.
There wasn't room on Main Street.
All of it was filled with wide petticoats.
Speaking of the Christmas parade, the Christmas stuff was the one thing I never saw.
Because as a local, like you stayed away from Disneyland during the holidays.
So like I don't remember going to Disneyland and seeing Christmas stuff until I was like a teenager.
Right.
Wow.
And then like, yeah, they didn't do Halloween on the level they do now.
They didn't do Halloween at all.
Like I think this was I think the state fair was kind of during that around that time.
Yeah, maybe.
I wonder when they first tried like they first did like a pump Mickey pumpkin.
Like I don't remember any sort of Halloween stuff at the parks growing up.
The first time I remember like you would go to Knott's Berry Farm for Halloween.
Right.
That was the thing.
Wow.
And then I remember.
The creator of the haunt.
When Horror Nights started at Universal and like Penn and Teller being there.
Oh, wow.
And also as a scared kid, like I didn't want to go to any Halloween stuff.
Yeah, yeah, right.
And the Disney version was a little too intense.
Yes.
Can I play a little bit?
I just want to zoom through this actual parade, the state fair parade.
Yeah.
Just get a get a sense of the song and then get a sense of some of these characters I've never seen before and have not seen since.
I assume you guys saw a little of this.
Oh, yeah.
But this is just a little bit of like the music you would hear.
And like this is yeah, this is from 1988.
Appetite for Destruction came out a year prior.
I always like to think about kids are like into Guns N' Roses, but they're going to see this in 1988.
State Fair.
And then maybe you have a song from Meet Me in St. Louis.
But yeah, a bunch of like straw hats and like, I don't know how you would describe it, like Bert from like Mary Poppins style jackets, green blues.
The white suits.
Yeah.
And just this was a huge parade.
Huge.
There are so many floats and people and performers.
And just like a couple of weeks before this, they would have been playing like fifties television characters in The Blast of the Past.
Greasers were just they traded their greaser outfit.
They went back.
They went 50 years before The Blast of the Past.
And then a couple of months before that, they would have been like lion tamers or whatever in the circus parade.
Right.
It's wild.
Show your chops.
And it's not like anything is so like crazy impressive expensive, but it's like just a tractor coming down Main Street.
And there are weird scarecrow guys and weird crows and they don't look like Disney characters that I've seen before.
They got all those.
I was just saying they look like they look vaguely like the scarecrow from Return to Oz.
Yeah, vaguely.
But they don't think they had.
Did they have Return to Oz ever in the parks?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
But I'm just like, oh, these suits seem like they might have been created for this.
Well, then you got a whole original lineup of characters.
You got the vegetables.
Well, right.
Yes.
And that comes after this.
So you see these scary scarecrow type characters.
And I don't know if you saw these, Scott.
These these are very much like Raggedy Ann, Raggedy Andy style performances.
And they're dancing with crows that are also human size.
Right.
The scarecrow and the crows are getting along.
And then coming up behind.
So this is like a tractor.
I hate these crows.
Oh my God.
They're giant gaping mouths.
Yeah.
And now here come the vegetables.
There's a giant anthropomorphic carrot, tomato, broccoli with these big nose like floppy.
The broccoli boys.
Big floppy noses that look like they're inflatable noses that are just bouncing up and down.
And have you seen these characters ever in your life at Disneyland?
Where did these suits come from?
Did they?
I don't know.
Like the corn has like overalls to act like it's his whatever is what do you call the
outside of a corn husk.
Thank you.
And boy, it's just that's weird.
And then here come like Chip and Dale and aprons.
Like all of the costume characters like that had like different versions for each of these
events.
Right.
And then it's into it like 12 minute parade.
There's so much stuff they packed in here.
I don't mind the the broccoli boys and the vegetables.
I could say I could stand the vegetables hanging around.
Sure.
I'm not mad.
I'm I would be interested to see all of them.
I just wondered.
Hey, I think the tomatoes look cute.
Yeah, I agree.
Beautiful eyelashes.
Well, I mean, it looks beautiful.
Yeah.
A little sexy.
If you really want to be honest, you feel free.
I was complimenting.
Well, I'm just you know, like I'm talking about like, you know, weird tomato porn stuff.
That's what I'm thinking automatically.
I don't know, Jason.
Is there a tomato?
You're being weird.
You're a guy.
I'm normal.
I just said that her eyes sparkle.
Now here you are talking about tomato.
I knew what you meant.
I was reading your signals.
Now the pumpkin.
Hang on.
I don't.
The pumpkin seems like a real meanie.
Oh, yeah.
This staring must of the pumpkin will foreclose your house on you.
The Disney characters that get featured in this parade, the three little pigs are in there.
Sure.
Clara Kluck, I feel like is hanging out.
She's in a barn.
Yeah, she's in a barn.
In like the top of the barn.
Yeah.
I had to double check that name when I was watching the parade.
I was like, we chicken from old Disney.
OK, Clara Kluck.
And I believe one website about her referred to her as an old friend of Mickey's.
OK.
So I guess she was in some old shorts with them.
From before I was famous.
I keep her around.
I got to be nice.
The people you came up with.
We had a thing.
We had like a Nicholson Mather.
We dated for a while.
And then we were working together.
We were a comedy duo.
And then we kind of stayed friendly, but we're not as close as we used to be.
And then they just start bringing live animals down Main Street.
Oh, boy.
There are like these big pens or cribs that I think there's a cow and there's maybe a sheep in there.
There's maybe a pig in one of these, but I think there's a cow.
There's these weird.
I don't know how you even describe these.
I guess pens like fancy kind of fancy cages, fancy cages that are being dragged down Main Street with like sleeping and real life animals in them.
And then like more animals like Dopey is in a car being pulled by a mule, like a real life mule.
Dopey is behind the animal husband.
Right.
And there's there's like a human being like making sure the mule doesn't go out of control and run into the audience.
But then there's a goat just being like pulled down Main Street and horses.
And what what are these ox like oxen like oxen are coming down Main Street.
I didn't make it to the animal part.
These are notoriously cantankerous animals to be surrounded by people.
There's a bunch of them.
And we're six minutes into a 12 minute parade at this point.
So I like I was just like, this is wild.
And this is where Justin tells us that he was attacked by the angry ox spirit.
He had to recover for many years.
And this podcast takes a very serious turn.
Right.
They would let you pet the animals.
Like they were not like close by.
Yeah.
Like they were encouraging it.
Right.
And then we get to the part where you get an anthropomorphic box of sugar.
You get like a sugar box.
Weird.
And then like I think this is a milk bottle with eyes walking down.
I completely missed all this.
Who are these characters?
Where do they get all these?
These are the elements of the pie.
Right.
These are the pie ingredients walking down Main Street.
What's that one?
What's the bottle?
Vanilla.
Vanilla extract.
A bottle of vanilla extract with a big bow and gloves.
Now this, Jason, you have to admit, turns you on a little bit.
This feels like Jason's vibe, yes.
This is for all fair.
This is for private times.
This is just wild.
We're seven minutes in now and we have the ingredients for pies walking down Main Street.
Well, Jason doesn't want to hook up with any of them.
He wants them to all get in a big pile.
Because when these guys get in a polycule, the baby they make is a pie.
A polycule.
Polycule of, that's what you refer to in baking.
It's a molecule of ingredients.
Makes a delicious pie.
Jason's starting his own polycule that's all anthropomorphic pie ingredients.
Makes a lot of sense.
So yeah, okay, so yeah, we're going down and there's...
Is there a butter stick?
I don't, hold on.
This is, I don't know who that one was.
Who ran by.
He looked mischievous though.
There's a little, like in the Itchy and Scratchy parade where there's a little cute axe.
That's what that looked like.
Yeah.
It's one like scurrying behind.
There's flour, that's milk, that's vanilla.
And then what, is this salt or sugar?
Like the sugar was over here.
It's too far away and it's overexposed.
I don't know.
Yeah, that looks like a sugar bowl.
Maybe a dish of some kind, yeah.
So I don't, I'm just, yeah.
Yeah, and then there's a country bear representation here in like big floats.
And then I'm trying to see if there's any other real, like Donald shows up and I don't know.
This is wild.
And then like full like marching band style, like performers are coming down with and they perform with,
I don't know what you would call this.
People that perform with sticks in a marching band.
What do you call those performers?
Yeah, they got those marching sticks.
Then there's flag performers.
I like, this is more ambitious than any parade, even like Paint the Night.
Paint the Night has like, I feel like 10 performers in it and impressive floats.
This has like 200 performers.
And like that's a big reason why these events felt special.
Like all the performers, like it was kind of overwhelming.
Wow.
So like, yeah.
I didn't know the grandeur of this.
I had always heard they did a state fair thing in the end.
Yeah, I didn't know the scale.
We've only briefly mentioned the peak races.
We got to get there.
Yeah, that is the main event.
I mean, we can get there.
Believe me, we can get there.
We can do that right now because yes, back in Big Thunder Ranch, they were having an event called Pig Mania.
When I told my mom that I was coming on the show to talk about the state fair,
she immediately said, oh, the pig races.
I loved the pig races.
Like my family loved the pig races.
And it was another thing that I remember openly wondering like,
why is this not just here all the time?
Because there was nothing else going on back there.
This is before the barbecue restaurant.
Right, Big Thunder, whatever it was called.
Before whatever is there now.
What's that thing called?
I don't remember.
Galaxy's Edge?
Something like that.
Were the goats back there?
The goats were back there.
This is the first time I ever remember going back there.
It was for the pig races.
It's possible to know you didn't go to this.
If you're a kid and you don't go on Big Thunder, maybe you don't go back to that part of the park at all.
Exactly.
Yeah, because we would do Fantasyland and then Skyway over to Tomorrowland.
So I don't know if I ever went back there.
The pigs lured you to this zone.
Four pigs at a time, seemingly.
Yes, four pigs at a time.
And then they would do like a hee haw type show.
Yeah, it was another big production show where you had another emcee just like at the Lumberjack show and you had another full band.
And they were doing bits and they were also doing crowd work.
Are you going to make us do a second gate about hee haw?
Justin's the expert on hee haw.
Oh, really?
He loves hee haw.
He can't after the show.
Yeah, we'll do it.
Talk about that.
That just seems like a Mike campaign of the future.
I love Hillbilly Nonsense.
I love it more every year.
You love Hillbilly Nonsense more every year?
This is an effect I knew about you.
When I was a kid, I was very much only space.
I didn't like the past.
I was not interested in the past in any way.
I didn't care about that type of thing like fiddles or banjos.
I was already a huge Country Bear fan at this point.
Country Bears was my favorite attraction at the park.
He's a longtime Hillbilly Nonsense fan.
Oh, yeah, from way back.
So this was like a live version of the Country Bears, which was great.
So yeah, in the last decade, I'm much more into this genre.
It's the little Jimmy Dick.
We talk about the old time country music I'm into after In the Wake of Bob Wills,
little Jimmy Dickens.
This is definitely another episode, but several times I went to the Country Music Awards at Universal.
They did it at the amphitheater?
Well, they would do the awards in the amphitheater,
but then they would sprinkle the acts throughout the park.
So it would be like live from Jaws, Brooks and Dunn.
I didn't know that.
And then they would do their song and out would come Jaws.
In the performance, really?
It was wild.
Whoa.
Wow, yeah, we got to do that.
I mean, I meant to bring it up earlier, but your father had a hit song in the 70s.
Yes.
Billy Don't Be a Hero.
If he was here, he would tell you three hit songs.
He would correct you.
Oh, I'm sorry, yeah.
He is not a one-hit wonder.
He would be mad at me.
You're on the flip side of the Buffett thing.
He was in the top 43 times.
The 20 songs that all Jimmy Buffett, that all regular people know.
And a sane person would refer to him as a one-hit wonder.
Sure, sure, okay.
Hang on, I'm a three-hit.
But yeah, Bo Donaldson and the Haywoods.
Bo Donaldson and the Haywoods.
The Haywoods, yeah.
So you were around a lot of the old music, not the old time like Jimmy Dickens, but the
old music.
Well, eventually I was because, so my dad had a pop hit in the 70s.
Right.
And then his band broke up in the early 80s.
Actually, toward the end, he was playing a lot at the Disney parks.
Right.
They were one of the regular bands on both coasts.
Geez, wow.
And I actually, I had been searching for footage of them playing at the parks my whole life.
And finally someone uploaded footage just a couple of months ago.
Really?
Of them playing on the Tomorrowland stage.
Oh, cool.
On the terror of the rising 12th.
Yeah, exactly.
Wow, that's cool.
So that was also a thing as a kid is like, since my dad played there all the time, he
knew about like the behind the scenes of the park.
Wow.
My dad was always telling me about like the underground corridors and stuff like that
when I was a little kid.
Oh, so it maybe sparked the interest.
Yeah.
And then my mom would also like tell me the history of the park.
Like she would always be like, oh, this is where the flying saucers used to be.
And this is where the House of Tomorrow.
So I was getting both sides, I feel like.
So really making me like a Disney junkie at a very young age.
Your dad, I feel like I talked to your dad.
Was it about Michael Iceberg?
Yes.
Like the last time I saw him.
The keyboard guy at the Tomorrowland.
My dad said that he was one of the best musicians he's ever seen live.
Wow.
There was a bar at one of the hotels in Florida that like all of the musicians would hang
out at.
And my dad would hang out with him.
Wow.
Yeah.
Oh, and Iceberg.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
He loved him.
Wow.
It's the guy who would like, and there'd be mirrors on stage so you could watch what
his hands are doing.
Yeah.
We should do more.
We should go more in depth than this real quick because we just were talking about him
recently.
When your dad would tour, did he tour with Bobby Boris Pickett?
Oh, yeah.
Well, this was not in like.
The Monster Mash guy.
So in the late 80s, early 90s, my dad's band reunited.
Right.
The morning, LA morning disc jockeys, Mark and Brian, reunited my dad's band.
Wow.
And I think like 91 or 92.
And once he was back together, he was like, we're hitting the road.
Like we're doing this.
Wow, he meant it.
OK.
So he was really into country music at the time.
So he put together a country band.
And because like my mom was really into country dancing, which we would also do.
Like line dancing?
Yes, line dancing.
She taught line dancing.
And actually, we spent so many nights at the Neon Cactus at the Disneyland Hotel doing
line dancing.
Oh, I was worried about that.
So that sign really takes me back if I look at old pictures.
We spent so much time there.
Wow.
Because it was one of the only all age line dance places in Orange County.
So my mom could bring me while she was line dancing.
So it was during that time that my dad started a country band and we'd go to the country
music awards and stuff like that.
This is in Prime Billy Ray.
Prime Billy Ray, my mom.
Where'd you find any room in the line dancing club?
My mom made me cut my hair into a mullet because of Billy Ray.
Like we were all into this early 90s country stuff.
Oh, you were a mulleted kid.
Oh my God.
But when that didn't work out, my dad decided to go back playing the hits from the 70s.
So he went on the road in the mid 90s with a bunch of other acts from the 60s and 70s.
And I went with him.
First to just like help out and then I became their road manager at 14.
Oh my gosh.
So I went into like a school work program where I would just take my school work with
me and we were just on the road for my teenage years.
And one of the acts that we were on the road with was Bobby Boris Pickett who did the Monster
Mash.
Wow.
I remember meeting him for the first time in Boston when I was very, very young.
And he was just a very reserved, nice, private man.
I remember we'd all go to like a Cracker Barrel and he would ask for a different booth so
he could just like quietly read his book.
Just like a nice.
Can I not be with them?
Yeah.
Just like did not feel like a showbiz guy at all.
And then he would come out every night just to do the Monster Mash and he would turn it
on and he did all the faces with the voices and he had a lab coat with a fake spider on
it.
Sure.
Yeah.
As you would.
Well he was reserved.
The horrors he'd seen.
Dracula's, Frankenstein's, Wolfman, you know.
And Bobby's, my favorite thing about Bobby is that his rate went up the closer it got
to Halloween.
So he had a set rate from November through August and then September it would start climbing.
It's like Homer Simpson investing in pumpkins.
And there was a theme park that he had a standing Halloween date at that like booked him out
for like years.
Wow.
I don't remember what the park was.
Permanent contract.
Huh.
Yeah Bobby was a super, super nice dude.
That's nice.
What do we do?
Disneyland's got state fair.
How do we compete?
We've got Pickett.
We've locked in Pickett for 20 years.
It's ironclad.
We have three minutes of entertainment every Halloween.
It's going to bring people out.
No one else can do the voice.
No one can perform this song.
It's an impossible impression.
Impossible.
No one does an impression.
What's his name?
Well we've got to do more like old time Tomorrowland like rock band stage stuff I feel like.
And if your dad has more stories or anything.
Oh he has a ton of stories.
Also I have mentioned on the show before that you put me on a three way call with your mom
to talk about Randy Runyon aka Chuckle the Clown because she remembered him from the
old days.
She remembered the show.
Yeah my mom grew up in Hollywood and like spent a lot of time just like being in the
audiences of shows like that.
And your grandfather was a performer.
Yeah my grandfather was on a variety show called the Western Variety Hour.
The KTLA Western Variety Hour.
And he was around like during the days of like KTLA almost becoming a national network
and stuff like that.
And yeah so my mom like grew up in Hollywood around the entertainment industry and like
went to a lot of those tapings.
Right.
Yeah local kid things.
Yeah it was just like what you did after school.
Sure she knew all the locals.
She knew all the most famous clowns in Los Angeles.
KTLA almost becoming a national network reminds me of a thing that fascinates me and a lot
of it is lost media at this point.
But the Dumont network one of the first television networks and it's just like it's gone.
Like all that stuff is like hardly preserved.
It's in every night at home.
Where is Dumont stuff?
Siri download Dumont Plus.
So let's go back to Pig Mania real quick.
Maybe not real quick maybe long.
So the character the Barley Boys were the band and the host and some of the performers
would go on to be Bill Hill and the Hillbillies who played at Disneyland for years.
And then they got fired right before Star Wars land.
Yeah I think this is kind of the lasting thing of from the State Fair is that the band
that was over with the Lumberjacks they would go on to be the house band at the Neon Armadillo
at Pleasure Island.
Because Eisner saw them performing at the State Fair.
He did a full like that guy.
He was like this is special you got to be performing at one of my hot clubs.
The band at the pig races became Bill Hill and the Hillbillies who played it for years at Disneyland.
So this was the beginning of that like with more comedy a larger band.
Right and then they were hired I don't know if they're still at Knott's but they were hired by Knott's after that.
Pretty quickly.
Yeah but I don't know what their status is right now if they're still going or not.
But yes they would have they would do a whole like hee haw-ish routine with jokes.
They would play swan-y but they would play it with they would say it's swine-y instead.
There would be a lot of pun style pig jokes.
And much like the movie posters that we would get it eventually at Muppet Vision.
There were like fake movie and event posters with pigs in them.
Yeah so like this is a picture of like a Jaws parody with like a warthogs throat and underside like and it says chops instead of jaws.
And there was like a Rambo parody and like a Frankenstein parody Pigcasso Albert Einstein.
So that was all in the queue to get into the tent where the races were.
Hambo Rambo.
I like the phrase Hambo.
Pretty good.
Like this is like Chuck E. Cheese style animal parody stuff.
Huh.
And there was a big like kind of circus tent where the show would take place.
Yeah.
And it's interesting.
I'm kind of confused by the geography of it.
I remember the barbecue restaurant.
But it's pretty much exactly where the barbecue restaurant was.
So yeah I'm just interested to see what because it feels so big.
It feels so this feels so much bigger than the area around Big Thunder Ranch.
My memory of it.
How does that all fit in there?
Because I know there would be like would open up certain things for events even 10 years ago and Jason and I were going when we were all going a good amount.
Yeah.
Crazy Kirk and the Hillbillies.
Oh yeah.
Their new name still seem to be performing regularly at Knott's.
That's good.
Disney held on to that Bill Hill and the Hillbillies trademark with an iron grip.
Oh yeah.
They wouldn't let them they wouldn't let them take that name to Knott's.
There's some lawyer.
Well it's like pro wrestling like oh you can't leave you can't be Teddy outside at WWE.
I know.
But you can be Ted.
Sure sure.
It's different.
I just think they should have allowed it.
That's all I'm saying.
But I guess if you want somebody you know you want the option to do the show again.
It's precious IP.
But I don't you know what I don't feel like they're going to ever really bring back Full Hillbilly nonsense to Disneyland.
Never say never.
I feel like it's sort of not a vendetta.
I have no idea what a vendetta this was for you.
I don't think I would have ascribed you as being interested in Hillbilly nonsense at all.
You don't think so?
No.
I haven't caught this.
Because of the country bears whenever they kind of reignited.
I like country bears kids.
What's probably happened is that I've put up a wall when you talk about you know who I've been listening to is little whizzy biggins.
Can I make a face that shows I don't want to hear anymore about little whizzy biggins.
I know you don't want to hear about it.
He died of cholera on 1990.
It was the first noted case in America in 100 years.
Well Jimmy Little Jimmy Dickens has a song called Hillbilly fever and that it's he talks about how it's going around.
Did you encounter much of this in Illinois.
No.
Oh OK.
I didn't care about it when I was a kid.
This is all mostly an adult thing.
When you were so when you were a seven year old child you weren't interested in Hillbilly music from the 1910s.
No I was not.
What kind of child is this?
I just meant more as you got further into the sticks or like the Wisconsin.
When I would be seven and we'd be driving into the sticks to go to like an old creek.
Look Pennsylvania has some sticks.
I think maybe I encountered that a little more.
If I had seen pig mania but I think as an eight year old whatever I was when I was younger than that and I went to Disneyland and it's like OK there's a there's pig races over here or star tours.
I have a feeling I would still have been like star tours is awesome and I'm confused by this.
It was a maybe it's too sophisticated.
I was too kind of a dumb little child to understand the sophistication of the Hillbilly humor.
I'm going to you're putting down your child.
So I was a dumb ass.
You see now I understand that Hillbilly nonsense is where it's at.
Why go to space when you can roll a log.
You know what if I'm really analyzing myself if I really if I think when I really start to get into country music or the start of it is getting into Wilco in college.
Alt country early Wilco's considered which is an annoying title alt country and there's a lot of no depression music no depression.
Yeah. Yeah.
And Uncle Tupelo Jeff Tweedy's original band.
So that that's maybe a straight line to me listening 20 years later to get into the Wilco eventually leads you to like.
Oh I got Hillbilly fever.
It's right.
Yeah.
Listening to Bob Wills.
Now I live in a pig pen.
Something like a song like pecan pie.
Like this is definitely a connection between the two piece of pecan.
Yeah.
But forget the flowers.
I'm being like there's plenty of little like country shuffle type music songs from the early Wilco.
So that leads yet to me listening to like I'm trying to think what the y'all come by little Jimmy Dickens song about everybody coming over having my wife and he got one tooth between us.
I like the idea of a song about everyone come over now.
You hear.
That's all it's about.
And that like that comes back to the country bears.
Yeah.
I get it.
I understand.
And you you're a big country bears guys and you're very pro new show from what I remember.
I think it's great.
I do.
Like it when I was a kid you know the country bear attraction felt like it was always changing because we had the summer overlay and we had the holiday overlay.
So like I don't think it's like necessarily wrong to precedent.
There is precedent.
Sure.
Change.
The things that bothered me were very very small but they bothered me a lot just like removing the stove top hat from Henry from Henry.
Right.
Like to me he doesn't look like Henry anymore.
He's a different jacket.
Yeah.
The jacket's fine.
Right.
Like but why lose the hat.
Well because Sammy would be in the stove.
Yes.
That's the whole game.
You can wear a hat and there's not a skunk in it.
It's still possible.
That bothers me.
The name change I feel like is a little clunky.
Yeah.
But the actual show itself like I think like I have the same kind of feeling about that that I have with Tiana's which was.
Like Splash Mountain was so broken down in a shell of what it was.
Yeah.
And the last time I went to Country Bears like it felt the same way.
So like I'd rather see these rides be updated like this.
Whatever juices it up.
Then just rot away.
Yeah yeah.
Can I name the pigs that would take place in the race.
Yes.
First race featured Chop Suey, Pig Oh My Heart, Four Squeal Drive and Pigfoot.
I like Four Squeal Drive the best I think of all of them name wise.
I think that you're just you're just laughing at all this.
Second.
And then it's.
It was done like medieval times too where it would be like this section is for this pig.
That section is for that pig.
And then they put the names of the pigs up on a board and.
Would you get anything if your pig won.
Just the pride.
Sticker.
Oh OK.
So was anyone gambling on these races.
Oh I'm sure it had.
It had to do it on the slice.
Because these were real pigs.
So it wasn't like they could rig.
Yeah I guess we should have clarified.
Yeah these are real pigs.
These are real pigs.
It's not animatronics.
It's not suits.
They would do a fake out before the final race where they would build up that the final race was happening.
And then instead of the real pigs coming out.
Right.
The three little pigs and the outfits would come out and do the race.
Sometimes chased by the big bad wolf.
Yeah.
And then they would do the final race.
Right.
So the way.
Well first of all let me go back.
Second race was boar Winkle Piggy Sue Pig Pig.
And the curl next door.
Which I guess the curl is the tail.
I suppose that's the joke there.
And then third race features three little pigs.
The old limb pigs.
Nineteen ninety eight.
And this is followed by a race of four very hefty black pot belly pigs who fall and crash into each other a great deal.
The show ends with the band and the three pigs singing and marching into a rousing version of the Battle Hymn of the Republic.
With new lyrics about pigs.
Well now that they need in Galaxy's Edge.
We need some.
The Battle Hymn of the Republic.
Yeah we need to see all the characters singing that.
And yeah this is like a 20 I think 20 minute show that you would get.
And it had like a full set.
Did you see that you watched the videos and everything or saw a picture of it.
I didn't watch the full pig race video.
No I'm not asking for the full.
I'm just saying you saw the set.
I know that they had this.
They had a little set here.
And yeah so I was I was trying to figure out I think I would have liked.
This may be blasphemous to say after I was talking about hillbilly music but I think I might have even liked the parade better than the pig races.
But I wasn't there I wasn't feeling the thrill.
Yeah you weren't feeling the thrill.
Of the live pigs racing.
And it was a mixture of everything like it was the atmosphere.
It was the excitement.
You got to meet the pigs after.
Yeah I remember just absolutely loving this as a kid and everyone in my family loving it as well.
And being very excited that it was coming back the next year.
I believe these are the lyrics to their new version of Battle Hymn of the Republic.
Suey Suey hallelujah.
No one loves you like we do.
We raise our banner and salute thee.
Our pigs go racing on.
Suey.
So you would all do a sing along at the end there.
Yep they would bring that banner out and you would read the lyrics.
Is that disrespectful to the United States of America to rewrite the lyrics.
I feel like somebody I made like a parody of the Pledge of Allegiance one.
Some adult told me that that was like a very disrespectful thing to do.
And does that extend to all the different.
I pledge allegiance to the fart.
Yeah right.
And like does that extend to all the different sort of America songs like this.
I don't know.
It feels like Walt wouldn't have liked it if it was and I don't know they would have disrespected his legacy.
The whole thing was a salute to America at the end of the day.
Well of course yes.
But yeah so I guess they approved it.
They approved it with Ronald Reagan and I'm sure he signed off on it.
Ultimately it's his country at that time.
I mean his mind was gone.
Nancy was running the country.
Sure yeah.
But yeah I just I don't know there's probably stuff we're even forgetting or leaving out here.
But I just I feel like I'm so worried that you're going to find more pig names more lyrics to these songs.
Around every turn I'm like what's left.
They changed.
They probably changed the names yeah.
No I don't have anything really.
I mean I was just looking through like there was a like a blimp that had state fair on it.
I don't know if this was just for an ad or if this would do you remember.
Watch out for that's going to hit those Space Mountain spires.
It did not. As far as I know there was not.
And it scanned which will cause it to pop.
Oh.
And remember not everybody likes pop stuff.
No but some people really like pop stuff.
Really into the pops.
So yeah this is just one where I just I again I get sad I get upset that we'll never get some dumb thing like this on this scale ever again.
The things that cause your depression on this show.
Yeah.
I don't get to go see Quacky Town.
There's a there's a parade with three big Donald butts walking around and I don't get to go.
Pixar Fest.
If I had to choose between Donald's Quacky Duck City or State Fair I would want them to bring back State Fair.
Hands down.
And I liked a lot of obviously I really liked a lot of the Quacky Duck City stuff.
But the idea that you would have so much new dumb stuff to see at Disneyland is would be very exciting to me.
I don't know.
I guess we should end the episode.
Should we just stop recording.
I am finding I am finding that your enthusiasm for this is oddly high.
I think you're waiting for us I think to go.
Hell yeah.
I'm not expecting you to do that.
I'm expecting this guy over here.
He's not backing me up.
I've known him for over a decade.
I know I'm into it.
I'm just quietly pleased I guess.
Are you thinking about balloon stuff.
No I'm thinking about turn of the century set musical.
I'm thinking about the music man and L.O.
Oh that's why we said the names of the songs two hours ago and now they're just spinning in his head.
I'm thinking about chili pots and pies.
He's thinking about chili pots and pies and a poly-cule of anthropomorphic ingredients.
What is a recipe but a poly-cule.
Perfect.
In perfect tune.
Yes I do really.
In the way that you thought I was going to be into blast to the past I'm into this.
Yes.
Wow.
The true.
It's not.
You would rather you'd forego your beloved rock and roll in favor of hillbilly nonsense.
I guess we just learned a lot about you here.
You would have loved the Western stunt show at Universal on the upper lot.
Oh yeah yeah I've seen some.
Yeah I've watched some of that.
Yeah.
Yeah that sounds good too.
It's like you put dynamite in your pants and.
Yeah.
More hillbilly fun.
It blows your penis off.
Yeah that's funny.
Live real penises burn off every show.
I also liked seeing I didn't realize that Disneyland did grocery store promotions.
Like obviously I saw that a lot with Six Flags growing up but I feel like Disney World was not.
There was Disney World promotions at McDonald's because you had the anniversary.
Right right.
You had different events and stuff.
But you're excited by the idea that you would go into Albertsons.
Yeah.
Go into Ralph's.
Spend enough money.
Get a free coupon.
Right.
Coupon is you have to do this to activate the coupon.
Which is very much Disneyland now.
You want steps.
Well if you buy a ticket you have to make a reservation.
Of course yeah.
All right.
Well that is.
Something about now that we're talking about excitement over Disneyland market promotions.
I think suddenly I'm feeling like I think I'm relating to the way David Sims has been
feeling at the end of every blank check episode lately.
I think I'm simsing.
OK.
This is a reference not for everyone.
Sure sure.
For some listeners it's an overlap of course.
You know you've heard it.
You know what I'm saying.
I know what you're talking about.
OK.
With that look I'm calling it.
Justin Donaldson you survived podcast the ride.
Thank you.
My current feeling is not withstanding.
Thank you for bringing us this this topic and all this stuff.
You're very welcome.
Thanks for the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug.
If you're here in L.A. at dynasty typewriter you can see Tournament of Nerds.
We've been doing the show now for 16 years.
Wow.
We did it for 13 years at UCB and now we're at dynasty.
So come check us out.
You can watch a web series I wrote and directed for All Elite Wrestling called Johnny Loves
Tyah.
A new season of that is coming out soon.
Isn't Hillbilly Nonsense Boy and some of that stuff.
I'm in it yeah.
I don't know if I'm in season two but I'm in season one.
We're riding you in there.
OK good.
Yeah.
Mike plays the dog's agent in the show.
Johnny Tyah's dog.
Oh it's about time we got him taking more bumps.
Yeah.
You need me to do.
I claim that it's professional wrestling's first romantic comedy.
I don't know if that's true but that's what I like to say when I'm on these things.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
It's a good tagline.
That's about it for now.
Great.
Well yeah.
Thank you for joining us.
Thanks for these memories and spotlighting these seasonal events that were more meaningful
than I realized.
For us for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
A new twenty dollar tier where you get customized podcast the ride inflatable stuff.
If you want to see us grow if you want to see us pop that's your place to do it.
We do demand a little more money for that.
It's worth it.
But I realize I just found a button you get when he says my pig won at Disneyland.
So I'm assuming you got a button that said your pig won.
Look at that.
You don't say.
Now if I hit the red button down there that would stop the recording.
Can I just reach down and that would just.
It's actually it says extend the recording an hour.
It's actually.
Well we gotta talk about this new button.
You gotta talk about the button.
I'll just leave.
You can do it.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.