FOREVER!
DOG!
Hey, it's Podcast The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast with facts that are drier than my family's Thanksgiving turkey.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
You know, you don't want to undercook poultry, it could get real sick.
That's why it's all dried out.
That's the main thing my mom taught me when I was growing up, is that we have to overcook chicken and turkey, so food-borne illness doesn't kill me.
Sure.
And that's in my head, and it's apparently in your head as well.
It is, yeah. Well, that's why I like dark meat, because, you know, it's so easy.
What do you mean?
It's naturally more moist, like naturally greasier.
So you're saying if you overcook a piece of dark meat, it'll still be juicy?
It'll still be, yeah, reasonably juicy.
Oh, I didn't know that.
It's the extra fat.
Is that true?
It's fattier, yeah.
Yeah, there's not much fat in a breast, and so they dry out more.
Wow, really? This is interesting.
Our guests are coming in already.
A chicken breast, anyway, I don't know about a human breast.
Just a fact Jason shared enough.
He doesn't always have a bear dog.
I appreciate it.
No, I don't often get this.
Yeah, a chicken thigh is a more reliable thing to cook, like a reliably yummy chicken breast.
Usually he'll get the business from me for a while, and then online, the people come to your rescue online.
Yes.
I think that's why I jumped in.
I wanted to make sure.
Yeah.
Sure.
Justice for Jason.
I'm a big chicken condiment, so I appreciate that.
Dark meat enjoyer, Jason Sheridan.
With me as always, dark meat enjoyer, Jason Sheridan.
It's true, he has said that on the podcast before, so that is something that the fans know, the listeners know.
Let's bring the guests in though, so they can talk about turkey as well, fully with their credits.
These are showrunners, Jason, and head writers.
Yes.
On the new, well, on new to Netflix show, Fairly Oddparents, A New Wish.
Okay.
I've been familiar with them, known them both for years.
Yeah.
Ashley Crystal Harrison and My Love, that's the famous way I introduce her, Lindsay Katai.
Welcome back.
Welcome back to Podcast The Ride, both of you.
Thank you for having us.
Yes, of course.
She's also My Love, I should tell you.
Oh, well, that's good, yeah.
You know what?
You have to say it though in a weird, like, I got made fun of because I said, My Love,
like I said in a weird, strange, like-
Kind of cracked, and my lady love, Lindsay Katai.
I almost said it like Jerry, like nice lady or something.
Nice lady love.
Lindsay Katai.
I think you're trying to be nice and sincere, and it just came out.
Squirrel-y.
Story of my life, brother.
Very squirrel-y.
Story of my life.
But they're here, we sent them on a mission, we sent our two guests on a mission, a Thanksgiving-ish
mission.
I was about to break out in a cold sweat because I was like, oh my God, what didn't I do for
the podcast?
But we went.
We did go.
Okay, that's good.
It would be a big reveal if you actually lied to me.
No, that would be really funny.
It's just that it was escaping me what we were here to talk about for a second, so when
you were like on a mission, I was like, oh no, I messed up.
This is ostensibly a Thanksgiving episode, but Thanksgiving is a little bit harder to
find big, specific Thanksgiving stuff in relation to theme parks.
It's here and there, so you really have to look-
Well, this fits perfectly, I feel like.
So you look for it and then sometimes stuff will pop, like little temporary stuff, but
Halloween and Christmas, so much stuff out there.
Oh my God.
Over-saturation.
I would have loved to come on for Halloween.
I did so much in October.
Oh really?
Anything you want to shout out real quick?
What's the, it's not called Delusion.
It's the one in, it's in an old Burlington factory.
Oh, in Buena Park?
In where?
Oh, in Buena Park.
You did the crazy thing.
A year, a year, a year, an hour away.
We should have had you want to talk about this.
It was incredible.
It was so fun.
I would put it in my top one place, Tide.
Really?
Tide, yeah.
It was tied with my not scary experience.
Did they shrink wrap you or something?
I saw a video of this.
It seemed crazy.
Oh my God.
No, we didn't get shrink wrap, but we got in a claustrophobic, tiny, tiny like bridgeway
to connect us into the actual like experience.
The maze.
Yeah.
And it was just like the production quality was amazing.
We didn't know what to expect because it's like people who put it together, they're not
like, you know, they're not, it's not like, you know, one of the bigger, yeah.
It's not a big theme park.
Universal Studios theme park.
Yeah.
Am I thinking of the wrong, is there, were there like live bugs in it or something?
Like there's a really intense one that friends of ours have said, no, never again.
I'm just trying to make sure it's the same.
That would be horrifying.
Is that one downtown?
Maybe.
You know what?
I'm thinking of a different one.
I think, I think you're probably describing one that's less intense.
Is Buena Park an hour away?
Yeah, about that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right by Knott's.
And it's in the mall.
Yes.
It's in the mall right next to ice cream.
Right next to ice cream.
Cold Stone Creamery.
I don't know.
It might be a different one.
There's a couple different Buena Park mall haunts, believe it or not.
Wow.
And one which Marissa and Justin both said, no, never again.
And I looked online and they like, yes.
And I think there were like live bugs.
Reign of Terror.
I think it is Reign of Terror.
That's the one.
That is the one they said, never again.
It was great.
So you loved it.
I loved it.
Yeah, I loved it.
And you do this every year?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I have a friend, Patrick McDonald, shout out if he's listening.
Yeah, of course.
But yeah, we go.
We do like Super Bowl Sunday of Halloween, the Sunday before.
And we try to pack everything in all day.
Well, next Halloween, maybe we'll send you to do something or.
Yeah, you gotta do.
I do the pumpkin run every year in Alhambra.
Yeah.
It's so fun.
That's cool.
Yeah.
So yeah, next year, we'll keep that in mind.
Sure.
Jason also has said, because Jason's not a haunt guy, but he has sort of suggested possibly
going to one next year.
I think my toes in.
We're open to haunts these days.
His little toesies into the pool.
Well, I.
Get those little.
What are you scared of?
I'm easily startled.
Yeah, yeah.
Very easily startled.
With me as always, the easily startled Jason Sheridan.
The easily startled chicken thigh induces.
One tart meat.
No, I mean, we did get to talk to people at Knott's once in one or two mazes there.
Yeah.
And you did.
You did one.
I did.
I couldn't remember.
We did.
OK, you got scared in the maze, but then you also got scared when we were walking through
a scare zone.
You clung to me also.
Oh, I mean, the scare zones are in some way scarier.
I agree.
On their knees.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, they're scary.
I'm more of a curse.
So like, you know, Universal Studios has the chainsaws, which I thought that was so scary
and not scary.
They have those sliders.
The sliders.
That's what they are.
Oh my God.
I hate those sliders.
Freaked me out so bad.
I had no idea.
Because you don't know if they have control, true control, you know?
And that's my biggest fear is someone losing control at me.
And they spark and they have the whole milk carton.
And it's loud.
With the loud bolts in it.
And that's a unnerving sound.
And really my fear with those guys is one of them decides tonight's the night.
Yes.
I don't want to think about that.
Because I'm in a position to.
Of course.
But they're all theater kids.
That is comforting.
Yes, that is very comforting.
And I do it every year.
It's not just some nutball.
They're fellow theater kids.
Right, they're theater kids.
I just want to give you a nutball.
There's some camaraderie there.
Yes, sure, sure.
Some solidarity.
I should remind myself of that when I'm there, yes.
I was going to like dip my toes in board this year and I was like, all right, I'm going
to watch a bunch of horror movies around Halloween.
Good.
But we started with kind of an oddball, which is Halloween three season of The Witch.
Oh, that is one.
Which is the one.
Oscar Montoya was telling me and Kelly about that movie.
People love that.
One episode of Team Freaks.
I've actually seen it, yeah.
Yeah, it's beloved.
It is an interesting movie, but it was also very slow
to the point where Jane fell asleep halfway through
and I'm just sitting there, I'm like very intrigued by it,
but I was like, I gotta read all about this movie.
Like it is interesting, but I was like,
the director must be like a BBC guy.
No, very American.
Wow.
Like the director and the star both went on to be like
horror movie royalty, like they've done so many horror movies.
So was that the only horror movie you watched in October?
Yes.
Oh, then you were totally tapped out by Season of the Witch.
Drop the ball and then the world became horror movies,
so I've not gotten back on it.
That was in November though.
When did you watch Season of the Witch?
October 31st.
October, it was like the 30th, it was really-
You were getting a little bit of a late start there, Jason.
I was, yeah, no.
That's okay, that's okay.
You know, I had a lot going on.
It's like, this year I'm really gonna do it two days before the day.
Two days, we kept putting it off, putting it off, you know.
Horror movie procrastinator, Jason.
Horror movie procrastinator, you know,
we had to finish English teacher,
what we do when the shadows started.
Oh, nice.
As I was saying before the show, Dr. Odyssey,
we went all in on Dr. Odyssey.
Oh yeah, tell us more about this Dr. Odyssey show.
A Dr. Odyssey, it is an ABC drama,
which I didn't know until a couple episodes in
that it is a Ryan Murphy produced show.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
So it is about a luxury cruise ship.
Wow.
And the medical team on the cruise ship,
led by Dr. Odyssey, Joshua Jackson.
Oh.
What, Joshua Jackson?
The performer who was the original Eliza in Hamilton,
I think, I got her name.
Philippa something.
Yeah.
Good job.
And then the other guy has just been in a million TV shows.
He was in Rain and the show called, I think, Incorporated.
But the captain of the cruise ship is Don Johnson.
Oh, I have seen this advertised.
It is like a new love boat.
Like Tina, Rachel Drasher's guest starred.
Oh wow.
Jason's gonna list every actor that's been on the show
regularly concurrently.
It's like, so the guests.
Philippa Sue.
Philippa Sue, yeah.
And I forget who else.
There was another really good guest star.
Oh, Margot Martindale.
Oh my God, it's tagline is big deck energy.
No.
This is very different than I was thinking.
Yeah, big deck energy.
Big deck energy.
Jason doesn't wanna talk about theme parks ever again.
He just wants to talk about Dr. Odyssey.
He wants this to be what's got,
this episode is Scott free.
Jason's new Dr. Odyssey podcast.
Dr. Odyssey podcast.
Every episode since Scott's been gone,
I've had to cut 45 minutes of Dr. Odyssey talk
from him just so we can hit a reasonable amount of time.
And that's from episodes of two and a half hours long.
Bethy Squire said the Vulture group chat
was all about Dr. Odyssey.
The Vulture.
You need to get in the Vulture group chat, I think too.
Yeah, I do.
I mean, I love a network television show
that's really just a showcase for guest stars.
Sure.
I fully support this.
And I assure you, it heightens zero to 60 very quickly.
I believe it.
And Joshua Jackson's like secret,
like his motivation is insane.
I gotta check it out. I cannot wait.
He's looking good.
Pacey's looking good.
Pacey's still got it.
Look, he's looking really good.
Don Johnson.
Lookin' pretty good too.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Hello.
Don Johnson and Joyer, Jason Sheridan.
Phillipa Hsu, still in her prime, so.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jason pitched this idea that we would rate the attractiveness
of the cast of Dr. Odyssey on today's show,
but I said, no, we're not doing that.
We have to talk about friends giving.
You know I love rating the attractiveness of actors,
male and female alike.
That's right.
You wanna say one through 10.
You love this.
You love that scale.
Yeah.
I love my scale.
I have a thing.
Before we talk about the actual topic though,
we have been sent a gift.
And I thought it was for all of us.
I thought it was for the three hosts of Podcasts, right?
But it was actually just for Jason.
Oh, really?
Oh.
And I was so delighted by this gift.
And especially because, you know,
when this is Thanksgiving, you think of food, it's a lot.
So I felt like this tied in pretty nicely.
But I opened the box just thinking it was a gift
for three of us, but no, no, it's just for you.
And I am gonna give you this gift now
from a listener who's, there's a little note with it,
but here you go, Jason.
This is what you've been gifted right here.
Wow.
That's great.
Oh my God.
It is a hat of a minor league baseball team, I believe.
And it is, is that Scrapple on it?
I think that this is a Scrapple egg and cheese.
What?
This is a Delmarva Scrapple new era hat.
For Podcasts of Rides, Jason Sheridan,
thanks for all the meeteries.
There's a name on there too, in the bill too,
I think you should read, just a thank you.
Thank him on the air, on the top right there.
Top right.
Joseph Brokowski, thank you, Joseph.
Is that a real name?
Don't read his address.
From Massachusetts.
His name is Brokowski?
Well, you mean like cause of the bro in there
doesn't seem real?
It sounds like a nickname you'd say.
Sorry, it's Borowkowski.
Oh, sorry.
Jason misread it, so.
Ironically, I do have the-
I knew something was up.
Thank you for not sending me
the Reading Fightin' Phil's hot dog hat,
because I have a nearly identical hat
with a big hot dog on it.
Okay.
So, minor league baseball is very fun.
Honestly, I want this hat very badly.
I really like this hat.
We talk about Scrapple, it is an East Coast meat
that I have never come in contact with.
Okay, I was gonna ask.
And Jason has fond memories of it from his youth.
And anytime we have somebody from the East Coast
on the show, we bring Scrapple up,
they understand, they know what it is.
I just, it's not, it was a regional thing.
But now you have Scrapple on your head.
And it delights me that this has been gifted to you.
Well, I now, I have to look up to the,
is it the Delmarva Shorebirds?
Which is, yeah, it's a Maryland minor league team.
I knew about the New Jersey Blue Claws,
which is another, that's a North Jersey.
I think that's another Phillies minor league team.
Okay, so you don't have all your Phillies
minor league teams committed to memory yet.
Well, no, I have the Iron Pig Scrapple.
I remember it.
Oh, so you have a two second Scrapple, yes.
Is there?
If anyone was going to, it would be you.
Absolutely.
Well, here's what I say.
Or anyone in the agreement.
Yeah, here's what I say to the listeners,
keep them coming.
Why stop at two?
Let's get one for each day of the week.
One, you could wear one,
and then you could really coordinate with different outfits.
Yeah.
Are they all only food items?
No, I think a New York team did like
the Brooklyn Seinfelds one year,
and had like one of the, not putty,
it had one of the regular guest stars on.
Okay.
I really appreciate that the minor league teams
have some fun with their names.
Some creativity.
They are able to.
It's like an improv name.
Yeah.
Jason, for Thanksgiving,
have you ever had Scrapple back home
when you would be back home?
No, because maybe in,
well, stuffing, it's usually sausage,
but I don't think ever.
Sausage in your stuffing?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's done.
I've heard of that.
Okay.
Bacon?
That's not how, yeah, I've heard of that.
I mean, not in my family,
but I've heard of putting sausage in stuffing.
You've heard tell of it.
Yes, exactly.
I feel like we just would have stovetop
that would have maybe a little gravy.
Yeah, we were stovetop.
Yeah.
When it comes to cooking.
Which, you know, you've been there.
I have been there, yes.
Oh, right.
Because we are one another's loves.
We are one another's loves,
and don't forget it to the listeners.
So anyway, yes, you'll be wearing that.
We'll take a photo and we'll post it to the socials,
and that will inspire.
And then I'm gonna steal it.
Even if 10% of the listeners send you a Scrapple hat,
that's a lot of hats.
That's a lot of hats.
Scrapple hats.
We're niche popular, but-
Could you explain Scrapple
in a little more detail for Ashley and I?
Because I'm from Reno and then San Diego,
and Ashley's from the Great Pacific Northwest.
Right.
Hmm.
Scrapple is like a loaf.
It is a loaf of-
Oh, that's not what I was expecting.
Meats.
So it's like a spam type creation.
Kind of, yeah, but so you slice it,
and then you put it in a frying pan,
and the edges become crispy,
and the inside is like softer.
Okay.
And it's very salty, obviously.
Like, you go to an East Coast diner,
and you choose bacon, sausage, Scrapple, Italian sausage,
sometimes sweet and hot, pork roll.
Pork roll, that's what I've had.
Yeah.
Pork roll.
In New Jersey, I had it.
There you go.
You've been gifted Scrapple at a live show by listeners, too.
I believe I was also gifted pork roll.
Pork roll, yeah.
So people are whipping meat at him,
and clothing with meat on it.
Wow.
So, yes.
A king.
So yeah, we'll see.
By this time next Thanksgiving,
I hope you have every article of clothing on your body
with a picture of Scrapple on it.
Maybe like a workout pants with Scrapple on the butt
or something.
Yeah.
Instead of juicy, it says crispy.
Yes.
Yeah, oh, yes.
I wanted to say crispy on Jason's butt.
Yeah.
Thank you again to Joseph Borkowski.
I think I've said your name every possible way,
and I apologize, the print is very small.
And I will be calling you Brokowski.
Brokowski.
Because he's a bro for sending Jason that hat.
Yeah, exactly.
But okay, on to the business at hand,
the Thanksgiving business.
The Friendsgiving business.
Yes.
So the term Friendsgiving is a newish term, I feel like.
Last decade, what, two decades?
Two decades, I'd say.
Okay, fine, I didn't check, so why would I?
You threw it out there.
I did throw it out there.
That's really solid though.
I was just picking one.
And a recent episode where we talked about
the Warner Brothers Lot had started a relationship
with the Warner Brothers Lot in Podcast the Ride,
which is very nice.
Oh my gosh, amazing.
We got invited.
They were all very nice there.
Yeah, everyone.
So they made us aware that there's something
in Warner Brothers Lot called Friendsgiving
that is based on Thanksgiving and the TV show Friends.
Yeah, because Friends is just very known
for its banner Thanksgiving episodes.
Okay, so that was a question
because I've seen maybe one episode of Friends
25 years ago. Thank you, I have two, same.
It was not my show.
They were young and attractive people
in their 20s and whatever, 30s,
and they were like dating.
I wanted none of that.
Not interested, I said.
It is so fascinating to me how the two years
that I have on you made a world of difference
in terms of how we interact with pop culture
because for me, that was the aspiration.
No, but I think you're thinking of it
in terms of like, oh, in a couple of years
then I would be somebody who wanted to watch Friends
and enjoy their lives.
False, I think. That is true.
You just want to be a little boy forever.
I wanted to be a little boy forever
and that's really what it's about.
Like I liked Seinfeld because they were sillier ideas
and bigger comedic ideas and sillier performances.
Whereas I fantasized about being
like a 29 year old psychologist with my own apartment
and I would just like visualize my apartment.
Jerry would have a different girlfriend every episode.
I didn't care about that.
That was not on my radar.
I was much more into like, oh, wouldn't it be,
if I could be as funny as like Jerry and George talking
or Kramer.
What if Kramer was my friend?
Yeah. Yes.
That's really what I care about.
I did not, any of the adult stuff, no.
I wanted to be one of the Friends characters.
I wanted to be a little boy,
but as funny as Jason Alexander.
That was my feeling.
So I never watched Friends.
I was not into it.
Jason, you agree with this or you were a Friends boy?
No, I wasn't.
I was just a normal American adolescent who loved Frasier
and just shoot me in Seinfeld.
Okay, but not Friends.
Well, I-
Too cosmopolitan for you?
Well, I just, I remember like some adult cause it well.
Your issue is that they were too youthful
and your issue is that they were too adult.
I was the one going like, more Elliot Gould.
Add him to the Friends.
Exactly.
Add him to the regular cast.
And there are a lot of episodes with Elliot Gould.
There are a lot.
Not enough for me.
Not fair, yeah.
I, at some point in syndication started watching it more.
And I remember my freshman year in college
turning in like a term paper
that I had like pulled an all-nighter on.
And I had like dropped it off
and I was walking back to my dorm and I'm like,
oh, Serious Family of Friends is on today.
I guess I was just so brain dead.
And I was like, I guess I'll go watch some of that.
You know?
Must see TV.
I got caught up at the very end,
which is not that different from my Seinfeld fandom.
But I mean, the very end of Seinfeld,
I think I was about 12, so.
Yeah.
But have you seen all the Friends
or you're just saying you watched the end of it?
I have caught bits and pieces here and there.
I know about the Vegas arc.
By the way, the very end of Seinfeld was 1999.
Whoa.
So, a 99?
98 or 99.
I guess I would have been 14.
So you were a little older than 12, I would think.
Yeah, so I.
Because Green Day's, you know, the graduation-y song.
Time of Your Life.
Good riddance.
Yeah, thank you, good riddance.
1997. I knew it had a different.
Okay, so that was used in the finale.
We played that showing scenes from the tapings of Seinfeld.
So it had to exist.
On Green Day's Nimrod.
After that was released.
How do you know this?
The clip.
Welcome to Podcast Arise.
Oh my God.
In general.
We are really, so I'm not, I don't know,
I'm not a theme park expert, but you break up the television.
Yeah.
And I'm gonna have a lot to say.
Nobody binges like, nobody binges like Lindsay Kate.
That's true.
Yeah.
I'm not joking.
Amazing.
Now, first off, you were both right.
It's called Good Riddance, parentheses,
Time of Your Life.
Time of Your Life, yes.
I know that.
And also that montage was in the clip show
that preceded the.
The finale.
Finale, finale.
I just knew it was played the night of the finale.
It's also in the credits of.
I had a very specific memory of that.
Oh, absolutely.
In Wolverine.
Sure is.
Where they're eulogizing,
they're eulogizing the Fox era of Marvel.
Oh, okay.
And it's hard to tell.
I think it's sincere.
I don't think it's played as a joke.
I think it's pretty funny.
Ashley.
Yes.
You're 90s TV watching.
Oh yeah.
What was it like?
It was.
And did it include friends?
So what happened?
It didn't, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
It's okay.
I was watching like.
Okay, 1998 is one sign for that.
I'll just say that.
Go ahead, Ashley.
I think, like, I love, I knew of friends,
but I think, you know, similar to me.
You know, I was watching the black shows.
Sure, sure.
I was watching Fresh Prince of Bel Air
and Living Single, which we had a good chat about that,
you know, on the.
Yeah, that came up on the tour.
That came up on the tour.
Girlfriend was a big one, which was very similar,
you know, also about friends living life,
trying to make it, you know, in the world.
So those were like my shows.
But I definitely, I mean, I knew friends
and I loved Jennifer Aniston's haircut.
And I, you know, the Rachel.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
And I knew all the characters, you know,
and I just wasn't like, you know, I didn't watch.
I didn't sit down and, you know, seek out.
I have to watch friends.
Were you more of like watching, like being like,
oh, this will be my, like, who shows, like,
oh, I'm going to be a young adult soon.
Yeah.
That's fun.
Or were you more like me?
Or like, I want to be Pinocchio.
I'm wishing to be Pinocchio.
Oh no, I wanted the life.
I was like, I want to.
Living Single was according to our tour guide,
the inspiration for Friends.
For Friends, yeah.
Oh, was it?
Which I had heard that before, completely forgot about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, so Ashley was saying she was watching that.
So she was watching the original Friends.
The proto Friends.
The prototype, yeah.
Wow, okay.
I know, right?
Sure.
So they did, Warner Brothers has done like
these different events over the years.
We've talked about, they did a Horror Nights thing
a couple of years ago, which we bring up all the time
because we didn't do it and I'm so upset.
Like there was an Arkham Asylum maze.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
And there were a couple other different things
they did in the lot, but they're like,
I feel like they're experimenting on the lot,
which I like.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like, we were talking about that,
how it's nice that they're like injecting like
more events into the tour.
Because I did, they invited me to Batman,
this Batman thing I went to a couple,
like a month or two.
Oh, that's very fun.
And they did stop by that exhibit, really cool.
Yes, the exhibit's really cool.
They got all the costumes.
I think they have the Robin costume he was murdered in
in the Zack Snyder movie.
Oh wow, that's cool.
Which is a little dark.
He's not in, like you never see him,
but I think it's in Batman versus Superman.
You just see Robin's costume and he's like,
Joker has spray painted like something on it or something.
Yeah, so it's really, but then you see the Batmobiles
and that event had like a Batman screening
of the first movie in their big like movie theater.
And we did, we saw some Batman stuff on that.
Yeah, so there's a lot of cool stuff there.
And just, it's nice, if there wasn't enough
theme park stuff near us already, more please.
Yeah, we need it.
More themed experiences.
This is Hollywood, this is why people come here.
Like we want to, we want entertainment,
good entertainment, you know?
And also things like around the business of entertainment.
Like people come here to look at the Hollywood,
you know, the stars on the Walk of Fame and all of that.
So it's like, do more around like celebrate the studios,
celebrate the history for tourists to check out and stuff.
Yes.
So I was saying like more studio tours.
So yeah, and it is.
I agree.
Bring back the feud, Betty versus Joan maze.
Yes.
You would live in there if that was still there.
I would live in there.
That's the one maze.
Oh, what, I'm gonna get the name wrong, it's horrible.
Whatever Happened to Baby Jane is a very creepy movie.
What would you,
would you want like a Sunset Boulevard maze?
Like what would be your ultimate like scary maze?
What old movie?
What old Hitchcock?
Like that would, and honestly, as I say,
it's a good idea to do something like this,
like an old movie maze.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not like synergistic in the way they like.
So scary.
Yeah, yeah.
Marnie or something.
The ghost and Mrs. Muir maze.
Rebecca, Claude Rain, like a 20 something playing Claude
Raines in a maze.
Oh, that'd be great.
Yeah, your guy Claude.
I have a Claude figure cause he was the invisible man.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Hell yeah.
I would love a Sunset Boulevard maze.
There's a revival of the musical on Broadway right now.
I don't know that.
I did know that.
And it was in the news recently.
Well, one, because they do a thing
that I'm not crazy about musicals
where they follow an actor with a camera
in the lobby or outside the theater,
which is confusing for Sunset Boulevard.
Don't care for it.
Cause it takes place in Hollywood,
but you're clearly in Times Square walking around.
Yeah, that's confusing.
The Nicole Scherzinger from the Puzzle Cattles
is Norma Desmond in this production.
I know all the stuff going on with her,
but I didn't know it was a musical.
And she was talking about like a truck head.
We don't have to go too far into it, but she knew.
She's a truck.
She's a magnet apparently.
Yeah, I just saw something about that today.
I know all of that,
but I didn't know it was Sunset Boulevard.
And that's where all of our respective interests diverge.
You know about all of the pop culture.
I know all what Nicole Scherzinger is doing at all times.
Yeah, whereas I knew there was a Sunset Boulevard.
She's supposed to be good in it too, right?
Wow.
She is in it and the Patti LuPone
was going to see her in it.
Oh, and there's a whole thing.
Right around the time of that half comment,
everyone's like, did she post about this hat?
Cause she got a frosting reception from Patti LuPone.
That's become a meme recently
where people are posting photos
of people wearing funny hats
and then having her comment under it say,
where did you get that hat?
And I think today we've got an opportunity to make our own.
Yeah, to make our own.
No, well, to make our Photoshop,
Nicole's comment under a picture of Jason
wearing the Scrabble hat.
That's what we're doing today.
Might be the picture.
That's what I saw online.
I saw all those memes and I had no idea
what it was in reference to.
And I've seen nothing about any of this.
I just saw something, something MAGA.
She came out covered, like in the first performance,
she came out to greet the fans covered in blood still.
That was what people were saying.
She came out on the street and she was covered in blood,
not fake blood or whatever.
Okay, interesting.
Okay, now I understand that.
But honestly, a classic movie like Hornets would rule.
That is actually a really good idea.
Now that I say that out loud, that's such a fun idea.
Yeah, cause there's plenty to pull from.
They've always, the last few years,
they've done the Universal Monsters mazes
and they kind of change it up every year.
It always seems to be a big hit.
Yeah, so why not branch out a little?
Go beyond the monsters.
Well, the monsters are at least,
they're always trying to monetize the monsters
in different ways.
So that's the, you know.
I mean, I understand why I just think that they should.
Well, I agree with you.
But yeah, Warner Brothers, lot's doing like fun stuff
and they are doing an event.
I think it lasts till Thanksgiving-ish time
or whatever this month called Friendsgiving.
Friends X Thanksgiving finally happening
and we sent both of you to do this.
We didn't actually talk about how much I know Friends
cause I only recently, I only recently finished
the entire series up until just like last month.
I had only seen seasons one through four
and I love seasons one through four.
I still love seasons one through four,
but I have seen the other seasons now
and I don't love the other season.
You got through all seasons and I swear to God two weeks.
Yeah, two or three weeks.
Wow.
Because I'm watching while I'm cooking
and I'm watching while I'm breastfeeding
and I'm watching like whenever I'm like doing something else.
Yeah, she's saying it nonchalantly,
but I've never seen anything like it.
I've never seen someone binge like this
and she's binging in all whole new ways.
Like it feels like she goes, she's always like to binge
and that's always been sort of a disagreement
where I'm like, I like to watch one a week.
Yeah, that's how I am.
I'm not a binger.
Nuts, maybe two.
But it almost feels like, you know, in gravity,
if you go close to a black hole, time changes
and somebody ages faster.
It almost feels like she goes towards a black hole
and watches the whole show.
I'm able to binge faster.
Emerges from the kitchen.
She emerges from the kitchen 10 years older
and she's seen all her friends.
I've seen, yeah, the entirety of something.
Yeah, it's wild.
And you're able to hold that information
is what's fascinating to me.
Oh no, it disappears very quickly.
Oh, okay.
She remembers nothing about the show,
but she watched it all.
I couldn't tell you much about it.
Like I've seen The Good Wife in its entirety multiple times.
I could not tell you more than five specific episodes
of the show.
It disappears, but Friends I remember
because I watched it when I was young.
My problem is new memories being forged.
So I remember the first like four seasons or so
of Friends really, really well.
And then I couldn't tell you what happened
in all the ones I only just saw.
I can tell you some of them,
but I also, I have a lot to say about the show
and I know some trivia.
Ooh-hoo.
Well, I'm not gonna ask you the trivia.
Here's what else.
Oh, you're gonna say the trivia.
No, no, no, I'm not gonna just spout off.
You'll learn trivia on the thing as well.
Yeah, because I watched some of the behind the scenes.
We were supposed to have trivia on the show.
That is one thing we can talk about.
But I will just say my opinion on Friends
is the reason the seasons one through four are very good
is because it's more like a Nora Ephron sitcom
and then five on it just like turns
into like the goofiest, broadest sitcom
you could think of and I don't enjoy that as much.
The characters become very cartoonish.
The fat jokes are coming fast and furious.
They introduce a diverse cast of actors
only to always have them be either getting
the short end of the stick or like broken up with.
I mean, that's like kind of standard
because like any relationship on the show
is gonna be a source of comedy,
but it is sort of like I felt like they,
like the black characters that they did have on the show
or just non-white characters they had on the show
always kind of got screwed over a little bit
and so that's a critique I have.
How do they treat Elliot Gould though?
Fantastic, fantastic.
Elliot Gould is highly respected,
a very beloved character on the show.
Got it, Jason can take a sigh of relief now.
Breathe easy and then I always wanted Monica
to end up with Tom Selleck's character, Richard.
And the fact that she ends up with Chandler
is still upsetting to me because,
that's Courtney Cox's character
and Tom Selleck's character.
She was dating somebody like 30 years older than her
and they were great together.
It was like a really believable couple
and they're only together for like two thirds of a season,
but I still am like, she should have married Richard.
And that inspired your two year age difference.
The Stembo romance, yes.
Because Mike wants to be a little boy forever
and I've been an old woman since I was 10.
Yeah.
I love it.
Ah, my two, my two modes.
I love that side of it.
Both little boy and old man.
Yeah.
So that's a brief overview of my thoughts on the show,
which is that I am both a fan and not a fan.
Okay.
At the same time.
Schrodinger's France fan.
Right, so this was a perfect,
so when I got this email I was like,
I know who to send this to.
Cause I just finished binging.
Perfect.
So yeah.
My black hole binge.
It's like every, it's like every,
the Batman thing too, like it's almost kind of,
they build these things into the normal studio tour,
which is kind of like the universal train tour
where you get on the tram and they drive around the lot,
but then they point out different facts and stuff
that are specific to whatever the movie or TV show
your event is based on.
Like they were showing me like where the Riddler
in Batman Forever like drops,
where Jim Carrey drops like invitation off of Wayne Manor.
And tapes it to the-
Yeah, we didn't get any of that.
Yeah.
Oh, well I got like, he was like,
this is where Jim Carrey put the invitation
on the gate at Wayne Manor.
And I had like chills ran down my body.
Oh my God, that's cool.
And then the courthouse from the 60s Batman is there.
And they were like,
does anyone want to take a picture?
And then like, I was like,
I don't want to be the guy who puts his hand up first,
but somebody else, somebody else,
are you sure nobody wants to?
No.
And then finally somebody in front of me put their hand up
and I go, yeah, oh, I'll do it too, yeah.
So I have an awkward picture in front of that.
And then what was weird is that we got off the tram
and then their friend's couch,
which I'm sure you've seen the fountain.
Yeah.
They have their, everybody want to take a picture
with the friend's fountain and the couch.
And it took all my energy not to yell at everybody
and go, what's wrong with you?
This is Batman day.
This is not friend's day.
That does strike me as strange because-
It was a Batman event.
It's not even a real couch.
Right, it's not the real friend's couch.
And they moved the fountain.
So it's like, why are you at Batman day
getting more excited about friends?
I know, and the 60s Batman is one of the best Batmans
and nobody was paying homage.
They were not honoring that holy place
where Adam West ran up to talk to Commissioner Gordon.
So, and then everybody,
we waited so long for everybody
to take their stupid friend's picture.
Oh God, I bet.
And I was just like, I was like, I can't believe this.
And I bet if it was like,
I bet if it was a Heath Ledger Dark Knight,
Dark Knight situation where it was like
something from there that's more recent
in people's memories and that's their favorite Batman,
fine, but-
There is a definite flavor of basic Batman fan
that is only a fan of the like Christopher Nolan Batman.
Yeah, you know what I call them?
Fake fans.
Fake, fake fans.
And as we've established recently,
you don't like fake friends.
You don't like fake fans.
I don't like users.
You don't like thinkers, period.
I've been using the term users a lot.
Users?
I'm using the term users.
Look, we all have users in our lives, you know.
Yeah.
People who take advantage, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But yeah, so I was like, oh man, Friends is so popular.
And then when they, and I saw they were doing this,
I was like, oh yeah, that makes sense.
Friends is, I guess, still ultra popular.
It's one of those shows that-
Cause like a new generation is discovered.
Yes, and it's just, you watch nine seasons of it.
It's like the Office now.
I'm surprised there's not an Office thing
like this already. There should be.
That'd be fun.
That would be something.
Does Universal not do show or IP specific tour?
Well, they're, because that would be-
Not really.
Not a tour.
Universal property.
They're doing this like fandom nights.
Oh yeah.
Coming up.
Yeah, so that's when they,
but they're not covering the Office just yet.
They didn't say they are.
They're doing Star Trek and Back to the Future.
Star Trek's not theirs either.
I mean, that makes more sense.
Honestly, we've talked about it before.
An Office something would make a lot of sense for them
because of how much people love Office.
A show I have never seen.
The American Office?
Of the UK Office,
I've never watched the American Office.
Wow.
Okay.
It just feels like it's not for me.
I think I've only watched clips,
so you're not alone in that.
Yeah, I've only seen clips.
That's okay.
Yeah.
Something you might learn about me
is that I don't get references.
Because I don't watch a lot of things.
Sure, yeah.
It was like, when we were working
on this show though,
you certainly got enough references.
Where it didn't feel like,
oh, so it's not like Ashley's saying it's like,
Ashley doesn't know anything about pop culture.
So it feels like you know a lot about pop culture.
I do know a lot, I should say.
But in general, like in a broader understanding of it.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah, the main stuff I get.
Is there a show you're watching now
where you're like, this would be a good event?
It could be a good.
Watching currently?
Sure, yeah.
No, I'm not watching.
What am I watching right now?
I watch pro wrestling,
that's mostly what I watch at this point.
Yeah, that's the only thing you watch consistently.
And I'm behind too.
Yeah, yeah.
It's okay.
Well, I was going to say Twin Peaks
would be a fun one to do.
There are a lot of Twin Peaks things.
I don't know why that popped in my head
when we were talking about like,
what would be a fun maze to do.
I feel like that would be something
I would be interested in, right?
Twin Peaks immersive on a lot.
Oh my gosh.
I got the blue rays for my birthday
and I get to crack it open.
Cause I was trying.
Are you scared to do it?
Are you a little scared?
I've seen the first season.
It is a little scary.
There's a scene in Mulholland Drive
that is probably the most I've ever been scared
in a movie, cause it's so startling.
Which scene?
The diner, they go behind the diner
and like a scary man just kind of slides out
from behind the diner.
And I saw it like 15 or 16
and I had to like leave the room and calm down.
Were you upset because you think the diner
is such a holy, sacred place?
Yeah.
How dare you turn my beloved nation
into a place of horror.
And now you can't go into a Johnny Rockets ever again.
I can't, no.
Someone might be behind the building
and startle me.
No, I was excited.
I was like, oh, I can blank check
it's doing the David Lynch series.
I can follow along.
I'm already very behind.
David Lynch.
So you know how Last Culture East does.
They ask the question, like,
when did you realize culture was for you?
David Lynch is one of those things where it's like,
I go, that culture is not for me.
I don't get it.
I don't get the David Lynch.
But I'm such an offbeat,
a lover of offbeat things.
You would think I'd love him.
Yeah.
It's just, I don't, it's not for me.
It's a little twisted offbeat.
When I view Twin Peaks as more of a comedy than a drama,
I enjoyed it more that way.
But I just don't.
Yeah.
There's something I don't get about it and don't love.
Something's preventing you from binging.
It's keeping me at arm's length.
Yeah.
I tried to, early, early pandemic,
I was like, oh, we should find a show, Jane.
We should find a show to watch.
And we watched the pilot of Twin Peaks.
And I think she was just like, this is very campy.
And I'm like, well, no, it's not.
It's moody.
But I was like, so I was like,
maybe we need something lighter.
So that's when we jumped to
the very Twin Peaks inspired Riverdale.
That's true.
I have seen, I think, all but the last one or two seasons.
That is another show I have never watched.
That is a good one to put on while you are doing others.
That's a binger, yeah.
That's a doing other things binger.
That can't be like two, right?
That is really campy. It's too shiny for me.
Yeah, it's very shiny.
I wouldn't be into it.
I will have somehow finished this show
by the time we get home.
Oh, very good.
Yeah, you won't know.
It's a magic trick.
I'm still shocked.
In a way, the train loves Riverdale.
The, right, like Owen and Alex and Maddie,
yeah, the other cartoon.
Well, I've worked on a few shows, yeah.
Don't talk about your exes.
My first job, Infinity Train.
I'm so sorry.
You're so right.
They mean nothing to me.
Thank you.
I'm just kidding, you guys.
I love you.
No, no.
I'm shocked that Jason likes Riverdale
because to me, it feels so sacrilegious
to the original Archie comics.
Archie comics are so wholesome
and 50s in Americana.
But there are so many actual horror Archies out there.
Well, now there is, yes.
Now they've expanded it out.
It's so far removed.
Yeah, you don't even think of it at the same thing.
Wow.
Yeah.
So, and I really-
Who's the person who posts all the weird Christian Archies
of the like 70s and 80s?
There's so many, like, weird Christian centers.
On, post on what?
On Twitter?
On Twitter, yeah, somebody posts a bunch
of Christian Archie panels.
Weird.
That's weird, because there's so many other Archies
to where I was like,
this is the most heavy-handed double entendre
that I've ever seen.
Archie is very horny, too.
Yeah.
That's true.
This is like a pure phase, or a Puritan phase.
Yes, there's a, yes, there's a, I don't even know.
I mean, I read that-
Who's running it?
That was as comfortable as I was with being an adult,
was seeing 16 and 17-year-olds in a comic strip, like, date.
That was the most romance you could handle,
was like Archie, Veronica, and Betty.
And then Cheryl Blossom once in a while.
Right.
Yeah, when she got thrown into the mix.
Sure.
She had red hair.
And then Betty and Veronica would like team up against her.
Wow.
Because they had been fighting over Archie for 50 years,
and now a new 17-year-old came into play.
Were you not threatened by Midge?
Midge? No, I liked Midge.
Okay.
Midge was always around,
but Midge was never vying for Archie's affection.
No, she was pretty locked down with Moose.
Yeah.
Well, it's not, Mike wasn't saying he was threatened
by Cheryl Blossom, he was saying Betty and Veronica.
Oh, okay.
No, I, that was none of my business.
They were up to.
I was there for Jughead's antics, you know.
You wanted Archie to make a decision
and not strengthen these women along.
Settle down.
Put a ring on one.
Yes.
So let's talk.
I guess we should talk about Friendsgiving.
Yeah, so Friendsgiving, we've derailed again.
Scott is screaming somewhere.
So yeah, so it starts out basically very similar
to the Warner Brothers studio tour,
the traditional tour where you go to the entrance
for the studio.
Okay, sorry, go ahead.
Cheers.
Let us set the scene.
All right, go ahead, yes.
We receive our tickets from you.
The tickets say on them, departure window 1030 to 11.
Yes.
Makes sense to me that I can get there at 1030
and we'll leave by 11.
Yes.
Until it begins at 11.
They left at 1030.
Oh, really?
So Ashley and I were.
And I got there at 1050.
45-ish.
At 1045.
At the tour entrance by like 1050 or so.
So luckily, it seems the bulk of what we missed
was the safety message.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And the cool movie in the beginning
where they take you into that little screening room
and you watch a little movie.
So we didn't get any of that.
So I couldn't tell you about the usual start of the tour.
And then the other issue we ran into
is this was the first day they were doing Friendsgiving.
So we want to cut our tour guide some slack
because he was very nice and he shared a lot of trivia.
What he forgot to do was a Friends trivia game
at the start of the tour where they gave away buttons
that said Friends 30th anniversary.
Oh, okay.
So I never got to show off all the Friends trivia, I know,
so we didn't get actually the bulk
of the Friends tour section.
I see.
So we basically just got a WB tour
with maybe a few more Friends facts thrown in,
but it felt like things that they would,
that they typically show anywhere
because it seemed what we were talking about
is it's like whichever tour you get,
it depends on because there's so much trivia to share.
There's so many things that have filmed on the lot
that you're gonna get a different tour
depending on the interests of your tour guide.
So like our tour guide was a dancer,
so he shared that there was an LMFAO video shot
on the street.
That he was in, yeah.
What?
Yeah, it was their most famous song.
He played one of the zombie dancers.
Yeah, one of the party rockers.
Party rockers in my house tonight.
Just real quick, Jason.
No, come on.
A couple months ago, Jason said
that one of the members of LMFAO had died.
I swore he had died.
I thought the uncle had died.
And he insisted that that was right.
It was very wrong.
When I said what, were you thinking of LFO?
No.
Because two members of LFO have died.
But no, you said no.
And we still have not gotten to the bottom
of why you thought that.
I have no idea.
People have thrown theories out online.
There were some other musicians had passed.
He denied it.
I was letting them off the hook.
Because the letters were similar.
So we still have not gotten to the bottom
of what you were thinking of.
No.
Yeah, but listeners have very generously
thrown out different theories that you've all shot.
You've shot them all down.
I swore I read a news story about it.
And I either went, oh no, the uncle or oh no, the nephew.
Is that what they're called?
Oh right.
No, they're uncle and nephew.
Oh, are they actual family members?
Yeah, there's an uncle and a nephew.
See, I know nothing about them.
Yeah, anyway, so that's funny
that he was in the actual music video.
Yeah, he was one of the party rockers.
So we didn't even get the most friends heavy part
of the tour, which was the trivia game at the start.
But apparently one of the other tour guides,
she didn't remember till the last minute.
So people were thrown off their game
because it was the first day of leading the Friendsgiving.
Right, yes.
So sadly, we cannot comment on what the trivia game
would have been like.
I really thought you were gonna say
they forgot the Thanksgiving meal.
That was a shame.
We spent the most time probably at the meal part.
And we were the last ones to get up and out.
Wow.
We didn't realize.
We were just sitting there talking about Wicked
because you were going to see this greeting at night.
And then I looked around and I went, oh,
we're the only ones here.
Okay.
And of course, I'm such a slow eater
that it was largely my fault
because I was still picking away at the food on my plate,
which was very good.
Which was great.
The food was fantastic.
Gotta give it to them.
Okay.
Yeah, we had ham.
We had all of your Thanksgiving hits
and ham, turkey, mac and cheese.
Yeah.
We had biscuit thingies
and all of the food had very like Friends specific names
for them. Oh, really?
Do you have a picture or anything of what they were?
All of the food was a reference to a Thanksgiving food
that they cooked on the show.
Oh, that's really good.
A big, big one.
This was not at the Thanksgiving meal actually,
but it was in the Central Perk Cafe
that they have set up,
was Rachel's trifle dessert
because in one of the Thanksgiving episodes,
two of the pages of Monica's cookbook stuck together.
And so she included a meat layer in her trifle
and they're also desperate to make it
to the end of the meal
because they, see, I just watched it
and now I can't remember the reason
for them wanting to make it to the end of the meal.
But so they're just like eating this meat layer
in this British dessert.
Right.
So they did make that.
Yeah.
I guess so, yeah.
Right, right, right.
So that they have available to purchase
in the Central Perk Cafe,
but they had like a soy something thing.
I should have taken pictures of all these things,
but I think they listed it somewhere.
Oh, I actually got a video of something.
I got lots of video.
I intend to make a fun reel of our experience,
but we've got Rachel's buttery biscuits.
And that's from the show.
That's from the show.
So everything is an actual reference
to something made for a Thanksgiving episode on the show.
Okay, we'd love to see it.
Yeah.
We've got Phoebe sauteed, uh-oh.
It's like green onions with like garlic,
and she sauteed garlic and toasted almond green beans.
That might not actually be from the show.
We've got Ross's lumpy mashed potatoes.
That is from the show.
So that's an episode where he makes lumpy mashed potatoes.
That's from the first Thanksgiving episode,
hence me being able to remember it.
Their first Thanksgiving,
none of them want to be at a Friendsgiving.
They all wanna be doing their usual Thanksgiving activities
with their families,
but none of them can make it for one reason or another.
Did Friendsgiving start because of the show Friends?
Now I'm wondering.
The name of it?
Maybe.
Ooh, interesting.
I mean, certainly people have been having Thanksgiving meals
with their friends.
No, not with their friends.
Only family.
But it's possible that's why it's called Friendsgiving,
but I don't think it would,
I don't know that it was ever like marketed heavily
inside a Friendsgiving episode.
It was just that like, it got to be a tradition.
They didn't really do like a big Christmas episode,
even though they would do episodes around Christmas,
but it was their Thanksgiving episodes
that they were, that the show like really hammered home.
And their Thanksgiving episodes
are some of the best episodes of Friends.
So like in the Ross's Lumpy Mashed Potatoes,
Monica is a professional chef,
and so obviously she can make a good batch of mashed potatoes,
but he insists that they include lumps
because that's how their mom makes them.
So that's why Ross's Lumpy Mashed Potatoes.
So to review, were the mashed potatoes lumpy?
Or were they like,
like do you think they effectively recreated it?
Cause they were still trying to make a good dish.
So they weren't super lumpy.
They were really good mashed potatoes.
They were really, really good.
Okay, I like hearing you enjoyed them,
but I don't like that they didn't commit fully.
Yeah, so there was no meat in the trifle.
And also, and again, the trifle is just at the cafe.
It wasn't in the, it wasn't at the Friendsgiving buffet.
They had a pretty mediocre pumpkin pie.
It like wasn't that outstanding.
I liked the pumpkin pie, but I'm a pumpkin pie person.
It was fine.
There was nothing crazy about it.
It just wasn't like amazing.
What did they call it?
You're very specific in your taste.
Lindsay is very specific in what she,
sometimes she'll say like, oh, I don't like this.
And I will be like, I don't know, it seems fine to me.
I don't, I hate to be such a man,
and a dumb husband who's like, I don't know.
I think it's okay.
It could be my failing sense of smell.
So like, maybe I just like,
wasn't tasting it as fully as other people were.
But it didn't, it wasn't that flavorful to me.
Whereas like the cheesy, the buttery,
cheesy buttery biscuits were really good.
Really, really yummy.
Is that from an episode?
The mac and cheese.
I think Rachel did make like buttery biscuits.
I think that is a reference.
Yeah.
Oh, those were the buttery biscuits.
But maybe it was a later episode.
Or a later season.
How does it sound?
I mean, it's making me very hungry.
And then I look to the side
and there's a beautiful step, like in cheese.
Could we, should we be miking your stomach
during this episode to see if any gurgling is happening?
I feel like I didn't do a very good job
prepping for this episode
because I should have taken down
what all the names were of their.
Oh, I have them.
Yeah, she's got them.
Yeah, yeah.
We do have every single one?
Oh, great, okay.
We got Ross's lumpy mashed potatoes.
I said that.
Not that lumpy.
We got Tribbiani, how you doing mac and cheese.
Okay.
That is not from.
So that's invented.
Well, that's his catchphrase,
but it's not in a Thanksgiving episode.
Joey is too much of a fool to commit the time
and energy of making a dish.
Yeah, Monica's making most of the dish.
Yeah. Right, right.
But you gotta get each character
having their own meal, yeah.
So we got Grandma Geller's homemade soyrizo stuffing.
Okay.
That one's interesting to me
because you would think it would be Phoebe the vegetarian
making the soyrizo dish.
I would think that, yes.
I would think that.
We got Joey's sweet candy yams.
So two Joey dishes.
Interesting, interesting.
And I don't think he makes yams for a Thanksgiving.
Okay.
Okay. Hold on.
We got.
Does he say gams in the show,
like talking about ladies legs?
Seems like he would do that, right?
No.
He is the ladies man, but he never calls them gams.
That would be, he wouldn't know what that word means.
He's an idiot.
I didn't play Joey.
Yeah, Jason.
If I was in, I probably would have.
Jason was doing his Joey interpretation.
When Jason's ranking people's looks,
he often talks about gams.
Yeah.
That's a big part of that, the factoring in.
This is, is there any,
what was that?
Is there any last one?
The ham, the ham is, well, this is,
we were on a break, cranberry sauce.
Right.
Chandler's honey Dijon glazed country ham.
Okay.
Not Chandler ham.
Chandler famously hates Thanksgiving
because that's when his parents told him
they were getting a divorce.
Oh my gosh.
Got it.
So interesting.
So he would not be making any Thanksgiving dishes.
Were there any side characters?
Brad Pitt was in a Thanksgiving episode.
He was a guest star on the episode
as a guy who went to high school
with Monica Ross and Rachel and hated Rachel.
He and Ross were in the I Hate Rachel Green Club.
Oh, okay.
Whoa.
And the story is that he was chubby in high school
and Rachel ignored him and now he lost all the weight
in his Brad Pitt.
Oh, I love that.
He's 90s Brad Pitt.
Because he and Jennifer Aniston were an item at the time.
An item.
Dang.
90s Brad Pitt is a 10.
Don't you think, Jason?
I mean, I suppose so.
Yeah.
10 plus?
Well, 10 plus once you get to Fight Club.
I mean, he's got those crazy-
The crazy abs?
It would have been around that time.
Prime Pitt.
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably around.
It probably was around that time.
Did you have an opportunity to go to the fountain
and the chair and the couch?
Of course.
Do you have a photo from that?
We do.
Because that feels like the thing.
Because it's difficult.
With Batman, there's so many different Batmans.
Friends was shot on a soundstage, one set.
Yeah.
But they have the, from the opening-
And we did go in the Friends soundstage.
Oh, you did?
Named Ford.
And the Central Perk Cafe.
And gift shop.
Because they recreated the Central Perk set
and now it's there permanently.
And so we got our photos taken there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you feel like, one of the Horror Nights mazes
at Universal was, I forget which, I always forget what,
it was, they were using one of the soundstages
that the original Universal Monsters used,
one of the original movies.
And I'm like, it feels kind of like, oh cool,
it's like haunted or whatever.
Yeah.
Going on soundstages is so funny because you're like,
oh my God, this is where Friends was.
And then you're like, it's an empty building.
But it's an entirely different set now.
I know they just shot a different, a new show,
a show in here.
It's been announced.
Yeah, it's some show called Leanne.
Yeah.
Who's on Leanne?
Jason, you're up on this.
I'll tell you who, a comedian named Leanne.
Really?
It's a Chuck Lorre show, I believe.
Yeah, it's called Leanne for this comedian.
Oh my God, I didn't know anything about Leanne.
She's like the Tennessee grandmama or something like that.
And I turned to Ashley and I was like,
I bet this comedian is like southern and white
because I can tell by the set.
Yep.
Because this is like a rich and strong thing.
She Googled it right then.
Wow, okay.
Yeah, Leanne, but I can't remember her last name.
They have only shot the pilot.
Yeah.
Are you sure you're not breaking news here?
Like as far as- It's possible.
Chuck Lorre is gonna sue Podcasts to Ride?
No, she looked it up and it looked right up.
I wouldn't even know who this woman was
if I hadn't found it on Google.
Chuck Lorre will come to Forever Dog himself.
And choke me out if we are spoiling something
about one of his shows.
I will say, I may be giving it away
that it is called Leanne.
Because online it is just, I think the untitled,
blah, blah, blah.
Or comedian Leanne so-and-so shooting a sitcom
with Chuck Lorre or something.
We don't know, it might not be called Leanne.
It just could be a, you know.
No, it's definitely called Leanne.
I'm not giving myself any out.
It's on all of the little car stoppers
at parking lots, parking spots and stuff.
Jason, if you could bring in one of those leather saps
that an English hooligan would have in the 1930s.
The thing to hit a guy in the back of the head.
Because Chuck Lorre is going to come in here
and try to kill me for this week.
Oh.
So you want me to hide in the corner
and sucker punch him, basically?
I don't think I've given anything away,
but we were told we're not allowed to take pictures.
Okay.
So I won't describe.
If they're telling you about it on the studio tour,
I'm assuming it's.
There is a couch.
There is a fridge.
There's a kitchen.
I was doing this Batman tour
and there was all these Teslas parked there
and somebody asked about them and somebody was like,
ah, I don't know what you're talking about.
And then three weeks later,
the big Tesla unveiling happened at Warner Brothers Live.
Whoa.
But I saw the guy be like, oh yeah, I can't tell you.
Dang.
And honestly, I was like, duh,
I don't know what he's talking about.
Of course that makes sense.
There was some Teslas,
but I almost thought it was something else.
I didn't put two and two together at the time.
Oh, I actually do know who this comedian is.
Right now, I may have given something away.
It says Untitled Leanne Morgan Project on IMDB.
Well.
You could have given away the working title.
We should just post it.
That's what she was saying.
I think it's the working title.
Grandmother's life is upended
when her husband leaves her after 33 years of marriage.
She navigates this new chapter with the help of her family,
grace, dignity, and jello salad.
Wow.
This is gonna go for 15 years.
I've seen this woman stand up before, I'm realizing.
This character seems like she should take a trip
aboard the luxury cruise ship, The Odyssey.
Wow.
So you did get to go, that is cool
because you got to go on the soundstage.
But yeah, they don't have it fully recreated.
There's a little version of it on the tour,
which is cool.
Yes.
But then that's, yeah, that's the same area
where you can do.
Because I went on the tour, what did we figure out?
2016.
2016 was the last time I did the Warner Brothers tour.
And it's one of my favorites, but it had been a while.
But I visited that and you were able to walk around
and interact with things
and you're not able to do that anymore.
So that was kind of a bummer.
Had a bunch of pictures over at the counter
of Central Perth.
Yeah, there was a lot of props.
Now you wait in a line, there's a rope, they let you in.
There's a professional photographer.
You have to buy your photos from them if you want them.
They do take photos of you with your own phone as well.
And a previous podcast, the Riot episode
about Warner Brothers, Lamar Woods, who was on the episode
is the one who set all of that up.
Okay.
He worked for the company.
Oh, he made it so you can't wander around?
Lamar.
I don't know that he made what you're talking about.
How dare you?
That might've been after the fact
because I think he quickly had to leave the job.
But he's the one, his team set up the whole new version
of the photo experience there.
He hired people, he got them moving.
They had a really stressful stress test.
It was very professional, very streamlined.
Yeah, so I compliment him on that,
but I didn't get as full of an experience
as Ashley got back in 2016.
That might not, Lamar might have nothing to do with that.
I'm sure he doesn't.
They specifically hired him to make it.
No, no, I'll text him.
Did you text Lamar?
Send him a very stern text.
Lindsay would like to wander.
But yeah, if you listeners have not heard that,
go back and it's fascinating.
He had to go to Orlando.
Lindsay wanted to pretend she worked at Central Fire
instead of just sitting on this very farm.
Yeah, yeah, he had to go to Orlando and train.
What?
He got poached?
He worked at Madame Tussauds,
and then the company behind the photo technology
then approached him to open up the new photo experience
at the Wyrmbrothers lot.
That is so funny.
He had to go to Orlando or the area, like Florida area.
He's like a professional Q guy now.
Kind of, yeah, but not now.
But then he opened that up and there was a whole,
he tells a story of course better.
He opened it up and then immediately got staffed.
Yes, he immediately got like a TV job.
Yeah. Wow.
It seemed like a stressful couple of days
when it opened initially.
So yeah, that's it.
I love that.
It was running very smoothly when we were there.
So excellent work, Lamar, even though it wasn't as fun.
Yeah, it's cool,
because they had cameras set up, like multi-cam.
So while you're in line, you feel like,
or you can look at how it looks on the set
when you are taking your pictures.
Yeah, it's kind of fun to see.
I saw, I don't know if I've talked about this before,
but in college, I went to a couple TV tapings
on the Wyrmbrothers lot.
Because one of them, they gave the group,
they like got, they booked groups,
like school groups and stuff
to fill out the studio audience sometimes.
And the one time, if we went and watched this taping,
we could get a discount at Disneyland tickets.
So yeah, of course I went to that taping.
The other time, I think,
maybe we got some discounted tickets,
but we mostly got class credit
for going to a taping of- To a TV taping.
The New Adventures of Old Christine.
Really, that was sort of popular.
Yeah, Joel and Lee Dreyfuss, and-
They needed to force people to go to that?
The guy from the Shield, from the Shield TV-
Not force, but you gotta pull from a wide range of,
cause like you start running out of people and-
Yeah, it's like tourist groups, yeah.
But the, oh God, what's the guy from the Marvel movie?
Yeah, Clark Gregg.
He was- Agent Coulson?
Agent Coulson, yeah.
And then another, the other day we went,
it was called The Class.
That only lasted one set.
I remember that show, not very good at all.
Yeah.
Was trying to be like a new friends.
Yes.
Writing not so great.
So- And did you like that?
Yeah, I liked seeing how it was done.
I did not like seeing lines done over and over
and then all the alt lines, you know, about alt jokes.
But yeah, I think hour three, I was about ready to leave.
But we had to stay like three or four hours, I think,
to get our discounted ticket prices or get our class credit.
It was like-
So you had, you needed to be incentivized to do it.
That one was actually also David Crane
who created Friends.
Yes.
The Class was.
Wow.
And there was- Not still having the juice, yeah.
Was there an actor-
Lizzie Kaplan was in that.
And Jon Bernthal?
The Punisher?
Yeah.
TV's The Punisher?
Yes.
Oh my gosh.
TV's the, yeah, actually a bunch of people, great casting.
Yeah.
So I don't know why-
It was a very good cast for us, yeah.
Like I said, it was the writing.
It was like the jokes were nothing
and the laughter sounded canned.
But I'm sure that taping stage was used
for like Friends or Frasier or something.
Well, as I said many times, the Warner Brothers lot,
you will go there and you'll see on the wall a plaque.
Jason Ritter, wasn't it?
My God.
Jason Ritter.
I mean, we're talking about Andrea Anders.
How many more names will we see today?
Jon Bernthal, Lizzie Kaplan, Jesse Tyler Ferguson.
My family's Jesse Tyler Ferguson?
Heather Golden-Hernes.
Oh my gosh.
Sean Maguire, Jason Ritter, Lucy Punch for God's sake.
Yeah, this should have been a hit.
Sam Harris.
It should have been a hit.
I mean, fantastic casting created by David Crane.
Oh my God.
What went wrong?
Is that a picture from the experience?
Yeah.
I want to hear more names from this show.
Wow, it's a whole class.
I want to hear more about how Jason graduated college.
A whole class.
I need more of how he got his credits.
We need more of it.
I did on the tour, after we left the Leanne set,
I asked, did James Burroughs, is he directing Leanne?
And the tour guide didn't have an answer for me.
And I was like, my question is friends related
because I noticed that there was a like a pillar
in the middle of the set,
breaking up the kitchen from the living room,
which James Burroughs insisted there be like a pillar
in the middle of Monica and Rachel's apartment set
because he thought it made
for a more dynamic looking stage picture.
And they got rid of it after season two.
Look, he got Jimmy Burroughs.
You got Jimmy Burroughs.
He's one of the top moment camp directors of all time.
Jimmy Burroughs is the master.
I guess he directed the class.
He's still going, Jimmy Burroughs, I heard the anecdote.
He took the friends cast out and he said,
like they went to Vegas and he said,
this is the last time you're gonna be able to walk around
as normal people.
Your lives are gonna change.
This is how this guy's been in the game so long.
He knew.
He knew friends was going to blow up.
He's still around.
He's in his eighties.
He's still doing it.
I think he's in his eighties.
Ironically, he's great on the comeback
as the director of the fake show
that Lisa Kudrow's character is starting on.
We have not talked enough about Jimmy.
They call him Jimmy sometimes.
We don't know him personally.
I love, if we ever do video again,
I'd love Jimmy Burroughs to direct our podcast video.
That would be great.
If I don't work with Jimmy Burroughs
before he leaves this plane, I will be so upset.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Wow.
He actually is.
He's a fucking king.
He's a sitcoms.
Yeah, I would love to work with James Burroughs.
Let's find his address.
Let's dox him.
Yeah.
I would love to create a good sitcom
but very hard.
I think a good sitcom is the hardest thing to write.
Sure.
I think it is easy.
I think that it would be easy to do it.
I could do it tomorrow.
If somebody would give me a chance, I could do it.
I dare you to make a good sitcom.
I will.
Lindsay, do you mean specifically a three camera?
I mean specifically a multi-cam sitcom.
All this time.
Yes, classic style.
Yeah, classic live studio audience sitcom,
I think, is the hardest thing to make.
And that's why there isn't a-
It hasn't been a truly great one.
In a while.
It's like Stephen King, I believe, says that
short stories are the hardest, like book format, right?
Like very difficult.
Well, maybe it was just because of
how much coke he was on back in the day.
It could have been.
He couldn't stop himself.
That's how Jimmy Burroughs is so good at directing TV.
He's a big coke user.
To joke, I'm joking.
I don't know about his cocaine use.
Maybe not.
Parody.
Jokes, jokes, jokes.
Chuck Lorre is gonna be after me
and fucking Jimmy Burroughs is gonna come in here
forever, dog, kick the door down.
You've angered all of sitcom royalty.
You're gonna get your ass roasted
in one of those Chuck Lorre credit cards
at the end of the episode.
Chuck, I love the Ninja Turtles theme.
What if I watched the class now and I loved it?
Our daughter, Lindsay and I's daughter,
sings the Ninja Turtles theme.
Look at little baby Jesse Tyler Ferguson in this show.
No more Jesse Tyler Ferguson.
I'm sorry, I'm obsessed with looking at the class.
He does improv.
God has entered my body now.
I have to be on topic.
Look at little baby Joe Bernthal.
Wow.
What are they, 20?
Babies.
Yeah, they're like 20 something.
If the show was about young people
and I don't wanna hear about it.
It just proves you gotta have longevity in this business.
I do remember some adult cousins at a party
and they had just married and moved into a house
and they specifically had a lot of friend stuff
and I'm like 10 or 11.
I was like, this is a grownup show.
I can't wait to move to a city
where a lot of oversized open button-ups
like Joey and Chandler wear.
Bowling shirts.
It was a ball,
but didn't Chandler do a lot of bowling shirts?
He did a few bowling shirts this time, I believe.
I know Drew Carey's,
all the clothing on Drew Carey's show
was like bowling shirts,
but I feel like Chandler had sort of button-up.
That was generally his style though.
That was a very 90s.
That was a Smash Mouth type dressing.
That was very 95, 96.
Yes, 96, walking on the sun.
96, 97, I think it's 97.
We went through the whole Friends gift shop area
and I just couldn't have wanted to own anything less.
Yeah, we were like, what?
Which is like, it's not that it's bad stuff.
It's just that I'm not the kind of Friends fan
where I'm like, I want merch in my house.
I want a cookie, an oven mitt.
Yeah, that's Friends.
I want a shirt that says, we were on a break.
There's nothing I'd rather own less than I can think of
than a shirt that says, we were on a break
in the year of our Lord, 2024.
I like the logo.
I feel like it's a very iconic logo.
I was telling Ashley,
I think I had a Friends shirt back in the day.
Or it was one of those parody shirts
that were popular in the mid to late 90s
where it looked like the Friends logo,
but said something else.
But it said something else, yeah.
Like I had a shirt that was in a FedEx logo,
but it said Fed Up and I was like, 15.
I feel like I've seen a picture
of Anne Hathaway wearing that shirt.
Maybe, that does sound familiar to me.
I think I've seen a picture of Anne Hathaway.
I had like at least three logo parody shirts at this age.
I had no fashion sense.
I was desperately trying to figure out
what my fashion identity was.
So I was wearing that.
I was wearing my grandmother's shirts from the 70s.
Oh my goodness.
Or I was wearing a cardigan and khakis.
I was just wearing all my older sister's clothes,
like everything, The Gap, like Abercrombie.
Cause you had how many older sisters?
Two.
Or older siblings?
I had two older sisters, but one that lived,
the oldest one's like way older,
but I would always steal my sister's older,
my closest-in-age sister.
But yeah.
I would just, I just dress the same.
I dress like the same, like a little boy.
You know?
Your character.
I mean, I guess I'm wearing a Rolling Stones shirt,
but that's not a cartoon character, but I don't know.
It's about the same.
So you got the photo op with The Fountain.
Did they explain to you that The Fountain has been moved?
Yes, yes.
That was explained on the tour.
It was explained.
It wasn't, it was also explained
that it's not a real fountain in New York.
It's not based on a real fountain.
And it was just a fountain that was on the lot
that they shot in front of.
Some people think it's the fountain with the big angel
that's like, that's in Central Park.
It is not that fountain.
It's a tiny little fountain.
Yeah.
We were not allowed to sit on the fountain.
We took some photos of me sitting
and we got a stern top.
Yeah.
And others followed her.
You're gonna get me in trouble
from the Warner Brothers now?
There was no signs.
There was no indication that this would not be acceptable.
If we could sit on the couch and take photos,
I thought we could sit on The Fountain and take photos.
Right, sure.
But a guy came up and he was like,
you can't sit on The Fountain.
And I was like, show me the thing anywhere
that indicates this wouldn't have been okay.
No, no, no, I was thinking that.
And I said it to Ashley after.
To him I said, oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh gosh, I had no idea.
I never would have sat if I had any idea.
Yeah, she did say that.
Was The Fountain on?
Yeah, I think so.
The fountain was on.
The fountain was on too.
Did you consider hopping in?
I definitely knew not to do that.
But I did think I could sit on the edge of it.
It was just before she got reprimanded.
Oh my gosh, right before the crime was committed.
Look how happy I look.
Just before I got yelled at.
At least we have the photo though, the legal photo.
And then she had to stand.
Oh shit, now she looks upset in that photo.
Well, I had just been reprimanded.
Well, yeah, you got a sap to the back of the head.
I was legitimately taken aback
by how much he scolded me.
Wow.
He like rushed over.
I felt very defensive because I don't,
I'm not a rule breaker.
I don't like breaking rules.
I don't like having broken rules.
And then yeah, the couch itself
is made of like a very hard plastic of some kind.
The couch is almost like the Snick couch or something.
It's like a cartoon version of the couch itself.
It's an exaggerated mock-up.
Because so many tourists sit on it.
They're like, you can't possibly have a real couch.
Well, then is the real one in that set,
that little other set, that's the real one, right?
Okay.
Or a real one because they tore the set down
like the day they were done shooting.
Right.
Because they had to get out of there.
Yes.
So they had to shoot the clips.
They recreated it later.
They had to shoot new adventures.
They had to get Jimmy in to shoot the clips.
They had to get, help Jason finish college.
Yeah.
They had to get Jason to finish college.
They had to boss him in.
Yeah, just a basic communications class.
Oh yeah, they had umbrellas for us.
Isn't that fun?
I don't know if they always have umbrellas.
I'm showing a picture of the umbrellas,
which I did have a question about.
We didn't really get an answer,
but I thought what was the significance of umbrellas?
Don't they have them in the opening?
Yeah, they have them in the opening.
Well yeah, but why?
I think it was just to create a fun pop of color
in the opening.
I think it was just to have movement
and something different in some shots.
You don't buy it, yeah.
I know that.
You're a little superfluous.
I think they were,
because the trivia I did know is that
they told them they weren't gonna have opening titles.
The creators, like without asking permission first,
went ahead and shot those opening titles
in front of the fountain with the couch
and the umbrellas,
and then showed it to them
with REM's Shining Happy People playing over it,
and they were like,
see, isn't this better with an opening title sequence?
And they were like, yeah, it's better with an opening.
And then he wrote the song.
The Rembrandt song.
Wow.
I do like the Friends theme.
Yes.
I will say, I always like the Friends theme
even though it's a day.
It's a solid theme.
It's iconic.
Yeah, it is iconic.
And the guy said, who wrote it,
he was like, well, if I'd known it was gonna be as big a hit,
I might've spent a little more time on the lyrics, though.
Oh, yeah.
The lyrics are, yeah, they're fine.
They're fine.
They're very serviceable for the show.
Gonna feel this way.
I'll be there for you.
No one told you life was always gonna be this way.
Cluck, cluck, cluck, cluck.
I always think of it in the same realm.
Your job's a joke, you're broke.
There's like, it's like a wife's day.
Is that what it says?
Your job's a joke, you're broke.
Your wife is dead on a rival.
Relatable.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because it's all about the struggle of your 20s
and how your friends and your family
when you're just out of college.
Yeah, I couldn't relate to the lyrics.
Yeah.
I wanted to be a Pinocchio.
I wanted this to be a Pinocchio song.
You wanted to be a superhero.
So were there any things you thought of in the moment,
like, oh man, if they did something next year,
like an extra element, oh man,
I wish I could put on Phoebe, like play Phoebe's guitar.
I know she plays the guitar with the Smelly Cat song.
You know that.
That would have been great.
They should have had a woman dressed as Phoebe
playing her song.
That would have been so fun.
Look at that, I've never even,
I just know that as a reference.
That's how I've observed things.
They were playing music from the show.
This is how good a theme entertainment is.
It's all like 90s jams.
Like, weirdly, when we first arrived at the buffet,
they just kept playing all by myself on a loop.
Yeah, that was weird.
Is that on the show ever?
Yeah, it's in one episode.
What is going on?
And then finally other songs started to play.
This is a good playlist.
These songs that were used in the show.
Yeah.
Would you have liked it?
But yeah, they should have had a woman there
playing Phoebe's songs.
Singing while we're eating, maybe,
that would have been fun.
And they just like throwing some other stuff in there, too.
Yeah, Smelly Cat.
As if she was playing at a cafe.
I didn't see any Smelly Cat stuff.
Or merch.
Would you have liked?
That's weird.
Yeah, it is.
Because of the celic, Courtney Cox relationship,
would you have liked to see an older man
kissing a young woman?
I would have loved to have seen a mustachioed
50-something year old kissing a woman
just about to hit 30.
I would have loved it.
And that could just be happening the entire meal.
Okay.
Here's what I would have loved.
Awnings.
Tents of some kind protecting us from the sun.
Oh, a lot of sun, okay.
Full blisteringly hot in that sun.
It was like 80 degrees.
Ooh, yeah.
So we're sitting eating hot Thanksgiving dinner.
Yeah, sure.
In the blazing sun.
Okay.
I also would have loved some coffee.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, did they do coffee on the show, Michael?
I've never seen it.
Central Perk?
Central Perk is the coffee shop they always hang out in.
But do they drink coffee there?
Constantly drink coffee.
You can get a tea.
It's giant bowls.
No, they're constant.
Even I know that, Mike.
Giant mugs of coffee in every episode.
So I married an axe murderer or a cappuccino.
The reason they didn't have that
is because they have the Central Perk Cafe
for you to purchase all of these coffee.
Correct.
So that's why there was no coffee at the buffet,
but I desperately needed caffeine.
And they only had soda.
Gravy didn't do it for me.
Jason drinks caffeine with gravy.
Oh, the turkey was delicious.
The turkey was moist and delicious.
The ham was fine.
Would you like to hear the specialty drinks?
Oh, yes, please.
Special tea coffee drinks.
So we've got the Joey, that's mango cold brew tea.
Okay.
We've got the Monica.
What do you think that was?
Oh my God.
I'll tell you, it's the one I ordered.
It's the one Lindsay ordered.
Sprite, Sprite.
Coffee drinks, Michael, coffee.
Oh, coffee drinks.
Right, right.
Sprite mixed with coffee, Sprite infused coffee.
Actually, that sounds good.
It probably is good.
Midnight mocha cold brew.
Okay. Okay.
What do you think the Rachel is?
I'll tell you what the Rachel is.
Hair. Should have been the Phoebe.
Yeah.
Oh, it's noodles in the coffee,
like to look like Jennifer Aniston's hair.
Noodles.
Yeah, because it would just be noodles
in the shape of her hair.
That's fun.
I'm an expert at themed entertainment.
I love that.
It was a cup of noodles.
You know the cup of noodles?
A cup of noodles in the coffee.
The Rachel, you drink it on the Warner Brothers line.
It was a matcha latte.
Okay, okay.
Oh, okay.
I've heard of that.
It's very strong.
This one is the Ross.
Okay.
Classic flat white.
Nailed it, nailed it.
And then we got the Chandler.
That's a caramel hazelnut latte.
And then the Phoebe,
which was a cookies and cream ice blended.
That seems way more Rachel to me.
And then the matcha seems way more Phoebe.
Yeah.
It's a bit of a, yeah,
departure from everything else.
Character assignment.
But yeah, so those were available
and the cream ice blended.
Yeah.
So yeah.
And you know what I got?
Oh yeah, please.
A hot chocolate.
Not themed to any character.
Nothing like baking in the sun with hot chocolate.
Hot chocolate.
We were inside by this time
because this was at Central Park.
Baking in the sun I feel like is a complaint I see
about a lot of new theme park lands
or attraction lines.
Yeah, all you have to do is set up some of those
I know.
Yeah.
That was a mistake.
I hope they figure that out.
And you look at the early photos
of Tomorrowland at Disneyland.
There's these giant shade coverings everywhere.
Yeah.
So to sum up, is there any overall thoughts?
The experience was nice.
You had a nice day together.
Very nice day together.
It was a nice day with friends.
It's always fun to be in the lots.
Yeah, it was a nice day with my love.
Yeah, my love.
Yeah, any other.
It was a bummer that we didn't get the friends trivia.
Honest mistake, I'm sure.
Yeah.
And he threw in, I think we got a fair amount
of friends trivia during the actual tour.
Yep, yep, yep.
This is where they filmed this scene.
This is where they filmed that scene.
Yeah, here's the movie theater from this episode,
all of that.
And then the meal was really good.
Yeah.
I'd say worth it for the meal alone, honestly.
Looking for a nice Thanksgiving dinner.
Check it out.
Yeah.
All right, well, Jason, I mean, you don't care about friends,
but maybe we send you over a couple more days
of this event.
Yeah.
You get one of your to-go bags, you load up.
Are you allowed to bring a doggie bag,
by which I mean a black trash bag?
We were wondering, I was like, we should have brought wine.
This would have been so nice with a nice wine.
They could have charged like a little, you know,
extra price and sold alcohol, I think.
I wonder, yeah, I wonder if that's probably a whole like,
to do, getting a liquor license.
Probably.
Yeah.
I'm sure it's to do with liquor license.
They should let, on any studio tour,
they should let you drink.
Yeah, I agree.
Also the catering staff was super nice as well.
Yes.
And they were not in character.
Everyone was very nice, not in character.
Okay.
So maybe more characters next year.
I would say your idea for somebody playing the Phoebe.
The Rachel drink?
Mm-hmm.
Not so the Rachel drink, more so the Phoebe,
somebody playing Phoebe's music
would have been a really good touch.
All right, well.
I feel like, you're not too far off.
I feel like espresso tonics were a thing I saw
for a while at Cafe Menus.
I think I've never seen anyone suggest a cup of noodles.
He's saying my Sprite idea, right?
I know, Sprite idea, yeah.
I think the big ramen manufacturer,
I think there is top ramen with caffeinated top ramen.
Really?
Like Gamer Fuel top ramen.
What about caffeinated gravy?
Whoa.
No, a man can dream.
Do you have your morning cup of gravy to start your day?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's possible.
You could make, I mean, we really,
we've talked about so many different business ventures
on the show that have never come true,
but Jason Sheridan's caffeinated gravy
is something we should put to the front of the line.
After the fact, it was funny because it didn't seem,
like I seemed the most excited about coming in
with like Friends Trivia on the tour
because the guy was like, and then on this scene
is where you see, down that alleyway,
you see Monica and Rachel talking.
I was like, I know, they were talking about
Jean-Claude Van Damme in the episode
where they're seeing the movie.
Yeah, yeah.
And I seem to be the only one really like being like,
yeah, this is the list, and like pushing the nerd glasses up.
And one other gal.
Yeah.
The Laren.
And I think that's because we were there on press day.
And so a number of other people were all there
to cover it for something that weren't so much there
because they were Friends fans.
And I didn't realize that until the meal.
Yeah.
That was maybe what I was dealing with
with Batman Day as the press.
Yeah, possibly.
But yeah, there was all the, the guide was like,
cause yeah, they give them all these very specific things
to say cause it's not their normal guide speech.
And the guide for Batman Day was like,
he said something about Aquaman's villain, Black Mantra.
And the villain's name is Black Manta,
like the aquatic life.
And I just was like gripping my,
I was like, I'm not gonna correct him.
He's doing his best.
He called Mr. Zomp.
He sent a very long email after.
Yeah, you sent a Zazz live email.
Did you go to the Turner Classic Movies tour?
They invited us to an event.
Yes, I did go to that.
I would have loved to have gone to that one.
Well, there was a whole,
we talked about this on the show, did we not?
With Ben Mankiewicz and the marching band.
Yeah, Ben Mankiewicz was there and a marching band came.
All of a sudden like playing 76 trombones.
Oh my gosh.
And Ben Mankiewicz on a tram car
turning around the corner and we were like, holy shit.
And then there was like an old cowboy.
I forget the actor's name,
but he was just like there to be like,
the movies are great or whatever.
I would have loved that.
It was really funny on the tour
because we're sitting next to this other couple
and he would tell us the fact,
he'd be like, and here's where Growing Pains was shot.
And Ashley and I would be like, oh.
And then he'd say, and here's where
like Pretty Little Liars did this.
And we were both like totally silent with Bill.
Or he would start to say something,
he would go, ah.
Yeah, yeah.
Because it would seem really interesting
and then become like abruptly less interesting.
So it would be an, ah.
Just me freaking out.
Freaking out on a tour when they go like,
and this was Philip Marlowe's office building
in The Big Sleep, Humphrey Bogart walked through this door.
And I'm like, oh my God.
Exactly, it's like, yeah,
Ashley and I both going, ah.
Giving away our age as soon as he was like,
and this is the Seaverse house.
And we're like, what?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did that when they said Adam West.
I just got very, I get giddy.
I do feel like Ashley and I were the most vocal tour.
For sure.
Okay, so you won the tour.
We won the tour.
Let's say so, yeah.
We're definitely the star pupils of the tour.
We were, yep.
That's good.
And then I really appreciated the fact
that they showed a trailer for the second season
of the Gremlins cartoon.
Oh, right, right.
On Max.
They showed that on the tram in the little video.
They showed that on the tram video.
Oh, that's good.
When we were like leaving the buffet.
Yep.
Synergy, that's nice synergy.
It was just nice to see an animated show get some love.
I know.
That's right, P.S. guest Joan Ford worked on that.
Yes.
Oh.
Well, let's say, and I'll do it really casually
and quietly, but Lindsay and Ashley,
you survived Pomcast, pod.
That usually does it.
I'll do it quietly.
Did I call it Pomcast?
Pomcast.
Yes, Pomcast.
Oh my God.
Oh.
You survived podcast the ride.
Let's exit through the gift shop
now that we're talking cartoons.
Whoa.
And you do the, let's do the sell.
Let's do the art sell.
Oh, that was perfect.
Ashley, quickly before we do that is,
Ashley was on the hunt for something
to do with Tiny Toons.
Yes, you were Babs Bunny.
Oh yeah, I am.
Because she is Babs Bunny.
That is awesome.
Sometimes I forget.
Yes, I forget.
We're talking to Babs Bunny.
I know, crazy.
So Ashley bought like a really cool
original animation sell from the original Tiny Toons.
Yeah, because it's, I'm always like everywhere.
I'm like, any Tiny Toons stuff anywhere?
This was a big hit show also.
And it's always Looney Tunes, you know,
and then Space Jam stuff, you know, all that.
So, but we went outside and they had like a whole,
not marketplace, but like a whole.
As we were exiting through the gift shop.
As we were, yeah.
All of these original like vintage sells
from different shows.
So I asked if they had Tiny Toons stuff and they did.
They had like four bins worth.
And Tom Rugger, who created Tiny Toons,
he comes and like signs them and like.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah, but he wasn't there that day.
So, yeah.
Ashley got a really good one.
Yeah, I'm gonna get it signed.
I bought one.
Yeah.
Did you try to like.
The Princess Leia, yeah.
Get it on the house.
Like hey, this is.
I did, well, he was like, I told him.
And I was like, yeah, I'm the voice of Babs Bunny.
And he was like, oh my God, what?
And I was like, yeah.
And he was like, oh, well, you can get an employee discount.
And I was like, what?
I don't work here.
You know, I don't know how he.
I was like, how are you gonna prove that?
Technically employed by WB though.
I guess so, yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, so I got a pretty hefty discount.
Which was really nice.
You are subletting the water tower from the Animaniacs.
Exactly, yes.
I am Warner Brothers royalty at this point.
You are.
Seriously, yeah.
Just kidding.
I kept threatening to out Ashley
as the voice of Babs Bunny on the tour.
I was like, please don't do it.
If he so much as mentioned Looney Tunes,
I was gonna be like.
Um.
But it didn't happen.
You got reprimanded for that impulse.
After that fountain sitting incident.
And it was by the ghost of Jack Warner.
That's why you were so startled.
I was like, oh my God,
the four Warner Brothers are reprimanding me
from beyond the grave.
But yeah, so now that we've discussed
the actual exiting through the gift shop,
please watch my and Ashley's show,
Fairly Odd Parents, A New Wish.
It is out on Netflix in multiple countries,
including the US now.
Premiered November 14th, I think.
Thursday, November 14th.
We don't know what time it's gonna drop,
but that's okay.
But yeah, that's when it will be coming out.
And I think this episode comes out after.
Probably after that day.
I think this is our Thanksgiving episode, probably.
It should already be available to watch.
Please. Yep.
Please watch it. Set a timer, set a reminder.
First half of our first season that already aired.
Yeah. On cable.
But the views of this will supposedly be considered
in giving us the second season.
It's important to see this.
So if you could leave your TVs on
with it playing all night.
And it is important that you finish it
and finish it all in one,
like binge it as much as you can and finish it.
And read it.
Within the first 30 days of its release.
Give it five stars as it starts.
Two thumbs up.
Two thumbs up. Loved it.
Loved it. Give it a loved it.
If you're gonna let your TV play,
remember to set a timer to wake back up
to click the yes, I'm still watching.
Yeah. Right.
Are your pets home alone?
Put on Fairly Odd Parents a new wish.
Keep them company.
Watch it multiple times.
They are probably sick of Roku City at this point.
So a little change.
You're going to Thanksgiving.
Family members have kids.
Let them know this show exists.
Yeah.
Suggest it to your friends with kids.
Suggest it to any parents you know.
We would really appreciate all the views we can get.
We really would.
We're really proud of the show.
Here, let me hold.
Everybody did such a great job.
Let me talk turkey to the listeners.
Turn the fucking show on.
Okay.
Do you want to feed our fucking kid or not?
We have a kid here.
We need season two, okay?
Yeah, we do.
If you have a two year old at home,
she needs food and clothing and shelter.
This dumb podcast that we've been doing for seven years.
You owe me.
Do nothing else.
Okay. I'm talking turkey.
Cause it's Thanksgiving.
Help get our show reviewed.
That's why.
Yeah.
That's why you're talking turkey.
So thank you for doing this.
Cosmo and Wanda, the fairies will be put down.
Yeah.
They will die.
Their lives are on the line.
We're letting Hazel go, but Cosmo and Wanda will die.
Yeah.
So that'll be on the listeners of podcast if it happens.
We've gotten great fan reaction online.
Huge support.
A really big round of support.
They have really just taken the reins on this.
It's been really heartening to see.
We really appreciate everybody who has said something
about it on social media.
Promoted and posted and did fan art and shared.
Just like, yeah.
So much love for the show and we really appreciate it.
Let's keep the train rolling, the love train.
So yeah, as for us,
you can find us on all the socials, podcasts, the ride.
You can go second gate.
You can hear a bunch of different weird stuff
we've been doing all month.
Jason talking about Generation X, the weird Fox movie.
We did 20,000 leagues under the sea,
the Tokyo version with Matt Mazzani.
And yeah, I'm trying to think.
I guess we just put out an episode
about a really weird Thanksgiving parade
that we literally found hours ago.
Hours ago, we're like,
there's an original song about Goofy being a dinosaur
called Goofasaurus.
Goofasaurus.
Never heard of this before.
Wow.
A couple hours ago, we're going back and forth
and I was finding something and there's this weird
half Macy's Day parade, half Disneyland parade
where it's like very dinosaur Flintstones themed.
No idea what it is.
Finding Eisner treasures every week still,
Eisner era treasures.
The man was a treasure trove.
God bless him.
And then to go out,
I bought myself a gift weeks ago at Disneyland
and I want to open it right now.
This is gonna be my first munchling
now that we're talking about food.
These are Disney, this is a new thing I'm about to collect.
So Lindsay, a shutter should run down her spine
as far as stuff I'm collecting,
but these are characters that are meant to also be food.
So I could get Scrooge McDuck who's pancakes.
He's half Scrooge McDuck, half pancakes.
Huey, Dewey, and Louie who are in a cereal bowl
filled with fruit.
Kit Cloudkicker from Tailspin who is a brown sugar muffin.
Darkwing Duck who is a fruit cup parfait.
Gosselin Mallard who's freshly squeezed orange juice
or Gosselin from Darkwing Duck.
She's the plucky little girl.
Goliath from Gargoyles Berry Breakfast Pastry.
Wow, Gargoyles.
Or a mystery character.
So I'm very excited to do this.
I've been meaning to open this up on the show for weeks
and I think Thanksgiving is a perfect time.
Mike is just tearing into the box.
Your chaotic boxing thing is so stressful to me.
And we've got, oh, Scrooge McDuck is a pancake.
Yay.
I gotta say, it's gotta be the best one, right?
The Darkwing Duck Parfait was the one
I maybe wanted the most, but this is pretty good.
They all honestly are really good.
And we're going to Disneyland soon with the family
and we'll get a few more of these boxes when we're there.
Nice.
As long as Fairly Odd Parents gets picked up for season two.
Yeah, only on that condition.
Just to share a brief theme park story.
Regarding our child, she's been talking to the nightlight
in the bedroom at night.
She says, hello, Lelo nightlight.
And then I talked back as the nightlight
and I said, hello, Ramona.
And so then I did this a few times
and now she just like continually tells the yellow nightlight
about her last trip to Disneyland.
Whoa.
She's like, I was at the castle.
I saw Mick and Minnie and Goofy and Daisy and Donald.
It's so cute.
Daddy went on a 15 minute rant
about something called Lightning Lane premium.
Yeah.
Well, she knows and she knows what the problems are
with the system.
And she can list them.
She can list them and she does, yeah.
But in the cutest voice possible.
Anyway, thank you for listening.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog team and liking our page on Facebook.