Okay, I'm going to try something here just this is for the episode, but I just want to
try a different intro. Okay. Here we go. Welcome to Point Brothers, a podcast hosted by two
non-biological brothers who love points. My name is Mike Carlson. Joining me as always.
Hey, it's the points master, Jason Sheridan. Points master, Jason Sheridan. That doesn't
feel right. First off, you didn't tell me you were recording. Second off, you are the
points master, so I should not be taking that title. Well, no, I mean, you can be the points
master. Is there something more supreme than points master? The points god? The points guy?
Yeah. The points guy will comfort you if you steal his title. Supreme chancellor of points.
Yeah. Mike, we could be, I thought about this, it could be the pointer brothers,
like the pointer sisters, but I think there are pointer brothers in some sort of space.
There's a Tim Robinson sketch, yeah. Yes. Well, there's that too, but I think I saw different
people that already took that name, but Point Brothers, I think, is available. Right. So,
if we wanted to quit podcast the ride and do our own thing, really forge out on our own.
We're quitting? We're not just doing it in parallel? No, there would be no time. Oh,
okay. This would be full Point Brothers. We would have to do 60 hours a week on this to really
master. Because you got to book flights and buy appliances to test stuff. So, yeah, I don't know.
By the end of this episode, we'll determine if we should quit podcast the ride. Oh, okay.
That's what we'll do. It's possible. Sure. Hi, everybody. Hi. Club 3. Welcome to Club 3.
Welcome to Club 3, you sickos. You sickos who voted for this episode. You asked for this.
You asked for this. Sickos in a good way, of course. I think they would have been more
sicko if they had voted for Madame. Do you think so? I think this is the ultimate sicko
choice for them. Do you think so? Yeah, because Madame still is like, even if you think Madame
is scary, which she is, this is a hardcore choice because everything else, I could see the value
in it. I could see the fun in it. But the only fun in credit card points is hearing how annoying
I am about it. You know what I'm saying? I'm happy to get an update, actually, because we've
talked about it in a little while. But everything else I could see, I could tell a person on the
street, we could go out right now. I could tell a person on the street, hey, we're doing a podcast
about American Idiot. And they go, oh, the musical or the album. They would say, OK, I understand
that. I say, there's a puppeteer and a puppet named Waylon Flowers and Madame. And I would
explain the sitcom. And you go, oh, I could see where that would be, a podcast. And then I would
say, well, we're doing an episode about my credit card points, not even credit card points in general.
It says on the choice this was this was chosen or written, excuse me. It says Mike's credit
card points. That's what people voted on. Sure. And somebody would go, oh, yeah, I guess.
Well, what do you mean? They're clearly not like haunted by the clip of Madame driving a big old
car like I am. Like, I think that was from our sitcom intro or her talk show intro. And she like,
it looks like she's driving a big old car and like she's a little horrifying looking.
So that little scary theory kind of scares me. Although lately, I've also been like upset.
I've been getting a lot of ads for L.A. and Vegas performances of Vicky Lawrence and Mama.
Mama is not mad. Mama is not mad, which I had to remind myself sometimes to do it. And also,
so Mama was a character on the Carol Burnett show. That's right. Not portrayed by Carol Burnett.
Right. And then she got the character, got her own sitcom in the 80s that ran for a while.
Yes. And I really don't know anything about Madame, just that she's giving you a look when she's
posing back to back with. No, not Madame. You said Madame. Oh, see, I can't. I told you Mama
is not Madame and you didn't listen to me. Look, I'm just overwhelmed. I thought about
Madame driving that big old car and I got startled. Is this going this? This can't.
Mama and Madame cannot become the new Pucca di Beppo. This cannot happen. No. We cannot afford
that as a podcast. The confusion in the marketplace of Mama and Madame. By the way, I got to find this
because I want to give them credit. Someone did a super cut of the full
Pucca Saga and it's on YouTube and I do want to give them credit. The Pucca Saga. But I am terrified
to listen to it. Oh, you didn't listen to it? I listened to it. I haven't listened to it yet. It is like
half an hour long. It is so long. Somebody cut together. In case you're on Club 3 and you don't
know, just Jason has called. I want to ask you to do it again right now. Could you do it?
Do you know what it is? I do know what it is because I saw the logo and I hope to God this is
right. Okay, do it. Pucca di Beppo. Yes, you got it. You got it. Okay. So yes, there's been a long
multi-year saga of Jason calling it Pucca di Beppo and somebody cut together all the instances of
this happening on the podcast. God bless you for the amount of time on your hands to go through
and find all that. At ancientsroman11 on Twitter is the one who. Yes. Wait, no, he tweeted about
Sha Na Na. Shit. Oh, Jason shouted out a different wrong user. I mean, that sounds like a good user.
I guess Twitter would have a good listener. But I just used the word user like I did a couple
weeks ago on the show. That's not what I meant. Somebody who uses people. You hate users. You
hate fake friends. Fake, yeah, fake ass friends. But yes, so there's a lot of topics we've covered
that were voted on this month. American Idiot, the musical specifically, but it is also like
an anniversary of American Idiot. And there was an episode idea for Olivia Rodrigo's guts
for me to review the first half of that, which I would I was excited about that. I was like,
oh, I would like to do that. Then there was Don't Blame Conan, the segment that David Letterman
did over a decade ago during the whole Conan NBC fiasco that we've talked about on the show before,
which is just such a fun, funny thing that a lot of people like. Evan Susser, of course, likes it.
Guy Selga is a big fan of Don't Blame Conan. He was tweeting about it when we posted the-
It's one I recall every so often. I have the book. I never read The Late Shift, but I definitely
like when, oh, I'll Ask for Christmas, that Conan J. Leno hardback, and it's in a box somewhere here.
I never read. Okay. Just to clarify, the user on YouTube, Banshee Neat, cut together a fan
compilation. It's called Buka D underscore Epo, podcast fan compilation. It is 26 minutes, 17
seconds. I have it saved right in my watch later, so I didn't lose it. I lost the tweet. Thank you
so much for doing that. I will go down that rabbit hole. Yes. It's fun. I have a lot of questions
about the Pepo saga, but that would take too much time today, I fear, but there's still questions
because there's so many different ways that it manifests the Pepo situation.
This simple mispronunciation was going on for years before I actually ate in the restaurant.
Yes. One of my favorite things is that you said the wrong thing because you never ate there,
which is really good, like as if you went to the restaurant. That's a pretty reasonable
excuse. I guess, but it was out in the world. It's not like you go to a new restaurant and
it's like you're saying the name of it all the time while you're eating. But anyway, check that
out. Today, we are doing credit card points, and we are, of course, Scott-free. We are free to be
naughty. We are free to be bad little point boys. You get extra points every tangent.
That's right. Yeah. Bonus category this month. Do you think Scott would grimace when I said,
well, this is an episode hosted by two naughty little point boys? Yeah, absolutely.
You think so? Yeah, I might have grimaced a little. Did you? Well, no, I liked it.
You like it, yeah, because you're a naughty little point boy. Yeah.
Yeah. So yeah, today's episode is hosted by two naughty little point boys, but Scott has sent
in an audio message. Oh, fun. And he told me not to listen to it before it goes on air.
It's just going to be incredibly distorted static. It's possible. It's going to be a shock to our
system. Do you think it's some sort of audio weapon? It could be a weapon. It could be like
Manchurian candidate activation, you know. So he's going to activate you or me or like,
what do you think? Okay. Well, I hope it's not some sort of auditory bio weapon. I guess bio
weapon is not what the word is, but an auditory bomb or something. But here we go. Scott here
in a Scott-free episode. I'm just going to take a few minutes of your otherwise Scott-free time.
First of all, I want to thank you for selecting Mike's credit card points. I think it will be
very educational. And here's why. I think this will serve for you the listener as something of
a Scott simulator. You will get to sort of being John Malkovich into me as my co-hosts talk and
talk and talk and talk about the kind of thing that they talk about whether on or off the show,
whether in a podcast or at a party, if I don't change the subject. And we'll see if by the end,
you don't start expressing a certain degree of, I don't know, annoyance or boredom or
some of the qualities that I sometimes express. Perhaps you, the listener will unlock your inner
Scott. But if we want to do something very different next month, I would like to vouch
for the topic. Bug main does whatever it wants. And in doing so, I want to acknowledge a voting
block that I know is out there that I will call the never buggers. I see you. I know you're there.
I want to see if I can make a cell to you specifically. Let me say this. I know bug main.
I know this man. And one thing I know about him is that he is a true blue theme park fan. He is a
big Epcot guy. He is a Disney world hotels guy, like all of us. He is us. Bug main is us. Honestly,
if you're the kind of person who's mad that club three is not about theme parks more often,
your best bet might be to let bug main do whatever he wants. Another thing that could happen
is that what bug main wants is to not do this. He might ghost me in text message form,
not show up to a record, and then we would just move to the next topic down. So a vote for bug
might be a vote for not bug. Think about that. It is definitely a vote for chaos,
a vote for Skittle, and a vote for Scattle. Please consider that, especially after you have
listened to what I assume will be two hours and 45 minutes of Mike's credit card points. All right,
have fun, everybody. Buzz buzz. Okay, well, wow, what an impassioned plea. Yeah, I don't know why
you wanted me not to listen to that. I was thinking he was going to like really lay something down
and shock. Did he think I would maybe like railroad bug or something? I like that he used
the terminology Scott free. Yes, but that's very respectful. But he used it twice very close together.
So that could be fury. And you think that would also be understandable. It's I've been respectful
and furious before. It's very complicated. When was the last time you were respectful and curious?
No, respectful and furious. Oh, sorry. Like you're biting my tongue. It's a new thing.
I'm working on it. Respectful and furious. Can you think of a time when you were respectful and
furious? I think, oh, probably any time I've had to deal with like a car dealership for sure.
Like, I don't want to scream at the people, but I, you know, you're there for like,
you're going on the two hours and it's like, you're approaching, you know, you know, you're
going to be approaching our three soon. And it's like, oh, I, these people are just doing
their job. Unfortunately, their job is totally nebulous and insane. Right. Okay. That makes
sense. So you're saying you have, you had a problem maybe with that and now you're, you're,
you're better. I think so. You're better at it. Well, I don't think today I'm going to make you
furious. I think you're going to be elated. I think I am going to be elated. Yeah, for sure.
Yeah. I mean, very interesting, uh, bug main hypothesis, uh, voting block, a lot of voting
blocks talk lately. Uh, so I'm curious to see how that would play out just so, um, to give people
some context. We are recording this, uh, Thursday, November 7th, about two days after election day.
So the one recorded on the Monday before election day was a little squirrely and this one is
probably a little squirrely in a different way. Um, I guess, yeah, I think we'll be squirrely. Uh,
hopefully it doesn't sound like we're, uh, depressed. Yeah, sure. Um, but yes, uh,
we're doing this Thursday. So it sounds like Scott is planning on being back for the next
maybe three, I suppose, unless he just thrusts bug upon us, which it would be funny too. So it
sounds like he will be back for at least a club three if bug is involved, but I wonder if bug
doesn't win this, will he just say, I can't do it? I don't know. Here's a good question. Does bug
know anything about this? Does he know anything about our Patriot tier structure? No, no, does
he know anything that he has like was an option? Oh, I don't know. I bet he doesn't, but I could
be wrong about that. Um, well, Jason, do you want to throw some, I mean, I'm not anti-bug,
um, but do you want to throw anything out for the future club three poll? Well, um, you know,
the runners up, uh, we're all pretty fun. I actually like, Oh, hotel talk could be very fun.
You just want to call it hotel talk. It could be Jason's hotel.
I just met like, there's so many Disney and universal and like theme park hotels that we
have not touched upon. And I feel like I appreciate hotels and amenities more and more as I get older.
My mom always said like, Oh, you hardly spend any time in the hotel room. And I'm like,
I spend a lot of time in the hotel room. These days, you know, I spend much more time in the
hotel room. So you're, so what do you want to call that, that choice to throw to the list?
I think I met more like, uh, uh, you know, Polynesian or grand California and club three,
like, well, I don't know. It's what the people want. Okay. So you want to do the
grand Floridian on club three. I don't know. You can put it on somebody else to nominate it. So
we can't, it's possible. We could do like the, um, you know, uh, the moderate, uh, moderate or
something, um, Port Orleans or Port Orleans. Okay. Pick one. Throw to the listeners.
I'm not trying to put my finger on this scale. I'm asking you to do what I'm asking you to put
your Scott just put his finger on the scale. Okay. He put his buggy finger on the scale. Well,
we all approach it differently. You're just throwing out ideas. I had the phrase right
before I pulled in here of a show, an episode on club three called, uh, Mike and Jason's infinite
playlist, where we just go back and forth and talk about the music we've listened to in the last week.
So I'd like to throw that out on that would be, and if Scott's there, it would be Mike, Jason,
and Scott's infinite playlist. Oh, sure. Yeah. And that's just, that's just talking about what
we've listened to. Well, you know, I played, I listened to so many podcasts. I feel like I
listened to more of that. Well, then that's on your infinite playlist. Sure. Sure. Okay. I love
to shout out, you know, especially friends and peers and stuff. Well, you will be able to shout
out so many peers and then I will be able to shout out many peers too, like Sabrina Carpenter
or Olivia Rodrigo. Okay. Cause we're all in the entertainment. Yeah. That's what I'm saying.
My man. All in the entertainment industry. Okay. So today's topic on club three, and let me read
the full, full little blurb here. It was nominated by Ethan Abraham. And he said,
I don't think it's a full episode, but I want to hear Mike's credit card point stacking reward
technique. And then did add maybe a small time griffs and living, uh, living frugally round table.
So thank you for that suggestion. And this, this sort of idea, I just simplified it when we put in
the poll, but I said on the second gate that I think we have to expand it a little bit to other
points, other reward apps. And yes, if, if a grift, you know, happens upon this conversation,
then we will talk about it. Sure. Um, because, uh, I think you and I share a love of points.
We're both point enthusiasts when it comes to apps, when it comes to credit cards, et cetera,
et cetera. Um, and it's, it's a daunting topic for me because I really, I tallied everything up,
how many different rewards points I'm subscribed to. And it's like 30 or so, like it's at least
30 when you combine like fast food apps, when you combine hotel rewards, uh, airline rewards
and credit card points, like it's so many. And there's things I'm even forgetting. Like
I thought I would be able to have a concrete number and I, I I'm still finding different rewards
points. And for the average person, I feel like I was trying to analyze this. Why is this? Why do
we like points? Is it just cause it's gamified? Is it because like, Oh, this is, uh, we're winning.
It's at like having like playing a fighting game and you get a certain amount of points
or like you collect coins in Mario. Is that where a lot of this comes from? Do you think?
I think so. I mean, just getting freebies, like just knowing there's money on that tape, like,
Oh, free, free, uh, burrito, like free burrito at McDonald's. So yes, I will. I went to McDonald's
before this and spent some points. Oh, great. I spent 3000 McDonald's rewards points. I think
it was 3000 on a large coffee. I think, wait, let me check out my McDonald's. So what we're
going to be doing a lot is, and I hate to be vulgar. You know that I hate to be vulgar,
but we're going to have a little bit of a Dick measuring contest here today. We're going to say,
how many McDonald's reward points do you have? How many Jersey shore shore points do you have?
And we'll try to figure out like, who is the superior points haver as well. Well, there's,
so there's so many questions to answer today. Will we stay on podcast the ride or we leave to
do full time points and who has more points? I suspect it's you. I suspect you have more points
than I do. Okay. Well, let me tell you, I just found out the bad, some bad news. Uh, my McDonald's
points, I am currently at 3023, but I had 1300 points that expired at the start of the month.
Well, that's the, that's the most depressing news I've heard all week on Thursday, November 7th,
2024. That's the most depressing thing that's happened this week. This is a thing that I hate
with point when they do like, you gotta use them or they expire. That shit sucks. Yes, they do.
They do that. And it sucks. I feel like how did you let that expire? I don't know. And I live so
close to one. You should be going twice a day. Yeah, I don't, I don't think that will be good,
but don't have enough health concerns. I've already pulled back on refined sugar and
unfortunately I do feel pretty good, but I also feel a little bad.
That you're not eating more McDonald's? No, I'm not eating more sugar. Sugar specifically.
Cause you just said this, the doctor said you should probably eat less sugar.
Yes, she, she's very, she's big on like more fruits and vegetables. Try a smoothie at the
start of the day. So I'm like building a target. You can get a sugary, natural smoothie. I think
she, she is more like natural sugar is better than refined sugar, than like candy sugar. I think
that's probably right. So she's saying it's better to have a strawberry than eat pixie sticks. It's
like, I'm going to try making like almond milk, frozen berries, handful of spinach, scoop of peanut
butter, ice. And that'll be sweet. So that will taste sweet. That will taste sweet and it will also
like be good for your body. Cover up the greens and be good for the body. So, but I was bummed
at the points expiring. I am bummed that CVS doesn't just send me $4 for candy every week.
They're too crafty now. They send $4 in like- Have you noticed the CVS has changed since we started
talking about it? The last two years, I feel like it's changed a lot. Sometimes I get $4. Sometimes
I get like $10 off 40. Yes, I know. And it's like, why the fuck would I be spending $40 at CVS?
Like- CVS is like a devious boy, like a boyfriend who treats you poorly, but then like for a couple
weeks treats you well. Yes, that's a great metaphor. And then you're like, oh, you know what? We did
have a rocky month, but look at what the boyfriend is doing now. But we had a really fun weekend.
We had a really nice weekend because that's when you get that $4 like scot-free. You get that $4 off
or a 50% off sometimes you get. It's like 50% off one item at CVS. One item that is not on sale.
Every other item at CVS is on sale. Well, that's the little trick too. But yes, once in a while,
they give you that good weekend with that shady boyfriend. Yeah, you go to like a bed and breakfast
and you have so much fun. So much fun. And then it erases the sting of the last few months of like
not responding to my texts, not calling me back. But then, yeah. So here's another pet peeve.
And this is I'm trying to fix it. But before the pandemic, for the start of the pandemic,
I would sign up for every like stores email newsletter to get coup, like free side dish,
free dessert. Yeah. And then 2020, everyone switched their marketing to emails. So now
I am bombarded with like so many emails. I signed up for too much. And so I have 6,000 unread emails
in my inbox. I have to go through every day and look for actual emails from like friends and
coworkers and doctors. Like I have to find the real emails. How long does that take you to find?
I mean, I know what you're saying to some degree, but usually they'll stick out. It doesn't take.
They stick out. And I've been, you know, faving those senders so they go to the top.
Yeah. But have you unsubscribed? Because you can unsubscribe. I'm trying to unsubscribe.
Open your email right now. Let's take a look. It is open right now.
Okay. What do you got in there? Let's start reading it.
Like Roman's bookstore. I like from its bookstore.
Fromins? Roman's. In Pasadena. Oh, yes. That's where we met Robert Evans, of course.
And so Rita's Italianized. I should probably unsubscribe.
Unsubscribe right now because they do it live on mic.
They moved out of the valley. I will unsubscribe right now.
Yeah. So you're getting, because you know, you can bulk a race, like promotional emails
and go in the promotional tab on your Gmail and then you can auto select all of it, essentially
6,000 emails at once and then trash them all. Is that an auto?
Yeah. But basically, I mean, you have to do a couple, you have to do a couple clicks,
but it will do that. So you can, you probably won't miss a personal email,
but it won't get thrown into that pile. But there could be deals. There could be
deals. I need the old Navy emails. Old Navy always has a deal.
They always have a deal. And there's always like a weird, like every
different store has a different way to try to trick you into going in there.
And old Navy is like, there'll be like four stacking codes on top of each other.
It's like they'll have a sale, but then they'll have an additional 10% off code.
And then if you like, maybe sign up for their email, you can get an extra five or something.
This is a hypothetical. I don't want to slander old Navy by getting their
promotional strategy wrong, but they have a thing where it's always a running some
like percentage off sale. If you look at their website.
Yeah, I was always to like, I was, uh, that's one of the things that I sometimes find difficult
with credit card points is like, I don't buy clothes a lot. Like I go through little phases
where I refresh my wardrobe, but I was always an old Navy guy.
And then I kind of tried to switch to J crew factory, uh, cause I thought that you tried.
I did for a few years and then I thought those clothes got worse, but old Navy and gap factory
felt like the quality got better. You made a blanket decision in your life to
pivot from old Navy to J crew. It wasn't a blanket decision. It just happened naturally.
It was an organic decision to pivot away from old Navy.
Was it, was it cause you were like, I'm going to have to be dressing fancier now that I'm an older
man? I, I, uh, I think it was in my lead twenties, early thirties. And I was trying to like dress
nicer, especially when I was like on the dating scene, I was trying to look respectable.
It wasn't until I realized, uh, well after that, like, oh, some people,
mostly men show up to dates looking like trash or like super shitty hypothetical dirt bag
boyfriend. We were talking about CVS how you end up with a dirt bag boyfriend or a new term
that's probably going in the dictionary of like word of the year. Situation ship.
I don't hear that. I mean, I hear that a little bit, but I hear that mostly from you.
I believe young people are saying it, but I don't, I don't hear it in my everyday life.
Here's the thing. Also young people might've been saying it through two to three years ago,
and it just got to me. Well, I believe that. Yeah. So are, what would you say now your clothing?
Are you more of an old Navy man still? Um, I think now I try to, but be a little, um,
I don't think old Navy is the worst offender fast fashion wise, but like these pants are old Navy.
The shirt is D pop, uh, and this jacket is just, or this hoodie is just for the loom from Amazon.
Uh, I just wanted a plain gray hoodie. Um, and did you start shopping at old Navy because you
were a little sailor boy and you liked the name old Navy. I ask them every time I go in and I
salute them and I confuse all the teenagers and 20 year olds. I worked there and say at ease boys.
When you come into old Navy, I, before I come in, I say permission to come aboard and I have to scream
it because no one's ever at the entry way for that store. And you want all the employees to
kind of line up and salute you as you come in. I know there are, have too many obligations to do.
And you play a good ship lollipop on your phone. You blast it as you're going through. Yeah. Well,
okay. I mean, I'm clothing brand sort of agnostic. I'll buy, I'll wear anything from any place.
I don't buy anything that's that expensive. Generally. I do buy on D pop like second hand
thrift. It's not a big fan of second hand. You don't like it. Jane got me really into it. And
there's just so much theme park stuff on there. There's nothing wrong with it. And I like having
some old stuff, but there is like part of me that like feels like the ghost of the people who wore
it are in the clothes. Sure. Even if they're not dead, I feel like there's like something like the
shirt could take me over. Like I I'm, I'm being half serious when I say that there's like something
about secondhand clothes where I'm just like, Oh, another person wore this. I almost feel like
I'm invading their space or I'm inhabiting their body on some level. I don't know. There's some
weird thing I've had since I was a kid about wearing someone else's clothes. I like it to feel
like it's, Oh, this is mine. Like I have, I have planted my soul in this t-shirt that has Chuck E
cheese on it, which I do have a lot of graphic teas of characters I liked when I was 12. Yeah.
You're much better at rotating stuff. I feel like maybe I am. I don't know. I have a lot of shirts.
I have too many shirts and I have to get rid of a bunch because there's just too many make a depop
account. Sell some of them sell shirts now. T-shirts. Yeah. Huge market for it. Yeah. Yeah.
But how much am I going to make for like, not a lot, but a Coles Mario t-shirt that I don't wear
anymore. Oh, I see what you mean. I don't have anything really good in vintage. I think I,
I have my old rock and roller coaster t-shirts somewhere and that's like 20 years old,
25 years old. So there's a few old pieces, but I don't think anything I have right now is valuable.
Okay. So yeah. So you're, so you're primarily your old Navy man now.
I think so. Okay. You know, joggers only hold up for so long. Yeah, sure. Like whether they're
sweatsuit or, um, twill, uh, I believe is the word. I always call it like khaki material.
Okay. I just call all slacks khaki. I tried to put on my old, some older jeans
to my LCD sound system show and I was like, Oh, they were like too small. And I was like, Oh,
dad, I don't want to think about dad can't get into his old jeans anymore. Yeah. No, I don't.
I did, by the way, I got into them when I wore them. Oh, so I still, I still got it. I'm just
saying, I was like, Oh, this is a really, Oh, this depresses me. Well, I also, the slim fit jeans.
There are a lot of styles of the 2010s was a menace. Why did we do that? Why did we all
make ourselves so uncomfortable? I don't know. I don't know. Um, anyway, so you have how many
McDonald's points? Uh, I said like 3000. Okay. I have 2,277 McDonald's points. Okay. Just use
3000 to get, um, uh, a large iced coffee. And for me and McDonald's, I tend to hoard points.
I tend to get up there. What you're talking about 12,000 points, 13,000 points. And then I'll try to
maybe use them all at once or on a big order. I don't know why that is, but that's my McDonald's
strategy. I think with every other type of points, what I'm generally doing is I'm getting some and
I'm spending them. That's what I've been doing lately for almost everything is I'm spending those
points fast. I think maybe five years ago when I talked about points for the first time on podcast,
the ride, I was more of a hoarder. I was more like, Oh good, I'm going to save it up for a big
thing. A big, uh, vacation, a big Wendy's meal. I would, I would take my points and I would,
I would put them in a little pile and wait and see them accumulate. And now for whatever reason,
I'm just like a jumpy with points ready to spend. I'm ready to spend them. And I don't know why
that's just life. I guess you change when you get older and I've changed. Um, and I, and I'll say
this, I have less time for points right now. And this is the thing I love. I love this topic
suggestion, but I do have less time for points. We're still, we still have a lot to talk about,
but I do have less time for points. And that's just what happens when you have a child and you
get older. But, but you know, as she goes to school, I will start to gain more hours. I will
start to get my time back and get more points back. Sure. Um, as far as other fast food points,
what, which ones do you like? Which apps, which, which rewards programs are you a fan of? Uh, uh,
Jersey Mike's, I think Jersey Mike's has a very good rewards program. It's called shore points,
which I appreciate shore points because sometimes it's just McDonald's reward. Sometimes these fast
food companies, they don't have a fun name. And I feel like that really hurts it, but shore points
to me, I've always loved, I've loved shore points. Yeah. And of course you are from there. So that's
why you have a personal affection is because you feel when you spend your shore points, when you
gain a few points, you feel, it feels like home. It feels like home. I mean, it's more North Jersey
was where Jersey Mike started, but still Jersey Mike's you step in there, the employees behind
the counter say, hello, Jason, you salute them and see, I say Addie's boys. There's a number of them
in Burbank. Uh, now actually, yes. One is opening up pie chains, old apartment. And it's like, can
you imagine if that had been there when we would eat there three times a day, we'd eaten there so
much. Uh, I do think, uh, Jersey Mike's is reasonably close to a decent, like East coast Hoagie.
Yo, do you think it's comparable to the back home Hoagie? I think it's comparable. Um, uh, I love
Philly's best, which is a local chain of like Philly centric food, cheese steaks and hoagies
and tasty cakes and such, but they could put a little more meat and vegetables in those sandwiches.
Oh, you want more? Well, you can add like double meat and you can add, but it's a little more
money. Yeah. But Jersey Mike's I think does a pretty good job at loading those up. Even if you
get a smaller one. Right. Um, I have 59 shore points in my account currently. I spent
shore points last night on a free sandwich. Oh yeah. So just yesterday I spent free spent points
shore points on a free regular Jersey Mike's sandwich. Um, and I'm trying to figure out it's
the app makes it a little confusing how much, uh, how many like points add up to actual sandwiches.
And that's what, uh, that is a pet peeve of mine when it comes to points is that I want to clear,
um, a clear answer for how much one point equals how much a dollar or what 50 points equals. Yeah.
So if they keep it a little bit nebulous, sometimes I feel like they can change stuff
and I don't like that because Dunkin donuts, these motherfuckers had me on the hook for a while. They
opened that Dunkin donuts in Burbank a couple of years ago. And man, it seemed like you could get
a free coffee every other time you went there. Yeah. And points, man, points meant so much more.
They were worth more at Dunkin donuts in these early days. And then all of a sudden the switch
was made. Yeah. Well, the food quality has gone downhill remarkably. Like it is gnarly. The donuts
still fine. Okay. Like I much more prefer our many local mom and pop donut shops here, but I like
their fake sugar coffee at Dunkin. I don't make the concoctions like on TikTok where it's like
20 caramel swirls and 10 caramel shots. Yeah. All right. Like, let me hold on one thing. You just
said the food quality at Dunkin got worse because I don't know that the food quality at Dunkin has
ever been high. I feel like the breakfast sandwiches there used to be delicious. I read
sandwiches and bagels. We also always used to get them before it went on trips.
You're not tearing up thinking about that, right? No.
I disagree with that. I think the food has always been awful at Dunkin donuts. I think the coffee's
been good to find. The donuts have been good to find. But anytime I've ever gotten anything else,
it's like it fell on the floor and they're handing it to me in a little paper bag.
Well, the Burbank Dunkin donuts always had some sort of funny business going on.
There is always funny business in the Burbank Dunkin donuts.
I am not just being facetious when I say that. All the employees, I think, walked out and they
had to bring in new employees at some point. There was some sort of a massive walkout.
I hadn't been back there in months and months. Then about a month ago, and I'll talk about this
in one second, about a month ago, two weeks ago, whatever, I went in there and I was wondering,
hell, is it different or is it the same? No, it was absolutely the same. No one knew what was
going on. They're doing their best in there. It just seems like there's a problem with the
way it's organized. It seems like there's a problem with communication because I had to ask
for my mobile order and they didn't seem to know where it was. There's a lot of fumbling around.
Then I said, well, I ordered the Halloween Munchkin donuts and they were like, oh,
we don't have those. Then they just gave me a bunch of other ones. I didn't want those.
I wanted the ones with the black and orange sprinkles.
Yeah, I was mostly at some point going to try the half of this is coffee and a half of this is
orange syrup or half of this is coffee and half of this is green.
I guess I would have tried it. Here's a grift. Here's a small-time grift.
I don't know. This maybe doesn't always work, but what I would do with this Dunkin',
okay, don't tell anybody. What I would do with this Dunkin' is I knew by the end of the night
which donuts they wouldn't have in stock. Say Dunkin' closed at eight, which I think it does
seven or eight, they would always be out of a jelly donut when I would try to do it.
But what happens then is because it's the end of the night, there's a bunch of donuts they got to
get rid of. They give you the day-old. I would order on mobile a jelly donut. You go up in the
front or you go up either the front or you go on the drive-through and you would say, oh,
I'm mobile order. You would say your name and they go, oh, we're out of that. I would go, oh,
you are. Oh, I'm sorry. They go, well, do you want something else? I go, oh, yeah, regular donut,
whatever. Then I think there's two things going on here. They feel bad that I came expecting a
donut with jelly in it. Then at number two, they got a bunch of donuts they need to get rid of
because it's the end of the day. They would hand me a bag and it would be full of donuts.
Okay. I showed up at a recording once with a bunch of donuts and I'm like,
oh, Duncan's about to close. They gave me the day-old. They gave me the end
and everyone thought I was insane. But this is pretty common for bakeries or donut shops.
That's right. But that is a little bit of a trick. You would have to agree.
They open a Boss Bagel around here and they gave me a ton of bagels because it was closing.
Bagel Boss.
Bagel Boss. What do they call it? Boss Baby?
They open a Boss Baby.
They open a Boss Baby. A Boss Bagel would be good.
Bagel Boss, of course, unfortunately, a few years ago became notorious on the internet
because that crazy band screamed at it. Remember the Short Muscle Man?
I'll never forget the Short Muscle Man who screamed at the Bagel Boss.
And then he almost had a celebrity fight, but then he pulled out and I forget who he was going to
box. The guy from Bagel Boss.
No, I don't think so. What was that guy's name?
Well, he's in the Trump cabinet now.
Yeah, he's going to be the Secretary of State. I know the yelling man in the Boss Bagel is
definitely going to be in the cabinet. But yeah, so that is a little trick and I did do it a couple
times. I haven't done it in a while. And I'll be honest with you. I don't know now what they won't
have at the end of the day. I'm not confident like I was months ago.
I do know. Oh, here we go.
Yeah, here we go. Here we go.
You order the limited time stuff.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Because they're not going to have a lot of that.
Right.
In theory, unless it's like a dud where they end up with a lot of it.
So maybe if you're going to Starbucks, order the Wicked drinks at the end of the night.
You think they'll be out of the Wicked drinks?
Maybe. Well, I think the Halloween stuff, like they had spider donuts at Duncan,
where like it would be like a big spider in frosting.
Yeah, they don't have a lot of those.
They don't have a lot of those.
Like one tray or a half a tray of those.
Right. So yeah, you try to do that and you want to make them feel bad for you.
If I have a tip for all of the listeners out there.
Oh, you always want to make the service workers feel bad.
You want to make the service worker feel bad for you.
And then when they feel bad for you, you get extra.
Sure.
And that's the biggest thing you could probably take away.
None of this is financial advice.
I wouldn't recommend getting into points unless it's something you're ready into.
But a thing I can offer to all of you is that you should make
the people who work at these places feel bad for you, feel sorry for you.
Don't yell at them.
They're working probably for low wages.
They're doing their best.
It's a hard job.
So never make them feel bad because you yell, but it's okay to look pathetic.
It's okay to seem sad and pathetic when you do this,
because sometimes you'll get an extra little treat.
I think that's a smart play.
All right. Coming back a little.
I have a hundred and fifty eight short points.
A hundred.
Oh, you could get a couple.
I feel like you get a couple of regular giant.
Oh, I've never.
See, I always use my short points before getting the giant
and I've never ordered a giant from Jersey Mike.
Well, you know, I think what's happened is I use the app for delivery
a couple of times where we're like, it's later in the day.
We're tired.
We don't want to cook.
We don't want to go out.
Let me ask you this question.
Have you post mated a Jersey Mike's?
I've used the app to order delivery.
Oh, so it'll go through the app.
I think it goes through door dash.
Because I was going to wonder if you could get short points
when you do a Postmates, but it does auto do it through the app.
It auto does it through the app.
Is the giant sub like Dagwood sized?
Have you ever gotten a giant sub before from there?
I've seen.
I think Jane has ordered it.
And I think once we both ordered giant subs where you both ordered giant subs.
Yeah, we were really hungry.
You could.
But isn't a giant sub a giant?
I think it's just like two regular size subs.
And you ate that in a meal?
No, I would eat half and then say the other half for lunch the next day.
OK, well, that's a smart play.
Yeah.
That's a good tip.
And I'm being serious.
Well, you were, you know, during early days of the pandemic,
you were like, if I'm getting takeout, I'll get two entrees.
Right.
I have one the night and then one the next day.
Because the cost of even starting up a delivery is so high,
it does it like adding an extra entree doesn't really add too much more than just
like you may as well get it.
You may as well have the person bring an extra one
because that's not going to shoot up your costs.
You're already paying a certain high cost to have food delivered.
Yeah.
It's not going to jack it up so much.
You have to tip a little bit more.
But other than that, you may as well do it if you're going to like indulge.
For sure.
Yeah.
And I always try a lot of the restaurants I like at Burbank have
if you order direct from their website, if they have their own delivery guys.
That's better.
Yes, of course.
That's better for the business and often is faster
and often is like cheaper because they're not taking like this middleman.
These apps are all middlemen.
It's like this is the love and hate with apps
because a lot of these apps, these delivery apps,
they're basically just a middleman who's going to siphon money out of
you and the company that they're delivering.
Well, sure.
And even social media now, it's always just been data harvesting.
It's like if it's free, you're probably the product, right?
That's what they say.
Like, you know, I want to go ahead.
Sorry, I'm jumping all over the place.
I am too.
We should.
What did you want to talk about?
I want to talk about the Wendy's app.
OK, you're building the credit card points.
That is what?
Yes, I'm glad.
Yes, that is what we're doing.
We're building to the what's called the chase trifecta.
Are you still on the chase?
I am still on the chase trifecta, which is this is just a teaser, of course.
We still have another two hours of these other things to talk about.
Great.
The chase trifecta is having multiple three cards.
You can there is something where you have four cards, but I don't fuck with that.
I have three chase cards and you combine them to maximize your points.
That's sort of what we're building to.
But I want to get through a couple more apps and a couple more point reward systems.
A thing I like about Wendy's is Wendy's has reward points
and they also have deals in the app, which I like.
And the thing that I like about this is you can stack deals and rewards,
which is not the case.
McDonald's does not let you do that.
Correct.
So McDonald's will say we have a deal for what a dollar large drink,
two dollars for three cookies or something.
That seems crazy.
They wouldn't do that.
But you get my point.
It's a deal.
And then in addition to that, you would like to use some of your reward points to get a free item.
They will not let you do that.
It drives me crazy.
OK, but the trade off and I this I am not the only one who had said this.
I have seen on the way are Wendy's on Reddit.
Wendy's quality has gone way downhill the last few years.
They used to be the best fast food.
Now it's like I feel like Burger King's quality has gone up.
Wendy's has gone down.
Although Burger King chicken has gotten shittier during the chicken sandwich wars.
It was a big proponent of the chicken sandwich.
OK, wait, hold on.
Hold on.
OK, you've.
So wait, you're you are.
I am I am playing the game of this episode and I'm just don't think you left.
I am doing a lot of food like you're this is this is the second time in the episode
where you've stumped me by the take of the food quality.
Do you think when I'm trying to focus more on?
Well, that's what I'm trying to think about.
I'm trying to figure this out because I'm I'm being more analytical in talking about the points.
But then, of course, and I'm not mad at this.
You're talking about the quality of the fast food, which is a thing I like to talk about as well.
But some of this I haven't considered the Dunkin Donuts take.
I think it's completely absurd.
That food has always been garbage to me.
That food has been awful.
Maybe we just had better ones.
It's possible.
Sometimes you get stuff.
I thought my Jersey Mike sub yesterday was delicious.
I had a tuna.
I used to be a lot more skeptical.
I like their tuna, too.
I think it's great.
And I added banana peppers.
I added dill pickles to it.
You can do that in app.
I like the hoagie spread.
I like the chopped cherry pepper spread.
I have cherry pepper spread in the fridge.
Hoagie spread.
Some places call it hoagie spread.
And that's what you're saying.
It's chopped cherry.
Chopped cherry peppers.
Is that come out of Mike's way?
Jersey Mike sub?
You have to add it manually.
No, it doesn't come on manually.
They don't give you a jar.
You mean you have to add manually.
I had to buy a jar just to have it.
So and what brand of hoagie spread do you have?
I believe it's here.
I'll find it.
Bento hoagie spread.
I'm getting the name wrong.
It's Italian American brand.
Italian American.
Going back in my Amazon orders,
which I do use Amazon more than I used to.
And it does suck shit.
That has definitely gotten worse.
Yeah, sure.
I'm just interested.
I don't know that you've ever said hoagie spread.
I don't know if you ever said those two words together
on podcast the ride before.
I feel like I don't call it.
I never call it that.
I just said hot peppers.
I see.
But that is called hoagie spread.
Some places call it hoagie spread.
I don't love that they call it that.
Hoagie is one of the funniest words for a sandwich.
I recently saw someone refer to the Philly accent as hoagie mouth.
And I think that is very hoagie mouth.
Hoagie also would be like a funny nickname.
Like if your little rascals character would be
like Jason Hoagie Sheridan or something.
Oh, it's Hoagie.
Here comes Hoagie.
He always has a big sandwich with him.
It does seem like a Hoagie's Heroes character.
Well, because on Hoagie's Heroes,
there would be a character named Hoagie and Hoagie.
Nicknames?
Yeah, I know that.
But I'm saying if it was called Hoagie's Heroes,
why would there be a different character named Hoagie?
Look, they weren't as precise at writing.
Well, you think writing was bad in the 70s.
So they would say, ah, shit.
Not Pento, Cento Hoagie spread.
OK, we got a character named Hogan on the Hoagie's Heroes.
We need another name.
What about Hoagie?
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
If you go into an Italian deli back here,
there's just a wall of Cento products.
It looks similar to salsa.
Kind of.
I mean, it's chopped cherry pepper,
is probably a little vinegar.
And it's good.
I have it in there.
I've had it in there for a while.
And I don't know.
I never know how long pickled or preserved products last.
So I don't know.
That's another Club 3 episode.
It's Pickled and Preserved Products with Jason.
If somebody wants to suggest that.
I don't.
I am a lot more conscious of expiration dates nowadays.
Because I used to eat anything.
Jade, living together.
Jade's like, throw that out to me.
You are like Homer with the big Hoagie behind the radiator.
I am like Homer with the big Hoagie.
It's just that nowadays, if I get a cold,
or I get stomach ache or food poisoning,
it's 10 times worse with that mess.
But in the old days, you would welcome the food poisoning.
In the old days, I had an iron stomach.
Although in the old days, I feel like you would be like,
yeah, my stomach really hurts.
And now it's because you were eating expired Hoagie sauce.
You were drinking a glass of hoagie.
Let's get to the whethies.
Hold on, hold on.
No, there's another thing, too.
I'm trying to imagine an episode of Hogan's Heroes
where Colonel Clink is very confused
because there's a character named Hogan
and there's a character named Hoagie.
And they had to write so many episodes a season.
Perfect.
One episode done.
Hogan and Hoagie.
And then Hoagie gets transferred to another Prisoner of War cam.
I mean, there's got to be a show where that is like a common joke.
The two characters.
I guess on New Heart, they had the three guys
that were all named the same.
Was it Bob?
Not Bob.
But they were Daryl.
This is my other brother, Daryl.
They would have the same name.
So that was kind of the gag there.
But Hogan and Hoagie.
Because maybe Seinfeld should have had a character named
Kramer and Cramie or something.
There's a character named Cramie.
Sure.
And Kramer keeps getting mad
because everyone keeps accusing him of the stuff Cramie.
Right.
All right.
Well, if you want to suggest for Club 3 next month,
Hoagie stuff with Jason or Hoagie sauce or pickled items or anything.
Anything in that vein.
I'm interested to hear it.
So Wendy's lets you stack.
So sometimes it'll say free large drink with purchase.
Sometimes it'll say free cookie with purchase.
And I like those because with Wendy's, you can click on that
and the free and the purchase can be a free item in your rewards column.
Did you know this?
I don't think I knew.
I don't think you knew this.
I don't think the world knows this.
Wendy's app does have decent offers.
They still do have decent offers.
So we'll get to the food quality in a moment.
But what you can do is you can go into your app
and you can say, OK, I'm going to use some of my points.
And like I'm just I'm in here.
For instance, I have 618 Wendy's points right now.
And I could get let's see with that.
I could get a Dave's single, just a regular hamburger.
So you could click on that and get your free hamburger
and then you could combine it with a deal.
So for instance, here I can get a dollar small chili with qualifying purchase.
So that would that would be OK.
So I can get now go to Wendy's after this and maybe I will.
I can get a hamburger for free
and then a small chili for a dollar.
OK, and that is so protein.
That's a great protein.
Even though you shit on Wendy's just a second ago.
I love Wendy's.
I just you lament the fall lamenting like I hate that lettuce
they use now with the big stalk down the middle.
They change lettuce.
They did change the lettuce a few years ago
and I had been researching this and following this
and trying to get to the bottom.
You've been following.
Is it just the West Coast or is it something else?
And I think it was during 2020.
Let us supply this is a disaster.
This is disaster capitalism.
Yeah, this is when there's some sort of crisis.
That's iceberg lettuce.
So you said the best chunks of lettuce.
And now it's just like it's just stock like.
Did you you crave iceberg lettuce?
I I didn't crave iceberg lettuce.
I craved Wendy's iceberg lettuce.
Really?
I've never heard another human being on the planet.
You get a beach.
You would get a big chunk on the junior bacon.
Yeah, no, I know.
I know what you're saying is like one of our things.
You like the Quarter Pounder.
You like Dave's single.
I like a junior bacon cheeseburger or regular McDonald's cheeseburger.
I like the little ones.
I think the little ones they use on the Big Mac are the little ones.
Maybe that's why you think some of the quality is declined is because.
Those I think are fine.
Those I think.
But I just I don't like the lettuce.
I feel like the cuts of chicken are not as good.
Like for the spicy chicken sandwich.
Yeah, I I would give you that.
Maybe there's a 20% drop off in the quality of Wendy's fast food.
But I don't think it's abysmal and it depends.
It's it's one of those where like you go to the one by the Empire Center
and it depends if they've got the A team working or they get the B team working.
Sometimes it's a little chaotic going to that one.
Sometimes the Empire Center at rush hour at night.
People are going into work.
It's right by a freeway off ramp on ramp, you know.
So it's just a little stressful.
Yes, I always order.
Let me ask you this.
Do you order your items, your fast food before going?
Oh, yeah.
On the app.
Yes, you do it.
I almost exclusively do that now.
I get really mad at myself when I forgot to do it or which is rare.
Well, I got really mad because I was I was visiting family.
I was back east in Pennsylvania and Jersey recently for the first time in like a year.
And I forgot to log into the Wawa app.
And any time we go to Wawa, we'd be at the cash register.
I was like, shit.
And I would try to open the app and it's like, log in.
And I'm like, I just buy the two dollar coffee.
And you couldn't get your rewards just by putting in your phone number?
I don't think so.
Or maybe you can.
And I just only go a few times a year.
How many Wendy's points do you have?
I have six hundred and hold on.
Hold on.
Six hundred and I know six eighteen.
I have three hundred and eighty three.
Three eighty three.
Oh, yeah.
Never mind.
I take it back that I was going to be losing to you in points.
It seems like I have more points than you, maybe.
I think so.
OK.
And what was and you still you were going to Wendy's like you would you redeem for,
you know, usually redeem redeem for a junior bacon cheeseburger
because those used to be a dollar and now they're like three bucks.
Yes.
I mean, everything is going.
Everything is up.
We know the price of meat is up.
But yes, now you also said and there's so many things you keep saying
that I keep forgetting to dig in on.
You said the Burger King has gotten better.
Well, I just think, you know, we get the Wednesday
Whoppers and Impossible Whoppers are like three bucks.
Is that a weekly?
Do you get that every week?
No, we don't get it every week.
You get the offer.
How many Wednesday Whopper days are you celebrating?
Maybe like once a month.
But like Jane, if we're doing fast food, Jane's vegetarian.
So she really likes the Impossible Whopper.
And I like it a lot, too.
That's another thing.
I don't like the Whopper.
I like the Whopper Jr.
Whoppers too big.
This is crazy.
I'm a little guy.
I guess that's it.
Is it because is it more to do with the amount of food
or is it is it overwhelming to hold?
No, it's not overwhelming to hold.
It's just like the amount of food.
Like, I don't have a huge appetite.
I had a huge appetite for sugar and doctor's orders.
I'm supposed to cut back on that.
Sure.
The last time I went to Wendy's, I got a son of a baconator
and I had never tried the baconator set up before.
And I thought it was disgusting.
Too much bacon.
Hamburger tasted like hot dog.
Well, that doesn't sound bad to me.
Hamburger tastes hamburger tasted like hot dog.
It was just too much.
It was better to have a little bit of bacon
to get the flavor of the bacon and the cheeseburger.
How much was too much bacon?
How much bacon do you think is too much?
This is like it's a number of strips of bacon.
A number.
I forget the difference between the son of a baconator
and the baconator, but it's a lot of strips of bacon
and mayonnaise like I like the lettuce
and mayo to counteract it.
I don't think there's anything that I mean.
Okay, wait, no, I take that back
because the Duncan thing floored me.
The loving the fast food lettuce to me is wild.
It's only a Wendy's.
Burger King has okay lettuce too.
Is there another, and I guess I have to ask the listener,
is there another human being on the planet
that craves Wendy's lettuce?
There are a lot of posts on our Wendy's about the lettuce.
I'm not the only one who has noticed this.
How often are you on the Reddit for Wendy's?
Well, I think I follow it on my burner.
So every time I open the app, it shows me a gnarly picture.
Can you open up our Wendy's right now?
Yeah, sure.
I just want to see what the topics,
do you ever post on our Wendy's anonymously?
I don't think so.
No, I just, a lot of these apps I just like on
and I'm trying to get off them and read more books
and watch more movies.
Because you are obviously the best reader
of the three podcasts, the right host,
but when you say you read a lot,
is a lot of it just that you're reading the Wendy's Reddit?
No, no, I have my paperbacks and I met Kendall.
Like here's one.
Is this normal?
And I don't know what this stuff is,
but it's like a drink.
It's like a milkshake or it's a frosty
and then on the bottom there's orange sludge, orange goo.
It's the Spongebob pineapple frosty,
which people are very not thrilled about.
I had it.
How was it, the burger or the frosty?
The frosty.
Do you have the burger?
No, it's just a day's single with special sauce.
Yes, here's the thing with a lot of these promotions
and a lot of the fast food places.
They dress everything up to make it look different and it's not.
Now I will say that frosty is a different flavor,
so I appreciate that.
Pineapple, yeah.
And it is a pretty good, it's pretty good.
I don't crave it, but a lot of the times obviously
they're just trying to trick me.
Now I get tricked often to go and try a new item,
but it's generally the items they already have
and they're just like putting them in different sizes
and different configurations when you go.
Are you looking through our Wendy's?
Yeah, here's a picture of like a shitty looking spicy chicken
sandwich.
Yes, and they've opened this up and it's like half,
you can see inside.
A big nugget.
And that lettuce doesn't look good to you?
I don't like, I like leaf lettuce in a salad.
Okay, so that's not the type even of lettuce.
They changed it.
That looks like a healthier piece of leaf lettuce
or a healthier piece of lettuce.
Iceberg just is like a tasteless.
But it's mostly stock.
Let me ask you this about the lettuce.
Is the crunch satisfying to you?
Is it more of a texture thing?
I like the crunch.
I just think I like the lettuce, the way the lettuce.
You will say it's taste.
It's not taste because a lot of people have texture with food
and I feel like I have less of that,
but you think that it's more just taste
and not that you like a crunch, a healthy crunch.
Okay, do you notice different brands of water?
Can you taste it?
Yes.
Okay, I can do that too.
You can do it.
Do you think you do better than me?
I can't.
I didn't say I can do it better than you,
but I like hate the Sani and Awafina.
Club three, I agree with you.
Club three, water taste test.
If somebody wants to nominate that, Jason and I.
And then if Scott's there,
if we want to taste test different bottle of water.
Arrowhead and Evian are like.
Better.
Yes, better.
The kind, oh God, I forget the brand.
There was like a fancy brand they used to have at the Arclight.
And alkaline water, some places have, I like alkaline water.
See, I stopped doing alkaline water
because I feel like I saw a study that said it was bad.
I don't know.
And now I'm all, I know I tried to all be glass bottle
because of the microplastics.
Right.
So I try not to even have any of the glass bottles,
but yes, water I can taste.
But this lettuce thing is interesting.
I could see how it's better or worse,
but I didn't realize that that was such a thing that people missed.
There is also very funny comments on that spicy chicken sandwich picture
because someone talks about color correcting it.
Oh, to me it looked bad.
And they're like, wait, that's not your photo.
Did you color correct someone else's photo?
That's insane.
Someone on the Wendy's Reddit stole a photo
of someone else's dirty chicken sandwich.
I can't tell.
It's so confusing.
Here's a funny post where it's like,
all this stuff looks like it's on sale.
You put it in your bag.
It's $2 more.
That's fucked up.
Well, Wendy's was using that dynamic pricing.
They were like messing around with it, like it was Ticketmaster Airlines.
So if you had a Wendy's like outside a concert or something,
they would raise the price at the concert came out.
Yeah, that's psycho.
Dynamic pricing at fast food or at grocery stores,
you should be in the socks.
You should be at the center of town.
Cut me off in 15 seconds.
That's where the country's headed.
Yeah, no, I know.
That's where we're going.
I forgot.
Your Magneto helmet is right here that I bought you.
Yeah, my Magneto helmet is a place of honor.
It's under a big history of Marvel Comics coffee table book.
It's so cool.
You have a full-size Magneto helmet that I bought you.
Anyway, it's right here.
And I just got distracted by it.
And I'm not going to cut that part out.
Oh, here's one I think someone is being positive.
Their frosty and fruit cup and loaded fries look reasonably good.
Yeah, I mean, that could be color corrected to make it look a little more appetizing.
It's kind of a grayish hue to it, which isn't so enticing to me.
Look, I'm on some subreddit.
I'm on Reddit a little bit.
And I've never thought to even go on Wendy's.
And I'm not again, I'm not I'm going to go on.
It is what I'm really because I was trying to get to the end of the chicken sandwich.
I feel like I started you unintentionally got me into these subreddits because I follow like
the squared circle wrestling subreddit.
Sure.
Yeah, Marvel Legends subreddit.
People do cool little scenes with their actually pose their figures or they have all about it.
I know all about it.
You know what I like?
When you get points and rewards points like I buy these toys from this company NECO.
We've talked about it before.
Generally, Ninja Turtles.
I just got my comic con exclusive.
For some reason, it took forever to get those in the mail.
OK, Peter Laird, Kevin Eastman, creators and Ninja Turtles.
Their original turtle design toys came in the mail.
That's very cool.
I was hoping it was the action figures of them.
Well, they did make a Kevin Eastman for New York Comic Con, which has been procured
by Griffin Newman for me.
Oh, OK, that's good.
Which because I get sold out so quickly on the website.
Because you got me.
There was a Todd McFarlane action figure in the nineties.
Of course.
And you would mail away for it.
You got me that.
But there was a more recent two pack with Todd and a spawn action figure based on his
original childhood drawing.
Yes, which is really fun.
So yeah, I love that.
And there's a character.
They just made basically a Jack Kirby figure in the Ninja Turtles.
Which I have in the other room.
Which is great.
Which is so much fun.
So yes, I am hoping there's more Kevin and then eventually Peter figures.
Because there's like animated versions of them.
That to me is so much fun.
Stan Lee figures, they've had those before.
But to have the figures of the creators of the stuff hanging out with their creations
on your display.
Very fun.
Eating pizza, having a party with a boombox.
Like you always do fun little setups.
I have so many fun little setups.
But anyway, so yeah, I just finally got those toys in the mail and those are awesome.
Because I don't know, they're great.
Because they're original.
The original version of the turtles and Kevin and Peter both had slightly different
designs for like the original turtles.
And they've rendered them beautifully.
But so I looked on the website and I was checking like to...
I forgot, I was just checking to make sure it said it had shipped.
And NECA has reward points now.
And they gave me like retroactive points for all the things I've bought over the years.
Wow.
Wait, did you have to ask for that or they gave you that?
I just was in my account.
Wow.
And I was thrilled.
So I'm looking through and I'm like, oh, I can get some of the universal monsters.
I can get some gargoyles.
And I have like...
Disney gargoyles or just decorative gargoyles?
Disney gargoyles.
Okay, thank you for clarifying.
And I have 28,855 points.
And each figure is like 5,000 points.
So I can get like five figures.
Five figures.
I'm like, you know, that's how much I make every year.
And then that's how many figures I'll get this year for free.
Yeah.
So I like that.
Anytime I...
That was a surprise rewards point situation.
Because it's generally, yeah, you get rewards points for fast food, airlines, hotel.
But toy reward points?
Get the fuck out of there.
That's crazy.
So yeah, if you ever order from there, it will accumulate and you can get free toys.
Let's see here.
I wrote so many different apps and things down here.
What do you think about Target reward points?
Well, okay.
So I like Target reward points.
And that was, for a long time, I resisted.
Like getting a store specific credit card.
But I did get a Target card like six months ago.
Just because they give you 5% off immediately.
I resisted this too.
This is where the point brothers are falling just in line with each other.
And this is never...
We've never talked about this before.
No.
You're hearing this conversation live for the first time, folks.
But yes, I resisted as well.
But this Target card, you get 5% off all your purchases.
And then you also do accumulate points that can then be redeemed.
Now, they just changed their point system.
They had started like punch a phone number in a few years ago.
Right.
And I do go to Target fairly well.
We still do the dry about pickup.
Sure.
You can do that.
And that is one where I was like, oh, I try to have cash on me so I can give them a tip.
Um, you know, because that is very nice, but I imagine kind of sucks.
Although maybe it's nice to get out of the store and get some fresh air.
Can't it be both?
Can't it suck and be nice to get some fresh air?
I'm assuming that's probably the most common.
Yes.
Yeah.
Here's a little trick.
If you're doing a Target order, okay?
If there's a coupon, say there's 25% off a $50 order.
Yeah.
Something like that.
And you don't want to spend $50.
Maybe you only want to spend $30.
Like whatever it's household products, it's beauty products.
They do, um, like soap, beauty and soap stuff a lot.
And then they do like, yeah, household stuff.
But it's like often $10 off 40 or $10 off 50.
If you still want to get a little bit of a discount, you can buy stuff.
Say you sort of sending it to the home, send all your stuff to the home.
You can buy $40 worth, get that $10 off.
And then return stuff and you'll still get a chunk of that discount.
Because what they do, they don't go item specific and then take the discount away.
If you return things, they just split it up among your items.
And it's a percentage of discount.
Right.
You're not going to get the full, say it's 25% off.
You'll get basically 13% off.
Okay.
So if you buy, if you, as long as you spend and you hit that discount,
you could return an item and then you will still get a chunk of it off.
Sure.
So it won't, it won't penalize you for returning other than just take a little bit
of for the percentage of the discount, but you'll still save some money.
Well, I will sometimes, sometimes we've had the experience where they,
this isn't really a hack.
It's just like, oh, I don't pay for that.
Like you get grapes or blueberries and you open it up and there's a moldy one right in the center.
So they do make it very easy to just go in the app and make a couple taps to get your money back.
Oh, oh, if you get, this is like a Postmates or where?
In the Target app.
Oh, in Target.
Yes.
And the pavilions like grocery store app.
Like that is, yes, you can do that with Walmart.
You can do that on other apps is that sometimes if you go, oh, I need to return something.
It just goes, keep it, which is what Amazon used to do, but Amazon is a lot stricter.
Now, if there's a, like a, like a low priced item that you're going to return,
they want you to return it.
They're ruthless.
They do.
And like I had, I think I got one of these hoodies and the big hole appeared was in the cuff.
And I was like, can I get a replacement?
There's a big hole in this.
And they're like, yes, send it back.
And I'm like, well, you're just going to throw it in the garbage.
Like I watched that Brandy Hillfield documentary and now I'm scared of like,
oh my God, all this clothing waste is washing up on beaches in like Africa.
And I'm like so guilty.
And so I'm like, you know what?
I'll take the new one and I'll just keep the old one.
Just charge of whatever.
So you'll pay for two.
Well, in this instance, I was like, well, I don't want to send this back for $13, you know?
So I'm like, well, I'll wear the one, wear the one out and I'll wear the one around the house.
You know, so you didn't get any sort of discount.
You just got a new sweatshirt.
And this is because you're worried about clothing waste?
Yeah, I'm like, if I send this back, I'll throw it in the garbage.
But it's like, well, if I keep it, I'm sure I'll get used to out of it.
You know, or like if I had to paint or something or like scrubby stuff, you know?
Scrub.
Okay.
Interesting.
Or like I'm going to physical therapy.
Oh, it doesn't matter which hoodie I wear.
I just need flexibility.
Can we go back to that moldy blueberry?
What about it?
Would what's the moldiest piece of fruit you've ever eaten?
I do not eat moldy fruit.
Okay.
I throw the line somewhere.
But a few years ago, I tried to get money back because I did a Walmart pick up.
God, a dozen eggs.
I kept picking them up and they were all broken on the pot.
All but like three or four were broken on the body.
We just kept picking them up and just egg would fall out.
And it's just a huge mess.
I need to call to get the money back.
And it's kept getting transferred to calls.
It was so much.
Jason, I want to just describe what he's doing.
I've got my head in my hands.
He has put both of his hands on his head looking like so frazzled,
like his cards blew up in front of him or something.
Yeah.
How long ago was this?
When you had all your broken eggs?
It was like 2021 or something.
So we were doing the podcast.
Did you bring this up on the podcast?
This feels like you would.
I don't think so.
You would be like, can we do a topic called eggs?
It was like a wimpy thing where he keeps picking up eggs and they fall out.
And they didn't break because you did something comical with them?
No.
And it was like the Eglin's best, which is like a nice brand of eggs.
A classy brand of eggs.
It was reinforced.
It was on sale.
It's like top hat egg.
That's like an egg wearing a top hat.
I really don't notice the difference, by the way, with brands of eggs.
I notice it with water.
I don't really notice.
Do you think you would notice the brand of eggs if you ate more raw eggs?
Well, that's the thing.
In Japan, they eat raw eggs.
They mix it with rice for breakfast.
Like their eggs are better quality so they don't have a lot of food poisoning.
Well, Rocky ate the eggs.
The movie Rocky.
Rocky did eat the eggs.
Yes.
But you know what I'm saying?
The cooking then obscures maybe the taste or the quality.
I wouldn't know what is better unless...
If it was right from the farm and it was properly prepared, then maybe I would notice.
What's the ripest?
You've never had eggs at a farm before, right?
No.
I think I went to a nice brunch place and it's like, oh, this yolk is so colorful.
It's just like a better color.
That's probably the fastest the egg has come out of the chicken and then into your mouth.
Because I wonder what would be the difference?
Say they had a chicken...
I think it's just a richer taste of the yolk.
Is there a restaurant where the chicken is in the back room?
That's how fresh the chicken is, that the egg is.
Excuse me.
I don't think so.
I mean, maybe a coop in a backyard.
Do you think it would be a fun idea to have a restaurant with a chicken
pumping eggs out, a bunch of chickens in the back?
I don't know if I've ever seen...
Someone must have tried.
To have it like, oh, this is...
You know how they bring out seafood restaurants where you see,
oh, I would like to choose this salmon or I'd like to choose this whatever fish.
This one would you be like, oh, I'd like to pick this chicken to hatch to open my egg.
Exactly.
Yeah, I don't know.
Probably not.
It seems unreasonable.
It seems like a hard thing to do.
Let me ask you this.
Do you like when you get the fish with the tail and the head on it?
No.
Okay, I don't either.
If I'm eating meat, I don't want to be reminded that it's alive.
I just find...
People eat fish heads, but I don't...
I just find I don't know where the bones are.
It does seem scary.
It's hard.
It's too treacherous.
Yeah.
It seems like I'm going to bite right into the bone, but I don't know...
I'm very stupid and uncultured.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Don't put yourself down.
I think a lot of people don't know where the bones are in a fish
and are maybe hesitant to bite into a tail and to a little fish skull.
I mean, like sardines.
I got a couple cans of sardines in there.
That's a good lunch or snack, but those you can crunch.
Those bones you just chew right through.
Oops, I ate the bones.
Yeah.
Oops.
Well, but that's not an oops.
You're not supposed to de-bones.
Oh, good.
I ate the bones.
Nice.
Yeah.
No, that's good.
It's good that you ate those bones, but they're tiny little bones.
My stomach just rumbled so hard after talking about the tiny bones.
My brain, not even thinking, not even consciously, got so...
It would start salivating.
My brain started salivating at the idea of tiny bones.
I know they say do other point, like try others, include other stuff too,
but they just really become a foodie podcast.
Let me ask the listener this right now.
And I guess Scott is a listener right now.
So let me ask the listener this.
Is this what you wanted?
Is this what you thought this would be?
Let's get to some credit card stuff.
Is this what have you wrought?
The people want the credit card.
What have you done?
So the Target card, I think is a good deal.
Well, if you go to Target a lot and you buy groceries there and you buy other stuff,
it makes total sense to do it.
It's 5% off every purchase.
And if you're even casually checking the deals, it makes a lot of sense.
And if you're a toy person, they recently have been having 25% off like one toy,
and they'll have different deals like that.
And you can get a pretty good deal on something.
I bought the neck of Vincent Price figure that just came out yesterday
on the Target app.
Because I get all these, I have all these different alerts when a new toy is available.
And they also, Born to Rock Alf is on the Target app,
but then it sold out before I was able to buy it.
And he's dressed like Bruce Springsteen.
And it's the episode where Alf sings to the teenage girl on the show that he's in love with,
which Jason's making a face and I agree with the face.
But it was the 80s.
They weren't really thinking.
Well, I was saying this, Jane, the other day,
because we were talking about like 2000s teen movies.
And I was like, yeah, I was in high school.
So it made sense that the characters were like teenagers, like cute, cute girls.
And it's like, obviously, the actors are all probably 20 or 25 or something.
But it's like, oh, yeah, there really was a lot of sexualization of teenagers in the 2000s.
Sure.
That was weird.
It's weird now.
Yeah, I hear you.
But it all started on Alf.
It all started.
How old is Alf, though, supposed to be on the show, Elf?
That's a good question.
How do they age on Melmac?
I don't know the answer to it.
OK.
But I don't think I've clocked a lot.
I knew Alf.
I had a stuffed Alf.
I loved Alf.
I don't know.
I just called him Alf, which is like Hoagie on Hogan's Heroes.
Alf and then his friend, Alf.
His friend.
His cousin.
His cousin, Alf.
They didn't think to name him like Spike or something.
There should have been like a knockoff foreign Alf called Elf.
There could be.
Hey, I like to eat dogs.
I just learned about I was OK.
I've been getting advertised bootleg Star Wars blu-rays of like they call it the
specialization like the original.
It's ripped off original 35 millimeters.
And I was trying to find on the website and there's, you know, all the new Star Wars
stuff.
They put the Mandalorian in a bad patch on blu-ray.
But there was also like Turkish Star Wars knockoff like called The Man Who Saved the World.
Yeah.
So these are.
Yeah, these are.
We talked about this last month, like the different foreign ET knockoffs.
Yes.
Like Koki, which I think I forget which I forget which country that one's from.
But yeah, after something's popular, a bunch of different countries and American
filmmakers also will just make ripoffs of it.
Well, I think I really hadn't gotten a lot of bootleg stuff, but I for Jane's birthday
one year, I got a Spice World on DVD, Spice World, very out of print.
Oh, so you bought a bootleg.
So I bought a bootleg off eBay unknowingly.
Oh, and then I thought it was real.
I thought it was real.
I thought someone had just found a box of it or stuff because I bought like Unbreakable
on blu-ray recently for like six bucks or something.
But that was not a bootleg.
That is still in the shrink wrap.
So what is a bootleg copy of Spice World look like?
Well, here's the thing.
The insert of the front and back of the case just seemed a little janky.
And then I put the DVD in and I think it just starts the movie and it's a decent quality.
I watched through some of it, just make sure it was okay to give as a gift.
Should we delete this?
Because now you're implicated in a bootleg crime.
I guess it's on Club 3.
Let me ask you this and the audience this.
Does anyone from the FBI listen to Club 3?
Do we have any FBI agent listeners?
Because I once asked if we had any pilot listeners because it didn't seem right to me.
People who are pilots to me seem so professional and together.
Why would they listen to our nonsense?
I think we did have one person say they were a commercial pilot.
Oh, okay.
Maybe two.
I forget it, but I think one person did say.
So I'm asking now how many FBI agents are in the audience?
Do you think we have one?
Or do you have a desk job at the FBI?
Yeah, that counts.
Are you a receptionist or a paperwork or a paralegal or something?
Or like whatever position Skinner had, Mitch Pileggi on the X-Files.
Or a third-party vendor.
I'm sure they outsourced some stuff for the FBI.
What would they outsource at the FBI?
Entry or temps.
I don't think that'll count.
You don't think that counts?
Okay.
But what if the person who brings in donuts and coffee,
this has to be somebody who's a food vendor at the FBI.
I don't think I would count that.
You don't think you would count that?
I would still be curious about that.
I love learning how systems work.
I would be interested if you said, oh, I go into the FBI and I change the light bulbs.
Or I go in there and I'm trying to think what you would need in an office.
I go in there and I just make sure that the pens have enough ink in them.
There are nice pens at the FBI and I fill them with ink.
The ink filler at the FBI.
I do want to hear about it from the listener,
but I don't consider that person what I'm talking about.
I don't consider them an FBI agent.
Yeah.
Okay.
But is the FBI where you're not allowed to say you work for the FBI?
No, I think you're allowed to say.
Okay.
Because I knew a guy at the church I went to growing up.
Guy there worked in the counter-terrorism division.
Got very busy after 9-Eleven.
Okay, sure.
My stomach just grumbled as soon as you said 9-Eleven,
so I don't think it's related to anything food-wise.
I don't think it was rumbling earlier because of the bones.
I think it's just because I'm hungry.
Very funny detail.
We were recording at Casa de Claire in Sheridan.
It's the first time we've ever recorded here besides Zoom calls.
Yeah.
And Jane just texted from the bedroom, are you done?
I assure you we are not, but I told her we can take a break.
Are you dumb because it sounds like what you're talking is just dumb casual conversation
or just because she wants to come out here?
I think the dog needs a lunch.
Okay.
Well, she can come out here if she wants.
We could take a pause.
Anything's possible.
We could keep talking while she comes out here.
There's a puppy now here.
We're talking about credit card points.
Oh, we're about to really get into it.
Jane just exhaled very, very loudly.
We're creating content right now.
All right, let's take a real break.
Okay, fine.
All right, all right.
Jane has left your back from the restroom,
and now she's left the apartment so we can get naughty again.
We can start talking.
The Point brothers can start getting to be little naughty Point boys again
without the public commenting, without people hearing us
other than the wonderful Club 3 listeners.
Credit card stuff, credit card points in general.
Again, not financial advice also.
This is why I was thinking about this.
Is anyone going to go into major credit card debt after they hear?
Yeah, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Maybe just don't do anything because I don't want to be responsible.
This is not financial advice.
This is just a lively discussion about what might be possible
if you engage with certain credit cards.
But there's a couple things you can do that I do.
I'll speak personally as far as credit cards.
You can get bonuses from signing up for certain credit cards,
and then after that bonus, you can earn rewards.
Every card is a little different.
Every card is a little confusing.
You go on websites and it'll break down all the differences in the cards.
But still, it's sort of confusing.
And you have to make sure you're not signing up for something
that's going to make you pay a big amount of money every year
because some of them have fees.
But there are cards where you can get 60,000 bonus points
just for signing up and then hitting a certain amount of money
spent on the card within three months.
Yes.
And that's, I think, when people say credit card churning,
that's especially what they mean.
People will sign up for credit cards specifically to get that bonus
because then you can redeem that bonus for travel or whatever,
depending on what the card is.
And that is the most exciting thing when it comes to credit card points for me
is those big bonuses if you can find a card that has it.
Have you ever done this?
Have you ever done a big bonus situation?
Me?
Yes.
A number of times.
OK.
What's your, can you recall?
I think as I started to become a big boy, I started to become an adult.
When you started going to J.Crew.
Yeah, when I started going to J.Crew, I opened cards with Bank of America
because that's where my accounts were.
Sure.
And so, yeah, if you spent a certain amount of money,
you would get like 150 bucks or something.
Right.
So you've gotten, you think that's probably the biggest reward is like 150.
I think the biggest I've gotten have been like 300 maybe.
OK, OK.
It's a contest, I suppose.
What I do is I mostly use two cards nowadays.
Yeah.
And one that I like is a Capital One Saver card.
And it's 3% cash back on food.
Yeah.
Be it restaurant or grocery store.
So that's only for food.
Yes.
And I have a Bank of America card, which is very confusing because it was like,
you're a loyal customer and you have such and such accounts with us.
So we're going to give you 1.25% cash back and then we're going to double it.
So basically, that card is 2.5% on everything.
Yeah.
But it's like, oh, you need to keep up this balance between all your accounts over X
number of months.
Right.
And so that is a pain in the ass trying to make sure I have enough money in accounts
or whatever.
But it's just nice, like I just use that card for everything that's not food.
And then I pay it off every month.
Right.
So and that's a big way to get points is like put all your purchase on cards,
pay them off before interest happens.
Yes.
Well, that's the big thing is like.
Or pay the statement balance and that'll take care of it.
Right.
Because you don't want to get the interest because that's where they get you.
These are all like designed to screw you essentially.
They're designed to like make you get excited about the bonus and then you get like in debt
and then you start having to pay them like 20% or something like something crazy.
Interests are terrible on most of these cards nowadays.
I feel like my parents have had cards like since the 90s and they're like,
oh, God, this is getting up to 11%.
And I'm like, my credit card is like 18 or 25%.
Like it sucks.
Yeah.
I mean, some of these bigger cards is like 21.9.
I'm looking right now, 21.99% interest.
And yeah, you want to you only want to do this stuff if like you can pay your cards
down every month if you just have money.
Yeah.
But like so if you're going to get a bonus on one of these cards,
what I like to do and I've seen people recommend this is if you have a big purchase coming up,
if you go, oh, shit, I need to like my car needs new wheels.
It needs a new engine.
It needs a new windshield.
Let's say something bad happened to the car.
I'm going to have to spend like two grand or something.
That's the time to sign up for your new card to get the bonus because it's just
you're going to be spending a bunch of money anyway.
As long as you have the money to pay it off, then you can use that to get your bonus.
Like that's that's the way to go about that in my mind to be to be responsible
because you don't want to get in a situation where you're just trying to like spend another
couple grand to get your bonus.
You need to have a plan to get that bonus.
Yeah.
And that's like when we moved last year, I really probably should have opened a new card.
It's a perfect time to do it.
Thing on that, because the one car that people like that is the Chase Sapphire Guard.
Well, yes, that's a big one thing.
All these days, you don't need it.
You like it.
I hate saying all these financial institutions.
Well, that's true.
But you like that one has very good perks and bonuses, but you have to spend so much
in three or four months.
And I just never could finagle like Chase Sapphire Reserve credit card
earn sixty thousand bonus points, which basically translates to six hundred dollars
after you spend four grand on purchases in the first three months from account opening.
So, yeah, you have to be like, oh, I'm going to be spending a good like if you move in
maybe to a house and you're going to spend on a washer and dryer, you're going to buy
a new fridge, you're going to use that credit card to pay for the moving itself.
Then that starts to get up there.
It starts to it starts to add up.
But yes, it is four thousand bucks is a lot of money to have to spend.
But you get six hundred free dollars if you can hit it, which is good.
Yeah.
And I don't remember.
I don't even see this is I got this so long ago.
I don't even remember what smart way I did this because I think I did it smartly.
Well, because that's one of the ones with an annual fee.
Well, yes.
And this is look, this is a discussion we I guess we have we can have it now.
So so basically there are multiple Chase cards, but they call it the Chase trifecta.
Yes.
Which is the magic combination of three cards.
The Chase Sapphire Reserve card, the Chase Freedom Unlimited card,
and then the Chase and Freedom Flex card, I think is what they're calling it now.
You should just be freedom.
And that's one where you pick each financial quarter.
There's bonus.
There's different ones.
Sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Different ones for like gas is five percent cash.
Right.
And there's this quarter there's you get five percent cash back on any PayPal
transactions on certain charities, on pet shops and vet services and McDonald's.
OK.
So you have the freedom.
Oh, I actually just have the regular freedom.
I don't even know if they offer that anymore.
So so but it's the same as I think the Freedom Flex, which changes.
I kind of gave up on these Chase card because it was too much to track.
This is what I will admit to the listener now.
I have slacked in my tracking and sometimes I forget to even activate the bonuses
and then I go, oh, shit, and then I completely miss
that I should have been using my Chase Freedom card to buy my McDonald's
and not my Chase Sapphire to buy my McDonald's.
Right.
So and I try it.
I should be better because you could.
But if you're really into this and you have free time on your hands,
you can really optimize all your points because five percent
cash back is pretty good.
Obviously, McDonald's, if you're eating, you know, in the old days,
you were reading McDonald's every other day.
So you really could have added a point with five percent back.
So that's the fun.
If you have a brain for points and math, I feel like you can you will enjoy this.
And I did.
I did stay on top of this for I feel like for a year or so where I was like, OK, good.
Now I have to make sure that every time I buy groceries, I go to this one.
And when I do trap, when you go out to eat, you do the Chase Sapphire Reserve.
So and I was really on top of it.
And now I have like I still know the general points like how much
something gets me depending on where I'm shopping or what I'm doing.
But yes, so these are these three cards.
And basically then what happens is you get all these points
and then you can you can take the points and transfer them.
So you can take your points from the freedom.
You can take your points from the unlimited and transfer them
to the reward portal of the Chase Sapphire Reserve, which has the best rewards portal.
Yeah. So essentially all the points go in one pot.
So you put all your points in one pot.
You can use that for your stores or travel.
I both travel for the show once or twice
on like these rewards portals.
I do think they, like everything else, are progressively getting worse.
I agree with you.
Yeah. The offers are not as good.
And it's like you are sometimes better off just going to the hotel company's website.
Don't fall for third party booking.
That's a trick nowadays.
Third party booking is a trick.
You're correct.
And it's like hidden a lot.
So like oftentimes going right to Hilton or whatever, you will have a better.
Yes, I agree.
Sometimes sometimes if you have an airline tracker that says, oh, prices to Japan
for flights is or they're down, whatever, there's a good deal going on.
Sometimes you can then go into your rewards portal for the Chase Sapphire
and see if it's reflected there as well.
And sometimes it isn't.
Sometimes it's not.
Sometimes you add up and you go, oh, I may as well just spend $500 on a flight
versus the like $600 in rewards points it's going to cost.
So you do have to be vigilant as far as figuring that stuff out.
But in the rewards portal, I find sometimes there are good deals
where you can use your rewards points to get gift certificates for other businesses.
So for instance, right now in Chase Ultimate's rewards,
you can get Apple gift cards, 10% off, Under Armour gift cards, 10% off.
Chili's, my beloved Chili's, which I know you said is so far away right now in Encino.
You and Jay love Chili's.
You turned down us going to Chili's recently on the Marissa and Justin Halloween episodes.
Because I get tired.
I understand you get tired, but it is 20 minutes.
We could do it.
We don't have to do it today, but we could go because I want you to be a cheese
influencer.
I do want to see you do a cheese pull.
Yeah, I do want to see it and I would love to see it added.
But I also said I don't really like the mozzarella sticks.
Well, when was the last time you had their mozzarella sticks?
Not in a while.
And you called them mozzarella planks.
Well, because the tech talkers were calling them planks.
But Scott called them a different thing.
I didn't say they were the official company brand, you know.
It sounded like they were.
It's like when we call it the Avatar Ride or something instead of Avatar
colon flight of passage, you know.
But planks is such an unnatural way to describe mozzarella sticks.
I agree.
I was just watching a lot of these.
Why do these take?
Where did mozzarella planks come from?
It does look like a plank of wood.
But but I know.
But don't you think somebody like somewhere called them that first and then it just caught
on?
You think some tech talker just called them?
I think someone called it in passing and then it caught on.
Do you think any restaurant has something on the menu called a mozzarella plank?
I mean, I'll Google it.
I don't know.
Maybe.
So OK, back to the rewards portal.
Let's go back in the portal.
Macy's, you can get 15% off gift certificates.
This is where I do think the value comes into play here.
I think this is a smart way to use your points, at least lately.
And again, I'm not doing as much travel, so I'm thinking more along the lines of,
oh, do I have things to buy gifts, et cetera, et cetera?
And that type of thing is attractive to me.
They have a thing.
If you buy Samsung, you get 15 times the points on your purchase.
OK, yeah.
So if you're going to get a new phone or something or if there's a different Samsung
product you want to purchase, 15 points times 15 times the points is a very good deal.
This is like I've seen hacks like this with Disney gift cards where it's like
Chase or something has like more points.
And then there's bonus for Costco or something like that.
So they go and buy gift cards at Costco or CVS and they know they're growing on a trip.
So they put money on that card.
Now, if you put a lot of money on Disney gift cards, you have to
you don't lose that card.
You know, it's not really tracked well.
So here's OK.
You've stumbled on something that I forgot to say during the target part.
This is how I get a little money off my annual pass.
OK, is what you do is target red card five percent off any purchase.
Great.
You buy Disney gift cards.
OK, you put those.
Now, Disney does it in the dumbest way possible.
You have to go to a separate Disney website to input your Disney gift cards.
You cannot just use your Disney gift cards on the Disneyland website.
There is a separate Disneyland website to load all of your cards into an account.
And then you have to link that website to your Disneyland account.
Now, I do it because I want to save.
I want to save money.
I want to deal.
But you can do that five percent.
So then you whatever Disneyland pass cost of the time, 450 bucks or whatever.
And then that's that adds up.
That five percent adds up.
So I buy the amount I need in gift cards.
I get the five percent off.
Obviously, I pay that off on my credit card.
And then I use that gift card to buy the annual pass.
And I don't do the payment plan.
Generally, I just do that.
Now, one time a year, generally, target offers 10 percent off on gift cards.
And that's around the holidays, around the holidays.
And that's the time to strike.
That's the time you really can get some money off of the extra five percent.
So you do that.
And then you get even more money off of your annual pass.
And I mean, depending on how often you go to Disney,
it would make sense to just get some cards as well.
If you're going to because you can use it in the park.
So just so I have this straight.
Yeah.
Disney gift cards, you buy them at Target.
They put the value on the gift card.
But if you want to link that gift card to your Disney account,
you have to go to a Disney gift card website.
Yes.
To then log into your Disney account.
And throw the balance, like link the two.
Correct.
This is so much work.
This is like when we were trying to link five day tickets
and we were all having a terrible time.
We needed this was hard.
All linked to get a virtual queue and finally figured out the queue.
If we scanned a QR code, it would register.
You go to Disney.
I swear you go to Disney gift card dot com.
So, OK, this is where we said this.
That sounds a little like a scam.
We've said it.
It does seem like a scam.
We've said it on every episode, but there is no episode more
where Scott is like having a stomachache right now or a headache
and he doesn't know why, but that his podcast has been taken over
by talk of a website called Disney gift card dot com.
That's coming in spoken.
Well, the people have spoken.
Obviously, they're loving it.
They're listening to this and hooting and hollering,
but coming like late in the episode to introduce a new website
that we've never talked about before.
Disney gift card dot com, which is the instead of just using
a gift card on any of the Disneyland websites,
they have a specific dumb website that you have to go to
and that adds that basically you have to use.
It's another middleman between you and just using a gift card.
But it is also the same login as your Disneyland and Disney store login.
It's all the same login, but you still have to go to different stores.
Anyway, we will promise this and I'll tease this,
more app talk coming up, more Disney confusion and app talk coming up.
If in case you thought we'd get less naughty after this episode,
all contrary, we're going to get more naughty with the app talk going forward.
Basically, you can get a decent little deal off of Disney stuff
using that confusing method.
Now, if that was confusing, let us know.
I'll make a little video, a little explainer video on this process.
If you want, if you don't want, tell me also if you don't want it.
See if I don't want to hear any more about this.
You know what I'll save for the other episode,
my reason that I get every Disney email twice because I have two logins.
Oh, well, I have a couple of logins.
Yeah, and it's a fucking nightmare and that adds to the email clutter.
Yeah, I will let it.
Was that your I have some, you know, talking about other points.
Oh, well, hold on. Let me or credit card.
Let me finish. Let me finish out this.
OK, so so you really have to.
This is it feels like such a young man's game
to stay on top of the credit card points and the chase trifecta.
I'm more and I'm more and I wish you know what I wish I could do right now.
So I should get rid of all the cards and start new.
You know, I wish I could I wish I could start fresh.
I wish I could just watch your credit score.
Wish I could be born anew. Sure.
Start again if I could start if I could start again, a million.
What's the line from Hurt the Nine Inch Nails?
If I could start again, a million miles away, I would start.
Keep myself.
I would close my accounts.
Because I do want to start because because once you have these cards, then
depending on your credit score and how much they won't, you can't get unlimited cards.
No, it's best to not open and it's best to open right cards a year,
especially to if someone inquires, you need a car loan or your credit inquiry to rent
a house or apartment. You have to watch that stuff.
You have to watch that stuff.
I had a very weird one where like I had a Wells Fargo Amex a while ago
and it converted to a Visa and I'm like, I got this for the Amex Bennett.
Like I got this for whatever signing bonus and like early deals on concert tickets,
you know, Broadway tickets.
Yeah. Well, like I look that happened sometimes with the card converts without
your consent, essentially.
Like I had a Virgin America card and then Virgin went away, the airline,
and it converted to an Alaska card.
So I have an Alaska card still open.
Yes.
But I don't look Alaska.
Come on.
I wanted Virgin because of the purple lighting in the cockpit,
not the cockpit, in the whole cabin.
But I'll say this.
I haven't traveled much and that Chase Sapphire Reserve card,
they've upped the annual fee to 550.
Jesus Christ.
And the thing that would still be okay, because it comes with a lot of things.
You get in lounges at airports if they're not too crowded.
Yeah, but they're cracking down on third party cards.
Yeah, that's true too.
So that's a knock against it.
But you would get a $300 travel credit.
So basically if you were going to be traveling a lot,
$300 would come off of the bill anyway.
And a little tip, if you book your travel,
like say with a hotel within a couple of months and then cancel,
they would already credit the card.
So you could kind of get around it.
But it used to be like 450, it used to be maybe even less.
I think I'm going to cancel this card.
Okay.
I think that I'm going to give up my Chase Sapphire Reserve.
That is okay to do every now and then.
Yes, you shouldn't do like constantly open and close cards.
That'll knock your credit score.
But I think I got to close it this year.
I think this is the last year, at least for a little while,
of me having Chase Sapphire Reserve card.
And it's a little disappointing to me
because that's like my cool card in my wallet.
That's a thick card.
Is it metal?
It's not metal.
I hate the metal cards.
I got a fresh one.
I lost my other one.
Ironically, you have a fresh one.
It's not the full metal.
But look, listen to this.
Folks, listen to this.
Put this up right against.
If you're listening to your phone, listen to your phone.
I'm using it.
To cut cocaine on Jason's kitchen table.
And I'm going to hand it to Jason.
To cut Old Bay seasoning.
This feels like metal.
Maybe it is metal.
Maybe you're right.
It's thick.
It's satisfying.
It makes you feel important when you put and you buy stuff with it.
So it really kind of hurts me.
But we just haven't been traveling a lot.
So I don't think it's worth it.
I feel like I'm going to have to downgrade my Chase trifecta.
I'm no longer going to be participating in the trifecta.
Sure.
Here's the thing with these.
Well, you can sign up for that Capital One card and use my link and I'll get a bonus.
No, but you'd love that.
I would love that.
I'd love everyone to do it.
Do you want to give out your code to the listeners?
I don't know.
That's pretty low.
I do have a lot of copays, though.
The listener should sign up for it.
Everyone in the Club 3 should sign up using Jason's code.
There's a limit.
I was going to say, is there a limit?
Yeah, that would be a great scam.
The problem with these metal cards, you can't put them in a shredder.
You have to send it back.
They give you a little envelope.
Do they?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
Well, because usually I just sometimes I get a bag of shredding.
I go to UPS or Staples and they have the iron mountain or whatever.
And they put it in locked.
When you get a new card, if it expires, they send generally a little envelope
and it goes somewhere magical.
I have never gotten that.
You've got a tiny little envelope.
Oh my God.
So that makes you feel special doing that.
I love this card.
They just sent me a new one.
So it's fresh again, fresh and important.
Let me ask you this.
We talked about the Target card.
Do you have the Prime card?
No.
OK.
I have that.
That gives you 5% off.
And then if you wait a couple, like if you're like, oh,
I said this to me in three days instead of two.
Right.
There's another 6%.
Another 6% or just adds it to it?
It takes up one.
I think it no, no, it adds it on top.
That is pretty good.
Yeah.
And I forget whether that's in your account or I think it's all Amazon points.
It kind of sucks that like everything else, Amazon is getting worse and worse.
It's more drop ship crap.
I just use it because I don't get out a lot these days.
So but Target is like, OK, well, this is like a little more reputable.
Like it's a Hamilton Beach can opener or it's like a OXO brand.
Like it's not.
Hamilton Beach?
Hamilton Beach is like a known kitchen supply brand as opposed to just.
Hamilton Beach sounds like you grew up on Hamilton Beach.
I between coffee makers and can openers are probably frankly.
Yeah, is it all a big scam though?
You know how like the like people who make like in microwaves,
there's a big article or something, a story about how there's all these
different brands of microwave, but they're actually all the same.
They're all coming from the same place.
Oh, it's like how like Costco brand liquor is like, yeah, it's probably brutal.
Great.
Like everything's a scam.
Everything's a big scam and trying to confuse you and the different like one
thing's a luxury brand, but it's only just because they ship it
to a place that's more expensive.
Oh, probably.
I learned recently about some made in the USA stuff is bullshit.
It's like finished in the USA.
Oh, wow.
Really?
Yeah.
So like looking like union made in the USA, it's much different.
There's a lot more qualifications on that.
But do you think you could bring awareness to this by doing a parody
of Bruce Springsteen's born in the USA called finished in the USA?
Finished in the US went down to a drop town.
I think it sounds like yes is the answer to that.
I mean, maybe.
Oh, yeah.
I've seen Hamilton.
I know Hamilton Beach Beach.
I've swam on the I've swam in the water at Black and Decker.
Like these are known brands.
Again, this is peace of mind.
Like you're saying this could be all bullshit.
Yeah.
But if it has the potential to burst into flames, I don't really like buying it.
That electric kettle is kind of a no name brand.
And it's because I thought it was a pretty color and didn't take up a lot.
Let me throw out this idea for Club 3 next month.
We record again at Jason's apartment and I walk around and comment on things I see.
I mean, I would rather you not because I've got shit everywhere.
We only ever have fun packed.
Well, just just like maybe in the kitchen.
We can even limit it to the kitchen.
Kitchen's in order.
Office is cluttered, but in order.
And then you have to admit, OK, so if someone wants if somebody wants this,
they can nominate.
Mike walks around Jason's kitchen and fridge and comments on things and talks.
I need permission from my better half.
All right.
Fine.
Don't nominate this.
We'll talk about it.
Maybe for January.
We moved all our Tokyo treat boxes.
Do you know about Tokyo?
Yes.
There's a little box of you get a box every month of different snack foods from Japan.
And it comes from Japan.
You track it.
It comes right from.
Right.
Because I want to just I want to I want to root around in here and see if there's I can
find the Taffy.
I want to see if there's Taffy box.
I think we've tossed any.
Oh, there is.
That's the that's the famous Taffy box.
That's there is usually a few Taffy, but there's no Taffy in it.
I don't think so, because I would love to see you massage your Taffy live in person.
Oh, between the hands.
Right.
To keep it fresh.
Well, maybe maybe everyone will get.
Oh, I bought brought you guys back Taffy before.
Yeah, yeah.
I who knows how if it even gets it's always so hard to eat so much of it.
You're not always in the mood for Taffy.
Taffy is a real ordeal to chew and it can finish.
Yeah.
You know.
OK, well, maybe in January I'll go through your fridge.
OK, I have some other to do.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Let me finish.
Let me finish this real quick.
Credit card.
OK, I just want to say, yeah.
So the Chase Sapphire is probably going to go away.
But if you like travel, that's if you're like traveling a lot,
I think it makes some sense to do it.
But yeah, that's that's that's the big credit card stuff that I've been doing lately.
But maybe I look at all of this as a way to overhaul my whole my whole deal.
My whole situation.
It's always good to reexamine habits and structures you establish.
Right.
But anyway, yeah, you go ahead.
What you were about to say.
So I have some even stupider points that like.
OK, so airline miles.
Are you an airline miles guy?
Geez.
What do you think?
I know the answer to that.
Of course.
So they call me Mr. Miles.
Well, you got a lot of names.
You got more names than I do.
Yeah.
So I LAX Philadelphia is a route I fly regularly for 18 years now
for a long time.
That was on USA.
Like USA had a big hub in Philadelphia and I would fly USA exclusively.
And then the price started to get bad.
I started flying southwest and wouldn't fly direct, but wouldn't.
They used to have a lot of flights where you would fly into Vegas,
but you didn't have to get off the plane.
But you'd have to sit there for like 30 or 40.
Sure.
And then it would go on.
Right.
That was fine because you just kind of sleep through it.
Or you read a book or something.
So US Airways gets bought by American Airlines a number of years ago.
And all my US Airways points converted to American points.
Now, I don't fly that much.
So I've only bought flights with credit card with airline miles like twice.
So I think I'm coming up on a free ticket.
I think I have like 16,000 airline miles or something.
Sure.
Now, in the early days of 2020, I had not used these miles or had not taken a flight.
So they're like, your miles are going to expire.
So I called and I'm like, there's a pandemic going on.
I don't need to fly anywhere right now.
What do I do?
And they're like, oh, here's what you do.
You go to the AA Advantage shopping portal and you can like go like this is just a middleman.
So like, here's the home page right now.
It's got like Apple, CVS, Nike, and basically what's Kohl's.
And basically what it is, is you select the store and it just takes you to that website.
But it places whatever marker.
It knows you went there through the American Airlines portal.
So I remember specifically the person on the phone was like,
oh, you can go to like the Walgreens website and buy a toothbrush
and you'll earn one airline mile and that will keep your account active.
That's what we've been telling everyone to do.
Oh, so you just have to get more points to keep your current points.
Yeah.
So I think at the time I probably bought like a cheap maybe they always have Old Navy on here.
And Gap on here.
So like for a long time I have been slacking lately
because then all these companies have apps and they make it so easy
buying shit on your phone and paying with Apple Pay.
So it used to be very good about like go to the American Airline,
the AA Advantage shopping portal, eShopping, I think it's called now.
Then you go to Kohl's.
Hmm.
Okay.
Then you go to Kohl's.
So but they have bonuses like on this with airline miles.
So you'll earn five times as many miles.
Right.
Yes.
Or eight times like Sephora right now.
Now three miles per dollar.
Eddie Bauer.
Are we headed for a complaint here or are you just telling me this?
I'm just telling you this.
I'm just like if you're telling the listeners if you're an airline,
if you have one airline you fly all the time,
see if they have a shopping thing and you can rack up some more miles.
So you're not redeeming your airline points for toothbrushes.
You're just merely gaining more points.
Yeah more miles.
How many of you accrued the miles right now?
Like 16,000 miles.
16,000 you know how many since the start of the pandemic 2020?
I don't well I have flown a bunch since 2020.
Oh I see.
Went to Orlando, went to New York.
And you used all those points and that's your airline of choice generally.
That is my airline of choice and I think I'm just racking up points while I do it.
Now the even stupider thing that I do because it's just like well I'm dicking around on
the internet I may as well get something out of it is the Bank of America advisory panel.
What?
So this is the thing I signed up for years ago
where you just do surveys on your phone or on your computer.
It tells you where you can do the survey.
And it's like are you do you use investment at Bank of America?
Are you happy with your savings?
And it's just all that like we're redesigning the website.
It's all Bank of America specific surveys?
It's all Bank of America specific surveys.
So then at the end of the survey you get a certain number of points.
And once you get to 20 points you could start cashing that in for e-gift cards.
So you get a $5 gift card to Dunkin or Starbucks.
Oh and this is called the advisory panel?
Yeah the advisory panel.
And then sometimes if you're the member of the month you get like extra points.
Or like if it's a long survey you'll get 10 points.
Have you been a member of the month?
I've never been a member of the month unfortunately.
How many members of the month are there?
I don't know.
I don't know how many people are in there.
How do you even know about a member of the month?
Well you only know if you go to the landing page for it.
Well does it list who the member of the month was?
Yes it features like the member of the month.
Does it?
Am I serious?
Is it a picture of the person?
I don't know there's not a picture.
Like the rebel spy?
The Bank of America rebel spy?
I just this was a helpful thing when I was like broke in 2017 and I'm like oh cool there's a
survey I can get a cup of coffee.
How many surveys are you taking a month?
I'm not again I'm slacking on all this.
At the height of your survey taking though how many were you doing?
Probably like five.
Five a month?
Probably five a month.
Okay that's not so wild.
So and then there are hoops to jump through like they give you the points you have to go to the
points store then you get the e-gift card then you have to keep track of that e-gift card.
And so you're still getting emails because you're on the panel?
Yeah.
The advice can I become a panel member?
Do you have an account?
The Bank of America?
Yeah.
You probably can.
Or did they select you like were you selected like the owl selects kids in Harry Potter?
Here's an April quick survey up to two points and one entry in the quarterly prize drawing
which is probably how they got me because I love prize drawings and raffles and I've won them before.
So what's the survey?
What is this?
What are their quizzing just on like Bank of America website?
Up to what is this about?
Take our April quick survey so and then they say like here's the closing data
the survey here are the devices you can potentially use it takes five minutes
but sometimes it'll say it takes 10 minutes and I also or like 20 minutes I can do them much faster.
Oh wow this is the cockiest of social media usage survey up to five points
and one entry in the quarterly prize drawing time 10 minutes.
Bank of I searched Bank of America member of the month and it says AI says it doesn't have
a member of the month program there's preferred rewards is this just something special is this
a special little thing?
It's the advice it's specifically for the advisory panel this is the stupidest thing
I waste my time on but at least I get a little treat at the end.
Advisory panel I just like how confident you were about taking a survey that you were really fast
at it okay I do see.
I am very fast at sometimes I just lie.
Whoa again you've admitted some things today that really could get you in trouble.
That I'm very particular about my lettuce and I'm bootlicking.
No no bootlicking spice world mostly okay I'm joining the advisory panel right now
uh how do you want to see I mean I'll do this I guess off off computer because.
Yeah don't take a little while.
I just want you to be member of the month more than anything I want you to get a sash.
I am trying unless I missed an email at some point and I honestly think they potentially
maybe just give you a few points and then they go like round of applause for Erica you know
there's like nothing to it and they never call you or anything it's all online.
I I've never gotten any phone calls.
Okay and is this like like I mean look we're this episode probably should have been over
30 minutes ago but um is this still the thing you're doing more than like the my Vegas rewards
app like I want to talk about Cole's cash today I want to talk about my Vegas rewards we don't
have time for that unfortunately but is this the thing that you're spending the most like
what are you spending the most time on to get a couple dollars out of it.
I think it's I have not Jane's much better at playing my Vegas.
Right but is there what is the biggest time waster that gains you any sort of rewards
right now are you doing anything.
I don't think I'm doing much of anything occasionally I check in on this.
Okay so what sounds like you've slacked as far as it sounds like the listeners have voted on
doing this episode when we're at our lowest as far as getting uh rewards and on top being
on top of things.
Hey if you're in the gutter at least you're looking at the stars you know.
I know I mean what you said couldn't be more applicable to what I said
that's for sure there's no doubt about it that that corresponded thoughtwise.
You're lying in the gutter at least you're looking at the stars.
But points are fun that's what I think I get I think that it's a fun little thing now you
would have had a lot more time in my life if I completely cut all of this out and I decided to
like commit myself to writing a novel commit myself to learning a new skill yeah probably by
now at this age I would have had some other accomplishment sure but everyone's trying to
screw you left and right you got to save money where you can everyone's trying to screw you
left and right it's only going to get worse and you got to save money where you can you
got to be smart about it and you got to stay on top of what the different words my stomach
is growling so aggressively again has nothing to do with food on like a flay of fish or something
that flay of fish seems like it's more than 3000 oh the flay of fish are so much that
inflation hit filet of fish harder than almost any other mcdonald's item I feel like and you know
around um easter season fridays you know some people they got the filet of fish right they
mark it down that deal gets worse and worse every year what did it change it used to be like a dollar
50 of filet values get two filet of fish eat like a king I feel like it's worse now would you get
fries in addition to the two filet of fish no I it's too much I feel too bad you would feel bad
if you had fries and two filet of fish two filet of fish in a glass of water or a diet cookers
that's enough glass ice water maybe a glass ice well you can have a double you can get a double
flay of fish as well yeah I wish I don't really I rarely do that but I like a flay of fish
that I've said I do one time they they screwed me on a breakfast sandwich and they just put a
patty from the flay of fish on my like bun or my my like whatever my uh uh your eggs my saw my
like bacon egg and cheese my biscuit okay my biscuit had a flay of fish patty on it once
filet of fish and the yellow folded egg that's I think there were both yeah or instead of the egg
they liked we're trying to pull a fast one on me once at mcdonald's that's crazy they put a
flay of fish patty on my biscuit I would like it if they sold that as an option I ate it a biscuit
yeah sure no problem I don't care with a flay of fish on it you know my problem with the big
the chicken big mac though is I haven't tried it yet just a lot of breading a lot of bread and
breading yes a lot of breading I mean look I've tried this with Wendy's like pub specialty
sandwich burger delicious sub a you know doing a spicy chicken on that pub sandwich with
mushrooms and bacon and a pretzel bun were way too much I like those I don't know I feel like
we have different opinions on fast food in some ways yeah but that's okay sure that's what the
country is about it's not the time for that sort of talk no I know uh anyway uh I hope this episode
lived up to the expectations I don't think it did quite frankly I think we fell short here
I think that we didn't hit coal's cash I think there were different big targets
you want to hit coal's cash no we're still running out of time coal's cash that much not really okay
but I think it's funny to talk about coal's cash sure well that's a future episode our parents are
retirement yeah that's why I told my mom that's why inheritance
is whatever coal's cash is in the family look I love a covington brand pajamas or lounge pants
covington brand you grew up in the town called covington right which is I think that's one of
the coals or crofton barrow you must have some crofton barrow my mom loves crofton barrow but
you lived coming you lived on covington which is next to hamilton beach right which is where
you used to go during the summer these are rare I know these brands better than the names of
extended family members crofton barrow yes crofton barrow I've heard that before but yeah coal's my
mom it loves a coal's like she loves the way that coal's confuses people and gives them coupons and
deals like that's a fun game the game of it's gamification in a lot of ways look I was a big
fan of uh jcp the jc pennies rebranded 2011 or 2010 where they just lowered the price on everything
but then everyone got mad because they're like there's no coupons I'm not getting a deal
the the rebrand of jc penny was just calling it jcp jcp yeah you got a bunch of t-shirts and
shorts let's say jcp on it yeah the tags have jcp oh but now you didn't get like a big on the
front of like a logo on the shirt no I got some track pants that have jcp on the butt
yeah I do have bookmarked there are some like uh t-shirt companies and stuff
that are uh they sell t-shirts with like old department stores that are long like janes way
caldor okay is mervin still around I think it is but I don't know I think it is but like clover
did you have clover no that was probably an east coast one boscov's is the one that's hanging on
boscov's boscov's oh big boscov's is great they used to have mirrors the entryway on the ceiling
there was neon signs for all the departments there's a candy counter and an optical and a
travel agent and a ticket master a travel agent yeah you could book a vacation at boscov's and
buy some sensible so like it's a target where you could go book a book a vacation it was like an all
all of us are seeing a department store wow boscov's and it's gone no it's still going oh
it is still going and you still hanging on still travel agents in there I don't know I don't know
boscov's you know I I did finally get to zombie sears and burbank oh yeah and it is sad it's only
one floor it's half full but I bought a cross body bag what for how much was it a good deal
well here's think it was 50% off from 40 but then there was another deal so it was only $15
gosh well yeah we we should have done more sears talk on this episode but I don't know I mean to
sum up to sum up I think I would love to hear it from the listeners in the comment I guess
it shouldn't be in this comments because that's for club three but and on social media I suppose
let us know what your deals are what what your this is points oh I mean like in the patreon yeah
I guess that might be hard to track instagram or whatever wherever we post
because I think everybody has their own little deals they like I think this is I think this is
a common thing for people I just don't know if they go as hard into all the apps yeah because
I have I look through I have every fast food app I have points in every account yeah and I don't
know if I don't know if that's common or not can you hear my stomach my stomach is so loud to me
I can hear it I wonder if the mic picked it up okay I wish I thought it was distracting
oh no I didn't know did you skip breakfast I had a donut for breakfast okay so anyway apologize
if you can hear my cake raised okay well that's why the cake sticks in your gut a little more
was it because the raised donut is so light and airy yeah so I basically ate like a cloud you ate
a cloud of sugar yeah out of sugar I was eating a slice apple and peanut butter when you came in
and I was when I came in that you said you were covered in peanut butter you used my lips on my
fingers I didn't want to get it all covered in peanut butter like a baby that got into the
peanut butter jar I was kind of getting ahead of you you thought I was gonna say you were gonna
say are you you're just covered in peanut butter I was gonna be like look at this like I was gonna
come up with some like you look at this peanut butter jerk off or something and that would have
followed you around and you don't want to hear that are you like least the new lisa lampanelli
you're the king of me yes I am the new lisa lampanelli I'm the king of people uh the peanut
butter dickhead the peanut butter dickhead worthless users yeah there's one there's a
couple different nicknames that came up for you on this one but peanut butter jerk off I think
well your point brother and whatever there's another one in there and I can't remember what
it was but uh anyway I mean you've survived podcast the ride club three again is this what
you wanted is this when you thought about it I think it is what they want it I don't know
maybe it is I think we were being light you know I do think we were being light I don't think we
were getting into anything we were being we were we're getting into our our dysfunctions our
personality you know what we don't do a lot is you know what we don't do a lot is is review the
our own performance but before the microphone is shut off sure you're right I think we were
being light and I think there was some information in here that's useful I think you're right I think
it is I think some of it's useful I think that the conversation was was was was was comical
I think the tangents were good just be careful just be careful don't get too deep in all this
don't get too deep in it don't eat too much fast food or like although honestly I love those stories
when like a chemistry teacher did you see this few years ago a chemistry teacher only ate hostess
snack cakes for a month and he like dropped a bunch of weight because he was just raw
calorie counting and it did work now that much sugar I was trying to wrap the show up but you've
pulled me into a conversation that I'd actually like to have I do think about that sometimes it's
like well meeting like McDonald's for dinner but I didn't eat lunch all day this is the argument
this is the argument is it is just a amount of calories but the quality of ingredients then
somebody will argue is a longer term issue because I know you can on the Taco Bell app count your
calories very effectively you can take ingredients off you could really calorie count your way into
losing weight just eating Taco Bell every day right you could do that but see that's this
different fast food I got to talk about I want the goo baby I want the nacho cheese but you can
selectively put the goo on well yeah I do I sub everything for beans and then if I want to pick
out I sub it for potatoes or fries hardshell taco is a little bit less caloric than a softshell taco
I didn't know that okay but then you take the beef you take the beef away and then you put on
either like a beans black beans or you can do chicken which is also less caloric than the beef
then you go okay I like a taco supreme better than I like the regular one because it's got
sour cream on it but then you go do I really taste the cheese maybe I take the cheese off
and you pull the cheese off that takes another 10-15 calories off and you just say sour cream so now
you got a hardshell taco with beans or chicken you put your tomatoes on there which obviously
have no calories maybe something else too and you still get your sour cream so now you've knocked
a lot of the calories off you've maybe 30 or 40 calories off of just one taco are you subbing
the sour cream for cheese or no I'm saying taco supreme comes with cheese and sour cream but you
if you think about it on my tasting the cheese on this maybe not pull the cheese off take it off
and then you still get your sour cream and you still get your goo because I hear you if you're
gonna go to these places you gotta get your goo I want my goo I want my baja blaze caffeine boost
you gotta get even though you know you're really not to put too caffeine after 4 p.m. it'll keep
you up at night now this is a good if you and I were to write a book about losing weight on fast
food it would be a picture of you and it'll be called ggg gotta get your goo yeah and it would
be the the highlight of it would be making sure you still have the caloric big mac sauce if you're
getting it which I know you don't like Big Macs what I love Big Macs oh wait I'm thinking to
somebody else a quarter pounder I never get a quarter yeah that's right too big of me patty you
and I I read about the onion recall well yes I killed a couple people it's the first thing I did
I saw the news story then I sent you that's because of the hydrolyzed debate we had months
ago how you couldn't get sick from eating a mcdonald's which I guess that disproves it
but it was the onions specifically it's not the meat and it's not the goo yeah they had gotten
some onions from a distributor who I guess was doing a bad job keeping them clean so it was like
they were spreading foodborne illness but uh uh back to talking about delicious fast food is that
yes I think there is a way to take the calories off and get your goo because you go to those places
for your goo yeah and I don't know did we did the show just end I think so oh wait
one more thing okay yeah I as much as I enjoyed this I do think we should probably stick with
podcasts a ride I don't think we can become full-time points guys points brothers points
brothers well the yeah the points guys already got it locked down okay so I guess we will not
be leaving podcasts the ride fortunately it would be really funny if we left it before Scott came
back too because like no one would be doing it oh it's like the sting you come back and the
casinos gone yeah or yeah we could leave right before Scott comes back and he comes back and
we're just gone from the record with a little note from the state yeah family's gone no trace
of us whatsoever and we're just like it says like or we just only a little note like that says like
ggg going to get our goo don't explain it yeah