hello second gators Michael here before you start this episode I just want to
make you aware that we recorded like live video of the computer as we were
watching the parade so we were able to stop and pause so I think the ideal way
to enjoy this episode would be to watch the video version of it but look do
whatever you want I'm not gonna tell you what to do I'm not your boss so enjoy
it either way but again there's a video version also that's been posted on the
patreon right now and I again I'm recommending doing that but again I
cannot tell you what to do so whatever you decide I am mostly happy with it
welcome to podcast the ride show where four men are out on a patio to keep it
wild and to keep it real as we explore some of the deepest and darkest crevices
of this our American nation's obsession with content is that right yeah so I'm
glad it worked out yeah that makes the show sound really smart like we're
really this is like there's a mission statement here to examine why we create
sometimes it's long conversations about the Disney app sometimes it's deep
delves into the history of this fine nation and it's celebration I think
today is one of those celebrations. That's Zach Greino and I'm Anthony Gio. That's right our special guest for this episode. We've never had a guest in the intro before I don't think. No it's kind of fun. Well hold on you two are our guests so Anthony keep going.
So today we're going to posit what Alexander de Tocqueville meant in democracy in America and how long it would take to deteriorate as a country. Oh wow. And are we there yet? I think we've arrived. Well can you then introduce me please? We're here with our special guest. Father of loving father, husband, father of mine, our dad and yours it's my
Carlson. Hi thanks so much for having me here. I'm really excited. And also we have the captain of the ship that will never sink. Hold on. Old glory himself? Old hickory himself? Had he built the Titanic it would still be floating today. That's right it'd be a cross from the Queen Mary and you can stay there for cheap before you got on a
cruise. America's historian, your dad and mine Jason Sheridan. Hi. Thank you. This is so exciting to be on our own podcast but not. Yeah we love having you guys. Thanks for coming to Mike's backyard. Yeah it's really good here. The first brisk night of the year as one of you said. That's right. As of record the time listener is 821 p.m. just to give you an idea. The sun set a mere six hours ago. You may hear some fluttering from the
tarps that Michael has constructed what I can only refer to as a human terrarium. We've got our little heat lamp. We're on my patio and there's a big tarp around. I felt like it was going to protect us from the wind. And it is doing that. It is doing that. But it is also making a little bit of noise. It is also putting the sails in Jason's ship.
It's really like the very sails of the Mayflower. That's right. When you were on the ship. When I was on the ship complaining about like the food. I also could see when you're talking about Mayflower. You could see a scenario where Jason's like oh have you ever been on the Mayflower and we're like what are you talking about.
Mayflower Airlines. The official airline of Pennsylvania from 1985 to 1992. Or like I used to drive Mayflower moving trucks. Me and this guy who kept talking about painting houses. We would always drive these trucks.
We were here today to talk do a commentary which we haven't done in a while. Yeah. Like a live commentary. We did. We did one like six years ago but we haven't done it because I'll be honest I don't love doing it. Oh but I do. Jason loves doing it because you just get to hit play and relax.
But for me I was like well is there a way we can enhance the experience of doing a live commentary. And I decided to figure out a way to make it very complicated. So we're going to be able to do today is watch this. But if we want to stop we're going to stop.
OK. We're going to talk and rewind. We can do anything we want. But I'm going to be recording the video and audio as well. So you the listener can just watch along as we pause and stop and hear our audio. And if it doesn't work you won't hear this part of the podcast.
So live in the sense that we are we are alive while we're doing it that we are alive. Yes. But the thing that we're watching is in fact quite old and not being aired. That is correct. We're not watching something live right. Right now while we speak the Tyson Jake Paul fight is happening.
We are not watching it though. Millions of young men across the nation sit down to watch Mike Tyson fight Jake Paul. We're sitting down to watch. We're sitting down to watch. Although let me find the official name of it. It is called.
This is true. Zach and I don't know. Yes I've only kind of hinted at it. There there is a there's a thumbnail on the on the projector. Yeah it looks like it is called about six pixels quite old.
It is from 1992. It is called All American Thanksgiving Day Parade. A CBS tradition where they show the Macy's Day Parade and other things. In 1992 happened to be a year where they show a bunch of stuff that was happening at Disneyland that year.
So that's the tie in. So this is not the Macy's Day Parade. Well you will see some parts of the Macy's Day Parade on this special. It's like a mashup. So we're going to discover. I haven't. I've watched some of it but I haven't watched all of it. So we will discover things as we go.
It's a parade mega mix. Basically. But this wasn't this. Nobody put this together. This was actually the live broadcast because it has commercials from the era from 90 from 1992. And it starts a little abruptly. I wish it started with more of like the intro.
But I found a big chunk of it online and it starts just right to Disneyland right to a parade that I've only kind of heard of. OK. And I was blown away immediately by it. And I said well I guess this is what we're talking about.
So just to recap. 1992. This is on CBS. This is pre ABC Disney. Right. Pre. OK. Got it. When does that happen. I think the mid to late 90s. Too late. Yeah. Yeah. Whenever Michael Eisner had the premonition to do it whenever he had the feet like an angel spoke to whenever they traded Oswald the rabbit for Michael.
It was like 2000s. Is that right. I think so. It was like 2011 20 California venture like 2012. I think. Yeah. I feel like they traded within 12 years with 13 years is when Al Michaels broadcaster got traded for a character. Yeah. Which is true.
So we may have to cut here while I do this but I think we'll be all right. Don't cut. Leave it in. Leave it. OK. You guys talk while you. This video is a very complicated looking workflow graphic on screen. Sorry Michael. What is the.
What is the. This looks like it's how long. It's two hours and 48 hours and 40 minutes. We don't have to watch all of it.
We don't have to watch it. OK. The thing is two hours and 40 minutes. Welcome to part one of three of us watching. Maybe it's a yearly tradition and we watch it in parts.
You don't have to watch all of it. We can zoom around broadcast television. That's strong. Everyone. There was one channel and it was this. Oh my God. Yes. Everybody was watching this in 1992. Can I. Before we even start. Yeah.
Say immediately Jason how excited are you to see a carnation instant breakfast sign in the background.
Look I lived on carnation breakfast during my summer theater years in high school. They made hot. They still they made hot chocolate long after they made that. They made breakfast. They still make the breakfast. Yeah.
I only know them from nutrients. But wasn't the chocolate the breakfast. Huh. There is chocolate in the breakfast. Is there instant breakfast a cup of hot chocolate. It is glorified vitamins and drink. It's fortified.
You dump it in a glass of milk and you laugh. But I lost a bunch of weight the one summer I was from carnation. From doing nothing but drinking hot chocolate.
No. Every day from breakfast we're going into the summer theater camp where I was counselor. I would have a glass of carnation instant breakfast and a delicious piece of buttered white toast. And then I would do the elliptical before.
There was probably more that and less the toast. I think it was just cutting out soda. I think I largely did it. There were a lot of variables to that experiment. There were a lot of them. Well look. That is the breakfast of a GI unit in 1944.
Actively deployed overseas. Jason is eating rations for breakfast. Hardtack. This is pre-MRE. Space ice cream. Have you ever had space ice cream for breakfast.
So carnation. So let's see. This is going to we're going to start and if you want the video should be up right now and you will be able to watch along. But here we go.
Here we go. Was that Pete's dragon. No. So there are a bunch of like people dressed like the Flintstones and goofy is singing.
So this is actually a couple of years before the Flintstones features. Why would this be happening. So we have wandered right into a goofy parade.
So let's do the first pause here. OK. You look blown away. There's so much going on. He is dressed like a caveman and the song is about the goofasaurus. And there are ladies dressed like Wilma and Betty with like a diner kind of like trays walking down Main Street.
Is this though. Is this cross property. Are they supposed to be actually Wilma and Betty. No. Or are they just blatantly ripping off the Flintstones. They're stealing from the Flintstones. Oh really. You thought this was a Flintstones parade. I thought it was a Flintstones thing.
Because it looks exactly like. No this is not Flintstones. This is just goofy. So that big dragon thing was not Pete's dragon. That was the goofasaurus. That was the goofasaurus. Now this on the Thanksgiving Day parade.
They're showing a thing that they did in 1992 called the World According to Goofy parade. A parade all about goofy. Now I don't know what this has to do with Thanksgiving but they were showing it in 1992.
Goofy's first appearance was 1932. So this would have been his 60th birthday. So to celebrate Goofy's 60th birthday a bunch of people dressed up like Flintstones characters. OK. Does it make sense.
Yeah it does. There's an original song called Goofasaurus. So do you close your mouth. It's a gape. Because we're going back in. Button it up. I'm stunned.
Well the other thing is you have children doing pattern. There are children. Wait till you see who that is by the way. Because that's coming up. So you have dinosaurs. You have Goofy dressed as a caveman dancing.
And there's like a early man playing drums with bones on the parade float. Now we have cut to a stegosaurus. OK. There is a like horrible looking goofy hybrid here.
Yeah this is we've seen a few abominations. Yeah. Imagine like the like the movie The Thing. But Goofy's head is on one of those creatures.
I know I like this one. I'm on board with this guy. You like this guy. This looks like Pete's dragon. This is like Goofy. This does look like a pre Pete's dragon Pete's dragon.
It's just a big green Goofy with a big stretchy green neck. Looks a little like Magellan from Eureka's Castle. It does look like Magellan from Eureka's Castle.
OK. So there's a lot of like dinosaurs with dresses. I like these little freaks. They're good. That is tail. Yes. Well.
Tails usually are in the back. Yeah that one's sticking right out the front. That's a choice. I'm sorry. That's a choice. There's no reason there's no reason they couldn't have put this float the other way.
That's a choice. This took a long time to build. The Goofasaurus loves to fuck. It's Goofy's 60th birthday and the Goofasaurus loves to fuck.
And he's got a curved erection. For 14 seconds. We only have two hours 50 minutes to go. You paused it like three times. We only have two hours 50 minutes to go.
It's also impossible to do commentary over it while every 15 seconds a new child pipes in with some quip. Well that's why I think we may be not be able to get through this whole thing today.
That's what I'm saying. Isn't this a snake though? Is Goofy a snake? No he's a big dinosaur. Are you sure? He's on his back I think. Those are his hands though aren't they?
I guess so. Are they fins? Is he like a Loch Ness? I guess he is. I guess he's like a Loch Ness but he's on his back. That's why it looks like his tail is his wiener.
He's preparing himself for Amazon position. For what position? Amazon position. Did you elaborate on that Jason? Hold on raise your hand if you know what he's talking about.
Context clues I have a guess. Is there a sexual position called Amazon position Jason? Correct. That's where a fella lies on his back and hoists his legs up.
Hoists his legs up. Okay like you spread eagle? Yeah and then the lady mounts him. Clarabelle? Clarabelle what are you talking about?
Goofy? No he's talking about Amazon position Mike. Don't be ridiculous. I'm saying if Goofy was here in this position it would be like Clarabelle mounting him.
It would be too far. It would be first of all a Clarabelle dactyl because this is the Goofasaurus. Fair enough. It wouldn't be just Clarabelle Mike. It wouldn't be just Clarabelle Dyson is like a fuck a cow.
In Amazon position Jason is the man getting pegged or? No no he's like the lady like takes a position as if it was man. This is like a woman on top but the man's legs are up. Like in Amazon.
Right got it got it got it. Amazon position. Clearly Goofy is readying himself for his late wife Mrs. Geef. Jason what are you talking about? Goofy is a widower. What? Who is? From Goof Troop his wife died.
Is she canonically dead in that movie? What is he divorced in Goof Troop? How cruel would that be? In the 50's he has a spouse occasionally called Mrs. Goof or Mrs. Geef. So did Mrs. Goof die at the start of Goof Troop?
Well she's long dead. He's also connected with Clarabelle cow and someone named Glory B. Zanubia and Sylvia Marple. That's from an extremely Goofy movie. Oh I actually haven't seen all of extremely Goofy movie.
So that's who would be Amazoning. That's how Mrs. Geef died. She died Amazoning? Yes. You've got to prepare. Every time Jason says Amazon the wind just starts to whiff.
And whips the tarps at us. Okay so these ladies are dancing. And Goofasaurus. And then there's this triceratops. So this parade just to kind of give it. Oh god. Goofy looks horrendous. He looks like a werewolf Goofy. He's so furry.
He's got a little bit of a. What's that little ugly thing from the Halloween? Fuzzbucket? It does look like Goofy merged with Fuzzbucket. Yeah. Okay so some context for this. I'm curious. Would this be happening on Thanksgiving at the park? Why would they show this?
That's a great question. Because they were trying to get. This was going to draw people to the park. This wasn't a Thanksgiving parade. This was just what they were showing on the Thanksgiving special. So like this year at the park. Right. That's the idea behind it.
But this is a big. There's so many performers. Okay now here we go. Take a look. We have. Wait what? We have Nicole Dubuque from Major Dad. And on the right we have Clark Duke as a child. Wait. I assume so. Fill me in. Who is Clark Duke? Clark Duke has been on. What's the famous Clark Duke? I think Hot Tub Time Machine. Hot Tub Time Machine. Clark and Michael. Michael Cera and Clark Duke.
Had a web series 15 years ago. Greek? Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. How old was he with that web series with Michael Cera? They were young I'm sure. Because this is 92. And this kid is already. This can't be the Clark Duke right? I don't know. We'll take a look. How old is he? There's no way to find out right? Hold on I gotta close this. I guess for the listener we've just paused on.
The first shot of Nicole Dubuque and Clark. Clark Duke is born 1985. Easily is him. Could be him. Has to be him. Has to be him I think. Hell of a gig. Yeah. And I wish. So he's seven years old here. That looks right. May 5th. May the 5th be with you right? Star Wars day. May the 5th. It's May the 4th. What? What? Huh? What are you talking about? Yeah you know there's that that.
That overwhelming power in Star Wars. Called the 5th. Use the 5th Luke. Did you really think it was May the 5th? No I didn't. I was being silly. Oh okay. That was silly. Okay so they're hosting.
President elect Clinton. President elect Clinton. So Clinton had been elected recently. That was the only person. Okay now we get to our first commercial here. Lego Technic. Oh yeah. Sure. I never had any of these. The Legos I was not interested in.
Yeah I wasn't interested in them either. No although I feel like they have tried to rebrand versions of this to this day still get made. They just call them other stuff. Yeah. Yeah. This felt a little too much like school to me. Yeah yeah. I know what you're saying. It didn't have the fun. Technically speaking it rules.
Oh Jason toothpaste commercial. What toothpaste brand were you as a family? I think we were a Colgate but I've been a Crest Pro Health man for a long time. You're a Crest Pro Health man? That's the yeah. Okay. Zach what about you? What? Sorry I'm watching in real time.
America discover toothpaste tubes where the top doesn't detach all the way and where you can stand it on it. Okay now we're at a Sears. Now George Bigelow from Sears is here. Yeah and he's going to sell you an old speaker.
Looks like Ted Cruz. Yeah. Promise Ultra? The early 90s was all about. Promise Ultra Spread. Giving you the like the worst food and calling it low fat. Yeah. It's the Pillsbury Doughboy now. Oh Jason stood up and saluted. You saw the dope Pillsbury Doughboy. It's the low fat or the poppin' fresh.
Well you were standing already so it seems good. I was yeah. Jason what does this do for you? This is a brownie commercial. Oh a little fudge on that brownie. Yeah I like that. Yeah. Cool. Pillsbury Bake Tops.
No giggling. Commercials haven't changed. So okay now we have switched from Disneyland and we are now in New York City. Okay. And we have different hosts. I don't know that guy. I know that is Mary Lou Henner from Taxi. Who has the thing where she remembers every second of her life. Oh wow. Yeah so she has like a perfect recall of everything in her life. What a curse. What a curse.
Wow. Hey me too. I spent my honeymoon in Hawaii. Nice. Nice.
I mean I guess. So now we are going to watch a parade in Hawaii. So they are jumping all over the globe here. Okay so that was in New York now they are in Hawaii. With Jeffrey Meek and Cynthia Geary. Yeah Cynthia Geary. Do we know are they from. I don't know we have to look that up. I said Northern Exposure maybe.
I just want to tell you guys in 1992 Clark Duke was one of the main stars of the sitcom Hearts of Fire starring John Ritter, Markey Post and Billy Bob Thornton. Wow really. Lasted 54 episodes. Clark Duke is fourth build. 54 episodes of a show I have never heard of.
1992 to 1995. The lowest staff writer has got a mansion in the Hollywood Hills from that show. Yeah currently buying off of council members so their house doesn't fall into the ocean. Good for them. Hearts of Fire. The creator has the sinister name Linda Bloodworth-Thomason.
Wait what? Linda Bloodworth-Thomason. No that's metal. Linda Bloodworth is cool. I mean it's pretty metal. Has she done anything else? Yeah some light vampire summonings. How much blood does she drink? She wrote on Designing Women. Oh okay. Pretty good. Have you ever watched Designing Women Jason? I really don't think I have. Maybe I saw like one episode. So I'm going to scan through. This is just a parade in Hawaii. This is just a parade that's happening in Hawaii and like it looks nice but I'm going to zoom so we can get more
to the Macy's stuff and back to Disneyland. There's more commercials. Okay so now we're back. So we're back in New York. Garfield's coming. Yes. CBS This Morning. Wow he worked it in nicely. Mark McEwen and Mary Lou Henner.
Chicago Airport. It's me too, Mary Lou. This is just the two of them. They're just talking. Stretching yeah. They have thrown to so many different hosts. Yeah wow. Over the course of 20 minutes.
We've had five sets of hosts. This is Toronto. So CBS still does this parade. They've changed the branding but there still is a parade special every year.
Oh yeah. The networks are using this to be like here's some new actors on our shows that we have. Right. Smart. There's some bagpipe thing happening behind them in Toronto. Oh there's a big duck. This is good.
So now yeah they're in Toronto. In Toronto they don't have. This is not the budget of the Macy's Day parade but it is still pretty impressive. It is like a cuter version of like the penguins duck from Batman Returns. No they're saying this is a goose. If they say it's a goose I will believe them. It looks like a duck to me. Yeah. And there's some unhappy looking children sitting on the goose. Yeah they're freezing and they've been out for five hours.
So they're also like they must be like really like belted into the top because that goose looks precarious. Right yeah. They're locked and loaded into that goose. Yeah. Cheerleaders, drummers, bag fibers. Yeah. Oh they're doing Christmas songs. Jason we've got Peter Pumpkin here. Where is his face? He's leaning. I'm not quite sure where his face is.
What is Peter Pumpkin eater is the. Oh my god. Okay. Oh my god. Okay. So Peter Pumpkin is I would say a Peter Pumpkin eater. That's who we're talking about? Yeah. But that's Peter. He's kind of resting on his room or something. He's a porcelain doll of a man. I guess. It cuts away. I don't know who this is but I've loved it.
This is a big pink snail. This is a big pink snail with a big green shell. And then there's somebody that people are waving from the shell. There's like windows in the shell.
What the fuck? I guess something called the snail started even earlier. You think this parade float is a commentary on the housing crisis? No they turned the shell into a Canadian housing crisis. Canadian housing crisis. Whoa. Look at that cow. Big cow now. Yeah. There's a lot of like big porcelain doll looking faces. This is all fairy tale. This is little boy blue. Oh that. What is that thing coming in and out of the haystack? I didn't realize what's going on. It's a sheep.
Yeah what's going on bud? This is all public domain. Oh. It's Canadians cheaping out on you. It does feel like. Also none of this lines up. Like they couldn't even afford like Felix the cat. No no no. Felix was too expensive in 1980. They're playing an aggressive marching band version of Carol of the Bells. Is it public domain as well?
Nothing says Thanksgiving like Carol of the Bells. I'm trying to guess what it is before they say. Oh god. The cat in the boat. The boat cat. The owl in the pussy cat. 1883's cat in the boat. There's a bunch of pigs in this boat with them. There's four little pigs?
This is based on Chopin's cat? Honey. Some of these floats are based on old like classical music pieces. We're getting like Chopin trivia right now. We were shitting pretty hard on Goofy and it's looking good compared to this parade.
Yeah they had Goofas. The song was really lively and it was a character that was only 60 years old. Yeah the Goofasaurus is looking. Mommy mommy there's Chopin's cat. You know Jason said that when he was younger though. Of course. Mother rewind the tape. I want to see Chopin's cat. Jason was at the Chopin concert where he played a new piece of classical music and the crowd rioted. You can look at two horrible elves and a dead horse. Oh my god. What the fuck.
Two pervert elves. One of them has got his lips pursed like he's like mmm I'm an elf. I thought my time signature that caused a riot was bad. Look at the horse's legs are broken. I'm sorry. Nothing we have seen has not been ugly. This is all so ugly. The snail is the only good one. This horse might not be dead but it was maybe giving birth.
Just a quick update on Linda Bloodworth-Thomason. Thank you. She actually created Designing Women. Oh good for her. Among a number of TV shows like Filthy Rich that starred Delta Burke and Dixie. Delta Burke and Dixie Carter.
Delta Burke and Dixie Carter. But most importantly she created the TV show Emeril. Whoa. Wait like Emeril? Emeril Lagasse. Like garlic Emeril. His 2000 to 2001 only got 11 episodes. Oh man. We haven't done Emeril on the show. We've been talking about we've been threatening an Emeril episode for a while because Emeril had a restaurant. Yeah yeah.
So yeah we really should get on that. Jason have you ever seen an episode of Emeril? Oh I watched a number of episodes. We were very excited. Well that would likely be all of them. Yeah 11 episodes. I don't think I watched all of them. Were you as a family like very into Emeril?
My brother really loved the Food Network so he loved Emeril and I think we're all excited. I mean I know he broke through. He kind of loomed large for a while. I liked him. I liked when he said bam. But I wasn't so excited about the sitcom. I learned in this moment that he had a sitcom. Okay.
I saw him on pasta sauce jars. Yes. Okay. He didn't have a big commercial presence. I mean he was supported by Sherry Shepard and Robert Urick. On the sitcom. Yeah. Was there another? He didn't need support in the kitchen. Is he the only chef?
Yeah. You can keep playing this mic. I just wanted you to turn the sound down because I couldn't hear Jason. Oh sorry. I was too just like when I hear these people talking I'm too distracted by what they're saying. They're so beautiful. And they're not saying anything so you can turn this. So we got Lego. Lego is bad technically. Oh there's some dog butchers blend dog treats. Feed your dog meat from a jug. Probably poison meat in a jug. Toothpaste. The toothpaste that stands up.
Oh here we go. Macy's. Let's do some Macy's right here. Okay so we're horrifying turkey. So now we're back in New York. We're back in New York. The weather looks pretty tough. Sleeping Garfield is a good float. Yeah it's like he's sleeping on an invisible bed or something.
Jason what sex position does that resemble the most? Mike. What? Like prone? Prone. Prone bone. Prone bone did you say? Yeah. What does that mean? Like just a little line on your stomach.
Oh my god. Prone bone. So I just want to point out very similar characteristics. We got Garfield with a tail choice to put his tail in the back. Something that they did not do with the goofy. Yeah he's not on his belly. Also not sleeping just crouched lying down. Yeah he's wagging.
And then we have some. Big Muppet dog. So this is like a big puppet dog. I will say this. USA is flexing here. This is significantly better looking. That thing looks big. That's pretty ugly though. Oh there's two dogs there. There's two dogs.
Wait this is like a big robot. Those are good puppets. It looks like the back dog is giving the front dog dome. This is a body episode. Look at the faces. This is pretty ugly. I'll say most of the stuff we've seen is pretty ugly. Oh no. Look it's an angle then they're pushing a ball back and forth.
I take back what I see. There's space between them. That one dog isn't going down on that other dog at all. Oh it's the Nestle Quick Bunny. Oh man I totally forgot about this dude. He's wearing his admiral's outfit. Reporting for duty sir. Jason's saluting him.
Wow hand to heart Jason. And that's hard for me these days. That was Jason's colonel when he was in the service. He served under the. Nestle Quick Bunny called for a coat red. I could do nothing to stop him.
Quick Bunny. That's the wrong bunny idiot. That's the Energizer Bunny commentator man. Wow this is great. I think also just a floating true like balloon float elevates it so much. Yeah I agree. Is it Donkey Kong? No this is the bottom of the Quick Bunny.
Oh he's got a drum excuse me. He's like marching in a band. That's why the other guy thought he was the Energizer Bunny. He's got a cue on the front of his drum. Huh? Right? Think about it. Yeah he sure does. Jason. Blue cue. Now a horrifying eyelash caterpillar. With a woman just sitting on its head.
Yeah she's like stuck there. Oh a doodle bug. Never mind I take it all back. What is that? It's a doodle bug. You know the famous bug with a lady on top. It's a doodle bug. I know that's a man I'm sorry.
Wow Mary Lou Hunter does speak as if she has like total recall. She remembers everything. That was incredible. That guy's a musical archivist. She didn't need any notes. Oh is it raining? Yeah the weather's really bad.
Yeah this doodle bug is really. There's got to be like 50 people in that doodle bug making it move. All non-union. I think. Oh no there's wheels. I guess there's wheels. I think doodle bug's a car. Maybe the doodle bug is just a car. So to drive the doodle bug is that an honor you think? I think so but do you have to get like a tractor's license? It's a special license yeah for sure. I say this every year. This is the last god damn time I'm driving that doodle bug.
If this podcast has to end Jason you're going back to driving the doodle bug in the Macy's Day parade. Sorry. You hung up your doodle keys so many years ago. One more doodle ride. Oh the quick rabbit Nestle quick rabbit is coming. Are we going to see a float crash? Fingers crossed. The weather's pretty bad. They've cut to a camera that is covered in rain.
Yeah. The Nestle quick rabbit that was doing pretty good. He looks good. Like so far so good. Jason did you ever have carnation for dinner and quick for dessert? As a breakfast food don't be ridiculous. I know he drinks it quick with dinner. It's Bart Simpson. It's a Nestle's car bomb. It's a weird Bart Simpson. His eyes.
If it's carnation and then you chase it with quick it's like a Nestle car bomb or something. Like what would be the name? Nestle quick bomb. Nestle quick bomb. Okay that works. Bart is going very close to the street lights. I can't tell if it's the angle. Yeah you're right. I can't tell if it's the angle. But also the most. He is almost tilting. The most forward part of Bart's head is his upper lip.
Yeah they teased. Now we are now. The CBS News is giving us a commercial. Eye on your children they said. Oh yeah they're doing a great job. Oh god. Dan Rather. ET. Wow.
ET was on that night. Yeah you could watch four hours of this special and then two hours of ET. Well with commercials probably three right. That's a good point.
Hallmark Hall of Fame presents Brad Johnson and Kathleen Quinlan. Brad Johnson. An American story Sunday. CBS made for TV movie. Yeah yeah. It was Hallmark wasn't it. It seemed like a Hallmark the first CBS yeah. Alright let me zoom here. Join us for an original presentation on a one on one high community with an Eastern exposure. Eastern exposure. Oh that's a little play on Northern Exposure's popularity. Yeah I think that's right. Okay yeah let's go. Let's see what we got.
Oh Lego of course Technic is sponsored. There's a lot of commercials on this. Okay back to Macy's. Bart Simpson. The iconic Bart Simpson. Bart doesn't he look like he's getting close to the buildings. Yeah he seems out of control. His teeth and eyes are like about to pop out of his head.
It is a good pose for a flow. He looks like he's like they blew him up a little too much. He's plump. He's got gout. Jason recently on an episode alerted us to a thing that I wasn't familiar with that's like an inflatable fetish. He has the proper name I think. But I didn't know about it. It's a fetish where people like seeing characters blown up like balloons. Yeah sure.
Yeah you guys have not heard of this? Adam Sass messaged me and he's like yeah that is a fetish. A lot of people defended Jason because the three people on the podcast were stunned. They'd never heard of this before. Myself included. Plenty of listeners have said this is real. Jason's right. I didn't think he was wrong by the way. Is there a term for it? I think just an inflation fetish. Okay so it's like. It sounds like something Biden has.
Scott looked it up and people were accusing the animators of Tiny Toon Adventures for having this because a lot of the characters suck on helium and blow up. Which was not a thing. And we were trying to figure out what it meant and it's hard. Oh yeah Bart is getting close.
Bart is he going to crash? I can't tell. I don't know.
Oh Bart. He's alright I think. There are compilations of Macy's. Yes we've talked about balloon disasters on the show before. But I don't know from this year if we did 92. He hit something. Are you sure he wasn't just doing a wicked trick?
Oh my god who's that? Oh everything just went white. Everything. And now here comes the lord.
Oh my god all those figures from Tall Tales are coming to take over Gracie Mansion. Oh my god that's just like a statue.
Okay so this is a little closer to what we were saying. There's a guy on a horse. Yeah this is like Americana. Yeah kind of vague. Wax figure-esque although not wax. This is like an old steam train.
When do you guys think this stuff kind of expired? Because there came a time when they were like why the fuck are we putting Davy Crockett on the frame? At some point someone...
I think once we realized we could charge some company for IP and we're not going to put Davy Crockett out there if we can take money from whoever made Heathcliff and put Heathcliff on a big float.
Speak of the devil. It's Snoopy. I love Snoopy. Snoopy and we're talking about American IP. I see what you're saying. But there was something. What was the year when we had to stop?
When they were like enough of this public domain. There came a point where someone was like we gotta ring it out. Every second of this needs to be profit.
I think that Davy Crockett TV movies were like split up multiple different ways and then I think they were re-aired on early Disney Channel just because they needed something.
I remember Davy Crockett being like I would see the hat in like a toy store or whatever. I knew what that was. I'm into that. It was still a popular figure. Although I think it was probably very much on its way out even then.
Yeah but I mean when we learned about him whatever that story of Davy Crockett must have been 150 years old already right?
Yeah born on the mountain top of Tennessee.
I share your question. Your curiosity about the question of what was the year when it was done. I'm not sure.
Yeah.
Snoopy was wearing a Macy's sweatshirt.
Maybe when Al Michael got traded.
Well they got some good deals at Macy's that sweater those earmuffs.
Did I say this about Macy's? I ordered something online and I never picked it up because I didn't want it and I'm like I'll just refund it or whatever and instead of just sending it back to the PayPal I used they sent me in the mail two gift cards with the amount.
Just taped to a letter that said here's your refund.
Go back to Macy's buy it again.
These are gift cards or Macy's gift cards?
Is this Dumbo or is this Clown Elephant?
I think it was like I don't think it was Dumbo but Cabbage Patch.
These are the Cabbage Patch you could take in the bathtub so they wouldn't their paint wouldn't run if you just got them soaking wet.
Oh my gosh.
They're splashing tan.
Probably glazed with lead so they could get wet.
We melted lead down and gave the Cabbage Patch a bath.
Not to backtrack but you know what I just realized is that Davy Crockett is unique and that he is a hero whose fiction exists within American lore.
One of his things is that he patched up the hole in the Liberty Belt.
The Liberty Belt is cracked and in American lore Davy Crockett is the one that fixed it.
He's kind of a Forrest Gump like.
His fiction very much overlaps with.
They never fixed the Liberty Belt.
Well Davy Crockett patched up the hole in it though which is weird because it is a crack and not a hole.
But I guess there used to also be a hole.
So like Davy Crockett like if there was a Davy Crockett now in like 150 years it would be like Davy Crockett stopped 9-11.
Davy Crockett always said if he had been there that they wouldn't have gone down like that.
Yeah Davy Crockett would have stopped those steel beams from melting.
He would have held them together with his hands.
Right okay because he would have been in the building that's how he would have stopped it.
Yo stop it from the inside for sure not from the plane.
The plane still has it.
He just holds the building in his hands.
Is that what Mark Wahlberg meant as well?
He's got to get to the plane.
He meant he was actually in the building.
With the power of his Catholic faith.
Well stay prayed up he says.
That's right you got to get the app.
For $99 a year you can stay.
Yeah Jason's prayed up.
I text him every morning.
You prayed up?
One thing I like about prayed up is that if you get your prayer streak past a year.
What?
What about your prayer streak?
If your prayer streak past a year you go to heaven.
You go to heaven.
It's like Duolingo.
How long does that streak have to be?
You have to go a full year.
That's it though?
With no saves though.
What do you mean?
You can't freeze your prayer streak.
You can't hoard prayers for like one week.
You can't sin and break your streak.
And then like pay the owl.
Pay the owl?
I assume it's still the owl running it.
Well yeah God's an owl.
It's still the Duolingo owl.
God's owl.
Wait y'all don't pray to like owl, raven, crow, wolf.
Zach's religion is owl based.
The old gods.
The real ones.
This country's original gods.
So we're zooming through here and then
this is from, what does it say, New York?
And then there's just like ice skating going on.
But this isn't part of the parade because this is an ice rink.
This is an ice rink. This is not part of the parade.
This is outside
Central Park perhaps?
Yeah it looks like.
This doesn't look like it's live.
This looks like it was pre-recorded.
And they're just doing like
15 people ice skating.
One man and a bunch of women.
Yes.
Pretty good odds huh boys?
What? Pretty good odds huh boys?
Lower your eyebrows.
What? What are you talking about?
They normally wear Egyptian eyeliner
but they didn't want it to run in the rain.
Good commentary.
This is interesting.
There's only a couple people even watching this.
So this was just shot.
This almost feels like river dance ice skating in a way.
It is both river dance.
This is supposed to be Egyptian.
It does have
questionable music.
No this is traditional Egyptian music.
Traditional Egyptian ice skating.
That's right.
Done by traditional Egyptians.
Very pale.
Mike I'm curious as a
guy from the suburbs of Chicago
does Mary Lou Henner sound like every
mom you grew up around?
Because I can't stop hearing that.
She sounds a lot like
relatives of my mom.
Oh they're doing Walk Like an Egyptian now.
Oh yeah. No we're in an Egyptian mega mix.
The only song that has the word Egyptian in it?
Well you know Paul McCartney has an album
called Egypt Station.
Steve Martin's King Tut?
Although Paul McCartney's Egypt Station
came out like 5 years ago.
King Tut out at this point?
Oh yeah.
It's been out for years.
This is a third song.
Yeah I don't know what this is.
That was only a little bit of Walk Like an Egyptian.
They didn't want to pay the full
money.
They didn't want to pay the bangles money.
They did it one second before they had to pay him just to screw
him. Just to stick it to the bangles.
This is interesting. I think we should zoom through
though. Oh they went back to the bangles.
Okay okay. What is this?
We're getting to a commercial with a ventriloquist
and we need to watch it.
Alright so for the listener we're about 45
and a half minutes in.
Yeah something like that.
Man names were different back then.
Okay so now
a ventriloquist dummy
is sick. He's sitting on his
operator's lap.
Well me too. What's not complaining?
I'm not complaining. Somebody is complaining.
Then we'll take something.
Not that cough syrup makes me gag.
When you're all blocked up, Ludens helps.
Ludens helps.
Alright who
What in the ventriloquist dummy's
hands were you a Ludens family or
a Halls family? Jason?
Yeah we were a Halls family.
Do you have any Halls on you or in your
apartment? I do have Halls
in my apartment. Okay.
Is this the President and the United States
playing with a tank? That was Gorbachev
playing with a tank.
They're just showing people
like throwing batteries
carelessly away.
Oh these are rechargeable batteries.
These batteries
have not decomposed at all.
They are sitting somewhere on this
planet earth. These giant
disposable batteries
rechargeable batteries.
You know Ikea only sells
rechargeable batteries now. Is that right?
Yeah they don't sell single use batteries
anymore.
Oh yeah.
Wow. I remember
these. Yeah do you have these?
This is a Tiger Electronics Little Mermaid
handheld. These games were awful.
They were really bad.
Unplayable.
Even at the time. I had a number.
I did too. Tiger Electronics
made so much money on
unplayable games. Absolutely unplayable
plastic. Unfun
unplayable games that you were just excited
about. This is the height of your imagination. You could do anything.
You could go play in the yard with a fucking
stick all day.
Someone would pick up a Tiger Electronics
and you'd be like this sucks.
Ursula's fin would go
up and down, up and down. She wouldn't
move. She wouldn't animate at all.
They suck.
They're one of the worst products ever.
It's true.
I'm getting mad.
You know what sucked a lot about them is they
looked good.
The package was fun.
When I said they looked
good, I mean if you saw it in a toy
aisle before you turned it on, you'd
be like oh this is like more
colorful than any handheld game
system that would come out for the next like 20 years.
Because there wasn't really, I mean a Game Boy came
out late 80's but that's a high
premium, you know high price.
But like I had a Darkwing Duck one and it was
purple and it had the characters on it.
God I had one and I cannot remember what it was.
And the reason is because I played
it for two seconds and then threw it at a wall.
Of course it sucked.
It was not even, it wasn't, there were like
four things the characters
could do. You know like there was
nothing. It wasn't so much animated as like you
would hit up or down and like
the sort of black silhouette of Ariel
would like disappear from the bottom row
and reappear. You were basically
turning lights on and off. Yes.
You were turning little cell.
Alright I want to look up
the people that, whoever
created Tiger Electronics. We got to do a Tiger Electronics
episode. Oh we do it? I want to know if they ever went to
jail. Someone just uploaded a bunch
of scans from the Toys
R Us. What? Oh yeah yeah yeah.
From like
93 or 94 I think.
What happened? And half a page
of it is Tiger Electronics.
I swear. They had an X-Men one
that looks vaguely familiar to me.
Vernon Hills. Tiger, Vernon Hills
can we find the founder?
Okay so. Oh it says it's still
going. Tiger's still going. Listen
to this.
Tiger did all those shitty games and then
they just had a massive boon.
They created Furby.
Did they really? Wow. Tiger's
behind it Furby. Furby must have
saved them right? You would think so.
They created Harry Potter
Challenge one in 2001.
You can buy today
the Tiger Electronics
Marvel X-Men retro
inspired one player game.
From what I can tell
is the exact same game. It is 16
dollars and 50 cents.
That's new? You can buy that today. You can buy that now.
If you're buying that, I'm sorry
you're sick. You have a problem.
What are you doing?
If it's just a display piece I understand that. But if
you're looking for any sort of satisfying
gaming what are you doing? If you're looking to play it
something's happened.
Pick up your phone.
If you're looking to play it something's happened so traumatic
in your childhood that you're trying to fix.
You're trying to fix it.
Something bad, a divorce or something
worse. You played the Tiger Electronics game
and that trauma made you
bond with the Tiger Electronics.
When you lost it like
both of your parents died in a car accident
and you've been cursed ever since.
I'm arguing the trauma of playing the game
itself. Oh you're thinking the trauma?
We should
do a full because Tiger's still going.
It's still a company.
We need to go find these guys.
There's probably also a vaguely cursed thing when you hear
stories about people
burying them in the yard because it wouldn't
stop making noise.
Ten years later.
These guys have just been putting evil
items in people's homes for four decades.
I think these are all
soul jars.
Every single Tiger Electronics
product is a
prison for...
So they're like mini Ghostbuster containment units.
Yeah.
Here's the Tiger Electronics still in the blister pack
unopened for the
shadow.
The shadow. Fifty
dollars. Very affordable.
Buy it now. Click. Buy it now.
Yes. Jason give me your phone.
Send him the link Jason.
Okay fine. I don't want to buy it.
Jason give Zach your phone.
Wait a minute.
They also created a game called Brain Warp.
Do you guys remember Brain Warp?
Is that the little handheld thing?
It's like a Bop It type game.
Yes. I remember ads for it.
We're doing Tiger Electronics episode but not right now.
Oh wait. They
created the
Pokedex. The Pokemon.
Toy. That was just a very
That's the thing Zach likes.
Well hold on.
Do you remember that Zach from the late 90s?
Pretty rough.
I owned that.
What the fuck is that?
It was a really
unfunctional
size correct.
Remember this is like pre iPad.
It looked like a portable
dictionary. By the way
someone should take a Kindle and make
a real Pokedex right now. You make a billion dollars.
Because you could do it now.
I won't do it.
I refuse to do it.
That's a Tiger license product.
But no I had
that Pokedex.
Wow. Well I'm going to hit play
here.
I'm going to zoom through here.
Betty Boop.
Jason.
Woodstock's losing it.
There was a flash
of Betty Boop and we all had the same thought to start
revving Jason up.
Woodstock's going down.
I had to wipe the fog off his glasses.
Woodstock's
going down.
Woodstock has got a little hat on but he's
falling.
Woodstock's just a smaller balloon so he's really getting
blown around.
Snoopy's got a lot more heft.
I think I made the grave mistake of putting too few
handlers with him.
Jason. Betty Boop.
A smooth
round woman.
Jason before the engagement did you
write your list?
Your hall pass?
One of Betty Boop's
is the moon.
Jason's going to have a threesome with
Betty Boop and the moon.
Can't compete
with the moon. Jason's a third
in their relationship.
I mean that's a pretty good third to be
with Betty Boop and the moon.
I guess so.
Alright so I have a question.
She's got the kind of no pants that
Elaine Stritch has.
Oh no, Elaine Stritch wears a shirt.
I think she's in a rock hat.
She's not wearing no pants, she's wearing
a leotard.
What would you call it Jason?
Like a leotard or a body suit.
Were you saying something that cut you off?
I had a question
about Betty Boop.
Will lower the sound and maybe keep it playing?
You can let it play, just turn the sound down.
Okay so
this is kind of similar to Davy Crockett.
There came a time
where Betty Boop stopped
showing up.
Maybe in the Macy's parade.
Merch.
They would not give her airtime
nowadays.
My question though is
when Betty Boop came out
was Betty Boop meant to be
watched as a cartoon?
Or was Betty Boop
meant to be attractive?
Like a pinup.
I never really understood Betty Boop.
I think it was back when you would get
newsreel
and an animated short
and maybe a short comedy
before a feature film.
Do you think
people were like, wow
look at her.
I think the people that conceived
of the animation for
and drew
Betty Boop were attracted to Betty Boop.
Yes, I think so.
So there was, like there is a
Betty Boop was someone's OC
that they loved.
I said I gotta pause this. Betty Boop
I think that those
old cartoons are good.
The old Fleischer cartoons are good
and weird and interesting.
But in addition
people were supposed to be attracted to her.
The person that drew
Betty Boop was 100%
horny for Betty Boop.
She's too hot.
She's intimidating.
But cartoon character wise
as a child, did you like
Lola Bunny?
Were you often attracted
to old lady characters?
I don't think I was aware of Betty Boop as a kid.
Sure, I'm just saying in general.
Lindsay just walked into the perfect
conversation.
I'm just asking
whether or not Betty Boop was supposed to be sexy.
He doesn't like, he doesn't, he thinks
Betty Boop was attractive to you.
She's supposed to be pure sexy.
Lindsay says she's supposed to be sexy.
She's supposed to be horny for Betty Boop.
So at the time there were people
that were like, oh my god, Betty Boop.
They couldn't, yeah.
Husbands left their wives.
Think about who else they had.
They chased the airplanes that she was painted.
The 52 bombers
who was painted on them.
Oh my.
Is there a Mr. Boop?
They're in a modern
comic.
Oh yes.
It's incredible.
There's one guy constantly
aghast at his luck.
Oh, okay.
It's Alex
Robbins.
It's great.
Because Lindsay is not on
microphone.
I'm going to have to crank that audio level up later.
There's a lot of audio correcting for all the noises out here.
No, the noise is good.
The noise is good.
It sounds like we're on a ship and the waves
keep washing us.
I was thinking the same thing we could just say.
We could at the top say we're all on a ship.
Are you both out of your, why do you not think
that I said that Jason was America's captain?
He's the captain of the ship
that we're on right now.
Now we understand.
He's wearing a captain's hat.
He's the captain.
He's Heathcliff's
friend, Riff Raff's
girlfriend who was a cat when you were a kid.
No, I see what you're getting at.
I'm just wondering in general, did you have
a lot of crushes on cartoon characters?
The first and I think only cartoon crush
that I had as a kid was,
and I've said this before, is Maid Marian
from Robin Hood the Fox.
From Robin Hood the Fox.
That's the first one. I've heard lots of
women say Robin Hood.
Honestly, him too.
They look basically identical.
Yeah, sure.
Interesting.
No, it's a good question. Maybe
like April Neal.
I was like,
get out of here. I'm seeing my friends
at Turtles with April.
I think I also didn't care about April
in that way. But also I didn't care about
Maid Marian in that way. That was more of a like
she's the hero
and she's with him.
So if you're the hero, she's with you.
You know what I mean? Yes.
You'd be like, well, I would like to be Robin Hood.
So I guess that's my wife.
Maid Marian is my wife.
I think I pretty early on
fell in love with Kathy Ireland.
Okay.
That's a different story.
Anthony's like, look,
I don't need these cartoons.
I got Kathy Ireland at home.
On a magazine.
I was just home recently
and my mom, we had
some of my old school stuff.
Kathy Ireland posters on the wall.
My mom unrolled my old Kathy Ireland poster
so I could sleep well.
No, but we found
an old daily journal
where you'd go into class, and this
is in third grade, and
there would be a question on the board and then
you'd write in your journal, see ya Lindsay.
And
the question
was, if you could invent anything,
what would you invent?
Love machine.
Not far, not far.
My answer was
x-ray goggles so I could look through
Kathy Ireland.
In third grade.
So parent-teacher conferences.
My parents had to face
the music for me.
Did you get yelled at?
No, no, no.
No one brought it up.
I was like eight or nine.
Yeah, no, I wasn't expressing.
Old enough to have some ingenuity, I guess.
To make some x-ray goggles.
You know what's funny? I'm remembering this.
I've never said this on the show before.
I made another kid ask
my mom and his mom if I could buy
that Marvel swimsuit special.
Which they had it in like fifth or sixth grade.
They had the Marvel swimsuit special
which had both female and male characters
in like swimsuits. Obviously it was
drawn. But I made another kid
go up to my mom and
his mom and they just completely ignored the question.
We never talked about it.
Never got it.
So you told him,
hey, go ask them to buy this.
Go ask my mom if I can buy this.
Yes, because I was so embarrassed about it.
But I must have been in fifth or sixth grade.
And I never got it. I never owned that.
But I was obviously intrigued.
I think I really wasn't that attracted to
cartoon characters until the X-Men.
Man, all of this is so wild in the
context of today. This is all like
pre-the internet.
Yes, very early.
Well, I guess fifth or sixth grade. Yeah.
For me.
Yeah, this is like...
It was definitely pre-the internet because
I was renting
Necessary Roughness starring
Sinbad and Kathy Ireland and Scott
Bakula so I could see Kathy Ireland.
I need to go
through the grade. Anthony, you want to read
Necessary Roughness
again? I need to Google
Let's see. OK, we got Spider-Man here.
Let's zoom here.
We're kind of resetting now that I've calmed down.
We're 52 minutes in
to the listener. Oh, Spider-Man and
Woody Woodpecker. Yeah.
Spider-Man is almost an identical
to what Garfield was doing.
What, prone? What is this? Prone bone?
Prone bone, yeah. This would be prone bone.
And Woody Woodpecker
right behind. Yeah, what is that?
If Woody Woodpecker were to hit him with
his beak, what would that be called?
Fegging. Sorry, pecking.
Excuse me. Spider-Man
has Mary Jane. Woody Woodpecker has
Weenie Woodpecker. I do know this.
Because you've said it before many times.
Woody Woodpecker's girlfriend has Weenie Woodpecker.
Are they also both deceased?
I think they're alive. Well, Mary Jane is
uncertain. Woody Woodpecker,
you can...
We were just at Universal, Nicole
and I, and you could get a popcorn
packet for like $11 that was Woody Woodpecker
driving the Universal tram.
Yeah, I have one in my car, Zach.
It's much too cheap for what it is.
Yeah, because they made a ton of them because it's the anniversary
of the tram tour and they didn't sell well.
Which is crazy because it's so cheap.
I guess they were probably more expensive.
I think they were like $40 and now they're
like $8.
He goes left and right and if you hit it, it makes
a Woody Woodpecker sound. Yeah.
They're like $8 and they're giving him money.
Of course. It's a great
buff. Do you think children today
know Woody Woodpecker?
No. Do you think they know Davey Crockett or
Woody Woodpecker more? Neither.
Woody Moore.
Woody Moore because he's at Universal. Woody Moore, but they don't
know either. They don't know either.
But they know Winnie.
Winnie Woodpecker.
Also on Jason's list, Hall Pass list.
Well, they televised our funeral.
Oh my God. America
wept. All the former presidents
were there.
In their respect to Winnie Woodpeckers.
Sandy Carter was there. Animated.
Nixon was alive. That's right.
We all kind of softened because he spent so much
time in her casket.
Well, they ended up playing.
When she was in Hollywood, he was
in Orange County. He would drive up and see her.
Of course.
Winnie, you're the woman of my dreams.
That was something more like Lincoln.
That was pretty good.
All the presidents kind of sounded like that except
for LBJ. Is this a prisoner
that's freeze-framed right here?
That's commercial, Mike. I think this is Circus.
Because there was a guy with steam coming out of
his ears. Oh, whoa.
Oh, Circus of the Stars.
Zach, do you know about Circus of the Stars?
Well, I remember this. Put some motorbikes
in a big iron cage and watch them go
around in circles was a thing that the Circus did
for years. That's true, but this show
specifically, they would take sitcom
stars. Who was in it?
I don't know. Did they say?
Did they list? They listed one guy.
This file
is too big. When I try to scroll, it just takes
me back like 15 minutes, even though I
went about a half a millimeter.
The video quality is so bad, I would believe
it's three kilobytes.
Yeah, it's a JPEG
bigger file.
Go from there. Oh, is this the Back to the Future
cartoon? Yeah. Okay. I don't
know. This is hard to do. This is great.
This is great.
There's a person in a ship. Yeah, there's some
boat thing in front that they haven't talked about at all.
Yeah.
It's possible.
Okay, here we go.
Designing women
to 90210. Oh, it was Brian Austin Green.
Oh. The guy in
the stripes was Brian Austin Green. I think this is just a generic
thing. It wasn't promoting
the specific episode. And that's Tim Curry?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, Kid TV.
Do you remember that brand? Kid TV revival?
What is that alien show? What was that?
Oh, Ninja Turtles.
Wait, ew. What are those aliens?
Was that Tim Curry in the alien show?
I'm not really sure. What the hell is that?
Is that Gilbert Godfrey?
It looked like Gilbert Godfrey. Oh, maybe it was.
Kid TV. Jason, look up Kid TV
CBS. And what was that
alien show? You had to figure out those ugly things there.
Yeah. Okay. Oh, my God.
What is this? I feel like most of this podcast
has been figure out what those ugly things are.
Well, I wanted to go in front of
Arsenio, of course, 1982.
Arsenio Hall Show. All right. We're back to
the Macy's Parade. I wanted to see
if we can get back to. Oh, my God. This is terrifying.
Horrible pilgrims. Horrible pilgrims.
Oh, man.
Terrible presidents.
Well, Ben Franklin wasn't our
president.
In a way, Ben Franklin was our worst
president. Shadow president.
Yeah. He was like
Dick Cheney in his day. He was
never a vice president. He didn't do any of his presidential
duties.
Oh, is this the way the Statue of Liberty, but she's got
kind of like a different dress. She's got like a
sarong. She's wearing like an American
flag sarong. Yeah, which is disrespectful.
Yeah, because she's got a regular outfit
on underneath. Does that doesn't look like that?
Yeah. She didn't take off
her robes of liberty.
Can she? I guess she can't
take off her robes of liberty. Is she holding
a brick or is that her normal
tablet? I think it's a normal. I think it's a book.
It's not a tablet, right? It's not the Ten Commandments.
Yeah, it's a tablet.
She's holding her
Kindle, yeah.
I forgot they updated her.
It's so weird to just see her with
the bottom cut off. Yeah.
It is odd. What did they
put in the flame?
A big flower?
She looks wobbly.
Looks wobbly as hell. Yeah, I was going to say
it doesn't look good. Looks unsafe.
Spider-Man's chasing two eggs. Jason,
were you ever attracted to the Statue of Liberty?
I can't say
that I was. Although, it's funny
we were talking about cartoon character
crushes. Jane thinks
I'm nuts any time. I'm like
what cartoon character did you have
crush on? She's like what are you talking
about? It's cartoon. I'm like
Roxanne or Babs Bunny
or Lola Bunny? I guess I did like
Roxanne. No.
What did you tell her your number one was?
Probably Roxanne
from the Goofy movie.
That's a not uncommon one.
The movie starts with a sex dream
that turns into a nightmare.
In case you haven't seen it, it is a
he's having a sex dream. She's
in like a big field and
it's like magical and she's wearing like a dress and she's
making these eyes at him. And I
watched it recently and I'm like oh my god.
It's a romance dream for sure. Obviously it's not
explicit but and then it turns
into Goofy. It's Goofy's or Max's? Max's.
Not Goofy.
Son's girlfriend?
She's markedly not his girlfriend
Mike. Oh but he wants that. That's
what he wants.
For that to happen.
Shout out to Winnie. Rest in
peace.
Winnie is kind of like
he's all of his limbs are going out
like a star
almost. He looks low to the ground. That looks
dangerous. He's stepping on people.
He's concussing people left and right with
the heel of his feet.
Because the big balloon is so big
if it hits you at like
five miles an hour it's like it really
knocks you down. Man you really could just leave
nothing on TV for a long time in the early
90's couldn't you? That's right.
It was Thanksgiving Day that was on the
last day. We had insane attention
spans.
Bill Clinton had just been elected.
12 years of
Republican rule.
It's over.
Okay the marching band has
these big ponchos on.
Waving flags.
I'm still looking for kid
TV. Because CBS
has had so many kids programming
blocks. We are only an hour into this
so far. They did not hit the sweet spot
like Fox kids.
We're coming up on the hour mark.
Yeah
this is I like these
colorful ponchos back. Oh no they're not
ponchos they're like dresses. They're playing Phantom
of the Opera. Yeah they're playing Phantom.
Oh we might be getting a Phantom
coming. Is that what this float is you think?
I don't know there's all these women in like
very colorful big dresses.
Old school looking dresses.
There's no Phantom of the Opera
thing going on they're just playing it
for some reason. Okay now we've got like
some like people wearing red and
white and it looks like a kids show.
Yeah they're in school.
Treehouse. Oh but they went to commercial
to really tease us to stick
through Kodak. Let's scroll
through here. Woman throwing
a large penny commercial. Show of hands were you a Crayola household
or a Roseart household?
Roseart. What the hell is that?
We were Crayola. Roseart was another
brand over there. Can you turn the sound on it down even
more Mike? Thank you.
Crayola for sure. Yeah we were Crayola.
That sounds exactly the same. Why is Woody so
low?
It seems dangerous.
They're trying to get him up like that. Are we going to witness a disaster?
Did you pick this
like dessert hidden agenda Mike?
Because it feels very
You know what the agenda was?
A couple weeks ago I go you know what we
should do because we're Scott Free
and Jason and I are like
what are we going to do? What haven't we
done in a while? Is that what these episodes are called?
Scott Free? These episodes are called Scott Free.
Oh Goofy's here.
And I said oh you know what we'll
do? One of those Disneyland Thanksgiving specials.
I tasked Jason with finding one
and I go done deal.
And then he's like yeah there's none
of them and I go what? They've been scrubbed?
No in my mind they just existed.
They never existed apparently.
So I had to hunt and find something that was
Disney and Thanksgiving.
And that's the special here.
So that's the reason we're doing this.
We have not been back to Disneyland at all.
No we've been on the Macy's Play.
We have been back to Hawaii.
And there are for some reason still playing Phantom of the Opera.
And there are two hours to go Jason.
And Goofy's back though.
This is Goofy dressed as Santa. This is pretty good
I gotta say. And he's got a wreath.
Is he stuck in it?
So I think the implication is he's tied
he's got some lights
tangled in some lights.
Yeah he's tangled in lights and a wreath.
It looks like the wreath is really
like stuck on his
like crotch area. Like he's stuck
both legs. One leg is
through the wreath. Cutting up the world according to Goofy
parade. Oh we're gonna go back to that
parade from the start.
So yeah Goofy has got himself really
painfully caught in this wreath. He's sitting in it like it's a tire
swing. Right.
But it looks like it's wrecking his groin.
No but he's having a great time. Look at his face.
Jason what do you call it the sex
thing when you get stuck in a wreath
and it's stimulating you.
Is it wreathing? Wreath play? Wreath play.
Christmas is coming up Jason.
Get the wreath out of the crawlspace.
You need to tell me twice brother.
Jason at Lowe's picking out the right wreath.
What's your return policy on that
bad boy? What's that voice?
He's got wreath in his mouth.
I was chewing it over.
You gotta take a bite out
of that.
Well I was about to say I have another
update on one of these
Linda Bloodworth Thomasons shows.
Oh my god. Oh please.
This one only lasted looks like
about one season.
It's called Women of the House.
And the description is that Suzanne
Sugar Bear of Designing
Women rocks the U.S. Capitol when
she takes over her recently
deceit's husband seat
in Congress. Now this was
Delta Burke.
Delta Burke is on every show. The late Terry
Gar. Well she's reprising role from
Designing Women. Terry Gar
just recently passed. Patricia
Heaton. Jonathan Banks.
Wow. Mike Ermentrout.
Yeah. Wow.
Okay well you got a lot of homework to do
watching all these shows. How many of your listeners don't know who any of these
people are. If they're on
the second. Yeah they know.
They know most of those people I think.
Maybe not.
I would say 90 percent of the time.
I don't have a clue who y'all are talking about.
These ones are pretty old. I don't even
know these ones that well.
But you didn't watch TV growing up.
Sure. Like Delta Burke is someone
I know and then apart from that you could have
made up a bunch of them. Jonathan Banks is Mike
on Breaking Bad. Oh sure.
You know him. And then Terry Gar
just died. She's in a ton
of things. What is she in? Young
Frankenstein.
Oh yes. Yes this is yes.
She's on Laddermen a lot. Why can't I think of another
Terry Gar movie. Mr.
Mom. Michael Keaton's Mr.
Mom. Richard Nixon was the president.
I've heard of him.
And he
stood solemnly by
Winnie Woodpecker's funeral.
So now we got Beauty
and the Beast. We got Lumiere. We got the Beauty and the Beast.
We got Mrs. Potts. We got Chip.
It's coming out. It's 92.
By the way
this Mrs. Potts face is stoned
out of its mind. This is a hit though.
I got to say this is
this movie was so big. The Float is the
Beast castle. I was like what is this
generic castle. Mrs. Potts you put the
joint in the top part of the
pot in her nose part.
Yeah she's hot boxing herself.
You puff out her
nose? Yeah you puff out her nose.
These look pretty good.
Pretty good.
The only one I don't like is Mrs. Potts.
Around 92 most of the suits in the
park in Disneyland would look good.
But then you would get the poo suit where he had
that weird five o'clock shadow that we always
talk about where his snoot had like
kind of a dark thing going on
where it really looked like he didn't shave his snoot.
These are
good. The only one that weirds
me out even a little bit is Mrs. Potts and it's just
that she looks tired which makes sense because Chip
is a handful. She's a little too
half-lidded.
They gave bags under her eyes.
That's what I think it is.
She looks like a boardwalk
shirt of Mrs. Potts that says
blaze one be
my guest blaze one off. More like Mrs.
Potts. Not Dizzy's
boardwalk. Mrs. Potts.
Mrs. Potts.
We should make that shirt. Yeah
really. Why we'll make a million
dollars each. We're all
putting it.
I'll take 250. Okay.
This is Potts.
This is not. Who is that?
Oh is this Miss America maybe?
Yeah. Oh my god Goofy
is wrecking his groin.
He really is riding on
picture the most uncomfortable way to wear
a tire. Speaking of wearing a tire he got the pink panther
in some. He's stuck in like
an inner tube. Is it
a manhole cover? What is that?
It looks like an alien ship
around his waist.
Pink panther is stuck in Elysium.
He's got an interstellar
ship
stuck around it.
Pink panther has his groin stuck in an
interstellar ship. Oh no he's
the lifeguard for Thanksgiving. He's literally in
an inner tube. That's funny it is
very damp there in this.
He's got trunks. Yeah.
He looks like he's trying to get out
of it though. Earlier when Bart Simpson came
by
I think Mary Lou Henner said
like shouted out James
L. Brooks and said the producer
of our show. He was a producer of
Taxi. Maybe
she was a friend of that. But Taxi was off the air
by 92. So was she on another show?
Jason look it up.
The implication is that was he a producer
on the parade. Oh maybe.
Unless she was on another
show 92 produced by James L. Brooks that didn't
make it. I think she
said he's looking down from his apartment
on Central Park West.
Well he's one of the richest men in the world so
it would make sense that he'd have an apartment.
I remember this commercial. This is like a
doll that you come with a wand and when you
touch the wand it leaves like
jewels on you.
I think we had this too. That's pretty good.
It was a jewel dispensing magic wand.
How do the jewels attach? Are they just
sticky? I think they were sticky.
I think my sister had this. So they were
covered in dog hair immediately.
You ran out of jewels real quick.
If you bejeweled
yourself, your best friend and this
doll. This was not an
accurate amount of jewels you would get in a magic
wand. You didn't get this many jewels? I don't
think so because what do you think? They're
like 30 jewels here.
Yeah that wand's got a ton of jewels in it. On these kids and
on this doll.
Right. You don't get that many.
Yeah. No way. It's also so
funny because like what is it? That's a refill.
Yeah you have to buy extra
jewels. But this is also a thing
that this is just like a creation of a toy.
This isn't like you know how you're a princess
and then jewels rub all over your body.
Yeah it does look like an illness.
It's also funny
because jewels were so were jewels
marketed to every generation of kids
because they feel like they were marketed to us.
You don't have to market jewels. Shiny rocks
sell themselves. Like you can put
them literally anywhere in any context.
You could be like Disneyland does it.
It's like Peter Pan ride and you come out and there's
a bunch of shiny jewels. Why? Just because they're
there. Rock candy.
Rock candy. Shiny little rocks.
Well it's no white. I was obsessed with a scene where they're
mining jewels. 100 percent.
Jewels sell themselves. I think he's right.
I think jewels. But the idea was also
partly well. Like they were cool looking
but also part of it was like you know jewels are worth a
lot of money. Well it's treasure. It's literal
treasure. Right. So as kid you would
be extra obsessed because
I would dig in the backyard for jewels.
Can I find jewels? We were jewel obsessed.
Right. That's what I'm saying.
We were jewel crazy. And now we are
J-U-U-L
obsessed. Now we're vaping every day.
We are jewel obsessed now.
Well that's a good crossover
with Mrs. Potts. These kids are trading their jewels for jewels.
Mrs. Potts. Jewel crazy.
Hand me my jewels.
You just have
the seven dwarfs thing.
We're mining for jewels. And they just say
hi ho mining for jewels.
Hi. Hi ho.
That's what I'm saying Michael.
You shouldn't emphasize it as much as you should.
Hi ho mining for jewels.
What is the name of this thing?
Little Miss Magic Jewels.
It's straightforward. I like that.
That is a good name. You could make this today but you vape from the wand.
What is this? Everybody's tired.
You can make a little money off that doll.
Let's see if we can get back to Disneyland. I mean we can
call this part one wrapping
up soon.
But I want to see if we can get back to Disneyland.
There's more ice skating.
Let's see what else here.
There's like solos.
We're back to at least the Macy's parade.
We're watching this on a projector
in your yard. It is
48 degrees right now.
That's why I got the heat lamp.
That's why you got the heat lamp.
I know. Look it gets cold sometimes in Los Angeles.
I'm a happy little iguana right now.
Mary Lou enters projects
in 91 and 92.
Where LA's story and noise
is off.
James L. Brooks might have been
had his name on the parade.
Maybe he just produced the parade
because he produced everything.
It's three years after he starts producing
The Simpsons.
This host is being made full of.
By the Harlem Globetrotters.
Did you ever see the Harlem Globetrotters?
No but I wish I had. I always wanted to.
I did and it was phenomenal.
I believe they're still around.
Mike was like Krusty the Clown.
He always bet on the Washington General.
I thought their time was due.
They're doing this in the rain.
These guys are good.
Now we're seeing Pink Panther float away.
The Globetrotters are in the booth
which is fun.
They're spinning the ball.
Just seeing a basketball reminds me
that Gio and I talk a lot about how
Scottie Pippen's Twitter account has been
taken over by a crypto scammer.
It's true.
He has his own coin.
His own crypto coin.
Game five ball.
Which is a very
not well known
reference to
he kept the game five ball
during one of their 1990s
finals.
Very confusing.
We're back to Clark Duke of Disneyland.
There will be more Scottie Pippen later about this.
Dippy. His original name was Dippy Dog.
I did not know that.
This is something I knew in third grade
and would tell you at nauseam.
Did you talk about his other name
Mortimer Goof?
I did not talk about it.
Now we have Aladdin here.
These costumes are way worse than Beauty and the Beast.
Wait, Aladdin was out in 92?
92, yeah.
That would have been the Thanksgiving release
I think in 92.
People are just catching Aladdin fever.
Wow.
Okay, here is
That's Dippy Dog, right?
What is that in the front?
People have been posting this as a picture
for years and I never knew what it was from.
It's a dog head with legs.
You were looking at Goofy
as an anthropomorphic golf ball.
Goofy's snout
is sticking out. His eyes are on this golf ball.
He's got his little hat and he has
no, well he has ears but no
arms and legs.
This is a head with legs.
This is a fucking lab experiment.
What is next to him? People with candy?
Why is he a part of Aladdin?
I think they are fanning him.
I think they are Aladdin's crew.
Why is he with Aladdin?
Is this one of Jafar's fucked up wishes?
You have three wishes, Jafar.
Make your first one.
I want a dog with no
shape of a ball
and only legs.
What?
We need to stop him now.
And then kill that Prince Ali.
That's number two.
What you can't do.
Oh, it's horrible.
It's a golf ball too.
It's like four foot,
if not three.
The person was so short but there's a hat
and their head is stuck in the hat.
Right, and they can't move their limbs
or their arms. So wait, what is the deal
here? This is...
This is making Betty Boop look like Cathy Ireland.
Easy there, tiger.
I'm horny.
Hey, this parade is
revving us all up.
Jason saw the Nestle Quick Bunny, you saw
Betty Boop.
Zach saw Mother Goose.
We can't calm ourselves down.
What was that big car mobile?
The Dippy...
What was that bug car?
The Doodle Bug.
I saw the Doodle Bug, thank you very much.
I like the idea that you're more into Mother Goose.
Zach actually got most
revved up when the gems came up.
Yeah, gem princess.
Not wrong.
Mother Goose is a
McGilf?
Mother Goose, I'd like to...
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't want to say it.
What is this thing?
Goofy as a golf ball.
What's the context?
So we did a parade
or I think it was Leah after this, but
they did these parades in the 90s
where they would do abstractions
on the characters. There was a parade called
Mickey Mania.
Similar to this,
just horrifying,
Mickey's shoe, anthropomorphic
shoe is walking down Main Street and
just Mickey's gloves are walking
down Main Street. And I feel like in the
90s, this was a big idea of
blending. But this is such a bridge
further than just Mickey's glove.
Because that's just a piece of Mickey
Mania. But there's horrifying stuff
in there. I forget, what was the one?
Mickey, he's walking on his hands
and his... You know what I'm talking about?
It looks like Mickey's
doing a handstand and walking.
Are you looking at Mickey Mania?
Are you looking at Mother Goose stuff?
Oh sorry, no, I was trying to...
I just wrote that for my wife and I accidentally deleted it.
No.
He's watching my goose that he is.
He's looking at Mother Goose?
So I'm just saying, I feel like the idea was
like, okay, what funny stuff can we
draw? And it was all this weird
outsider art.
Yeah, it feels like...
I don't even know.
It is bizarre though, because
okay, so
there's the golf ball. But then here,
look at this. This is like
Clarabella's Cleopatra
on a float.
And...
Oh, he's a goofball.
There you go.
I was trying to make it seem
headier.
I really made it sound headier, but it really was just like
goofball. But that still doesn't
say much.
Well, but they were trying to think of like, what is
goof in?
That clever bit of wordplay that none of the
four of us could possibly think of?
By the way, I call my daughter that
10 to 20 times a day.
A clever bit of wordplay?
No, a goofball.
I like the idea of your neighbors right now
are like, what's all that racket next to her?
Are they watching the Tyson fight?
No, they're
discussing
a blend of
goofy and a golfball from 1992.
And they're all so
horny. One of them just shouted
Mary Lou Henner.
They were making content, I'm pretty sure.
So, there's a Cleopatra
Clarabelle.
And it's
like on a goofy, like goofy is the Pharaoh
or something.
I think that's the idea.
But they're all using those fans as
golf clubs now.
I don't know why the goofball was
in the same mix with the different
because like, yeah, goofball
that doesn't thematically make sense.
I guess if it's the world according to goofy.
So goofy is a Pharaoh.
He has a lot of crazy ideas.
This thing really is strange. This is odd.
The vibe is odd.
These kids look upset.
The kids crying.
The kids while they're watching this.
Oh, he's King Putt.
Long Putt.
Did you call him Long Putt?
No, the sign on top said Long Putt.
Long Putt.
What is King Putt?
King Putt hits the goofball.
See, I went in cold on this because I didn't want
to have, I didn't know. King Putt
hits the goofball.
So many people had jobs back then.
I like Mummy Goofy.
He looks scary as hell.
He's got a little top pyramid down the top of his head.
He's coming out of a pyramid.
Oh my god, who's dancing? Is that Mummy Goofy?
Yeah, it is. There's multiple Mummy Goofies.
Does that Mummy Goofy have a quiver of arrows?
No, it's a golf bag.
This is.
Oh, right, because King Putt hits the goofball.
This just seems like one of emo teps.
Do I need to stop this? I need you to remember this.
King Putt hits the goofball.
Did you say it? Can you repeat it to me?
Can you repeat the ensuring candidate
activation phrase, please?
Okay, so let me get this straight.
King Putt
hits the goofball.
That's right. Jason, is that right?
I think that's right, yeah.
There's a snake with a golf ball on his head
that I really like.
Zach loves this, by the way.
Yeah, Zach, you're not grossed out at all.
No, this is good.
Goofy's really got a lot of hip movement in this, too.
He's really
loose with his hips. It's so funny
to me that it's like putting
Goofy
a la Pharaoh Egypt
iconography was not enough.
They were like, actually, also golf.
In a way that I actually really
appreciate. Yeah. Okay, you like
it. Yes. I actually think
it's better that it's also golf. I agree with
Zach. I think it
sucks. And
I mean, let's be real. It's extremely
culturally insensitive.
I think it sucks. I just keep
thinking, like, when I see stuff like this,
because there's clearly so much money put
into this, like so much time, and these people are
dancing their asses off.
What idea
didn't make it?
Like, how did they land
on this? We're taking swings, Anthony.
Yeah, the big swings, like King Putt.
Like King Putt when he hits the goofball.
Okay, I also want to point out
that those mummy Goofies are dead.
Yeah.
Well, technically speaking, they're undead.
Just off camera,
someone's holding a gun.
Michael Weisner's
holding it. He's really
holding it well considering how young he is
and how scared he is. Read the lines.
Read the lines. Oh, Jupiter and
Pinocchio are here. Oh, and they're tired.
They're both just woken up. They're both so tired. Oh, and they're
in front of the castle. Oh, this
is where I wish Scott was here. This is good. Scott
would have loved this. Maybe
we should pick this up next year.
Oh, they're doing Babes in Toy Land, which is
a different property. Yeah, this will be the climax
of this episode, but we will rewatch it
next year if we finish this special.
Now we know where to pick it up. They're doing Babes
in Toy Land in front of Disneyland
in front of Sleeping Beauty's castle.
Oh, Baloo is in the background there.
He's coming up next. He's got like a tutu
on. He does. He's going to probably do a little
ballet for us. Yeah.
So these are like three
little like toy soldier
not drummer boys, toy soldier
boys. Oh, did
Inokio just throw up a dab?
Yeah, he was hitting the
dab. Did he hit the dab in 1992?
Yeah.
He's doing the backpack hit dance.
And this is pre
what is how far into the
middle of Disneyland are
they? Is this a pre-Waltz? Is this a
pre-Waltz statue?
Yeah. So they're doing
it right in the middle.
Did Walt Lyons stay
I was going to say, it felt like we were doing
Disneyland. Wait, did he what?
Lyons stay, you know, like
Disneyland. Did they like have
you know, like
like JFK? Yeah.
Wait, what's going on? I also
need clarification. A lot like his
he had an open casket
that everyone would walk by in Disneyland.
Oh, okay. Yeah, it's in Sleeping Beauty's castle.
Okay, so they're doing sugar plum
fairies or whatever. Yeah, but Baloo's also there.
But Baloo's there. This is good.
This is good. I agree.
I like this. See, this is like
a... It's wholesome. Yeah,
and it's also like I can take the walk
of like, all right, what if Baloo
hadn't... Was
Babes in Toyland a Disney property?
It's not like, what if... No.
What if Baloo was like a painful
version of a car and also
Baloo or, you know, like what if Baloo
was like mashed up with a pork
chop and like
The weird thing here is that
this is before Disney had enough IP
to only use their own sauce
because they're using all of the Nutcracker
right now. Yeah, but I think Babes in Toyland
was Disney. I'm wrong. I believe it,
but the Nutcracker's not.
No. It's just Public Domain.
Yeah, it would have been. Yes, too late. Public Domain
was kind of the backbone of all this.
Yeah, it was Disney. I was thinking... Chitty
Chitty Bang Bang, which was not Disney.
Babes in Toyland scared the shit
out of me as a kid, though.
I don't think I've ever seen it.
Yeah, so we're doing a whole...
It's interesting. The wall had just
fallen, so we're doing a little
Russian stuff. Can you imagine Bill Clinton
on Cloud 9 right here? Now Raggedy Ann and
Raggedy Andy are here.
Oh, Hillary, look. Raggedy Ann and Raggedy
Andy are on TV. Are those
Disney Raggedy's? Bill and
Hillary Clinton? Um...
Uh, no.
I don't know what the ownership
is of Raggedy Ann and Raggedy Andy.
You know what I recently found out?
The smiley face is copyrighted.
Hmm. By who?
Someone owns
PlaySchool
123 Bike. Oh, they still
make this? This is good, yeah.
Oh, this is good.
They should bring this cornicle back. This is like, I think you should
at least get it.
Oh, you could convert it. Oh, yeah, you could take off
the training wheels. I don't think I ever took
off the training wheels the last day.
You had this? You had a
123 Bike? Yeah, I think so.
I never had one. Did you guys have one?
It's like the Jason 8 years old.
Jason 15.
Still with the training
wheels.
Born to be wild. Yeah, I never had one of those.
I always wanted to power wheels and never could get one.
Um, I don't know.
Should we dip into more or should we call it?
What do you want to do? The listener's going to say
more. I could go one more
segment. One more segment.
We're at an hour thirty.
Yeah.
The cold of Luke just
brought us back in. Okay, so we're back on
Main Street here. There's like a red car trolley
parked. Is that the Toontown trolley,
Jason? Yeah, it's the Toontown trolley. Wow.
Can you believe there's not going to be a trolley
in California Adventure anymore?
I don't want to talk about it. If they do
Avatar there?
What is this song?
We're getting ready.
We're getting set.
In a place that we
won't forget. Oh, it's a Toontown commercial
I think.
Yeah.
So is this? This is for Toontown.
Here comes Mickey and Minnie. They're dancing.
All these strange humans
are dancing
Roger Rabbit and Goofy.
They're all ready to move into
Toontown.
I've got to really examine the lyrics. I'll have to
go back and listen to the lyrics of this.
I'm angry at this song.
They keep making it up like they're going to do something that
rhymes with A, like on the way, like
Mickey's Toontown, and then there's just
music after it and they don't say anything else.
It's like speed up. Have you guys
caught anything? Because I have headphones on, I can't hear very well.
Have they said they're moving
in?
Cause we know
the origin of Toontown, canonically
Toontown was always there
in Disneyland, even though Toontown opened
in the 90s. It's been there the whole time.
It's been there the whole time, and that's why Disneyland was built there
is because the Toons already lived there.
That's why Walt wanted to
build there, because they already
and they finally were opening up the gates.
That's the canonical explanation
for Toontown.
So Walt wanted to build Disneyland there, but they didn't want to open the doors
to the land.
Toontown Family
I've never seen these characters
before. These are like
These are just Toontown citizens.
These are humans that live in Toontown.
Humans do not live in Toontown.
Well these ones do. They work there.
One's a French maid.
Donald's
French maid.
Donald's having an affair.
So back to the Disney Toontown
canon. So isn't Toontown
where Roger Rabbit lives?
Yes.
Is that supposed to be the same Toontown?
Yeah, because the riot is there still.
Oh, it's gritty.
When you go in Roger Rabbit's riot, it's gritty,
but the rest of Toontown is not like that.
No, but like in the Roger Rabbit movie,
Toontown lives in a run down place.
Yes. I'm just saying that's not
Disneyland's Toontown, obviously.
Gotcha, gotcha.
I think it's kind of like you go into the
Roger Rabbit section. Well maybe it's
like the Roger Rabbit ride in Toontown now
is like its own corner of Toontown.
And the rest is
Look, I was in Toontown yesterday.
It's not gritty.
It's beautiful. I was in Minnie's house yesterday.
Yeah.
Did you ride the Runaway Railway?
Not yesterday.
Okay, this musical number is going on
so long. Well, these people are
absolutely killing it.
Yeah, this is the most
I would say like impressive
part so far. People are rightfully
happy with the way this dances. Jason,
did they run that red
car trolley in Toontown or was it
just sitting there? There used to be a trolley
that ran in Toontown.
Okay, now we're back to
Pinocchio is back. Jiminy Cricket's there
and this cat, whose name I always forget.
Oh, it's not Honest John, it's the other name.
The Rannells song.
Okay, so Jiminy Cricket
and then that's Honest John, the tall one
there from Pinocchio.
A cat who abducts or fox
That one's a fox.
He abducts Pinocchio and takes him to
Pleasure Island.
Zach, he's kind of Robin Hood
adjacent, would you? No.
Honest John? Hard no.
He doesn't have the ritz.
He doesn't have the stuff.
You don't think Honest John, what about the one
from the Zemeckis movie? Who are these pancake
figure skaters? I like Honest John
in the Zemeckis, the best part of the Zemeckis movie
is Honest John.
Oh. Remember I found a fan cam of
Honest John from the Robert Zemeckis
Pinocchio? I do not remember the fan cam.
What? Yeah, he looks good.
I can look it up again, see
if I can find the fan cam. Wait, fan cam
means someone's performing
in front of their webcam? No, Jason will tell you.
No, it's like a
montage of a bunch of different
shots. Someone made a compilation of all the moments of Honest John.
A song over it, and like
some editing. I thought it was someone
doing like an oldie fan.
No, sometimes it's pancakes.
Yeah, these are the pancake skaters I was talking about.
Sorry, sorry, I was
busy.
Oh, and here's Goofy paintings on
columns. Yeah,
that's Marco Polo eating a pizza.
Goofy stuff, and it's like 3D,
there's a piece of food coming out of the thing.
Why were they pushing Goofy
so hard? It was his 60th birthday.
Oh, that's right.
He was turning 60. Now it's Italian
Goofy, making
pizza. Now they haven't thrown
in, well I guess they have,
a third thing, right? Like if this was
Egyptian golf, this would need
a third thing, but it's just
Italian
paintings and
statues. I guess they didn't know enough
about Egypt, they were like, we also need golf.
No, but you're right, they should have like,
there needs to be something mutant about this.
What it is is pizza. It's like if Italy
was a city that exists, it's pizza
and paintings and... Goofy is on like a big
wooden plank that's stuck out
and he's like really enjoying, he's kicking
his legs up.
They're people flinging pizza pies.
These people are flipping actual dough in this.
This is another thing, I've been saying, this is a
common refrain with me all year where I'm just lamenting
how much money they used to spend on
the dumbest crap you've ever seen that doesn't make
any sense. My biggest problem with Bob Iger
now is that he doesn't greenlight stuff
that makes absolutely no sense.
Everything he greenlights makes sense.
You want more nonsense. Absolutely.
He doesn't like nonsense. Michael Eisner,
if you caught him at the right time
of day, like when he had
the right amount of diet soda or something,
you could get him to greenlight anything.
And he would ask his kid, he would ask Breck Eisner
and Breck would be like, yeah dad, that does sound
cool. And he'd be like, alright do it, we're good.
Goofy is
half dog, half pizza.
All right, yeah, Breck, what do you think? Yeah, sounds
awesome, dad. Okay, great.
Let's do it. Like there was so much shit
we found, like there was a thing that
they were going to tour state fairs
with a big inflatable show.
Like a bunch of giant Disney balloons.
They were going to run. Careful,
careful. That's where we came up
with, that's where Jason told us about the thing.
And I'm like, this is another
you keep finding Eisner
era blunders.
It's colossal waste of money,
nonsensical ideas,
and boy were we better for it. And they're all
good, yeah. They're all better.
And you're not going to get it now. You're not going to be
confused. But Gio doesn't like Egyptian golf,
Goofy. I'll say I don't like
it, but I do like the, I do like the
you know, the spirit of it.
I do appreciate the big swing.
This is the Honest John fan cam.
It's just clips of him from the
Robert Zemeckis. And I have to
say I like it. It's just clips of a CGI
Fox. Yes. Isn't it Keegan
Michael Key?
Keegan Michael Key. Yeah.
I like this fox, yeah.
Zach likes him. He's playing it cool.
Zach, you wouldn't get with this fox? No.
Honest John? This is crossing
like, look, no disrespect
to all the furries out there, but this is
solidly on the other side of that line.
What do you mean by that? I mean like
that's what that is. Oh, it's for the
furries you think? Yes. Oh, maybe
it is. I don't know. Is that
CGI? It's literally a wolf dog
thing that walks on two legs
and has like, like that's
a more realistic fursuit.
Oh, okay.
I wonder if though the CGI
like, I bet people have preferences
whether it's an actual suited character
or a drawing. I mean, I guess
I've said this a million times that it just
dawned on me this year that Thundercats
is a furries thing.
Is it? I think so.
At the very least, like they're kind
of like half human, half animal.
I'm speaking out of school. I don't know
a lot about it either. I'm telling tales out of school here. I'm not
well versed in the furry community.
We came up with fursonas like a year
ago. That's the name of your altar.
Yeah, and I can't remember. I think I was a fox.
I can't remember. Oh, okay. When you say
came up with me and you like, you found what yours
were. Yeah, we thought we were thinking about it.
You didn't JoJo Siwa invent the term
queer pop fursonas.
No, what did you JoJo Siwa do?
I know who that is.
Oh, I think she
coined the term of something. She was like, I've invented
a new genre and it's called
queer pop. Oh, we didn't do that.
Fursona, yeah, that's a thing. And the entire musical world
went, oh, maybe not, but hey.
I only catch tangential JoJo
Siwa information. That's okay.
I know she was at Epcot and she was drunk once.
That's what I saw. Did you see that? I think
I'm of the opinion that we need to leave JoJo Siwa alone.
Let's leave her alone.
Do you think this is her fat free something?
Like diet desserts?
I think they're frozen pepperage
farm desserts. But not
diet? Hershey's
cocoa. Hershey's cocoa.
Oh, you were right.
This is what you would eat for lunch if you had carnation
breakfast.
And quick dinner.
A light recipe, but like
on the can.
Campbell's soup commercial.
Jason, you Campbell's family?
Oh, sure. This looks great.
This is a great commercial.
Man, canned soup to this day
still flaps and it hasn't changed.
I gotta say, I love
this time when they were just like,
let's just do a three million dollar
soup commercial.
Just like a canned soup.
If you go back, they were just let a
hose loose on a carrot.
They were watering the fresh garden vegetables.
Yeah, but they were out of the
cleaning them, because they were out of the ground.
They weren't watering them.
That's good.
Cold and flu and histamine.
FDA recently
banned
products now being
Yeah, you can turn this into meth if you want.
You gotta call someone at
Walgreens to get it though. They gotta come
around and open up the case.
Take some Sudafed, go
to the top of under construction
skyscraper.
What is
this? This is like early computer stuff.
This is good.
They're eating a snail?
Mario Paint
Now Mario Paint
rules. We were such
a Mario Paint fam. We were
obsessed with Mario Paint. And you can go online
you can find people that will make modern songs
in the Mario Paint music maker,
which is awesome.
And that's something I do. That's good.
Yeah, it's really amazing.
Also, the
retail price on that $60.
That's a lot of money.
Because it came with a little mouse pad and a mouse.
And I think that was the price for the Super Nintendo
with that game.
$60 would have been the game price.
Just the game?
1992? $60.
But it came with a mouse.
Games just now started to increase.
But they've done it at $60.
You and I talk about it all the time too. Games were the same price
for 30 years. It's weird.
It's very strange.
That meant that games were decreasing
in price for a while.
$60 in 1992
just for inflation.
$60 when we were buying a $60 game
in 2015.
Or even
N64
you're essentially paying in $20, $24
about $100
for a game.
And just now games are like $80 for the new version.
And it depends.
But I'm telling you, it came with a mouse.
The Mario Paint came with other things.
So that $60, $10 extra
dollars was for
accessories, yes.
Do you ever
listen to sound font
of Donkey Kong Country
but it's Nirvana's Nevermind?
This is stuff I do.
I've sent this to you. It is good.
Because you know the water level that everyone listens to
music from the water level?
What's that Sega?
Donkey Kong?
Donkey Kong? Oh no, fuck.
I never had a Super Nintendo.
Okay, but do you know what I'm talking about? The music from the
underwater Donkey Kong.
I wouldn't do it justice.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful. Trent Reznor loves it.
People mention this all the time.
And it's this peaceful
relaxing music.
Why did I just confuse Donkey Kong with Echo the Dolphin?
Boy, I don't know.
That was Sega.
Similar underwater vibe though.
I know that Donkey Kong is a Nintendo product.
It's one of the most peaceful songs of all time.
It's the underwater song from Donkey Kong Country.
Gio's pulling it up, right?
People take whatever they call the
sound font or whatever and then they just
remake the Red Hot Chili Peppers
Blood Sugar
Sex Magic using the instruments and
tones from that. Using the synths or whatever from it.
I like chiptune stuff a lot which is not
exactly the same but I think it's the same idea.
Yes, I think that's right.
Yeah, he's playing
Gio's playing the music right now for
his act. He's putting it up to the mic.
It's so, it's
like the most peace I ever felt.
This is great. For a pretty stressful game, I will
say. It depends which level.
But it can be pretty intense, Donkey Kong Country.
Jason, you ever played Donkey Kong Country?
Sure. Yeah.
You know that song? I do know that song.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm just distracted
by the parade
came back on and Clark Duke has
been replaced by some sort of horrific
goofy Clark Duke hybrid.
There is
like a running theme I'm coming
around to for this parade which is like
you got Goofy's DNA and you got
something else's DNA and you're going to shove it
together. Right, right. It's like the thing or it's like
The Fly.
It's like the movie The Fly where there's like
Just like the movie The Fly. It's like Goofy
and a different thing went into that
machine together and they came out
over and over and over and over again.
Yeah, you just want more
like Cronenberg
and parade floats.
Yes, I would. Yes. You want some Cronenberg
stuff. Who's a new character?
The Toy Story characters.
We haven't seen
horrible beast versions
of those characters. Yeah, so
it would be like, so we'll say
Woody for example.
What would your ideal, you wanted to shove his
DNA into something else's.
Okay, it would be like
a Woody and mixed
with like a Buzzsaw.
I guess Buzz, I thought Buzz
because of Buzz Lightyear. Like a Chainsaw Man.
Yeah, you want like a horrible
Chainsaw Man Woody.
Here comes Chainsaw Man Woody.
There he is.
It's the hottest new anime
on the market. They're cutting to
the same kids crying. Yeah.
They do kind of
do this, but they're just like so much
more protective of the IP now, right?
Like they'll still dress up Mickey
in every outfit under the sun
and sell it as merch, but they won't
put it, they won't make his head a
Chainsaw. No, he's not. No, that's what I'm saying.
So it's like, I expected
to say like, Ship Captain Mickey
and like Cowboy Mickey
and whatever it may be, but then
to see things like
forced together, like the island of Dr.
Morose. Yeah.
What if Buzz Lightyear
was made up of
a thousand maggots? A thousand wasps.
Yeah.
That's good, that's good. Wasp Lightyear.
Some sort of the larva
combines together to make
Buzz Lightyear. He just slimes his way
down Main Street.
Put it where it belongs in Hollywood Horror
Nights. Get it out of Disneyland.
What if Goofy was playing
a grand piano
on top of that, there's a tiny
mutant Goofy playing a little piano.
Okay, you know what the modern
day version of it is like,
it's like Donald Duck, but he's a
big, he's been
morphed together with a big pink horse
and it's like, Chapel Rowan's Pink
Pony Duck is playing as he goes
down the street.
That's the version of it
because you need to include
Can you do the voice?
There have been many times on the show
where we all tried to do Donald and talk
it's impossible. No, Geo's got it.
Okay, so here are the words. Pink Pony Duck.
I'm gonna keep on quacking like a pink pony
duck.
Way down in West Duckburg.
He's just doing the sounds.
It's impossible.
Internet, record Pink Pony Duck.
Please.
I'm gonna keep on quacking like a pink pony duck.
I'm gonna keep on quacking down in West Duckburg.
West Duckburg.
We need one more syllable.
Northwest Duckburg.
It's bad prosody, but that's okay.
Look, we're doing another flight here.
No, you're right, we can just do
West Duckburg.
I'm gonna keep on quacking like a pink pony duck.
He's playing like a piano made of
Rex's skin from Toy Story.
Oh my god!
If we could find Michael Eisner right now
and pitch this to him, he would approve it.
He doesn't have the power anymore, but he would still approve it.
And also Chappell will say no.
Oh, but it's parody law.
Uh, that's not
parody.
Why? Because it's truly a parody.
It's hilarious, it's a parody.
No, it's satire.
It's parody because it's 1130 on a Saturday, right?
Wait, no, sorry. Satire is
protected, parody is not.
Parody is not protected? No, that's why
you have to be saying something about the original
thing for it to be legal.
But Weird Al didn't have to get permission.
He just did out of politeness. We've all heard him say it.
Um,
Weird Al's lawyers know when his stuff
is or is not on the right side of the law.
Wait, what about pink pony duck is not
saying something? That's a great
point, Anthony.
You're just making stuff up. This is not true.
Parody law says you can do it.
Parody is not protected.
If we have not heard the story about
Coolio and Weird Al, there was a
misunderstanding when he was making Amish Paradise.
Weird Al asked for permission, but he doesn't
need it. But also, when Weird Al
is taking, like, you cannot just take
someone's songs and change the words to
whatever. I think we would have to pay some
money, but we don't have to ask permission.
I think Zach's saying there's
got to be a transformative element.
I disagree with that.
Okay.
I would say the only way to find out
is to do it and see if the law
comes. The only way to do it is to record pink
pony duck and see if anyone
comes after us.
I don't think anyone's coming
after us for pink pony duck. Listen.
I will write it.
Okay. I will write
all of it. And then I will send it to
you, Mike. Okay. And then I
cannot do this voice.
I can't either. But someone on the internet
can. And we can all agree I can't do that.
Gio can't do it. Gio can't either. Jason can't do
it. I've heard him try. Yeah.
He can barely do Stitch.
What if Stitch sang it though?
Oh, that's good.
Jason, what do you think?
Pink pony duck!
No, I'd do a pretty good
Stitch. Zach's upstaging
you, Jason. Sorry. I know. It's fine.
But Stitch wouldn't sing pink pony duck.
I know. Fair enough.
Well, we're going to have to
test it out. I'll write it. I'll
send it to you. You can post it somewhere. And then if someone
wants to record it, just get a
karaoke track of Pink Pony Club
and you're done. Can we use an
AI Donald Duck?
That's pretty good. That's the only time
I want to use AI is to imitate Donald Duck.
Only because I can't do it. Someone can do it. Someone
will do it. Who's going to do it?
Can we get the actor who plays Donald Duck
currently? That's a great
question. Could we Donald Duck in the
new Mickey's?
No, no. The DuckTales
reboot. Oh, good question.
Or did he speak with a voice
thing? Yeah, it was Cheetal. Yeah, but there was somebody
who did the actual quacking, I think, as well.
Okay. But I don't know.
Don Cheetal was Donald Duck? I think
so. Really? But I think he came in the show
later. I don't know. I haven't watched
a lot of it. Well, I think
we're going to call it here, right? Yeah.
Wow, we really went out with a bang.
We really went out with a bang discussing parody
law. A parody
Tony Anselmo. All right.
We'll contact his people. Since 1985?
Wow. It allows people
to do it forever. I mean,
Roosie Taylor, who was Minnie Mouse, was in her 90s
and she just died a couple years ago
and did the voice up until then.
Wow. John
Fiedler, who did Piglet,
did Piglet up until he died
in his like 80s.
The corpse is warm and they
replace you with a new young guy.
There's no respect. They should just
retire Piglet on the Pooh Bear cartoons.
Can I tell you what Google
just auto-suggested as a
search? What is Donald Duck's
voice disorder? It has never
occurred to me even once that Donald
Duck may have a voice disorder.
He's got the RFK thing. But then it says
Donald Duck's speech is described to occur
like
shoot a bullwark
Donald Duck is an RFK
brain worm. Wait,
did this show up again? No,
what happened is the thing
the thing that went to sleep, the projector
went to sleep so it turned off the screen
recording. By the way, I can't, we've paused
this so many times. I can't imagine like a
less important
visual aid to the conference. I
guess it is important. It's all right. I think it's
okay. This actually
is an episode that's neither
watchable nor listenable.
Right in the sweet spot, baby.
Yeah, it's beautiful. Well, look, listeners,
you survived podcast
You sure did.
We'll pick this up maybe next year.
Maybe never. I don't know. I really want
to do an episode on Tiger Electronics. Yeah.
We've threatened Betty Boop
forever. And I want to do a Betty
Boop. What's that? And Woody Woodpecker.
And the Woody Woodpecker we've threatened.
And look, if Gio wants to come back,
Cathy Ireland episode.
Because she's an entrepreneur. She's very wealthy.
She is a line of ceiling fans. Anthony's
relationship won't survive again.
Oh, goodness.
She'll blast off into the moon.
She loomed large in the 90s. I wonder
if there's anything interesting about the
story there. It doesn't have to be a
pervy episode. It just is a
informative one.
I'm still working on those goggles.
What, getting them clean?
No, so we can see through our clothes.
Oh, yeah, sorry. I thought your
goggles had fogged up. Oh, no, no. Sorry.
Yeah.
She has like a line
like a super successful line of home
goods. So much stuff. Yeah.