FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcast may contain a pointless boat,
sleepy cave songs,
adorably disguised liquor bottles,
and the unbridled energy of freshly graduated grads.
Kyle Mooney returns to reminisce about Disneyland grad night
on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast hosted by three men who are so hip and youthful,
you'd be shocked to learn that they graduated high school 20 years ago.
My name is Mike Carlson and just saying that makes me hurt, makes my stomach hurt.
Jason Sheridan joining me as always.
Well, I'm just a little guy. I'm so youthful.
Like, I'm just a little, I've got my big lolly for my recording.
Are you equating your size to how old you are?
My sailor's too high?
I'm going to jump on you.
Oh my god, who's that?
Yes, okay, well hang on. We'll put a pin in that.
But just so you're, so if you're short, but you're 80 years old,
that's almost the same as being in high school?
Yeah, sure.
All right, fine. Okay, now go back.
I just wanted to clarify, and that's actually a good way for me to come back,
is with clarifying a Jason statement, but now let's do it as planned.
And daddy's home, Scott Gerdner is back.
Hey, get back, get back.
The Jay Leno, the night show promo.
You caught the reference that it's not get back, it's that I'm,
it's me and I'm in a convertible and I'm driving in the back and there's a sticker that says director
and it just peeled off and now it says podcaster underneath.
The stickers fix themselves.
Can you go out and shoot that by the time this episode comes out?
Yeah, maybe, or I can kind of, hey, I can ask AI to put my face onto.
Yeah.
But it seems disrespectful to Jay, who's going through a tough time lately.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I don't want to do that until the face bruise is healed.
Yeah.
But yeah, I'm back, I'm back baby.
Wow.
Scott free, no more, Scott full.
Playtime's over, as they say.
We're getting down to business, all right?
The show is so different for six weeks.
Yeah.
And now it's going to be so different going forward.
Yes, so markedly.
Well, the thing is, I've, what I've learned about myself that I didn't even know until I started listening to the show without me and reading comments is that I hate tangents.
I didn't realize that until you and the listeners said it.
But now, I guess now that I know that about myself, no more of those tangents.
That shit's over.
Jason and I invented tangents in the last six weeks.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Podcasting, you never had it before.
Yes.
We perfected it, we perfected it.
No, and something I have certainly on the record is never having done.
You'll listen to seven years worth of episodes, you will hear me staying micro-focused on topic every single second of every single one, as it will be from now on.
And to that end, now there's various business of me returning to the show, which we can deal with at a later time.
You were, you know, working on something.
Now you've come back with a face bruise on the other side as Jay.
You have the other side of bruise and an eye patch.
And you have not explained that either.
It's just, boy, that's what a shoot will do to you.
Boy, you get banged up.
Right for Hollywood, am I right?
Is he like, what's the Star Wars, is it a dyad?
What is it?
Were there two halves like Rey and Kylo are two halves of the same thing?
It's like Scott and Jay both got hurt at the same time?
Of course it's a dyad.
It's a dyad, right?
Okay, well Scott and Jay Leno are part of a dyad, basically, is what you're saying.
Yeah.
Well, at least we were with everything we've been through through the month of November, but now we're back.
The triad is back, but actually it's going to be a quiad.
And I wanted to, why I wanted to save any business of me coming back is that there is a much more important return to podcast the ride that is in progress right now over there in the fourth chair.
I can't believe he's not been with us in three years.
I think that was the last one.
Is that true?
I believe so.
Yeah.
Can you believe that?
Three years really flies.
It probably especially flies for this guy who used that time to direct his feature film directorial debut, which he also wrote along with Evan Winter.
It's a great movie called Y2K, which you can see right now.
I've seen this film.
This is a great film.
Highly encourage you to see it.
But first we're going to talk about a bunch of bullshit with the great Kyle Mooney.
Hello, man.
Welcome back.
Damn.
It feels good.
I told you it would.
I've been talking you and talking you into it for weeks, trying to get you off the ledge.
And now that you're in it, doesn't it feel great?
I've been on the ledge and I do want to apologize for constantly being on the ledge.
Yeah.
So the last time we recorded would have been around November 2021.
Is that right?
I think so.
I think it was Zoom because you were back in New York.
Yep.
It was last season on SNL maybe?
Last season we were about to put out Smash.
Morning All-Stars.
And I do.
And I don't know if I've ever told any of you this.
I'm sure we've talked about this to some degree.
But that was, of course, our step-by-step episode, TGIF episode.
Yeah.
Well, there's a lot of...
We tried to pack in three of the shows.
And I think the feeling before was like, I think we maybe all asked, is that too many?
And the answer was yes.
We kept you for a long time on a fucking Zoom.
It was good.
I had a lot of fun, but I remember feeling like, Jesus, we have really...
I was participating and I didn't...
You guys did nothing wrong.
But I will say that in that appearance, I got sort of...
You know, I kind of...
I was confused and I thought that maybe the butt master wasn't...
I thought that the writers of step-by-step were creating some sort of fake product.
Oh, right. That's what happened.
Because I knew that the Thigh Master existed.
The Thigh Master, which was Susan Summers' product, who was on step-by-step,
who's passed away since we recorded that, I believe.
And then they made a reference to something else, the Butt Master,
and you thought that was a fictional product.
I thought it was funny.
It sounded like such a 90s joke almost, you know what I mean?
Like, yeah, I guess you got to get your butt master.
And anyway, I felt so bad when I feel like you revealed that.
I think I...
Well, that's a thing.
I um-actually'd you, I think.
Yeah.
Another thing, that's what...
My podcast aren't about tangents.
They're about um-actually.
They're about correcting people constantly.
It was fully fair, and I'm thankful that you did, because like...
Anyway, then I would say the next day, maybe two days...
I think it was the very next day.
I had to get some dental surgery, and they put me on nitrous oxide.
And for some people, this is like an enjoyable occurrence.
I have a friend who like, she says like she like listens to like fish concerts
while she's on nitrous at the dentist.
For me, I got fully high.
I felt like I was like I was in the dentist's chair,
and it was like sort of folding into the floor below me.
And the only thing I could think about is how I fucked up the butt master thing.
And it was like the worst high of my life.
Oh God.
So you're hearing about nitrous as chill, man.
You can have a hell of a music hits harder instead.
I'm like, they're going to cancel me.
They're coming after me.
Oh my God.
Is that us? Is that the listeners?
I don't know.
You don't want to be inside my brain, Scott.
You know what's funny is I had a plan.
I was like, you know what might be funny at the top of the show
is to reference the butt master thing and bring it up in a way of like,
now Kyle, I want to put you at ease and let you know
we've not been thinking about the butt master for three years.
That's water under the bridge.
It has not been something constantly on our brains for three straight years.
And then I was like, is that like a bothersome joke to do at the time?
Then you go right into, you were beating yourself up much harder.
So you actually have been thinking about it for three years.
Well, no, I was thinking about bringing it up as if it's a thing that we cared about or thought about.
It's been such a long time since we've had you, Kyle.
And by the way, the butt master thing was fine.
I understand the confusion.
Everybody does.
There were never flame wars in our Facebook or Reddit entirely about how flame wars.
It's a retro phrase.
Y2K, you see?
Yeah, smart.
No, I feel like you also maybe mentioned it.
I know you at least texted about it after too.
And if you want to cut all the butt master stuff, feel free, I think.
I felt bad.
I do remember now that I felt bad that you felt bad.
I don't know how long it lasted.
I unfortunately just suffer from neuroses and anxiety and all of that.
So like, yeah, I just get obsessive about stuff.
We put out two episodes a week and I can't go to bed until the episode posts generally.
I have anxiety every single time.
And what is the main thought that is?
That either there's something technical I've screwed up, something's wrong with it,
or that just something I've said in the episode is wrong or somebody's going to get annoyed by it.
And it's fine.
If it makes you feel any better, I also stay up usually.
I have a terrible time getting to bed before midnight.
So I usually stay awake and check on Wednesdays and Fridays as well.
Well, I think it's what a lot of listeners do too because they can't wait for the newest podcast The Ride and Drop.
Has there ever been an experience where those thoughts have turned out to be true or as bad as you imagine them?
Rarely for anything I'm saying.
Once in a while, though, I posted for the wrong time or once in a while I'll do something technically is wrong.
It's rare, but once in a while.
So that keeps you going.
That keeps your brain going when it happens twice a year, once a year, whatever it is.
There's also once or twice a year where like, oh, there's a hosting outage, the hosting or iTunes or whatever.
And it's like we can't do anything.
I get what you're saying.
There was a weird thing recently.
I think it happened while I was gone.
I don't know if this is a mistake, but you put out an episode that was entirely about your credit card points.
That must have been like that was like an error.
That was just something we recorded that in private.
And I accidentally posted that instead of an episode.
That's what I thought when I listened to it.
This is what they would have been talking about.
I'm going to post a real episode, which is about Goofy's barnstormer.
But it was accidentally about credit card points.
Well, I want to say something as a representative of the audience for you, Mike.
And that's that we're cool with whatever we get.
Thank you.
You don't need to be losing sleep over it.
And if there's a mistake, that's fine.
And that makes you human.
Thank you very much.
I do appreciate it.
It's a really beautiful.
That is a nice thing to hear.
Wow.
You know, I feel like we got to look out for each other.
Yeah.
That's the us and the audience.
Thank you for standing up for the whole audience and and saying I don't listen to the show.
You're saying a nice thing, but I get it.
I understand.
I still accept it and enjoy that.
That makes me feel good.
That's beautiful.
It's really nice to and I'm glad that I'm back here to Kyle's back here so that we can all like, you know,
you know, because I think there's a history of you on the show.
I feel like you like you helped us get some nice like connective moments.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
Go in that one where we were all drinking and we went to Buffalo Wild Wings after.
That was the first.
I don't want to let to put you on the spot with personal things that we all we talked about it the whole episode.
Then let's let's go to Buffalo Wild Wings.
Let's go to Buffalo.
And then we went there and that was the first that you opened up that you were maybe going to pop the question to your now wife, Kate, I think.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
But you were like workshopping the idea.
That was probably the first you told anybody, right?
You hadn't even thought about doing it until you stepped foot into the Buffalo Wild Wings.
Yeah. Yeah.
Something about their wings.
And the buffaloes.
What about that buffalo?
Or something about hanging out with three dorks at the Burbank Buffalo Wild Wings.
You're like, I got to lock my relationship down.
I can't do this shit anymore.
What have I?
What has my life turned into?
The wise counsel of John Jameson's product, you know, helped you push you over the edge.
No, but I think.
I forgot about that.
Thanks for that reminder.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, that was that was a nice thing.
Let's keep it up.
And it's working.
And it's working out.
We got a baby.
Yeah.
That's happened since you've since you've been on the show.
Congrats on that.
I have not told you, I don't think in a year and a half.
Congrats.
There's nothing like microphones to put the pressure on.
All good, brother.
And I know that you've been busy.
Yeah, you're right.
But it's one word.
At the end of the day, it's one word.
You can always make time for one word.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
I haven't been there for you.
I don't think we need to cover anything else today.
I feel like good about it.
Our personal business is square.
Yeah, no, we're all we're all set.
You said the audience is good with anything we do.
Sure.
So just a 10 minute episode where we say nice stuff.
They like you.
If you're earnest.
If you're coming out there being like, this is something I care about.
I think that they're going to appreciate that.
Hey, Kyle, it makes you feel any better when the but master first came up.
I had a split second in the row season.
I went, Oh God, which of the four of us was the but master?
And then it all came flooding back.
You thought somebody was a character?
Yeah, I thought it was an insult.
And then we said step by step and it just unlocked.
Like I could picture where I was when we were doing this.
You literally don't remember any of this.
So that's good.
So I remember entirely now.
And I remember feeling so bad that he felt bad.
But I thought like for a split second, I went like you.
OK, here's what I think actually.
Yeah.
Is that you were like, oh shit.
There was an episode where everybody named me the but master because of something I said.
And now I'm freaking out because I don't remember any of the inside jokes.
I think if I had been Chris and the but master, it would have come up every episode.
We should vote.
Who is the but master?
Jason.
I painted back myself into a corner.
Yeah, you did pretty much ask for it.
And what makes him the but master?
Oh, you know.
Just give him a look here.
You see him.
He's the but master.
He's Jason.
Speaks for itself.
We did learn a lot about various sexual things that Jason knows a lot about while I was gone.
That's right.
I feel like that's going to get revisited a lot.
That'll get revisited soon.
Let's flip hard the other way because we talked about we talked about your daughter.
Look, OK, let's just hard separate.
OK, before we started recording, you were talking about just yesterday.
Just yesterday, you were at Disneyland.
You started the process.
You're taking your kid to Disneyland, a beautiful thing.
We love hearing about this when guests switch into that mode and you had something you were starting to say.
I forget if it was about Mickey's house or you had an observation.
That's right.
OK, yes.
So we went to my movie came out.
Our movie came out.
There's a lot of people that make a movie happen.
So I'm just not trying to take personally singular ownership over it by any means.
But the movie came out yesterday and I kind of wanted to get away.
Get away from the scene a bit and just sort of do my own thing.
So the noise was sort of off, so to speak.
And so my wife and my daughter, we all went down to Disneyland and she's one and a half.
So she's like not fully aware and engaging with that sort of universe.
You know what I mean?
She knows who Mickey is.
But like, you know, we took her on Small World probably like a few months ago.
And I think I don't know that she really gets what's happening.
Sure, sure.
That's a little bit in the rain.
I forgot.
You started telling me right around this time.
Around that time.
Yeah, we took her on Small World and she like clapped.
Yeah.
Something.
But she likes Mickey Mouse.
She has a Mickey Mouse doll.
We have Mickey Mouse t-shirts.
And you say like, oh, where's Mickey?
She like points to her no matter what shirt she is.
When you say Mickey, she points to her shirt because she knows that Mickey's on her shirt sometimes.
Any of this.
All to say that I had never gone to Mickey's home in Toontown.
And so we did that and we were sort of, I don't know, I was really curious as to what her response would be to meeting Mickey.
Because I feel like it could be full just silence, awkwardness.
It could be fear.
It could be anything.
And we waited in line.
And I'm going to get to my note in a moment.
But I just wanted to say that like when you're in a line, you watch a movie and then they open a door and then you're like right outside of Mickey's, I guess what, is it a cabin?
Is it a dressing room?
He's shooting his movie barn.
His movie barn.
He makes movies in his barn.
Yes.
Much like Walt Disney with the Alice comedies, if you will.
He knows his history.
Smart.
And when the door to the barn opened and like we saw that there was like Mickey Mouse in there and she recognized him, she was like, oh shit, pretty psyched.
And when we finally got up to him, she was so excited and laughing and touching his nose.
And it was really, really touching.
And I think when we left his house and like we were back in Toontown and we walked past Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin, she's like pointing at it and laughing.
It almost felt like, oh, now this whole universe makes sense.
This is like a weird, wacky place where people are having fun.
Wow.
Like she figured it out by going through the, by like meeting Mickey made her understand what this is.
That's what I'm projecting.
That could be incorrect.
Okay.
Here is my issue.
And I'm curious where you guys fall on this.
So the Mickey we met was classic Mickey and it almost, I think he was wearing like, he was kind of like the Fantasia Mickey.
I don't know that he had on the wizard cap, but he had like a red robe.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
But they still do the thing where it's like recreating scenes and he's like on set, quote unquote.
Because we saw Mickey a couple of weeks ago and he was wearing a Steamboat Willie outfit.
Okay.
So they do strip on rings.
That's not my issue.
I liked, I liked that it was iconic Mickey.
My issue is that the movie we're watching is one of those like new movies, a la the like Mickey Railroad.
Oh.
That like the Mickey.
Stylistically is so different than the Mickey Mouse you're about to interact with.
Right.
And I almost feel like my daughter was like confused, like doesn't, didn't know that was Mickey Mouse that we're watching on the screen
because she knows round face classic Mickey.
Basic Mickey.
And I feel like there's a contradiction to have those two in the, in the exact same place.
Yes.
It's interesting.
I'll say this about my daughter who's a few months older than your daughter.
Yeah.
We, she has now watched every different version of Pooh Bear.
And I think that taught her, like she now accepts, you just go that's Pooh and she goes great.
Like she didn't say great, but I almost feel like eventually you just get, the kid gets used to the fact that there's a hundred versions.
They look different sometimes.
But because of Runaway Railway, which is that style of Mickey, I do, there is a weird contrast now.
And especially because they've ended the shorts, the shorts now are over.
So I don't even know if they're going to abandon that style completely.
So there may be a time when we have like three or four verges, like styles of Mickey in Toontown.
So I got, I hear what you're saying, but I feel like it's going to get even more chaotic from here.
I think, I think get out those shorts.
Really?
I don't take them out.
Oh really?
I've not been on that ride though.
I've heard it's great.
It's a, it's a very good ride.
Yeah.
Could be a scary one for, for a little kid freaking out.
But we haven't done that yet.
Why not just show like plain crazy or something like that?
Yeah.
Didn't they used to?
I mean, this is news to me that it is the new style.
Maybe that was a move to make everything consistent with Runaway Railway.
But I think probably that is weird.
If you're going to show that Mickey and then you want to meet that Mickey.
Hmm.
But it would also look weird if they had made a suit out of the new Mickey, that new Mickey.
He would look strange and he would, he would scare kids.
Yes.
Cause he's unnerving.
And there's the animatronic in the ride of the new Mickey and it is very weird to see three dimensional Mickey and Minnie.
The proportions are strange.
Yeah.
In person.
Here's my knee jerk though to that.
I mean, I don't like if it caused confusion for your daughter, but it makes me flash to the Chuck E.
Cheese conundrum that we all dealt with growing up where Chuck E.
Cheese on stage is different than Chuck on screen.
Right.
He might be animated and a puppet and a robot on the stage and a suit in the room.
And they're all visible all at the same time.
Yeah.
Which has only gotten crazier because now some, then you might also see the bad CGI one voiced by the guy from the band bowling for soup.
Right.
And did I get the band right?
Yep.
Great, great.
And then there's a whole other one.
Right.
I think maybe it's, you know, I don't mean to do that kind of like generational thing of, well, you know, she's got to deal with it.
She's got to like, you know, I dealt with it.
But I think maybe I like that it like if you're challenged by inconsistent brands to have to like overcome and process that there's four completely different renderings of the same character in one room.
Well, this is a thing I feel like, Mike, maybe you're the same way that I learned very early on in the 90s comic book boom because everyone drew the X-Men differently.
Everyone drew Batman differently.
And I was just like, oh, there's different, different artists for these things.
That's true.
But you didn't do that when you were one.
Right.
And it wasn't.
I was like eight or nine.
Like I was, I was gaining media literacy.
I would think the plus I would understand, like I'm sure they probably just put those shorts though in that line because the whole thing is very 90s Mickey.
The whole house is 90s Mickey.
That's a thing.
The video feels.
Video Michael Eisner just soaked in the walls as far as like 90s because Toontown, that's when they built it or that's when it opened or whatever.
But they probably just put it in for synergy.
And I could see now that they're not doing those shorts anymore.
I could see somebody go, well, let's put the old stuff back in that line because we have the new stuff in a full ride.
Exactly. They can be two isolated things.
Yeah.
That's the thing.
How do you keep them separate?
You go into that one right.
You're going to see that Mickey.
You go into this house.
That would be my for sure.
Have you shown your daughter Mickey Mouse Clubhouse or any of those versions?
We just watched for the first time, like truly a couple days ago.
It looks worse than Reboot from the 90s.
Really?
The CGI on it is dog shit.
I will say, yeah, I agree.
Yeah.
But it was making me laugh because like it feels like I'm watching a video game.
Yeah, it's a cut scene from a video game, like a PlayStation one video game.
Do they have no gravity?
Does everybody just kind of fly around a little bit?
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Sure.
And there's a couple like fun, like they might be giant songs that like the theme in the
end.
Yeah.
And those play in Toontown now.
And my daughter loves Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
It's the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Clubhouse.
And they got like music.
Come inside.
It's fun inside.
You know what I haven't said on the show?
There's a music version of that playing and like goofy movie.
But if you go to the very back of Toontown under the cave, there's like sleepy versions
of all those songs.
There's like a dark part back that my daughter loves to run around and pick up leaves.
They keep it calm over there?
But there's like calm versions of the exact same soundtrack.
So if you move out of that area, you get the more high energy version.
But the slow, like the sleepy version.
I haven't seen anybody mention.
I just noticed it the last time we went.
That's really nice.
Yeah.
But the show is unbelievably bad looking.
What is the name of the one where they're, it's two dimensions.
They're like racing or something?
No, no.
The one where they're all in like a nightclub?
Uh oh.
That's, that's older.
House of Mouse.
Yeah, that's older.
That's even older.
But that's where it looks better because 2D animation each is better.
That's where like Hades is at the nightclub.
Yeah.
And you guys remember Gushers?
I guess I do.
That was crazy.
Pikachu.
I mean, that was wild when Pikachu showed up.
Well, you know what?
Look, we.
Alice.
Oh, the Alice Cooper was on Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Oh.
As a dog character.
I heard about this.
Probably from here.
Yeah.
That's probably right.
No one else has talked about it.
Okay.
So we got that to cover.
We got the back.
We got like, we got the grass to cover and the back of the grass to cover.
Right.
But.
We have the three or four, the, the, the Twitter account lost media busters, posted
the pictures from the attempted Herbie, the love bug CG cartoon.
Really?
That there's like, no, there's like nothing.
Wow.
About, except a few screen grabs.
And it looks weird.
We were talking about when we were pitching what we're going to do here, Kyle, you threw
out the possibility of that.
There was this little mermaid, Jim Henson show.
Is that the thing you were talking about?
That there was a.
Ariel's.
Ariel's Island.
Whoa.
It was a, yeah.
Produced by Jim Henson in 1990, like pretty soon before he, he, he passed and apparently
he just was not happy with, with the, with the, with it.
Yeah.
It was just him?
Like it didn't pass?
He didn't, I don't, I think he was just a producer on it.
I don't think he directed it or co-wrote it or anything like that, but it's live action
and there are puppet, puppet representations of all the little mermaid characters.
And they look like the Disney versions?
Yep.
Wow.
Little Mermaid's Island.
Huh.
Is there, is it any, is it viewable?
Like.
It's on YouTube.
I think there were two episodes made.
I only know that one is available on YouTube.
I don't know if both are.
But yeah, it's fast.
I mean, like it doesn't, it feels like somewhat related to like a sort of next generation
of say, welcome to Pooh Corner or Dumbo's Flying Circus or something like that.
Oh, sure.
Right.
Well, speaking of different versions of characters, that's very much in that where it's like the
ones you recognize, but there's something off because they got to be big enough to fit
in a suit or they're just that, I mean, it's really just that like, what is, where does
the creepiness of Pooh Corner come from?
It's that like, it's the like painted backgrounds and suits on.
There's just, I know that locked into your brand, the like inherent scariness of those
shows.
Oh yeah.
I don't, yeah, you're right.
I mean, like if we were staring at the image, I feel like we could call out all the things
that are weird about it.
Sure, sure.
I mean, in the one case it's weird that Winnie the Pooh is talking to Piglet about strangers
and drugs and stuff.
But there is like, yeah, maybe like sort of a deadness in the eyes or something like that
that isn't very warm.
Yeah.
And when you've seen the like animation from the best era of animation and that's how you
know the characters, then going to sort of creepily dead eyed suits.
Yeah.
I watched all that stuff too.
Yeah, I liked it.
Yeah.
But let me, let's try to talk about the thing we're supposed to talk about.
Guys, remember, tangents are over, all right?
The scutful policy, okay.
No, I am excited to talk about what you, you pitched this a while ago and I've been amped
on it for a while.
So I'm excited that we're finally talking about Grad Night.
And if you don't know what Grad Night is, just the basic cliff notes of it, it is the
Disneyland and at one time Disney World tradition of renting the entire park out to high school
seniors, to graduating high school seniors.
These events that are put on throughout May and June where high school seniors get the
run of the park from dusk till dawn, an overnight event that does not interrupt the regular
flow of Disneyland business during the day.
But, you know, they cut the teens wild and it's a really fun area we've never explored.
And I'm glad you brought it up.
Is there anything that you could point to of like, what got you excited about that initially?
Well, did you do it?
What's that? I did do it.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think, well, that's a question.
Is if anybody here, I think probably only me, unless you guys didn't do like the Disney
World.
You didn't travel, you know, super far to go to.
No, but I ended up at Disney World right after I graduated with the high school band.
Okay.
But it wasn't like, I mean, it was sort of a like, but it was a bunch of, it was every
class.
That's not staying up all night.
That's not going crazy.
We were staying up all night.
That's just your own choice.
But that was our choice.
Is there any Disney company making you stay on property?
If you want any sleep, you got to go do it on a bench somewhere.
Right.
No, not the same thing.
And yeah, Jason, you haven't, you didn't do it.
No, I didn't.
I was trying, I was reading up on the Florida one, which was kind of, it ran for a while
and then it was kind of start stop.
And Jane was like, did they still do grad nine at Disneyland?
And it's like, oh, you're thinking about this.
Disney World ended a while ago, but yet Disneyland has been going since 1961.
Yeah.
Disney World stopped in the 2000s sometime.
But Kyle, you were, so you did, you did not actually do this with your high school.
No, we had a grad night though, which was like in our gym.
And I think that, you know, there was like, it was maybe casino themed and like you could
win like a, you know, an Xbox or something.
Sure.
Or like, you know, I don't, I don't know what the like prizes were.
The main thing I remember was Cody Green got hypnotized.
Do tell.
He, I don't know, man, like the hypnotist came and like Cody was going off and doing
some weird stuff.
Like he's on nitrous or something.
He's like, I am the butt master.
Cody Green, the original butt master.
I've not seen a ton of hypnotists.
We don't need to go down this route.
That is a pretty wild thing to see.
There's some naughty ones in Vegas.
Yeah, I'm sure.
There's like dirty hypnotists.
I'm going to be forced to be the butt master.
The whole point is like, and maybe this is the sort of mission statement with the Disney
one as well is like, let's, because I guess it's the night after graduation.
Well, it depends.
I think the, I mean, the Disneyland one runs, it's like, I mean, maybe they try to time
it out that way, but there's like a ton of school.
So just like whenever works probably.
I think for us, it was like, I want to say the night after our graduation.
And the idea is let's keep all the kids contained so they don't get drunk, essentially.
Let them go wild.
But in a, in a way that we're checking and like, there's a question.
Just like start like having sex all over.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
I mean, were there, were there any corners of that gym where that would have been a
party or it was that pretty lock?
Oh, I feel like you know a little more than you're letting on.
I might have kissed my girlfriend.
Okay.
Well, I might not have either.
I don't, I don't fully recall.
Now is that due to sneaking in booze or is that due to you being hypnotized as well?
No, I did not get hypnotized.
I actually think it was very, it was for me personally, incredibly like a clean
interaction, like experience.
Sure, sure.
We had one of these kind of lock-in things.
It was post-prom.
Okay.
So we have to the senior prom.
Everyone went home and changed or changed someone else's house.
Wherever the cool limo dropped you back off.
But you got in the cool limo?
You were in the cool limo?
I was in the cool limo and we were at the Philadelphia, the Hyatt right on the Delaware
River and it was pouring rain all day except for the morning with the drunk driving
demonstration.
This is all the same day?
This is all the same day.
That's a big day.
This is where all of Jason's memories come from is one day.
And then we, so you had to be at post-prom.
It was like, it was like one a.m. to five a.m.
And yeah, there were casino tables.
There were raffles.
There was like the big sumo suits.
The pool was open.
Oh my God.
Sumo suit.
There's some classic stuff.
Oh yeah.
I don't think I've ever done a sumo suit.
Did you do a sumo suit?
I did not do a sumo suit, but everyone.
Should we do sumo suits?
It's so sorry.
Let's do it.
We'll find a place to do it.
Even if we have to sneak into a post-prom party.
Fine.
Yeah.
Everyone who went was guaranteed at least one prize from the drawing.
I won a little 13 inch TV that sat in all my college dorm rooms at my first place out
here until each TV is caught on.
Was that the TV you were using until Mike gave you his TV?
Was that a clean transfer from the prize to?
There was one TV in between I think.
Just one though.
I had a smaller bedroom TV and that was just given away on Craigslist.
How's my TV doing by the way?
Hanging in there.
Great.
It's still doing good?
Okay.
Yeah.
From what year?
From how long we talking?
2010.
Wow.
It's a 14 year old TV.
Just set up a Blu-ray player in there.
Wow.
Watched the Walter Hill directed movie Last Man Standing starring Bruce Willis.
The first TV commercial I ever booked bought that TV.
That's right.
That's cool.
Glad to hear it still.
I bought a PS3.
Still humming.
PS3 with that TV I think also.
Wow.
I was like well I'm really living it up.
Geez.
Sure.
Glad it's still in good hands.
Try to watch taking of Pelham 123 on it but Hoopla was being real buggy.
The library one.
The library one yeah.
The Walter Mathau Pelham not the John Travolta one.
Oh the original.
Okay.
The original.
Kyle any thoughts about Mathau Pelham?
Just funny guys I guess.
Some funny Robert Shaw is in there.
He's the main robber.
Robert Shaw okay.
Okay here I will pivot it over though to the.
Well actually I'll ask you Mike though.
You didn't do it as anything.
Did you have anything like this?
Did you have some like everybody stay sober?
No not really.
I mean after prom we went to like a boat.
We like drove downtown to a boat for some weird reason but then we went home still.
So I don't know what the point of it was.
It's just a lot of travel.
40, 30 minutes.
Was there anything fun on the boat?
I feel like it was the same boat that we went at the end of like eighth grade where I just
remember like dancing with a girl while Casey and Jojo played.
Yeah.
Wow.
And I just like was like vibrating with intensity which we've talked about how much we like
this all my life this song by Casey and Jojo.
Because I'm like my son's super into it.
I don't know if I passed that to you Kyle.
Oh I didn't know that.
Actually not so much lately but there's a there was a couple months there where we just
catch him like alone in his room.
Oh my word.
I prefer someone like you.
That's very cute.
Yeah.
It fell off though.
You know why?
Long string intro.
Yeah.
He gets bored.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't remember that on the radio.
There must be an edited version.
There must be.
Yes I think that was chopped.
It's not exactly like some like amazing orchestral Mozart piece of work on those strings.
That's worth the chop.
I think you got chopped that.
But no we didn't have anything.
No lock in.
I'm not sure.
I don't think there was something I didn't get invited to.
I don't think.
We like stayed at my friend's house maybe after.
I don't remember.
I don't think so though.
Nothing like this.
I'm feeling really lucky that I got to do the real deal that I did the Disneyland overnight.
And I did it twice in fact because I joined my little sister for it a couple years later
when she graduated.
And it's fun.
When you're me when you're a like you know like well I guess a couple of things like
I'm you know I probably lost the Disneyland nerddom the most that I ever did in high school
but it never fully goes away.
You're just like you're just burying it a little bit.
So the opportunity that like oh the thing is going to be the big party is going to be
a Disneyland thing.
And you know men may of course I'm going to be there having fun and mainly like trying
to pretend that I like the music that's playing.
But maybe once in a while they have us waiting on Main Street for a while.
Maybe I could point to one of the windows and say that's actually that's the name of
somebody who worked here.
Maybe somebody maybe I get a smooch because of that.
I would say the answer is no that did not happen.
It definitely did not happen.
But yeah I so I would have this would have been 2003.
That was my as referenced in the joke.
It is over 20 years.
Yeah.
Is that everybody that's or you know I'm 2002.
No I'm 2003.
It was OK.
And Mike sorry.
What's what are you to say a little louder Mike.
Oh 2002.
OK.
I was just I just want I just want people to hear I wasn't trying to embarrass you or
any.
Oh no.
Want to make sure it's OK.
Yeah.
Because he's an upperclassman.
I am now.
You mentioned it.
I'm the upperclassman on the show.
You're the but master and I'm the upperclassman.
You don't pull rank enough.
You don't toss us around like you should.
Yeah.
2025.
That's our new our new name.
Yeah.
Scott's got a figure.
Oh he's daddy.
Scott is daddy because daddy's home.
You're the but master.
And I'm the I am the most daddy now of the of anyone.
Now with the two kids.
That's right.
By default.
Right.
I am daddy.
You are more daddy than me.
Much more daddy.
That's talking about pulling rank.
Yeah.
Hey I'm more daddy than you.
Upperclassman.
All right.
I don't know.
Does daddy outrank upperclassman.
That's another debate.
I'm prepared to have that debate for a while.
I hope this is someone's first episode.
Anyways yeah I mean it was great.
I was really looking forward to it.
The all night challenge of it.
I was that's not something I did a ton and I was worried that I would lose steam.
But you know you just like you know you go wild with the sodas and then you know.
And every ride is open.
Yeah.
Yes.
Unless I had this question.
I meant to look up like what is not like do they not do great moments with Mr.
Lincoln.
Are they asking for like dark room make out trouble if they leave something like that
open.
But as far as I know yeah it's everything is open and lines are relatively shorter
because it's not you know it's a very populated part.
There's probably like I don't even want to guess but I'd say you know at least it's
somewhere between 50 to 100 high schools there.
So it's still a lot of people but not nearly as bad.
And the big thing I think I liked this as a trying to be quiet about it theme park fan
that they do all this stuff to make it cool for teens or whatever.
Like there's a bunch of there's a lot of like DJ setups those little like nightclubs
and dance zones.
But I of course did not want to do any of that shit.
So that means less lines for me so I can just tear through all the rides.
Yeah you don't get caught in the distractions of dancing to 50 cent or whatever.
Did they have any characters dancing or was it just grads.
That's a good question.
I don't recall I will say I'll jump around a little bit and say that there is some grad
night energy preserved in a special that Doug Jones reminded me existed which is called
Disneyland's summer.
What is it.
Disneyland's summer vacation party.
Yeah this is a very good special from 1986 hosted by Malcolm Jamal Warner and a couple
of the facts of life girls and they run through tons of bands.
So many that the lineup see that.
I saw I only watched the John Cicada one.
Oh yes I sent you that one.
Yeah yeah that's the there are two weirdly there are two specials that they tried to
make out of that was a Disney World one which which I'll circle back to.
But this this 80s one very very good.
Highly recommend it.
I didn't even there's not even much in it in terms of like clips or funny stuff to play
because it's just good.
You just like pop around.
It's Videopolis.
Videopolis is new and you get the bangles over there and you get Miami Sound Machine
doing bad boys over there.
I know that clip because Doug put that in one of his one.
Yeah one of his compilations.
Yeah I love that.
Which is great.
He did a really great remix that is just like he just cut together all the footage
from this thing.
It was an Everything is Terrible video.
Forgive me Doug.
I don't remember the name but there's we could post it.
But there's like he just cut together all of the kids dancing at the various acts and
there'll just be a sporadic character in there once in a while.
It's pretty like there's like and it's always weird ones.
It's like just Captain Hook at like the fifth dimension or something or my favorite 80s
ELO.
ELO in 86 and they're performing in front of the castle with a stage that's set up just
for that.
That's all neon triangles.
So my vibe and it's ELO and it cuts to the audience and it's entirely human except for
one lowly Fantasia ostrich in a sea of people.
Just one ostrich head poking up like oddly chosen characters but a hell of a part.
This is by the way and this is I think what I wanted to say about any of this is like
I know it's things we can't look.
These are like old high school events right.
We're not supposed to be there.
We're older than nice.
But any of these I would kill to time travel to like era like 80s 90s grad nights.
I mean yeah I'll sort of state the obvious here and we can go into it as much as we want.
But like the line the musical lineups over the course of grad night history are incredible.
Insane.
That's so crazy.
Yeah this must be what you spark to as I have here and there.
Like if you catch these brochures ever going around you will sometimes yeah you'll look
at like and this is a program they stopped by the way.
Today it's just DJs and stuff.
But up until like mid 90s I would say there would be these years where like as extra enticement
there's five major recording acts or more.
And we've dealt a lot of times with like who Disney thinks is cool and good to put in these
things and in grad nights in the 80s and 90s they weren't off at all.
They were right on them.
They were good good bands.
Yeah I've got I don't know if you guys have access to a list but I mean for the sake of
Y2K our movie coming out takes place in 1999 going into 2000.
The headliner for the 99 grad night is Britney Spears.
Oh my god.
Jesus.
Britney Spears real big fish and sister Hazel.
Like that is.
Wow.
That's like yeah.
That's like yeah you know today that'd be like what?
Chabalrone or something like that?
Yeah.
That's like an idea.
And actually of the moment like correctly calibrated pop culture person.
Here I'll email actually.
I have something here but you probably have a better list.
And this is the thing I think to do throughout as we as we just get excited about these lists
of names.
I'll tell you I'll tell you the lineup that for me was most exciting that like if I could
see I think it's I want to say it's maybe 85.
OK.
Yes.
85 is Midnight Star.
Fuck.
Who great R&B funk group they did No Parking on the Dance Floor.
They had a song called Curious which is one of my favorite songs of all time.
Chalamar.
Another great group.
A Night to Remember.
One of the good.
That song's a masterpiece.
Yeah.
This is for Lover and You.
Tina Marie.
Tina Marie every night.
Some of these were just one night.
Some of them were just like were five of them.
Wow.
If you went to Grad Night 85 you're guaranteed Tina Marie.
You're guaranteed Square Biz.
And Emotion.
So we got we got some sort of new wave in there.
Run DMC.
Now this is like Run DMC pretty much entering the peak of their powers.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
85 is like exactly when that's that's when Aerosmith happens or kind of right after.
Or it's certainly after a couple of the big after Rock Box or big ones like that.
Yeah.
Wow.
Shannon.
Some good freestyle music.
I mean all of these even in 89 I see you know who went to the 89 one was our friend Mike
Moon.
I remember him telling me.
Do you know who performed it?
I have no idea.
It's like information society.
That song.
I want to know what you're thinking now.
But new kids on the block were there in 89.
That's wow.
Yeah.
You're a graduating high school senior.
You get to spend all night at Disneyland and you get new kids on the block.
It's not even like so.
Now sometimes they get it wrong.
Like there's a kid like in that special I was describing one that we've bemoaned recently
Shannon.
They're still trying to shove their bullshit in there.
But for the most part these lists are insane.
Yeah.
There's a lot of Shalimar.
I see Pointer Sisters throughout.
That's always a good thing for sure.
I think that was what 82.
I'm trying to find that one.
I see them in 81.
I see 82.
I see Sister Sledge, Bertie Higgins, Key Largo.
That's wild.
And Frankie and the Knockouts.
Do you know Frankie and the Knockouts?
I don't know Frankie and the Knockouts.
That's a yacht.
Well you might know it if I.
I don't know if you've ever heard of this on a yacht playlist.
Sweetheart, it was you from the start.
Now it doesn't ring a bell.
I don't know if I know that.
It's kind of good like you know like fine early 80s band.
They were really good on Fridays.
Sometimes I'll put on all the musical guests from Fridays.
I've never done that.
Fridays was so great because it'll be like cool.
It's yacht stuff.
It's Kenny Loggins.
But then like the Beach Boys were on.
And then but then like actual like, you know, edgier, you know,
Devo the Clash.
Then I feel like every I'm forgetting one.
There's a real like Boz Skaggs.
Anything.
And if you don't know Fridays, that is the early 80s competitor to Saturday Night Live.
That is why Larry David met Michael Richards.
I don't know.
I can't speak to the show, but music always I feel like every single week of Fridays.
Music was right on the money.
That's great.
That's that's that endorsement.
Yeah, I'm looking at 87 right now.
Also, we might be looking at different lists because I have I think Pointer Sisters 82.
Sister Sledge 81.
OK.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
That's different.
BJ Thomas on 75 with the Pointer Sisters on this.
Oh, yes.
I emailed like this is a version of it.
But it's not like, yeah, it's probably some of the same stuff.
It also might be that like these people were all there and like I'm seeing a selected.
Yeah, maybe.
I've also seen lists where they like merge Disneyland and Disney World.
Oh, maybe that's so that I think some of them are all over the map in that regard.
But then.
Oh, here.
All right.
Let me throw out 88 is a strong one.
Expose.
I didn't even.
Roger Troutman.
Roger Troutman in 88.
That's if you don't know.
That's is he.
He is the vocoder voice in Zap.
Not Zap isn't the vocoder voice.
Is he?
I don't know.
Yes.
Roger is performing the is it a vocoder or a talk box?
Oh, you probably know better than me.
But yeah, I think their very first record he's credited as also as Zap, which is like
he's both.
Is that what that's confusing?
I mean, the group is called Zap.
Yeah.
But like if I think if you look at the back of the record, like you'll see all the band
members.
And then I think like Zap is I think also sort of like the guy who's singing through
these songs.
If that makes any sense.
Oh, OK.
Oh, like a character.
I could be Mr.
Roger plays.
Wow.
I don't know.
Don't.
Maybe.
Maybe not fair.
That sounds that sounds up our alley in a Garth Brooks game.
Roger.
Yes.
Roger is is definitely doing everything in the mastermind.
Wow.
So even like you get to see him at Disneyland.
Holy shit.
Michael Bolton.
Bolton in 88.
Men Without Hats.
Kind of confusing in 88.
Yeah.
That's as I'm picking years.
That's when I'm looking at that brochure.
And by the way, all these brochures also just like awesome fonts, awesome neon, weird squiggles,
weird like diagrams showing the kind of clothes that the men and the women have to wear because
there was a dress code for all this.
You had to you had to be fancy for it.
But I'm looking at like I'm seeing I get to see Roger Troutman.
Star Tours is new.
Videopolis is new.
Captain EO is new.
Any of those.
Holy shit.
For that to be my fucking graduating year.
You see you see Mr. Bolton like when a man loves a woman.
That is pretty cool.
But that was almost like he walked into the room just now.
No, it's not even like that, Scott.
But I do appreciate it.
Hey, so you were lifting us up.
I got to lift you up.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, I mess around.
But like honestly, it's just like cool to kick it with guys like you.
But yeah.
Do you think there's video of all of this somewhere?
No, I don't think so.
Because I looked a little bit like in a fault somewhere online.
God, maybe.
Yeah, yeah, not on YouTube.
That's right.
Maybe Disney documented in some way.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably.
I mean, besides the specials, I don't really know.
Now, I do have a very specific grad night Disney story.
OK.
But it's morbid.
I was wondering about this.
I had a memory of I was I was going to ask you, but I didn't want to put you on the spot
about it because the whole idea of this, by the way, let me I'll back up and say this
started in 1961 and it started in a morbid way because I think there was a community,
I forget what city in the San Gabriel Valley.
There was, you know, things like this, like overnight events for high school seniors were
very common.
But, you know, there's the potential for people to get hurt.
There's potential for drinking and driving and stuff.
And I think there was a tragedy in some community and they started talking about is there a
way to do something that is safe and where we essentially like shake everybody down before
they get in, put them in a place where they can't drink and, you know, but but in a positive
way, you know, give everybody like a fun, safe time.
And this guy, Jack Lindquist, is who that's a name that we mentioned here and there, one
of the like great Disneyland old white haired guys who thought of a lot of the stuff.
And he heard the community out and thought maybe that is a good idea.
Hey, and a way for us to make a little bit of money, too, even though then he had to like
consult with various concerned, like the sheriff's, the local sheriff's department had to
weigh in on.
Can this happen?
And the sheriff's department told Jack Lindquist who wanted to do this.
The kids will burn Disneyland down.
Scary shit.
Wow.
In fact, they did not.
As we know, Disneyland remains open to this day.
The teens didn't burn it down.
It was a huge hit.
It was only one night then, but it was such a massive success.
It expanded to all these nights.
Now, all of that said, the idea is for it to be a safe event.
But there are many ways that this can and has gone awry for which now I will throw to
what I thought maybe you had loaded up.
Yeah.
Have you?
Did you relearn about this or react?
I did.
I was just trying to remember if it was, in fact, you or your mom, correct?
Yeah.
My stepmom, Rose, went to high school in San Diego, and they had grad night at Disneyland.
And she was class of 80.
And I'm looking at the lineup here.
And she's told me before.
But yeah, Casey and the Sunshine Band, it says Cool and the Gang, Robert John Tantrum,
the Carr Brothers.
For some reason, I thought maybe Shalimar was there, but I could be misremembering.
This is a good lineup.
This is good vibes, right?
Did all of grad night go as well as the grad night?
I feel like Celebration came out in the 80s.
So you're seeing some Pete Cool and the Gangs.
Wow.
The idea, this is a running thing, I think, that anything where Disney tries to address
current pop culture, they're always seven years late.
So the fact if we're getting Celebration the year of, if we're getting Drive Me Crazy
the year of, that's kind of insane.
I believe Backstreet Boys in 97.
Yes.
Along with As Yet.
As Yet coming off their hit cover of Hard to Say I'm Sorry by Chicago.
And I see on this other list of 97, I see also Goo Goo Dolls and Aaliyah.
Wow.
That's a good one.
97 slide era.
Izzy up the girl.
I just woke up.
All these other garbage you guys are talking about.
They're zapping on about Zap.
They're zapping on and zapping on.
We've got Art LeBeau here or something like that.
But then, by the way, look, I don't mean to, I shouldn't come back and immediately give
shit, although it's a little bit of what I do.
Jason, I'm so disappointed that Black Balloon was on your Spotify wrapped.
That is so funny.
That's insane.
Number four?
I don't know how that happened.
Well, number five.
Wait, wait a minute.
Actually, you may have heard this on the show already or not.
Kyle, do you know the song Black Balloon by the Goo Goo Dolls?
I don't.
Yeah.
Well, but you heard it.
It's a great comeback for Scott.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, now play it or whatever or sing it.
What do you have to do to...
I can't sing it well.
It's not...
I can sing it well.
Coming down to the forest of love.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
I hear that song.
Okay.
Let's hear it.
Because that sounds...
Now it sounds...
That also sounds like a 90s rock song.
It sounds like everything.
Yeah.
The rhythm is familiar.
If you could only see the...
See, I got pipes too.
I can do...
I could maybe take a little 90s band show on the road.
We're going to sit here and listen.
We're just far away from the microphone.
It's just copyright strikes left and right.
Yeah, I don't want to get sued by John Resnick.
I want him to like me.
You would never.
We're the only podcast that compliments his music.
I don't even really like this song that much.
After all this.
You're just indignant that people don't know it.
I'm a slide guy.
I'm a Broadway guy.
I'm not necessarily a black balloon guy.
You're not a black balloon guy, and yet you're still making us hear it.
You're making Kyle hear it.
Well, you asked him if he heard it.
What is it?
Can he hear it?
Is there a hook?
Oh, wait.
He can play the chorus, but the answer is that no, there isn't a hook.
I'm sure I heard it in the era, but it's not...
Kyle, I'm loving this answer.
We've been fighting for a year about it.
A lot of people are on my side, though.
It's not like I'm completely...
I'm not taking a side.
I'm just telling you how...
That's what I'm saying, Kyle.
Your radio station must have been weird when you were growing up.
I can only live my truth, and my truth is I don't know the song.
I can't know the song.
Jason's listening to it so much in this year of Our Lord 2024.
Espresso number one, black balloon number four.
That's an insane list.
It was really insane.
I think what happened was I kept forgetting how it went, and Mike kept bringing it up,
so every time he would bring it up...
What did I bring up?
Three times?
Well, yeah, I would listen to it.
I'd go like, oh, yeah, this played on the top 40 station into the 2000s out of Delaware.
Jason's Spotify raps might be three listens each because he listens to most of his music on a Victrola.
He's got to crank that thing.
I know.
His Victrola rap would be a whole different list.
Glenn Miller again.
Sitting on the dock of the bay was number five because I dozed off listening to it, I think is what happened,
and it was still on repeat from when I really had the song Wichita Lineman, one of my favorite songs.
I love Wichita Lineman, too.
I had that stuck in my head, so I had that on repeat,
and whenever I jumped or I turned it off and turned it back, I don't know.
You were just looping sitting on the dock of the bay?
I still had it configured.
What kind of serial killer shit is that?
It wasn't intentional.
Somebody who's waiting for somebody to come back into the bay, you want to shoot in the head.
I think I was listening to the album.
Baby's Black Balloon makes her fly.
Since we're talking about Mike, I have kind of a hip lineup from Disney World in 2011.
Wait a minute, let's close the loop on the tragedy, and then we can swing into the happy.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
Yes, wait your step, Mom.
Well, essentially, high school senior passed away.
My understanding, and you can read up on it if you look up Grad Night 80,
he was in one of the cars in the People Mover, and I believe he tried to walk into the car in front of him
and then got run over by the car he was actually just in.
He got caught up on the tracks, essentially.
The way my stepmom describes it is they took buses back down to San Diego that night,
and none of the parents knew the name of the kid who passed,
and so everybody was just incredibly fearful as to who was this child.
So yeah, pretty dark.
That's insane.
But they knew that something had happened, but just nobody knew.
I think they knew that there was a death, I think.
Jesus.
That's so crazy your stepmom was in that class, but it is a weird thing about it.
We don't talk about these Disneyland deaths a ton, but how many are there?
There are like 10 to 14, is it in that range?
I don't know the number, but two of them are Grad Night.
One of them is that, and one of them is a monorail.
Somebody trying to sneak in who was struck by the monorail.
It's often these more benign rides that have done the killing.
Insane. That's crazy.
So are you against the event for that reason?
Are you here to say they should end the event because of the capacity for danger?
Grads are calmer now, though, maybe in the year 2024.
I feel for this person's family, obviously.
Sure.
At the same time, maybe it's not the safest thing to get out of a moving vehicle.
Yeah.
But it's very tragic.
But I also say that my stepmom, she still likes school and the gang, so it hasn't fully...
That's what he was getting at.
Yeah, he was getting at the cool and the gang question.
It came on at your wedding and she did not storm out of the room or drop to her knees crying.
No, no, I mean, accidents happen, right?
Yeah.
Unfortunately.
It's a funny thing throughout this that people have still found a way to, despite aiming to be a super safe event,
there's still a lot of weird bullshit that's happened.
I have a book called More Mouse Tales by David Koenig.
It's a lot of weird Disneyland stories.
And they describe a story in the mid-90s that what's described as a very brawny high school football star showed up on acid
and was just freaking the hell out.
And it took 16 security officers to bring him to the ground.
And apparently what came out of that is that now, that or any future Grad Knights, the Disneyland security is allowed to use handcuffs.
Oh, wow.
Hooray!
Thanks to one enterprising football star.
Are they themed handcuffs?
That's a good question.
I think you could easily put a Mickey Mouse on them.
You could like...
Yeah, on each cuff with the ear.
The ears are in each cuff.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, that's nice.
That would be nice.
So at least you're still in the spirit, even though you're stuck in Disney jail and coming down from acid.
They've described people trying to swim in the rivers of America and all this stuff.
People still find ways to freak out.
I mean, you're what, 17, 18?
You're going to be causing trouble.
If you don't have the respect for the sacred ground that is Disneyland, you're going to be causing trouble.
Well, this is my...
Oh, sorry.
I was going to say, it's like when I went to Hershey Park with the middle school courts.
I see these people every day.
I'm not going to be at Hershey Park for a while.
I want to enjoy Hershey Park.
I'm picking the super duper looper over you all.
Sorry.
You're going to treat it with respect.
Yeah, I'm going to treat it with respect.
You're not going to drink on anything?
That is how I felt.
And that is the story of my 2003.
The only strong memory I have of the 2003 one was that...
I probably said this on the show long ago.
But what I remember is that there was a group of girls, the girls in the Venn diagram,
they were the coolest girls who were willing to talk to me ever.
And so I was always like...
And the kind of girls who were throughout high school was always varying degrees of crushes.
But then I was always like, why didn't it happen for me with any of them?
And then now I know the answer, which is that at grad night,
at some point they lifted their shirts to show that they had taped various drugs and pharmaceuticals to their person.
And even though I'm a high school senior at this point,
that was the year that I started drinking and I started very performatively pretending that I liked smoking pot.
So I'm like past...
I'm starting to drink, I'm starting to do drugs,
but I still fucking square me at 17 is still like...
Disneyland though?
How do you know?
Disneyland gives you a high in and of itself.
Why would you need that?
So then were you no longer crushing on them?
It's not that I was no...
For me, it just answered the question of like...
I was like, how come it never worked out for me?
And I was like, the reason it never worked out is because I am so fucking uptight.
I'm such a goddamn square.
Even though I drink and kind of do drugs,
the idea of having drugs in Disneyland at that point made me like hot in the face.
And I just walked away like, well, I don't know about that.
There's fun, but then there's a little bit too fun.
I'm just like, why could I not have mellowed out at that time?
Why did I need to...
Why was I wound that tight as a 17-year-old?
This is the closest I've ever felt to you.
Because the perspective of my 30s was like,
oh, why didn't we ever...
Why did it never work out?
It's like, oh, I was neurotic and annoying and square and mouthy.
Mouthy?
I mean, everyone back where I grew up was very mouthy.
So that actually probably should have been a bonding thing.
Yeah.
I'm with you.
Well, let's listen to Wichita Lineman and kind of think about regrets.
And we'll have a moment on this later.
I listen to it.
I think about Glen Campbell wandering through the tall grass under the monorail track.
Oh, that's right.
Disney World opening.
I don't know that he's singing that.
I wanted to compare that experience, though, to you, Kyle,
who my sense is that you were not me at that time.
You were not an uptight square like Skycare Nerd 17.
Had you done one of these, what do you do?
Are you taping drugs to your chest?
Are you trying to sneak in a vodka in the water bottle as portrayed in Y2K?
Or is that just a work of fiction?
There was a sort of Christian group that threw dances,
I think, starting around my sophomore year of high school.
And it was a way to meet kids from other schools.
But there was also a sort of religious underlying component.
And to one of those dances, I remember getting drunk before.
I don't need to say the F word.
That's actually not cool.
You're a square now, now that you're a daddy.
But I got caught by the main guy, and I got kicked out.
Do you remember the name of the organization?
Was it some teen term?
I do. I feel bad throwing them under the bus.
So I had to leave the venue, and I went in my friend's car,
and I just started crying because I was like,
I can't believe I got kicked out.
And then I think some other people found out that I was crying,
and they started kind of clowning on me.
So is that the bit that you were kind of further along
in terms of comfort with that kind of thing, with getting F'd up?
But your thing was hiding the sensitive side and hiding the anxiety.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not sure that I'm answering this fully accurately,
but I will say that I think that was a moment where I tried something like that,
and I tried to be a bad boy, and I knew I was actively breaking the rules.
And if, for instance, that occurred prior to me going to Disneyland Grand Night,
I would avoid it.
I would be nervous to do something sketchy like that,
because if you are caught, you're fucked.
You can't hang out for the rest of the night.
I read a story in that book also about somebody who came into the park
with a big film canister, like what should I hold?
35-millimeter film for photos.
But there was a couple, and neither of them had a camera.
So security's like, what's up with that?
They open it up full of something or other,
and then they have to sit on the bus the whole night.
That would not be... You might want to forego...
Hey, if you're graduating high school soon and you listen to Podcast the Ride,
first of all, I'm sorry for wherever you're at socially,
but secondly, you might want to be careful anyway,
or try to pregame it, because that would be the nightmare.
Sure, succeeding and then you're having fun,
you're effed up at Disneyland,
but then, yeah, the sitting on the bus is so not worth the...
That's dark.
Especially, I didn't realize schools in San Diego are going,
I watched some vlogs on YouTube of people who were college freshmen
now went this year, when they graduated,
spring to crab night, and they're like,
we have to get to the high school to park at 5 a.m.
and then we will not be back until 4.30 the next morning.
Oh, yeah, right.
Because it's a two-hour each way, and it's like, good lord.
I think groups come in from Sacramento and stuff.
There's versions of this where you leave on a bus in the morning,
stay on the bus, go all night to Disneyland,
and then come right back, and there's no overnight sleep anywhere.
That's intense.
I had heard various stories about Naughty Naughty at crab night.
A past guest of this show has told us stories
about sneaking cigarettes into tampon wrappers.
Is it Marissa Strickland?
Yeah, that's why I brought it up.
That was probably one of the first 10 episodes.
Cigarettes, that's kind of...
Because they would have been 18.
And a clever way to do it, too.
Yeah, no one's looking in there.
But the better story, the even better story,
I had heard someone who went in the 70s,
this woman and her friend went with some guys,
and pretty quickly they ditched the guys
and just shared a joint on the sky buckets,
just shared a joint on the skyway.
That's not bad.
Now, it's a different substance,
but it's very much like former president Barack Obama,
also smoking on the skyway, getting kicked out.
That was just cigarettes.
Did you know that Obama got kicked out of Disneyland for smoking?
I did not know that.
When he was in college, yes, cigarettes,
when he was at Occidental College,
and he said security was very nice,
and they said, you're welcome back any time,
but you have to leave now.
I showed you a picture of my lanyard
from when I worked at Disneyland.
Oh, that's right. Yeah, yeah.
You brought this up on the show before, right?
Your brief spell working at Disneyland.
I was there for, yeah.
I never even made it to my first day of work.
You didn't do one shift.
I was so afraid of the popcorn machine.
Is that what you were assigned to, popcorn cart?
It was general vendor, so you didn't know.
You could get the churro, you could get the popcorn,
you could get glow toys,
but the guy went through the popcorn stuff so fast.
I'm like, I don't remember what he fucking said.
I was nervous that I was going to have to go up there,
and I was going to burn myself.
Yeah, I get it.
I'd be scared of that today.
That's too real of a piece of machinery.
I'm scared of, I don't have a popcorn machine in my house.
That burn, getting the oil going, that's scary.
No, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, the kind of things my parents used.
I heard all Jason's food service stories,
and it put me off of it forever.
Jason spilling sauce.
Spilling sauce, stabbing myself.
A scar I still have with a prime rib and a roast beef.
Where's your roast beef scar?
It's right here, because I was slicing.
We've seen it, but Kyle hasn't gotten to see the roast beef scar.
Show Kyle your roast beef scar.
Hard to see.
Maybe it heals.
We're under theatrical lights.
I think it's right there.
There's a little white mark right there on my left hand.
I said Kyle seems unimpressed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm speaking for you.
Because you've got to wear a chainmail glove,
but it was right underneath where the glove stopped.
Jason, I'm not playing right now.
That is the best roast beef scar I've ever seen in my life.
Truly, I'm like, damn, that really was roast beef.
They had to throw out the whole round the roast beef.
They had a lot more, thankfully.
Because all Jason's blood was all over it.
I was.
They had to scrub down the whole station.
You were wearing the Falconer's gloves still, too?
I was wearing, it was right underneath where the glove stopped.
That was another thing where they're like,
you're going to work this station.
Here's how you do it.
See ya.
Scary.
Yeah.
That is scary.
I'm talking about playing with danger a little bit, though,
because I thought there might be a good little thought exercise to do.
Because here's another way that people have managed to get fucked up at,
I'm sorry I said it.
I know.
I started something.
That's on me.
I make my own choices.
My parents, yeah.
Barack Obama's choom gang.
What?
Remember the choom gang?
That was his crew he ran with in Hawaii.
I've never heard that in my life.
This is wild.
I'm back to the obscure Jason references.
It was just a joke they would call,
there was just these buddies I think in Hawaii.
What's that word?
I don't know.
But Fox News jumped on it and were like,
Choom gang?
Obama's new choom gang are at it in Washington.
We were just off mic saying we've got to wrap this up soon.
Yeah, I know.
We can't get into choom gang right now.
Choom is slang for smoking marijuana.
I looked it up.
So we are not your choom gang, Scott and I.
No, no, no.
No mistake.
I like that song, but I'm not in your choom gang.
What I was going to say is,
another thing that people tried to do,
and probably unsuccessfully,
was kind of do a little buried treasure with booze
during the day you or somebody you know and trust
goes to Disneyland.
Berries, beer or liquor or whatever it is,
maybe in the rivers of America,
you do a little X marks the spot.
A day before scenario.
Or day of potentially.
You try to sneak booze in somehow
that you can uncover during grad night
and now you're set for the evening.
I'm like, this is a smart group of people.
This is a group of people who all like to drink at Disneyland.
Do we feel like we could figure out a successful way,
and also this seems like a mic challenge.
Do you think we could figure out a successful way
if some teens asked you and said,
hey, you, are you cool or not?
And that would light the fire under you, I think,
to prove that you are.
And the way that you could prove that you're cool
is to hide booze at Disneyland during the day
that they could enjoy a grad night.
Do we think we could figure out a way to do it?
Yes, I would be conflicted
because I'd want to prove to them I was cool
because it's an eternal problem, I feel, in security.
But yes, I would also be a little worried
that I would get in trouble.
But yes, easily we could figure out where to do it.
I immediately think of somewhere in Grizzly Peak.
It's a little quiet back there.
It's a little quiet.
Grizzly Challenge Trail.
Yes.
Something over there.
That might not be open for kids.
That might be a kids area that is not really open for.
Yeah, but then sometimes they can theme it
for like Halloween party.
I don't know.
If it's not open, then I can pivot here.
California Adventure is a lot of pavement,
a lot of open space that doesn't feel like.
Yeah, I think you could go digging around there.
You'd like find a kind of an obscure spot in a planter.
You have to do it in a way where like,
you got to count rocks, right?
Like start the bend because we're not going to mark it
because that'll draw attention to it.
But maybe it's like, all right,
so it's the 42nd rock as you head up east on the trail.
Has Toontown open in this scenario?
I know that Toontown at least was,
it was open for Erin's grad night.
She remembers getting to go on Gadget's Go Coaster
three times in a row.
So that was a fond memory.
Nice.
So I think it might be.
Yeah.
I think Toontown is,
I think somewhere in Toontown is the place.
Yeah, sure.
Honestly.
Any thoughts in the new,
does the new grass scenario change things?
Again, in the back of it,
there's a little cave area and it's a very nice place.
Now a lot of people go there
and there's a little bunch of rocks.
And I bet you could even put like a bag that looks like,
cause people are always back there.
So we just have a bag sitting by benches.
It's always going to seem like somebody there's bag.
And maybe, or you could also like, maybe if,
if like we're talking bottles of beer or vodka or tequila,
put a little funny cartoony label on it,
like three X's or something like that.
Oh yeah, like Moonshine.
And now it's just part of.
Oh, now you think it's like,
it's a prop at Goofy's gas station or whatever.
Go to Mickey's kitchen.
On your way to Mickey's house,
get a cartoon jug of Moonshine
and put it on his kitchen table.
Oh my God.
Yeah, that's really good.
Oh, Kyle's got it.
I think, yeah.
You just say it just has to be like bulbous enough
and you gotta like be careful with the writing.
You can't just take a Sharpie.
You gotta get your friend who writes the best.
I would deploy Erin for this
if she wanted to get in on this game.
Really good penmanship.
I think she could do like perfect cartoony triple X
on something.
Yeah, that'd be good.
It has to have like some bulge to it.
You put that in, oh my God.
And then it's hiding in plain sight.
That's what you gotta do is hide it.
Yeah, you'd have to put it up maybe elevated
so kids wouldn't grab,
like maybe on top of the fridge or something.
There would be a place somewhere in the back
that you could probably put it in part of his house.
There's no way whoever is kind of in charge day to day
of Mickey's kitchen.
Right.
There's no way that person knows what all the stuff is.
They don't pay that much attention.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I bet you'd be fine.
That's it.
We got it.
And then what are you putting in there?
If you're trying to make...
Piss.
Imagine that...
Oh man, and then after all that...
Bite.
Piss.
Oh, okay.
That's good.
That's a mixed bag.
It's a bit of a punishment,
but how bad do you want to get fucked up?
Let's see.
If it was 2003 and I was 18...
Yeah, what are you drinking then?
I think we were...
Well, we were into screwdrivers, vodka and orange juice.
Right.
Nice.
So if we have access to sodas,
I would say just make it a liquor
and then we can maybe do a little mix and match.
Yeah.
That sounds great.
That makes sense.
I would love to...
I'd love right now to go split a cartoon jug
of screwdrivers with y'all at Disney.
That'd be great.
That's the next thing we got.
Last time was...
Buffalo Wild Wings,
you had big revelations last time.
What's going to occur to you
over a big jug of screwdrivers in 2024?
Well, you know what?
When we started I said we could get a drink out of this
and you guys said you have somewhere to go.
That is...
Wait, has the episode come...
Okay, here's what I'll say.
The episode...
Yeah, that is lame.
You've proposed getting a drink
and we can't because we have to go do something
that there's going to be an episode about.
I think the next second gate that comes out.
So when you see the title of the next second gate,
know that it's what prevented us
from grabbing a drink with Kyle
and you will be disappointed for us
that we had to choose this
because we're already in the tank.
It's something we bought tickets for.
Oh, it's...
Oh, my God.
What are we doing?
We can put something on the books.
Yeah.
Let's do it in the future.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, how do you make it helpful
to what you guys... your art?
Oh, the hangout.
It doesn't have to be.
You mean using it for content.
Anything can be content, I think.
Anything can be content.
There's a bunch of new garbage at CityWalk.
Let's just go up there.
Or we could go to a place for grownups.
I don't know.
Yeah, but the Hello Kitty Cafe looks very cute.
A lot of things changing up there.
You want to get fucked up with us at the Hello Kitty Cafe, Kyle?
Yeah.
Do they have booze?
No.
No, they have sugar.
But if we bring in our own...
Yeah, a little cartoon jug of screwdrivers.
I mean...
And Hello Kitty is not a cat.
No, she's a little English child in a costume.
Right?
That's the canon of it.
I heard a girl.
That's the canon.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Okay, that felt like...
All right, that was probably a good end,
but we probably have a couple more...
All right, what were you going to say?
Well, I was going to say my solution for the booze,
which I'd be too scared to do,
because nowadays it's immediately a suspicious object.
It's a suspicious object.
They just call it the bomb squad or counterterrorism.
But the planters scattered throughout Tomorrowland,
you could probably cover some airplane-sized bottles of liquor.
Oh, yeah.
Like some nips.
I've heard them called nips.
Nips, yeah.
You could probably put soil or mulch over that.
Yeah, that's true.
Those little guys, for sure.
And just say, like, okay, go over, sit on the ledge.
I don't think it's a spoiler.
Reach your hand back.
If listeners or anyone ever gets to see the project
that I was just out directing, nips is a giant component.
Is that right?
I had no idea.
Nips is a major element of what I was just doing.
Well, we had a conversation about nips when I was here.
Did we?
We all talked about it.
And you said the word nips?
Yeah, because I had a bottle with me.
And I was like, you want to take a nip?
Oh, that's right.
Here I am acting like I'd never heard the term nips.
Nips was on that episode?
That's crazy.
You're probably right.
You showed up with, like, one third bottle full of rye whiskey.
We're not going to talk about that.
That was before the mirror.
That was a different Kyle.
What were we going to say about bands, lineups?
We got to wrap it up.
Is it quick, Jason?
It's very quick.
I thought you would appreciate it.
This is the Disney World lineup.
The last full year at the Magic Kingdom, you have Ryan Starr.
I don't know who that is.
American Idol person?
Yeah, maybe.
The band called, I don't know how to pronounce this, 30H!
Oh, 303.
303.
They did a song with Kesha.
Yeah, yeah.
My first kiss.
Tayo Cruz?
Yeah.
And then Pete Wentz.
Solo Pete Wentz.
You said this was for me because he's from...
Because it's all very hip.
I feel like this is hip music.
He's from the town over where I grew up.
Yeah, that's right.
Yes, we played the same shitty...
My band, not the same show as him, but the same shitty place.
The band?
Wait, what's the name of your band again?
Second Level.
Second Level played...
Second Level played Back to the Office, which is a place that Fall Out Boy would play as
well.
Wow.
And when I told Pete Wentz this one time, he could have cared less.
You had a moment to tell that to Pete Wentz and it didn't resonate at all?
He wasn't mean or anything.
What's that?
When did you meet Pete Wentz?
I did a live read of some old movie at UCB Sunset, and Pete Wentz was involved in it
as well.
And he wasn't rude, by the way.
He was perfectly fine.
Oh, okay.
I mean, I'm sure Pete...
Was it something random, like snakes on a plane?
It was something random.
Okay.
It was not snakes on a plane.
Did you go up to him and go like, hey, you know, Fall Out Boy is actually from The Sims?
Did you know that?
Did I tell him that the reference he was making for his band was...
He might not know.
I think he knows.
It's actually not a catch.
And my thing on the way out the door, in the lineup thing, the best one, for me, the one
I'm chasing a thousand percent, 1984, Daz Band, Matthew Wilder, Nobody Gonna Break
Up My Stride, who did the songs from Mulan later, Weird Al, apparently, some nights on
one particular night.
Cheap Trick.
Good era for Cheap Trick, too, coming off a Todd Runger produced album.
And Every Night, 84, Sparks.
That is the grand night of my dreams.
Can you imagine?
I'm looking at a schedule that's like...
They trade on and off.
They're at the space stage where Halyx played before, alternating.
And at 4 a.m., Sparks, and at 2.45 a.m., Cheap Trick.
Jesus Christ.
I want to be at that so bad.
And Daz Band was there, too?
And Daz Band, I think, would play where Fantasmic is now.
They would play across the river.
Oh, wow, yeah.
That is the lineup.
I want to be there sharing a jug with you guys so bad.
Well, let it whip now.
Yeah.
I feel like I'm sorry about the copyright stuff.
No, that's fine.
It's a short window.
We cannot give you a new thing to be regretting.
That can't happen every time.
We need to be regret-free after this episode.
That's not fair.
I definitely got regret.
Well, then you know what?
Let's see you out with a hero's exit.
And hopefully as much of a regret-free exit as we can do.
And I'm so happy to say, Kyle Mooney, you survived podcast The Ride.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Because I know you got something to plug.
You got a fucking movie out right now.
It's a great movie.
I'll say it before you say anything about it.
If you're not sick of talking about it, do you want to say something about Y2K?
Y2K, yeah.
It's about two high schoolers who go to a party.
And at midnight, Y2K actually happens.
And for those of us, all of us were alive when Y2K happened.
It was pretty much a major letdown, so to speak.
And this movie sort of rewrites that history.
And I would say there are some laughs, hopefully.
And there are some scares.
I was going to say those things and put the word hard in front of both.
Hard laughs, hard scares, good kills, not to spoil anything.
It goes hard.
Maybe it pulls your heartstrings at moments.
It 1,000% does.
It's so great.
I've seen this movie.
Thanks, buddy.
Scott helped me out.
He gave me some great notes early in the process.
And yeah, we're really proud of it.
So if you can, depending on when you're listening to this, go check it out.
Yes, in theaters.
We're seeing it in theaters because the turns.
I'm happy I got to experience these things in front of an audience,
because there's huge, great, funny, exciting stuff that happens.
It turned out so great.
Hope you're super proud, as you should be.
And the episode, equally proud.
How are you feeling at this point?
It got dark there for a second.
And I don't know how people feel about it, but that's truth.
It's life.
Yeah.
We dealt with it in an OK way, right?
I think so.
I think it was respectful, acknowledged.
You said good things about the family.
I think all bases covered.
I think everything was good.
Yeah, I think everything was very good.
I'm feeling great.
I think we could maybe punch up the Hello Kitty restaurant place
and maybe go somewhere else.
Yeah, I think it's probably another option.
I'm not married to it.
But do you want it to be the kind of stupid shit we do,
or should we all go to a bar for adults?
Let's text about it.
Let's figure this out.
OK, great.
We will solve this.
As for us, three bonus episodes every month at Podcast the Ride,
the second gate.
One more bonus episode on our VIP tier, Club 3.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
One more main feed next week.
I'll kind of talk about some more stuff and what I was doing while I was gone.
And really quick, Y2K thing on the way out the door.
It's Y2K Eve at Disney World.
It's December 31st, 1999.
You have a choice of what you could do.
Everybody vote.
I was like, I wonder what you could do on Y2K Eve.
And the options are pretty good.
One is Disney MGM Studios.
You see Cheap Trick.
Youngstown, whatever that is.
And LFO.
The light funky ones themselves.
Or you go to Pleasure Island.
Rebranded for that night only, PI 2000.
And at Pleasure Island, you see Hootie and the Blowfish.
B-52s.
And Styx.
Pick your path.
Where are we going?
It's going to be hard to top Cheap Trick.
But the combo of those three.
You can watch it on YouTube.
It's a very good trick.
They do Downs.
They do a very good version of Downs.
The combination of those three and the name PI 2000.
That's very strong.
Yeah, PI 2000 I think wins.
Yeah, PI 2000.
Wait, that was the one.
That's Hootie B-52 Styx.
Yeah, that's a cool lineup.
That's a good one.
Another one.
God, I want to do all these things.
What's that thing that the guys that say in the Facebook group about Pleasure Island?
The wistful thing?
Man, tonight would have been a great night at Pleasure Island.
And tonight would have been a great night if we didn't have to go to this dumb thing and we could get Margs with Kyle.
I know.
Oh well, we'll figure it out.
Soon enough.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.