Five, four, three, two, one.
Oh, he's naughty.
I've just seen him on slot machines.
I guess I didn't realize his comics heritage.
He's got baby Huey family, Richie Rich.
Okay, okay.
We look similar, the big round head.
Yeah, he looks really cool.
I love his character design.
Yeah.
I just got a, I just actually hit record.
Maybe this is part of it.
Okay, great.
I was in Target just now and a very aggressive, like, bro, bro.
And I go, I turn around like, oh no, something's wrong.
And he goes, where'd you get that shirt?
And I'm wearing, of course, a Hot Stuff the Little Devil shirt.
And I go, I got it at hottopic.com, Black Friday sale.
And he goes, that's awesome.
And I went, whoa, wow.
That's like the greatest compliment I could have ever received.
I didn't think people knew Hot Stuff.
Maybe he didn't know Hot Stuff necessarily.
He just likes the design, yeah.
He just liked the child devil.
Right.
That's the idea of it was good.
Anyway, podcast The Ride the Second Gate, we're here.
And yes, I am wearing, let's go around the room.
Jason Sheridan here.
He's wearing Islands of Adventure sweatshirt.
I'm in my Be Cozy Islands of Adventure sweatshirt.
Yeah, and our guest today, Nick Weiger's wearing, what is it, blue or gray?
This is just a gray t-shirt.
It's very boring, but I'm wearing it.
I was wearing an underlayer under my much more exciting Tiger print sweater.
But it was just getting a little warm in here, so I took the sweater off.
Smart, yeah, that's a very cool sweater.
Yeah, I like it, thank you.
What brand we got on that t-shirt?
This t-shirt is a, I don't know the brand because I was in Toronto and Air Canada lost my luggage.
So this was like one of two shirts I bought when I was waiting for my luggage for 48 hours.
It looks nice.
It is, thank you, it's very comfortable actually.
Yeah, well I wanted to start with just some wholesome talk up top here, you know,
because I feel like the good listeners today are going to get bombarded with naughty talk, dirty things,
because of the topic of today's episode.
So now that we've gotten that out of the way, a wholesome sort of discussion about our clothing,
let's start talking about the topic today, Santa's Secret.
Santa's Secret.
Jason, you want to say Santa's Secret?
Shh, don't tell Mrs. Claus.
That's the tagline.
Now, I did not make it to this outing.
Yes.
But I wanted to get a little background on Santa's Secret, and learned it came from New York originally,
and that there, I watched, I accidentally watched a YouTube short that showed me everything,
and I don't have the context for it, but I'm like, oh, okay.
A YouTube short though, like how short was the video?
No, no, the like vertical, YouTube shorts are like YouTube's version of TikToks.
But aren't those usually shorter?
It was like 40 seconds.
But basically for a minute, it summarized all the acts is what you're saying.
All the acts.
So my, I'm aware that there's a New York show.
I think the LA show is different.
In fact, I think the show is largely dictated like Cirque du Soleil style.
I've seen one of those where it's like, it's kind of a review where each act brings their own thing to the table,
and they just sort of string it together with a loose narrative.
It was that sort of format.
Yes.
So this is something that started popping up into like our algorithm last year.
That's right.
And it would be like a hunky guy in a Santa outfit, shirtless guy.
Then there would be like maybe like a sexy lady elf or something.
Right.
Woman that seems to be nearly nude in a big martini glass or in a big eggnog glass.
I can't remember what oversized drink it was.
And we were definitely all fascinated by it last year.
Yeah.
And we were talking about potentially going.
And I don't know quite why it fell through.
This is also, of course, we're talking with our good friend, Eva Anderson, who accompanied us.
Yes.
Scott Garner and Eva Anderson accompanied us, Weiger and I, to Santa's Secret last Friday,
which by now you've heard the Kyle Mooney episode,
which we discussed having to end early to go to a secret thing.
Ironically, Santa's Secret.
Wow.
And now it's been revealed that we were going to Santa's Secret.
Kyle asked if we wanted to go out for margaritas.
We said, no, we cannot.
We have tickets to a very important content related show.
Should have brought Kyle out to the Beverly Center.
We offered, but there were tickets available.
We enjoyed Santa's Secret.
So here's the thing.
I think a lot of our discussion was centered around what is Santa's Secret?
Are we going to learn Santa's Secret?
And I think that was a lot of what we were intrigued by.
It was, yes.
They were like, what is Santa's Secret that Mrs. Claus can never find out about?
And so a lot of us anticipating this event was, what are we going to learn?
Right.
And then it definitely felt like there was, yes, a big question hanging over it.
So we're like, what could Santa's Secret possibly be?
And I said, you know, we're Scott-free today in studio,
but I was talking to Scott, you know, at the event,
and I theorized that Santa's Secret was perhaps the show itself.
That we're going to like, hey, Santa's Secret is that he's got a little burlesque that, you know,
he gets a little horny when he's not on the clock, you know.
Right. Santa's Secret is just that, yes, he enjoys a leggy elf.
He enjoys seeing the kneecap of a lady elf or something once in a while.
But the show itself represents just the average dreams of a horny fictional character.
Yes. But in fact, Santa's Secret was much more than that.
I will say, Jason, I would have loved for you to be there,
but it's probably for the best because I think you might have gotten so horny you would have levitated.
You know, Jane's mom was in town and I didn't know you guys had moved this outing until like,
oh, we got to run right after this.
We have to go to Santa's Secret.
And I'm like, oh, that's probably for the best.
I don't know that I would have taken my future mother-at-law to Santa's Secret once I saw what it was.
Yeah. But I will say, I think it was largely an older crowd.
I think it was the kind of experience I have as a man in my 40s now where I go to see like a jazz concert.
I love jazz music.
And then like these silver haired people will be like, oh, it's great to see some young people here.
And I'm like, well, I'm in my mid 40s.
But yeah, I guess I qualify as young in this.
I think that was one of those things where it was like, you know, there were a lot of just maybe that's who this appeals to,
or maybe that's just who lives in Beverly Hills.
There's older folks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's at the Beverly Center.
It sure is.
It is a higher end mall.
Yes, it is a higher end mall.
Some might call it a fortress.
Some might call it an impenetrable fortress.
Kind of famously, famously inconvenient to navigate, I believe.
It's wild how hard it is to just get into the Beverly Center from street level.
This was a whole thing.
That was a whole thing.
Finding out how to get down to the bowling alley was impossible.
We tried after the show.
It took 20 minutes to figure it out.
But the Beverly Center, I will say, is not a place that you necessarily think about, oh, I'm going to go see some light nudity.
It's more of like, oh, they have higher end stores or whatever that means to anybody.
Yeah.
Well, that's what I asked you when you were talking about it.
I said, well, wait a minute, because I thought this was just a straight show.
I didn't know about, I'm not going to spoil anything, but the immersive elements, a word that pretty much means nothing nowadays.
But I didn't know about any of that.
But I asked you, is this a performance base or an abandoned Sears?
Well, we performed an abandoned sports authority and the answer appears to be half calm, half combi.
Yeah. Did you figure out exactly what it was?
I think Scott was doing some research and he found that it was the old food court that has been taken apart.
Yeah.
And hollowed out and inhabited like a hermit crab by Santa's secret.
Would you say that the old food court was dug out?
I guess you could say that. Yeah. Yeah. I think it's fair.
It's a, I at first, because there used to be a top floor movie theater.
It's on the top floor of the Beverly Center, which is like an eight level mall.
It's absurdly tall.
And so we're on the eighth level of the Beverly Center, which by the way, also you have to take sets of escalators that are not connected.
So you have to like go up one set of escalator, then like walk to the other end of the promenade to take another escalator that goes up.
So anyway, so, so we serpentine our way all the way, all the way to the top floor.
I was, I was the last, the last to arrive.
I read basically right at showtime.
And I at first theorized that it was the, there used to be a movie theater up there.
I thought it was the movie theater.
And I was like, that kind of makes sense for a, for a presentational space.
But no, I guess it was, you know, where the Wetzel's pretzels and Panda Express were.
Yeah. But it was hard to tell. They did dress it up well.
They did.
Where you didn't necessarily feel like you were like walking by an old pretzel maker or something.
Like I couldn't tell what it was. We didn't know.
No. Okay. So, so you were in line that were queued up.
It's a little complicated, I guess, because I was late.
Like I'd missed the pre, the pre cocktail thing where you get like, yeah.
So I didn't get a, I didn't get a cocktail in advance.
I had to like, you know, order that separately.
Yes. We are pre prepaid for cocktails in line on a phone.
But then you just like sweet talked a person at a window and got a cocktail anyway.
So, so this is the other thing I will say is that it's one of those things where everyone there is attractive because that's part of the whole burlesque thing.
So it's like there was, there was like this, you know, hunk wearing a vest who was working in the bar.
Sure.
And handed me, you know, I think I got the Rudolph's, the Rudolph Rita or something like this.
It was a red margarita. And, you know, but the thing is, it's like, it's not like they were whipping up craft cocktails back there.
They'd batched everything and he just handed me a glass that was already finished.
So, yeah, it was a big, it was like a jug full of mixed liquor.
Yeah. Oh, well, we love a milk chug of liquor.
Like an icecoach.
And yeah, and then you would go. So yeah, once you finally went inside, there was a little like, it said train tickets.
Right. Right. Right by where you would get the drink.
So I, so I also want to just acknowledge with the narrative that they're what the story they're weaving is, is that we're going to the train.
We're taking a magical train ride to go see the North Pole, essentially.
A Polar Sexpress, if you will.
A train that goes in a tunnel, backs up, goes back at the tunnel, backs up.
A real North by Northwest situation.
So yeah, so we all had our mixed cocktail.
And at this point, you're waiting in this little lobby and I really did not know what to expect.
Me neither, no.
But there was a door and there was like kind of a hunky guy in a vest, sort of a vest with no shirt on underneath.
Yeah, that was like kind of standard look for men.
Sort of vest with no shirt.
Yes. Or just no shirt.
Or just no shirt.
But then he had like a little conductor's hat on.
And I've just, the whole time I'm thinking, oh, Jason would have loved this.
You would have loved that. And also the, the bartender blew a little train whistle and did like an all aboard when drinks were ready.
I wish they all would.
It's hard to get there. I wish you could blow a whistle.
Oh, that'd be great.
To flag down the bartender a different tone than the whistle they blow to say your drink is ready.
Have you, Jason, can I ask you, have you ever in your life worn a little vest and a conductor's hat?
Just those?
With no shirt.
No, I can't say I have.
Okay, I haven't either. I just wanted to know.
I'm open to it.
Okay.
But I'm carrying a little extra weight right now, you know.
Well, hey.
I'm trying to get my diet, my sleep, and a little bit of exercise leveled out, you know.
Sure.
Aren't we all this time of year?
Well, me too. Yeah. Next year you're, like in about a year's time you'll pledge to wear a vest, no shirt, and a train conductor's hat.
You are always trying to get me to pledge.
I just want sort of an informal agreement between the two of us that you will wear the little vest.
I think that'd be a good look for you.
Huh?
Thank you. I appreciate that. I'd give it a shot, you know.
It kind of looks like Aladdin.
It's funny you say that because I bought some just around the house cozy baggy sweatpants to wear.
Okay.
And when I got them home and tried them on, the cozy baggy sweatpants I thought I bought looked more like Aladdin's pants.
Oh, okay.
But then they shrunk up a little on the wash, so then they just looked like normal sweatpants.
Okay. Yeah, it kind of bums me out though that they're regular now.
Yeah, that is a bummer.
I know. I was a little bummed too because I was going to turn it into content.
So, oh well.
Oh well.
I can't believe how long it took me to figure out that my wife and other women I've cohabited with are correct to size up on their lounge wear.
You know what I mean?
It's like at home I should be wearing an XXL sweatshirt because it's fun to have a big cozy sweatshirt.
It's really comfy.
You want to swim in it more.
Yeah, exactly.
I would usually just get stuff that's my size and I'm like, well, I'm not as comfortable as I should be.
That's a good point.
I feel like everything my old t-shirts I sleep in now, they're like too small.
Yeah.
And that's not as nice.
No.
Oh, I've always been a baggy t-shirt boy for lounging and sleeping.
That's the way to go.
Oh, yeah.
Would you always buy one size or two sizes up?
Well, I think when we were little, we would usually just buy like a big adult size shirt to wear in the pool.
Oh, okay.
When you go to the pool or the beach or around the house or something.
And then in the 90s, baggy was very popular.
Yeah.
Now it's popular again.
Right.
And then there was that hell in the 2010s, 2009 where we all were very uncomfortable in slim skinny jeans and awful American barrel shirts.
Yeah.
Well, this hot stuff, the little devil shirt is XL and I'm usually a large guy.
But I went XL this time because baggy is in.
It looks great.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That's all I needed to hear.
So we go in there and yeah, there's kind of like a train lobby sort of setup.
And we're queued up outside in the mall.
Then we go inside.
There's kind of like this sort of train station that we're hanging out in.
And then we're ushered through just a black tunnel.
It is just dark and hard to see.
And I, again, still don't know what's going on at this point and what to expect.
And we come out on the other side and I would say we were all enchanted.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty good show on the other side.
It was good because you went through the tunnel and I'm like, oh, is this going to just be, first of all, it felt like a horror night's maze or something.
Yeah, exactly.
It's going to be scary or we're just going to go straight into the nightclub.
And there's like, we didn't even know if there's going to be a pre-show, you know.
Because you could hear the loud band playing.
Right.
You could hear like somebody playing Simply the Best by Tina Turner in the distance.
And you're like, okay, who knows what this, but yeah, you're right.
We walked out of this dark tunnel into a winter Christmas wonderland.
It was a winter wonderland with some robots.
There were some animatronics.
Yes, there was like a good amount of robots, this whole like kind of walkthrough area.
And a part of me also was thinking like, oh, did I read wrong?
I thought this was a show, but maybe it's just a maze.
Yeah, maybe it's just a walkthrough sort of thing.
Because of how elaborate the decorations were.
I thought, oh, maybe that's the experience.
I guess at this point also we should say that we were given a ticket for our party.
Yes, yes.
And in advance, like this was not a drink ticket.
This was a separate ticket.
They were like, hey, this is for the show.
Give this to the, was it the gingerbread lady?
Yes, I believe it was the gingerbread lady.
Give this to the gingerbread lady for a special treat or something.
Right.
Or for some sugar.
Was that what the language was?
I don't remember the specific language.
Something like that, yeah.
Yeah, so it was a little bit like winky, winky, whatever that.
You knew what it meant.
But like, here, give that to this person.
But it felt like a quest or something you had to go on.
Right.
Which is a fun part of an immersive experience.
I agree.
We go through there and there's like, you know, there's a bunch of animatronics.
There's a, but this is the other thing is like you said Winter Wonderland.
I think that's a good way to characterize it.
Because Jason, it's very wholesome at first at least.
Yeah.
There's nothing that's at all body except for there's the guy with the Santa hat who's like very, was it the Santa guy?
That was a little later.
It was a little later.
It was a sexy lumberjack, right?
It was a sexy lumberjack.
Yeah.
I sometimes, it's hard to tell where, which sexy guy was in what scene.
But I think for the first room, there wasn't anything.
Nothing was getting me going in the first room.
Yeah.
You know?
It was, I think it was a guy with like a, you know, like a winter hat and then like, you know, short shorts.
And he was shirtless.
And he was just there to like take our picture.
He's like, do you guys want to take your picture in front of the big Christmas table?
Right.
I was in such a mood to, excuse me, a mode to look out for things.
I guess I was in a mood too.
That I was like, oh, maybe I'm taking pictures of things.
I'm like, oh, that Santa's like a pervert.
Yes, right.
He's a peeping Tom Perl.
And then you look at the phone and you're like, I don't know necessarily if that's what they were going for.
It might just be Santa standing behind a tree.
And then I'm looking at the elves and I'm like, which one of these elves is a sick fuck?
And then I'm like, I know they all seem like nice and innocent.
No, yeah.
And then I think I said something to you in the first room or two and I was like, what are these?
When are they going to get sexy?
Yeah, when's it going to be horny?
Yeah, because I was like, oh, maybe they overplayed their hand.
Maybe this isn't going to be a very sexual show.
Yeah, we kind of chased and maybe there's some people wearing skimpy outfits.
But if I'm just looking at stuff that would be at like a Christmas superstore.
I will say the one bit of show I really enjoy is it's the looping conveyor belt trick,
which they had a conveyor belt of presents that would just go around.
Oh yeah, and we had a little Christmas, I guess, mouse there looking at a pretzel.
Is that what that is?
Yes, there's a Christmas.
I would say he's like a two and a half foot tall Christmas mouse.
His head moves.
He's got an adorable face and he seems to be doing something to a giant pretzel,
like one of those like, you know, baseball stadium pretzels.
I think he's maybe just eyeing it.
You think he's eyeing it?
I feel like he's holding a candy cane as well.
I don't know because it feels like he's working on it, but maybe he's not.
Maybe that's what he's making.
Maybe that's his job.
He says he's a pretzel maker.
Yeah, is that a Christmas tree?
Like, is that something you would have for Christmas?
A big stadium pretzel?
A big baseball?
I can't say so.
Yeah, I don't think it is, but maybe it was an East Coast thing.
I was going to say maybe little smokies, little pigs in a blanket,
but those are usually crescent rolls.
You would never get a big baseball stadium pretzel in your stocking?
I can't say.
No.
Get an orange or two maybe.
Okay, sure.
Tangerine.
That feels like the kind of movie you heard about when it's like, oh yeah,
that's what Dutch Christmas is.
They all have like big pretzels and then like someone wearing like a racially
inappropriate outfit.
Yeah, I was going to say big pretzels and then something that is ghastly.
Yeah.
Yes.
So yeah, the first room and a half, two rooms were just like that.
And I was like, wow, this is really elaborate.
And they put some money into it.
Yeah.
Because a lot of times, you know, when these temporary things pop up,
it's a big ripoff.
I expect to be completely half-assed.
Like, oh, they put some wrapping paper on the walls, like wallpaper,
that sort of thing.
It's like, no, but they got a lot of animatronics here.
They put some work into staging this.
Yeah.
Tickets were $75.
Yes.
Which is expensive.
We could have gone to the press night, but it didn't work out for everyone's
schedule.
So we ended up paying.
So we can be as honest as possible about the $75.
Yeah.
Which I would say for this experience, just on the cusp of outrageous,
like $75 is a lot of money for what we got.
Wait.
Does that include a cocktail at all?
No.
Okay.
The cocktail was separate and the cocktail was, I believe, $22.
Yeah.
But I would say the average enjoyment of the average show-goer was through
the roof.
That's true.
People were having fun.
So I think that there was hooting and hollering going on at this thing.
I was like, oh, everybody here was loving this.
So I feel like if you like this type of entertainment, you know,
it would be good to write up your alley.
See, now I'm very curious because I think maybe I've been to one or two
burlesque shows and so I don't have any bearing for it.
I get it.
I know there's craftsmanship that goes into it.
I appreciate there seems to be, at least in the LA scene,
like a real body positivity and acceptance angle.
And also, it's a little horny.
It's a little sexy.
But what you've described so far seems to be waiters who are dressed like
Chippendales.
Yeah.
So we are still in the pre-show and we kind of snake our way through this
maze.
And at what point do we meet Santa's secretary?
Very quickly.
That's like the next room.
Yes, the next room.
So we come into this room and there's a performer there that,
as you just pointed, as you just said, is Santa's secretary.
And there's a little desk and kind of a little tableau of what it might look
like in Santa's office.
All the big Christmas characters were represented.
The gingerbread lady, the ice queen, and Santa's secretary.
Santa's W2 employee secretary.
Needs a lot of help around the holiday season, so it makes sense.
So you've got sets.
You've got photo ops.
And so she's kind of got like, I guess, his study or whatever.
It's like sort of set up like a state.
She's supposed to be like a sexy librarian.
She's kind of coded like that.
And she's got a little hand implement.
And she asks, who is the naughtiest person here?
Yes.
Now, Gerdner and Carlson both immediately say, oh, Weiger is.
They point at me, which I'm like now scared.
Now, I think we both wanted to say Jason, but he wasn't there.
Jason wasn't there, yeah.
So just because the other male in the group was you,
I think that's why it fell on you to be the naughty one.
Because if it was Jason, there's just no way we wouldn't have said Jason.
It also kind of felt like, from my perspective,
like self-preservation on your part.
That's also part of it too.
Absolutely.
So you said it was a naughty one.
I said, I'm nice.
And then I got trapped because she was like, whoever says he's nice is actually the naughtiest one.
I was like, well, there's no way out of this.
So then Jason's nightmare, which has been detailed.
I had nauseam on this show talking about the Las Vegas story where he got too high in the German restaurant
and was afraid.
Hofbrau House.
And it was so afraid of getting paddled by the lady.
Yeah.
He, Weiger, took one on the butt.
Right.
With like a riding crop.
Riding crop.
Yes.
That looked, I saw the clip of the riding crop lady.
It looked much more gentle than the like two foot long paddle.
It was really gentle.
I mean, there was no real like, you know, no real impact felt.
Yes.
So, okay.
At this point, what happens now?
I have been a request.
Scott has requested that we give him a phone call and talk to him about the event that happens next.
He wants to tell it from his perspective.
Okay.
Hello, Scott.
Hey, hey.
You have me, Scott.
Hello, everybody.
Hi, Scott.
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, Wiggs.
Hey, Jason.
Hey, Mike.
What's going on?
Sorry.
I couldn't be there in person.
I'm also a tad under the weather and I didn't want to spread it to you guys.
Now, am I a tad under the weather because I drank from a shared liquor bottle that was handed to me by a gingerbread lady?
Possibly.
I don't know.
I have to do some kind of test on that.
Well, we're sorry to hear that.
But I hope you would, you know, even if you did get an illness from Santa's Secret, I hope you would do it all again next week
because of how much fun you had.
You know, I think I would.
And that's not to jump around too much.
And I don't know if you guys have kind of like reviewed the experience in mass.
But here a few days later in the harsh light of sobriety, am I crazy or like that was great, right?
I thought it was really fun.
I had a fun time.
I think it was a fun experience.
We've been kind of going chronologically.
So we're really just sequentially up to where, you know, we're still in the pre-show period.
OK, OK, sure.
Well, I didn't, you know, I wanted to give that overall thought and just ask if I was crazy or if I'm just like if my perspective is different
because I don't I haven't been getting out too much lately because I'm kind of just working and taking care of a baby.
Maybe I did I respond to it just because I it was nice to be out of the house.
Was it that or was it the magic of the North Pole?
I think it was a combination of factors.
I think it was that that it was above expectations in terms of, you know, the decor, in terms of the staging, in terms of the production value.
I think that was part of it.
I think the it had elements of you were actually seeing, you know, human mastery.
Like some of these the acts were like, oh, that's actually a genuinely impressive bit of dancing you're doing, you know.
Absolutely.
And and but I think there's there's also the just obviously the the ironic level and then just like the, you know, outright lewd level.
But I think we were having a good time.
We had a good group as well.
You saw a lot of people's nice stomachs.
A lot of nice stomachs.
Indeed.
And well, and I don't want to I don't want to say too much about a certain furry creature who stripped in unexpected ways.
I'll leave that to you guys.
But yeah, no, visuals like I can't erase and don't want to erase, frankly.
But I let me let me jump in.
So you guys already covered we've been going room to room at the North Pole and we've made it up through the the Weiger spanking.
That is correct.
Weiger has just been spanked by Santa's secretary in the chronological order of events.
Who keeps the naughty and nice list, of course.
He's in charge of the list.
So, you know, I watched this happen and I got a little bit jealous, like not necessarily of the spank itself, but because of the quality content that we got.
Here I am.
Here I am just sitting, taking a back seat and taking a video of Weiger's little butt getting spanked.
And meanwhile, my little butt, nothing is happening to nor Mike's.
And we're the host of the show.
Right.
So as soon as the spank has occurred, I'm like, oh, you know what, we should get one of us, too.
So so I turn to Santa's secretary, who has turned fully away from us at this point immediately.
And I go back and like, hey, actually, you know what I was I was thinking?
I actually I think my friend and I here have been a little bit naughty, too.
And she's like, huh?
And I immediately feel tension.
And I go, oh, well, I was just because, you know, because you spanked him because he was not interested.
I thought we maybe he and I could could also do like we've been.
And then I start dropping the naughty thing.
I'm just I just wanted to feel that we just film it like could we could we do it together?
Is that OK?
And it's the answer is it's not OK.
Like we I broke in that moment some fundamental unwritten rule of Santa's secret that I was not aware of at all.
It was so uncomfortable. Am I correct in that assessment?
I was uncomfortable as also but I will also say the whole thing was genuinely confusing.
And this extends to our interaction with the gingerbread lady.
Like we didn't know going into each of these interactions that they were.
There was one designated person who was going to have this experience.
Like no one told us in advance.
No, we figured out the pattern by the gingerbread lady, which I can get to maybe while you still got me here.
But the yeah, like there was nothing saying only one of you gets a little spank.
I thought everybody could get a little spank. So she agrees.
She doesn't want to say no, but it's a very like here.
It's fine. It's fine. Just do it because we got to move to the next.
Oh, sorry. And I even say, oh, we don't have to.
And she's like, no, no, no, let's just do it.
And so so then I'm handing the phone over.
But then like that's taking to even having to hand you the phone.
Weiger is too much business. Right.
I felt like, all right, it's already in progress. Let's just do it. Let's just do it.
So we film a video and it's Mike and I and we both turn around and we get our little butts spanked.
He he he. But the it was not worth going.
But it's not like that was any funnier than than why you're doing it.
It was probably less funny, honestly.
So just know that when we post to this extra content,
the the awkwardness that was set through while in order to get it like we read.
And the difference in the vibe from Weiger's little butt getting spanked to our little butts getting spanked.
Everything changed. Everything changed in that 30 seconds.
And I don't quite understand why it went from her being like, oh,
they were having a naughty little bit of naughty fun to like, all right, come on.
You know, let's get it over with.
Like, it was really strange.
I completely disassociated after 20 seconds of you talking to her.
And all I remember is just like, I want this to be over.
Whatever happens, I want it to be over.
It felt a little bit like, you know, not to say I've done a lot of like, oh,
trying to get a picture of the celebrity or getting an autograph.
But if you ever like if that if that interaction ever takes more than 10 seconds
and you like make make somebody sit around while a flash.
Oh, sorry, I went with the flash. Can I try one without?
Like, that's the most mortifying thing ever.
So it was it was the pressure of like you're with an A-list celebrity,
except the A-list celebrity was Santa's secretary.
It was the strangest vibe.
I felt so awkward about it still the next day.
And I texted our little thread about it.
And then Eva responded with, you coerced Santa's secretary into unpaid sex work.
This is an epic burn of me.
No, it did not help me feel any better about it.
And I wanted to be forthright and share that statement with the audience.
But I disagree with that assessment. That's not what I'm about.
That's not the kind of guy I am.
That is not what I intended to do.
It was all just accidental missing of the protocol of how Santa's secretary room worked.
It was it was so weird.
So I just had to like express that awkwardness myself rather than having it be told.
But what but should we go into?
I forget if it was right after.
But I'm holding in my hand the card that kind of redeemed things for me a little bit
because we were handed a card at the beginning and I was keeping it for the group.
I believe it was the next experience.
So here's the thing.
As I mentioned, we got the card.
They said, give this to the gingerbread lady for a little sugar.
Santa's secretary, there's no card involved.
You just go up there and everyone like one person in their party.
And I guess if you've got a two person party, one person gets their butt spanked.
If you've got a six person party, one person gets their butt spanked.
That's what it seems to be the rule is.
The thing I will say in your defense, Scott, before we get to the gingerbread lady is
I was shocked that she had not dealt with someone else asking before.
Like didn't you expect there to be either she's like, sorry, we can only do one.
That's just the rule.
Or either she has that set up or she's like has a little playful banter
because she's encountered this before where maybe there's like kind of a Randy party,
a bachelorette party where everyone wants to get their butt spanked.
You know what I mean?
Like I was just surprised that she seemed like completely like baffled by the request.
Could it have been?
Yes.
But maybe it was her first night as Santa's secretary.
I guess that's a possibility.
It could have been night one and maybe we could have been an early group.
Like maybe the Santa's secretary had to go.
Right.
And they got a new Santa's secretary.
So she was the understudy.
Well, so here's the other bit of awkwardness and that I not just you,
but I also felt in the aftermath was when we got to the stage show,
Santa's secretary is a singer in the show.
And so like when we had this interaction earlier, I was like, oh, well, she's like a dominatrix.
This is like her thing.
But now I'm like, wait, no, she's a singer.
And they say like, hey, also you have to spank people's butts as they come into the theater.
Yeah.
That was really strange.
I got mortified when I realized these were like talented performers.
We'd all had these little intimate moments with people who'd like display their talents on a stage later.
No, just just like skin crawling, all of it.
And yes, how like this is the first time this has ever come up.
And the biggest problem, maybe not the biggest problem,
but you would expect a problem to be like a guy getting a little too like, oh, hey, you know,
that's it's making my candy cane grow a little bit.
I would expect like a little comments like that.
Not that the biggest problem you encounter is ignoring invisible protocols.
I didn't see any signs about this.
I'm a good boy.
I would never have broken such a rule.
I just thought it'd be funny to have a little video.
That's the problem, though.
She noticed that you and I were too good.
That might have been it.
We weren't naughty enough.
Oh, she knew we belonged on the nice list.
Yes, yes.
The biggest sin was pretending that we are naughty
when we are so clearly visibly nice.
Right.
She would have been like, assume the Amazon position, Mr. Sheridan.
Prone bone at once.
Yeah, yeah.
It just didn't make sense to hit us.
There was no reason for it.
Should we move into to the gingerbread lady?
Yes.
So we're there.
And that that itself is kind of like an antechamber because we go into another room
where there's like a bunch of these experiences.
And I think the first I believe the first one was the gingerbread lady.
Yes.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, yeah.
And it was that beginning of the question of like, oh, is this one of the oh, this is one of the things.
And there's oh, wait.
So not every card is the gingerbread lady.
Like people have different cards for different things.
You don't get to talk to everybody.
So we're like figuring out this product, which it's kind of fun to like figure out a little system,
especially while little cocktails kicking in good cocktails that really like it onboarded me really fast.
So I was enjoying what I was drinking.
But then I didn't realize that, you know, well, first of all, I was given the job of keeping the card.
The card says, present this card to the gingerbread lady to get some sugar.
And and then I lost the card.
I was given one job.
First, I fucked up the situation with the secretary and then I didn't do my one single job.
So I'm feeling very humiliated by this point.
But then thankfully, the gingerbread lady was very nice.
She was willing to break little protocols and she let me still come and sit in her gingerbread throne.
I went behind a velvet rope.
It was all it was all big thing.
And I felt bad that it became me just by virtue of that.
I was the one who got the card.
I think everybody would have enjoyed this experience.
But but only I got it and I didn't deserve it after, you know, everything I'd done.
But so I sit in the in the gingerbread throne and then she puts the lolly a big lollipop in front between us and the guests.
So you guys can't see what I'm doing.
Yeah, maybe like implying like, oh, what's going on back there?
Is he getting a little smooch?
And I'm I'm feeling awkwardness back there because I'm like, what is this turning into?
It said get some sugar.
Is this going to am I supposed to kiss this woman?
I can't imagine it's that I like I'm not going to make the first move here.
Absolutely not.
But is but is is she going to is that part of her kiss?
I didn't try to kiss this woman after forcing Santa's secretary to pound your butt.
This would be my last episode of the show, Santa's Secret, the episode where Scott is canceled.
In reality, you were hidden by a big lolly and transported to a world beyond pleasure and pain.
I got to do it.
It's the move that Jason uses to get away with everything.
Just hide behind a big lolly.
But no, thankfully, all that was happening back there was she did get right in my face and I'm like, oh, what is this?
And then it and then it just becomes she is whispering to me, do you like it sweet or spicy?
And I took I took a swing and I said spicy.
And then she produces a bottle of fireball or some facsimile like a Jack Daniels, you know, spiced cinnamon spiced equivalent.
Now, this is a kind of alcohol that I typically despise, but I'm in the spirit.
I was I'm I'm all for it at this point.
I'm on the gingerbread throne.
Cannot wait.
And she pours it into my mouth.
Now, granted, with enough distance like that was that was a good pour.
It was a good couple inches and it landed perfectly in my mouth to where I don't think that's what made me sick.
But it did remind me of like accepting the chalice of wine and church where like there did feel like germ risks there.
Right.
So if you hear my slightly hoarse voice, I don't know, could have been from fireball.
Was it worth it?
I say yes.
This was a delightful.
I'm glad I said spicy.
And boy, did it all get me in the mood for for a hell of a show.
The fireball whiskey killed any surface germs on that bottle.
Had to have.
Yeah, that couldn't be.
It's it's whatever you got.
It's it was airborne.
That's what I think.
Do you have any sense of whether it was what what what the liquor would have been if you'd said sweet?
Yeah.
Do you see another bottle?
Oh, I don't know.
But you know what?
I'm glad I'm glad that I guessed because if we're talking the genre of like holiday liquor, like if it had been some peppermint thing, I think I would have been very unhappy.
I would have loved would have loved a quart of rum chata poured down Scott's throat.
Give me a story.
Scott had to go to the hospital.
He ingested a pint of rum chata.
Well, you know, we were right next to Cedar Sinai, so it would have been the place to do it.
Great facility.
Really world class.
Well, yes, they do great work over there.
I've done better than Santa's workshop.
Well, that's I mean, that's kind of the end of my experience.
And I won't make you guys be on speakerphone any longer.
I do.
And but I and I don't want to jump around too much, but I wanted to get just a few more just just quick hits in before I jump off.
And I'm sure you'll get to some of this or maybe already have.
But I wanted to say, I think this experience convinced me that the Beverly Center is the worst place in Los Angeles.
Okay, great.
You've covered this.
I mean, how do we not?
I mean, we might get we might get into it in more depth in a bit.
But I would just say, like, well, while you're here, maybe we can talk about our post-show odyssey of trying to get into Lucky Strike.
And how that involved exiting the Beverly Center and then reentering the Beverly Center, I think twice before we took our way all the way up to the was it the do we ever go up into the fourth floor and then go back to the lobby level?
Is that what their solution was? Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Yes.
I know.
And so this is like like this is us we're talking about.
We're all kind of mall aficionados, specifically mall parking garage aficionados.
This is the group.
Yes.
Let's crack this situation.
And yet we were all completely flummoxed.
Yeah, like because the show gets out and we're still feeling a little charged up from it.
What do we do?
Let's go like let's go play arcade games or something.
Because we are on the way in.
We saw the ground floor, like most featured on Los Cienega arcade facility.
Like so we all knew it was there.
So let's let's let's jump over there.
Let's have some fun.
Let's go outside the Beverly Center onto the street to the corner where we all saw it and know it existed.
And then there's no door.
There was no door to the place that's facing the street.
This is the most pedestrian unfriendly thing I've ever seen.
Here's how much the Beverly Center sucks.
Eva was like, oh, is the P.F. Chang's still there?
We should go check out the P.F. Chang's.
And we went over to where the P.F. Chang's was and it was now an escalator.
Yeah, bizarre.
And then like we by the way, I checked the website of like what what they say about how you get there.
And it does kind of confirm that like there isn't an entrance from the street.
There's one from deeper into the parking garage and like the valet.
But we sure didn't see that.
I'm also seeing that I believe that Lucky Strike is officially open today as we're recording this.
That is a brand new thing.
Oh, wow.
Which didn't really read to me.
I'm getting this news right now for the first time.
And but didn't it like I felt it felt to me like kind of a rundown.
I was like we're walking around like this old place ain't doing so hot.
It's new. It's new today.
Yeah, it had already had the feel of an off strip casino.
Oh, very much so.
The sad little like fake food truck that you got to order for nothing better than a fake indoor food truck.
What's more fun than that?
I really dislike a place where it's like, hey, this is you're going to go you're going to go sit down.
It's like it's got like the the the aesthetics of a sit down restaurant.
But there's like a counter where you put your whole order in.
Like it's just like like like for certain for certain concepts, that's fine for like a pizza concept or something like that's fine.
But for this sort of place or it's like I want to just hang out at a booth or sit in the sit at the at a lane and be ordering food from a server.
Yeah, they got a lot of problems to work out already.
I think for that spot a lot, including the bizarre because we couldn't get inside.
So we were stuck on the outside.
So we're staring at these like 1920s movie posters that are all the most A.I.
made garbage like where they're just missing letters and it's all fake movies and fake movie stars.
Just like absolute horse shit.
Because is that what Lucky Strike is going for?
They're trying to do like a flapper sort of thing.
They're trying to do like like a Gatsby sort of vibe.
I think that's for Hollywood.
I bet that's exclusive to Hollywood.
OK, so there is that because that all the posters.
Yeah, they were like they were like fake, like, you know, you know, 1930s gangster and Hollywood sort of movies.
And yeah, but I was just like, why is this not, you know, like a bowling lane or something?
Like, why is this nothing that evokes bowling?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I just I completely did not understand what that was doing there.
But yeah, they also just look so bad.
And they look like shit.
Like they had one guy and they weren't really paying attention to what he was doing.
So we just did all everything through chat GBT.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
We probably didn't tell them they weren't paying attention.
Like, oh, yeah, no, I can do that in a couple of days.
No problem. Just straight to A.I.
I'm easy as check.
He ever got. Yeah.
No garbage.
And then it put us in a bad mood.
Like we we eventually made our way in just to say that we did just to like feel pride as adults that we cracked the code.
But the whole experience is so frustrating that we ended up giving them zero dollars because like it was just so confounding.
And we were so mad about the posters and the lack of street access.
Just a very strange experience.
There's one more little negative thing that I will say on the way out the door.
And mostly I would say positive things.
And I'm curious what you guys will say when I listen to this back later.
One downside, though, those mini beef Wellingtons didn't do it for me.
Those were kind of gut bombs.
Like I felt a little shitty the next day and I could like I like honed in on that.
Like error error found like that was the thing the thing in my stomach that pushed it over to not the best night.
So I don't know if anybody sees this.
Avoid those.
I'll take the L for advocating for the mini beef Wellingtons.
But also I knew what I was doing because I was like everything else that we've ordered is something like spinach artichoke dip or like a pretzel twist.
This is all conventional stuff.
We got to get one of the weird things that they have there.
And the options were either the mini beef Wellington or the ninety five dollar Ocetra caviar service as Jesus.
Yeah. So it's like let's not get the caviar.
Let's get the let's get the beef Wellingtons.
They did suck. They were awful. They made me feel like shit.
Did they to you, too? Am I not alone in that?
I didn't like the taste of them, but I was fine the next day.
I mean, that's why you and I punish our stomachs more regularly than you do, though.
So you probably just couldn't handle it.
And Jason would Jason, I think, would have not only survived them, but like saved them for later and said they were better four days from now.
Well, sure. I would have just gotten a doggy bag and wheeled over to Cedars and I would have been all door dashing in order of mini beef Wellington.
Put it in a blender and put it in the IV bags and just drip it right into your veins.
Well, thank you for letting me get those thoughts out.
The food wasn't particularly good. The food was not as good as the jokes, I would say.
No, no, no, no. And I'm excited. I hope that this episode takes a positive turn.
I hope that the correct praise is given to various aspects of this, or at least that you were like you enjoyed being flummoxed by it as I was.
I have been unable to even though I liked it, I've been unable to produce one fact about this that made my wife, Erin, understand why I liked it.
I've not like there hasn't been one thing I've said where she went, oh, that sounds fun.
And yet somehow I did still I did still enjoy it.
So curious what you guys think. Excited to listen back later and I'll jump off.
But I will also say I'll see everybody soon.
And Mike and Jason, you guys get your little butts ready because I'm going through my naughty list on that Club 3 episode.
So get in get in get in prone bone position because whip whip boys.
Well, while we're on that topic, Scott, I mean, I did want to talk about the Amex trifecta, which I think we didn't really get into on the club.
Oh, what's that? I think you guys are you guys are coming out.
I'm not hearing you so good. All right.
I was too bad. Reception is ruining this whole thing. It's all been going great.
All right. I will have fun, everybody.
Merry Christmas. I'll talk to you soon. Bye, Scott.
Feel better, buddy. All right.
All right. Thanks. See you.
So after the gingerbread lady, there's just like a few different characters.
I think we probably speed through this because we didn't have a ticket for any of the rest of them.
And we didn't realize that these were all like ticketed experiences.
So there was there was a toy soldier, hunk toy soldier or no, the nutcracker.
It was the nutcracker specifically, hunk nutcracker, a hunk nutcracker.
There was a there was a oh, she was she was the snow angel.
She was supposed to be like a sexy Christmas topper, right? Yes.
Christmas tree topper. There was her.
Christmas topper is another thing that Jason talks about.
Well, yes, she was supposed to be like, yeah, the thing, the nice angel you see at the top of the tree.
And, you know, very like the wardrobe was all really good.
I mean, that's the thing you get to get with an L.A. sort of production is like, oh, there's really talented like,
you know, costumers in this town who just like, oh, yeah, I'll take a job at Santa's Secret.
And so all that stuff looked great. Then then there was the ice queen, right?
That's who the ice queen ended up being the emcee of the show, who is a drag queen.
Yes. And again, all these experiences were like you had to have a ticket to go up
to do whatever the equivalent of the fireball whiskey shot was with them.
Right. The one thing I will say is I wish someone had told us going in like, hey, you only get one of these.
And I also kind of wish even if we didn't know exactly what we're getting, we got to choose.
Yes, I agree. If they were like, hey, do you want the gingerbread lady? Do you want the nutcracker?
Well, what's what is each experience like? Well, I can't tell you.
It's like, OK. I mean, like you at least feel like you had some like choice in what you were what you're receiving.
Yes, I agree. It was just kind of granted to us.
Oh, and then there was also the photo op with the hunky Santa where we get to sit on Santa's lap.
So, yes, there's this there's a big kind of a big ish room.
It's a pretty big room where there's a hunky guy.
He's got just like little Santa shorts on Santa hat boots and then like fluffy cuffs.
Yeah, no beer. Yeah, no beer.
But like, you know, beard like mine. Yeah, I'm not trying to say I'm like this hunky guy.
I'm just saying beard similar to mine. Yeah.
Probably 10 years younger than me. Let's be honest.
And then next to him, there's a sign that says come salivate on me.
That looks like a Salvation Army sign. Yeah, that's fun.
And it says doing the most good and then good is crossed out.
OK, so now we're real. Now we're really in naughty territory. Yes.
Here. So at this point, I wasn't sure what we were supposed to do.
But then they even I gave my phone to the person to take a photo.
Eva ended up getting a solo photo with Donkey Santa,
which is great because she like has like a like she looks sad in the photo.
She looks upset. So she looks like a sad woman who went to this experience by herself.
She's staring nowhere with kind of a neutral face. Yeah.
But then sorry, just real quick, can you go back?
Can I get a spelling on that? Come salivate me. Is it a question?
C.O.M.E. You wanted to see you missed opportunity.
But isn't that a hat on a hat at that point?
I guess this salivate is already unusual. Maybe it's gilding the lily.
So then here here is everyone sitting on this like 30 year old hunky Santa's lap on his big throne.
We did get a photo with all four of us with hunky Santa.
Unfortunately, his physique is covered up because we're all like, you know, crowding him.
Weiger and I both said this independently of each other.
We're like, but now you can't see how jacked Santa is.
I wish we were seeing more hunky Santa.
But I will say hunky Santa is an experience the Beverly Center has had or used to have back in the day.
And I'm not sure if Santa's Secret is like kind of like the, you know, the successor to that.
If they were kind of like, oh, well, we had hunky Santa.
I guess Santa's Secret is a natural fit for it.
But there is precedent for Santa for a hunky Santa there.
Was he shirtless? Have you ever?
Yeah, it was like it was like a it was like a it was like for mom and dad.
There was a hunky Santa and then there was a conventional Santa for the kids.
Well, was it they were not next to each other?
No, they were in their separate parts of the mall.
And I think it was even it was maybe even separate times.
Yeah. But yeah, so like the that's a thing they had like a decade plus ago.
And the one thing I will say is that this this this actor, I said, I said, you're looking very hunky Santa.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He had a canned line for me, which I liked, which is like, thanks, but laying off the cookies.
And he kind of patted his abs. Solid.
It's pretty good. Really good.
You know, he said that 30 times.
It was a good line. You should use it. Yeah.
You ever use stuff? I'll text the same joke to three different text chains on my phone once in a while.
Yeah, of course.
So at that point, I'm really looking around for like little like little horny stuff.
And then again, I don't know if I just I'm seeing things where they don't belong.
But then there's this like picture or excuse me, this statue of Santa and one of his reindeer that looks kind of vaguely sexual to me.
I think they were starting to even if they weren't like already sexy, you know, statues or animatronics, they were like they reached a certain point.
They were like, we can kind of pose these in a lecherous sort of way.
Yeah, it's definitely a come hither look. You sent me that photo with no contacts.
Yeah. Well, you knew where we were. I knew where you were.
So it's not like out of nowhere.
You're like, why is this statue of Santa and Rudolph looking at each other longing?
Yeah. Oh, wait, I'm really we missed one thing.
This is one of the few times that I was scandalized, which is speaking of Rudolph.
Yeah, there was a Rudolph performer, a woman with a with a red nose, but she also had like lines of cocaine.
Yes. And she was like, kind of like, oh, but that's why my nose is red or whatever.
Right. And I was like, I think that's like too far.
I think Rudolph should be doing cocaine. And also, this is like a horny like body thing.
I don't think we need to bring hard drugs into it. Yeah.
But it wouldn't be the last hard drug reference of the night. That's true.
Because the hard drugs was a theme of the whole show.
Yeah, I would have thought it would have been I would have thought a bit more like I mean, I guess people have sex on cocaine, but it would be more like ecstasy.
Yeah, sure. Rudolph was on ecstasy and he wants you to pet him.
He just wants you to put your hand through his fur.
Like that would have made more sense to me versus cocaine.
But I guess cocaine is just an easier reference for, I don't know, everybody to understand what it is.
Or they just had it.
What's funny about all what's funny about all of these interactions is, you know, we've done some of that horror.
We've done horror nights. We've done delusions, stuff like that, where performers are fully in character.
Everyone here felt like they were half out of character.
A lot of them were not full committed at all.
So when you would like look them in the eye and they would deliver their line about, I'm Rudolph and I'm doing cocaine, you would see a performer inside going, help me, help me.
I don't want to just move along, please.
Like I feel like everyone's eyes was just like, please move along.
I want to do my like talent in the show.
Yeah, when you get when we later got that, like, oh, these are all the performers who are in the burlesque review, then it was like, oh, I think this was like an ad like an added thing that none of them were super into.
Yeah, yes.
They're all like, oh, I have to do this pre show meet and greet with basically like I'm a dancer.
This isn't my thing is in my comfort level.
Right. So like I felt like not that I'm not that I'm always wanting to talk to somebody in character, not that that's the number one thing I like, but it definitely felt like, OK, you we made eye contact.
Keep moving.
Keep going to the next person.
Yeah.
But everyone was good.
Everyone did their job.
I just they weren't 100 percent.
They weren't committed.
Maybe the gingerbread lady.
I felt it was the most gingerbread lady was pretty locked in.
It felt like the snow angel was kind of like, you know, maybe just by via presence.
She had a presence for sure.
Yeah. But the nutcracker who had a great act in the show.
But the nutcracker, I think I was I think I was like, oh, what's you know, like I just tried to send something Christmassy to him is like, oh, what's what's the occasion or whatever?
And I think he just said, I'm the nutcracker.
It's a ring toss game.
Yeah. So so that lasted what?
I felt like 10 minutes.
Yeah, it was pretty substantial.
There's a lot of there's a pretty lengthy walkthrough, a lot to look at.
Yeah. So so that in and of itself, I was like, oh, that's pretty good.
The production value is pretty high for this.
And I was trying to I was also like, is there another like did they repurpose this during the day for something like I just it felt right.
It felt I didn't expect it, I guess.
So but I think it's all just for that.
And they I'm assuming they just bought off the shelf all these different like little elf like robots and statues.
Yeah, I assume so.
Yeah, because they were cute.
They weren't that scary.
So so that part was really it was really fun and unexpected.
I really like the pre show.
So we go in, we go through this whole thing, and then we go into a nightclub that's been set up and we're ushered to our table.
And the next hour basically of the night is like a an 80s cover band.
Like it's like it's like a good it's like a good like they're good studio musicians and a good singer.
But like we're basically just just watching them, you know, sing like, oh, I want to dance with somebody or, you know, yes.
Basically, like, you know, the show, I don't remember at this point, but like so the show over the show was at six then the ticket.
Right.
But from six, I believe, to seven is people fill into the actual room.
There's just an hour of covers, not Christmas songs.
No, no Christmas music at all.
Okay.
Just covers.
And again, the singer fantastic.
The band sounded great.
But yes, not a Christmas song to be found.
No, they're doing Michael Jackson's Pretty Young Thing.
Yes.
And people are loving it.
I will say like the crowd was was really into it.
Yeah. So they sounded good.
So that was fine.
It just it was a little because I guess maybe you don't want to step on the toes of the Christmas music in the next hour.
I suppose so much Christmas.
Yeah, it's true thing.
It's like it's like, yeah, I know they were using and they also weren't just using Christmas songs for the acts.
A lot of them had different songs, too.
So I wonder about because I would like to be more Christmasy.
Maybe even just like one out of every three songs is like, you know, the company that puts this on is called Voss Events.
OK, which sounds like the evil corporation from the show, The Boys.
But this company puts on just a lot of like drag show, RuPaul's Drag Race Live or whatever.
I wonder if this band isn't from another part, another show.
And they're just like, you don't have to learn.
Just this is for warm up.
Just do your standard set, whatever.
Just get the energy up.
Yeah, I wonder if that's something from another part of the touring thing.
Yeah, that would totally apparatus.
That would totally it totally makes sense.
By the way, speaking of Drag Race, I looked up the the emcee, the drag queen afterwards, who was on RuPaul's Drag Race, a very, very well known drag queen, Lawrence Cheney.
Yeah.
And then, yes, RuPaul's Drag Race Live, I guess that's they were on the live tour.
There's many different credits on this Instagram, but was very good, very good host.
Yeah, they're good.
So, yeah.
So I guess about eight o'clock is when or no, seven o'clock is when the actual show.
Right.
Started the part of Santa's Secret.
And again, we're talking amongst ourselves.
Are we going to learn Santa's Secret?
Like that was a big thing.
This is the thing we've been anticipating the whole time.
Are we going to learn Santa's Secret?
By this point, I've made peace with like we're not going to learn Santa's Secret or Santa's Secret is just like an abstract concept.
This is haunting you.
We're just thinking about it.
Well, because also we've been talking about this for a year.
Like, what is Santa's Secret that he can't tell Mrs. Claus?
Yes.
And during the year, they've changed it.
It was like, oh, what's St. Patrick's Secret?
They did.
Yeah, they had Uncle Sam's Secret.
Another seasonal one.
Well, that's just a handful of coup d'etat.
You know, it's not even that interesting.
Yeah, yeah, we all know.
So, yeah, we're kind of we're chatting it up.
I forget.
Eva said, I think her husband made some joke that felt like Santa's Secret is that it was like a standby me thing or like they saw a guy get killed.
Santa saw a guy get killed and he has to keep quiet about it.
I was like, oh, yeah, I guess that could be it.
But yeah, we really to lower our expectations said, I don't think it's going to be a real secret.
It's just going to be a show or whatever.
And then the emcee Lawrence Cheney, right?
Correct. Yes.
Gets out there and in character as the it's the ice queen, right?
I mean, it was ice.
Yes.
In character is the ice queen.
And I think one of the first bits of copy, they say, is tonight you will learn Santa's secret.
And we go nuts.
We just go fucking crazy.
Like you're going to learn the meaning of life tonight.
Yeah, I was thrilled.
But but here's the thing.
Santa's secret is not a secret.
It's a series of secret series of secrets that are unveiled one by one.
Yes.
So that yes, this is like all of all of the skeletons in Santa's closet, all of his dirty laundry.
So now we are going to learn the secret and there are many secrets to learn.
Yes. So imagine our delight to hear this.
And I don't think the secrets disappointed, quite frankly.
They don't.
But I will say that there was a little bit of narrative confusion and it could have used some structure and clarity because.
So just to skip ahead a little point a little bit, there was another table that was next to us.
And I think like us, the woman there was tracking the secrets.
So a few secrets are dispelled at a certain point.
The the emcee says, now time for Santa's secret number four.
And the woman turns to us confused, like four, because I think at this point we'd only learned like one or two secrets or or like what was clearly a Santa secret.
But I guess some other bit of information that was dispensed to us was in fact a secret.
Yes. Just another podcaster, just Jamie Loftus at the other table like, hey, can we compare notes?
I think I missed something.
Weiger, you haven't worked as a television writer in a few years at this point.
But is this sort of you kind of informally saying you would kind of go back to the job if you could be showrunner of Santa's secret next year?
I would love, look, I would love to just just make a few tweaks.
I think it was as simple as up top they're like, you're going to learn Santa's secrets.
Each act will tell you a new secret about Santa.
You know, like then it'd be like, oh, OK, because it took me a minute to lock into that even that each of these acts was was like, hey, this is what was the was the emcee's act first.
Was it the first one that was up?
Yes, I believe so.
So the ice queen is like the Santa's first secret is that Mrs. Claus had an affair.
Mrs. Claus is not Santa's first wife.
Yeah, Mrs. Claus is not Santa's first wife.
It was me, right?
Yes. Yes.
That's what it was. Yeah.
Right. And then they made Santa divorce a drag queen, basically.
Right.
So so we're going through a few different like it's it's pretty complicated.
But basically, like she would like like the like the the drag queen was Santa's original wife.
That was it was an untoward marriage.
The North Pole, you know, power brokers would not allow it.
And then they also had an affair with Frosty.
But was that I don't think that was the reason for the divorce.
That was just another thing.
And then that led to Frosty being melted.
And there was a gag holding up a plastic bag of water that said Frosty on it.
Yeah.
But then that led into an act where the ice queen was it was a was there was there a frosty?
Because I know a carrot got involved.
It was a frosty, right? A frosty getting melted.
Yeah, I think later during the musical numbers, what is your remembering?
Yes, because they were like jerking the carrot off.
They were jerking the carrot off, which was fun.
Yeah.
You were like just basically like slow down.
There was too much.
Let's make a meal out of all of this.
OK.
You know, that's why you got to have a good producer, good director, good stage manager.
And you got to review like, you know, we have everything we need, but does this make sense?
Should we start cutting?
Should we start simplifying?
Simplify 100 percent.
I think that would have gone a long way.
Anyway, that did lead to the thing that made me like laugh so hard, which was I mean,
I mean, the ice queen was was a was a very funny performer, but but was it reached a certain height
into a certain point where they were jacking off like the carrot, like it was, you know,
like a dick and fighting the carrot.
And then the music, which I don't remember what track it was.
Oh, that's a good question. I don't.
It might have been like it might have just been like Frosty the Snowman or whatever,
but like Frosty the Snowman had a and then it cuts out.
Oh, yes. Yeah.
And played Hawk Tuah.
Just went Hawk Tuah, the actual audio clip from the viral video.
I just feel like the house would go nuts.
People loved it.
It was that is legit.
Like, you know, some of this stuff you can enjoy kind of ironically.
I'll say there's no irony in that.
I was laughing so hard.
Really, really funny.
And really well timed.
Almost one of the maybe the funniest things of the whole show.
It was great.
And then, yeah, and then that also led into a grape fruiting thing that using using that
that video audio.
And then it heightened to the carrot tip exploding with a load of bubbles over.
Yeah.
So the carrot tip came, Jason.
OK. Yeah.
Are you guys getting to I don't want to spoil anything.
I saw a shot of a giant champagne glass.
Yeah, there was something like that.
Well, here's the thing.
So some of those I think some of those those elements were not as forward in the L.A.
show. OK.
Yeah, because I I feel like you would have jumped at this because watching this clip,
I had to rewind it.
I'm like, I can't be seeing that right because there was a giant champagne glass that someone
was splashing around in and the white cloudy liquid they were splashing in.
And I'm like, look, I don't want to just talk about cum just because why?
Right. Right. Right.
But it's because the I was like trying to figure out like what besides rum,
Chata, would you imagine?
I guess eggnog.
Eggnog looks like cum.
It's definitely meant to be like a double on top.
Yeah.
Yeah. Or I guess melted frosty could be a little cloudy.
Oh, his melted frosty.
The snowman.
I don't really I don't think they had the what you're talking about.
I don't think they had someone in a big glass full of eggnog rolling rolling around.
I don't think I guess I guess not.
I feel like we I unfortunately it's since closed.
But Pennsylvania in the Poconos there was like I don't even know what you would call it.
A love, an American love hotel, like a romantic retreat for couples.
And there was a hot tub in a giant champagne glass.
Really?
Two stories sweet.
And you would get in upstairs and the stock would go to the bottom on the floor.
And there are a lot of photos from the 1980s of like loving couples sharing champagne in the giant champagne flute hot tub.
But with regular water, not with with regular water and maybe some soap bubbles.
And it's closed now closed like it's been condemned six months ago, a year ago.
Like because everyone's like, oh, maybe it'll get redone.
It's like what hotel group is going to redo the fuck hotel with the giant champagne glass tub?
If this all goes to shit ever, you could go back and reopen it and just manage that hotel for the rest of your life.
Oh, sure.
It's like a spin off sitcom.
Like if Niles and Daphne moved and opened a bed of breakfast or something.
Well, like Newark.
Yeah, like Newark had the inn, yeah.
Yeah, you could do that.
I think you'd thrive there.
You could just have to polish the big glass after a couple left every day.
Well, I get a power wash every day.
Okay.
Wear a Bess with no shirt and a local sailor cap.
Oh, that's the worst outfit for the Poconos.
Jesus, it's so snowy.
Yeah, so yes, you're right.
They were hitting you with a lot of things, sometimes contradictory as far as maybe logic is concerned.
So I don't remember what the gingerbread lady's secret was.
That was the thing.
But gingerbread lady was next, right?
I can't remember what the order was.
Scott was nice and wrote down a lot of the revelations.
Oh yeah, we had a text thread where Scott and Eva were chronicling the Santa secret sometimes in all caps.
You have some handwritten notes in a field notes that I'm assuming you're throwing at a dumpster so you don't get pulled over with these in your car.
Yeah, I'm burning this afterwards.
Just to rest it on principle.
There's just random things though, like Scott wrote down.
There's a man who can handle a big sack.
And then he wrote Ice Queen and then he wrote Santa doesn't allow sex at the North Pole.
And then he wrote not a secret.
So that was not an official secret.
That's just a piece of lore.
Yeah.
That was the other bit of confusion.
A Christmas angel sucked too many dicks and Santa threw her on top of the tree.
Yeah, so that was the snow angels one, right?
And yeah, I don't remember how we got into the gingerbread lady.
I do remember I was wrong about this, but I thought I knew what was coming.
Yes, you leaned over.
So the two performers dressed up as like in gingerbread band mascot suits come out
and the gingerbread lady comes out in between them.
And the song that's playing is Lollipop, right?
Lollipop, lollipop, lool.
And I leaned over across and I was like, this is going to turn from lollipop into 50 cents candy shop.
I was so confident that they were going to do that and it was going to get horny.
It's the cockiest and most confident I've ever seen it.
I thought I nailed it.
I was not right.
He leaned back, he put his hands behind his head.
He put his feet up on the table.
Watch, Junior, he said to me.
Not what happened.
But then the gingerbread lady did do a little.
But that's why you should show run Santa's Secret.
Yeah, I think people would like that.
Because that would have been good.
People would have popped for that.
I thought you were right too.
You said it was such confidence and it makes too much sense.
I go, he's right.
It's going to be candy shop by 50 cent.
But yeah, I don't even remember what the song was.
It was not particularly notable.
Yeah, I don't remember either.
But yeah, I mean, if Jason was show running, he would have been like a good ship.
Let's do good ship lollipop next.
You know, I think Wiger and I might have to go in on like directing together.
Because he can be the more creative director and I can be the producer.
Like, well, I don't know if the budget will allow or like, is there another way to do this?
Like, could we move the chairs around to use that or something?
Oh, you want to make sure you will be the cost cutter?
Well, no, I don't want to be the bad guy.
I just we both done a lot of stage sketch comedy.
Right. Yeah.
And so I think we we and it's always good to have a second set of eyes.
Yeah, we have the reps to figure out how to make it work.
Yeah, right.
Just you would want the lollipops to be bigger every time.
He would just get candy should be bigger.
Guys, let's not skimp on this.
This isn't reading like eggnog.
Make it more opaque.
Jason, that lollipop was pretty big when we gave it to you.
You took it backstage.
Look, I go, I don't know.
I mean, I don't I was trying to find out if we could find out who writes this.
But we I could not.
Yeah, it was hard to figure out like how credits weren't there.
Yeah, I think it could have used a little bit.
You know what? It's kind of like.
It's like Medieval Times or Pirates Dinner Adventure where you want there to be like just enough where you can track what's going on.
You know who you're waiting for.
And this I thought was just a little convoluted.
Gingerbread Lady.
There was the Snow Queen had had.
I mean, a lot of these were just like like the same sort of acts.
It was like pole dancing or trapeze, you know, something that Ariel stuff that's very impressive.
But it's it's also stuff that I think as Scott was saying, it was it was kind of not even all that sexual.
You know, it's like it's not like we were like watching you.
You know, I mean, it's like well, you would get you would get like fake out like removal of clothing generally.
Somebody would remove like the top part of their clothes to reveal a slightly smaller shirt.
Yeah.
And then they would go do a wire act.
And again, you could see their stomach.
Obviously, they're very good shape, but it wasn't something that was so dirty.
There were a couple of things like a man in the chair later and a woman comes up and suggestively dances.
But it wasn't it wasn't horny.
You're like in a different context.
This is just this isn't a circus.
But this but this audience of boomers was still getting horny as shit like they were like losing these boomers.
They're T levels.
If you were to like take the reading before and after, it would have been a 50 point jump.
They were all just chugging eugenics beforehand.
Well, yeah, they're using those like Rudolph Riddos to wash down a tattifil or a sedentifil.
There was a guy there was a guy and I assume his wife or girlfriend and they were in full pajamas.
They were wearing pajamas. Yeah.
Christmas pajamas.
I clocked them while the show was happening, going nuts, putting their arms in the air.
And then we saw them leaving.
Yeah.
And you just I think to them, you go, hey, great show.
And the guy was like, great show.
Well, they're having a good time.
Yeah, they were having a great time.
And yeah, they were what?
Ten years older than us.
Fifteen.
I don't know.
Yeah, I mean, it's certainly certainly a slightly older demographic.
Everything I do in Los Angeles, I'm still one of the youngest people.
One hundred percent.
Me too. Yeah, for sure.
That's more about what I'm doing than it is about the demographics in Los Angeles.
It sounds like when I'm sure I told them before, but when I went to go see Sideways when it came out alone
and I was the youngest person there by like 20 years.
And then I made the mistake of like, I'll have a healthy snack.
And I brought an apple and I took a bite during the trailers and it was like a gunshot.
And I went, oh, no, I cannot finish this apple.
What was I thinking?
So all the 45 year olds turned around and looked at you.
I feel like I got some looks, but I also was like, maybe there's an action movie trailer.
I can like crunch during this apple a little.
That's why I've done the movie theater apple.
Yeah, you just have to wait till the sound design really kicks into the score.
When was the last time both of you had an apple in a movie theater?
Honestly, pretty recently.
Really?
Yeah, pretty recently.
Here's the thing.
We go to the movies once a week pretty much, but it's kind of like a regular thing.
And if I bring an apple, I won't get nachos.
But I'll still get a big soda, but I won't be getting the empty calories of like a big tray of corn chips and cheese.
It's not every time. It's not a universal thing.
And honestly, a bar or something is safer, something a little less crunchy.
Okay, so you want all of it, but with whatever fruit you have in the house.
Yeah, I'll toss a banana in the bag. Why not?
Okay. Jason, when was the last time you ate an apple in a theater? Was it sideways?
That was the last time I ever took one off.
But I went with a friend once and we got like Pan Express or some sort of Chinese food.
And I was like eating really fast. I'm like, oh, we got to get to the movies.
And she just, she's like, I know.
And she took the takeout container and just shoved it sideways, shoved it in her purse like upside.
And I went, geez, that's going to leak.
And she like ate a full like two entrees and noodles like during a movie.
I love that.
How long ago was that?
I was when I was in high school.
Okay.
Although we...
I went to...
We went, I remember Bundress went to see Bridesmaids when it came out.
We sat down and Anthony Gio went, well, time for my movie sandwich.
And he pulled out a full subway football.
Really?
Yeah.
He's like, oh, I always get a big sandwich when I go to the movies.
Oh my God.
I don't even remember that.
We got to ask him about that next time he's on the show.
I cannot.
It probably lives one of the clearest images I have in my mind.
I'm going to text him while we're doing this.
I went to see a movie with a friend of ours and she was like, we go to Chipotle before the movie.
And we sneak in burritos and go see the movie.
And I go, oh, okay.
And I did it.
And I've never felt more wrong doing that.
I felt like I was smuggling in like contraband or something.
And then just the smell of a burrito in the theater.
I was like, no, I'm never doing this again.
I think burritos in LA is pretty common.
Yeah.
I think it was the Arclight.
I was like, ah, this is...
Remember that Chipotle, right?
There's a Chipotle right by there.
It did have me thinking we absolutely could have snuck food into this.
I think we wouldn't have had any problems with it.
Yeah.
We should have snuck apples in because of how loud it was.
No problem.
Was there a menu of finger food?
Yeah.
That's what we ended up with.
Sorry.
Fingering food.
All right.
You do need Jason on this team if you're going to show run.
I like it.
Yeah.
I think they could have had some double entendres in the menu.
But there weren't.
But yeah, that's how we got the mini beef Wellingtons or whatever.
That's where that was from.
Wait, that wasn't from the bowling alley?
No, the mini beef Wellingtons, sorry, were from Santa's Secret.
From Santa's Secret, yeah.
Oh, guys.
Guys.
Even I have my limits.
I thought it was just like, oh, no, it's upscale bowling alley, blah, blah, blah.
No, you would have had the beef.
You would have ordered the beef Wellingtons.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, your hat would have flown off when you saw the price.
But other than that, you would have had the beef Wellington.
Well, that's true.
But that's a weird one to fuck up because it's just dough and beef.
You'd think it would be pretty straightforward or something they could prep in microwave.
But yeah, it was not a good excuse.
Yeah, but also in a converted mall food court, you might be running into trouble.
Right.
I texted Gio, did you eat a big sandwich when we saw bridesmaids?
And then I just wrote Jason's memory.
And then he said, hmm, I might have.
Mostly true.
I think Snopes would give that.
Yeah, yeah, so pretty good.
I swear.
I mean, I feel like he was practically doing like the fingies, like the don't mind if I do kind of fingers.
Like Dagwood sizing up a sandwich.
Yeah, because we we weren't by a subway.
So we had to prepare.
Are you not maybe did you do this and you're putting this memory into another friend of yours?
No, because when I would go to the Arclight, I would always get one of their chicken sausages.
Gio thinks you're right.
OK, he says, lol, I think he's right.
So your memory is Kurt was probably correct.
Yeah, no, and never again with a burrito in movies.
Yeah, you just got to be conscious of the smell in any sort of confined space.
Yeah.
So let's see, we had Gingerbread Lady, the Snow Angel we talked about the.
Oh, so here's one one other note I would say.
As this is going, it's kind of what we're hearing is Santa is a piece of shit, right?
Yes.
Like it's like kind of like like all these secrets are like Santa is did something not just like naughty, but Santa did something like bad.
Like Santa like exiled somebody for, you know, like like like like a four hadn't.
Oh, yeah, that's the Santa's secretary who had her who had the act where she sung.
The thing was that that Santa's wife had an affair with Santa's secretary.
Right.
And then Santa's secretary got punished somehow, maybe having this job as her punishment.
Yes.
So it's like like all you're hearing is what a piece of shit Santa is.
But then when he comes out at the end, it's just like, hey, it's Santa.
You know, I mean, I was like, I think we need a moment of.
Just this guy getting his comeuppance or.
His comeuppance.
Yeah, there you go.
All right, you're on the team.
I think I think we need a moment of that, or we need to just like skate, like make the secrets be body, but not like like like sins.
You know what I mean?
Did you want to see Santa punished for his crimes?
I mean, that's the thing.
If that led to some sort of S&M thing, you know what I mean?
Like he was kind of being led around.
All the characters take a turn.
They'll take a turn, give him a little paddle.
And then he's like, I guess I learned my lesson.
I can be on the naughty list, too, or something like that.
That might have been like a little bit of.
Right.
Somebody takes his somebody's paddles his balls.
Somebody paddles his butt.
Yeah.
Someone puts a nipple clamp.
A cut cage on his balls and dick.
What was the phrase? Cut cage?
Cut cage.
Oh, cut cage.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
I got it. I understand.
With context clues.
Jason, you know what that is?
Sure.
Not my thing.
We've started saying it's not my thing, but I know about it.
Yeah.
So so they have this.
Oh, OK.
So so oh, and this is the other thing.
So sometimes there were double entendres.
Sometimes there were things like like like like, oh, you know,
he he actually there was a different sort of cookie jar Santa
liked reaching in.
But like when they talked about this is another thing that really made me laugh.
They said, you know, actually, Mrs.
Claus had an affair with Santa's secretary.
It was like, oh, what the fuck?
And the drag queen goes, that's right.
She was licking snatch.
There's no attempt at a Christmas pun or anything.
Did you say snatch?
Licking snatch.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
I wrote here.
I'm looking at my texts with Lindsay and I wrote I was giving her some updates
and I wrote Mrs.
Claus was licking snatch with Santa's secretary.
And then I wrote under Wiger is dying laughing.
Is that specifically I felt like you sort of convulsing.
Yeah, I loved it.
Just that there's a point where like the lack of any sort of effort
and being clever is makes it extra fun.
I can appreciate that, though, too, because like you can only get so much
like a cookie jar, like whatever.
So much of that.
Sometimes when they do saying something filthy, you're like, well, it's good.
It's pretty good.
It was good.
I was I was I was consistently entertained by that.
They had.
OK, another of his secrets was Santa's secrets.
Oh, that his brother was the Grinch, right?
That led into.
Yes.
Scott was well, that's more like.
Was that later?
It's a little later because there's we're talking about hard drugs.
Oh, right.
We have Rudolph's secret, too.
Yeah.
And then I don't know.
I just have some of Scott's notes.
There's crack in the candy.
That's what it is.
Maybe that was the the the the gingerbread lady that I think that's what it was.
And then at a certain point, just our emcee said like Santa came home
with a beard full of crack.
Crack.
What?
What are we doing here?
Crack bewildering.
But the amount of time they just kept saying crack, I was just that was really
that was really making me laugh.
That choice, I guess.
But again, I guess boomers know that.
I guess so.
I guess they know crack because that's a little right.
Exactly.
So I'm like, I guess I guess that's for them.
And look, it killed.
It did.
Yeah.
So I guess they win with that choice.
But yeah.
So at this point, Scott writes in the notes, I guess there's been four secrets.
That was that was part of it was unclear of what it was.
Is this a secret or is this not?
That's when that's when that when you know the when the Ice Queen said that was
the point where the Ice Queen said the secret number four and we're like, oh,
I guess we must have missed one or two.
Yeah.
I don't know if Ice Queen was just listing and forgot to say a number or we didn't
hear because it was very loud.
It was a very cavernous room.
I mean, look, it used to be a food court.
So the acoustics were not perfect in there for a bawdy show.
Some of these dirty things are a real journey.
Like, yeah, it's it's such a leap to get there when so much of Christmas snow
snowflakes, even the icing on gingerbread cookies.
It's cocaine or cum.
It's right there.
Yeah.
Santa came home with a beard full of cum.
Yeah, it would work, too.
That would work, too.
I guess so.
Did they say the word cum?
I don't think they said cum at any point in the show.
I don't think they did say the word.
I don't think they actually did.
Do you think there were words that were off limit?
But didn't they say jizz?
Am I misremembering that?
I feel like jizz is softer.
Yeah, it is a little softer.
But maybe it's more of like a boomer writer.
That could be it.
Yeah.
Rudolph has cocaine dick and he can't jizz.
He can fuck, but he can't jizz.
They had, OK, so they had, yeah, Rudolph comes out.
Rudolph has the coked up routine.
It also does some aerials.
This was actually another thing I wanted to note is just from a pacing standpoint.
So it felt like all of the female acts were frontloaded,
and then the males were saved for last, the males and couples.
Am I wrong about that?
Oh, um.
I kind of felt like it could have been interspersed a little bit more.
Maybe, yeah.
We could have done two women and then a hunk third, you know what I mean?
Just so there was something for everybody.
Because one demographic might get bored.
That's what I felt like.
I felt like this was appealing very much to the straight male gaze, if you will.
That's what it kind of felt like it was appealing to initially.
And it was just like, well, are we ever going to get to some hunks?
And then when we finally did get to some hunks, that was great.
But it would have been nice to see some of that earlier.
Going back and forth, sure.
Exactly, yeah.
I get it.
I don't know.
Maybe there was some sort of technical reason you had to do structure.
It could be right.
Because they would send the wire back up to put a different apparatus on it
before a different high wire trick happened.
So somebody had the ribbons, somebody had a big hoop.
I don't know if there was some logistical reason they had to do that.
You're right.
Maybe all the wire work had to come first.
Was there?
Did I see right?
There was pole dancing, but it was on an aerial contraption.
That's what it was, yeah.
That's very impressive.
It was cool.
I was a little scared for the performers, too.
It seemed dangerous.
It seems borderline unsafe.
They both seemed dangerous.
So combining them together, I'm like, well, that's very risky, I feel like.
Yeah.
So I mean, there was definitely like...
I felt like it was fairly equal as far as gender stuff.
It was.
It just was kind of like half and half, basically.
Yeah.
The other thing I would say, and this was a thing you actually touched on earlier, Jason,
when you're talking about the burlesque scene oftentimes has some body positivity,
I will say I think there was a missed opportunity.
The Santa guy was great, but there was a missed opportunity for a hot big guy
with a big beard and a big belly to be Santa,
because that's a type people like.
And instead, everyone was like a cut hunk, like a Luigi Mangione body.
And that's fine.
That's fine.
I like looking at the male body, but that's part of why I like wrestling.
But it would have been nice to see a guy with a big belly there who also had some moves.
Sure, yeah.
There could have been more diversity in that area.
Yeah, definitely.
You know what?
I didn't see anybody who looked jacked like Hulk Hogan standing with muscles.
I would have liked to see somebody freakishly big.
Right, like a super muscly guy would have been fun, too.
I would have found somebody that one hand bench pressed us while we were sitting on a bench or something.
Yeah, a big muscle man could have just been another type, just to vary it up.
Because again, everyone looked great, everyone was very talented,
but it was pretty samey in terms of body types.
Yes, yes.
But yeah, it felt, I don't know, it felt like they had put some thought into it overall, I would say.
Let's just put it that way.
And then at the end, yeah, I would have liked a Santa either getting his comeuppance
or Santa just coming in and being like, what's all this here?
What is all this?
Comes in and says, you were having this party and you didn't invite me?
Right, takes his clothes, pulls his pants off.
They were like, yeah, we love it.
And we finally see his dick.
So one bit of nudity we see in the show.
Just some clinical Santa slowly lowering his red pants and showing his little dick.
And then he just stands there.
He doesn't even move.
And then he pulls his pants back off.
Simply the best by Tina Turner plays.
Was there, were you guys alluding earlier to some sort of striptease?
Like, was there like a polar bear?
Polar bear, was there an unusual Christmas?
Like that were the Coca-Cola bears, like horny or something?
No, I think if anything, they left some of that stuff on the table, like sugar plum fairy, not touched on.
That felt like that was an easy one.
Yeah, Coca-Cola polar bears could have been something that, you know, and they did use the Grinch.
They sure did.
And that was like the, I think the secret was that Santa's, I think I said earlier, Santa's brother is the Grinch.
And that was one of the couples routines where the sexy Grinch was wearing a Grinch mask,
but like muscles out and then like a little bit of like furry gloves, very green gloves was doing it.
Oh, this was actually, this was the second time in addition to the cocaine use from Rudolph,
where I was like actually scandalized because it seemed that Grinch's couples act was with Cindy Lou Who.
Oh yeah.
Which was like, seemed like it was in really poor taste.
Yes.
I mean, did they say the name though?
Or was that just like, could it have just been another member, an adult woman from Whoville?
I guess it could have been an adult woman from Whoville, but it seemed like it was kind of like that.
Mrs. Lou Who, Cindy's mom, let's hope it was that.
Let's hope it was that.
Even if they reconnected later in life, that can be very dicey.
Jason, let me show you a photo of the Grinch right here.
I don't know if you can make out.
Was there any, yeah, it's very green.
Grinch's wearing like assless underwear, like leather underpants.
You can see his hairy butt.
There's multiple missed opportunities there.
Yeah, seeing the Grinch's big green hog or like though the Grinch's Santa are brothers,
and then they do the, like one of them puts the bow on the other, like the Folgers incest ad.
You're my present this year.
Or they're like, they're like Santa and the Grinch are brothers,
and then they go like step brothers and they start kissing or something.
Yes, because it's allowed.
It's allowed.
Oh, it's allowed.
Yeah, it's allowed.
America's losing its mind and it's mostly concerned with it being allowed.
They should have had like somebody dressed as Ron DeSantis run into the show
and try to shut it down during the show or something.
That would have been fun.
Yeah.
But I don't think people might not know who that is anymore.
Yeah, I don't know.
It came and went so fast.
Well, I think the only, I mean, yeah, I don't think this is necessarily the most politically engaged crowd.
No, no.
The only, oh, so there was...
There was a little reference early, I feel like.
There was a little bit, and there was also a point in the show where,
so we all had like little cards to write secrets on,
and it was like, tell your dirtiest secret or whatever, and they would collect them,
and then towards the end of the show, the MC was reading them out.
Yeah.
Carlson has one of the cards here.
I guess that's a blank one.
This is the one that was not written on because ours was collected.
And then all the secrets just, they all felt like made up Reddit, am I the asshole post?
Right.
You know, like just like fake secrets that weren't really, you know, like I'm here with my girlfriend,
but then I just saw my wife, you know, that sort of stuff.
They all felt like bullshit.
Too perfect.
Yeah, exactly.
Too cutesy.
And then, but then there was one that was like, that didn't really...
It felt like one they put in there just to set up the impression, right?
The President's one.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because there was one that was about like, I think it was like I sucked Joe Biden off or something like that.
And then the Ice Queen said, can you imagine if Trump sucked Joe Biden off
and then went into a pretty good Trump impression of Trump blowing Biden?
Yeah.
So that was as political as Santa's Secret got.
Okay.
They weren't, yeah, they weren't, they weren't tackling any of the hard questions or the hard questions.
You know what I'm saying?
I get it.
Yeah.
There's a lot of...
So Scott wrote down a secret on our post, one of the postcards on our table.
It was not read, but I believe, and I don't know if he has a picture of it,
but I believe it was something to the tune of I am very into Amazon position and inflatable stuff.
Yes.
There was some inflation fetish.
An inflation fetish, but we were hoping, we were really hoping that the Ice Queen would read that, but that did not happen.
Okay.
It was not selected.
But it definitely felt a little bit state, like fake.
Yeah, it felt like they either had some prefab ones that they knew would hit or they just picked the most outrageous sounding ones that were made up.
Right.
But yeah, that's a fun element.
I mean, it definitely felt like people knew, it definitely felt like somebody, oh, they're reading ours.
Yeah.
So maybe there were at least a couple that...
Yeah, it might have been.
And they may have all been giggling to themselves, oh, we're going to be naughty and write something there.
There was a full bachelorette party up in that one area.
I don't know if it was bachelorette, but they were all ladies in dresses, silver dresses.
There were a bunch of people who were dressed up in Christmassy outfits, 60 Christmas outfits.
And yeah, those women who were in the corners, a group of a half dozen women all dressed to the nines.
They all had glitter dresses of sequined dresses of different shades.
They'd all coordinated.
Yeah.
So it was definitely for a lot of people, like, this is our big night out.
We're going to stand in secret.
We're going to get so horny and we're going to get fucking trashed.
We should have dressed up, first of all.
Yeah, we should have.
We did not really dress up.
No.
We didn't get that horny.
And I think that was a mistake.
Yeah, and we only had a couple of drinks.
We should have gotten completely fucked up.
A couple of drinks, regular amount of arousal.
It's an average Friday night for us.
But yes, yeah, they, they, people might, because I went, I was like, is anybody going to be here?
I didn't know.
Yeah.
And the thing that did give me a clue that this is kind of a thing was that I think the night before,
the Green Goblin himself, Patrick Page from Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark, who's in a lot of other things,
he on Instagram posted a photo of his wife and he, or I think it was just his wife, at Santa's Secret in New York.
So I was like, this is a bi-coastal event.
Yeah.
The Green Goblin himself knows about it.
And, oh, maybe this is more of a thing than I expected it to be.
Because, you know, we see all this stuff.
We've all been to weird, quick pop-ups that go away very fast and feel half-assed.
But I was like, oh, I think people know and are excited about this.
It was, I would say the, one of the weirder moments was for me was just like stepping away to use the bathroom,
which was just like a full fluorescent light, like mall bathroom that was right next to the space.
That was not themed at all.
No effort.
Yeah. I think actually did not go to the bathroom I'm thinking about, not there at least.
Yeah.
But yeah, they should have done a little something in there, but maybe there's some sort of building code.
Probably.
That you can't theme it.
Was the music, could you hear, I mean, I guess it was loud enough you could hear the music in there?
Yeah, I know you could hear everything, yeah.
Oh, okay, so.
I'm just thinking back, because when I was trying to figure out if I could go,
I knew there was a walk-through element, I knew it was in the Beverly Center,
and like theme parks, malls, casino, anywhere with a lot of walking nowadays,
I opt for a wheelchair rather than the cane just for ease of like,
I don't want to get eat shit or get overly fatigued just to do an event.
And I'm just imagining now us in Santa's office and her going, who's naughty?
And five adults turning around and pointing at the one in the wheelchair.
It would have happened 100%.
Yeah, absolutely.
I just want to read a couple of things we forgot to say.
The Grinch's cock grew ten sizes bigger.
Right.
First of all.
Okay, got manageable and comfortable.
Some of the music, there was a Meghan Trainor song,
a Christmas song playing that I sound clouded and showed everybody.
Then Charlie XEX was playing while the Grinch stripped off his fur.
Mrs. Claus likes to go to a strip club called the Toy Factory also.
These are all little details.
Oh, right, that's what we got in the Nutcracker, yeah.
And then she got a, I don't know who even wrote this.
She got a lap dance from the Nutcracker and Santa saw it and got mad and made him stiff.
That is Santa's biggest secret.
And then his darkest secret is that it's Grinch's twin.
So anyway.
Yeah, that was the other thing.
It felt like we were going towards one big revelation,
but they all kind of seem to the same level.
Yeah.
That's really kind of out of his control if the Grinch is his twin.
That's true, yeah.
He couldn't have done anything about that.
What I was about to say is that if indeed they want to do Uncle Sam's secret again this year.
I'm kind of interested.
You're saying I would want to see what they do with Uncle Sam's secret.
You're saying you're a Yankee Donald Dandy in that case.
I think so.
So I don't know, Jason, you may not have to wait for Santa to come back around.
I'll get my best Old Navy American flag t-shirt out and pop it on.
We're not making a mistake again.
We will dress up this time.
Yeah, you got to have some sort of patriotic look.
New president next year.
Exactly, there you go.
We're going to be a whole different set of people.
I already got the hat.
Sure.
You're wearing the hat now.
Yeah, I'm curious what they would do because there's certainly more fantastical things
and fun to be had with the Christmas aesthetic.
I'm curious what they do with the sort of patriotic burlesque take.
I'd want to see it.
I'd go back.
And it also seems like for an otherwise hulking vacant space in the Beverly Center,
like basically half of a floor's worth of real estate,
they were able to turn this into a profit center.
So I understand why they're wanting to find a way to do it in other seasons.
Yeah, because they have it all set up, you may as well.
But I feel like the chance for problematic things in the Uncle Sam version is high.
I feel like they're going to have to really sidestep some things,
but maybe they don't.
Maybe they go there.
Maybe they could lean into it.
I don't know.
Maybe there is like a two-minute long monologue of like,
hey, we had a lot of fun tonight, but let's remember,
we're a country of different, we're more united than divide at a really heavy hand.
Yeah, well, let's hope.
I mean, but maybe there's still a chance for us to influence the show.
Maybe Weigert could show around Uncle Sam's secret.
I'd love to get involved.
But anyway, I did.
I had a great time.
Part of it is because Dad doesn't get out of the house as much as he used to.
PWG hasn't been running for a year or two or a year and a half.
I don't remember exactly how long.
It's been a while.
Fingers crossed it comes back.
So yeah, Dad, meaning me, hasn't been out.
But I had a ball.
I was so tired.
I didn't even make it to Jimmy Angel at the smokehouse later because I was too tired.
You bailed on Jimmy Angel.
Yeah, Jimmy Angel.
Because you said you were going straight there.
I was.
I go see Jimmy Angel because of a friend of the show, Trevor Zam, and I said this on the show before,
introduced me to an 89-year-old rock and roll singer named Jimmy Angel, the last of the 50s Bobcats.
And I was going straight from the Beverly Center to the smokehouse because Jimmy's set starts at nine
and it would have been perfect.
And I got so tired from all the raucous innuendo that I said, I'll see Jimmy.
I'll see him next month.
I'll just wait.
So I had a great time.
Yeah.
I had a ball.
I had a lot of fun.
I liked it.
Yeah.
I look forward to future installments.
You would have taken, next time you would have taken like a, you'll take a blue chew before you go in there.
Really up the excitement.
Take the rowing, the new rowing one that's Sidenofil and Tatafil.
Wait, what?
Have you not seen these TV ads?
I haven't seen them.
I don't know who's watching cable.
What is it?
It's two things at once?
It's both.
It's Viagra and Cialis because Cialis stays in your system longer, but Viagra is faster acting.
And it's both at once?
It's one combo pill.
Oh my God.
Viagra, you know about this?
I don't know about this, but I do know that someone just walked into our studio while we were having this conversation.
It was.
And we're not doing a blue chew ad read.
It was an uncomfortable situation.
I agree.
Well, we'll have to talk about it on another episode because Jason's just, again, telling me this information for the first time.
I'm hearing it for the first time.
But Nick Weier, You Survive podcast, The Ride.
Thank you so much for being here.
It was a pleasure to hang out.
Oh my goodness.
What an honor.
I always loved doing the show.
And I think since we were behind the paywall, it's fine for me to not be talking about a parking garage.
Yes, I agree.
Well, I mean, yeah, I think it's fine.
The Beverly Hills Center does have a pretty big and bad parking garage, I will say.
And I do.
Multi-level maze.
We ended up talking more about this.
I know you wanted to talk more about points.
Yeah, I wrote a full page of notes on credit card points because I listened to your episode and I told, as I told you in the group text,
I had to keep pausing it because I had stuff that I wanted to say.
I think we had more than enough to talk about with Santa's Secret.
We did.
I mean, if there's one thing you want, do you want to say one of them?
I mean, I don't want all this stuff.
You could wait, save it for next time.
I would just say like back on the Amex trifecta.
I think the one thing that you are getting from the American Express ecosystem is for travel benefits.
You get into a lot of airport lounges, including the Amex exclusive Centurion lounges, which are very nice.
Oftentimes like a little step up from like a Delta Sky Club.
And then they've also got their fine hotels, which you can use through their travel portal.
And so that's really great for like, you know, we've had a lot of success like booking like a hotel at a discount with points.
And then you get a bunch of like upgrades that are part of Amex perks through that.
So that's one thing that I think that what I've been because I used to do a lot of churning.
I used to do a lot of like trying to min max this.
And then I reached a point where I was like, I just got to simplify this.
I do about like 20 percent of the work that I used to do.
And I still get about 80 percent of the results just by doing like three cards and keeping it simple as opposed to trying to get all these sign up bonuses.
So I would just say like, find whatever works for you and just keep it straightforward.
Well, can I next year invite you to do points too?
I would love to. With us.
It would be the honor of a lifetime.
I think I say this on an episode that's about to come out.
But I know how to do point the credit card points to episode.
I know I know what I want to do for it, but it's going to be a big episode.
And you're obviously very passionate about this.
And I assume you know all about fast food app points as well.
One hundred percent.
And I we need another heavy hitter in here.
Yeah, I would I would love to.
We need to clear four hours for that.
But I would like to formally invite you, if we do, if we're allowed, if daddy lets us to do points to next year in twenty twenty five.
Look, if there's ever a window, I'm always happy to do the show and talk about it.
But yeah, credit credit card points are a thing that I have some strong opinions on.
OK, well, exit to the gift shop as well.
Oh, yeah. Hey, check out Doughboy's podcast about chain restaurants and check out a get played podcast about about video games.
Great podcast. Check those out. Yes.
And as for us, I don't know, this is second gate, you know, you know where you are.
Can you say, can you say, can you say, are we in club three?
No, this is second gate. Sorry, I'm all mixed up.
Can I say Sheridan? You're too boring, you're confused.
Sheridan's going to be coming on an upcoming episode of Doughboy's Patreon.
Oh, yes, I heard, yes.
Something that I know you've also discussed on podcast The Ride.
The quality of Wendy's lettuce. Yeah.
I mean, it's not that it's not that narrow.
It's not that narrow, but I've written a few things down.
All right. Well, I'm excited to hear that. So yeah, check that out.
And yeah, we'll be back to see Uncle Sam next summer.