FOREVER
DOG
Warning
The following podcasts may contain
Muscley Waiters
Copycat Little Rascals
An Apathetic Fear of Snakes
And Skull Counting
Yes, finally
It's the sequel that
Everyone has been asking for
Indiana Jones Adventure 2
On today's podcast
The Ride
Intro Music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
A theme park podcast that has to remind you
Do not look into the eyes of our hosts
Or else
They will take that as an invitation
To talk to you about all the weird
Annoying stuff the Disneyland app does
My name is Mike Carlson
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan
Where did that one come from?
Have you been sitting on that?
I completely invented it off the top of my head
Like five minutes ago
That's why you're the best
Look, we've done so many of these dumb intros
At this point it's like
Pulling teeth to get something out of my head
That's not the same shit
So there I got, I came up with something clever, right?
We have a lot to do today
And we have a very important guest
He's returning to Podcast The Ride
And most importantly
He is the Indie God
Which is very appropriate for the topic today
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome back
Matt Cardona
Oh, thank you very much
Deathmatch King, always ready
Internet Champion, the complete
But most importantly for this episode
The Indie God
Thanks for having me guys
Matt, some of the history
The recent history is that Scott
Is on hiatus for now
So we've been doing these Scott free episodes
I'm a listener of the show
Sure, but sometimes you'll text me
And you'll say like for instance
At Tomorrowland where we sort of redid what we thought
Tomorrowland should be, you said like
What is this fantasy booking crap or something
You'll text me things
So you'll be like, I'll be like
Okay, sometimes he doesn't listen, that's fine
I tried to get you to listen to McGruff one and two
And we're like, no, not interested
I skip
I skip the City Walk stuff
That's fine, some people say that's the high
Watermark of the podcast, that's fine
Some people say that's the good stuff
And the rides are bad, you know, it all depends
You're right, it all depends
I'll listen to the City Walk, the Orlando
City Walk stuff, but when you're going into
The Hollywood City Walk, I'm not even familiar
With that
I get that, that makes sense
So have you gone to the piano bar
Orlando City Walk? Many times
Okay, so has it packed in there
Because when Scott and I went, we literally were
The only two people in the room that closed it down
I've been in there when
It was, I wouldn't say packed, but it wasn't
It wasn't just two people
Okay, well that's good because I was worried
About it. So here's the thing, and I know
We're here to talk about Indiana Jones
But I
Listen, I live in Orlando, okay
And it's great, I feel
Very lucky, very fortunate, blessed
It's great to be living in Orlando during this
Theme park renaissance, Disney vs. Universal
Who's gonna top who, you know
It's a lot of fun, but
I will leave my house
To go to Disney
Springs, I will leave my house to go eat
Somewhere on Disney property
I will not leave my house
To go to
Cowfish
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, cowfish is
Awful to find
Cowfish sucks
I don't think anything on universal property
Food wise is good, if I'm in the park
I'll stop on the way out
But I'm not leaving my house
To go to the NBC grill, you know what I'm saying?
I will leave my house to go to the California grill
Sure
See, this makes sense
But the problem is we have
Where we live in Burbank, City Walk
Is very close, so that's the closest
We can get there in 15 minutes
To get to downtown Disney, depending on the time of day
Our hour 15 could be 90 minutes
So we have to take what we can get
So that's I think why we end up spending more time
Just at City Walk
Than at downtown Disney, but I do understand what you're saying
Disney in general
Higher quality restaurants
More scenic, more interesting
Stuff
That being said
The Margaritaville has a lovely porch
The Jimmy Buffet Plane is there
The Hemisphere Dancer is there
So there are things that I would once in a while
Navigate to
I would make a point to go there
If I'm not at the park
I will not go to any of those places
If
You would not even meet a friend
At City Walk, would you insist they go to
Disney Springs?
The parking situation for City Walk is atrocious
You know that
We didn't actually have to park
There
The Uber is even worse
If I'm going there, I'm drinking
I have the annual pass so I can do the valet
But I can't drink and drive
So I can't even valet
So I'm going to take an Uber like a sucker
And you're all the way at the top
Of that garage
Oh my god, it's like 20 minutes
It's a big walk, and it is a big walk to get in
That is true
But I guess we didn't have that
Really what we should have done for the City Walk Saga
Is we should have done a simulation of your life
To know what a local is experiencing
I should have slept
In your toy room
And then I would have taken a lift over alone
To City Walk
Gotten hammered
And then taken the lift back at like 3am
And of course slept again
In your house
And then I would have known what a local is experiencing
So maybe we just have to do the whole City Walk thing again
To really figure out what it's like
Another trick I do
If I'm going to the darks
I will Uber to the Hard Rock Hotel
And then I will walk
You know
Or if it's perfect timing
Take the water taxi
Right, yes I've done that
I had to negotiate with the bus
This is repeating stories
But I had to negotiate with the bus driver
Who was taking me from
Accidentally me going to Volcano Bay
And he didn't understand what I was telling him
I was like I'm going to Hard Rock but I can walk from Hard Rock
To City Walk and he's like no you can't do that
And I was like dude I've done it
I know what I'm talking about
Bro I know
And then he told me to get off at the wrong hotel
And I was like is it this guy's first day
He seemed like an older guy
He seemed like he had been there a while
But then he realized I was right and he let me off the bus
So yeah that trick
Can I ask about California Grill
Do you ever do the frowned upon trick
Of doing a lift to Contemporary
Getting out
And then walking over to Magic Kingdom
No comment
But I will say yesterday
I don't know when this is airing
But Chelsea and I we had an early Thanksgiving
Because we're not going to spend Thanksgiving together
So we had dinner at the Liberty Tree Tavern
In Magic Kingdom
And I took
I knew I would be having a couple cocktails
So I took an Uber to the ticket
And transportation center
But I had to
I feel dirty lying to the people
To get into Contemporary
I'll admit the only time I've ever done that
Is when I was running so low on time
It was the only option
And I had a reservation
And then I ended up for Contemporary
To eat at Chef Mickey's
But then I ended up having to cancel it
And yes I will admit I'm bad boy
They can ban me if they want
But I will always from Magic Kingdom
Walk to the Contemporary
To get my Uber home
Always
Why not
And then you have to go to Contemporary and smell the lobby
Right
Last night we had a little after dinner drinks
At the California Grill
There's nothing better
Have you guys dined at the California Grill?
Yes
Is that your number one?
What's your number one?
I haven't done everything possible at Disney World
Neither have I
But I've done all the hits I believe
As far as
We did more of a pizza
And drinks at the California Grill
Pizza?
That means you sat at the bar
It does mean I sat at the bar
I didn't do a full meal
Wait so you've never sat
You've never been to California Grill
There's a price mix menu
Oh you were talking about the whole
They tell you what you're eating
Well that's how it is
I'm not just sitting at the bar like a Gironi
You went to California Grill on pizza?
But isn't part of it
The ambiance isn't part of it
The service
You can't be looking out if your back is
If you're facing the bar
You're going to be the weird guys turning around
Watching people eat dinner
There's an area where you can sit in couches
That's not just the bar where your back is to the view
It's in between
You're still getting some of it
You're still sniffing the experience
No wonder California Grill is not your favorite restaurant
You only had a pizza there
I guess
Jason have you done it?
Honestly it was a good pizza
I did
10 years ago
Guys
What are we doing?
The last time I was down there with family
We ate at the Topolino Terrace
I like that a lot
I like it a lot
You can see the fireworks
You can see some of the Epcot night time show
It's great
To use a wrestling reference
I refer to Topolino's as
NWO California Grill
You know what I'm saying?
NWO Sting
It was like Sting but it wasn't Sting
It's California Grill but it's not a California Grill
A little different
A little edgier
It's rooftop
It's not the same guys
It's just not
Have you ever been to a real restaurant
At Disney World?
Do you consider Ohana?
Malaysian?
That's a real restaurant
It's not in my top 5
I've had it 3 times in the last decade
I feel like the first time was amazing
10 years ago
Then it's gotten worse since
I've done Liberty Tree
I very famously on the show ate a meal for one
At Liberty Tree Tavern
I packed it in
Right before a plane
Like 4 rolls
Just trying to shove it in
But I was trying to
Join the Clean Plate Club
You're a big Boathouse guy
We both agree
Boathouse
That might be my number 2
I like paddle fish
A lot
Whatever we do
With Disney Springs
You're pegged for the Boathouse episode
I think you need Ricky too
This is also part of it
There's a guy you know
Ricky that you keep talking about
The best waiter there
You mentioned Ricky
I hope we're not doxing him
He's like 265 pounds jacked
I don't want to get him in trouble
But he always gives me extra potatoes
This sounds like your guy
Good potatoes
Extra potatoes
I didn't make it down there
The last trip
Have you done the little car in the water?
I have not
I've never done that
That feels like an important part of the Boathouse
It's one of those things
I'll do it next time and you never do it
I lived in New York
For 30 plus years
I never went to the Statue of Liberty
I live here
I'll do it eventually
So you've never done it
It's kind of tiny though
It's kind of unimpressive
I haven't been over there
But every time I'm in New York
It's kind of small
You're seeing it from a distance
Just watch Ghostbusters 2
That's true
Then it moves and it's doing cooler stuff
That is very true
That doesn't upset me
It upsets me more that you haven't been in the little boat in the water
Than see the Statue of Liberty
Honestly
I did once eat at the Boathouse with
I'm going to name drop Lentesta
Now we're talking
That's like a power meal
They recognize Lent
And they come to the whole meal
Wow
Oh my god
That's like a power
If somebody listens to Podcast the Ride
Dave and Buster's
They're like have a free drink
That's more than enough
I don't think we've ever had
The meal is on us Mr. Testa
That's impressive
He has a reputation
For being a nice man
Everywhere
He's very nice
Next time
You and Len were both out of town
Last time we were in Orlando
This is the tragedy
We did the big Orlando trip
You were wrestling and Len was
Lecturing at MIT
Len was giving
Some sort of symposium somewhere
On something smart
It might have been theme parks
But it was from a smart angle I'm sure
So I don't know
Hopefully fingers crossed
Epic Universe time
I'm very excited about that
I'm excited and nervous
It's kind of safe
Explain why you're nervous
I don't know why
Well anytime
Any company opens
A brand new ride
Let alone a whole new park
And a park that is being sold
All this technology
All these advanced rides
I feel like
I'm just hoping they work
Hoping they work operationally
And then crowd wise
It seems like they're
Managing crowds
In a smart way
You're thinking everything can just
Break down
It'll be original, universal, Orlando
Where nothing worked
I don't think it'll be that bad
But I remember the opening summer
Of Diagon Alley
Waiting 3 or 4 hours
To do Gringotts
That's a little too long
Hopefully it's spread out
People are spreading it out
Because it's a whole new park
But yeah
I'm just trying to be realistic
And manage expectations
And again this is not a shot at universal
This is just like
Any company that opens
A new thing
There's going to be growing pains
They should invite us
To tour
With a hard hat on
Before it opens
We can see it running
Before it breaks down
When all the crowds come
Do you guys get invites as media
To do stuff like that
Six Flags invites us
To a lot of stuff
And god bless them
They're so nice
But for some reason Nats Berry Farm
Kicked us off the list this Halloween
I don't know what the hell is going on
Universal out here
Is still good to us
Horror nights
Not the red carpet events
But they'll get us into horror nights
We did a Mario press event
But
Universal Orlando a little quiet
And Disney
Disney would
Never acknowledge that we exist
Wow
I'd like to think that's because
We're like the edgiest theme park podcast
But there's a good chance
They just have never heard of it
It could be a little of both
But I'd like to think that they're like
Oh man we can't let those wild men in here
They're going to tear our new stuff up
Oh my god
Institutionally now we've talked
Plenty of people who've worked for the company
In various departments
And wings and stuff
Who listen
But yeah as an institution
No
We'd love to get on the list
I mean I've begged
Most of this podcast is me begging
To get into press events
That's a majority of what I do in the seven years
But yeah
So we'll see
I've emailed Orlando
They know we're there
So we'll see
And we know some people around too
So we'll see what happens
But I would like to enjoy it
Before the crowds break it
Well good luck guys
Thank you
So today I mean
Man we're already off topic here
I was going to talk about Muppets closing
But I don't even know if we have time
So let's not talk about Muppets closing
Real quick let's go around and say what we think about it
Closing
I will say this I don't like that it's closing
But for some reason I feel more bothered
By Rivers of America closing
Anyway Jason what do you think?
I'm a little bummed out
I
I think I understand
The logic if they're trying
To save money
Because a lot of the Monstropolis stuff
Is going to be redecorating
And re-themeing what's already
There
So when I realized that was what was happening
I'm like oh that's why they're not
Building at Star Wars
Launch Bay or Animation Courtyard
Oh
So they can re-theme the theater
And the restaurants and everything
So you like it or you don't?
No not really
I mean I hate
Always left Muppet Vision 3D
And my family specifically always left
Mama Melrose so that's gone
Sure
And I
Think I'm just in the camp
That's like Disney World is so
Much land
There's such a giant
Parking lot outside of MGM
Outside of Hollywood Studios
That
Like they could build fresh
So re-themeing
Doesn't
Make as much sense to me and also
Like there is
A theater next to Rock and Roller
Coaster just put Muppet's Vision
In there
I feel like would quell some people's
You know being upset
I think they're putting in
Some sort of villains
Show which does seem a little
Silly as they're building
A whole new villains land at the Magic Kingdom
So
Yeah I mean I'm not
Happy about it but it was
Going to happen you know it was bound to happen
I am kind of
You know they're giving us the Muppets
The Rock and Roller Coaster which
Another one of my favorites gone
But
You know it's not a museum as
Walt said or did he ever actually
Say that I'm not sure but I don't know if he said
That but somebody said it somebody said
It someone said Walt said it but listen it was
Going to happen Star Wars Launch Bay I don't know
What the fuck it's still doing in either park
Oh I know like what do we do
Well if you listen to our episode where we
Imagine different scenarios where
Star Wars Launch Bay went away I think you would
See we agree with you no yeah so
Listen it is what it is I also
Love Momma Melrose
But that wasn't quite Muppet
Themed anyway so
Pizza Rizzo is gone
Pizza Rizzo I mean that
Come on that needed to go let's go come on
Now that I know is a fighting
Words for many people not necessarily us
We haven't done an episode but that is
People are very protective of Pizza Rizzo
So well I mean
We'll look I don't know how long this is
I don't know if we're going to get a chance to do it before it closes
Both Rock and Roller Coaster and
Muppet Vision
But we will continue talking about this
And debating I honestly
I don't think Rock and Roller Coaster is the right ride
For the Muppets
Like it's too fast it goes too fast
It's not a whimsical ride vehicle
It's too like
What you're going to blow by a big neon
Kermit head I mean I'm not against that but
It just doesn't feel right to me
I feel like they're going to do something fun with the
Pre-show sure the
Pre-show that'll be the queue will be probably fun
And fine but the ride itself is like
It's kind of forcing a
Round peg in a square
I was going to say a round peg in a square hole
But you understand what I'm saying but I'd rather
The Muppets than some
Other random band
I think
I agree with that but I think
It depends I could be swayed
I could be swayed depending
It's a good question we've talked about
This the
I mean it would be funny because
You want the band in the intro
You want the band in the intro video
So like if you do the Beatles
Two of the members are dead
And the Beatles don't have the high energy music you want
For that either
But like the Rolling Stones
Here's what I want
I want old men to replace
Old men
So I'm trying to think of what old men
Even like Kiss is kind of
Interesting just from the perspective
Of there's a bunch of old men
And it's like they have some fast
Songs like that's what
I want to I want to preserve the oldness
Of the music in some way
I mean you could go new you could go
With some like I mean it's hard
Because there's not really many big new rock bands
And you can't predict that they're going to
Stand and test the time like Aerosmith did
That's true
So I mean people have thrown out Taylor Swift
But that music isn't high energy
Necessarily like it's not the high energy of the
You want for the rock and roller
So I really it's hard like
Coldplay come on
God stop it
That's what I'm fine with the Muppets
Would you want like a Backstreet Boys
Overlay on the rock and roller coaster
I love the Backstreet Boys but come on
Let's get serious here
Well their music is a little more like sexy
Yeah well there's some upbeat songs
Larger than life
Yeah yeah but that's I mean does that feel
Would that feel right going 60 miles an hour
In that limo
I don't think so either
They need a more like sensual ride
Not their high energy stuff but you want some of the sexy
The sexiness of some of their
Ballads as well
So again a different ride system for Backstreet Boys
The ride would be
Appropriate alright let's get
On to the topic at hand because there's
Too much to talk about we're all over the place already
We are doing
Oh go ahead Mike
Announce what we're doing before I
Comment on it
So for years now I've
Been suggesting to Scott
To do Indiana Jones Adventure 2
And he has been resistant
I'm not quite sure why I think on some level
He wants to finish all the other rides there's been
Big rides we haven't done yet Space
Mountain Mr. Toad but I said
I bet if you go back and listen to it was
Our second episode ever I bet if you
Go back and listen we did
A bad job we didn't go thoroughly
Through everything we kind of
Glazed over and I went back and
I listened and boy was I right we
Padded this thing out we barely talked
About the ride I was telling Jason yesterday I go it sounds
Seems like we talked about the ride for like 30 minutes
And we basically just highlighted
A couple things we liked and then we did a bunch
Of other crap and I think it's not
Right I think we needed to go back
And we need to talk more about this great
Ride and that's why we're
Here today now that Scott is gone
We were able to be naughty
And do Indiana
Jones Adventure 2
And that's what we're doing here today
And look we were young we were
Inexperienced you know we were not
We didn't know how to make love
Back then we knew how to
Have sexual
Intercourse but we didn't know how to take
Our time you know what I'm saying? Something on your
Mind today Michael?
What do you mean because I was talking about how sensuality
The Backstreet Boys
The Backstreet Boys just
Wound me up I think and then
It sort of just permeated into this analogy
That must be what happened
Is the
Show me the meaning of being lonely or whatever
That Backstreet Boys song is came into my head
And now here I am being
Creepy that's what happened
So anyway
We have a lot of stuff to talk about
Let's just go over in
General our thoughts
On this ride now because it's been seven years since we did
Our Indiana Jones episode
Does this ride still hold up?
Do we still like it? Is it
Better or worse? Is it the same?
Let's go with Jason first
Oh
Yeah I
I think it's great I haven't been on it
In a while and they
This is one that they continually
Do
Upgrade I mean I think
They have to do maintenance on it because
It's such an involved ride
So I'm happy to see
They do regular maintenance on it
There's been a lot of projection
Effects and like they've
Changed some of the scenes around a little
Yeah that's a big reason
We have talked today because there's new effects
Now on the ride since we've talked
About it the first time
Some might call them minor but they are there and
They do need to be discussed
Matt how do you feel about this?
Now okay you guys are California
I'm Orlando but even before that I was
New York so this is not
Something I get to go on that often so it's
Much more special to me when I do
Might be my number one
In all of California
Yeah that's including
California Adventure
It might be my number one and that's
That's not even you know taking into account
That I'm the indie god which is a play off of Indiana Jones
Like put that aside
I just think the
You know no screens
Animatronics
Huge set you know
And like I don't think you need to be a fan of Indiana Jones
To be a fan of this ride there's thrills
It's fun it's exciting
Yes it is
Yes seven years later I feel
The same way it's kind of still
In my mind the ultimate ride
It's like I still
I mean I know I have a contentious relationship
With Rise of the Resistance but
Even though Rise of the Resistance is a great ride
This ride I still
Like it better than that ride
This ride is so
Awesome from start to finish
And I've only loved it
More going on it's like I have
It hasn't dwindled at all
In my what at this point 15
To 20 years going on it
It's only gotten better to me
It's amazing it really is
You bring up Rise
I think Rise might be
The best theme park ride
Ever if you did every theme park
Ride once and compared them
I don't know if the rewrite ability is
There with Rise
Not very thrilling
You know some of the cannons don't even work anymore
Sometimes Kylo doesn't work
Sometimes the lightsaber doesn't come from the ceiling
Yeah
You know what I'm saying
I could go on Indiana Jones over and over
And over and over and over
And Indiana Jones like they'll break
Stuff isn't working
All the time there's like shit that's supposed to happen
Your jeep is supposed to round the corner
And fire is supposed to shoot up
I've certainly been on it plenty of times when the fire doesn't
Shoot up through the skull
And like lasers don't shoot at you
Stuff doesn't always work on it
For some reason it doesn't hurt it
Like it does for Rise the Resistance
And I think there's just so much shit going on
At once
That it doesn't matter as much
Talking about modern theme park stuff
Like Honda Mansion you're in the graveyard
And if something's not working in the graveyard
It's fine there's ten other things to look at
And it's similar with Indiana Jones
Where even if the snake's not working
A snake's big and it's there
But when you get into that big throne room
If stuff isn't working it's not as big of a deal
Otherwise it's like you're supposed to focus on one thing
And if that's not working
That's a bummer
Absolutely I agree
It's very much like
The Pirates of the Caribbean style
Where like yeah if you pack
A giant room with stuff
Everyone in the boat
Could catch a different
Story beat
They catch little bits here and there
Because it's just so packed
You might not have the same
Thing you focus on you know
There's a room on the ride where there's
Tons of skulls
And I don't even know that I knew how many
I didn't know the scope
Of how many skulls were in there until a couple years
Going on it where you finally take a look to the left
You see more skulls
And then there's a big projection on the wall
It would be so easy to miss
A ton of details when you're on this thing
And we missed a ton of details talking
About it initially
That projection I feel like they've upgraded
A few times over the years
To the point where I forgot about it
Watching different
I watched a few different ride throughs
Throughout the years just to try and
Catch
What's changed
Now let's go back to the start
A little bit because like the queue itself
And now Matt I also brought you
On today because
You're a little bit of a
Scott stand in
Because you and Scott often times have a similar
Opinion about queues
Waiting for things
Yeah not going to happen pal
You're both like all action guys
You know you and Scott are
Similar dudes in that way
So you feel free to contradict
What I'm saying or what Jason and I say
Listen I can appreciate a great queue
You just won't find me
Waiting on it
Right now this
This queue forces you
To go through it
Right
I'm not standing there
Waiting like a sucker
Looking at everything
Now I think once in a while
Standing looking like a sucker is nice
I think it can be
Very nice to look like a sucker
And wait
But let me ask you this
Do you have a feeling
I say this specifically at night
Have you ever come out of this thing at night
Or gone in at night
Yes Jason do you know what I'm saying
The atmosphere and the vibe
Of just the exterior portion
Of the line at night
Is unbelievable
Now the last time I was there
Maybe not maybe not the last time
The second to last time I was there
It was cold and it was a little chilly
So not across the street but across the way
I bought
An Indiana Jones hat
And leather jacket
And then went on the ride
Anyway those are the ones I wear anyway
So it was perfect
And then I wore the jacket
And then I went home put logos on it
I wore it to the ring
You can write that off
It was an investment piece right
But I really felt like Indiana Jones
Because I put the jacket on the hat
And then rode the ride
I mean that rules
That's next level
I'm trying to think is there any other ride
Where I've dressed
He's never dressed like Mr. Toad
And then gotten on the Mr. Toad ride
Though I would like to see it happen
Sometimes my normal
Attire is reasonably close
But not that close
I don't usually have like a cravat
Or something
You don't have driving gloves in general
You don't wear driving gloves
No but it's worth considering
Because it does get pretty
It can get very cold at the right time of year
Christmas is coming though maybe I'll get you driving gloves
The same one
With the
You mean fingerless gloves or like
Whatever Toad wore
I'm going to buy you
His pantaloons
And his driving gloves whatever they were
He has goggles
An ensemble yeah
No that is
I can't think of an example
Where I was wearing the actual outfit from it
I want to do it now
Now that you've said that such thing I didn't even consider wanting to do
Now but now I want to do it on some ride
And I don't know which
I don't want to do it in Indy because you did it first
But I want to do it on a different ride
And I can't think of I don't know
We'll see we'll come up with a better
I mean I guess dressed like Spider-Man on the Spider-Man
Ride in Orlando
They would probably call
One of that if you showed up in a full
Spider-Man costume like
If you weren't just in like
Spider-Man pajamas and then you put the mask on
Right before the ride started
I think you'd be fine
Maybe yeah I mean you'd have to
Manage
The 3D glasses certainly
I think
Sometimes by happenstance
I've ridden Revenge of
The Mummy in Florida and been dressed
Like Brendan Fraser
In the queue by which I mean
Casual slacks and like a button
Up over a t-shirt
I thought you were going to say you were wrapped in toilet paper like a mummy
That's what I was thinking
What's going on here
You said like a couple times too and I was like
What scenarios
Were you dressed like a mummy
Well that's the listeners too
Have you ever dressed like the character on the ride
You're going on
Have you ever dressed like Imhotep
At Halloween Horror Nights
And ridden the mummy ride
Well I feel like at Universal
Parks during
For the Harry Potter rides there's always people
Yes that's true the robes
Which I would never
Be caught dead wearing because just the heat
Alone
Not so much in California but in Orlando
Oh my god
It depends but no I'm not going to do that
But we'll see
I don't know maybe I could dress like Frankenstein for Epic Universe
I mean it's just a suit
Honestly
But the ride
Especially at night they're playing the
Kind of like old time music
The lights are flickering
The greenery
Is around you it's like
We often ask where you would want to like live
Or you would want to sleep in the park
We've said like oh pirates in like the
Bed or something but like that's kind of a joke answer
Honest to god
I think setting up a little bed in the
Out exterior queue right
By Jungle Cruise is the
Premier place to sleep
At the park not that it's
It's an easy way but if you were to be able
To construct a bed and do it
It's so good out there
At night well it is kind of like an
Expedition base camp you
Know it is yes there's there's
It's thematically it makes sense
But I'm just saying I don't feel
Other than maybe Big Thunder at night at
Disneyland which is we got the lights
Going around just there's that really
Good vibe going on there this
Is my number one like vibe
Spot and I wish I could hang out in it more
Because you got to leave once you're done with the ride
You can't hang around
But if we could like you could have a drink in this zone
Ooh ooh ooh
This would be good
Now have you ever done like the jock lindsey's
Hanger bar at
Dizzy Springs
To me that doesn't feel
Indiana Jones enough I know I agree
I was like I was really excited to do it a couple
Years ago and I was like it's not
It's fine but it's like oh you can
Look at oh it says Indiana
Jones on this clipboard on the wall
And you're like well is that
What is the theming here
I mean yeah it's better than nothing but
It's not it doesn't satisfy
My craving for being
Near Indiana Jones shit there was a pop
Up bar I think it's gone in
Hollywood studios
Like in Indiana Jones I think it's gone I never
Got to go yeah
I mean you know we're not going to talk about the show
With the show is fantastic I'm sure you both have done
It yes of course yes
Show's still going too
Timeless that thing should never get
Torn down yeah would you
Let's say
Say you were to choose Muppets goes
Or Indiana Jones stunt show goes what would you
Pick oh man
I'm a sucker for Muppets
Man I love the Muppets I still think
It holds up and I think there's a lot of things
That people don't realize like what's
Really going on you know there's a
Lot of attention to detail that gets missed
It's just one of the classic Disney attractions
Is a shame that it's leaving yeah
But it is what it is I pick saving
Muppets unfortunately but I agree
Indiana Jones should stay around Jason what do you think
Uh that's tough
Oh yeah that's really
Tough oh he's thinking it over this isn't
A slam dunk the one time
We went down there we were in Hollywood
Studios and everyone was kind of splitting up
And I'm like who wants to go see
The Indiana Jones stunt show with
Me and no one the
Answer was no one everyone just wanted to go
For once everyone else
Was going to take a nap and I'm like
The show's about to start
There's like hardly anyone here
And so
Sounds like you've made a decision
Might be Indy yeah
Not a bad choice
But you know you would rather see that
Than the legend of Jim Hansen live on I understand
Oh my god
I knew I was going to get that
Well okay let me say something that will make you happy Jason
I looked up the names of the old time
Songs that play in the exterior
Part of the queue at Indiana Jones
Did you do this? You did you sent me a playlist
Yes okay I did send you that already good
And a lot of it is by Glenn
Miller
Glenn Miller had an orchestra a hundred years
Ago oh my god
And this is a type of music
Jason likes uh he's
From a different era but the
Thing you know Moonlight Serenade is
Like the song that you've heard in like
Movies forever that usually plays and it plays in
A lot of these these loop videos but
I think that is actually that's like almost
A background piece of the atmosphere you're not
Even noticing is that kind of old time radio
Sound while you're listening to
Something that like somebody from
Some person from 1920
Was listening to
Like that's a big part
Of making this authentic
Which is also a big
Part of a lot of different ride queues is
Making like use
Of old music to give you
A different atmosphere like Radiator Springs
Racers is playing 80 year old
Country music to give you a different vibe
Because it feels like you're in a different part of
You're in a different time essentially
And it is smart I feel like it's a thing that's used
In a lot of different lines
To make you feel like you've been transported somewhere
Yeah it's a pretty
Like low key
Like clever trick that
Immediately changes
The vibe yes from area
To area yes
I will say this
I generally don't like to wait
If the ride is like the line is stretching
Back all the way to this point
In the actual exterior
Queue I don't necessarily
Like to wait in an hour and
10 or 20 minutes
But if it's like you see
Indian it's like 45ish minutes
You get a little time
Outside then you kind of breeze through
The actual themed
The really themed interior queue
That's closer to what I'm looking for
Obviously you know
The dream is at the end of the night when no one's
If no one's there
You can take your time going through the exterior
Queue and go through
That's ideal
Now I'm going in a couple weeks for a
I don't want to you know
Don't dodge yourself
I have a VIP tour
So I won't be
You know I'll be waiting a little bit
But not on the main queue
We'll probably go through the exit
Is that what they do?
I think they just go through the
Maybe they just cut the line
In the lightning lane
You don't go to the very very front
Maybe for Cody Rhodes but not for Matt Cardona
Oh well
He's a champ
There's a special entrance
For champs
I'm an internet champ but that doesn't count
But it's also like it is so hard
Because they built this ride
And it was a logistical problem
Because they needed to build a long queue
To get to the actual building that houses
The ride
So the reason it's so long was just a logistical problem
That they went well let's just build a long
Cool line
To take you all the way
To where you're going
Which is why it's not an easy
There's not an easy way in there
You have to walk that length
And even still like there's
You walk all that length and you've got to go upstairs
And you've got to walk downstairs again
I know a lot of lines are like that but
It does feel like you walk a mile
Total
To get to the ride
And sometimes if it's the end of the day
And your legs are tired it's like
Couldn't I just be on the ride
But I do think
Psychologically you feel like
You're way far away from Disneyland at that point
There's something that it does
That makes you feel like oh shit
We're literally nowhere near Disneyland
At this moment
I've done so much physical effort
I've exerted so much effort
I must be in a different place
I'm in a different country by now
But it's worth the wait
It's absolutely worth the wait
And they do single rider sometimes
On this thing and I think they
I don't know
I think if you do single rider they often times
Put you up in the elevator
I've never done the elevator no
You should ask the guide if you can do the elevator
But there is an elevator there
And sometimes you can take that up
Go over and then maybe take another elevator
It's very confusing but
You take the elevator up
Go a little
And then you take the elevator
The second one down
So you're crossing over the track
Basically
The other thing you should do is ask the VIP guide
If you can use the Star Tours bathroom
Really
I wasn't on my list to even go on that ride
We'll see if they'll let you do
The Star Tours bathroom
What's special about the bathroom?
It's just a bathroom that's not open to the public
It's a shitty looking bathroom
Is there like a bidet
But it's like a light saber and it's like red water
Or something like that?
It's R2D2's head opens up and you pee
Into his head
And he beep beep
He gives you like a happy beep beep
That was good
It's just a normal bad
To okay bathroom
That's
When I did my one VIP tour
I was like oh hey did you want to do the Star Tours bathroom
And I was like fuck yeah I want to do that
Whatever that is
And then it was a very normal like single stall bathroom
But
There is a bathroom in the queue for
Indiana Jones too
Really
They built a bathroom in
I've never used it
That's a good point
I've never seen it honestly
I always miss it
That is something that I haven't even thought about
You're right there's something in there
They did that with Avatar too because it's such a long
Flight of passage
It's such a long queue
That I have used
Multiple
Number one or number two?
Just number one
But it's like
That's a long
Can be a long queue
Like and
Like two hours
Can you imagine opening weekend or opening year
How many people probably had to go number two
In the flight of passage
Bathroom
Probably a lot
Jane got out of line
At the river journey
Because that had a long queue
And they gave her a card
They gave her like a return ticket
So
They could prevent people jumping
A line so they gave it to her when she left
And when she came back she just gave back to him
And she got out with us
In line
That's nice I don't know I feel like some rights
Do that but a lot don't
But it makes sense I mean everybody has seen the
People who cheat and like pretend
I don't like cheaters
Yeah I mean it's the phone you put the phone
To your I've never done that you put your phone
To your head you go oh you pretend that like
There's a person up ahead
And I mean have you ever put a
Like I've never said anything
Or like show me the person up ahead
Let me walk with you
I've never done that no
Because it's hard like
I swear somebody did this to us
We took my daughter to meet Minnie Mouse
And it was a short line that was just not moving
It was like 14 to 17 people
And somebody did that
And I'm pretty like I'm pretty sure
I'm not 100% they did it
But I'm pretty sure and I was like if they are
In a line that's the ballsiest move
Ever because when it's a long line
They'll be gone by the time
You don't notice but I swear
They like went into Minnie's house and maybe
They did meet family there but there's a chance
They just skipped 17
People in line and did it
And it pulled them off which I guess kudos to them
For doing it but
Cutting a two year old is like
Yeah that
Takes a lot
They had a two year old with them so they were cutting
A two year old
No excuse
I agree there was also a weird situation
Because it was like
Minnie's house
It said like 20 minutes or something so we were like
Let's wait and we were like to my daughter
You want to meet Minnie? She loves meeting characters
And then Minnie would like meet two people
Take photos and then leave
And I swear it felt like she was going to the bathroom
That's I swear I
Said this I said it feels like Minnie
Has diarrhea
And something
Is preventing her from just
Finishing these 12 people
And then like closing the meet and greet for now
She kept coming back and going
And I was like something is wrong with Minnie
She should just go home but she's a trooper
I hope it didn't happen in the costume
If that is what was happening
But something was up
Maybe they had to switch Minnie's
Like somebody had to go home and they had to find a new Minnie
But it felt like there was a start and stop to it
And then like
My daughter like runs up and meets Minnie
And I'm like oh man I hope Minnie isn't like
Really sick
That would be a bummer
Although I guess you know any germs aren't coming through the snoot
Or the costume
Or diarrhea isn't coming through the costume
So I don't know
Obviously no one is going to tell us that
But that was my speculation
But yeah we should try to figure out
The Indiana Jones I should have done that before this episode
We're going to have to do Indiana Jones 3
I'll be back
In a couple weeks maybe I'll check it out
Ask the guide
And post a picture
And you yeah
Make sure you save up though
As far as urine to go
In these bathrooms I'm talking about
In Star Tours bathroom and Indiana Jones
I drink a lot of water so I'll probably be okay
That's great
The Tiki room bathrooms
Are right by the entrance
Anyone can use those
But those are like single occupancy
They look like the 60s kind of
I like that
They've changed them a little bit though
I tried changing my daughter in these the other day
And they don't have changing tables
But there's only just two sort of family
It's good
Privacy but there used to be a little bit
I think there was like a stall and a urinal
And now they're just two
Lock the door you have the whole bathroom of yourself
But that is a good bathroom to go to
Because most people don't do that
The entrance right before you go in a Tiki room
You left two bathrooms
You have total privacy there
That's a good place to go to the bathroom
And that's what you get from listening to podcast
That's right
All these secret bathrooms
Exposed
Secret bathrooms exposed
We have been threatening to do a full bathroom
Episode and maybe that comes next year
Maybe we do that
We rank bathrooms
You rank how private they are
How comfortable, how nice they are
Guys
It's year seven
We got to stretch this thing out
More and more
Carthy circle though is maybe my favorite
In park bathroom off the top of my head
So let's go
Let's go back
Enter the temple, the temple of the forbidden eye
Mara is the god
Is the character in the ride
It's the big head
But Mara is also represented a lot of places in the queue
And I didn't realize this that the big stone skull
That's the big reveal of the temple
That is Mara as well
It's a decaying skull of Mara
Of the god itself
Who is angry at you
For looking into its eyes
Let me pull up a picture of Mara
This is right when you get in the lobby
This is a picture of Mara
A nice looking picture
First of all, does this picture look familiar to either of you?
No, not to me
Okay, because you breezed by it
Because you're so mad at the light
Jason, does this look familiar to you?
This picture
I believe so
You're all in the temple
The only reason I ask is just because this ride
Is still packed with such cool stuff
I was like, I don't even recognize this
And then it's like, it's the first thing you see
When you get in the queue
It's like the first thing you see
And I was like, geez, there's just so much cool stuff
Okay, so the whole idea of the ride
This is a little recap, but I should say, go back and listen to Indiana Jones 1
We do cover the basics of it
But I will repeat it here again
Is that Mara is
Basically going to offer you
Eternal life
Ultimate knowledge
Or ultimate wealth
As long as you don't look at the idol's eyes
So here, this picture is supposed to represent
All of those things
There's jewels and money
Over here
This eye, I think, is supposed to be knowledge
And then I guess this water is supposed to be the fountain of youth
The fountain of youth
It's not future knowledge
See the future
It's seeing the future
Oh, sorry, yes, you're right
Seeing the future
So Mara's pouring out the fountain of youth water
But all this to highlight
I'm like, this is awesome to me
This is such a cool piece of art
That really feels authentic
To some old temple
I'm going to look for it the next time I go
Look for it
Just give it a nod
If you learn something on Podcast the Ride
Or hear about it
I just want you to look at something, you go nod
And then if you're feeling really excitable
You nudge to your significant other
And you go, hey, take a look at that
And then they go, yeah?
Okay
And then you keep moving through
That's all I ask
Our job is done
If that's what comes out of
Listening to Podcast the Ride
So there's just a ton of that stuff
There's little things, and we talked before about how
There's like secret language
That is written all over the temple
And for a few years they gave out
The decoder little cards
That you could decode what the actual writing was
And most of it is like
Just like, be careful
Don't be aware
It's mostly warnings about Mara
Be scared of Mara
Don't do this thing
But it is cool that it's all there
But friends who grew up in Southern California
And were kids
Were very excited about those
Decoder cards
And did make the time pass a little
In the temple
Yeah, that feels like
That feels like a thing
And they've kind of, they put it on an app
One of the Disney apps or whatever
Where you can do it now
But that does feel like an old, like 30 years ago
You could occupy a kid by handing them a little piece of paper
And then saying like, oh, look at the wall there
And decipher what
I assume, like my daughter's brain is probably
Fried already from screens
We've just
Decimated that thing
She's already got ADHD probably
And that's not going to play so well
But I think there is some sort of app component to it
Where you can learn
What it is on your phone
I don't know if it's Play Disney app
I don't know if it's a Disneyland app itself
But there's some way to still see all of it
And then they also have all these things
Constructed to make it look like
Somebody is actively working on
This temple
Which I think is a very cool detail too
The temple is in construction as well
Like there's some great
I don't know, I guess it would be a painter
Painting these images of Mara
Which
I like that it feels like
We're still working on it
Like we're coming into an active site
Because the narrative of the ride is that
They've turned this
This is what we learned in the first episode
Sala has turned this into
A weird tourist spot
Where he now is having to send tourists
Into the temple to earn money
To keep this thing going
So you were part of some weird
Pyramid scheme that Sala has
Concocted
Which I totally forgot about
That we talked about that
Like I thought we were just
Looking for Indie and I think that's
What it became
But it's confusing because that is part of it
And then we also on the other episode
Also talked about how Michael Eisner
In a special said that they moved
The temple from India
That's the narrative, we moved the temple from India
To Disneyland but then on the ride
You're just supposed to be in India
So some wires got crossed as far as what the official
Narratives of some of this stuff was
What do you think is going to happen when this ride
Opens in Animal Kingdom?
Do you think the queue is going to be the same?
No
I think it will be a whole new
Ride elsewhere
They usually
They have a whole new story
Kind of a new set up
Are you excited for this
Indiana Jones
Attraction coming to Animal Kingdom Matt?
Very excited, I think Dinosaur
Sucks
I think at a certain time it was excellent
But now you ride through it
It's like they've known for years they're shutting this shit down
So much doesn't work
So much is blacked out
It's unfortunate because it was
At one time such a fun
Innovative attraction
But it's time to go, I do think it's interesting that
How old is this ride?
Almost 30 years old
Just about
That they're
Bringing us a 30 year old attraction
So I wonder if there's going to be some updates
Because obviously technology has changed
We do a lot of cool things
But I don't ride this ride
Now and think it's outdated
I think it's going to do a great job
It's held up
I think it's going to be
They said a totally new story
I think the queue will be way different
I wonder if they keep it
As a museum
Because you start out in a museum type way
So I bet they keep that maybe
And do something else with it
I could be wrong, we'll see
I think it's going to be a totally different story
I think it'll be probably
How
Tokyo is like different story
But it's kind of the same
It's like this will be somewhat
I think it will be way different than that
I'm guessing, just because there's been so much time
And why not do something a little bit different
Have you both done Tokyo?
Yeah I have, Jason hasn't
I have not
Have you been to Tokyo or no?
No I haven't been
We got to get Jason there
I say it every time we record
Disney Sea, it's like
People ask me about Tokyo Disney Sea
I try to explain it like this
I'm a psycho, and I'm sure you guys are as well
Sometimes I have dreams
About fantasy theme parks
Or dreams about fantasy toy stores
Tokyo Disney Sea is like
You woke up in that dream, but it's real
It's unbelievable
I can't even explain it to people
I was trying to tell this to my mother the other day
And I was like, no you don't understand
It's a different thing
And she's like, well I think I understand what you're saying
You don't
I was getting defensive before she even
Pushed back on me, and I don't know why
But I was like, Sinbad
You'll be reduced to tears on Sinbad
And it's special because of the song
But it's at a ride
Yes, but no ride has ever made me cry like this
Yeah, it's not
It's not quite explainable
The thing also
I was thinking about this cue
Oftentimes when we're talking about
We wish Disney would do a Horror Nights maze
To do a Halloween maze
In this line
It might not make
It might break some sort of code
For putting performers in small spaces
But this is the ultimate
Horror Nights maze
In a lot of ways
It's dark, it's cool, it's twisty
It's perfectly themed
Without even the ride
You are walking
In the most highly themed maze
You've ever been
So even though I'm like, Disney doesn't
Other than in China
Which they have done a little bit of this
Disney hasn't done any crazy mazes
That's what this is
This is perfect for it
I wish they would around Halloween
I know they won't, but I wish around Halloween
Look, wrap up a couple people as mummies
Have them pop out
Jason could be involved
He could dress as a mummy, or Brendan Fraser
Either one
Demanding coffee, yeah
I want to get a little more scared even
In this queue
And I want to get more use out of it
Because I think the way that the line has been set up now
People just breeze through this
And at least let
Some young scare actor
Yell at me
While I'm going through
It kind of reminds me of the Kong in Universal
Yes, yes
That's true, because they did have scare actors
And then they stopped that, I believe
I believe they did
I don't know if that's in the real queue
I feel like a real snob on this
You are, well no, but that's Scott's role
Is to be the one who says
I don't care about the lines
I just want to go on the ride
So you're filling a void right now
But I do appreciate a good queue
A good pre-show
Some rides just wouldn't be anything
Without the pre-show
Yes
Well it depends, I mean
Rides are placed in the park
The way everything is set up
There are so many other elements that
End up, even taking a ride
From a B to a C or a B to an A
If there's certain
Ways to frame it
Rock and roller coaster, even though it's cheesy
And you may not like Aerosmith
But if it didn't have
Some of the pre-show elements
I don't like the ride as much I think
Even though that ride is pretty simple
I think the pre-show makes
It's like a wrestling match
If there's no story
It just moves
If there's no connection to the characters
What are we doing here?
Yes, now you can
With wrestling
If the moves are cool enough I will like it
And if the ride is cool enough I will like it
But, doesn't it make it better
Will it stick with you forever?
I don't know, you might forget it
It depends, but yes, I agree
I'm agreeing with you basically
If rock and roller coaster
Outdoor coaster
No theme
I'd go on it once
And go, oh that was really fun
If it's not a long line I won't go again
But seeing Steven Tyler
The launch would be
The thing that carried it
Without the pre-show
Yes, but even if
Even just the idea that you're in the
Even the idea that you're in a limo
Is fun
You need the pre-show to set up that you're actually in a limo
A super stretch
And it's doing a lot of heavy lifting
For a pretty simple
Cheap ride
It's a regular coaster
With just some flats
On the actual ride
It's not even that great
And it does not hold up
That's why I'm a little worried about this Muppets
Just a fresh coat of paint might not be enough
Are you going to be
Going 60 miles per hour
And they play Rainbow Connection
That's what people have said
Even Moving Right Along
Is not a
Song as fast as some punk song
It's not like a Germs song
Or Fugazi
Like Moving Right Along
Or whatever the song Dr. Teeth
Sings
But they also have promised that they're going to have a festival
With modern pop stars
Or something
I think they are going to have some
You're going to get Megan Trainor
Doing a duet with Piggy
Or something on this ride
That's what they're teasing I think
Let me pull up the
Ride
The pre-show video here
The Sala video
Yes
Now a thing I never
Realized, oh you have the whole thing
I have the whole thing
Also can I say
I don't understand how people get these
Sometimes
People go like
Here's Captain EO
This doesn't look like it was recorded off a phone
This looks like a master
Who got this
Especially the pre-show video for Indiana Jones
Who stole this
Has Disney arrested them
Did a cast member sneak this home
That's the only way I can imagine
It being procured
Jason were you saying something
Play the video because I think
The thing I have will make more sense
After the video
So you're seeing Sala outside the
Temple of the Forbidden Eye
And he's letting a bunch of
People that look like old timey
People onto the ride vehicle
Onto the jeep
And there is a boy that looks like Alfalfa
From the Little Rascals
We talk about Little Rascals
I feel like on this show a lot
But I've never seen a full episode
But I am smart enough to know that
That is clearly Alfalfa
That is an inside joke for all the
Little Rascals fans
I've never noticed it
So the ride goes on and there's a picture of
Sala that looks like
He's been caught doing something bad
In the car, in the jeep
He looks like this is the police
Have found him
And he's pantsless in the ride vehicle
And here he is, he's been caught
It looks like he's taken a number 2 in the bathroom
Well, thank you for cutting to the chase
It looks like he's taking a shit in the jeep
It looks like Bigfoot
It looks like a blurry photo of Bigfoot
Yes, let me pause it
The reason I'm showing this even
Is because there are these pre-show
Videos that become iconic
Like the Soren one
Everybody knows it, they know the lions, they know the characters
It's very well known
But this, I think the placement of it
Because it's up high and it's in such a
Big cavernous room
That some of this stuff doesn't stick
With you
That these images don't last with people
As much as something like Soren
I was going to say
To me, I've never seen this but I clearly have
If I've been on the ride multiple times
It's always playing when you're in that room
And I just think it gets lost
Because there's so much going on
How have I not noticed Alfalfa
I should have noticed Alfalfa
But the video itself is really great
And deserves probably more love than it gets
Well, this is the thing
That sticks with me
He's holding a sign that says
Take heed
And then there is
A picture of like an adult
Dweeb
Who just keeps
He does look, clearly
He's looking at the idol
And then he becomes a skeleton
Yes, so it looks like
Alfalfa from The Little Rascals
Father is
On the ride and is on the ride with his son
And he is following directions
But Alfalfa's lame
Dweeb father is blowing
It for everybody by looking into Mara's eyes
They're not getting any of the prizes now
Because Alfalfa's dad fucked it up for them
The video should end with
Alfalfa's dad getting beat up
I think the thing
That I didn't know
I don't know how I never read this
Is that
That is Jonathan Rhys Davies
In
The pictures
But the voiceover is an actor
Named Bob Joles
Like it's someone else doing
A Sala impression
Really? Why wouldn't he
Do his own voice?
That's weird
I have no idea, but I saw his name
Mentioned multiple places
And he's like a go-to voice actor for Disney
Is it like Michael Jackson
On the Simpson episode
He would sing, but he would use his regular voice
Maybe he wanted to appear, but he didn't want to talk
I don't know
Because he was in the opening special
Or
We've heard a couple times now
Stories of people who do
The pre-show videos
And they do the whole dialogue
They do the day, but then Disney fucks up the audio
And they have to go back in and re-dub it
And this is like
These are major shoots
You would imagine they wouldn't mess the audio up like that
But we've heard two of these stories
Where they do all their lines
And they have to go back and ADR it
Oh my god
Yes, which is a nightmare
Harrison Ford is not the voice on the ride
No
I was hoping that maybe
I want to get Harrison
There's pictures of Harrison and Calista
And the kids
On the ride
He knows it exists, come on Harrison
Just give him a microphone
While he was actually at the ride
And say a couple of lines
Say it real quick
Or when they signed him for the
Star Wars movie
And he also made a deal for Indiana Jones 5
Just say we're going to replace the actor
And you have to do these ten lines
I'm sure it's a lot of money
I'm sure it's not an issue of can he do it
How much are they going to pay
He can do it
I don't know if he's going to be on the house
I'm just saying they should have done a deal
When the contracts were written
They should have done the Downey Jr. deal
That he just got for doing Doctor Doom
Where now he's going to go back
And he's going to do Iron Man in all the parks
That's what they should have done
But maybe they weren't thinking
Like that back then
Should have happened on the set of Dial of Destiny
I watched that last night
I watched Dial of Destiny last night
Because I hadn't seen it
And I'm like okay
We're doing the Indiana Jones recording tomorrow
Let me see if this gives any additional depth or whatever
And the answer is not really
It's fine
I don't know why it was so long
Because the first few are under two hours
And then with Last Crusade
It's like two hours and two minutes
And then Crystal Skull is like two hours and eight minutes
And this one was nearly two and a half hours long
Might have been over
Might have been pushing three hours
And I'm like I don't know why they did that
My take is also
They got a little cocky in that first section
Of the movie with that de-aging technology
The technology is not there yet
So you would want to hide it a little bit
But oh they're shining a flashlight
On his de-aged face
And you're like I can tell
That he's not that young
And his voice is not that young anymore
So I'm not sure why they were doing that
Oh well
I maybe just didn't like the passage of time
Like everyone just looks so old
You're saying
Yeah well I don't like the passage of time
In general so
I agree with that
But Sala and spoiler alert
Marion
Everyone's older
It depressed you
The movie depressed you
It was a little depressing
I mean I like Mads Mikkel said a lot
I thought he was a good villain
And I like Phoebe Waller-Bridge
I don't know why there was a kid
I couldn't quite
Follow why there was also a kid
He was fine
He was a fine actor
But I'm like there's a lot going on
I don't think they're going to
Add the kid to the Indiana Jones adventure
I think that's what you're getting at
No
We're already behind
Let's get to the big thing also that made me want to do this
A couple weeks ago
There's a plank that says
Send to Club Obi Wan
Which is a reference
To Temple of Doom
Yes that's a fun thing
Club Obi Wan, Temple of Doom
That's a club they go to and there's a little reference
That's like the type of reference you'll get at the Jock Lindsay bar
There'll be a sign that says
Go to the Club Obi Wan
Now if they opened up Club Obi Wan
That's cool I would love that
But they're not going to do that
We talked about this a couple weeks ago
In our Disneyland App episode
There is a disagreement about
What eyes
You can't look into
When it comes to Mara
Jason believes that
There's a couple
When you get in the ride vehicle
You've loaded
There's first a little Mara head with a blindfold on
And then you're presented with
Three different doors
And those are the things that represent the different
Gifts you could be given from Mara
Those doors used to move
They have not in a very long time
That's broken as well
It would give you the illusion that you were going
On a different path even though it was the same path
Every time
So those are sort of stuck with
They still do different
Projection mapping and different effects
Depending on what the gift
You may receive is
But the doors themselves don't move anymore
I was wrong
Because the new one makes it
Perfectly clear that it's the big
Mara you're not supposed to look at
So but in your
In your defense
I don't think this is an uncommon
Misunderstanding
I saw a lot of people online
Say they thought the eyes were the ones
Before you enter the big door
Now I think I on
A text chain with Matt and Len
Ask this question
I'm name dropping again
Forgive me but I believe
I don't neither of you
Actually had a good answer for which eyes you thought
Was the right I had no idea
What the hell you guys were talking you didn't know what I was talking
About right so that
I guess is another that's a third category
Some people don't even remember
The eyes some people don't care I think Scott
Knows the eyes but maybe Scott if you were here would say
What the fuck are you talking about what eyes
But I saw a lot of people online
Say that those eyes here let me go let me
Show you what I'm talking about I'll jog your memory
Please show me these eyes
You got to see the eyes because that's the whole point of the ride
Is that you're disobeying
What Mara is saying
But
I think
The new effects make it really
Clear and I think it's
Also a joke you can't
Practically drive
The car without looking straight
Ahead at this giant
Monolith thing
So it's a trick
Right okay so you have this Mara face
That's right before you start the ride and it's got a
Blindfold on okay and that's just
To remind you like don't look into Mara's
Eyes and then the ride starts
And then you're oh yes are you there at Sala
And this is the maintenance door that you never go
Down and then here you see the three different
Doors that rotate
They don't rotate but they used to now
I'm defending Jason here a lot of people thought
That these eyes were the ones not to look into
But you know
These eyes are not the eyes you see they open
Here okay so then
Obviously you go in the big room and this is the
Big Mara that's the one where
You don't look into its eyes
That's what I would assume as well
Yes but again there's a lot
Of confusion online or at least a little
I did try
To reach Tony Baxter to ask
Him a question
But there was no response
Damn okay well you tried
Yes I texted
Season pass podcast
Host Doug Barnes who's done
Maybe are the definitive interviews
With Tony Baxter and I
Asked him I said Doug
What eyes are the right eyes
And he said the big Mara
Eyes are the eyes so that's as close
I've gotten to a full confirmation from
Somebody involved in the project
Which is not a person involved in the project it is somebody
Who's interviewed a person involved in the project
I think this is a version of like
Adding some special
Effects adding some new technology
Helps sell
The story even more
Because
The projection and the music
Sting and the
The crazy
Indie with
Trying to close the door with a big vortex
Thing behind it
Is right after this
Here's what I'll say also
I'm not a huge fan of
Projection I'll ask you guys
Projection mapping in general Scott actually
Said on the original Indiana Jones episode
That he was not a big fan of
Like turning the castle into
A big present or something
You know it's making the castle look like something else
With lights I don't
Love it they do it at France
And they do it in the tower of terror
Is now a big gingerbread
House or something or it's it's like
Supposed to be a scary hotel I do like it during
The tower of terror is like a gingerbread house
I mean I don't hate it but
I just there's something about it where it's like
I wish it was on a building that was
Less scary like it doesn't feel appropriate
It should be scary
Stuff on tower of terror and then it
Should be I don't know there's not a big building
They could use but
I don't know there's something inappropriate
About it to me I don't know
I think my bigger problem is that oftentimes
I feel like it doesn't look
So good and maybe it's because there's too much
Light but like sometimes hard to make
Out what it is
Like I'm like oh is that Jeannie coming out
Of a window
Oh wait no that's Hades
But they're too blue but is he a window
Oh no oh no it's Stitch never
Mind but I'll say it about projection
Mapping on Indiana Jones is awesome
It looks so good
And they've done it they've even redone it I feel
Like in the last 10 years since they started doing
This it really looks amazing
And I think it's probably because it's dark
And they can control the environment but man
This clip Mara looks like she's melting
I think heightening the stuff
That's already there is
What I really like yes they're
Not painting a face on Mara with lights
They're just you know accentuating what's there
Already but look at that that's like the liquid is literally
Coming off the effect is effective
Yes the effect is effective
But even more
Effective way than any projection mapping
I've seen it's plussing up the ride
As you guys would say it really
Is yes I feel like
This the lightning effects in
This room have been improved over
The years have been upgraded over the years
Yes and I
Think I like that
I agree yes the
Lightning is very cool so on the right
You get to the part where the Jeep takes the hard
Left and you get the big reveal of the whole
Temple and sometimes the effects aren't working
But still this shot of seeing
The whole temple is the biggest wow
Moment I agree I'm with you and even
The AT-ATs are really cool
On Rise of the Resistance
And I was very excited I'm not trying to
To shit on it or anything I'm just trying
To think of other spectacle rides but this room
More than anything in Rise of the Resistance
Still gives me the feeling of like oh this
Is 20 miles long
This is I can't tell where I
Am or how far it goes it's it's unbelievable
And like you said there's so much to
Look at even the AT-ATs
You're just looking right there this you're like what
Am I looking at here where am I going because you kind
Of see some of the track you're like what
Am I what am I in store for here
Yes and also like you're getting to
See an overview of the whole temple
And you're going to get to see
It from a bunch of different angles which is
Something we talk about all the time we like to
Look at rides from different vantage
Points so you're going to get
To see the ride all over
You're going to get to explore it
Really thoroughly which is
Really fun and satisfying and like the AT-ATs
Like you do get another view of them from
Up but man it really feels
Like you're exploring every part of this
Place. Are these flames projection
Or real flames I don't I don't quite remember
Or is it a mixture? I think it's a
Mix of it because like when a new Jeep pulls
In to the actual temple a fighter should
Shoot out of that like one of the eyes of the skull
But a lot of it I think is just
You know orange lighting and to help
Accentuate the feeling of things on fire
I think it
Can be really effective if triggered
Right. Yes
I agree and it makes
A noise too that it's
Like a hiss I can't even describe it
Really well I should try to find it somewhere
Which it's not as scary as
The snake and the hiss because that's closer
To you but it is still sometimes that
Like can kind of get me a little bit like
A mild jump scare I'm not saying
I'm going to like freak out but
I go ah you know just like a quick one
Let me ask you this
As far as the ride
System itself you know it
Fucks you up a little bit it's
Which I like you know I don't think we've ever
Discussed it but I do you know I'm a listener of the show
I want to feel like I'm in a little
Bit of danger on these things
Right okay so you agree with me
Yeah
These ride vehicles are so
Unique I mean they've used them on the Indiana Jones
Rides and Dinosaur but they're
Not using it a ton
And it's hard to even imagine
Like what you would use this
For what other kind of rides
Like the trackless wifi stuff
Makes sense like there's a lot of applications
For that but this
Feels like it like it has to be like a
A rough jeep ride
It has to be a rickety road
Unstable terrain and that's
The only way you would want to use this
Well if they were ever to do a universal like a Jurassic
Park a new Jurassic Park and you're in the jeep
Oh yeah that's true
Because even the boat ride
I mean that almost makes zero
Sense it should be a jeep
Right yes but it is
Like the ride vehicle still feels like
Really unique to me and yes
It gives you it messes you up a little bit
Which is really
What you want on some of the stuff
Sometimes
So we should talk about there are
Different like little variations on the
Ride like sometimes
The car will stall
A little bit and make different noises
Sometimes certain effects will get triggered
Depending like I saw some
Like there's a bunch of little
Things that happen now I think this is smart
Because sometimes the ride will
Just break down or there's another
Thing happening like a ride
Vehicles it's taking a while to empty it so
Your car gets stuck on a bridge or something but
It's hard to tell if it's one
Of the randomized events happening
On the ride or something's
Wrong because this happens all
The time where I go oh we're stuck on this
Bridge for a while
I go maybe that's one of the randomized
Things is like your
Car won't start because that's you know they keep hearing
The ignition sound effect which
I think it took me a couple years to even realize
That was fake
That's just a sound effect
Obviously there's not a real
Car turning over
I just didn't think I didn't it's not that I thought
That it's just I never thought about it
You were like oh that must be
It is a great effect
To buy time if there's a delay
Like oh your car stalled out
That's what I'm saying where it's like
I still to this day I'm not
Sure what is like what is an
Effect when it's just not working
What is an effect that's randomized and
When is it like oh shit like somebody
Had a medical emergency at the front of the ride
And you're stuck now
But I'm like oh wow they really randomized
This thing this is awesome
I'm getting a totally unique ride now because
Of like I don't know I still
Don't know and I can't find like a definitive
List of all the different options you have
When it comes to this stuff
Like I think sometimes maybe the snake doesn't
Like hiss at you but
Usually it does
But again this would all be answered
This will be answered in Indiana Jones 3
With Tony Baxter
We'll have to get Tony
For one of these things
Okay let me let me get to
The new stuff
So I got very excited because
And we've talked about this before Tokyo
Disney has their own Indiana Jones
And they have stuff
In probably the most criticized
Section of our
Disneyland version
There's a room at the end with the blow
Darts or whatever you would call it
It's kind of just painted like skeleton
Man on the wall
And it really feels sort of unspectacular
Especially after what you've just seen
And yeah and after that comes the ball
And that's the big amazing thing at the end but you're still
Like ah this room feels like it'd be better
It is better in Disneyland
In Paris I was going to say Tokyo
Don't get me started on the Paris
Indiana Jones ride
Holy shit
Next
It's just an outdoor coaster
Yes it's horrible
Yes so
Over a year ago at this point they were like oh my god
They added stuff
To Disneyland
And I was like holy shit because what happens in Tokyo
Is there's a section where you turn around
A corner and
There's nothing there in the Disneyland version
But in Tokyo a fireball
Shoots out of like some sort of
Idol's mouth at you
Using a very similar effect to what they do on Big Thunder
Now when there's a big dynamite explosion
On the last lift hill
So I was like holy shit they're doing it
They're fixing the dead space
So I don't know if you guys have not
Been on this since they fixed it
So
When they say fixed it I don't know
I don't think it's fixed
That's what I'm saying
Well they got rid of the projection
Of a branch with rats on it
Yes which we call
You called out specifically on our first episode
Is that they used to do a thing with
There was a shadow of a branch
And a rat was running on it
And it would like jump off the branch
And that was supposed to like make you think
Oh there's a bunch of rats in our car now
I don't know
I didn't know what that was I didn't know what that was supposed to be
Until maybe Jason told me
They've gotten rid of it
Which is good is a plus up I will say
And they've added
Okay this is what they've added
They've added some weird like kind of
Electricity
Now I don't know what that's supposed to be
In the narrative of the ride
Like lightning demons or spirits
Or something
I mean what is a lightning demon
Is that a demon made of lightning
Fair enough
I mean I guess that's pretty self explanatory
Now that I think now that I asked the question
So then you turn
A corner and like okay that's fine
I don't hate that I'm not mad at that
So this is the part I'm like oh this is new
This is new and they made like
Basically a little like doorway
And there's two
Flame like I don't know what you call them
You know
Torches
And speaking back to
When Matt said no screens
There is a screen here
That basically just shows like
Rocks collapsing
And then you turn the corner
Into the room
I just criticized
And I will say kind of a let down
Yeah a little cheap looking
Kind of cheap looking
I get what they're going for
But I don't know
That it's so much better than the rat
You know
I mean I'm not mad that I said I'm mad the rat
Is gone but it's a little bit
Underwhelming considering
What you know you could get in Tokyo
And I know that's a common
Thing to talk about
Is well man you should see what we get in Tokyo
But
Yeah so that's there I'm not mad at it
But it is adding a screen
To Indiana Jones
Which kind of taints it a little bit doesn't it?
Yeah
It's like why do we need to add a screen there
It almost like dates it in a way
Because like so many times when you see things with screens
In the era that it was made
And Indiana Jones is so timeless because it's big sets
I feel like
That thing isn't going to last long
A lot of the stuff in like Haunted Mansion
Where it's like the projections
It takes me out of it
Like you said it's no longer timeless
It feels like you said the year
It was introduced
Yes and I'm like oh that's like
It almost made me
A little sad I was like oh don't remind
Me that this has to be like
Tied to an era
Now I'm sure
I don't know well they'll maybe upgrade
Things but I could see this in ten years
If they never give it another budget
That screen is going to look really weird
And I hate to harp on it it's such a short
Thing
But it tainted our beloved
Indiana Jones with a little screen
I don't know Jason do you feel anything about this
You haven't been on it so you haven't seen
The screen first hand to feel the sadness
That I felt
You know I like the blow dart room
I think the audio
The audio
And the air puffs works
For me I think it's a thing
In these kinds of adventure movies
That it's like oh it's cool to see that
Even if it is a cheaper version
So you're a blow dart room
Defender
I'm a blow dart room defender but I understand what you're saying
About screens I think I like the
Lightning spirits
Even though they're kind of
I'm not quite sure what that is
The lightning demons
Your words not mine
I like the
Lightning demons more than I like
The door collapsing
Sure
Again I don't hate
You know what's funny though it made me reevaluate
The blow dart room
Because I was like I guess at the end of the day
I'd rather have some like
Day glow looking
Like
Miniature golf course style
Skeletons painted on a wall
Than a screen
You know what I'm saying
It made me reevaluate on some level
The blow dart room and I go well
I'd rather maybe have this
Than some screens on here
Unless the screens are really fantastic
So I don't know I don't think you're ever going to be able to do
The full effect
That I want from Tokyo but
I don't know I'm sure they know
The imagineers know that section needed
From something and they're doing their best
Maybe they got a modest budget
And maybe they'll continue to do stuff as
The years roll on
And maybe if Indiana Jones 6 of Harrison can get out of bed
And do another Indiana Jones
We can get some more stuff
I would like one more
You know what I want three more
Oh come on now we're pushing it
I want him to be 90
Oh my god stop it
I want it to be mostly
CGI
I want it to be replacing
A young actor's face with Harrison Ford's face
I do want to ask this ending scene
Yes go ahead
I get a little confused trying to
Imagine the space of this scene
What do you mean the ball
The ball rolling
The ball rolling and then he's standing
In the rubble of the ball rolling
So what exactly is it trying
To convey
What
So the ball rolling is what an illusion
That's a great job at that
It's amazing and we talked on the first one
About how your jeep
The walls are
Moving it's a big part of it
But you go down
Do you find a tunnel
Or an exit
And then you're looking back at where the ball
Shattered a wall
I see what you're saying
I think I'm overthinking this
It reads
I know what you're saying
Your jeep go in a little secret hole
And then turn a corner
And see the ball
Are you supposed
To have gone underground
And then you're seeing the aftermath
Of the ball smashing through
The earth or something
I think so
And if that's the general
What you're supposed to take away
Fine maybe I'm
Overthinking it
I think you're probably supposed to be like
Right at the last second
You found a little part of the
Hill your car drives through it
And then
The car takes a right
But maybe in the imagination
You're just supposed to have turned the car
Around to see what happened
And Indy is there with the ball that's broken
And he has not been killed
He's fine
I think the ride
There's just no way to do it
Because you can't go down turn around completely
And see a broken ball
I think it's just logistically there's just no way to do that
Right yeah okay
This is generally what I thought
But the more I thought about it
As I was watching these videos
I was like am I missing something
Like in the way
I was looking at the wrong eyes
You know
Or it's something like kind of headier
Where it's like you do get crushed by the ball
And you die
Or you're like in purgatory
Or you're in heaven
And you imagine that you got out safely
And that Indiana Jones is there
And then you leave
I think that's a little too deep I don't know if that's it
I think that's probably a little too deep
But you know
A great art is open to interpretation
Sure
I guess another thing
We're well past the snake room
At this point
But watching it all over the years
In the snake room he says
Like snakes
You guys are on your own
That's not his line
He's supposed to say snakes
Why did it have to be snakes
Now at the end he says
One of his alt lines is like tourists
Why did it have to be tourists
So
Did we say this on the first episode? These are some of the shittiest
Line reads
I've ever heard
He goes snakes
You guys are on your own
The take they got from an actor
Maybe it was a one taker
He only would do one take maybe
I don't know
Maybe they had a tight budget
Maybe it's the take that survived
If they've had so many errors with the audio
But where's the urgency
Indiana Jones is in a room full of snakes
He's trying to get all these tourists
The indie is cool
But he goes
He would be like snakes
You guys are on your own
You would be a little more like that
The thing I didn't bring up on the first episode
Where is he
Where are we hearing him
Saying this from
Is he just like stuck in the temple somewhere
Maybe he's got himself
Is there a PA system
In the temple maybe
That Sala set up and he's like
He's just giving you directions
Also not very heroic
You got a bunch of dumb tourists in a car
They're there because of Indiana Jones and Sala
And he's going
Hey my hands are clean
You guys get the fuck out
It's a snake come on
I know he's afraid of him
But he's generally a hero that would even step up
I feel like to help a bunch of dummies
Alfalfa and his father
Get out of a bad situation
I feel like it's a little out of character
Also for him to say that
That is also very funny
In the new Indiana Jones
Where they encounter
Eels that are like snakes
And I'm like
What is the dry
Erase board where they were doing
Okay there's no snakes yet
But the eels could come
In the diving sea
Eels it looks like you guys are on
Your own
I hate eels
That is like a knock off
Indiana Jones
But do you think if the movie was a hit they would replace this big snake
With a big eel
Maybe
It depends on how much money the movie made
And that would have been a big change coming
Is that the big snake is going to be a big eel
Well maybe in the animal kingdom version
Oh very true yes
It could be all based on
The last Indiana Jones
It could be okay you open up
You open up in the ride
Let's brainstorm this real quick to end this episode
You start in Indiana Jones
Sad old man apartment
Just like in the
New movie
But then you get a mission
From Archimedes himself
Okay but I was going to say
Maybe slow down and you go through his mail
And see if you get a social security check first
And then
You learn about all the people in his life
Who have passed away
And then
It's depressing oh man that's a depressing way
To start the ride
It is a depress but it is accurate to the film
Indiana Jones
Indiana Jones meets the dinosaurs
Was the way to go and I don't think they're going to do it
Indiana Jones fighting dinosaurs
Back in time was the way to go
And it would have worked great for
The overlay of dinosaurs
They could have kept some of those animatronics
That's what I'm saying I'm smart I'm thinking budget wise
But yeah they'll probably
Indiana Jones is going to find
I don't know what does he find in the movie
He should find Crystal Skull
The dial he finds
He finds the dial of destiny
And they travel back in time to the
Battle of Syracuse on the island of
Sicily
You were really paying attention to this
He just watched it yesterday
I watched it like 12 hours ago
I watched it like
15 hours ago
I think more of a Temple of Doom
Would be my way to go
For the new Indy
I'm a big Temple of Doom guy
This kind of gives me Temple of Doom vibes though
A little bit? Yeah it does
There's for sure references to it
Even scary
It's similar to the scary
Climax of Temple of Doom
It's a lot of fire
It's a lot of scary stuff
It's less horrific than Temple of Doom
Disney's not going to do that
They're not going to pull a heart out of a man
I don't know if that's necessary
Kids do go on this attraction
But it is scary
At 13 I think you're ready to see a man
Get his heart pulled out of his chest
That's just
That's coming from a father
These kids aren't going to go on the
Encanto attraction
And then they're going to walk
Half a block to watch a heart
Be pulled out of an animatronic
Then they could sell
Hearts in the gift shop
Which by the way
I don't even consider a gift shop
Because it's not attached
Well that is a thing
Yes, that's a good point
The gift shop in a similar way
To Haunted Mansion
The way Haunted Mansion was out here
The gift shop is far away from the ride
Which I'll be honest
It is nice
To have that difference sometimes
Because it does feel
I don't know
I'm torn
Sometimes it's nice to get emptied into the gift shop
And exit into the gift shop
I want to impulse buy something
So you wish there was a full gift
Well you did
You bought a couple of things
That's true
Maybe I'd buy a whip
Something
How many more hats would they sell
If it was right off the ride
So you're saying that maybe
You're so jacked up
After the ride
It wears off by the time you
Walk across the way
We almost got
Slaughtered by this
Rolling giant ball
We're on this high
But then by the time we get out of there
Maybe we don't even see that gift shop across the street
Right, you don't even know it's there
And you've heard the Glenn Miller music
And now you're so calm and relaxed
Because that's the place I want to take a nap
Maybe you have a rush to get on another ride
After you walk
A half a mile back to Adventureland
Yeah
Gift shop
I think Disney is just
Sleeping on sales
Don't you think it would take a little of the class
It feels like a classy ride
Because it doesn't have the gift shop right there
Well, but if you theme it to like
Sala is trying to make a book
Hmm
It looks a little
Haphazard, you know
Yeah, and they sell a couple whips
Do they sell a whip? Can you get a whip in the park
With a child?
You used to be a few hundred percent
You can buy a crystal skull
Not crystal head vodka, a crystal skull
From crystal skull and it's like hundreds of dollars
You can buy like the artifacts from each movie
I don't know if they have a dial yet
If they do
I was just there, I should have checked to see if we could get a dial
I want a dial
I'll keep you posted, I'll be there in two weeks
Okay, let us know how many dials they have
And if the dials are selling well
Because I suspect the dials aren't moving fast
But I think I would keep the
I would keep the gift shop away
That's my opinion
Okay, fair, fair
Like Haunted Mansion, they of course
I don't know if it will be open by the time you're there
Haunted Mansion has built a separate house
Right outside the exit
And I know some people are mad at the scale of it
I have yet to determine if I think that's right or not
But it's
That feels okay to me
Because it's close to the exit but it's not in the ride
Okay, fair
I'm getting some of the classiness of the ride
But there are things
I mean look, Rock and Roller Coaster you exit
Back when you could buy Aerosmith merch
You exit right into the concert
You're buying your Aerosmith merch right there
I had some drumsticks
Yeah, I mean I got
Scott, I have a GeForce record producer
There you go
Yes, I have it just on the other side of the stable
So
I am pro
Gift shop at Rock and Roller Coaster
Indiana Jones
Anyway, there's so much
Indiana Jones is amazing
I hope every seven years we come back
And talk about it
Because it deserves it
Matt Cardona, you have survived podcast the ride
Oh man, thank you so much guys
Please exit through the gift shop
Now, plug away
Now is this gift shop attached or is it across the street?
Since it's
Well, since it's your gift shop
I guess you can choose so I guess it's attached
That's what you want
Whatever the guest prefers
Guys, follow me on social media
At the Matt Cardona
If you like wrestling figures
Collectibles, I also have a podcast
The Major Wrestling Figure Podcast
And we sell our own figures over at
CollectMajor.com
And if you see me at Disneyland in a couple of weeks
You're allowed to say hi, but I'm on the clock
With that VIP tour, so don't chat too long
You know what I'm saying
You gotta make it quick
Can I real quick, I've said this before
I think the people want
Jay Leno, Kevin Eubanks
Wrestling figures, I truly in my heart
Believe that
I would love a Jay Leno
If you can get him to sign with
With Major, I'm down
Okay, send me some paperwork
Look, he's got the garage out here
We need to try to interview him
One of these days
Because Jay with the blue
That blue t-shirt
And Kevin Eubanks, so his band leader
Had the cut off sleeves
He looked good, he can interfere to the match
I'm not against
Jay has to be first
I know obviously Jay is the bigger name
But Kevin was such a part of that match
The Hogan D&P match
Sign me up
I think a two pack with Jay and Kevin
Is what I want
I want a Michael Eisner
We need a Michael Eisner
Figure
Give us something
Somebody made us a custom Michael Eisner doll
That I have in the closet
Over here
We need official
We've tried with Michael Eisner on the show too
But he needs to sign with you guys as well
I would love that
Matt, if you move fast
You might be able to
Beat AEW
And get the Rizzler, AJ and Big Justice
I will say
They have left me on
Left on red
I slid into the DMs
That's like Tony Baxter with me
That's what
Knott's Berry Farm is doing to me too
Oh no
So you feel my pain
I bet Jay
We can get Jay to sign on
Let's do it
As for us
We're on all the socials
Go to Patreon.com
We have bonus episodes
On a variety of topics
We just watched a weird Thanksgiving parade
That's half Macy's Day parade
Half a weird parade about Goofy
Where he's also a dinosaur
And he golfs
It's a very strange parade
But anyway, Podcast the Ride
At Patreon, that's not the website
But you understand what I'm saying
Jason, anything else?
No, the website is
Patreon.com slash Podcast the Ride
A long time
Even though I think you've texted me
What are these episode topics?
You don't have to subscribe
I'm not offended
I'm going to stay subscribed
Why are you guys talking so much about Jay Leno?
Anyway
Again, you can cancel anytime
I won't
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson
Scott Gardner
Brett Bohm
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest
ForeverDog news by following us
On Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
And liking our page on Facebook