Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate where today we're getting into the spirit
of the season.
Merry Christmas, that is.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by my Carlson and Grimace when I made that joke.
No, I was grimacing at the folksiness.
Oh, okay.
It was just like an overdose of folksy.
Yes, it is an overdose of folksy.
I'm also adjusting levels too, so sorry I'm a little distracted, but yes, an overdose
of folksy at the top of this Second Gate episode.
Yeah.
New experiment by Spencer's Gifts, the parent company of Spirit Halloween in the new chain
of 10 locations, Spirit Christmas.
Right.
Is that how you would have intro'd if you had hosted like a Prairie Home companion?
Sure.
You would have started with something like that?
Yeah, with the Lawrence Welk Show or something like that.
That really would have gotten them rolling in the aisles.
Don't you think you would have been a little too, the Lawrence Welk Show's a little too
edgy for you, maybe?
You're looking for more Prairie Home.
It seems gentler.
Lawrence Welk, high energy.
Oh, the bubbles?
Yeah, the bubbles, there's so much going on.
Prairie Home is such a warm bath of a show.
That's true.
That I would think, yeah, maybe you would get too worn out from the energy, the high
paced action of the Lawrence Welk Show.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-huh.
So, I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Tell me, you're the expert.
I'm not the expert.
I was just trying to find something in the same ballpark, you know.
Yeah, it was in the ballpark.
Okay.
I'm curious what this is today, because this is something you pitched to me.
I didn't know what it was.
I didn't know what you were talking about.
You could have said literally anything.
I want to do a second gate on Garbage Man Christmas.
And I go, yeah, great.
Whatever that is, let's do it.
Oh, we love Garbage Man.
Garbage Man Christmas.
We both grew up watching Garbage Man.
You know, the spirit of improv still lies dormant in you and I, like a virus about to
unleash on your immune system.
Like chicken pox or something.
Like chicken pox and shingles, you know.
Right.
Secondary.
Sometimes it's just fun to leap before you look.
Yeah.
So you could have said anything.
Like, let's do a second gate on medicine and I go with the concept of medicine and you'd
be like, don't worry about it.
And I'm like, you know what?
I won't worry about it.
You know what?
You've pulled a don't worry about it plenty of times in the past.
So, you know, just trying to follow your vibe.
Don't worry about it.
Please follow my vibe.
Okay.
So Spirit Christmas, there are 10 locations of this that have opened recently.
And it's basically Spirit Halloween for Christmas.
So it's, you know, a pop-up store that looks like it could be packed up overnight, disappeared.
Empty retail space.
This, of course, has become memed in the last so many years, I guess, where, yes, anytime
something closes, there's a Spirit Halloween, like kind of banner type sign, temporary sign
that goes up in front of it.
Yes.
And like, say Sphere was closing in Las Vegas.
It's not.
Thank God.
And I will shudder at the even thought.
But if it did, you'll immediately see pictures of Sphere Las Vegas with a Spirit Halloween
banner.
That's just that's a joke.
Everybody does now because they look for cheap real estate to throw a bunch of Halloween
crap in and then they pull it all out and do it again the next year.
So now I happen to be visiting family in mid October, late October.
My dad was like, hey, the first Spirit Christmas in the country is opening in Maze Landing,
New Jersey.
So all the others were opening later in November.
This one opened up October 18th.
So a few days later, me and my dad and Jane went to go check out the Spirit Christmas.
And this really shows how, you know, you are your father's son because the excitement
about the first whatever retail location.
This is something that a lot of people would go, well, who gives a shit?
This is some temporary Christmas store, but and I'm not I'm I'm in your boat.
I'm not insulting you or your father.
I'm saying this is the this is the same brain that goes, oh, I'm excited about trying Cosmix,
the McDonald's place that you and I lust for, which is just like a little different
drinks, different color sugar drinks than a normal McDonald's.
They'll have boba in it.
They'll put like a little like flavor shot.
So I'm saying it's interesting to see that your father is the exact same way that we
are.
Yeah.
Well, he knew I would be interested in it.
And I, first off, did not buy anything because everyone in the family already has tons of
stuff.
Yeah.
But I took we between me and Jane took a few dozen pictures.
So I've made a PowerPoint presentation for you to Jason has we're sitting.
OK, this is another episode we're recording inside the apartment inside Jason's apartment.
This is the second ever episode.
The first one being points, which has come out by now.
Yeah.
And we're sitting at the kitchen table and I'm looking at an iPad that says we'll post
of course, but it's a very spirit Christmas by Jason Sheridan.
It is presentation style and it is it is on an angle a little bit so I can see it.
And then behind it, the there is a Mayor McCheese.
There is a Funko pop of Hershey Kiss that you got that I got you.
There's Wesley Dodd, the Sandman.
Oh, yeah.
G Force Records producers sign Islands of Adventure opening in 1999.
Yes.
Giant mug.
Holiday in sign that Scott got you, right?
Yeah.
Scott got me that for that my birthday.
Oh, yeah.
You got a lot of stuff going on.
So I'm really getting the full picture.
Yeah.
It really looks like I'm about to do a YouTube show complaining about like D.I. and Wicked
or something.
It's saying yes.
And if and I will say if I get bored during this presentation, I'm just going to go through
your shit.
Yeah.
Kitchen or other way.
Yes.
What I've been dealing with a week is multiple contractors here because our heat is now working
correctly.
And also there was a leak in the pipes in the walls.
So I had to clear out a lot of stuff from my office, which we had just cleaned up a
lot the other day.
Right.
We removed all the like precious items and then these are the the little things.
These are the treasures.
The treasures that ended up out here.
The little treasures.
So but let's let's move on to the slideshow and I will narrate this and we'll figure out
I'll figure out a way to get this online.
I don't know if it's worth just uploading a keynote file to the Patriot or this is in
keynote.
I know.
I suppose the photos, though, you could post some photos.
Yeah, we might not need to download seven gigabytes of a keynote presentation to get.
And then if you have to get an apple to actually enjoy this episode, you have to get an apple
product.
I don't know if you I mean, let me tell you this, you can export it, export it probably
as a PDF.
Oh, a PDF.
Probably.
Yeah.
And it just gives you every slide as if it's a photo.
But I would like to see a very large file be uploaded to our Patreon that makes everybody's
computer.
Of 30 pictures?
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, this is broken up into chapters.
Oh, OK.
So you're weaving a tail.
I'm weaving a tail.
OK, great.
Because as I was looking at all the pictures, I combined Jane and my pictures and made an
album of them and I'm looking at all these and themes started to develop.
Let me stop you right here.
Yeah.
Like, I'm just going to set my expectations for what I think this is.
OK.
Again, I don't know what this is.
Sure.
What would it be?
It would be a Christmas store.
It would be a Santa.
It would be Mickey and Minnie dressed as Santa.
It would be a Frosty the Snowman.
I don't know, Stan D. It would be some animatronics is like, you know, you have those big Halloween
animatronics and they do that with Christmas now.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm just trying to work out what I think is going to be.
So there's got to be something here that I'm not imagining.
I'm guessing big candy canes.
There's going to be a big candy cane.
Yeah.
Different Christmas lights, different types of lights.
Sometimes they have icicle lights.
Again, you're you're you're not incorrect, but there's so much more.
That's great.
I'm just I'm just trying to set my expectations for what is going to happen.
Well, let's start with part one.
OK.
Photo ops.
So this is about what you'd expect.
You know, there's picture of me in front of one of the signs outside.
And there's like.
Me and Jane.
Hold on.
Go back.
I'm going to set the scene for the for the listener.
There's a picture of like I would say like it's not a poorly drawn Santa, but it doesn't
look like a very specific Santa to me.
It's a very generic kind of winking Santa.
He's a cartoon.
And you are kind of resting in his palm, by the way, that this photo looks like.
It's almost like he's giving you a shove, like a playful shove.
Like he's either either him.
He could be hitting you like sort of with the heel of his hand on the butt.
And he's kind of giving you a good one from behind.
It's very exciting.
I knew you would see things that I didn't even notice in these photos.
Yeah, it just looks.
Yeah.
It looks like Santa's giving you a playful shove and he's winking because he knows he's
being a little scamp.
Yeah.
So now it's here's me and Jane at like the folding sign.
Right.
Smaller sign.
Santa.
It looks very similar.
He's not touching you in that one.
Now, here's where it gets to be fun.
There's photo.
There's like.
OK.
Stepping repeats and photo.
So I am standing in a big pair of boots, Santa boots with candy giant, what would you say?
Peppermint lollipops around.
Yeah.
They're like kind of peppermint style and then they have sticks on them.
So yeah, it almost looks like a peppermint with a stick and a big backdrop that it doesn't
look like they ever finished stretching out.
No, it's just a big like sheet with a couple like Christmas type houses.
Like if you're at Santa's workshop and these this foot, this foot, I don't want to call
it an illusion.
It's not an illusion, but this foot.
I guess it kind of is where it looks like you're wearing Santa's boots.
It's the same thing they do at a bubblegum shrimp where you sit by that bench and you
have a shoe.
You put your feet in the shoes.
Feet in the shoes.
Yeah.
There's a big suitcase there as if you're forest.
Is that what it was?
I think so.
Well, it's the chocolate box.
Yeah.
And his sneakers.
So yes, it's forest.
Now, this these shoes or boots from Santa make Santa look like he's seven foot eight.
Like he's massive.
He's like Andre, the giant size here, because these like the boots come up to your mid thigh
and like you're a shorter gentleman, but you're not two and a half feet tall.
There's like a step behind it.
There's essentially apple boxes behind it.
And I'm trying to stand in there and like manage a cane.
So it is the optical illusion is not perfect.
This is like the Santa in red one.
The Santa is fucking jacked.
Oh, yeah.
I would know more details if I had seen it or if anyone else had seen it.
Well, look, you can go see it right now and you can be next to a theater playing Wicked
and everyone doing the Tarzan.
People are excited about Wicked.
This looks also like this photo op was set up in like, like in the like, I don't know,
like foyer of a rest home.
It is set up in between two sets of sliding glass doors.
This looks like an old folks home.
Yes.
OK.
So go ahead.
Go ahead.
We'll see if Jane's is a little better on the other side of the room.
She's a gingerbread person.
OK, great.
And this is sort of just she's not inside.
She's behind this thing.
Just behind it.
So this is basically a photo op with a headless gingerbread, what made out of plastic or some
kind of material.
And that's fun.
I will say that's fun.
Yeah.
It's very colorful and it's a little scary, but it's scary.
Because, yeah, it looks like, you know, your human body is all gingerbread and then you
have a human's head on the top.
I mean, imagine that in real life.
Yeah.
Imagine you pull a tray of gingerbread cookies out of the oven and it's just cute little
gingerbread bodies and then there's human heads.
Human heads.
And they're realistic.
Well, hold that thought.
We'll circle back around to unusual gingerbread creatures.
What if it was like, hold on, I'm really just brainstorming here.
It's gingerbread cookie.
But then you've also cooked little pieces of chicken that look more skin colored for
the heads.
OK.
And then you can really like detail, like red and stimpy detail the eyes and the mouth.
So you're you're just creating a body horror like gruesome creature.
Yeah, exactly.
Because I'm inspired by this photo of a hybrid is a hybrid.
It is hybrid.
Yeah.
So because the boots like, oh, isn't it fun to wear Santa's boots?
Yeah, fun.
But isn't it fun to be transformed into half person, half gingerbread to like a five foot
tall gingerbread person?
So you'll get you working on this half chicken, half gingerbread cookie soon.
So right inside the store, there is a big sign and a little, you know, simulation of
a village called Gingerbread Lane.
I don't know if the simulation, I think it's more just, you know, a little, a little, a
little town, a little version of a town.
But this is, I think, what you were getting at earlier.
Lots of Christmas stuff.
Here's a fake inflatable Rudolph.
Exactly what I thought.
Where we go.
It's bigger.
Oh, he would be afraid of this because this is big, oh, big, big, big, big, big, who is
Brown?
For some reason.
No, I don't know.
Hmm.
I always think of him as green.
I don't know if he's green in the original movie.
I guess he's kind of cream, white-ish.
Okay, but this is what I thought.
Yeah, these are big inflatable, fun things.
They look a little cheap, but okay, they're fine.
Yeah, this is just kind of one corner.
Okay, they're big, but they're big things in a small room,
so it's good thing Scott's not here.
It's a good thing we're Scott-free today.
Good thing Scott's, this is Scott-free for sure.
Because he would be peeing in his pants.
Okay, we have arrived at part two.
Sorry, I'm taking over your hosting duties.
Part two, all your friends are here.
Okay, how many parts are in this again?
I believe four.
Okay, so we're almost, this is almost halfway.
We're almost at the intermission.
Well, part three.
Oh, that's the big one.
Part three is the big one.
Sorry, I'm getting ahead of myself.
So it's like Wicked in a way,
except there's four parts, not two parts.
Because Wicked is a very long first part movie, they say,
and then there's a second part
that's also gonna be very long.
So this is your version almost of Wicked.
Yeah, okay, so we got some fun socks.
Okay, yes.
We got Christmas Pickle Rick.
We have Buddy the Elf.
Yes, from Elf.
One just says Nutcracker.
We've got Garfield the Cat.
Yeah, and he's wearing a Santa's outfit.
He's wearing a Santa's outfit, SpongeBob.
Okay, he's got a Christmas sweater on, right.
I've seen, yes, socks, okay.
Scooby.
Okay.
Scooby-Doo down at the bottom Christmassy.
Got it.
Okay, now your favorite Christmas friends.
You know those weird CG Sour Patch Kids?
Well, they're trying to make them a thing.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Yeah, yeah.
Weird CGI Sour Patch Kids, what do you mean?
Like from the commercials,
the current commercials for Sour Patch Kids
is little freakish Sour Patch Kids.
What programming are you watching
that is advertising Sour Patch Kids to you?
I feel like, you know, just cable.
Cable TV, or like-
I feel like I haven't seen-
Before the movies?
Maybe I've seen a chocolate commercial
or something recently,
but I feel like I have not been advertised
Sour Patch Kids lately.
I feel like they were kind of trying a little something.
They were trying-
To class up Sour Patch Kids
for the adult, the sophisticated adult.
I guess so, or I guess just like,
hey, don't forget about Sour Patch Kids.
Sour Patch Adults is how they should market it.
They shouldn't be kids.
Oh.
If you want me as an adult to,
not me, not me, but like one, an adult, normal.
Like a tasteful minimalist packaging.
Like how Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen
became like the coastal jazz lounge or something.
So yeah, Sour Patch Adults would appeal more
to the working person.
I guess these are supposed to be stocking stuff.
There's a lot today.
I mean, I still hear, these are characters,
I've seen them on the boxes of Sour Patch Kids,
because I do look at the boxes of Sour Patch Kids
from time to time.
So yeah, I mean, I don't care for these characters.
Well, you've got some big like candy.
You will see these at It's Sugar.
Like It's Sugar at City Walk will have a lot of merch
of these characters no one cares about.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, prove me wrong, audience.
If you give a shit about the Sour Patch Kids kids,
let us know, but I don't know,
is there one person on the planet
that has any affection for those characters?
You remember those gerbils who used to drive the Scions?
What?
Like 20 years ago.
The gerbils who used to drive the Scions?
They were creatures, or like the Quiznos,
like little creepies, little ghoulies.
Who's the Quiznos creepy?
They talk like this,
and they kind of look like a raccoon or something.
What?
The Quiznos creepies.
This is probably going back 20 years ago.
The Scion gerbils and the Quiznos creepies.
The Quiznos ghoulies.
Quiznos ghoulies.
Was it Fuzzbucket style?
They did kind of resemble Fuzzbucket a little.
Oh, okay.
So those was like almost like a little,
the Quiznos spung monkeys?
No.
Is that what they're called?
I didn't know that was there.
What were the Quiznos creatures?
Mr. Potato Rats?
They were called Hell Lemurs
and the weirdest corporate mascot of all time.
I kind of remember this.
Yeah.
You're looking at almost like a stretched out,
printed out copy of a picture of a gerbil
with the mouth and eyes cut out and human eyes.
Of like thumb wars,
like a thumb war kind of face.
Yeah, but more scary than that.
Oh my God.
This is kind of the era of funny because it's weird,
funny because it's random,
like the berries and cream.
I'm a little lad who loves berries and cream.
Quiznos spung monkeys.
S-P-O-N-G-M-O-N-K-E-Y-S,
spung monkeys.
And this is a thing that I did not write
Quiznos spung monkeys down.
I was truly just trying to think like,
oh, maybe he'll remember this ad campaign.
Spung monkeys.
Oh my God.
Well, I was worried that we weren't going to have
anything good for Scott when he came back,
but Quiznos spung monkeys.
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
So you're saying that,
do you think that the Sour Patch Kids are worse
or better than the spung monkeys?
I mean, I think they're equivalent.
They're just kind of like little creepies.
Yeah, they're creepy,
but they're not on the level of these spung monkeys.
They're not.
But like.
Yeah.
No, thank you.
I say to these.
Folks, if you know what the Sour Patch Kid,
like little Sour Patch,
CG Sour Patch Kids are.
Why aren't they just Sour Patch Kids?
Yeah, they are,
they are the Sour Patch Kids.
Like the voice we were doing, I feel like.
Did they do that?
Or they're dead silent.
You're the one watching these commercials
for Sour Patch Kids.
You're the one watching programming their advertising candy.
I don't know, I feel like they've seen it before movies
or I've seen it like when A.W.'s on.
I guess you would have seen it when A.W.'s on.
I guess, I mean, maybe I'm not paying attention,
but I'm wondering what you're watching that,
unless it's just completely targeted advertising.
Cause I love Sour Patch Kids.
And the algorithm just knows
that you need to see Sour Patch Kids ads.
But they have to be called Sour Patch Kids.
Why would they be called something else?
They are the Sour Patch Kids.
Exactly.
Well, let's get back, let's get back.
Here's just a rack of gingerbread houses, kits.
You know, you have the peanuts,
which is just kind of like a standard gingerbread.
Wouldn't you think it would be Snoopy's house?
Well, is that-
Like his little dog house?
Is it, it's not his dog house?
I don't think so.
I can see his windows and there's a chimney
and Snoopy does not have a chimney on his dog house.
No, maybe he has at one point in time.
Yeah, but then there's not as much fun.
I mean, I guess, yeah, it should just be his dog house.
But there's a chance that that's just some generic thing
that they slapped the peanuts logo on.
Yeah, exactly.
So it's a bunch of bullshit.
Here's some other treats.
These are like just like larger candy and cookies.
Jason is just showing me a photo of like Twizzlers
at the checkout line.
I'm just, I'm just painting a picture.
Wait, did you say heightening?
I'm heightening.
We're starting low.
But this is D heightening,
showing me that you can buy a little like a personal bag
of chips ahoy by the-
Yeah.
Okay, all right.
Okay, here's kind of knickknack gifts.
It's a coffee mug that looks like a full pot of coffee.
Okay, is there a fire hydrant right there?
I, this, I believe you fill it with beer
and then you can dispense your own beer.
I don't know why you- Out of a fire hydrant?
Do that.
I think it's just a dispenser.
It looks like a fire hydrant to me.
What does that look like?
It says tap room.
Can you see it?
Well, that looks like a crystal skull to me.
It is a crystal skull whiskey tumbler.
Okay, if you didn't buy any of this.
That looks like a fire hydrant full of beer.
There's the beverage blaster.
You can put beer or liquor in this gun.
It's a gun.
It shoots beverages.
That's right.
Okay.
These are tall like,
tall nightmare before Christmas cocktail glasses.
Okay, let me take stock of what we got here.
Yeah.
Okay.
This all seems pretty normal to me.
Except for maybe,
I mean, the weirdest thing that we've talked about
so far is spung monkeys.
And that's not involved in this spirit.
Right.
A spirit Christmas.
It's all about to change.
Okay. Right here.
Okay.
But we're not even in part three.
So these are kind of a ghoulish Christmas ornaments.
Okay, okay.
So spirit is taking the spirit of what they do,
which is Halloween.
Exactly.
And they're infusing it into Christmas.
So you're showing me holiday ornaments,
gingerbread man.
He looks like he's been tortured.
A piece of his brain is coming out.
Yeah, kind of a zombie.
There's a skull and crossbones,
but the bones are candy canes.
Right.
So, I mean, it reminds me a little bit of like Shrek
when the gingerbread man is being tortured.
Like there's precedent for torturing a gingerbread man.
There's a Santa.
And what is he saying there?
I believe he is saying-
Hold on, I gotta look closer.
It says, fuck around and find out.
That's right.
And that's how we get into part three.
Christmas laughs.
Christmas laughs?
This is the meat of the game.
Okay, okay, okay.
This is the meat of the thing.
So now we get into bawdy Christmas sweaters.
Oh, because, oh, you said this.
You said Spencer's Gifts is the owner of spirit.
Yes, Spencer's Gifts is the parent company.
And if you don't know, folks,
if you're not a human being that's around our age,
Spencer's Gifts is still in malls across America.
Yeah, absolutely.
I've seen a number of people post online,
like the mall I went to as a kid is dying,
except the Spencer's has not moved in 20, 30 years.
And Spencer's, I mean,
I was in a Spencer's fairly recently
and you can buy wild stuff in a Spencer's.
You can buy regular Rick and Morty t-shirts,
but you can buy like lingerie and dildos in a Spencer's.
Like they really, it's still sort of lawless in there
and it's tucked, there's one in the Galleria
over in Glendale.
Right.
But they are an outrageous store
and they are getting away with it still in 2024.
That's right.
And they're even more outrageous at spirit Christmas.
Okay, so you're showing me these sweaters
and it's Santa on a like traditional looking
Christmas sweater.
And it just says, ho, ho, holy shit, I need a beer.
And next to that is another sweater.
And now these are kind of takes
on the ugly Christmas sweater trend.
And it's a bunch of red solo cops set up for beer pong.
And it says, just here to get my balls wet.
So it's, you're playing, it's not a beer pong.
You're playing beer pong.
That's how it looks.
And then this is just here to get my balls wet.
Now, who is buying these?
I don't know, but it gets worse.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
You're going too fast.
Slow down, partner, you ain't racing yet.
Yeah.
Let's see, do you know how,
well, first of all, I think they light up.
Oh yes.
A number of these have tags in the corner
that say light up.
So you've got an electrical current running
through your shitty Christmas sweater.
And how, do you know how much these are?
Did you check this price?
I think they're anywhere from like $30 and up.
Okay, $30 is not so bad.
I mean, I would say $50 for an unwearable sweater
is too much.
$30, okay.
But even just analyzing, where do you wear this?
I think you wear it to one party a season.
What party?
Like a boozy body party.
I guess if you're with the boys,
if you're with the fellas, then you can wear this.
Well, you gotta have something for the ladies,
like too pretty for coal.
Too pretty for coal, is it in coal?
It's a little vest.
Okay.
It's a little brown and pink vest.
What the fuck does that mean?
What does that mean?
Like, I'm too pretty, you can't give me coal,
even if I've been naughty.
So the adult woman has been naughty,
but she's like kind of maybe making goo goo eyes at Santa.
Yeah.
And saying, Santa, you don't give me coal
because I'm too pretty for coal.
I'm too pretty for coal and I'm black out drunk
like everyone else at this party.
Uh-huh.
Okay, well again, what part, like what party,
I guess this is-
This is an official office party.
I was gonna say, this is at least,
this isn't, this is no obscenity in it.
This is pretty clean.
Yeah, so I guess that's okay.
I just mean like, listeners,
do you have a Christmas party or a holiday party
you go to where like your uncle is wearing
an obscene sweater?
Yeah, this is, you know what,
I think that's a big market,
is the uncles wearing bawdy Christmas sweaters.
Kind of like, or these I guess would be the aunts,
the tiny vest sweaters that say Santa's little hoe.
You didn't buy anything from this place?
Come on, you didn't buy a Santa's little hoe?
I'm sorry, it's Santa's favorite hoe.
Santa's favorite hoe.
And the other sweater, which has mittens on it-
Oh my gosh.
On the chest that says tits the season.
Okay, let me take a look.
Tits the season, okay.
Who is buying this?
I just like, again, first of all,
cause I have like one,
I have a Ninja Turtle sweatshirt.
Pretty fun.
It's Christmas, they're like decorating a tree.
I wear it once a year.
Yeah.
Okay, but I could wear that to most functions.
This is such a limited amount of places you could wear.
I mean, if there was a bachelorette party
maybe happening during Christmas time,
this would be perfect for it.
A seasonal bachelorette party.
A seasonal, which I don't know if that exists,
but that seems like that might be some fun.
If you're maybe getting married in February
and you want to go to Vegas in December
and you just want to proclaim that,
hey, guess what?
Hey.
I'm Santa's favorite hoe.
The F1 Vegas Grand Prix is going on as we record this.
You could wear this.
You could wear these.
It's going to be a little brisk
and it's stuff that's already decorated for Christmas.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
And maybe you want to wear this one that says,
stop staring at my package
and it has a little present above the crotch
on the very bottom of the sweater.
So it's like a three, it is not a picture of a package.
It is like a little like plush package over your wiener.
Yeah, and similarly next to it
is a sweater that says certified freak
and Santa's got his jacket open
and there's mistletoe on his crotch.
Which would just be on someone's belly.
So the illusion doesn't work as well for that.
Why didn't you buy the certified freak one?
I don't know, I didn't.
I took a small suitcase.
Where would I wear this stuff?
I'm engaged.
I don't need to be signaling this sort of thing anymore.
Do you think I was saying that you needed to do this
so you could signal to other women that you were a freak?
That's not why I want you to wear it.
That would be my only assumption
that you would wear these things.
This seems like it would be worn at the one college party
before or after finals and then it would get destroyed.
Like this all seems like body.
Destroyed because the women would be coming on
so strong to you, they would tear the clothing off.
Well, because I feel like Keystone Light
just burns through fabric.
Certified freak, hold on, hold on, hold on.
So I'm guessing these are all around 30, $40.
Stop staring at my package.
Oh, okay, set the scene.
How many people are in the spirit Christmas with you?
I would say 10, including three of me and the employees.
Three of me is funny what you're saying.
Three of us.
And there's, okay, so Santa's also hitting the dab.
He's throwing up a dab, right?
He's kind of like, yeah, sort of doing that.
I think it's certified freak seven days a week,
wet and gushy.
It's the radio edit.
Oh yeah, wet and gushy, yeah, yeah, I'm familiar.
I think I've said that on the show before.
Do you think that certified freak is,
let's say, look, hypothetical, you're back on the market.
Certified freak, is that really,
would you wear that out to a bar, to a function
with the Santa, with the mistletoe?
I mean, you're not a super young man anymore.
No.
No offense.
He also has, no, none taken.
He has like red wave hair style laces on.
So, you know, he's ready to party.
Yeah, but what age are you,
what's the age you would wear this?
At 19?
You would have worn this at 19, you think?
Maybe 20.
Okay.
If this was like 20 or $15.
Again, I think these are all closer to 50
because they light up.
There's an electrical current going through them.
Okay, interesting.
Siri wants to get in on this.
I mean, these are gag Christmas gifts.
The store is mostly gag Christmas gifts
and then some legitimate lights and stock.
Can I say, are there vibrators in the store?
There are no vibrators,
but you could get your photo with Santa after Black Friday.
They were set up for Santa and he was there at the opening,
but he was not there when we were there.
Okay, but regular Santa, not like horny or drunk Santa.
No, I don't think he's drunk and horny
and I don't know that he's going to harass you,
but it would be on game.
Right.
With this, a good quarter of the store was body sweaters.
Obviously, of course, there's more.
There better be.
So let's examine.
These ones are very special.
One says, hold my beer.
The other says, ho, ho, hold my beer.
Ho, ho, hold my beer.
The other says, full of holiday beer.
And if you notice,
they have koozies around the waist of the sweater.
Okay, like four.
Like the bottom of the sweater, like four.
So you're going to have some brews.
Yeah.
You can have some high-lifes
and you don't have to go back to the cooler.
Yeah, you could put,
oh, you could put like figures in there or something.
You could put like, you could hold things too.
So I guess, yeah, like they're,
yeah, it's almost like the Ninja Turtles,
like weapon holsters.
Yeah, Leonardo, Donatello, Michelangelo, Rafael.
And then Sue, Reed, Johnny, and Ben, the Fantastic Four.
You could just put them in there.
Yes, that's true.
You can, these are like, I can see,
I can see people wearing this at the holiday function.
Again, the uncle thinks he's being funny here.
Ho, and like no one mentions it.
Everyone's like, oh, it's a little weird, but okay.
Should we talk to him about, every year we're like,
should we talk to him about it?
No, no.
Right, it's a whole big thing.
But yeah, so I get, this is a little bit more
I don't want to say normal, but there's a little more normal
for what you would expect at this.
Okay, so I, I'm just kind of.
You weren't expecting this, huh?
Well, I wasn't, no, I was not,
I didn't know we were going into body territory.
That's not why I didn't expect that, you're right.
No, just wait until we get to the details.
Oh my God.
But first, horny and lit.
There's a sweater.
There's a sweater that says horny and lit.
And there's a picture of a reindeer
with like a three-dimensional antler situation going on.
He's kind of embossed.
He's kind of, or embroidered, he's kind of raised
and there's some fake lights.
He's very raised.
He looks like a stuffy that's been merged
with the Christmas sweater.
It looks like there's a pound of antler on this sweater.
Yeah.
Man, we really, this should be, yeah,
we need to release the full keynote for people.
Horny and lit.
Again, this is a sweater, if it was reasonably prior.
I'm gonna look for this.
I want you to wear this if I can find it online.
Cause I looked up Spirit Christmas
and there's none in the area.
There's none in California.
No.
If you would like to visit a Spirit Christmas,
here are the locations.
Waterford, Connecticut, Dartmouth, Connecticut,
or Dartmouth, Massachusetts, Brick Township, New Jersey,
Marlton, New Jersey, Maze Landing, New Jersey.
That was when we went to.
Woodbridge, New Jersey, Albany, New York,
Bohemia, New York, Poughkeepsie, New York,
and Erie, Pennsylvania.
I'm gonna send your dad $30 in the mail
and I'm gonna tell him.
That's gonna buy two tea towels.
Go to Spirit Christmas and ship me
a horny and lit sweater for Jason.
Please.
Merry Christmas, Michael.
Love, Michael.
I wanna celebrate Jason and Jane's engagement.
Right.
I want a horny and lit sweater.
Horny and lit sweater.
Yeah.
That you're holding it, right?
That looks small.
That's not for like a child, is it?
No, no, no, no.
I think Jane is holding that.
So, yeah, I don't know.
The sizes were kind of all over the place.
Here's another one.
This says North Pole Dancer.
And it has a reindeer pole dancing on a candy cane
and the reindeer has a little bit of lipstick on it.
Hold on here.
Hold on, right.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Yeah.
Let me examine this.
Okay, this is, yeah, it's a regular looking pattern
for a Christmas sweater.
But it says North Pole Dancer.
Okay.
So,
the reindeer, why is it a reindeer
and why isn't the reindeer like sexed up?
I don't know.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I do know what you're saying.
This looks like a regular normal reindeer.
Say regular Reagan bass cartoon reindeer.
Right.
That is like hanging off a big candy cane,
as Jason said, with like a little lipstick.
So they've taken like a normal reindeer
and glued it to a candy cane.
And I don't know if this part of the reindeer
under the head is supposed to be like a chest.
I thought that would just be a normal rib cage
for a reindeer.
It doesn't look like-
It doesn't look like erotic in any fashion.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Maybe they thought they were gonna make
the reindeer have like human bosom.
Yeah, this one feels like a miss.
Like the word play is there.
Everything else was a hit, but this is a miss.
Everything else was a hit.
So, and there's like, they're not in a strip club
looking place.
This just, this looks like animal torture
out at the North Pole.
Well, it looks like the reindeer
is enjoying themselves a bit.
I can't tell that that candy cane is like room temper,
like icy cold.
Well, it would be out in the elements.
I assume it would be cold.
I would think so, yeah.
There are snowflakes all around.
This sucks.
Yeah, this one's pretty-
At least like, now I'm not mad.
I'm not offended by it.
I'm just saying if you're gonna make this joke,
quote unquote, like give me a full on
anthropomorphic hot reindeer woman
who's half reindeer, half woman, okay?
And she's gotta be hot.
Like a creature.
Yes.
Like a hot creature.
Yes, she has to be a hot creature.
And again, I don't want this.
I'm not making the demands because I need to see this.
You're just giving constructive criticism.
I'm a creative.
I was gonna call myself a young creative just now.
That's not necessarily true, but a mid-
I think you're still very young.
You're wearing a backwards trucker cap.
Thank you.
What says Margaritaville on the other side?
Nice.
I'm just saying I'm giving constructive criticism
that if you're gonna give this shirt,
it's just not fulfilling the promise of the premise.
Yeah.
It's confusing.
And I don't like it.
Let me see what the back side is.
And it makes me feel sad for that reindeer.
And I don't want, I want that reindeer to be empowered.
Go back to the other slide.
We're not done talking about this.
I want a human reindeer hybrid woman
who looks like she's having a ball,
not this actual real life reindeer
that is being forced to be glued to a candy cane.
What was that movie like 10 years ago
with the like lab creature, not slither,
it was like a lab creature, but it was kind of horny.
Do you remember this?
It was like a monster movie.
It was like a horror sci-fi movie.
Or wait, Shape of Water is the Guillermo del Toro movie.
No, Way of Water is erotic in many different ways.
Well, Shape of Water is too.
It's a horny-ish, some horny stuff in there.
I mean, it's a little more, I don't know,
innocent love in some ways.
It is.
They do fornicate.
What's her name?
Sally, what's her name?
She fornicates with a fish man.
Oh, in the way, in the Shape of Water.
Shape of Water, Way of Water.
Sally Hawkins.
Sally Hawkins, thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this one, this offends me the most
as a young creative.
Yeah.
As somebody who would come up with a premise
and then try to fulfill it.
Well, we're gonna reset on the next couple,
which are more like goofy uncle.
Okay, okay.
Sweaters.
Got it.
And before we get into a confusing territory.
So, gangsta rapper.
Rapper with a W.
And it's Santa with some Christmas gifts.
Yes.
And he's throwing up a sign.
Uh-huh.
So this is like,
this is like, you know, acoustic covers of rap songs.
It's like, oh, it's a little.
This is the dynamite hack of shirts.
The, what?
Dynamite hack did the Boys in the Hood cover.
Yes.
20 years ago.
Yeah, yeah.
That was on the radio in Chicago.
It's like a me first in the gimme gimme.
It's kind of like, ah, it's a funny swing cover
or Scott cover.
So you're saying this isn't the most cutting edge of ideas.
No, but it's probably so far the least unpleasant
of the sweaters.
Really, you think?
I think the least of like,
oh, people would laugh at this word.
Oh, ha ha, isn't that clever?
You think you're showing up
and you're getting a couple of chuckles with this thing?
Yeah, with your aunts who's a little more like,
oh, I get it.
I was young not too long ago, you know.
You're saying that gangsta rap has been around so long now
that everyone can enjoy a little chuckle or two.
Everyone can enjoy a little chuckle at this.
I will say, at least as premise wise, I understand it.
It's similar and the picture makes sense
to what they're going for.
Yeah, now this one's a little bawdy in a different way.
This is a bunch of weed leaves,
it's a bunch of marijuana leaves on it
and it says, Santa has your stash.
Okay, so Santa is stealing your weed?
Or bringing you weed.
Oh.
You thought he was stealing your stash?
Well, why would he, your, Santa?
For like a gift.
I know, but Santa has your stash,
Santa's gifting you a stash.
Why would it be Santa has your stash?
Well, Santa brings items, he doesn't take items
besides milk and cookies and carrots.
That's what I thought.
Okay.
Yes, that's my understanding is that he brings you stuff,
but this is confusing to me.
Santa has your stash, it just means like,
instead of your normal drug dealer or your dispensary,
this month Santa is giving you your stash.
Yeah, you have to sit and listen to Santa talk for a while
about the, oh man, the North Pole's kind of a bummer
some days, you know, I love the guys,
but it's a lot of work.
Well, the guys are the elves?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love the guys, but.
I love my old lady, but I hate December, let me tell you.
I love January, cause then I can put a bathing suit on
and go to the beach.
We had to make so many nutcrackers this year.
Who's buying all these?
Nutcrackers and wooden horses, that's all we make.
There's like 10, the spirit Christmas stores,
why do they need so many nutcrackers?
Did not see a ton of nutcrackers, surprisingly.
That's the perfect gift.
Yeah, I also, I feel like I didn't see too many nut base,
like nutcracker sweaters.
Wouldn't that be a perfect thing,
like to have an actual nutcracker
that you would crack nuts by the nutcrackers nuts?
Yeah, or like you'd wear one that says,
don't crack my nuts.
And he's got, it's like two nuts towards the bottom.
I'm talking about a practical nutcracker that works,
but it's not the mouth,
which is traditionally where you crack nuts
on a nutcracker.
You crack it at the crotch, is that what you're saying?
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, that could work.
Or are you crushing his balls?
That's what it would be.
Oh, like a nutcracker, could it play audio like, oh.
Every time you want a fresh walnut.
So, okay, picture this, Christmas Eve.
Yeah.
You want a fresh walnut as you do.
As Jason Sheridan does.
Well, I did grow up,
my grandparents did have a big barrel of fresh nuts.
What?
For many years, and we had the metal nutcrackers.
Wait, a big barrel?
A big barrel of like walnuts,
probably like three feet,
and they'd go and buy the uncracked nuts.
And we would crack them,
like with the crab cracker kind of handheld cracker.
So going into your grandparents' house
was like going into a Five Guys
where there was a big barrel of nuts?
Kind of, it was a little more elevated than peanuts.
Peanuts you can do with your hand.
But like walnuts, I guess, hazelnuts.
Was it a wooden barrel?
Was a wooden barrel.
It was three feet tall, full of walnuts?
It was like two or three feet tall.
You just go over and grab a few and get a cracker,
and you'd eat it with your little smokeys
or your broccoli and ranch.
This is before a Thanksgiving dinner
or before Christmas dinner or whatever.
Was there an animal around?
I feel like an animal would get at those nuts.
Interesting, I feel like the only animals
around my grandparents,
I feel like my mom had a bird.
Did you just say mum-mum?
Mum-mum and pup-pup were my mothers.
Have you never revealed
just mum-mum and pup-pup were the?
Those are pretty common East Coasts.
Man, I guess Mitch.
And then my dad's parents,
we call it grandma and grandpa.
It's pup-pup?
P-O-P. P-O-P or pup-pup?
Pup-pup, yeah.
But you would say pup-pup?
Yeah.
Pup-pup.
Pup-pup and mum-mum.
Pup-pup and mum-mum?
If you're saying it fast, yeah.
M-U-M, M-U-M?
M-O-M, M-O-M.
So it was pup-pup and my-mum.
That's how I would say it in Chicago.
But you're saying, you said pup-pup and mum-mum.
Pup-pup and my-mum.
You can say it how you say it.
I'm not trying to shame you for saying it like that.
I'm just trying to figure out what you think the spelling was.
I feel like I go back and forth.
It's like my own last name, Sheridan, Sheridan.
Sheridan?
Yeah.
What have you ever called it, Sheridan?
Occasionally.
Really?
Yeah.
Should I call you Jason Sheridan?
Sheridan is how I normally say it.
But if I'm trying to say it.
I usually hear you say Sheridan, I feel like.
Huh?
I feel like I usually hear you say Jason Sheridan.
Yes.
If I'm trying to say it to someone on the tele,
like a tele, you know, a pharmacist or a telemarketer.
Sheridan, because they get it wrong sometimes.
They write E-E-N and I'm like, no, O-N or E.
So this is my life.
Sheridan though.
Should I call you Jason Sheridan?
No, unless you're calling me
for like customer service reasons.
Which maybe I will.
Okay.
Hey, I don't know what job I'm gonna get in the future.
Oh, that's fair.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on, you just hit me with a bunch.
I was going off into this great comedic premise
and you just threw me off
with like a couple nuggets of history
that mum mum and pop pop had a three foot barrel
of walnuts that you would snack from.
And others stored at tree nuts.
And other tree nuts that you would snack from
pre Thanksgiving meal.
And mum mum is M-O-M-O-M but it would be mum mum and pop pop.
Mum mum and pop pop, I guess.
Mum mum and pop pop.
Again, you don't have to correct yourself
if you just call them mum mum.
I feel like I would say it both ways
if I was just speaking fast, you know.
I like pop pop.
Certainly as everyone got older,
as my grandparents got older,
I don't think they were into cracking real nuts.
What happened to the barrel though?
Huh?
What happened to the barrel?
I am, you know what?
I've been thinking about that this whole time.
Thinking about the barrel?
Thinking about the barrel.
The other, I'm trying to think of what else
was in that house.
A lot of my uncles were in the services in Korea or Vietnam
and there was a ton of military dress uniforms
down in an arm war in the basement.
Oh my God.
And I'm like, what happened to those?
Were they just paused?
You never put them on?
Huh?
I never.
A lot of jokes about you in the Navy over the years.
I never did stolen valor.
Was there a Navy uniform?
I can't remember.
I feel like it was Army and Marines.
But no Navy man's uniform.
No, I'd have to-
That would explain a lot if you could,
you were going over there all the time.
That's why you like good ship lollipops so much.
That's why you're a fan of the classics.
I had said-
The boogie woogie bugle boy, like the Andrew sisters.
I had said you and Gio and Zach,
hey, I found this sailor hat.
We were emptying some boxes today.
Yeah, you thought it was me.
Was this a mic purchase?
I don't think it was.
Yeah.
And so it might've been another sketch
that just didn't stick with me.
And because I have a captain's hat.
And I was like, yeah, Mike wouldn't derank me.
Mike wouldn't send me down to sailor.
How many, you were on what's called mod night
for many years at the UCB theater
where you would write sketches.
Yeah.
So what, six years, you have six years of sketches,
which is one a month?
Yeah, one a month.
Usually we take one month off.
So you have 60 sketches that you've written.
Probably, yeah, probably.
And then more that didn't go.
How many sketches involved someone in the Navy?
I don't know.
For a sailor boy. I wrote a sketch once
about baked Alaska night on a cruise ship.
Okay, that's close.
But a cruise ship that starts sinking
but the Raiders are still doing the baked Alaska dances.
Wait, what?
The big, I must've talked about it.
What is an Alaska dance?
Like when it was on the cruise,
I went on a cruise in like 1996.
My parents were like, oh, it's baked Alaska night.
And the waiters came out with trays of baked Alaska
dancing around with them.
And you can find videos of this on YouTube.
I think some cruise lines still do it.
Other waiters are following behind swinging napkins
and baked Alaska, they're carrying these things around
and then they put them down on a stand by your table
and then they light them on fire.
But they would do a dance.
Is this a thing that-
They would do a dance, yeah.
But is this just for that cruise
or is there a baked Alaska dance?
I think, no, I think it's just like a hup, hup, hup.
Like they're kind of dancing and carrying the trays out.
But this was just for this cruise
or is this how you traditionally serve a baked Alaska?
I don't think it's how you traditionally serve
a baked Alaska.
This is just the fun thing the cruise did.
I think it's a fun thing cruises did.
My parents had been on cruises before
and they kind of knew what was up.
Well, obviously they were like, it's baked Alaska night.
It's baked Alaska.
Which again, you're your parent's son.
It's fun.
We were excited about baked Alaska night.
Well, and we were excited for the midnight buffets.
I don't know if this is still the thing on the cruise,
but the one night was a buffet
where you went through one of the big kitchens.
So you got to pick stuff up
and see all the prep stations and stuff.
My favorite chocoholic buffet.
So it's all chocolate stuff.
It's chocolate mousse and cookies and cakes.
So that would be a night on the cruise?
It would be a midnight.
Every night on the cruise there'd be a different buffet.
Oh, so the chocolate would be,
one night would be chocolate at midnight.
One night would be chocoholic.
One night would just be a standard buffet.
No, chocoholic was one night.
They were all themed.
One night would be like seafood night.
Trying to think.
But wouldn't there be just seafood during the day?
Yeah, of course.
But wouldn't it be fun to eat a full meal at midnight
and then go to sleep on a rocking boat?
I mean, it would, but I'm saying like chocoholic,
okay, I get it.
They're gonna give you all these chocolate delicacies.
Everything else so far seems like,
well, that's not nearly as fun
as chocolate midnight buffet.
You know, I've just watching some cruise ship vlogs lately.
Like there's Guy Fieri branded restaurant on cruise ships.
There's taco shacks.
There's food trucks, you know.
Like at midnight you would have a Guy Fieri meal?
Fieri, whatever you pronounce.
Fieri, I think that's like a quick service.
Like you can go any time that it's open.
But you also want a lot of cruise ships.
You can get 24 hour room service complimentary.
Right.
So like, I feel like I'd be eating chicken fingers
in the room a lot.
Do you think, what do you think is a better dance?
The hot to go dance or the baked Alaska dance?
I'd love to see a version of the hot to go dance
where they serve the front row of the audience
some baked Alaskans, but it's probably not safe.
Can we get, can you release a song called Baked Alaska
and you just steal the dance from the cruise ship
and see if we can make it a national phenomenon?
I feel like that right wing guy is gonna sue me.
Oh, the baby whose name is Baked Alaska?
He's somewhere in Southern California.
Can we change it?
Like a B, it's like we take the A out.
You take it back?
Well, we should take it back.
We take it back.
We use like a Silicon Valley naming
where you just remove the vowels.
That's what I'm saying, yes.
And you just mush together.
Like it's an app.
Yeah.
Baked Alaska is an app.
I was about to say that you,
I was gonna set the stage for like Christmas Eve
where you were looking for a warm walnut
and you went to use a nutcracker that was pants-less
and probably had like a little wooden peen or something.
And then the section for when you crack the nut
was under his little wooden peen.
Excuse me for being vulgar,
but that's what you've introduced in this episode.
I thought it was gonna be above
and that way the peen guarantees the nut splits in half.
Wait, what was?
It bounces off the peen.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
The place.
It's a normal nutcracker,
but it's got a peen to make sure it breaks even.
Like it falls down.
Well, in my mind, the peen,
if we're talking about the peen,
is the part that breaks the nut.
So you move the lever back
and then the peen goes and crushes the balls.
Oh, instead of a jaw.
Okay, I see what you're saying.
Right.
And then you crack it
and you enjoy your warm walnut on Christmas Eve.
And you're of course in your,
you're in your,
I was gonna say your kerchief and your cap,
but that was what mother and father
in the night before Christmas wear.
Right, mine or kerchief and I in my cap or whatever.
That's the line from them.
So you're wearing that,
but you're also enjoying a hot walnut
from your body nutcracker.
There has to be a body nutcracker.
It has to exist.
You could change the picture here.
I feel like I've seen nude nutcrackers
at like each town. Dirty nutcracker.
Yeah, dirty nutcrackers.
Jason Sheridan's dirty nutcracker.
We can market that too, but yeah.
Dirty nutcracker.
I'm not seeing an actual,
I'm seeing like some like mock-up
where like there's an S and M nutcracker.
Yeah, it's gonna be easy.
But it's still like the mouth is where you crack it.
I want something where the-
But how could the mouth be?
Shouldn't it have a red ballgag?
Well, there's one that also has a red ballgag.
Oh, okay.
So you wouldn't be able to use that.
But there's gotta be something here, so.
There's gotta be something.
Okay, well, I was hoping to move on from bodying this
and then I saw what the next pictures are.
Which is a Hooters sweater.
Okay, well, but Hooters is in the scheme of things.
It says all I want for Christmas is Hooters
and it is the brand Hooters with an owl.
It is officially licensed.
It's got the owl.
We are back in the territory of like,
who's wearing this at what party?
And who's still going to Hooters
in enough that there are two sweaters.
The last time I went to a Hooters,
I went to the bathroom at a Hooters,
not to like pervert.
I literally, it was just,
there used to be one at the Burbank mall.
Yeah, next to the sushi place
and this was all built into a parking garage.
Yes, and then it's not, the Hooters is no longer there.
But I, the last time I was in a Hooters
was in Schomburg, Illinois.
Every time I've eaten at a Hooters,
I've gotten sick.
How many times have you eaten at Hooters?
Twice.
In your life?
I think so.
What ages?
Like 21 and 22.
Yeah.
Something like that.
If I told the story on the show before
about the high school teacher
who would always take the graduated students out to Hooters.
I don't like that.
Well, you don't.
I don't know about that.
Would he take the guys and girls?
No, but he was a guy who we think was fired
for stealing a credit card
and calling like a phone sex line
or finding a credit card in the high school
and calling a phone sex line.
But he was also the,
oh, I've talked about him before in a different context
because he would say creepy stuff about my friend.
Yes, and I've talked about that.
Okay, that's what I'm thinking of.
Yes, because we made like a movie in his film class
and he in front of the class said,
I swear he said like,
you got like a hot chick like blank in the hair
and you're not gonna use her more.
And we were like, uh-huh.
And we were all like, oh my God, this guy.
But he would take the students out.
Maybe I did say this to you.
He would invite all the kids out to Hooters afterward
and he came, oh, shit.
I'm gonna have to edit this because it's gonna seem,
well, I don't have to edit.
Basically, he came up to me after,
like at the high school, like senior brunch.
I've told this story, I know I have.
And he goes, hey, let's face it guys, blank's name,
who listens to the show, hello, is hot.
Okay? My God.
And we were all like, and I mean, I already had my like,
oh, let's see what crazy stuff this guy had.
That instinct in me at age 18,
I knew this guy was out of his mind
and I could probably fire him,
but her boyfriend slash now husband
is sitting at the table and I go, hey, Mr. So-and-so,
that's her boyfriend over there.
And he goes, well, I wanna shake your hand.
Yeah, that's awful.
Yeah, that's really rough.
And I was like, wait a minute,
then this guy would take the students to Hooters
and we have a debate among some high school friends of mine
that one of our friends went to the actual Hooters with him
and he claims that that did not happen,
but I believe it did.
And for comedy's sake, I wanna believe it too,
but really, yeah, you went with the-
He never turned down a free meal, you know?
I don't even know that he was paying,
but maybe he should.
There's other guys we know who I like, kind of like,
maybe did go, but we all were like, he invited us,
we were like, we are not going to Hooters
with our creepy high school teacher.
No.
We do not want to do that.
But I want it for comedy's sake,
I wanna believe one of my friends from high school
did do that.
I want to believe that he went with the pervious teacher,
out of a bunch of pervy teachers, by the way.
Yeah, well, we have plenty.
You would think it would be easy not to be overtly pervy
and teach high school.
Just keep whatever awful thought you have to yourself.
But apparently, it's impossible for the type of folk,
older man they let teach high school.
A friend of mine revealed it once.
We went to an open mic night to watch,
I think, as some friends were doing it.
But then this substitute teacher was also there,
playing acoustic guitar and singing.
That's just cool.
And a friend recently was like, yeah, when we graduated,
he asked for my other friend's phone number.
And I'm like, that's not cool.
Even if he was 22, that's bizarre.
That's not okay.
No, well, have I ever said this?
One of our student teachers came and watched wrestling
with us after the school year was over?
That is odd on a number of levels.
And then we went out in the backyard
and we were backyard wrestling and he was there.
And then he was like, oh yeah, chop me in wrestling.
And the funny thing about it was,
he put his hand up as if he was gonna brace.
In wrestling, there's a thing called a chop,
where you would take a guy who basically slaps
another guy in the chest, or whoever, a performer.
And it's just a move where you get slapped,
that's the move, you get hit.
And he put his hand up like he was gonna block it
or something, or take it, this is how you do it.
We were just like, this guy sucks at backyard wrestling.
This guy's older, but I go, he's a loser.
But only because he wouldn't take the hit.
He wasn't tough enough.
Yeah, I know a lot of those guys.
So it's like, why are you hanging out with high school?
Why are you hanging out with the nerdiest crop
of high school students?
I understand in hindsight, it is odd
because there's three or four years apart
when it comes to 22 and 18.
Yeah, it's really not that much of an age gap.
But it makes a lot of difference.
If you just wanna do a LAN party
and play Counter-Strike at the time, that kind of made sense.
But it doesn't, don't do it.
Yeah.
Don't, don't.
Anyway, this sweater vest has the classic Hooters ensemble,
the Hooters waitress ensemble getup on it.
Right, so it's almost like you put it on,
but it's like you're not really wearing the Hooters outfit.
But the sweater makes it look like you have
a Mark Weiner style.
Yeah.
From Weinerville, of course, from Nickelodeon,
where you would have a human head and a tiny body.
This is like you go to Myrtle Beach or the Wisconsin Dells
and you get the big t-shirt with the Bikini Bee body on it.
Right, that's a classic.
Classic.
Everybody can enjoy that.
Okay, now we get into funny socks.
Yeah.
Now these are a little, little small, little harder to read.
We've got Duck Off.
Okay, and it's a picture of a cute little duck.
This isn't even, this isn't even Christmas.
What is this?
Again, this is, some of these areas that were like,
what is that?
Stocking stuffers.
This is like a little knock.
Oh, I see, but nothing Christmas related here.
This is just different stuff.
Yeah, domestic AF, I think that's like a dish towel.
What is, and then that means what?
You're like-
A domestic as fuck, like you're-
I know that, I know that.
Yeah, you're like doing household stuff.
I see, you're like kind of like a housewife,
but it's hard, like you're kind of like a harder housewife
or a house husband.
Yeah, here's one that says go to hell.
And that's all it says, it just says go to hell.
It says go to hell and above it, live, laugh, fuck off.
Why didn't you buy one of these?
You should have bought something.
I don't know, I should have bought you back something.
So this is like for the, yeah, this is for like somebody
who like does all the chores, but they're kind of cooler.
They're kind of hard.
Call me, socks that say call me old fashioned
and has the cocktail on it.
Okay, okay.
Eat, sleep, pickle, ball, repeat.
Well, hold on.
Yeah.
Eat, sleep, pickle, ball, repeat.
So that's just like if you're a big pickle ball player.
Yeah, which attracts a much older crowd,
so would probably be a real hit with the boomer.
I guess, I understand pickle ball sweeping the country.
I am a little resistant to it.
I am a tennis player.
I'm a tennis and then I know pickle ball is very popular
and it's a smaller court from what I understand.
Smaller court, a bigger ball.
Bigger ball.
Kind of a paddle.
It seems like bullshit to me, kind of honestly,
because I'm a tennis guy.
We have a small ball in a big court.
That's the way I know how to play.
I.
If I'll play pickle ball.
Well, look, we can all pull your challenger level skills.
I think pickle ball with the smaller court,
there's a lot less running and stomping
that needs to be done, so it's easier on the joints,
but it is still active.
Yes, it's easier on the joints,
but come on.
Here's a sock that says,
I'm silently correcting your grammar.
So that's the gift for the like.
That's a teacher type.
Unpleasant person in your life or teacher.
Yeah, that's like the English teacher gift.
For the pervy English high school teacher in your life,
get them that and get them like one of the horny shirts.
Here's one with a dog and it says,
dogs make me happy, you not so much.
I was at the buds with pot leaves.
I get that.
I was disneyling yesterday
and a guy was wearing a shirt that said,
I basically like I work to afford my wife's Disney addiction.
Okay, yeah.
And I was like, okay,
and you're wearing that shirt around.
But you, yeah, that's weird cause he bought that shirt.
Well, it's possibly get gifted or a gifted.
Yeah.
So let's see what other socks and tea towels.
Y'all need Jesus.
That sucked.
Okay.
There's one that says the tiny human stole my sanity.
I don't really get that.
For like a mom, I guess.
Mom or dad, you know, sometimes the kids are a handful.
Sometimes your kid.
Yep.
Oh, I should got you those.
They're purple, your color too.
It is my color.
Sometimes your kid melts down outside a small world holiday
and you gotta get out of line.
Sure.
Oh, it's kind of a mess back there.
And the parade was going on.
Trophy husband.
I think that was.
That's cute.
That's a play on of course, trophy wife.
I'm real, I found them.
Do you feel like you're the trophy husband, right?
You should have gotten those socks.
I guess so.
You know, you grimaced hard when I said that.
I don't sew in like that much of a catch.
What are you kidding?
Come on.
All right.
Don't sell yourself short.
Another rack of socks.
I'm realizing in the midst of all these socks,
there was like a bunch of horror figures,
like tiny horror, like they said like
the world's smallest Chucky doll.
It was like an inch tall.
And I'm like, that's just a reason for you to charge $9
for an inch of plastic.
Well, look, I'm a figure expert.
So you would need to show me pictures of those.
But if you have no any of your pictures,
I'm not gonna be able to assess the value of them.
And if I think they're the right price.
My cat thinks I'm cool, grill master, don't be a dick.
Okay, these are pretty standard.
Yeah, these are all pretty standard novelty socks.
I mean, like my favorite salad is wine.
Do we have any of those?
Some classic sock market city walk style socks?
Bitch, please.
Okay, bitch.
And you know what I like the bitch, please.
Yeah, it kind of has a Kodak colors.
Yeah, I like that little rainbow on the bitch, please socks.
Here's a sock covered in lemons and it says, suck it.
I think.
Suck a lemon.
I mean, I guess suck it is like a derogatory.
This is actually using that.
That's not a, that's using sort of a sexual phrase
in like a go F yourself way, not in a fun sexual way.
Here's some socks that say bless your heart,
kind of the Southern fuck off.
Oh, I see.
Here's another pair with headphones on it that says,
go away, I'm gaming.
Oh, okay.
Here's a tea towel that appears to say kitchen closed.
It's pickleball time.
Wait, what's the point?
Pickleball is very popular.
Mine is very popular, but are there people that like
are so obsessed with a pickleball that they need to like
present it on a tea towel?
I guess so.
I'm sure it's playing on like ESPN three or something.
Maybe.
Bless this shit show of a home.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, there's the rest of the pickleball.
Is the rest of this just the gag gifts
that you would get at City Walk?
Don't make me poison your food, says one towel.
Is that a Phantom Thread licensed towel?
I wish it was.
No, that would be a bunch of mushrooms.
Oh, right, right, right.
This is just poison.
How much Phantom Thread merchandise would you buy
if it existed?
Oh, I would love. What would you want?
Novelty Phantom Thread.
I would love like the Phantom Thread characters
drawn like the Beetlejuice cartoon characters,
like a 90s.
You would want an animated series Phantom Thread.
Yeah. Figure series.
Alma and Woodcock, you know, all the guys.
Could you pitch on Phantom Thread, the animated series?
Well, cause like obviously they'd have to have
further adventures.
Well, he's got a lot of dresses to make.
Right, so they would just get into different antics.
Would it be period?
Would it be the period or would you put them in the 90s?
Would it be like Yo-Yogi?
Where all of a sudden Yogi Bear was wearing 90s clothes
and there was 3D episodes and it was like rap music.
I think what you're pitching is Phantom Thread Jr.
So like Woodcock Jr., like James Bond Jr.
Yo Phantom Thread or it could be that if you wanted like,
if you wanted a clean way in canon to explain why
Reynolds was in the 90s with, you know, a neon,
a colored clothing, I suppose.
But it would, so yeah, what year does Phantom Thread
take place in?
I think it's like the 50s, isn't it?
Is it? I thought it was before that.
Is it earlier?
It could be earlier.
Maybe, I can't remember.
I've seen it once.
Forget it.
There is a New Year's party in it.
Right.
But I forget what year it says.
But they don't even have a television,
I don't think in Phantom Thread, right?
No, I don't think so.
So I think Phantom Thread, new Phantom Thread,
another Phantom Thread.
The New Adventures of Phantom Thread.
And it's, and it's like, that's the start of the theme.
And it's a cartoon.
I like that.
I like, I think we've really stumbled
on something interesting here.
Hit on a lot of a new intellectual properties today.
What I think is funny that's happened on this episode
a couple of times where I feel like I've thrown on
a very good premise and you're like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Well, enough of that premise.
I'm just excited by my little slideshow.
I understand.
I'm trying to split the difference.
I don't want to lose track of these pictures.
But there'll be like, I'll be like, I'll be like,
okay, here's this, this is funny.
This is funny.
And you're like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I want to read a tea towel that says like,
I wish I had wine for dinner or I wish I had wine
for breakfast.
I'm gonna read the tea towel with a bowl of Froot Loops
that says, I can't adult today.
I understand that.
That's still going.
I'm not saying we're not getting to it.
I'm just saying the premises are rich.
I think we're-
These are rich premises.
I think we're both bringing a lot to the table today.
I didn't say you're not bringing anything to the table.
Don't misunderstand what I'm saying.
Well, as we wrap it up,
we'll be able to revisit some of your favorites.
Hopefully we can.
All right, what else do we have here?
These are all cocktail napkins that are like, body.
Oh, come all you thirsty.
Okay, does it say, is it C-U-M?
Is it, what is it?
No, it's not that body.
Oh, there's a line they have to draw
at the spirit Christmas.
Have yourself a merry little cocktail.
But is it regular cocktail or is cocking?
Yeah, no, these aren't, we've gotten away from sweaters.
This isn't body then?
This isn't dirty.
This is just kind of the stocking stuffer contingent.
Here's some gift bags with swearing on them.
Well, could you wanna read them, please?
Fa la la la la, let's get fucked up.
This one's clean.
You wouldn't buy one of these.
Why didn't you buy one of these?
This is exactly what you didn't ask for.
Okay, I guess that's kind of funny.
No obscenity in that, but it's rude.
It's beginning to look a lot like fuck this.
That really seems like you're just making this up
off the top of your head, but they're there, they're there.
Merry go fuck yourself.
Jingle, does any of, okay, let me guess.
Jingle Bell Rock, fuck you.
Wrapping is hard.
The 12 days of Christmas, go fuck yourself.
Santa got run over by a cyber truck.
Go fuck yourself.
Is that on there?
No, I'm trying to read this one.
It's really tiny.
Chestnuts roasting on a fucking fire.
Eat my ass.
I'm just trying to throw these out here.
I'm just trying to, I'm gonna guess.
I'm gonna guess from now on.
Rudolph the red-nosed.
Bitch?
Bitch.
Rudolph the red-nosed asshole.
Rudolph, some of them, you don't wanna make them too clever.
You really wanna make them very, very simple.
Right.
Yeah, cause that would be, how many more?
There's only a couple more slides.
Little drummer fucker.
Little drummer fuck boy.
Oh, too clever though.
Oh, little, oh yeah.
It's good, but it's too clever.
So that could be a guy wearing like a Speedo
and he has a drum, but he's got those sunglasses
that are just slats from the 2010s.
Yeah.
Like party boy in some gelled hair.
The little drummer boy is like a little fuck boy.
Little fuck boy.
Little drummer boy on F-Boy Island.
You would do that.
You would wear that, I think,
if we could get that mocked up.
That could be under the umbrella.
Matt Massani introduced the idea of big Jason t-shirts.
If we could make these under the same label.
That I think would definitely be big Jason t-shirts.
Old King, when was it?
Whence's loss?
Okay, I found, I was able to zoom in on the one picture.
It's like a gift card holder.
It says, it's got a checkboxes on it.
It says naughty, nice.
And the one that is checked says, tried my fucking best.
How about this Old King, whence's loss sucks.
Yeah.
And then he looks like a loser.
What do you, would you know
what Old King, whence's loss looks like?
Would I know that?
Yeah.
If I saw Old King, whence's loss on the street now,
would I know what he looks like?
No.
But I guess it's just, I'm critiquing now.
I'm like, how would you know a fucked up one?
But it would say old, it would say it on this shirt.
And he looks a little busted.
He looks a lot busted.
Oh, he looks really busted.
Like he has this, like a body sweater on,
but it's so dirty, you can't even read it.
Was there a play on whence's loss?
Like whence, whence to?
You're going too far.
I mean, that's too clever.
Old King lost at slots
and he's just sitting at a slot machine.
That's pretty good.
And that's pretty good.
There really was in gambling once,
despite this being 20 minutes outside of Atlantic City.
Right.
Did I already said Santa got run over by a cyber truck?
Well, that one's good.
I like that.
That one's topical.
You know, Elon would retweet that
with the like crying emoji.
Maybe he was laughing at those at the UFC event
that he was at with the-
Oh, when he was pretending to laugh
at something to make Trump notice him?
Trump and his potential cabinet members
and Speaker of the House.
Can we, how much do the people who make these come,
like how much do these people make a year
writing shirts like this?
Well, I don't think this is all original spirit Christmas.
No, I understand that.
I'm just saying, is this a correct,
cause we could do this from home.
We did the, we just,
I just shit out a bunch of great ones.
Yeah.
How much did the people that make these,
I mean, I'm serious.
Does anyone know,
does anyone work in this arena?
Does anyone work,
know people that write dirty shirts, dirty socks,
dirty tea towels for a living?
Is it lucrative?
This is sort of like a question,
like movies,
comedies or movies of character living in the city,
they need to have a cool job.
Oh, they write for magazines.
Oh, they write greeting cards.
Right.
Like her, Joaquin Phoenix was a greeting card writer.
Yes, that's right.
But is anyone-
Is anyone writing-
Dirty t-shirts-
Big Johnson-esque-
Right.
Spencer's gift shirts.
Somebody is doing it.
And I want to know who it is.
I want to know the guru,
the like Bruce Valanche of-
Who's the best of the best.
Yeah.
Cause I think we could do it.
I think we could be up there,
but I don't,
I want to know that the cash is there.
I don't want to give this away anymore for free.
Oh yeah.
If we don't have the cash.
No, do you want to be paid in cash?
Like they just drop a Santa sack of money off?
I want to be paid in the shirts we create.
I want just a hundred-
You want to be paid in the body shirts.
Yeah.
Little drummer fuck boy shirts.
I want 500 of them.
Okay.
And then I'm selling them.
I'm selling them out the back of the car.
You know, in the parking lot.
Rudolph the red nose horn dog?
That's good.
I mean, horn deer.
Horn deer?
Yeah, I guess that's two.
Yeah.
I think I already did.
I said already,
Rudolph the red old asshole,
I think I said.
Rudolph the red little rain dick.
I don't know, I'm not as good as you.
No, you're doing fine.
You're doing good.
I'd said something about his asshole before I think too.
I threw out a couple ideas,
but I don't know.
Yeah, I think we could do it in a second,
but I want to know,
I want to know who's doing it
and how much money they're making.
Yeah.
Well, as you say that about making money
and like we're weighing all these license properties,
that brings us to the finale of this part
for A Christmas Kiss Good Night.
Okay.
Because this is a Spirit branded store.
This is Spencer's gift to the store.
And walking around that first,
I feel like I was like,
I'm missing one of my friends.
I'm missing one of my beloved characters
whose movies I've never seen.
I'm missing Art the Clown.
Uh-huh.
And thankfully we turned an aisle
and it did not disappoint.
Here is some Christmas Art the Clown sweaters
from Terrifier.
And this is the last Terrifier a Christmas movie?
No, is he in like a Santa suit?
Is it kind of a Christmas movie?
I don't know.
I'm just saying like this would make sense.
I mean, was there a lot of,
you said there's like Chuckies involved in there.
There's a toy of Chuckie,
but does Art have the most presence
of any like horror movie character in this Christmas store?
I think so.
There's a little rack of like NECA or reaction figures,
are they called though?
Like three and four.
Those are super seven makes those.
Super seven.
There were some of those.
Okay.
One is says, a sweater says holidays are terrifying.
And the other sweater says,
the most, it's the most terrifying time of the year.
Now I think Terrifier 3 we're up to.
I think might take place at Christmas.
Okay.
So then it makes sense.
So yes.
I feel like you, you front loaded with body.
I think you should have ended with body.
Cause odd the clown.
Yeah.
I was kind of bringing us in,
like you're finally drifting off to sleep at night.
So Sanic can do all his business.
So you don't believe in a traditional climax
for like a movie or TV show.
Well, I do, but.
You like the climax to happen about halfway through.
Well, I wouldn't say halfway.
I'd say that the body stuff was like the majority of it.
And then right as I was leaving,
I realized they had kind of gift wrapped the stanchions
so that a car doesn't run into you.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
Like a candy cane.
That's cute.
And so that's when we'll say Merry Christmas to all.
And to all of fucking good night.
Oh, I should have done that.
Well, I'll update that before we put this somewhere.
A PDF is probably the best version.
Okay.
I don't think this store goes far enough.
Yeah.
I think if you're gonna do it,
you go all the way like a Spencer's.
I think Spirit Halloween.
I mean, Spirit Halloween also anytime I've been in one
doesn't strike me as an extra dirty thing.
I know more I feel like than other Halloween stores.
Maybe.
Do you notice dirty stuff in a Spirit Halloween?
There's like sexy nuns, sexy whatever.
But that's in every Halloween store.
And that's at this point, that's just normal stuff.
That's just an outfit.
I guess what I would say about this.
Like half the store was dirty sweaters.
And then half was like the big inflatables.
And get your photo with Santa.
Yeah.
And here's a bunch of candy for stocking stuffers.
And half are like deck the fucking halls you pussy.
Like sweaters.
So maybe it's like half for the parents
and half for like kids don't come over here.
Naughty, naughty.
Mom and dad are getting sweaters to wear
at the unofficial company party at Yard House.
The swingers party.
Well, I did not see any pineapple based.
Wait, what?
Oh, is that what you-
Upside down pineapple is like a code for swingers.
Where do you put it?
I think people put it at like-
No, I mean, where do you put it?
Where do I put it?
Oh no, just kidding.
Oh, I was just saying, yeah.
I feel like cruise ships, you say it.
This is for guys, a podcast about guys.
I am a mere observer.
When you would be on the cruise ship with your parents,
would you walk down the hall and see a bunch of pineapples?
I can't say I saw any body activity on the cruise ship.
Okay, but you wouldn't have known what a pineapple meant
when you were a kid.
No, I was 12 years old.
I wouldn't have registered that.
You would have just picked it up off the door and ate it.
You'd be like, oh, free pineapple.
Well, I wouldn't have been afraid of cutting my hand.
Oh, because of the exterior.
Yeah, because the exterior of the pineapple.
But you would wear your pineapple gloves.
Yeah.
To be able to handle it.
Sure.
That's like your falconry glove.
To be able to eat a pineapple.
I mean, it would just be my mittens
picking up a can of dull pineapple
because that's mostly what I knew of pineapple
for the first half of my life, I feel like.
The first half of your life,
you didn't know where a pineapple came from?
No, I knew where it came from.
I just didn't encounter it.
Well, I don't really chop open a pineapple very often.
No, I remember going to Ohana at Polynesian.
You can buy a drink at the bar there
served in a whole pineapple.
Oh, I've done it.
Yeah, it's really fun.
Yeah, it's great.
But it didn't cut up my hand.
Huh?
It didn't cut up my hand.
Yeah, it's gonna cut up your hand.
No, it didn't cut up my hand.
Oh, it didn't, okay.
They didn't give me gloves to wear.
It's probably three quarters of a cup of liquid.
You're mostly paying for the novelty.
Very much you're paying for the novelty.
But yeah, I don't think,
I don't know if they shave the coconut down,
the pineapple down so you don't cut yourself.
I think they shave it down on the sides,
chop the top off to fill the inside.
Do you think there are a lot of pineapple injuries
in the United States every year?
I don't know about that.
You don't know anything about that.
I don't know.
That's none of your business.
Anything about, none of my business.
What do you think about Spirit Crestes?
Were you expecting this much body sweaters?
No, I didn't think, again,
I don't think of the Spirit brand as being,
even though, yeah, Spencer's owns it,
and I never think of that brand
as being something that's dirty.
So I was not expecting that.
Now that I've seen it,
I do think it's in the middle
of a regular Christmas store and a Spencer's.
And I, look, I've been into Spencer's.
If you go, just go to Spencer's.
I want it to be either wholesome and normal
or vulgar and sexual.
Yeah.
So I'm kind of, I feel like it's in between
and that doesn't appeal to me.
I want the extremes.
I feel like I bought the famous,
the Simpsons poster with all the characters on it there.
But then also, a gaggle of 13-year-olds
would go and laugh at the Boner Pasta box.
Right.
But yeah, I was in,
I was shocked at how Spencer's is still Spencer's.
I am impressed.
I don't know what the business model is.
I don't know who's going in there and buying stuff.
But it exists still.
So yeah, spirit Christmas.
I feel like it needs to get more extreme next year.
I feel like no kids allowed.
No kids allowed.
No kids allowed in spirit Halloween
or spirit Christmas.
I keep saying the wrong thing.
Do you think it could expand nationally?
I feel like that's a pretty narrow part of the country.
It doesn't seem like it would.
What would be the reason?
I mean, people sell Halloween,
but I think the niche,
and somebody correct me if I'm wrong,
is that there's not a ton of variety
at like Target for Halloween.
They have decorations and they have some costuming
and like CVS has some costuming around Halloween,
but it's not a ton.
And there's probably a gap to be filled
in Halloween stores across the country.
We are in Burbank.
There's plenty of Halloween stores
just that exist here year round,
but not across the country.
So I bet that's a very smart business thing to fill.
But I bet Christmas is,
there's so much more Christmas crap everywhere.
I just think they could probably,
if they're leasing empty storefronts,
and this is in a part an area
that's just all strip malls and shopping malls.
I just, I don't know.
I will be interested to see if the market is there for it
and what their identity is as spirit Christmas.
I feel like, well, that's the other thing.
I don't think I was able to get a good picture of like,
this is half of whatever the store used to be.
Maybe it used to be Bed, Bath, and Beyond.
And I don't know if it's gonna open up
for the like full swing of the holiday season
or they're like, this is all we have.
Well, when they had a spirit Halloween
in the old Toys R Us over on Victory
by the Back to the Future Burger King,
which is now in Aldi.
I'm glad Scott's not here to hear all the different stores
that we like to shop in and what they are now.
But they had a spirit Halloween in there
and it was only half the Toys R Us.
And honestly, it creeped me out
because I would go to that Toys R Us on Victory
and then all of a sudden you're in it and it's empty.
That's one of the scariest like nightmares as a kid.
You go into a store and it's not the store you know.
Oh yeah.
And like this was spirit Halloween in the old Toys R Us
but it was only half set up.
So it was like some of the shelving from the Toys R Us
and like it gave me the creeps being in there.
But it was only, they never expanded it
to finish my thought about what you're saying.
It's sort of like the old Bed Bath and Beyond at Burbank
that was the exhibit of a big Disney auction.
And now it's a store called Glendale Halloween
but it is located in a Burbank mall.
Yeah.
I'm gonna predict the demise of spirit Christmas
in two years.
I just think if they're getting sweetheart deals
on short-term rental space for Halloween,
I feel like they could flip it in a day or two.
Yes, you're right.
That's true.
It's a nice transition.
But obviously they're only trying it in a couple places.
They're not doing it at every location.
So that's why I'm thinking who's going in there?
Who is it for?
And we'll see.
I think failure.
I think not happening.
We'll see in two years unless they wanna take our advice
and get dirtier my advice or hire the bad boys
to write some naughty little shirts.
Like a naughty super store.
I want a naughty super store.
Naughty mega store.
Okay.
You know what?
That's even a better idea.
Let's have Target but have it be naughty.
I like Target fine but what if it's naughty?
But no porno, just naughty.
No, no porno but everything on it is naughty.
So it's like wheat bread
but the wheat bread is giving you the middle finger.
Okay.
Yeah and like on the back and it's like the wheat bread
is like the packaging has.
A butt?
A butt on it.
On the back side.
Right and it's pooping.
Oh it's pooping?
Yeah but it's just on the package.
It's regular bread.
So it's gross.
It's not like a sexual butt.
It's not a sexual butt.
It is a pooping, a functionary butt.
Okay.
So yes, imagine Target but everything's naughty in it.
And I think you put Target right out of business that way.
Out of business entirely.
Well if you do it right.
Okay.
If you do the naughty Target right.
I'm always saying there's.
However it's medicine but it's dirty.
There's a bottle of dirty.
There should be even fewer stores.
Yes, there should be fewer, yes.
There should be all one store and it should be naughty.
Yeah.
It's vitamins but they're naughty.
Vitamin C and we know what that means.
Vitamin D.
Vitamin D and it just says you know what that means.
Vitamin E.
Vitamin F.
Vitamin F is cleaner.
Vitamin E also says you know what that means
but it's not explained.
No.
Because it's like we didn't really think of one for that.
It should be vitamin erection I guess.
That is cleaner than I thought.
That's clean, yeah.
And they all, I mean look, there's one word for everything
but can you imagine?
You mentioned the laughs.
If the Empire Center replaced the normal Target
with the naughty Target.
Sure.
You'd be hearing laughs every day.
It would be like a low rumble.
People would be going buying their vitamins,
giving a good laugh.
Well, Target already has those giant red balls outside
and I think it'd be pretty easy to paint them blue.
Oh yeah, that's great.
So yeah, and it will be called,
the store will be called Naughty Target.
So you'll be there, yeah.
So while the retail wars are going on,
you can decide, am I gonna go to Target or Naughty Target?
Do you think Bullseye should be smoking a big Stoge?
Bullseye should transform into the Dick's Last Resort
character that's a dog named Assbite.
Okay.
So yes, Bullseye will be bawdy.
He's gonna be a lot more.
It sounds like you're trying to make an umbrella
like Marcus Lemotis combining his fashion companies.
You're bringing Dick's Last Resort and Big Johnson
and Spencer's and Naughty Target.
Yeah.
And this is why you're a visionary.
You're a retail visionary.
Yes, so I mean, look, if Target, the company wants
to market these like McDonald's is doing with Cosmix, fine.
Hit me up, I'm willing to work with them.
But if not, we're just gonna have to do Naughty Target.
And if we need to change the name Target to like T,
like you're saying, like it's an app, TGRT or whatever,
like to get rid of the vowels, fine, we'll do it.
Okay.
And then the money will roll in.
All right.
And Walmart wants to do it too.
We could do Naughty Walmart.
I'm not against it. Okay.
You're trying to Naughtify all the stores.
Naughty Coles. Naughty Coles.
We could do Naughty Coles, Naughty JCPenney's,
Naughty Sears, which one do you want?
Do you think if everything was more Naughty,
you'd feel more comfortable?
Oh, oh.
If all the retail quadrant, all the quadrants.
I would think I would, I actually would know
I would feel more uncomfortable, but I would feel,
I would be rich because that was my idea.
Oh, okay.
So you could just rent out the top floor of a hotel,
like Howard Hughes and just retreat from society.
Finally.
So I, a failure, Spirit Christmas failure
next year prediction.
Okay, we'll see.
I don't think it's coming back next year.
You don't think it's coming back.
Everything you showed me is completely unremarkable.
Mark this time code.
Everything you showed me is not exciting.
I think even to like people that would buy stuff like that
and wear it and offend their relatives.
Okay.
So that's my prediction.
We'll see, we'll see what happens.
Grandma really didn't like that shirt,
that sweater you wore last year.
So if you could just wear one of the ones she got you,
it would cause a lot less conflict.
What do you mean?
The Santa licks my balls sweater, it's offending her.
Doesn't even make sense.
And then he kicks over the big barrel of walnuts
that grandma has in the house.
Don't you dare.
You need to find that barrel and get it in your apartment.