Club 3
Daddy's home and he's pissed.
That's right. You and your little tee-hee-hees.
Tee-hee-please.
Scott Free. More Scott than ever there be.
Here on Club 3. That's right.
Oh, he's speaking in rhyme.
I don't know why.
Uh-oh.
Yes, kind of like limerick or pirate or something,
which is not applicable whatsoever because this is Christmas, actually, is what this is.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. Christmas Day.
It's happy.
You there, what day is it? Why, it's the day Podcast Rides Club 3 comes out,
where Scott responds after weeks of Scott Free episodes.
Yes, that's right. If you are with your family currently
and you would like to go have a several-hour block to yourself,
it's completely unrelatable to your family,
something that they, as soon as you start explaining,
they will not ask any follow-up questions and they will let you go be on your own.
This is that episode.
Yeah, it's exciting. So, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. I'm not sure that we've had an episode come out on literal Christmas before,
and I started feeling kind of self-conscious that the schedule dictated that it be this.
But then I started thinking, well, you know what?
What says holiday gathering more than criticizing your loved ones?
Yeah, that's true.
That's one. This is a broader thought, and we'll get into it.
This is the episode where I'm responding to all of the episodes that I missed while I was gone.
One big note I have, having gotten a little busy for a second,
how do we do so many goddamn episodes? It's crazy.
I got a time-consuming job for a minute, and I'm like, I haven't heard all these fucking things.
The point was for me to listen to, I listened to a lot of them, but I couldn't keep up.
I literally haven't had the time. How does anybody do it?
That's what my dad was telling me last night. He goes, I'm so behind on these episodes.
I go, I know, I'm sorry. That's just what the people demand, though.
Yeah, it's a lot of content.
It's a content hose. We are blasting people at full fire department levels.
Yeah, but like Morning Zoo...
It's a riot control level of content hose.
But Morning Zoo people are like five days a week, four days a week.
That's true.
And they do it early, and they reroute their entire lives to make it happen.
We should be thankful that here, well, that anyone wants this, first of all,
and that we can do it at our leisure, that we can do it in reasonable hours.
Right, that's true. But I mean, there might be some people that want us to do it daily.
And maybe if the call comes in right now on the Patreon...
Scott's going to have a lot more to respond to.
Five days a week, and maybe they do want us to do it live at 7 a.m.
Oh my God.
And if the call is strong enough, we may as well heed the call.
That's all I'm saying.
One of us will stay normal. You'll still be Mike, but I'll have to turn into initials.
I'll have to be SG, and then Jason will have to become the Hooter or something.
Or the Buttmaster.
And the Buttmaster.
Yeah, that's Dacey on FCC-controlled radio, but that's about as far as you can go.
That's what Howard Stern fought for when he was fighting with WNBC.
He was fighting to be able to say Buttmaster,
and now Buttmaster is just a regular morning Zoo Crew show
that mainly talks about theme parks.
VTR radio with Mike, SG, and the Buttmaster.
7 a.m., five days a week, clapping those cheeks.
7 a.m. to 2 p.m. every day.
There's one from Foreigner.
Hot blooded chickens.
That would be fun to play music during this show.
I've never even thought about that.
That's how we would get through it.
There's a Clip 3 idea, one where we have to...
And the topic can be random.
The parenthetical would be...
It could be, what's a random triceratops spin?
Is that a ride?
It's jumping jellyfish, but you have to do it like a morning Zoo Crew.
And you have to hold for song breaks, and we play the entire song.
And now here's It Takes Two.
There has to be a list of approved songs, though,
like it was K. Earth or something, right?
Yeah, pulled from the 20s.
So we're throwing, once again, the Chainsmokers.
We'll be back with more Golden Zephyr talk.
This ain't a bad idea, actually.
Let's just see if we can...
We need kind of a whole new switcher, I think.
We'd have to do it live.
I don't want to edit in the songs.
Yeah, yeah.
And you'd have to do that thing where...
Back with more PTR here on PTR Radio.
Taking care of biz.
It has to overlap with the guitar.
Well, they call it a talk-up, is when you do the intro.
Is that the term?
The intro is a talk-up, where you talk up right when the vocal comes in.
I think that's a real skill,
and I think it'd be a great skill for us to learn,
because it really has to gather speed.
See, I mumbled, I couldn't do it.
You've got to gather speed all the way up to the point of where Hot-Blooded begins.
PTR Radio.
Don't stop believing starts, but you talk right up until the vocal comes in.
That's a really good one for radio,
because you've got a lot of instrumental to do ads
and talk about giveaways you're going to do
that we'll be hanging out at the...
at the Kia Forum, giving out passes for Summer Bash,
right here on PTR Radio.
But ours would be like,
stay tuned after this tune to hear a new anecdote about Al Lewis.
Who does a small town...
And stay tuned for discussion about whether Madam is Mama,
right here at PTR Radio.
So that would be a little different.
I like the idea of a format buster.
That sounds good.
I mean, look, what I feel at this point,
given the, I would say, the pole dominance of what we're doing right now,
of the desire of this topic,
the desire for me to respond to what I missed,
as well as the strong second place performance of my vice topic,
Bugmane does whatever he wants,
I feel like there is a mandate for change coming into the...
A desire for a new type of show, a new type of Club 3.
I feel this very strongly.
Interesting.
And that's why, you know, again, you know,
because we try to tee up the next month as we do this thing.
And I just want to say, you know, like I look at these comment sections
and after the hate and the division and the vitriol that I see in there,
you know, people fighting tooth and nail against particular topics,
I think it's time to all come together
and coalesce in the spirit of love and harmony
behind our new leader, Bugmane.
To just like give, what's the...
There's like a let go and let God.
Let go and let Bug.
It's time to let go and let Bug.
After all of this, please just do the right thing,
cast your vote for Bugmane, does whatever he wants,
and we can stop all this division and this...
Oh, it's been so nasty in there.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah, it has been nasty, yeah.
Hopefully everyone will just coalesce
and they'll all say, you know what, it's time.
Yeah, I think so.
Sure.
By the way, I don't want to put you guys on the spot.
Well, you know what, I won't even lead the conversation.
I don't think you've really said your thoughts
about the notion of letting Bugmane do whatever he wants.
Because I think this is attributed to me.
This is made very much a Scott thing,
but Bugmane is a friend of us all.
Well, offend of every man, woman, child, person on the planet Earth.
Yes, yes.
And in the voice memo that I sent you guys,
to make the point, he is a big Theme Park fan.
He's a good guest to talk about theme parks.
I thought if I made that point, it would help.
I think it only made things worse.
Oh, the discord that started occurring there.
I don't know why people can't cut this mere entertainer a break.
He's just trying to make you laugh.
He's trying to do a little song for you.
He's just a Lanuba boy, you know?
Ultimately, look right there, you know?
That's what I've been thinking.
He's in that universe where he is hosting a podcast about this kind of stuff.
About, I don't know, like an old Cirque du Soleil show or something.
He has opinions about it.
He's told me about that.
But what are your feelings? What are your guys' feelings?
Because if your feelings are you don't want him around...
No, no, I don't. I want him around.
There's uncertainty when he does whatever he wants.
Sure.
If he did...
Isn't that the thrill?
But that's the thrill.
You know, I like to roll with things.
Let's do it. Let's fucking go, I say.
You're always saying that we cut that before every record.
Right.
Right before we start.
Like, are we ready? Mike's sounding good?
Yeah.
Yeah. Let's fucking go.
And that pumps us. I know that revs me up.
I'm sure the same for you, Jason.
It revs me up, too. Yeah.
I mean, Mike has that prime energy drink sponsor.
Logan Paul's energy drink.
Just Logan Paul's energy drink.
You always pound those things. You crush the can on your head.
Yeah.
And then you turn off Mike
because that's an unpleasant sound to make the listeners hear.
Right.
Yeah.
But I'm ready for him to do whatever he wants.
I think it seems like the time...
I feel like we're out. Jason? Jason?
Oh, I like a leap before I look topic.
You know that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm open to it, you know?
Great.
It's fun.
I am...
Mike locked the door when we came in here,
but I'm still not convinced that he's not going to show up today.
Oh, now this was presented.
Because it's sort of a letting me do whatever I want kind of thing as well.
Yeah.
So, yeah, there was the notion presented
that I would come in with this so that you'd suddenly hear from the back.
You'd find a way.
You'd get in through the vents even though we locked the doors here at Forever Dog Studios.
Right.
I mean, I'd say the biggest hurdle to that
and to this even happening in January,
he's been real light on the text responses lately,
which, again, I think it's worth the vote
just to see if you do the vote and then the episode doesn't happen.
Yeah.
It's definitely possible.
He's like on a level of like Bill Murray.
Will he show up? Will he respond?
Plus all the great stories, the stories.
Yeah, the murricane going to the parties
and his family not seeing him for years and, you know, all those wild stories.
Screaming at people.
You know what? I don't think I even want to equate Bug Main.
Yeah, no, I shouldn't go that far with it.
I'm just saying the unpredictability is the specific thing.
Oh, well, it's really more like Belouche.
It's more like the Belouche.
It's the danger, the danger of Belouche, Jim Belouche.
You never knew what the guy was going to do.
Was he just going to talk like a normal guy?
Was he going to talk to Curly Sue?
Is he going to bust out a harmonica solo
and dance in a way that like clearly visibly wore him out
where he's like having trouble breathing after half of a song?
How long will the harmonica intro to Sweet Home Chicago be?
Will it be 20 seconds? Will it be 25 seconds? We don't know.
And can he properly pantomime a harmonica solo
that is clearly being performed by a better harmonica player just off stage?
Oh, no.
You know what? I feel like maybe we've got to,
in terms of like 2025 shotcalling,
I think we've got to do Blues Brothers.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because that's a theme park topic.
Yes, it is.
Blues Brothers.
And don't start suggesting that for Club 3
because that's a main feed if I've ever heard one.
Oh, sure.
I mean, that street show has been going
since the opening of Universal Florida.
So many men over the years have hopped around on one foot
and jingle jangled their hand to the delight of dozens.
I think it's time.
And the people still love it.
What's that?
Are they still?
Like, I know that Joliette Blues Brothers Con
had its last Blues Brothers performance by Dan Aykroyd,
but it was unclear.
You know that. We all know that.
They do a Blues Brothers Con in the last two years, I feel like,
three years at the prison in Joliette where they shot the movie.
And then there was some announcement about it
being the last Blues Brothers performance at Joliette.
Like, it was unclear language if Dan was retiring,
performing or not.
And I still don't have an answer, so I'm wondering if...
Because all of a sudden, he'll just, like,
pop up doing, like, three shows at a casino with Jim Belushi
and then nothing.
And you're like, what is that? Why?
Yeah, yeah.
So I wonder. I'm just going to quickly Google and see.
No, no, no, check it.
Doesn't it feel like the Blues Brothers performing at a prison?
Doesn't it feel like a hat on a hat?
Because I think any Blues Brothers live performance is already a prison.
Now, this is where things get odd, right?
Because here I am responding to things that I missed.
Here I am completely game to talk about this unrelated nonsense,
because it's unrelated nonsense I have a bizarre fascination with.
That's true, yes.
And really what starts to happen, the division occurs
when there are these things that I just don't,
that I don't have any interest in.
And, you know, I think it's why it was perfectly fair
in the time that I was gone that you guys explore some things
that, you know, where you know that I would start glazing over
if you were doing it with me.
Did you feel like you enjoyed the freedom
and that you got to seize the freedom to its fullest extent?
To its fullest extent, no.
I don't think we actually did go to the fullest extent.
Were there plans that didn't come together?
Were there things that you,
because there may be Scott Freira's in the future, I don't know.
Do you have already earmarked what we'd like to do if this happens again?
I don't know that I have any concrete plans.
I gotta say, I'm shocked Mr. Morrow didn't show up.
I was anticipating that every time a new episode dropped.
That was a thought I had had, and then that didn't,
not that it didn't come, we didn't have time to do it.
Sure.
We didn't have time to do it.
And I also wanted to get him in person.
I don't want to Zoom.
We had to do Matt Cardone on Zoom, I get that,
but like I wanted Morrow in person.
Yeah.
Well look, I had a great time with him on stage there.
I'm not saying get Mr. Morrow to do without me.
I would love to hang with Mr. Morrow.
He can come any time.
I thought that there'd be some play to plant him permanently in the third seat.
Yeah, that was a thought.
I do think there's a lot of listeners that are still sort of casually listening.
So part of me, and then we didn't know how long you were going to be gone.
So there was a larger idea in my head to make some sort of like finite little events out of it,
but I didn't have the exact time frame,
and we had already recorded some with you and without you.
And also it was not that long.
And also it wasn't that long.
Perhaps we were making too big of a meal out of this.
Yeah, you could have taken another month or two if need be.
Paternity leave is kind of different around the world.
So it was different, yeah.
That's the thing, I didn't take paternity leave at all.
Take it at all.
This was insane how much I did not get a break in order to do this.
But this was a very exciting time of my life if overwhelming in a lot of moments.
So if you had said I'm gone for eight weeks, starting at the start of November,
we're done at December, there would have been maybe a much more planned event that happened
where we auditioned, because there was some grander ideas.
Well, we're going to audition a third host as a joke.
But then I'm like, yeah, there's a couple of people.
But then also I'm like, because it's easier when it's Las Vegas month.
Here it is, there's the month.
It was unclear.
It was left unclear.
So it was hard to figure out a structure.
So we really just sort of dabbled in little indulgences.
Now, I will say, and people have heard this already by now,
because I've said it on a couple of episodes,
really what happened was digging into certain avenues
that maybe we would not dig into quite as hard on the regular show
has whetted my appetite to do a real hardcore version of it.
For instance, points.
We've talked about this.
I know now after doing the first credit card points episode,
how to do a second points episode.
And I did, of course, on Santa's Secret invite Nick Weigert to be the guest on said episode.
Wow.
So in 2025, Mike's credit card points, I would like to just call it points too.
Points too comes in 2025 at some point.
Not for a while.
You have the confidence in the franchise to where like there's a short end now.
It's points.
Well, he started telling us about a whole other.
Right.
Weigert's on a whole other thing.
So really what's happened is certain things that we've discussed.
Now I feel like now that we've sort of done the first version,
now we've done a new hope, I'm ready to do a lot of Empire Strikes Back.
But the problem is you're here now, so you may have to be involved.
I truly thought you were going to say now that we've done a new hope,
we can do a new hope special edition.
Well, that's almost what this is.
We're almost doing the remastered version by letting me go in and alter things in past episodes.
That's what that is.
Yeah.
I'm doing the Lucas special edition.
I'm adding my McClunkies right here and now.
Yeah.
So really what you saw on these episodes was the birth of new avenues.
Okay.
They weren't the full stretched out versions of what they would be.
The Frankenstein's monster of out of control app talk and mobile order talk.
This was just the beginning.
This is the problem I think you face now.
Oh, boy.
I have kind of an order in my head.
I'm going to build it because I think there's things to address here.
I've had thoughts about how to make everybody happy,
given the new information that we have and the response to certain episodes
and certain lines of thinking while I was gone.
I think there's places where I know how to proceed.
But let me go through in kind of the order that I was thinking.
First, I will read the topic suggestion, the official quote.
This is from C. Allen Kelly, a Club 3 topic winner veteran.
I looked it up.
C. Allen Kelly was responsible for Griffin Newman does whatever he wants.
Wow.
He's got a read on the Club 3 zeitgeist seemingly.
Wow, yeah, really.
So the official suggestion, if Scott is back, then I would like a Scott listens to
and responds to all the episodes he missed episode.
I feel like he's going to have a couple opinions.
Correct, Allen.
Edit to be clear, all episodes, including Second Gate and Friday episodes.
Thank you for that clarification.
Now, I feel like I have already failed the assignment because there are certain ones
that I did not and not due to any lack of interest, in some cases lack of time.
There's one I can say right off the bat.
I gave a real college try to Generation X.
And to me, Generation X was as if you recorded an episode entirely in Portuguese.
Yeah.
I just don't.
I just have.
I mean, OK, you might have got you might have explained this further at some point,
but I'm I listen for I'd say for like 15 minutes or so.
And I was left going, what is Generation X?
I don't know what Generation X is as opposed to the X-Men.
I did like for an X-Men lay person, I have no fucking clue what this was.
I'm pretty sure we said it was the teenage version of X-Men.
It was the new class.
They've done a few versions over the years of like the new class.
I said it was like the night.
I felt like a 90s thing of like the teens are happening.
And now we're going to do with the X-Men.
So and it launched the comic launched with a lot of fanfare.
Did you want an explanation now?
No, not necessarily.
By the way, maybe you said it in the time I was listening and I just glazed over it.
That's distinctly possible as well.
But here's what when you guys talk about X-Men, I feel like what happens is.
So today, Generation X.
Now, this is, of course, reflects the the Ralph Stedman era of illustration.
He drew things, you know, in a very active, you know, in a very like it was kind of a revolutionary style of.
And I'm like, what is it?
Wait, basics.
Give me the first line of that Wikipedia or I'm in a lot of trouble.
Well, it made up the movie that came along two years later that we talked about the made for TV movie.
It aired on the episode for you right now.
I was asking for trouble.
But Mike found the like I just watched a master copy that was uploaded.
But when it aired, it aired with interstitials.
It was Mardi Gras.
So there was body man on the street segments hosted by a number of of correspondents, including a young Jimmy Kimmel.
Well, also Jim Belushi was on it.
Oh, Jim Belushi was in one.
And Mardi Gras.
Yeah.
Was he the was he the king of Bacchus?
We discussed this feels like this must have come up before because I've previously.
This is something that would be way up our alley is that the people who are the Mardi Gras king of Bacchus.
Do you know this notion?
It's always like this like gregarious.
Just like, you know, like like imagine like a John Goodman type sort of just like, you know, kind of a loud larger than life party guy.
Yeah.
And they always designate somebody to be king of Bacchus.
And I guarantee if you go through that list, it's entirely people we like.
I think it's this might be.
When is Mardi Gras?
Maybe that's an episode we can do that is going through rating our favorite kings of Bacchus.
OK.
Is this the right phrase, by the way?
God of recovery and excess.
Yeah, I think so.
That's that seems right.
I mean, just like if you just skim through it really fast.
Oh, wait, sometimes they say crew of Bacchus.
That must be some other.
This is not a really unhelpful Wikipedia.
Crew of Bacchus is a New Orleans Mardi Gras super crew.
OK, well, if you explain what crew is first before.
But you look at the list and it's like Shatner, Gutenberg, Jackie Gleason, Phil Harris,
voice of Baloo, Henry Winkler, Glen Campbell, Gandolfini.
It's always.
Yeah, I don't want to spoil all of the names, but I've just noted this before that like,
I don't know any materials we can find about who the king of Bacchus is.
And anyway, I wonder if Belushi was one of those.
I hope.
Anyway, did that successfully pivot off of Generation X?
I don't know. I don't know.
Jason, Jason might explain more about the X-Men, though, I think to you.
We saved you.
The other big Marvel made for TV movie at the time was Nick Fury.
I will be here for as a major.
Saved Hasselhoff for you.
That does sound good.
And this this kind of connected in like Fox in the 90s had these.
A lot of these made for TV movies, a lot of the magic specials we talked about.
Alien autopsy.
Sure, sure.
All right.
Yeah, yeah.
Fox 90s, I think, is proven to be in our.
I think there was I think that I think we did.
I think we said the things you're talking about,
but they were sandwiched in between talk of Chris Baccholo, Scott Lobdell.
And I think at a certain point, that's like that wasn't an underlining generation.
So Scott Lobdell, let's talk a little bit about Scott Lobdell before we explain
the basic tenets of what I think there was.
Yeah, I think I think we came a little later.
All these one. Yes.
But it was Jason's birthday, you know, and I can't pick that.
So you gotta again, that's what I was saying.
That was one where I just backed off.
I'm like, you know what?
Not for me.
You guys have your fun.
Let Jason be the king of birthday Bacchus.
Well, in Max Headroom, we called the shot Max Headroom episode next year.
OK, which I want to do.
I've always been ambivalent about Max Headroom, but that's fine.
I don't have specific content.
There's enough content there that there's got to be something.
As opposed to and I know that whenever I do this, this just only leads to the episode happening.
But I started listening to Mike's credit card points with a lot of trepidation.
And then I was like jump scared by things I wasn't even prepared for,
such as when Jason started talking about how he's been getting a lot of ads for Mama's Family Live for Vicki Lawrence as Mama in Las Vegas.
And at this point, I am trembling.
I'm like, Dear God, do not.
We've already we know that Madam's inevitable.
I know this. I'm aware of this.
But Mama Mama is a bridge to at some point.
This podcast has to be about things that are happening in this decade.
Well, it is a show that's happening in the decade.
Yeah, it was content.
I'm not saying I'm ready to do it.
I'm just saying it is a new at least it's new mama content.
I watched a Vegas video recently and she was playing one of the station casinos, one of the bigger station casinos.
OK, good.
That doesn't mean we have to talk about Mama.
By the way, you are causing this nowhere on the episode.
Did I even say we got to do Mama's episode?
Like I was more of a haunting.
I was being haunted by Mama.
I really want to talk about the more we're going to end up.
I know that I'm just going to cause it.
The thing and you and in that conversation, then Mike, you were saying how Madam is scary and that we avoid like mad.
I my objection to Madam isn't remotely that Madam is scary.
My objection to Madam is that Madam sucks and Mama sucks about five times more.
That is some old out decrepit unfunny shit.
It wasn't funny then.
We can not guys.
You're we are not arguing to do it.
You're the one causing it.
Now it's I guess we have like it's making me closer to wanting to do it.
I thought I never argued that we should do Mama.
I walk right into it.
I guess I don't exist.
All right.
I have to stay.
But it's but I look I've been tasked to talk about things.
No, I understand that.
I should I should go back to this is what bigger fish to fry.
You're hearing things in these episodes that didn't exist.
You're you're like, I don't want to do Mama.
And if you go back and listen, we never women show half Mama, half Vicki Lawrence.
They got Mama covered.
I disagree.
This is not a I don't believe this for one second.
I think I think I feel like you're listening to Mama and your little gears are turning well.
Mama shaped gears.
There's other things, though, that we said on these episodes.
Let's do another. Let's do that.
Let's do that. There was no time when he said, Mama, maybe I think I chuckled that we moved on.
I don't think I ever said.
Well, then maybe my objection is Mama coming up at all.
I think that's what I've only added more.
I realize that's what I do.
Some of this is going to be about me processing and me learning.
That's fine. I'm just saying that if things get that things, probably a lot of things did just fly under the radar without me.
Yeah.
And then I come and I put a spotlight on them like as if like on prison prisoners trying to escape.
Clunk clunk. Right.
And now like now everyone's aware of it.
And then now you're talking about Mama.
I forgot that we talked about Vicki Lawrence and Mama.
I know I don't dislike Vicki Lawrence, but I don't care about Mama.
That's the problem. If you don't dislike Mama already, then we're not we're not operating at a good level.
There's plenty of old characters from the old days that I don't care necessarily about at all.
But now I'm like, oh, maybe something here with this Mama thing.
He's really upset about it.
Then we got it. All right.
OK, then moving on.
The rules of the Streisand effect have to take place.
We've said Streisand only made problems.
What was her problem? Was it about having was that about having a mall in her house?
No, no, no. What was the Streisand?
What caused the Streisand effect?
It was some sort of like gossipy thing, I think.
And she just kept saying, I don't want to talk about that or like was trying to get lawyers to go.
And it just made it more and more public.
This is me.
I had an email open to an attorney to sign a cease and desist to get to make sure Mama was never talked about on the show.
We're seeing Mama so much now that the phones are hearing us.
Then I'm going to start getting Mama and Vicki Lawrence stuff more so than already I would get.
Listeners, by the way, it's Christmas.
If you have been taken by your family or someone in your family.
Wait, someone in your family got or gave tickets to Mama Vicki Lawrence, a two woman show.
Please let us know.
I looked at it. I think this is way in the past.
I think this occurred in September.
I know who's still going.
I thought it would run for like five years.
You are correct. All the listeners will start getting pop up ads.
Jason is so behind on his email.
He's getting four month old Vicki Lawrence ticket on sale.
I know that like Jason has 16,000 unread emails or something to where you can't find your work email.
How many work emails are you getting?
Well, you guys are forever dog rats, but I've started everyone.
This is almost no email.
I know I deleted one of them accidentally when I was trying to clean.
You get two work emails a month and you deleted half of them.
Yeah.
I see six dates for Vicki Lawrence on the books here.
January, March and April and April and May and one in Branson in May.
So she is still doing this show.
And I again, I don't want to do it.
I don't. I had no interest in it.
And look, there is a way where you mean not liking something does not have to cause you liking it.
That is not how this has to work.
I'm just saying there's a feeling now.
Maybe there's something there.
We know where this is going.
This is a Batman Joker situation.
We know this dance.
We do.
I guess.
I guess we do.
Luckily, the rules are I can't kill you.
What if Bugman doesn't show up?
Can we book Vicki Lawrence on this Club 3?
What about Vicki Lawrence does whatever she wants on Club 3?
Let's get the next month, January.
Who wants Vicki Lawrence to get booked on Club 3?
I'll do my best.
It might be more likely that it happens.
Yeah, sure.
Just if the money is right.
OK, look, I already fucked up.
And I've already talked about a lot of things that are past the first thing that I wanted to talk about.
Because before I even knew there was going to be this episode.
And thank you, CL and Kelly.
Thanks for voting for this so that I can stretch out with this.
But when there wasn't going to be this episode, there is one word that has been echoing in my head for months.
And I knew when I came back, I had to say the word and ask more questions about the word.
Immersive.
Storytelling.
No, the word is cookieing.
We need to talk about cookieing, gentlemen.
This was in the episode about this year's Halloween haunts and such with Justin Michael and Marissa Strickland,
who were eventually permitted to talk after nine minutes about mozzarella.
The Toe Boys do that all the time.
They make you sweat like that.
A lot of podcasts do that.
I guess it isn't unprecedented.
It's not what we do.
And these are good friends of ours.
That's why I felt comfortable making them wait.
You shut them out at one point.
You slammed the door down on them.
Well, Jason and I were talking.
We had important stuff to finish before we brought them in.
They couldn't have participated in the mozzarella poll conversation.
Here's what, Jason and I lock in now, especially these last few weeks.
We're locking, we have a thing going.
I can't have that interrupted sometimes by a guest.
It's sort of like jazz, right, Mike?
Yeah, in a lot of ways when we lock in, it's like jazz.
He plays the notes that I don't play.
He fills it in.
This is something, maybe I should just dive into,
this will just be an all out of order kind of episode.
Sure, go ahead.
Because what you were saying has provoked,
this is a very specific thing that I've been thinking the whole time I was gone,
and especially in all the feedback, all the feedback that I've seen,
like what I've heard from you guys,
things that I've seen in the listener feedback,
things that guests have said.
It's like jazz.
Yes, so many people, everyone is saying that this is like jazz.
No, what is being said is this,
and I alluded to this in the episode with Kyle,
but this has been the theme of the whole thing for me,
is Scott hates tangents.
This is a, I will say a myth,
a myth that has been propagated in the time that I leave for one second,
and then this false rumor about me gets started,
that Scott is so buttoned up.
He needs, Scott, the guy who several times has planted a monster in the room
to come in and yell at Mike about getting off of deal accounts.
No, Scott, the guy who tries to turn the episode into a full time
Jay Leno, Helen Kushnick podcast.
Scott is so, he's just so buttoned up, you see,
and he doesn't let the guys explore.
He doesn't cut them, he's got them both on leashes,
and finally they're able, and jazz did occur to me,
because when I hear tangent, that is what I think.
I hear tangent and I think, wild, just free form, improvisational,
do whatever you want, go wild,
and I'm like, so do people regard me as like,
it's the 1920s and I'm a nightclub owner,
and I've hired two musicians to entertain the folks tonight,
but there's rules, there's rules.
In order to get your check, here's what you must do.
You must play all of the notes here on this sheet,
and nothing more.
No solos.
Dude, yes, no solos.
Perhaps if I point to you and I deign to give you a solo,
then you can have one,
but your job tonight is to play the notes as written,
because how things will go haywire if not,
and then the show begins and then,
what is this, what is this music that I'm hearing?
Jazz, you say?
This is too wild for my ears, my ears are burning,
I cannot handle this, this is too experimental avant-garde for me.
But then, so I, and maybe the answer is,
is this how you, first of all,
is this square with your feelings?
Am I the nightclub owner not letting you go,
go buck wild?
What it is really is that you're the owner,
and you will let us, like say you'll let us solo,
you'll let us play a song in the key of A,
you'll let us play in the key of C,
you'll let us play in the key of J,
like JB, JB Lushy, that's a thing we can do.
Here's the thing though, sorry, finish your point.
I'm just saying, but then there'll be certain scales
that we're not allowed to play in,
certain things that are like,
they feel too unpleasant to your ear,
maybe minor scales.
Look, I don't want, first of all, let me say,
I don't want to limit the notes,
I don't want to dictate the scale that we're doing,
but if we have said that the point of tonight's performance
is songs in the key of C.
Right, but maybe, you know what,
what it'll be is if we're playing in the key
of generation of X, we're playing in the key of X,
you say that solo can probably be 45 seconds,
but if we're playing in the key of JB, JB Lushy,
that solo probably can be three minutes, four minutes,
five, and of course, playing in the key of J,
that solo, as long as you,
that can be a fish concert length solo,
20 minutes, 25 minutes.
By J, you mean the key of J-A-Y.
J-A-Y, of course, yes, Jay Leno.
Yes, okay.
So that solo can be a long solo.
I see, I see.
So that's really what the parameters are.
Not that I feel so restricted by that, that's fine.
Well, first of all, I'm no boss of this.
I cannot, the only thing that's gonna happen
is that I am gonna tune out when it's things
that I'm not particularly,
because this is just to keep with the jazz metaphor.
I hear this, and if that's the feeling,
then I acknowledge this and I understand this,
but then here's what happens is that I listen to the jazz.
Okay, let's hear Miles and Coltrane rip here.
Okay, here we go, headphones on, and what is it?
Now, I use the My Panda Points Panda Express app,
but I don't care for the evaluation of the panda points.
I think that for 90 panda points,
you should get a medium orange chicken,
not cream cheese rangoons.
Well, now, that's when you're supposed to be listening
to the notes we're not playing.
I would happily listen to the notes you're not playing.
That sounds great.
Do you know what I'm saying, though,
that the notion that like, oh, Scott Gurr with his tangents,
let the boys cook, and then I hear the cooking,
and the cooking will be my other...
But the cooking to another person,
when we're talking about Jay Leno for the 50th time,
would be, what do these guys care about Jay Leno?
He's been off the Tonight Show forever.
This is fair.
Panda points, certainly mundane topic,
but is certainly the listener can feel that this is a conversation
Jason and I would have off mic.
I think there was some idea that we were doing points
and talking about it, like, oh, man, we're getting early.
Get Scott with this.
This is just what he and I talk about.
This is what we want to talk about.
Also, direct democracy told us to talk about that.
Well, direct democracy did tell us to talk about it.
That's true.
Well, as direct democracy swung the other way.
And you saw how many people love points.
I did.
People love points.
Yes.
Well, and this is what leaves me in a strange situation,
that here I am thinking, but like, you know,
because when you say it's the kind of thing we talk about off mic,
I'm like, yeah, I know.
That's why I'm worried about it.
And now you have done the full off mic conversation on mic
and I cannot remotely hide behind the fact
this was a very well received episode.
I acknowledge this.
I can't deny this.
I was not like cocksure about this being very popular.
This was when I was putting this together, I went, oh, ha ha.
That's funny.
Somebody said something about credit card points
and my points in general.
Let's put that on the list.
I thought that was headed for number five as far as voting.
I was shocked at that one.
I was shocked that every other, I said it on the episode,
every other topic, I was like, oh, that's one of those is going to win.
You could explain to a lay person.
Right. I said that you pulled someone off the street
and that wouldn't sound interesting to probably a normal person.
And obviously maybe to other people, it wasn't interesting.
But, but to the podcast, the Ride listeners who have been listening,
many people, you know, are having similar brains
and thought processes to Jason and I.
So it isn't surprising to me that a number of our listeners
also seem to be preoccupied with the idea of points in general.
Yes.
So I understand what you're saying.
But I also now in hindsight, of course, points was popular.
Of course people want to hear points talk
and want to hear more points talk going forward.
Well, this is where this and this is where I have a plan.
And frankly, this is what I was going to build to.
But maybe we can, we can go, we can go back and kind of like skitter
scatter through other things that I, because obviously, yeah,
the big, the big way that the differences came to a head was the points episode.
And at this point, with this point, with the reception of the points episode,
I am left to, I almost feel bad that I have been holding YouTube back,
that I've been holding the audience back.
And it's, and in fact, it's like the main thing that like I,
it was, this is a little experiment, right?
I leave for the longest stretch of time since we started the podcast
and what happens immediately.
It's talk about apps and points.
You're talking about mozzarella planks and all that.
It's the first thing you do when I'm gone.
It's a runner through all of it, all culminating in one giant points episode.
I had no idea what a biological need this was for you guys.
How like strong the torrent of desire was to talk about points and apps.
And apparently that the listener has.
But this, the God himself came together to give us the venue to do apps and points,
both topics not chosen by us.
True, true.
The Lord Almighty, whatever you believe, maybe you believe in multiple gods.
If you just believe in the idea of the universe.
The world gave us a sign.
The universe told us, told you to do this.
Converged.
And taught me a lesson.
I saw, look, I shouldn't even say it now.
I saw American Idiot.
What?
I saw the musical.
Whoa.
I was prepared.
I thought this is fucking winning.
I'm see, and I, this was all coming together.
I know.
I thought God was going to bless us with that.
You're like, I have to, I have to see American Idiot.
The listener is sure to force me to, I guess I better go to American Idiot.
That was something that was, that's coming.
American Idiot is coming.
That is something we didn't get to.
And it's coming when you least suspect it.
I'll say that right now.
Oh my God.
I saw it.
I have thoughts on it, but I thought that was winning.
But no, points and apps, app chosen by Jessica McKenna, points chosen by the listeners.
They desired, the other people desired.
And finally Jason and I were to let it all out.
We finally, but that wasn't our decision.
And it's kind of beautiful when you put it that way.
Right.
And that's why I'm not here to criticize and to butt heads on this.
Because I've, like it's something that I can't run from, that I have to acknowledge.
And I've been thinking how this does kind of fit into a like relationship structure that I think might be helpful in guiding us forward.
I feel like, you know, seven years we've been doing this.
That's a while.
That'd be a healthy amount of time for a marriage.
And imagine if, imagine a marriage where that is, that's rock solid, where everything's going great.
And you know, you came together over shared interests and that was the original bond.
And things have only blossomed and grown.
And you've had a lot of fun in those seven years.
But something has kind of risen to the surface.
And that is that one of the partners has certain needs, desires, predilections, you might say, that the other partner does not share.
Right.
Just for, just to, you know, just as a random example, let's say that one of the partners in the marriage has a strong interest in inflatable stuff.
It's popping.
Right.
And maybe the other partner is not so against it, not against it at all.
Maybe even has a light interest in inflatable stuff.
Right.
But the popping is just too, like ultimately, you know, the partner has to be true to themselves and say the popping is just not for me.
And there will never be a point where I am into the popping.
That's just not where we started.
And so I don't want this to be about popping.
That said, I see you and I respect you.
And I know that you have this need.
And I want to give you the freedom and a safe space to explore this interest, which is a perfectly healthy interest.
It's just not one that I share.
Sure. Yeah.
And that's kind of how I feel with points.
Because, look, there's things like American Idiot.
I know the value that I can bring.
I know that like sometimes it's kind of funny if I'm there and bristling and annoyed at what's happening.
Points.
I just I got nothing.
I don't want to go anywhere near it.
I'm not annoyed enough for it to be funny.
I like I'm glad that you found this and I'm glad that the listener has responded.
But there will not come a time where I understand why points and apps are interesting to talk about on a podcast.
So that's why I am.
Here's my proposal.
OK, go ahead.
Topic hall passes.
This seems like, you know, very healthy thing to do in a marriage, I think.
Oh, yeah, that really is.
Is give hall.
Let you explore.
Go and have some freedom and then come back.
And then there isn't the resentment that you can't explore certain avenues.
And this is what I'm saying.
I want to when you guys are feeling the need, when you're feeling the urge, just say, Scott, I think it's time for a topic hall pass.
In an episode, not for a full episode.
No, for a full episode, I'm saying.
Oh, you don't even have to guys.
Guys, you don't even have to ask me if you are like, for example, Kohl's cash.
Kohl's cash that like that is an episode like you guys.
I want you to be happy.
I want you to do this thing that you need and love to do.
I don't want any part of Kohl's cash.
That's like popping to me.
So don't even ask permission.
You guys get together in your own time.
Do Kohl's cash.
Get Wiger in if it feels good.
I want you to have.
I want you to be able to explore and be yourselves and and and and to not feel shame and judgment from me.
Right. Go do Kohl's cash.
It's like I don't know.
How do you do this?
Does it seem like a good plan?
So points to is that a hall passage with Wiger?
You will.
You're saying you'll take you'll sit that one out.
I think I set that one out.
OK, because then I'm because not only then then I'm I get the freedom to do it.
I get the freedom to do something that I want to do, which is anything else but that.
You guys get the freedom of being able to talk without somebody button in.
I realize something else about this, which is that, you know, a little thing that Erin and I have.
She loves The Bachelor.
She watches every season of Bachelor and Bachelorette and Bachelor in Paradise when they come out.
This is a rare activity that we do not share.
And I've tried to find a way in.
I'm like, maybe I'll watch.
And you know what I'll do is I'll kind of like make snarky jokes about this as it goes.
And she's like, no, that's not what this is.
This is I watch this of all that this one's this isn't like watching a bad movie.
We watch this and it's pure.
And that's what this is.
And that's how I feel about this points thing.
I don't think people want me button in and like and doing my little my little jaded buttons.
I think I think you guys should be able to just just do it right.
Hey, look, again, I'm going to let the universe decide.
I don't even want to.
I appreciate what you're saying.
And I appreciate that you would say like, oh, I'll just I'll bud out because I feel like I would be a hindrance to the whole thing.
But I don't even want to leave it up to me.
I want to leave it up to the universe.
I want to let the God himself decide God themselves.
So does that mean just points to have to get voted on?
But listeners, I could even see a poll where it's points to with Scott points to without Scott.
And because then because then because I'm also thinking of the audience here, I want the audience to get what they want.
And that's what you see what I'm saying.
We're like, maybe my snark has a place in American Idiot.
I don't think it does in points to.
But let's let them decide.
Well, I don't know if you want a precedent where the audience is voting on episodes with or without you.
I don't think that might be a good thing in general.
I'm not even because I know which way we'll go.
I just think that might start to be a bad precedent.
Yeah, probably.
Probably.
Just a guess.
Just knowing how if I see one comment about an episode Jason and I did, I go, oh, it bumps me out for somebody's like, oh, these guys, I don't know about this episode.
I go, oh, no.
How do you think I feel, Mike?
How do you think I feel about the comments that people have already written based on what I've been doing for the last 15 minutes?
Look, I know this is a this is both a very popular episode and a lightning rod episode.
That's what's going to happen with this episode.
Yeah, yeah.
Which, again, I'll say it was voted for.
And also, it's Christmas.
It's Christmas.
Do you have to be mean to the host of one of your favorite podcasts right now?
Come on, spirit of harmony, spirit of bug main.
I've also seen funny enough in these last so many weeks, I've seen both comments saying that Jason and I are out of control tangenting and seen comments saying we're more on topic than we are without you.
I've seen both both comments.
And I go, well, which is it?
I've also I've seen people say that what you've been doing without me is unhinged.
The guys are unhinged.
Then I'll listen to things and I'm like, I've never heard anything more hinged in my life.
I'm talking about the quality of Wendy's lettuce.
How is this unhinged?
Yeah, the Wendy's coming soon.
The Wendy's lettuce got me on a doughboy's double to complete when.
Oh, that's great.
He's expert.
Yeah, Wendy's expert.
Wendy's lettuce enjoyer.
Jason Sheridan.
Well, I was not alone necessarily.
Everyone had a lot to say about Wendy's.
Sure, I believe it.
You mean them?
Of the hosts.
Of them.
Sure.
But you know what?
That's great.
That is the perfect venue for that.
Maybe the perfect venue for points is the points, but the nasty little point boys podcast or whatever the hell you were saying.
But you see how there is it like, you know, I started I entered into a theme park podcast.
I didn't enter into a points podcast.
And I think it's fair to say that that's maybe that's like kind of outside of the bounds of what was originally discussed here.
But if but if it's what people want to hear, then I just remove myself from the equation and then everybody's happy.
That's what you want.
That's fine.
If you want to do that, I'm comfortable with that.
I think it is what I want.
I don't want to dictate that it is what that it's what you want.
But I feel like it might be.
I think it might be.
I don't know.
I'm fine.
I'm comfortable.
I can roll with again.
I can roll with whatever it is.
And I look I think that I think that no matter who you talk to, you will find that points touch all of your life, everyone's life in different ways.
So yes, here's OK.
Because another thing that struck me during all this, a lot of what you said about points are things that I do.
Like it was like a lot of it was about shore points.
And I and it was like which I I checked my app.
I had a lot of I checked the app after that.
I realized I had enough for a regular sub.
Right. But not enough for a giant.
Not enough for a giant.
No, which was a bummer, because obviously you want to split that giant up and save it for the next day.
Well, Jason, what are we talking about?
It's a sandwich.
I agree with Jason on this.
Saving the sandwich the next day should be fine.
I sometimes a little way Mike's way, but that's going to be so fucking nasty.
That is going to go.
That's a sponge now.
I'm not a big Mike's way guy.
But sometimes I add this question.
That's especially if it's like a giant.
I'm like, well, I'm going to.
Well, what?
I'm going to cobble this.
So we get it.
Yes.
You get it. Jason's way.
Usually, which is which is with the spread.
That's what Hoagie's spread.
Yeah. Hoagie's spread.
Pepper, hot pepper spread.
Hot pepper spread.
And I like that spread.
It's just I think it's not.
I think I always I it when I'm there and then I don't end up going to have it in the fridge.
Mike's way.
Sometimes it gets soaks into the bread the next day.
It's almost even better.
It's like a wet.
It's a little wet.
But you don't eat wet bread as much as I do.
I don't know.
Because like at Portillo's you get the beef and cheddar croissant and it's like the bread is kind of wet and it's good.
And it's probably even better.
I get that in like I get that in like a French dip in the in the 10 minutes after it's been served.
Yeah.
A next day giant.
I just don't see it's just not what I would do.
I don't know.
But it doesn't mean I'm wrong.
Jay, you've never had a next day giant that was in Mike's way.
I think I've had like four hours later.
I didn't have time to finish my lunch.
So I just like wrapped it up and I don't like that.
I don't like a four hours later.
So no, I think I think it would be fine.
This is not to me.
This is not a pizza next day situation.
I think I think Mike's Wade bread ends up nasty after the fact.
But it's Mike.
You know, again, I'm not here to dictate.
I've learned a lot about my opinions are not necessarily correct.
They might be fully wrong.
But this see what we just had here is interesting.
It is an interesting little spark of a conversation.
And that is the kind of thing you would bring to a points to episode.
It's a strong opinion about having a day old Mike's Jersey Mike's Mike's way sub.
And that's kind of it.
That's interesting.
That's a new dynamic.
And shore points are what we call the towns at the Jersey Shore.
What sure point do you go to?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You didn't say that on the episode.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
Let's sit and listen.
Wait, say that again.
Shore points are like the different towns.
Like, oh, what?
You know, I give me an example.
Like Cape May or a barn again.
So instead of saying like a little town or a city, you would say point.
What sure point?
Yeah.
Oh, that's why it's called shore point.
I believe that is the point on the shore.
It's word play.
Instead of city.
It's the town.
That is interesting.
Some people go to Wildwood.
Kind of interesting.
Some people go to Ocean City.
See, and this is the thing about this is the thing that was the reason points the episode
captured the imagination of so many people across the country and the world is that everybody
does have opinions like you just exhibited that I don't want to eat a sub the next day.
That's interesting that we all have little things we feel about fast food and points
and the way we redeem.
Yeah.
So everyone has a different redemption strategy.
And even if you're not thinking about it, which I think is your is your I don't want
to say problem, but I was about to say problem.
Your problem with points is that these aren't you're not consciously thinking about your
points use your fast food use and your all this stuff in general.
But you do have opinions.
You do have strategies.
And are you saying that my opinions are valuable?
I am saying your opinions are valuable and interesting and probably reflect a lot of
the listeners opinions as well.
And I sometimes maybe if we can be criticized, Jason and I are on the same wavelength about
a lot of things.
That's something that I felt a lot is that like it becomes just a hive mind without me
there.
It's like one voice talking at the same time.
And then once in a while, he'll say something like my grandfather was ran security at a
pencil factory.
And then it will turn the voices off as far as unison.
And then I got no notes on that.
I got no I'll hear about the pencil factory.
I want to hear more.
I mean, this is maybe not the episode, but I want to hear.
I want you to dig in.
I got to figure this out because I am fast.
And I think the pencil factory little nugget.
A lot of people responded to.
And I am very curious.
Absolutely.
Here's the problem for me with the points stuff is that like I said, I use like, you
know, like I'm on that.
I'm on that Starbucks app a lot.
I will definitely like right.
You know, oh, OK, well, if I go four days in a row, maybe I can get my 50 stars.
Right.
It would never in a million years occur to me that what I just said was a story worth
telling on a podcast that people pay for.
Never.
And if anything, I'm like, OK, if I'm learning that I'm wrong and that that thought is valuable
that me said, like, like, is that allowed?
Like this whole time I've been thinking about how to keep things brisk and entertaining.
And then it turns out that I could say so I got 86 stars right now.
So I'm almost to 100 and then I can get a free iced tea.
Was that good?
What I just did?
Well, when the discussion then rolls out into what your general strategy, what is the tea?
Do you ever add the extras?
Do you ever have the straw?
Like, because I sometimes you had strawberries to a drink.
I kind of think the points are too much.
Like when you start to expand on what you've just said, then it becomes interesting to
a lot of people.
And what I think also is that you clearly have just as many opinions and strategies
as we do.
I do.
I've had a long I've just I've I've thought for a long time that those opinions are too
boring to share.
Oh, that is where I've been coming from.
And if this is everyone telling me to jump in the water and say all of these, I will.
And then this all seems good.
And this is progress.
I will say this should probably still be a podcast about theme parks, for Christ's sake.
Well, I agree with you.
But the contradictions are too many to bear.
Like at this point, when you say it should be about theme parks, I agree with you.
But there's too many examples of not being about theme parks.
Also, those little tricks and stuff.
Well, those little point tricks kind of these runs parallel to like, oh, OK, when I go to
the park, try to get there really early, because then it's empty.
Then you do this first and you do this first.
Skip this.
Watch out for the parade.
And what points?
I think points bond us together even stronger than theme parks, because you do points.
You use points every week.
People don't go to a theme park every weekend.
Do you mean us, like humanity?
Humanity.
You mean people?
People, yes.
People on the globe, on the planet.
So are you saying that if we, if the, I'm not, let's take we out of it.
Do you, if you two started the full Nasty Little Points Boys podcast, is that going
to be, have we been wrong about theme parks?
Is that going to be the hundred times more popular, the way that you cash in, the way
that you're big enough as a podcast now to have Trump and whoever runs against Trump
next time on the show, to where like in four years you guys shape the election, because
Nasty Little Points Boys has become so much more popular than Podcast the Ride.
Jason's doing like a Tony Hinchcliffe.
Oh, it was good to say, no, we outpace Joe Rogan.
We outpace Kill Tony, you know.
I think, I, yes, I mean, honestly, I think points is more of a universal topic than
theme parks, probably by a factor of 50, 100, I'm not sure exactly, because I think
people have a visceral, the people who love it, love it, but the people who don't are
a little like, ah, what is, what's a point?
But points, points and deals, people get behind.
Everybody loves deals.
Everybody loves points.
Everybody, I do, I do think that is what the attraction is about this specific topic.
Well, then what are you guys waiting for?
Go do Nasty Little Points Boys.
Maybe we will.
Again, I didn't think we were going to do it.
This is all, this all happened to me.
I didn't choose this.
I chose some topics.
This, this points game chose me.
So if there's a, if again, if the universe wants me to do a full points podcast with
Jay, fine, but it's got to choose me again.
I need another sign from the Almighty.
Well, okay.
I think this has to be outside of the poll.
Maybe another can, can the, well, this should just be a poll elsewhere is just this podcast
happen.
But now we're setting you up to like, this is a dangerous thing.
We're setting you up to do a second podcast with Jason.
No, I can't.
You said that you want the universe to do it to you.
I know, but that's not just like, I have to be visited in a dream by three ghosts or
something tonight.
Or like there has to be such a clear, or when I'm awake, let's that's okay.
When I'm awake, I need to see a ghost dream.
I was going to say you're already as if you're not already dreaming about points.
Yeah.
I dream about, yeah, exactly.
So I need to like on my way home, a ghost needs to appear in the car with me or something
and then tell me his circadian rhythms are not consistent enough to hit three rims cycles
where there would be three ghosts.
You haven't gotten a three ghost sleep in years.
Yeah.
Right about that.
That is true.
I barely, I barely dream.
Oh my God.
My brain can't.
My brain hasn't been able to like clean itself out in a long time.
I, Mike was involved in a dream I had recently in that I was looking at my phone and there
was just a text from him that said 12 PM and I woke up with a start and I was trying to,
I thought it was real.
I thought I had fucked up.
You were worried about being like missing a record or something.
Yeah, because I messed up the time on the Mazzotti episode and I never do that.
So then I was super paranoid, double and triple checking on all the other ones.
I see.
So it came into my dream where like Mike texted me, but in the dream it seemed like a threat
or like a warning because he just texted 12 PM with nothing else.
That's high noon.
Maybe I wanted to have a showdown with you.
Yeah, that's true.
Where we were going to sling a gun slinging or something.
Yeah.
Draw.
We're going to have a draw basically.
If that's where things had gone, like I leave for what, you know, seven episodes or something
and like, oh my God, they got into a duel.
I guess the two of them didn't get along as well as I thought.
I think with that 12 PM, I think that's one of the ghosts.
That was a haunting of Jason's brain.
I guess it has to be you, but I think that's Jason's brain getting incepted.
That was a start time for the first episode of Nasty Little Points Boys.
Maybe.
Because note that I didn't get the time in my dream.
That's true.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, we'll see.
If there are two more ghostly signs, maybe it has to happen.
Okay.
Well, so that was approximately 20 minutes away, perhaps more from the initial thing
that I want.
A tangent, you might say.
Interesting.
But on topic.
Yeah.
On topic.
All right, fine.
Doesn't count.
Not a tangent.
So let me go back to the word that I said a while ago.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because there's some other things to catch here.
Right.
That is cookieing.
Cookieing was brought up as just the context here.
And another thing that came up a lot was the notion that like Scott is screaming at his
phone right now.
Yes, yes.
Right.
When we can't place a fact or whatever it is.
And I will say, Mike, you had a very good meter for that.
Yes.
Like when you said it was usually when I actually was.
But one that was not flagged was the discussion of cookieing.
Okay, so you were in a maze, correct, Mike?
Yes.
Well, in a line to get into the maze.
Okay, okay.
And when you suddenly felt grazed on the elbow by a stranger.
Probably a teen, but yes.
By a teen, you say.
I'm guessing.
A teen cookieed you.
And this is said, and then that phrase doesn't make any sense to me.
Right.
And then you further explain the phrase that this is something that Jason would do backstage
in the old improv days.
And that this might be accompanied with the line, hello cookie.
It would be accompanied.
Well, yeah.
I mean, rehearsals.
We were always goofing.
Jason's house.
We would be doing rehearsals.
That sent shivers down my spine when you did that.
Yeah, I was saying I was just being a nasty little creep and would make everyone laugh.
So that was the point of it was to be, that was like a.
Just being a little weirdo.
A bit of a creepy man.
He would take his two fingers, okay.
I always thought three.
Oh, would you do three?
Okay, well he's the expert.
Cookie.
Yeah, no, explain the position of cookie.
The first three fingers, including the thumb.
And then as if he was examining like a diamond, sort of like turning it around in his three
fingers, he would put those three fingers on your elbow and then kind of turn a little
bit and say, hello cookie.
And then we called, so we started calling a cookie.
Yeah, it was just like nonsense improv practice bits where it's like, yeah, explaining this
to a human or a civilian will sound totally insane.
It scared me.
It scared me so much when you did it just now.
The gesture is weird.
If the listener could see these gestures and then mixed with that voice, oh my God, which
I guess.
So again, if the intention was to be a creepy bit, then mission accomplished.
Yeah.
Do you want to come on over?
Do you want a cookie?
Oh dear God, I do not.
Oh, how much do I not want a cookie?
I think you should get cookie down the show, honestly.
I think you should get cookie.
Next stage show, baby.
That'll throw, if you come to a Puck has the Ride live show and I'm like, hey, welcome
to, my name's Sam, fuck no, it's not my name.
If I'm really off, then you know that I just got cookie backstage.
You got cookie backstage by Jason.
I think what, I mean, we're also in the bit realm territory, I guess, but it just reminded
me so much of there's one, this was, this might've been said six years ago.
I don't know, but it has never left my brain.
And that was the, and this is, I think a close cousin to that.
And this is when, because Mike and Lindsay are what, like seven months older than Jason,
that that was enough of an age gap for Jason to frequently say, hello, mommy and daddy.
Jesus Christ.
They just got their shit together for a certain I did, you know, respectful.
It was respectful in my world was like an erotic thing.
Let's be honest.
That's the thing.
The tone is very, yes.
Right.
Hello, mommy and daddy.
Yeah.
It was like a sexual thing.
Oh, I assure you.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah.
You don't have to assure me.
I assume.
I know.
I get no matter how much a shirt, Michael never changes his mind.
Yeah.
Hello, mommy and daddy.
He said it multiple times too.
And I think he would say it to me and other people.
Like Marissa and I would like call mommy and daddy or something.
Like he would do that to other people as well.
That's my thing.
That's my memory.
I'm pretty sure.
I'm just always McGooing it through life, you know.
Mr. McGoo would not call people mommy and daddy.
Well, if you couldn't see them very well.
You might think they were.
Mr. McGoo was old.
His parents were dead.
We don't know that.
Mr. McGoo may have had alive 127 year old parents.
And if he thought he was seeing them, but was in fact running into a construction worker
at the end of a beam that he climbed on, then he might say, hello mommy and daddy.
How much sadder would the Mr. McGoo cartoons have been if not only was he blind, he was so out of it.
He thought his parents were still alive.
It's a totally different tone.
That was a whimsical cartoon.
I mean, probably, you know, it wouldn't make it now of an old man who couldn't see.
And that's the whole bit.
But also he's losing his mind.
I've never watched a live action.
There was Leslie Nielsen McGoo movie, right?
Yes.
Yeah, I've never watched that.
You say that as if you know that's not good.
You say that with curiosity.
I'm curious.
What were you just doing that with?
There was another movie that was a like clearly 90s piece of trick.
You're like, I'm curious though.
Maybe.
Coneheads?
Probably.
You've never seen coneheads?
Coneheads is a real mixed bag.
It has its moments, but it has its...
Look, I like a lot of Dan Aykroyd's work.
This man should not be shirtless.
This man should not be mostly naked in things.
Same with Billy Crystal in Oscar's openings.
A couple of shows, a couple of movies where Dan Aykroyd's shirtless, I feel like.
Or in like, Exit to Eden?
Is it Exit to Eden or East of Eden?
You might be right. I'm not sure.
I think it's Exit, but I could be wrong.
Doesn't matter.
Jason, don't be curious about that one.
I wouldn't even watch Exit to Eden.
The one where Dan Aykroyd...
It's a sex thing.
It's a sex movie.
He should watch it.
Which one?
Isn't it Exit to Eden?
I watched Exit to Eden.
It has cooking in it.
Exit to Eden, yeah, 1994.
And they're like in...
Rosie O'Donnell and Dan Aykroyd, they like are cops.
They go undercover like as an S&M thing or something.
How could this possibly have ended up being the poster?
I've never seen it.
How do you put that on the poster and think anyone will see this?
I don't know.
Directed by Gary Marshall.
It is?
What in the world?
I never knew that.
Geez.
Well, maybe Exit to Eden, second gate next year.
Yeah, good idea.
Let's do it.
A-okay, Mike.
Is there a flying check tackled Gary Marshall yet?
I feel like that's a big undertaking.
That'd be an interesting one.
Yeah.
Although by the time you get to Valentine's Day...
Oh, you got to do all the days.
How much are the days going to be?
Here's the thing that really has happened a couple times while you were gone.
I don't want to hijack this, but I brought up Country Bears again
because any time we watch something, I feel like Jason goes,
I think this is pretty good.
The only time he's ever not liked something was Country Bears.
I know.
It just hit wrong.
It just hit bad.
I got to go back.
I'm so mad.
I got to give it another chance.
You haven't given a bad review to any piece of media, I feel like, in years
other than the Country Bears.
Dinosaur was walked out on that one.
But that's a long time ago.
When did that come out?
Like nine years ago?
Ten years ago?
I'm just saying when we've been talking about stuff on the podcast.
Oh, when we've been doing the show.
Yeah.
I was going to say let Jason watch Exit Teen, but he's going to love it.
He's going to say it's great.
Have you seen this poster before?
Do you recognize them in S&M gear?
I don't recognize that poster.
I feel like the premise is more familiar.
I found that the key to some of the Jason movie opinions is like, did he see the
poster when he was in a good mood after buying a comic?
That is true.
How could you like this movie?
Well, I had just gotten pizza.
Yeah, I was having a great time.
We've got to sort of have a really great day for Jason and then have a bunch of
Country Bears.
Oh, that's true.
Have I told the Conehead action figure story?
Doesn't sound familiar.
Not recently.
So I did get you Conehead action figures for Christmas one year.
I got you Beldar.
Thank you, yeah.
When they came in the mail, he said, hello, Beldar and Primat.
Hello, French mommy and daddy.
I have a very clear memory of this one old historic department store in Ocean State,
New Jersey was closing down stands.
The space is now a co-op with little vendors and stuff.
And it's very charming and it's great for the community.
But when the department store was closing down, they had like all of these clearance
things.
They had just every department and the clearance in the toy department was just a
wall of Conehead's figures and they could not get rid of them to save their life.
What year are we talking?
When did the movie come out?
92.
So this would have been probably 93, possibly 94.
So just in no way it was, I don't think it was still open for a year or two in the
mid 90s.
But I just remember.
Did you buy them?
No, I didn't.
I never bought any.
So the story is that they were discounting figures?
They could not get rid of them.
I didn't know.
I didn't want them.
I didn't know anything about the Coneheads.
You should have bought them at least.
There would have been a good finish to the story.
I guess.
I think we bought puzzles.
Coneheads puzzles?
Huh?
No.
Oh.
Now I'm settling back into some of the joy that I had when I was listening and I got
to just hear Mike clarify what was the story.
This was one that was kind of on my list and this is maybe, this is like a, I'm going
to give you a big chance here, a stage.
We tread these boards and I just want to hear you say it.
This is from, what was the episode?
Tivoli Gardens with the Pell.
Can you tell us the story in a rapturing way of what happened to you at Excalibur?
This story is better than this Conehead story though.
I will say that.
There's something there at least.
I've only ever been to Excalibur once.
Okay.
It was very dirty.
I waited in a line trying to get rewards like free play.
Watched.
From the app, from the My Vegas app?
This is not going to help the story.
No, it's just color.
There's color to it.
It's adding color.
You're trying to sell me on the story, Mike.
He's treading the boards.
I'm not out of the story.
I'm helping him tread the boards.
He is helping.
I am not a high roller.
I don't go to Vegas very often.
But you love to gamble.
I do love to gamble.
Guys, this is hurting the story.
I'm helping.
You are absolutely not helping.
You wanted an engaging background.
No, I wanted Jason to tell the story without Mike making it about points.
I'm painting a picture with words.
Great.
I know.
I want you to do it, not Mike.
Here we go.
Go ahead.
2021.
Okay.
A mast recently reinstated in Clark County.
Mast indoors.
We're all wearing masts.
What's the population of Clark County though?
I don't know.
Say the name of the airport.
That's something you like to say a lot.
Well, it was McCarran for many years and then it became Harry Reid.
But people still call it McCarran.
We are treading these boards now.
So then what happened?
We're all wearing masts.
We're standing in this player's club line.
N95s?
Huh?
N95 masts?
I think it was just, we were doing surgical masts at the time.
Those don't work.
We didn't know that at the time.
I'm just, all right, just continue.
No bug main.
I'm voting for Mike's mask opinions.
What kind of masks was Mike wearing in 2021?
Do people want to hear about my Fauci takes?
Everything's only like half open.
There's kind of some crowds watching the Olympics.
People are starting to have fun again.
Anyway, we're all masks.
Who was the president again?
How soon was January 6th in the rear view?
I guess it would have been a few months.
So everybody, we're all recovering.
We're saying, let's make sure this never happens again
with no clue what future we were headed for.
Fully vaccinated at that point.
So we're all in this line of masks.
And then there's a couple of like a 20 year old,
like kind of skeezy looking guy and a much older woman
with blonde and purple braids,
just like full on make it out this line.
And it's just a very strange sight to see.
And we were in this line for a while
and we got to the front of it and they said,
oh, I'm sorry, sir, you've cleaned all your awards
for this trip.
Now the story is taking a turn
where the story is not about the purple.
Because I feel like when first told, the story was,
I saw people kissing in a line.
Yes.
Is the story about the points?
No, well, he's just adding color I think at that point.
I'm adding color.
I'm trying my best.
I'm just Magoo-ing it.
I can't do a Scott Free story with Scott here.
Let me tell you, I'm going to steal a Tom Sharpling thing
right now.
I'm going to steal the Limp Pet Shuttle right now.
This guy came up with Scott Free
and he was so pleased with himself at that invention.
And he was so excited.
He didn't even realize it was Ridley Scott's production.
Every time.
I was shocked when I saw Glitter.
That was a very good Sharpling.
Yeah, thanks.
Now I feel, okay, I don't know.
That was one that I was listening to
and like Mike in the episode,
I was kind of confused as to why it was a story.
It was a very just startling image
as everyone around you is wearing masks
and set this one May-December couple
and they're just going to town on each other.
Jason was horrified by their love.
Show me your marriage license.
I think it's interesting.
What I like about the detail is that the purple hair
always comes into it.
So the purple hair scared you on some level.
Seeing a senior citizen with very long,
half blonde, half purple hair, like braids.
That is very strange.
I would pay $500 to see a picture of this woman
to see how old she was.
I bet she was 50.
Yeah, do you have a guess on the age?
I would say 60.
60 is not senior citizen, I wouldn't say.
Not quite.
Well, you can join the AARP at 50.
I've been checking.
Let's go over the women.
This podcast is going to go long enough
that both of you are talking about the benefits
of the AARP protocol.
It's entirely possible.
Absolutely.
As soon as we are eligible,
we will be talking about social security, AARP,
our pensions.
Well, Jason and I will compare how much money
we're getting from the SAG fund
that we've paid into for all of our various commercial work.
That's all fair game if this show goes on and on.
$127? Why even send the check?
Well, that's not what Jason is going to show you.
Well, he's not going to say that. Are you kidding?
Jason is going to say, I've taken too much out of this.
Yeah, so that is absolutely, that will be happening
in a few years.
I don't pay for the racquetball courts at SAG headquarters.
I shouldn't be paying into the,
there shouldn't be an IOA for me.
Is that the right term?
Maybe.
HOA? HOA.
HOA is Islands of Adventure.
Yeah, that's right.
The first mention of theme parks in this episode.
And the last.
Let me ask, I know you have a list of stuff.
Yeah.
Was there any theme park heavy stuff that you're like,
oh shoot, or any episode topic in general,
you're like, oh shoot, I like that.
I did tell them not to do anything.
Well, you know what?
I mean, as I said, the one with Mazani was delightful.
I certainly would have had a lot of fun with you guys
and Gio and Zach.
Let me say, look, very deep into this.
There were a lot of great episodes.
There was a lot of very funny stuff.
Oh, thank you.
You provided comfort for me when I was way out of the comfort zone.
And here's one I want to compliment.
The one about the app with Jess McKenna.
Now, as you said, this is one that I signed off on.
I was going to do that.
That is not some like, I think there's a lot interesting about the app.
And I like that it was kind of about, that it was like thematic
and about like the, now the app robs you of your ability
to be a Disneyland Sherpa and that kind of thing.
And the way it forces everybody onto their phones
and the broader themes going on, I think, really big.
But there was a point, like over an hour in,
where you said, now Scott is screaming at his phone.
And you were exactly right.
It finally got into just reading the names of that kind of,
but I don't even remember what.
Yeah, I don't remember either.
I will say this.
Sometimes there's, I feel like there's a lot of like foe rage
at like the systems Disneyland puts in place
and we have a new thing and a new name.
You guys both love it.
You love every bit of it.
You love every new bit of hassle because it's funny to talk about
and it's fun for you, Mike, to try to like climb over the fence.
There could not be more systems added to it.
It would never satiate.
You guys, you love it.
You love these things.
There's some truth to that.
Yes, there's, well, I acknowledge on the episode as well
that there is a, it's a double edged sword
that you're getting dopamine hits.
So there was an acknowledgement that some of it does prove satisfying
for a certain type of brain.
There are things, mobile ordering I love.
I couldn't love it.
I love now pulling times for mobile orders.
You keep double checking.
You can pull times like fast passes for mobile ordering.
So if you're a hungry bear, barbecue, jamboree, whatever it's called,
as the time says, well, you can make one for 5 p.m.
Keep refreshing.
You can get one for right now.
Let me tell you something.
This guy, this guy, one time we're at Bengal barbecue.
He mobile orders.
He beats me to my order for by about 60 seconds.
Look, he gives the smug look because he has a little stick snack.
60 seconds earlier.
The look on this face.
Efficient.
I would say efficient.
You had 60 more seconds of chicken enjoyment.
Well, not more seconds.
60 earlier seconds.
60 earlier seconds than teriyaki chicken.
I think this is what he said when we interviewed Len Testa in his hotel room
and I said something about checking and Len said, well, you're optimizing.
Yes.
Correct, Len.
Optimization.
That had like a gold bloom to it.
Yes.
Optimization, yes.
Mike's taking over the wizard role in Wicked Part 2.
He's practicing.
Bad news.
Yeah.
Well, if you like the casting.
I'll hold it.
So it's half true, half true.
I would get rid of that 7 a.m. wake up for the virtual queue,
which when we go to Tiana, we won't have to do it.
Oh, yeah.
They have turned it off.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
It's one less hoop you have to jump through.
That must be such a bummer for you.
That's 7 a.m.
If you're not waking up at 7 a.m. already though,
that sucks.
Yeah.
So I am happy that that doesn't exist.
That is insane.
Forcing PBI.
Look, I've been working about this.
Guardians is still on a virtual queue like that.
Really?
In Florida.
Oh, in Florida.
Yeah, sorry.
Is that the last man standing in terms of height and anything?
I think Tron is standby at this point.
Yeah.
And then Haunted Mansion went back already to regular.
I think Haunted Mansion holiday out here.
There is a standby.
Oh, I am so excited to figure out if I don't like the gift shop.
We're not going to talk about it until October, but the gift shop has a lot of discourse about it.
Which gift shop?
The Haunted Mansion gift shop.
Okay.
The big building they built outside the exit to Haunted Mansion.
Yeah.
And I've seen a lot of discourse and I obviously saw it being built, but I'm ready.
They put up a sign that I will.
Spoiler alert.
I don't like it.
You don't like the sign already?
It looks cheap.
The sign looks cheap.
We're already in a bad territory just with the sign.
So this is something important right here.
Yeah, yeah.
The sign looks kind of...
Did you see the sign?
Yeah, I don't know that I like the sign either.
I think they also...
I don't know if they...
I think it's supposed to be like the mansion's carriage house.
So the one side is supposed to look mansion-y.
The other side is supposed to be copacetic with Tiana's.
Like a shed.
That's a tough thing.
And I don't know if they...
I mean, they're the pros at that sort of thing, but I think they maybe cheaped out a little
too much.
We'll see.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't...
This almost feels like a...
This is like a regular feed, maybe worthy observation.
But maybe it's...
But it's also such a nascent observation that maybe I save it here behind the double paywall.
I got a bad feeling about Donkey Kong.
I got a bad feeling about this ride.
The videos are confused.
The one thing...
First of all, it's short.
Yeah.
Which is okay, but I picture you're standing in a two-hour line for that thing and you
end up feeling like that was that.
I think the problem, if there will be one, is just that those indoor show scenes are
underwhelming.
Yeah, they do seem...
That's the problem, because I bet being in the big temple, the temple looks awesome.
Being outside, I bet the ride system...
Animatronics is good.
Animatronics are good.
I bet the ride system does feel fun to feel like you're flying.
It's obviously not going to be on the level of Hagrid's, but I do think the bummer is
that it's just going to be short and those indoor sections aren't like, oh my God, cool.
It's just a little bit, I don't know, janky.
So it's not going to...
I don't think it's going to be a failure, but it's not going to be like...
It's not still going to be what we want.
It's not Mario Kart.
That's the bummer.
Yeah.
I was hoping it was going to be, well, this is it for Nintendo, and I agree it's not going
to be...
That it's going to rescue the entire endeavor.
Right.
Which we had questions about the quality.
I don't think it's that, but then there's so much other stuff like Donkey Kong, the
big suit.
You saw the photos of that, or pictures?
You know what?
That suit's giving me the big things in small spaces.
I'm scared of that suit.
Oh, no.
Yep.
That's a scary suit to me.
I'm impressed by it, but I think I would be...
I'm excited about this suit.
It's so big.
Even if you're outside?
They are testing.
Yeah, it's outside.
Yeah, that might...
I don't know.
It's still...
You know, it was giving me a weird claustrophobia just in the frame of the video.
This is a big suit.
What if somebody were to inflate Donkey Kong?
Would that...
Jason, you can answer this, too.
Okay.
Again, a lot of people have backed me up on this.
No, no, no.
As I said, we're not saying it's fake.
It's not my thing.
It's just fascinating.
It's a fascinating thing to now be aware of in my life, and I don't think it really helped
with my metaphor earlier.
It's a podcast fact now that you're the butt master and that you like inflatable stuff.
I know you don't, but it's podcast fact that you're into inflatable stuff.
With popping, I don't know.
It's...
We don't know about that, but I don't know...
People have to maintain some air of mystery.
The popping stuff is none of my business, but it's podcasts, it's kayfabe that you love
inflatable stuff.
I know you don't, but in the reality of podcasting, right, it's true.
Have fun with the character that you play.
Right.
Donkey Kong is awesome.
The land looks cool.
Getting to see the rhino come out of the box and stuff.
That's great.
Seeing Mr. Miyamoto going around.
That's all delightful.
Yeah.
I'm not counting it out.
I wanted to watch that video.
I hate to talk about theme park stuff, but have we seen the bioreconstruct, the footage
of the lighting packages happening for Helios Grand and for the...
A little bit.
That's so good.
This place thing is magical.
The roller coaster, whatever it's called now, because they had to change the starfall racers.
Star dust racers now.
With the lights off, it looks like a comet's going through the sky.
I'm getting so excited.
There's this crazy lightning effect from the Frankenstein castle or whatever, whoever's
castle it is.
It looks like it explodes somehow.
It looks like there's a glitch in the video.
The thing looks so cool.
Wow, really?
I haven't watched all of them.
I just saw this, I think this morning, and it looks like...
I couldn't tell what happened, but all of a sudden it shorts out and there's a huge
explosion of light that looked like the video shorted out.
There was some sort of electronic interference, and I was like, holy shit, this thing at night.
It's light effects so wild that our existing cameras can't handle them.
Right.
I think that was from bioreconstruct.
It was, I don't know.
You know what?
Send bioreconstruct to New Jersey to figure out what this goddamn drone situation is.
You already know what I'm talking about?
Have you seen these?
This is alien stuff.
Neither of you know about it.
I think we might be in another I'm not into the popping situation.
Jason does know.
I think it's often turned out to be like FedEx flights or...
Oh, Jason, you don't know.
Some of them are drones.
No, you do not know what you're talking about here, my friend.
People are shooting at them.
People are shooting lasers.
We don't have time to talk about this, but this is 2020.
This might be a tap out, but I would be interested to hear your feelings on UAPs.
Maybe I should be part of them, but it's possible that this could be an example of
a topic hall pass for both Jason and I to leave.
Well, I don't know, because there's that Acroid UFO special.
Yes, I own it.
Yeah.
I own a DVD of it.
You put it on multiple times at your old apartment.
Somebody also figured out, I saw on Twitter the other day, somebody also figured out the
same thing I figured out, that he's wearing his Christmas with the cranks outfit while
he's being interviewed.
So he's probably in his trailer.
Absolutely.
He's smoking chain smoking cigarettes in his Christmas with the cranks vest and shirt,
and this strange man is interviewing him about aliens.
Wardrobe loves when you return an outfit back to the smell of cigarettes.
They know what they get with Mr. Acroid.
Well, he's smoked on, but maybe he kept it.
Anyway, enough Dean Park talk, enough alien talk.
Let me carve out a little space for this.
I thought that I had my list.
I thought that I had my stockpile of the episodes that I wanted to hit and the moments that
I wanted to hit.
I thought it was done.
And then you guys dropped a bomb, and the bomb was called Spirit Christmas.
Yes.
The Jason's trip report from going to the holiday equivalent of Spirit Halloween, this
new store endeavor.
This had so many, there was so many little things in here.
I want to dive to this in our remaining time.
Because those sweaters are so funny, and you're jealous you didn't write them, right?
Let me really quickly, let me do my impression of the entire episode.
I think in two lines, I can sum up the entire episode.
So Jason, here's one.
It says, Fa la la la la, la la la lit.
And then Mike, now who would buy this?
Who is buying this?
Just like, it felt like, all right, and repeat 45 times and start.
We got to Phantom Thread, the animated series, there were a lot of good things that came
out of.
Oh, no, no, no.
There were.
Oh, absolutely.
And the listeners got the slideshow.
We put the...
Fa la la la la.
Yes, indeed.
Eat my ass.
You know?
Jingle, jingle.
All right, here's one.
Jingle bells smell my balls.
Now this is, now who, nobody would, who would ever, who would, that was a valid question,
who would wear it?
That's why I predicted they're going out of business.
Like fucking normies, you know, bad Christmas sweater parties, that dumb trope.
Yes, I hear that.
But that's for a small section, that's not the whole, a whole store, that's not going
to sustain.
But it's, don't you think, and maybe Jason, maybe you agree, that this is a, like, these
are meant to be purchased and never worn.
I think these are gag gifts.
Well, I said it's a gag gift, sure.
I think gag gifts.
Very possibly.
I think, and again, I enjoyed this episode.
I'm not saying this is...
Sure, sure.
I'm not saying this to say, I think what is so funny to me is the indignancy.
Mike's obs...
Sometimes I feel like Mike is going to lead a Tipper Gore-esque charge against PG-13 sexuality
in public places.
Your glasses get so fogged about the lightest...
But then you will start talking about, like, pegging and taints and shit.
But it's like, either you need it to be all the way, or if it's that in between, if it's
like, if it's in the PG-13 zone, you're like, you go red.
If I can control the dirtiness, it's comfortable to me.
If I see it in the world, it gets a little dicier.
If I see it in just a random store that people wander into and you purchase items, that's,
I don't know, like, why would you do it?
Why would you buy it?
But if I'm allowed to sort of run wild with the filthiness, then I think it's in, now
I can control it.
I can control sexuality.
I can control...
Listen to this handmaid's-tail shit this guy's saying, he wants to control sexuality over
here.
Well, not for the world.
I'm just saying I can sort of, once you gain, I can gain power over my sexuality finally.
You know, Jason's a comfortable sexual being.
That's right.
He wants to be comfortable with our sexuality.
He explained that sex was fun a couple months ago.
It was very helpful to me.
You know what, and I don't want to be too graphic, but, and we didn't go all the, but
my wife and I talked about it, and we are considering using sex to connect as partners.
It's on our to-do list.
Very cool.
Lizzie and I are not there yet.
We're both working on it.
But I think, you know, when I can be filthy, again, because by the end of that episode,
I was suggesting other filthy topics, then I feel right in the zone, but when I see it
out in the wild, I don't know how to deal with it.
I don't know how to grapple with it.
You clearly don't, because this is, this portion is going to be a little bit of a court
transcript situation.
Go ahead, yeah.
You start talking about the main store of the parent company of Spirit Christmas Day,
which is Spencer's Gifts.
Here are some quotes that you say in describing Spencer's Gifts.
You can buy wild stuff in a Spencer's.
You can buy lingerie and dildos.
It's still sort of lawless in there.
They are an outrageous store and they are getting away with it still in 2024.
Getting away with lawless.
And then when specific examples are prompted, your examples are lingerie and dildos.
Okay, lingerie, obviously that's silly to hear that written back to me, but you can't,
are there a place, is there a place in Glendale Galleria that you could buy a dildo other
than Spencer's?
Is there a dildo store?
Does the Westfield Mall regularly have a dildo store?
I'm not saying that dildos are bad.
I'm not saying vibrators are bad.
I'm just saying.
There wasn't that air in the way you were saying the sentence at all.
I'm just saying it's shocking to have it in a mall like that.
Target is carrying more like sex toy stuff.
Are they really?
Really?
Yeah.
Buy like the condoms and lube and such.
Is it an actual vibrator or a dildo?
Yeah, sure.
There's a dildo in Target.
Yeah.
You can buy a dildo, can I, mobile order?
Can I pick that?
All right, now I like the points conversation.
Can we use Target red circle points to get a dildo?
Can we have a dildo delivered here before the end of the record at least a vibrator?
There was a deal.
You get a $50 credit if you sign up for their $50 delivery service, which I did.
So I could get a delivery sent here as long as we keep recording for another two hours
or so.
And let's see if we can get a dildo delivered.
Just have it sent to your home.
I don't think we will be going by then.
Just have it sent to your home unannounced.
Lindsay gets the package and go, oh, I guess Mike does want to connect with me as a sexual
partner.
Okay.
Here we go.
There's a vibe.
I mean, what's the difference between a vibrator and a dildo?
Really?
That's also a thing.
Mike.
Isn't a dildo is more like it looks like a thing.
Yeah.
Vibrator can be a multiple shapes and sizes.
Right.
But do they both like, what is this?
Dildo also probably does not vibrate necessarily.
That's what I was going to say.
There's a motor.
Correct.
Okay.
We can get a Hello Cake spin stroker vibrating men's personal massager.
Oh my God.
You can buy a, you can buy a flesh light at Target.
Jason knows what he's talking about again.
He's so comfortable with sexuality.
He's buying flesh lights at Target.
Jason, do you have this spin stroker?
I do not.
It's or, oh, first of all, I love the orange.
That very fun orange.
Very sexually appealing color.
Can you buy it?
Let's see.
Okay.
This is not in store though.
Let's see if the things are in store.
That's really what I'm looking for.
I am surprised about this information.
I did not know that there were sex toys at Target.
Pick up.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Hello Cake, that seems to be the brand.
You can get, okay, you can get, Hello Cake, this is a thrusting vibrator.
You can get it at Target.
Wow.
Jason's right.
So maybe my feelings, because there's a Target connected to the Galleria.
My feelings are outdated.
I guess so.
What Jason has just proved is that there are multiple places to get sex toys in the Galleria.
And I will go back and we will special edition that episode.
And I will say, and I will say Spencer's is a normal store.
There's nothing weird about it.
Now, Target, it's a little like more reserved.
Spencer's gift, it is weird when you go from like a Pickle Rick to like Simpsons posters
to like a weird edible penis pasta.
You're saying Target is a classier place to buy a sex toy.
Low key.
Target is the more.
Spencer's is aggressive.
Yeah, Spencer's is like Bachelor Party.
You can buy like a vibrator with Shrek on it in Spencer's.
Yes, that would be funny.
The big green monster.
Which is still wild, lawless.
Because Shrek on a vibrator is lawless.
So I guess in that way I would, I could still.
I think what jumped out at me was the phrase, they're getting away with it.
Mike, what do you want to happen to the people who run Spencer's gifts?
Lock them all up.
Clear, lock them all up.
Still hanging on.
A lot of them in malls.
I saw someone like this, Spencer's gift has been here for like 40 years.
And that's what, yes, that's the thing.
This has been, you've had a lot of decades to acclimate to the fact that there is a store
in a lot of malls that sells sex toys.
And yet you are still using the phrase, getting away with it.
And also, if lingerie is a problem for you, lingerie in the mall, I've got bad news, my
friends.
These, I'm doing these off the top, sometimes you say things and you listen back and maybe
that was incorrect.
So yes, of course lingerie is in the mall.
It's a silly, I was just off the top of the dome.
And we love, you love to see it as the lingerie.
I put it everywhere and they'll put it out in the center court, I say.
When I get a pizza slice, wrap it up in a teddy, I say.
He's like Jack White, you know, he goes, like Jack White goes on stage.
He says he goes off stage, doesn't remember what he just did.
Mike's just created.
It's like jazz.
I mean, that is true, by the way, I don't remember a lot of things I said.
I'm the owner.
So what's the name of your band, White Stripes?
This will never, you did not play it as you played it on the record.
You demand it.
You'll never make it.
Are you husband and wife or your brother and sister?
What is with this tomfoolery?
The audience needs to understand it or they'll never accept it.
A mystery?
That'll never work.
Sutterfuge in rock and roll?
This dirty conversation has put my left leg to sleep.
It's on pins and needles and I don't know why that is.
What?
Yeah, my left leg is numb.
We broke him.
We said lingerie isn't, you said vibrator's at target and now Mike is like struggling
physically.
His central nervous system is shutting down.
You can buy Hello Cake vibrating stroker ribbed massager for him, which is like, look
at this.
This is just like a little plastic thing to put your thing in and I guess you rub it up
and...
Your thing.
That was a very confident yes from Jason.
I know, I caught it.
I like that as well.
Yes, yes.
Jason, are you familiar with the cake brand?
Well, I am familiar with the cake brand.
Thank you very much.
I will say this.
It's a reliable, trustworthy brand.
I love the design of these cake sex products.
I think that they're very colorful and they're very whimsical in nature.
They almost look like...
The figure he's finding his way in.
He's finding sex toys that are bright and colorful like the barely alcoholic drinks
that he drinks.
Right.
Now we've got it.
Now we can understand why a sex toy might be.
Bright pinks and purples and yellows and oranges and all the colors of the rainbow to stimulate
all the different parts of your body.
I was going to have to clear off a shelf for a different kind of tool.
It's toys, Mike.
It's completeness.
Toys at Target.
It's what you're all about.
This has always been waiting there for you.
There is a deal I think happening too.
$10 or maybe that's just a broad deal, $10 off.
They consider these beauty and personal care purchases.
So if you spend $40, you get $10 off.
And if you have that Target card, get 5% off automatically.
We talked about that, of course, on points.
Plus one waterproof and rechargeable vibrating ring.
Oh, this is like, is this like Green Lantern's ring or something, but it vibrates?
Jason, do you know what this does?
Yeah, that's right.
Yes.
I'm sure that's what the makers were thinking.
It's just like Green Lantern's ring.
But what does this mean?
Does it mean you stimulate, you use, how does this work?
Mike, it's a cock ring.
It is?
That's my favorite thing that's happened since I've been gone.
Jason, this is thick.
This isn't going on your cock.
Are you sure you think it is?
You think it is?
I think I, I don't understand the perspective I'm looking at here, but I would bet.
I thought a cock ring, I thought a cock ring has to be sort of the same circumference like
a ring around your finger, like a wedding ring.
I thought that it has to be there because it just has to restrict the blood flow to
make it harder.
That's my understanding of it.
Yeah.
So you're saying Jason is, Jason is balancing how much he wants to say.
And I'm excited to hear what he has to say.
You know what?
And I look, I've been, I've been giving it to Jason a lot, but I think it's fair for
Jason to not now have to reveal all of the things.
I do.
I feel like I reveal quite a bit of myself on this show.
Even I have my boundaries.
Yes, that's right.
But I will say, I don't know what I'm looking at with that thick top of the cock ring, but
I believe it as a, what do you, what else do you think it would be?
Let me guess.
Okay.
You can just give me a nod if I'm okay.
What it is then, if it is what you're saying it is, and I do believe that you know what
you're talking about.
This goes all the way to the close, like closer to your body on your penis.
And when you're doing the thing, this is hitting the outside and it's vibrating.
Yes.
Congratulations.
Very interesting, isn't it?
This has been the most educational episode.
It really has for, I assume Scott and I, but maybe not.
Maybe he's being coy.
I, no, I'm not being coy.
I honestly don't know anything about this area.
Wow.
That's interesting.
I never thought about it.
I always thought about those things in a different way, but this is like a new technological
achievement.
Sure.
This is good.
We are witnessing an awakening with Mike because as soon as he's realized, he's realized a
couple of things.
These are toys and you can use deals and apps and points to get the toys at a decent value.
I apologize to Spencer's gifts.
I really do.
I apologize to them.
I apologize to the people who purchase.
You're making them a pariah, which they are not.
What you found is the target is leading the industry charge towards affordable sex toys
in our shopping malls.
Now you can go into Spencer's gifts and feel a little more normal when you're buying your
smiling friends boxers or whatever.
I've never seen this show.
This show's apparently huge.
Yeah, people love it.
I haven't watched it.
I just haven't caught it.
There's something called Tush Cush, which is Tush Cush lube for backside play.
Correct.
I mean, I know what that is.
Yeah, a lot of people.
Yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
So now this is the new pattern of this episode is you just reading every type of toy, looking
at Jason for acknowledgement with a look that's like, do you know about this?
Have you used this?
Wanting too much information out of Jason, frankly.
I don't think anything I've asked, most people would know actually the answer to the questions
I'm asking is really, is really what I'm getting from him.
I haven't asked for anything specific.
Well, that's where I'm like, I don't know.
I honestly don't know a lot of things that you're talking about.
I think I just feel like I don't, I don't like, I just don't get so harumphy about the
notion that there's lingerie in a store that's a wall separated from a Lego store.
I accepted this about the world.
I didn't call for them to be put out of business.
Well, I just wanted to know what getting away with it means.
Getting away with it implies.
I didn't ask who the CEO of Spencer's was.
Just saying.
A masked man used an extra vibrating cock ring to assassinate the-
I did not, I did not ask.
The 3D printed ghost cock ring to take the CEO of Spencer's out of commission.
My goodness.
There's so many more things I want to say here, but we've asked two questions.
He wrote, didn't I depose Pickle Rick on the murder weapon?
I am genuinely, I'm like, cutting, I have so many things that I'm not going to do, but
there's, maybe, this might need a sequel, I don't know, but I love the ones that we
landed on on the way out the door and we'll wrap it up, but because we're in spirit Christmas,
I cannot let this episode end and not ask further questions about Mummum and Pup Pup's
barrel of walnuts.
Oh, the barrel of walnuts.
This was-
I think it's an old fashioned thing if you were born in like 1917 or 1919, you know?
Yes, which is also when you would have to be born to be entertained by Momma's family.
And again, this is a big thing I want to clarify, and I think it's a misunderstanding that listeners
have and that people have, is that when Jason brings up something, it's not that we're
saying we don't believe Jason.
I know that there are probably barrels of walnuts.
I've never, much like the type of cock ring you're showing me, I've never seen it, but
I believe that it's real.
So barrel of walnuts, I understand, and this seems like a cherished childhood memory.
Here's the thing.
There's no way this barrel was three feet tall.
That's madness.
There's no way that your grandparents had a full to the brim three foot tall.
I think it is smaller.
I mean, it could have been two feet, but it was a sizable barrel.
This might also help clarify for me.
Do you think it was full to the brim with walnuts?
Like is it walnuts from bottom to top, or is there some sort of like, is there some
cushioning or like, is it halfway full so that the walnuts are only towards the top
of the barrel?
I think there were walnuts, chestnuts, maybe cons or Brazil nuts.
It was on the floor, though.
It was in the corner of the dining room, yeah.
Here's the thing, though.
If it was on the floor, it couldn't be one foot.
You would put that on a counter.
That's a good point.
So that is an argument in favor of it being at least three feet, because if it was two
feet even, I feel like you're like, put that on a table.
Mike's right.
I'm trying to figure it.
So I would have been three feet tall for the kid.
Three feet might be the right barrel size.
Three feet is what's bothering me, because three feet is, I don't know exactly how tall
my oldest son is, or, and I don't know how tall your daughter is, but that's a degree
of barrel that would bury your children for the most part.
They're barely hanging on it.
My daughter's two inches away from going on Space Mountain and Big Thunder.
Well, that was an old thing, and you cannot make her go on all these rides.
I never said I was.
I was very concerned.
I was surprised that you could let somebody who was 40 inches, I thought that meant they
were eight years old.
I forget when that was, but I'm like, oh God, is he going to force her on a Guardian?
What are we doing here?
I am not forcing, Jess forced a family member on, that's what happens.
He throw Jess under the rug.
Hey, I'm just saying, maybe you got confused.
I didn't say I was taking her on Guardians.
She was the one arguing to you that size does not equal a willingness to do it, or being
ready to do it.
I'm not doing that.
That being said, I think my daughter would love Big Thunder Mountain.
I think she'd go wild for it.
I hope so.
If it was my first roller coaster, she would not, that anything, well, there's a little
darkness.
That's what I'm facing with my son currently too.
She loves to be whipped around.
She loves.
I think I probably went on it when I was in like third, first grade.
I don't know that I went on it at two and a half.
I am shocked.
I literally thought it's like, well, you have to graduate second grade to go on these rides.
And the answer is no, you can be two and a half years old and go on Space Mountain.
And that blows my mind still.
It's hard to imagine doing, and that'd be a disaster for my son for sure.
But this is, I just like, because the size next to our children, I think, makes me feel
like there's no way it's three.
And also three feet, I looked it up.
Three feet is a wine barrel.
That's like an industrial size.
It was skinnier than a wine barrel for sure.
Oh, that helps me.
Okay, okay.
It was skinnier.
Interesting.
But do you, I feel like, are you, are you getting closer to two?
Because that seems, three feet just seems like, like the pure volume, the amount of
walnuts that would have to be, or I guess it was all a variety of nut is what you're
telling me.
But like, how many, here's a question.
How many people year round have access to this barrel?
Well, I think it's always accessible, but it usually wasn't like, I think my pop-up
would fill it up at Christmas time when he was having people over.
Okay.
And you get the crab crackers out.
The crunchers, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
And then that's a fun activity for the, I was just, I was just bristling at the notion
that, because like, imagine, imagine me picturing, let's go back to Donkey Kong, a Donkey Kong
sized barrel that is nothing but pure walnuts.
I feel like we might be talking about like a thousand dollars worth of walnuts in there.
No, no.
It was a smaller barrel.
I didn't mean to imply it was a barrel that I wear with straps, you know?
It sounds almost like it's more of like an umbrella holder skinniness or something.
A little wider than that.
Okay.
But yeah, I don't know, is it not barrel?
I don't know what to say.
But it was barrel shaped?
Yes, of course.
How does it, what Mike is showing, how does that, what would you, if you had to take that
and alter it in Photoshop, where it was to hold it out, what has to be, imagine that's
three.
What do you do to that barrel to make it your childhood barrel?
Just shrink it skinny wise?
I yeah, I think a little skinnier, maybe a little shorter, but it was, I think it was
tall enough that an average size adult could reach in and grab some without bending down
too far.
Wow.
I bet it was that tall.
But my question remains, like, is that, like, is it literally enough barrels to where there's
there could be, because like the barrels, I'm sorry, the walnuts down at the bottom
are not getting touched for years, potentially.
Well, no, I don't think it was, it kind of, I believe it had a divider in it.
And so it was, that was probably, imagine it was bigger than a popcorn tin, but imagine
how that split up.
Sure.
So we refills it every year.
I don't think stuff is lingering in there for too long.
Okay.
So it's true to the bottom.
I believe so.
Well, that's what you just said, divider.
That's what that's still what's bugging me is that filling up, like, don't you agree
that that we're talking maybe hundreds of dollars worth of walnuts in there?
I don't think so.
No, I think or walnut prices 30 years ago.
Yeah.
So think about 30 years ago, he's buying like bags of the in the shell nuts, which I'm sure
are cheaper because they don't have to be processed.
You know, just because it's club three and people have to vote, why not walnut price
trends with Jason Sheridan on club three?
That's such an insane, that's so out of my realm of expertise.
No, what are you talking about?
I mean, I can look, I can...
You've made this man now, you've stared in his eyes to make him tell you what he knows
about cock rings.
And now we're going to make him research what walnut prices were in the 1980s.
I do have questions about that cock ring, I'll be honest with you.
What's that?
How many cock rings do you think would fit in one of these barrels?
Oh, quite a bit.
To me that seems, the cock ring seems unpleasant.
Someday when Jason becomes the pup pup and we have an even more, a sexually liberated
society that's not full of a bunch of Mikes who want Spencer to get locked up, then his
grandchildren will come over and he'll say, hey, go ahead and scoop into the cock ring
barrel.
Once you're imagining like a barren type, a benevolent barren type with a monocle, it's
like, ah, Lord Spencer, come let the children, the less fortunate in town pick what you would
like.
I have more than I could ever touch or know what to do with.
Take whatever you'd like.
Nightmare before Christmas, ugly sweaters and vagina shaped pasta for all.
Oh, watch out for Arthur Clown.
He might be hiding.
How does Arthur Clown come up this much?
Arthur Clown was the big closer on Spirit Halloween.
There's no desire to watch the movie.
I mean, I'll get around to it.
It's on like every streaming service.
You gotta get to Exited and Conehead and then the Mr. McCool.
What did you also catch, and maybe you didn't fully listen to this episode, the episode
about Friendsgiving where Jason said that he was making a point to watch a lot of Christmas
or Christmas Halloween movies this year and he got to one.
Yeah, I got fucked up.
I had a lot of doctor's appointments.
He said this year I'm watching a lot of horror movies and around October 29th he decided
to start and it did one and it was, what, Halloween 3?
Yeah, I picked the weirdest one.
I didn't even get to it.
There's a Hulu original Halloween horror comedy, Chris Elliott and DJ Qualls, and I'm like,
I'm gonna watch this thing.
I love both of them.
You didn't get to anything.
DJ Qualls?
Yeah, I think he's great.
He's changed from love to like.
I think he's great.
I didn't realize he's had a whole, he's been in like every TV show I haven't missed.
I don't really have an opinion on DJ Qualls.
I'm not mad at him.
It was funny in all those 2000 comedies.
I think it should be a choice now.
Maybe this is like whether you want to engage with DJ Qualls or take a hall pass in DJ Qualls.
Maybe Jason wants to do a solo episode about his strong love of DJ Qualls and then you
and I can sit it out and go get some fresh air.
If Jason wants us to leave.
I could probably talk to him.
It's just a whole career retrospect.
DJ Qualls, he probably lives here in LA.
We probably have friends of friends, you know?
Maybe we do.
If Jason wants, I would like Jason to sit with a mic alone and just talk about DJ Qualls.
Was that a potential?
That could be Club 3 Jason alone.
That could dethrone Bugman.
Jason's soul.
Is this something Jason wants to do?
The first Jason solo episode is just talking about DJ Qualls to no one.
I mean, I am interested.
I mean, I was texting about this.
I was texting with Patrick Monahan.
I feel like I could have a nice conversation.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is Jason solo.
I really figured solo episodes would be more monologue-y.
Yes, a monologue about DJ Qualls.
It's like the start of a Marin episode.
Some Mente music in the background.
Some David Lynch-esque music in the background.
If you want to play music in the background.
If music keeps the spirits up, then yeah, it gives you the energy you need.
Yeah, all right.
So, Lynch-y in music while Jason just talks about DJ Qualls.
Oh, I don't want to do this.
Bugman's fucked.
This is going to be so...
I'd rather research the walnut prices.
Well, there you go.
I want to be on the walnut episode, though.
Oh, okay.
Do you want to all pass for that?
I don't know.
That is a little interesting.
It could be interesting.
I'll determine when I get there.
This could be a case-by-case.
You're right.
We won't put it in the audience's hand because that could be dangerous to start saying,
who do you want to sit these out?
But, you know, this was, I think, very educational.
This is a fascinating conversation that went in a lot of directions.
I didn't expect it to go.
I'm excited to see where the future goes in terms of is it Hall passes or do I start...
Do I unlock my inner...
Like, it actually...
There was something kind of touching about you saying that my points...
Opinions have value.
They do.
And you don't even know it.
You didn't even know it until today.
Look what I've learned.
So, I thank C. Allen Kelly for voting me.
I thank the universe for choosing points for you.
I thank the universe for choosing this for me.
And just in terms of there being no hard feelings about various ribbings,
Merry Christmas, boys.
Oh my god.
Whoa!
There you are.
Thank you.
Thank you for enduring.
Can we add these sort of apps right now?
Let's see your speed.
This is the duel, you guys.
While I wrap it up, the duel is who can get the points loaded.
Now, I was wondering if you even like this.
Or if you don't like gift cards because you don't get to earn points.
I was like, this might be a problem.
Maybe I don't get it.
I love gift cards.
Wonderful.
I like gift cards as well.
That's been a common thing to talk about.
I don't know if you can add this, Jason.
I'm not sure that you can.
I believe I've added...
All right.
My points idea is with value.
I believe I've put gift cards in the app before.
You can use it.
I'm sure you're sure to purchase.
I believe you can, but I don't know that for sure.
And you know what?
If it doesn't work out, then I've given you an incredible gift, Mike.
Which is something to complain about,
about the Shore Points app.
You should be able to preload.
You got it?
Fuzzy in the background on this gift card thing.
Point Pleasant Shore Point.
Are the numbers revealed?
Or do you have to scratch off with a coin or something?
I've been scratching.
You can do it with your nail if you've got a nail.
I will cover the space.
Jason, how many points do you have?
I have 95 right now, but I can only redeem it for a regular.
You have 158.
You can get a giant, I bet.
I still can get it.
Yeah, I never claimed a giant.
And you can get one more giant with this.
Guys, I hope you have a great holiday season
full of soggy giants.
Which incidentally is also something
you can mobile order from Target.
Get yourself a soggy giant.
It's neon blue and pink.
I love it.
As you guys continue your duel,
you survived Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
There I am saying the things that you guys
forget to say every goddamn time.
Just read it.
Mike, there was one where you
forgot the web address of our Patreon.
Yeah, that was recently too.
What happened?
I didn't even get to Indiana Jones 2.
There's so many things.
But for now, I will say
thank you for a great 2024.
Thanks for lots of great suggestions.
I'm sorry I missed so many Club 3s
specifically, but I'm happy to be back here
learning, growing.
And I'm so excited that in January
we will be back with Bugmane in tow
to kick things off right.
A great January inauguration
you might say.
For a great beautiful future to come.
How are you guys doing?
You have to add it in
when you make an order.
When you make an order, you select
add promo.
Have I given you
a bad present?
Where's the garbage?
I'm throwing this card into it.
Fine, fine.
Look what I get.