FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcasts may contain
An invisible underwater movie legend
Walnut confusion
Near future magic key restriction innovations
And more sticky taffer bottle talk
All this plus it's a small world holiday
Ho ho ho! It's Podcast the Ride!
Holiday!
Music
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a theme park podcast
Who loves to celebrate a holiday icon
That's given us so much over the years
Eisner Claus
My name is Mike Carlson
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan
I like that, I like Eisner Claus
Just the man or the idea?
Just the concept
The concept, I think, yeah, thank you for saying that
I think he's somebody who you look forward to
Or we used to look forward to what he would give us every year
When he would come down the chimney
What would it be? Would it be a new parade?
Would it be something that made any sense?
Probably not, but that's what was great about it
But in 1997 he was like, let's stir up some Christmas lights
Of course, that's what I'm saying
Scott Garner is also here
Oh, Jesus!
Did you see him?
I didn't see him
I haven't looked right this whole 40 minutes
You forgot I even am part of this
Well, guess what I am
And here's what I have to say to that
Hello, ho, ho
Oh, that's really good
Really good, yeah
Ties it together
Boy, you know, when you first said it
I thought it was a stretch
And then once you said you're right
He had the biggest sack of goodies
Yes
Every year of the Disney decade
Or at least the part of it that we made it through
And as the years go on
All right, sure, there was my childhood bike
Or my Kinect set
Or the various things that meant a lot to me
Growing up as Christmas
But today as an adult
I still benefit from the toys he gave me
The swan and dolphin hotels
And the connecting Michael Graves Causeway
That's right
The Norway expansion of Epcot
Many, many wonderful appearances
And great skits on the magical world of Disney
You know what, I have to say
I do think Eisner Claus has done more for me
All told than Santa Claus ever did
I agree, yes
And your logic-ing of what I just said
Is actually the reason I decided to go ahead with saying it
Because I went, you know what, it's true
You like saw the logic at the end of the tunnel
Yes, right
I thought of the phrase Eisner Claus
Said maybe that's something
Maybe you can say that
And you know what
I don't know if he sold the property
But he definitely at least lived at a place way cooler than the North Pole
Oh, right
That incredible Malibu compound
That combined a bunch of other compounds
As far as I know
There's just one little dopey village up at the North Pole
I don't think Santa bought a bunch of properties
From adjoining Christmas millionaires
No
I don't think there's a lot of Christmas millionaires
That live at the North Pole
I don't think
That's a pretty specific area
Yes
Well, the thing is
Alright
As I will be getting into
I've been very busy lately
Very happy to be back
But with just the pitch that my life has been at lately
Big, big regret
I have yet to dive into the full Christmas universe
That exists in the feature film Red One
Oh, right
So when I bring up adjoining characters
Who would exist alongside Santa Claus
I don't know
That mythology has now been defined
Red One might have taught us about Santa Claus' neighbors
And I
Because I've been so busy like a fool
I haven't gotten to experience who his neighbors are
Well, Jason and I were both there opening night at Red One
But I just don't want to
So jealous
There's so much to talk about today
We were at the premiere
We walked the red carpet
And then we went to a couple of local cinemas
The same night
We were standing in the back nodding
Right
We were not involved in the movie
But you did the tour that the filmmaker would do on opening night
Yeah
And yours was not the satisfaction of having made the film
Yours is the satisfaction of watching a new audience
Greet this wonderful film
Right
And throw all their joy at the screen
Can I ask what's the name of the rock
Gael Gadot Netflix movie?
Oh, this is very confusing
I believe that is Red Notice
That's Red Notice
Yeah
Okay
And then there's other
Because Red Notice which as we know at least at the time was the most watched feature film ever made by anyone anywhere
But then that record was beaten by another Netflix movie with a color in it
Which I think was the Grey Man
That's a Russo Brothers Grey Man I think
Yeah
Is that a Tom Holland movie?
Is that Chris Evans?
Or is that Tom Holland?
No
Cherry is Tom Holland
That's kind of
Cherry is red
Cherry is red so it's close
But it's not exactly cut from the same
And it's an apple
Cherry on apple
Okay
That's kind of this
That's kind of part of the fruitiverse
Right
But Grey Man
Netflix is all about the color verse
They did Red Notice the biggest movie ever made
Then Grey Man the biggest movie ever made
But now Amazon has made Red One the biggest movie ever made
Right
So I mean you got to really stay on top of these charts
It's a lot
It's a lot to
I'm just glad you guys were there to support seeing it time after time
Did you like
The opening night's enough to pack in like
Assuming that you stayed up until like 4 a.m.
Like did you guys fit in like six viewings in the first night?
Six, yeah
Great, great
Well congratulations
Thank you for supporting art
For supporting cinema
Yeah, of course
And just to be
Also to be super clear
Dwayne Johnson's character in this is Callum Drift
So I assume that
Callum or Calum
Can I just guess
Callum
Well that
Alright well you just told me that you
You weren't dressed as Callum Drift because you would have known that
So you must
Oh yeah
You must have been dressed as Jack O'Malley
I was
Which is Chris Evans' character
And I
There's some
Jason there's something telling me that your costume was Gryla
That you were Kiernan Shipka's character Gryla
Oh yeah
I knew it
I knew
I was for sure
I can always tell
Astrological signs
And I can always tell who's a Gryla
And you're definitely the Gryla of the group
He's Gryla
He loves
He's the part of the Gryhive
They call it
Yeah
No I
You know
I think it's a shame
AMC theaters have been complaining about the Gryhive
Getting a little too
Rowdy
Rowdy at the screenings
Which I think is wrong
You want people to be engaged
You want people
Yeah of course
Sing
Are they so wicked
Do they want you to sing along
And then here they want you to be rowdy at the Red One screenings
Yeah
Yeah for whatever reason one of the screenings we went to we were the only people there
And there's no real song associated with it
That I've delved into yet
So I just started singing the
Unfrosted song
Oh yeah
There's no song
Sweet
I want to sing along to something during the movie
Give me that sweet morning heat
Yeah
Every single day of the week
I'm so glad that in taking up space in my brain
Me now as a parent of two
Holding space what you say
Holding space
Yeah
I had a feeling that we were not going to make it 10 minutes into this episode of that talking about holding space
Oh and it's going to be so timely by the time this one comes out
It's up to us to keep the concept of holding space alive no matter how many weeks have passed
Yeah you might say I've heard that people
I work in serial media
And I hear that people have been holding space with the lyrics of sweet morning heat
And really feeling that and empowering that
And I think that's beautiful
Yeah
And I think if you told that to Jerry Seinfeld
He would tear up and say that's what I wanted
And then Jim Gaffigan would weirdly hold his finger
They're going on tour again
I saw Jimmy Fallon a couple nights ago
Who is going on tour?
Jim and Jerry
So they're going to be able to hold fingers
Oh great
I hope that's what it is
I hope it's mostly them weeping
Yeah
Do we need to explain what any of this is?
I don't know
Maybe it's in if you know then you do and if you don't you don't
Maybe if you don't you've turned this episode off by now
Yeah yeah yeah
Well I look I'm so happy to be back and bullshitting with y'all
Yeah of course
As you're hearing this I think if I have the timeline correct
The listener has heard at least one episode with me
But this is in our chronology in our timeline
This is the first one we've recorded together in several months
So it's kind of my official homecoming
Right
In a way
That feels very pompous to be declaring for myself
Welcome me back guys
I believe I'm waiting for a welcome back
I was like I'm not sure how to do this is the big hello
Because then there's also an episode that people have voted on on the Patreon
That's your rebuttal
And I was like is that going to be more of the episode where we go welcome back
What do you think? Are you happy with what we did?
I don't know
You're going to have to go behind the paywall to maybe see exactly your thoughts
But then I wasn't sure
It's hard to figure this out
We're still in this weird multiverse
This weird timeline situation here
Yes true
It'll be settled next year I think
What it is
Is this is the
Well it's the main feed return
Although again you've maybe heard
No I think I've heard you by now
Yeah I think so
But I deferred
I didn't talk about it
That's right
You didn't talk about it
Yeah we're talking about it
Look the point is
Say welcome back
I'm waiting
Welcome back
Thank you dad
Oh boy
This is more confusing than trying to figure out a security detail for Santa Claus himself aka Red One
Yes welcome back
Now we know how hard Gryla's got it
The audience is now wondering why we haven't welcomed you back on any other episodes
Sure
Well we'll get this a lot more straightened out
Not that it'll be fully straightened out because I still don't know if I'm fully back
You might still hear ones without me
I'm still busy with things but I'm doing as many as I can
And I'm happy to be here for a little holiday homecoming
This is how I hoped that it would work out
This is the last episode of the, this is the last main feed of the year?
The last main feed of the year
Yes
Wonderful
For sure
Well then just like very Brady Christmas
Right
This is the time for the family to be back in one place
That's right
And to celebrate the great things that have happened in the time that we were apart
Which before I get into anything that I've been doing
Let me say for the first time on mic congratulations Jason
On your engagement
Oh thank you
I don't know how much you've acknowledged it on the show
But I have not acknowledged it in a way that counts
Which is in recorded media
In person and in texts that don't count for shit
But here I am on microphone saying congratulations Jason and James
I haven't congratulated him on mic
Well well
So you've beaten me to it
I'm waiting around to be welcomed back to them
I haven't done it either
He's not getting congratulated
Let's make all this right
Congrats Jason
Congratulations Jason
Thank you very much
Thank you both
Yeah no it was nice to see and a fun surprise during my little sojourn
And I just want to say with that
That I wish you to a very happy future
That is full of Amazoning and prone bone
And inflatable stuff with popping if that's what you want
But only if that's what you want
And mainly that you're
That you can be thrown around as if by one of the X-Men
As much as you desire
By my very own father
He's done his own homework
He's done a lot of homework here
Yes I've shown my cards
I've listened to a lot
You did drop a lot in the last six weeks
Now that he says it all out
Which Scott says it all at once
Yeah I mean one of those I was still there
This I will explain
You know if you didn't understand the wicked stuff we were saying
Sorry look it up and hold space with it
This I will say some of what I just referred to as second gate stuff
A lot of it was
But imagine me not being on these episodes
Just like kind of driving around
And then like hearing bits and pieces that just make me like
My eyes just like go wide
I'm making a lot of Kenan Thompson faces as Jason reveals
Well again it's just awareness of things
That doesn't mean anything
But like certainly dropping
You know something I think we face a lot
Mike and I that we face a lot
Is that Jason will say something and we don't know what he's talking about
And then in the comments a lot of people will jump in and say
That's a very famous thing
I know what he's talking about
It was heartening for me to hear
As he's talking about Amazoning and prone bone
That you're in a group with Anthony Gio and Zaccarino
And then nobody knows about Amazoning and prone bone
Which maybe that says more about us and us not being
To call Jason in touch with ourselves as sexual beings
Right
So I'm just impressed that you can throw
I'm impressed you can throw us these curve balls
Seven years into doing the show
And then like 15 years of knowing you
And I've never heard you talk about Amazon position before
So I'm just impressed
And in this context for the non main feed listeners
This was it was initially brought up in reference to
What a parade float of Goofy was doing
Well Goofy
The Goofasaurus
The Goofasaurus looking a little weird with it
Which we will have to I think we're not going to do it soon
But we didn't pay enough attention even to that parade
So I think down the line
Maybe we maybe we do the same sort of setup
And just watch the parade
I don't know
The full world according to Goofy parade
But
This was I so I will say you know
This is a little chance to address some of what happened
While I was gone
That that episode
Main feed folks you're missing out because the real
The good shit has all I feel like in general
A lot of the best shit is on the second gate
And that was an episode there with Gio and Zac
That made me jealous
Because when I realized like
Wait a minute you're backing into the world according to Goofy
Yeah
And I'm not there
I know yeah
There certainly needs to be more talk
You got you got to the goofball
The big golf ball Goofy hybrid
And I didn't get to be a part of it
You made me jealous
See that's what I was afraid of happening
I
You said don't know
He did tell us
We wouldn't get in trouble if you did something big
Yeah I know I said do big things while I'm gone
Even if it means that it never it can never come up again
Which is why it kills me that you took care of Mike's credit card points
While I was gone
But if that means that there will be no more points talk
In the future
Ah
It tears me up inside
Yeah I mean we'll we'll address this probably on the actual
Club 3
Oh there's gonna be
That's the
There's a lot to talk about
That's the grand daddy of what there is to talk about
In the club 3 episode
Yes
Oh God
Will that have come out by now
Will I say what I'm about to say
I don't know
Then or now
I know how to do points too
I know what I need to do now
I knew
You don't mean also
You mean the episode points too
Points too
Mike's credit card points
Episode 2
Okay
I now know what I have to do
Wow
And a couple days ago it really dawned on me
And I kind of put it together
It's not gonna be soon
I need a lot of time
To invest in this
But I know
Oh no
It's gonna be me
Here I am waiting
I know
It's not gonna be tomorrow
With bated breath for points too
Are you going to dissect the paternal grandparents that I would call Graham Graham and Graham Pop
Since you spent that one dissecting my mom and pop pop
Or is that another episode
Wait a minute
I don't know
What you're saying doesn't sound familiar to me at all
So it might have been one that I didn't listen to all of
I am pretty sure Jason is referring to a second gate episode that has not come out yet
Oh good
Okay
Let me question him on his pronunciation
We all gotta
Oh sorry
There was a lot of interrogating Jason's lore when you were gone
Well look at that
Let the record show this happens when I'm not on the show
Lest anybody think that all of the Jason interrogation is Scott driven
Look at that
Yeah that episode actually will have come out by now
So the listeners will have heard about your grandma and grandpa's barrel full of walnuts
Yeah
That you would go into and heat up and have a warm walnut
Heat up
What are you making up stuff
We've never heat them up
We just crack them
But there were warm
You mentioned warm walnuts on the episode
What
Well he was talking about the warm walnuts position
Now how does that work
Where do the legs go for that one
That's one of those ones that people post the images on Twitter
Position of the day the yellow and pink creatures
You think Mike and I are following position of the day Twitter's
Position
What's the account
Position of the day
I think it's a website
I don't know people post these funny
Now you don't know what it is
These funny graphics
What's this Twitter
I don't know I think it's a website
This is
A lot of what we stumble into with these things I feel is that you are just on different parts of not just the internet
But of Twitter slash X slash horrible place than we are
That's that's that's ultimately what and and you know what we're the dorks
We're the ones not experiencing sexual being
Oh I looked as we should be
I shouldn't have done the Google search I just Googled
Are they illustrations
No it's like real people
Oh
I don't need to look up warm walnuts
Maybe I have that wrong
Because I made that one up
No
Yeah no I think that's made up
We discussed warm walnuts Jason and the listeners have heard warm walnuts by now
A barrel full of walnuts with crackers and wet walnuts are the sundae topping
Maybe I'm wrong
Yeah I think you're wrong
It was either wet or warm
I can't remember what it was but it led to you talking about your grandparents barrel full of walnuts
Yeah
That's all I know
A wonderful memory
I know there was a barrel full of walnuts and the walnut was either warm or soaking wet
How did I go on without getting to be part of the barrel full of walnuts conversation
Thank God
Please celebrate me home
Back to the walnut talk please
Well I got a lot to catch up on
And you're right that some of this will
Basically I was going to come into this and consider this kind of the Scott return episode
And do a little bit of response to some of the things that happened in I guess what we'll call the Scott free era as you did
I was going to drop a few just a few sparing thoughts on the Scott free era
Lo and behold the great folks over at Club 3 the VIP subscribers have voted for me to do an entire full episode response to the entire Scott free era
So that's some of what you've just been alluding to
So if you want to get detailed granular episode by episode coverage of what I missed
Head to Club 3 which is patreon.com slash podcast the ride
I will I will I will leave this this thought and critique out of that one and say now after the run that we just came out of this is all right
This is this I this is something I think we have to figure out and I think this is this is non-negotiable as far as I'm concerned
This this thing because this happened it's look it's happening with me here too in so many of these episodes we end up in these like inceptions of yes now you may have heard of about this from the past
You may have already been hearing about this if it is in fact the future but divide that by four and maybe you haven't heard us talk about that we've got it we've got to get this figured out
I agree we cannot be tossing these Nolan isms to the audience left I think the I think audiences things understand that the content is recorded out of order
In friends the friends don't alternate camera and say this was actually recorded three months ago
Well that is a magic trick you see but I love hearing those behind the scenes tales
That's your note about friends you want more I'm sure I see how the how the characters are getting together but how is the sausage made I say do a reunion special every year
But it's gonna get it's gonna get sadder and sadder and sadder and sadder and sadder
Anyways that's just that's one that's one thought there will be other thoughts yeah forthcoming and now I get to kind of like luxuriate in it now I get to tag it relax and take my time but I will ask this at the top
How do you feel with the if this is in fact the end of the scott free era how does it feel how did it feel were you dreading this today taskmaster
Scott being we have to be both back on topic I mean it was interesting it was an interesting experiment it was an interesting thing to do sure that's good
Scott free I didn't realize was Ridley Scott's production company oh yes that occurred to me yeah I didn't realize before that brand so you couldn't see you didn't get any shirts made so I did not know I did see gladiator 2 though
What do you think that's good fine sure that sounds like a good review yeah you know I'm putting in some good stuff Denzel's great you know
I just saw gladiator 1 something I neglected to do my whole life so that's that's the kind of thrilling content that can be coming your way reviews of 25 year old movies
So no I mean it was it was an interesting experiment but it was you know I I didn't know if something like an episode about points if we would have you would have looked at our patreon and it would have been everyone canceled
Well I'm heartened by the listener enjoying some of the nonsense of the Jason and I nonsense this seemed like it this seemed like a very well received episode I have to admit I think that's true yeah yeah which and I have I have some thoughts about how to proceed going forward
Knowing that information but again that that that I will save before the club through I don't want to burn it off all you do a lot of heavy lift I will say this I missed that you do end up doing some heavy lifting on the show sometimes thank you for so what do you what do you mean
Well anyway heavy lifting is relative I suppose not not literal no no not literally we set up the mic stand surgery not heart surgery or anything sometimes we have to move these chairs were sitting in from down below the stage record on to up on top of the stage and how big how high is the stage like a foot yeah that's a big lift heavy so yeah sometimes you're like oh I'm I'm I'm sometimes I would be like oh I'm driving this episode I need to check my notes I need to try to interject and then I need to also question Jason about something he
said that I don't know his history so I'm like I'm like oh this is a tough job I'm doing and it's interesting now that I'm doing like I'm trying to like cycle through all of it in my head so I'm like oh Scott would have done two of these jobs so it's interesting it's interesting so so and you're and you're recording you know you're always wearing so it's an interesting at all times so yeah I can relax a little bit you know if
I know what you mean by the way about a barrel you know you could say what's that barrel all about or I could say what's that barrel all about now you know it is nice to have I feel when we've done two person episode there is something about like yeah it is like more of it is on you sometimes I feel especially when we have a guest where you know we want to do a good interview with the guest or it's a very funny person or somebody we didn't know I sometimes think like well I may be better off in host mode here and maybe I don't have as much fun like just with pure comedy that can happen
yeah yeah these are the thing not to not well though maybe we should get in out of the sausages made which is what Jason like that's true sure how did you feel about the scott free oh I mean I felt good I feel like I just brought my my brand of thinking I'm normal and accidentally bringing chaos that I bring even listening going back and listening to our second episode ever about the Indiana Jones adventure to prepare for
part two I'm like oh I hit on the chaos very early on that it was in there it was yeah there was some chaos I I think the first little bit of it what I did in an observation I had I didn't really say in the Mac or don't episode is that I'm like oh I feel like early on we were trying to be very professional and a little more button up and then I immediately
started talking about something it's saying and then and then we all loose end up yeah and yeah what was it what did you talk I don't remember now I also listen to the episode yeah I listen to the whole thing you know it's funny I guess this is the time whatever listener this it's kind of it's this reunion homecoming episode early memory I have and I don't know if it's that but I feel like we we've in a really good way we never talked about this too much we didn't do practice episodes we didn't super intellectual intellectualize it we just started
doing it and and this is the kind of thing I get perspective on having for the that was seven years ago this all started and this this couple months that I left is the first that's the longest stretch of not doing this yeah and seven yeah that's kind of a crazy thing like like the you know like like the longest stretch of a routine that's gone for seven years to to get away from that and to get a little bit of perspective and stuff interesting to do and I
something I basically something I remember is that like early on thinking like so what is it do we just like is it just analysis I mean I assume we could be a little bit funny but what are we gonna and there was something where we started doing like it was like hers like annoyed Harrison Ford voices something that has happened throughout the show yeah it's been a runner the entire time and that that the bit being like oh I see we do bits and voices and that's something that is part of this yeah that'll keep things loose that'll keep things fun
that'll make it a comedy show it was just a nice memory I recall and that we we never we landed on it fully organically that it can be that kind of show yeah then other things happened like well is it the kind of show where a character can come and interrupts and
hijack things and you put in sound effects of what the character is doing and we quickly realized no it's not particularly that kind of show has its following but later on maybe characters showed up sometimes some characters do worry you know yeah yeah yeah so it is interesting if you listen to the second episode yes I was like oh it's a little stiff up at top but then I'm like oh wait no it's actually even though we don't talk as much about the actual discussion of any of the
Jones I said this already in that episode the actual discussion of Ian Jones I bet is like 45 minutes on that episode and there's there's a bunch of top talk and then a bunch of segment talk at the end okay I go but if you listen to you go oh man I've been saying the same dumb shit for seven years because like I thought oh there's gonna be stuff I don't remember and I'm like oh I'm saying the same stuff I say the exact same stuff well that's something that I feel and this wasn't just in my absence but I feel like a very common thing said on the show especially by you is like yeah you know it's something I've been thinking and I've said this a thousand times on the show and it
is true there are these things that have been said one thousand times yeah on the show yeah and I there's there was a bunch of stuff I thought I had said in that episode but probably just said in other episodes but there's a bunch of stuff where I'm just like oh yeah this is I thought that I thought I was really scared to listen to that first or second episode because I was like ah is it gonna be embarrassing am I gonna be I'm like it's not embarrassing it's like a little different but it's the same it's the same show and we had like we didn't do any practice
but we had had a lot of lunches and meet like what is this and we had some documents like we certainly did prep work that's true yeah trying to documents it didn't just document or two I guess totally come out and like all right we'll get some mics and we'll just show up like that voice though back then that oh yeah well cuz we were all hanging at the cellar sitting around the dirty wet table you know yeah well who wants to hear entertainment from three white guys if
at least one of them doesn't sound like that that's true yeah but yes it was a you know it's interesting did you so does that mean did you find that the the the pressing ferocious need to cover to do Indiana Jones to was not as extreme as you have believed it to be for many years I think we actually found there was quite a bit to analyze I do think there's a lot of it I actually I didn't get to my notes we did we talked too much
about the Boat House and Disney Springs up top on that episode and I'm like Ty and then we did a little muppets and I'm like clock's ticking okay just a little bit and then we started going through and then I felt like I was racing through some of it but that is also a ride that benefits from being upgraded at least once or twice since we recorded that episode sure yes we talked we talked about the updates and some other stuff yeah I mean it's all well good so you got your updates are you happy are you sad
you got your sequel in how do you feel I feel okay about it just okay yeah yeah I think that's not the report I want I want the report that you loved it that it's your fully you're fully justified in pushing for it for all this time and we don't have to do it again now I don't know but I don't know but either of those I fully justified yes I don't know that we don't have to do it anymore I think we have to do everything again I you know that's my philosophy I think everything again I think he's thinking about in the part three already well I'm not it's a it's
not as hard it's not as clear in my mind as points to but indie three is seven years from now perhaps and oh by the way you said you know what you need to do for points I do yes I think I know what I need to do as well which is to book another movie sure sure I will say this one yeah well I can tell you I'll give you a six month heads up so you can know when to be gone
now it doesn't have a premise yet the or well all right there's a rough idea the idea is a guy is worried he's gonna be bored so he decides to make a movie as fast as possible yeah yeah we'll get into all of that yes let me let me say I want to say a couple and then we will get to a small world holiday I promise do we I don't know who how strong is the caring we will we'll do it we'll do it yeah well I mean but you want to get to it next year we can get to it next year
and that if we've done a fully deferred I guess we've done the fake out we've done the false start Frank Marshall get episode yeah like fully kicked the can I think we can do it we could just call this Scott's home for the holidays well that's nice isn't it I thought it was nice nice like the ride in theory well let's see let's let's see where it goes I wanted to share just a couple of things about what I just came from doing and just to remind to remind the listener the timeline but basically I think I am coming back from one of the
probably the craziest stretch of my entire life that's what that's what my hiatus what you can use the word hiatus but that implies relaxation and in fact it was the opposite of that basically if you don't recall the timeline mid September our second child showed up earlier than we expected kind of threw us like shot us out of the parent cannon dealing with that wonderful but also stressful and crazy and then just the way things timed out in this awesome opportunity that came my way but with
timing that was a little bit less than awesome but hey you gotta pounce wouldn't know when things come up basically like I went straight from oh my god new baby to a very intense run of prep into how I spent my November which is directing a movie I directed my first movie I've kind of alluded to that a little bit but I was I was being cagey mainly because I wanted to make sure that it happened that it occurred and then I didn't say a sentence that proved later to not be true but I directed a movie and I'm super
proud of it and I'm excited to see you know where it goes and hopefully like talk further about my adventures on that and fill the audience in on it I will say was a despite the like very compressed timeline phenomenal crew wonderful group of people like the crazy summer camp that you hear I mean I was going to say that occurs but I didn't know this occurred I've done like one longer form project but not a movie specifically and I was really hoping for that kind of like
crazy summer camp you're thrown in with a bunch of people you only sort of met and then you all gotta like go through adventures together and that's totally how it felt it was a wonderful thing the writers of the movie were also the stars of the movie it was a dream come true for them to get to do it so their enthusiasm was infectious and just like a like very very positive stuff so that that's what I'm happy to report even if there was you know a lot of good things happening in my life just like too many on top of each other I would say and it's been nice to like
settle down and slow down I bet that points episode was nice because it was such a relaxing discussion about two points enthusiasts and you got to hear about different interests outside of your own it must have been nice to just kind of slow the road just like wow this is so it's so like it's so relaxing and meandering did I put it on at point five speed no that's just what it is the peaceful easy feeling that song we all know
look it's nice to hear my buddies having fun and I'm gonna come back around I have a little story that involves that too that will come back around to that but I did want to like in thinking about things from this experience that were somewhat PTR coded to use that term there's a few that I wanted to bring back with me one of which was very special and I just had to share it lots of unbelievable
crew on this thing as I said like so many people bringing their a game like people like overqualified for the weird scrappy thing that that we were doing and you know you kind of a movie like this relies on like daily miracles and and and we had daily miracles because so many talented people were bringing their best and that included in the area of stunts we had some light stunts on this movie which which was a thrill because that's where you know like I'm coming from I've been doing more animated stuff
before this like in the lead up to you know switching over to to live-action directing and in animation you can write whatever zany shit and it's not that you know it's probably one of the easiest things to make happen is like a you know somebody flying across the room or getting her sure flying in the sky or getting like you know inflated really big and then floating up into the sky getting bigger and bigger as they go and you say that pop to say that a little quieter a little more intense and maybe
Jason look it's not it is not my thing okay I just know it's out there and I had multiple people backing me up we're not waiting I believe I guess I believe you that it's real this is yeah well and this is look to be to be fair that is correct knowing about a thing doesn't mean it's your thing and that's an unfair thing to bring to the table and also as I said like this isn't one of those situations where we didn't believe you I think what the I think I was a little skeptical
but I yes I eventually I believe I believe I believed Jason I think what I think what the city and by the way of all that there's things I just I just shot many many days of movie there's things that are out of my brain completely that happened two weeks yeah of course the the mention of inflatable stuff every bit of it is lodged as deeply as the holding space interview it is like it's permanently in there and I think it's what it's less that we didn't believe you and I think more that you made a joke that was supposed to that you believed would communicate
to both of us and to Justin Donaldson I think what you said was like well then the big problem for Mickey is that he'll be saying like oh don't blow me up and then we were all baffled like what does that mean because we didn't understand that that is like the idea that we were supposed to immediately unpack that and go oh it's a reference to inflatable stuff the very common fetish that was that I think was the issue for me well in your head were you like it's inflatable stuff everybody knows inflatable stuff
yeah I think that's what it was so I understand it you know it's the big he's online it's the big difference yeah yeah do you does that mean do you know what holding space is in general yeah yeah I feel like it's a thing that people said a lot more sincerely in like 2014 2015 I hadn't heard about it for like 10 years okay and then just seeing it in a
balloon returning yeah about the lyrics of like a 20 plus year old song yeah what a thing what a thing anyway point is I you know on a fairly low budget movie stunts are kind of like like a complex thing to get your head around you're like can we do that can we do that and we thanks to a really great guy named Chris a really great stunt coordinator we were able to put some some
fun little moments in this movie who he's like oh that's a breeze that'll be fine that's fun I'm excited it's gonna be great to get to so like like in a crew full of great people this guy Chris one of the best and what we always heard was you know because he comes from like big old stuff he's done Marvel he's like and we just caught him in the window where he had a little bit of free time so he can like do us a solid help us out great well that's what we need love that great working with him in general then the last bit that he did he had somebody up on wires and we were figuring that out now that's
that's gonna work and it was kind of a cold morning so everybody's bundled up a little bit and he's got kind of a knit cap on and the knit cap has an a on it and not just any a but the avatar a well not just any avatar a but the avatar way of water a well the improved font with with I don't know what it is in the middle we know one of the pirates plus what do you call it yeah papyrus new and improved and I see the a and I
get a feeling and I suddenly feel a little bit of nerves come over me and I say to him is that from way of water did you work on way of water and I think sensing the tone of my voice that it wasn't just asking a question that I was bringing some weight to that Chris looks me in the eye addresses me by name and he says Scott I was Jake Sully Wow and I go I go flying back as if I'm on wires
I like wait a minute what does that mean okay so he's Jake he's Jake Sully stunt double and I'm sure there were like a number of those all told but as he gets into it and he shows me some of the stuff that he did he's he's fucking Jake Sully stunt double in underwater sequences wow he's doing like crazy double helixes and shit like powered by underwater jet packs attached to his feet and that's not just CGI no it's all mocap they did all of that right it was yes he was in tanks he
flew he was all over the world he's in the Bahamas he's I forget if he did in New Zealand some of it's here but yeah no that all happened and he was the one doing it and in a mocap movie like Avatar you know the stunt double is not just like you know a guy in a wig and a wide shot although that's also a cool thing I'm not knocking that we had a really great stunt double on this thing but like that means when he says he was Jake Sully he was Jake Sully he's Jake Sully in lots of possibly in more scenes than
Sam Worthington so he was describing experiences of like doing a crazy underwater aerial helix thing and then getting out of like like getting out of the of the tank like he was in the tank he's in the tank with the ping pong balls wow he gets out and goes and consults at monitor with James Cameron and Sam Worthington who's giving him giving him character notes and then James Cameron will watch this like unbelievably complex thing happen and James is like no good the breathing was all wrong I didn't
believe the breathing five seconds before the thing at before the thing splashes down you need to be getting nervous I didn't feel any nervousness in your breath oh my god that's the sort of note that James Cameron gets he is analyzing human biology those are the notes that this guy got that's
there was the speaking gladiator 2 that got the cinematographer just trashed Ridley Scott for being lazy really it's like yeah he doesn't take as long to do things anymore and shots he wants just wrap it up and he like lets stuff go not the case was 70 year old James Cameron
no clearly not yes he's looking at a fucking rib cage yeah there's bubbles flying everywhere the things are on fire and he's like look he's looking at chest expansion and going no no all wrong the computer could fix that yeah yeah but I but not in his world like it all has to stem from natural biology when you okay remember the whole thing about Kate Winslet breaking the Tom Cruise underwater breathing record she was like she did over seven minutes continuously
underwater and if you Google basically if you go into Google images type in Kate Winslet underwater one of the first images you will find is her with kind of like the big wings like doing the the the wingspan and then there's two guys in scuba gear down below her helping her watching her this guy Chris is one of those guys whoa wow insane helping Kate Winslet being Jake Sully and you guys know and the audience knows how blue-pilled I have become how avatar-pilled I and here I am doing a kind
of like a nerve-wracking experience and right towards the end I got brushed with the magic of Jake Sully incredible yeah and the way he told me with looking me in the eyes where there was nothing braggy about it the way he said it was almost as if he was saying I walked with Christ I met him I passed in his glory yeah no no ego just just no he thought it was cool as shit too and he's like oh and then this one time and then I'm doing this and then I'm just like fucking coolest coolest wow so if you want it if you want
to see what I what I believe is a project graced with Jake Sully magic that that will be this thing which otherwise I don't really want to sure ruin any announcements about her right right too much so I had to share that couldn't keep that to myself that one more thing before we go into a small world holiday and I think you'll find this nice most of this experience very pleasant wonderful as I said incredible crew but I'm balancing a lot here I'm balancing very new baby who I've like barely met then I'm just thrown in this whole crazy thing basically I
switched places with my mother-in-law I went to live at her place in Chatsworth because we were filming in beautiful Simi Valley right that I could get my rest and then she came and took care of my new son my older son god bless her god bless both of our grandmothers they really kept us together yeah not my grandma the boys grandmother sure but anyway it's this crazy thing barely processed having a child later I will watch Jake Sully's family grow in way of water and I will
water is that was the first I ever cried in a movie about being a dad any way of water discussion anyway I will process via way of water later but I'm you know I'm away from my family it's this crazy experience second son first movie and what I'm getting at I'm driving to that that's the base of any day where I'm in this experience but what I'm getting to is day three of the shoot where all of that is going on a new factor in
day three of the shoot is that if you listener if you recall my son was personally in the NICU for a little bit doing great now adorable he when I left for my last week of work he couldn't smile yet and I came back smiling baby incredible wonderful so things are things are going great there but we had this NICU stay and on day three of the shoot we were operating from a reality where we thought that we owed the hospital forty two thousand dollars this turned out to be not true but these were the circumstances of the day
where I'm going to do a thing that is very stressful regardless and did I mention that this oh wait wait actually wait one more thing this is a fifteen day shoot listener if you know anything about film shoots have you ever been part of it or been part of one fifteen days is not this is not enough day this is the tightest schedule ever and there's so much pressure to you know like we can never go over time we can never like this this is the tightest schedule humanly possible there is there is no
room for error just remember that as I go into what I'm going into and did I mention the day three of the shoot was also the the morning after Donald Trump was reelected to the office of the presidency so everybody's up really early having probably checked their phones hoping for good news seeing the worst news and now having to go into a day of work and God bless everybody in this the cast and the crew everybody had this air of like okay going to be buttoned up and we are going to get through this and this is it is good that we have something
to do I'm really glad that this way we can you know purpose purpose to the day and as long as we could stay busy we won't stop and think about the terrible thing that has happened that get that that is that all is in progress from about 630 to 930 at 930 we're in the middle of a scene
audible power down shoot shoot loses all of its power everything goes dark total confusion what just happened here it was an unbelievably windy day in Simi Valley it was the most visible wind like distressingly visible wind and we start asking questions and we realize okay powers down to the entire building well can we just throw things on a generator no because then we would have no power to the basically like we need the lights of the
room that we're in itself in order to keep going with the aesthetic that we have established so we there is nothing we can film there is nothing we can do the power is out from 930 to 430 we lose an entire day now remember what I said about 15 days a schedule that is not possible this was so crazy it's like it's all this stuff it's all the stress in my life and then Trump and then fucking the winds of change knock out the power of the one like nice thing that we're all getting to do and
that's distracting us from these insane circumstances these were joker fiying conditions this is completely insane and what I needed to do
in this moment was just kind of like touch the earth get tethered to something that was comfortable and just like basically I took a breather I'm like let me step outside for a second and I just kind of like I just needed a minute and in this minute I realized you guys put an episode out you would just put out the episode
20,000 leagues under the sea with Matt Mazzani on the second gate and I thought I wonder how that is going over and I checked the comments of that episode and I see so many people saying this is making my day it is so nice to have just a regular funny ass PTR to listen to with the horrible news that we have just gotten and it was just wonderful to see
the you guys and I can there's a compliment I can give that I'm not even a part of because I wasn't part of the episode that just you guys doing what you do was making the listeners so happy and that the listeners were sharing such positive feedback and telling him telling us that you know it changed everything on a very tough day that made me so it lifted my spirits in this very difficult day and by the end of the day when I finally got to hear the episode I felt the same way it was my biggest barrel laugh is that a term barrel laugh
I guess Jason's the one to ask he's into the barrel play as long as it's not for walnuts or with straps on your midsection I think you're fine barrel boy Jason Sheridan barrel enthusiast no I felt as jolly as a barrel full of walnuts seeing all of that nice feedback on it on a truly bonkers day yeah well thank you for saying that that's very nice had to pass that along and pass that and pass along to Matt Mazzani one of the finest people I know there's
no thank you man yeah great guests fun episode to do yeah and well in a pot in a very like sincere and nice one you know dreaming of a better play you know I mean the the world of what could be better than escaping to the world of Tokyo Disney see sure most positive place on earth that's right as everything's going to hell yeah no I would like to tell you though oh man we strategically planned it just in case you know what what's counter-programming yeah yeah well it's a good thing you didn't
go the opposite way and get super cocky and that like and that the episode was about like all right today's topic the the Kamala robot the sure to be installed we're doubling down we know this will happen we know that voters will come through we saw the Iowa poll this
is a weird dude devoting a full episode to how resplendent that robot is going to be and how awesome her coat will be that could have been shoved into the back could be put into the furnace and never seen again could have been possible but luckily no no you thought you just did you just did a nice pleasant one so anyway just wanted to share that and say thank you for like in a time where I was literally like homesick doing a big crazy thing it was just nice to hear you guys doing what you do and being super funny it was like
it was like let's say Richie Sambora is now playing with Bon Jovi and he hears a Bon Jovi concert and he's it cheers him up here's one I don't know he sees it this is a difficult he like out of the bit don't they not get along anymore but then you may be coming back though maybe this doesn't hang this doesn't hang together I don't okay I'm putting it I'm putting a tangent clock on this one two minutes okay one of these all right one of these Green Day fuckers has some side project doesn't he well they all
well I mean Billy is a few bands Billy is a few bands I forget Mike Dern also I think has a side project as well what I always are to get they are very strong there's a tight three person unit they would never I don't think they've ever done maybe you know Mike Dern did have wrist surgery 20 years ago I think I think he had a carpal tuba that's a long time I don't think he missed any shows though would just say the name of one of their stupid other bands well then we can move on there's I'm trying to think the network was the one where there was like their
Devo band like 15 years ago I think maybe they've done newer network music as well but is that all there's still all I think that's them the long shot is a Billy Joe side project and I think it might just be him I don't know if there's another like this only two green name I think it's only one the long shot has some okay songs here's what I'm just gonna pull from a list here you know it's it's as if because the band didn't break up right that's what's happening so it's I am
as if I am Billy Joe and I have gone to do my 2011 side project the boo but I'm so I guess there's a lot of pressures to doing the boo and the pressures are kind of getting or aid the long shot same thing whether it's boo or long shot flying solo and doing a big ambitious thing outside your your perfect group Green Day is definitely stressful so hearing just like a great jam session happening between Mike and Trey yeah Mike would cheer Billy Joe up on that day
I'm Mike Dern Jason's Trey cool in this scenario oh cool the wild man Trey cool which one's the tall one though Trey Trey's big drummer he's a big guy kind of crazy no but isn't Mike Dern taller is he I don't know actually I should know that Billy's obviously the shortest of the three I think just to confirm can you tell us the name of Bon Jovi's wine company Hampton Water Hampton Water Green Day has their own coffee as well so but now
about the coffee and all the crazy items they put Dookie on right it's it's funny syntax but Bon Jovi has the wine Hampton Water but Green Day has a coffee why just cuz he's went us back to Bon Jovi I just wanted to get us back to Green Day we were on the Green Day Jag anyway look it's as if I was Billy Joe doing the boo and all the power to all my amps blew and I didn't know how I was gonna finish the boo my side project right there's no how's there no link
when I click on this on Green Day wiki the boo isn't even good enough to get its own page on Green Day wiki I'm not very familiar with the boo honest to god I don't know let's keep it that way now that I'm back on the show I don't want to see any votes over in club three about the boo I know I made myself the boo in this scenario but there's a Green Day is a Billy Joe Nora Jones collaboration here barf okay so it's a small world holiday small world holiday
we need to talk about don't we going strong since 1997 the only hiccup was the 2020 pandemic closure yeah no thank thank God the pandemic Mike if that laptops doing anything other than clicking over to the small world holiday tab then I want to see it shut Miranda Lambert and Billy Joe teamed up once seven years ago saying that all quiet and lascivious Lee as if you're talking about
some called ordinary world I was as good for it I was trying to say a nice sincere thing and then I walked and then I myself drove it right into Green Day land yeah I was deflecting from a compliment a little bit but I didn't want it I didn't I only did Bon Jovi which is not as interesting as Green Day so I would say Bon Jovi is not as interesting as almost any topic in the world I would agree with that but that actually does make me at least somewhat interested in it because of that he's really I'm just saying but
obviously it's not as loaded on the show not yet give it time but if Bon Jovi okay here's what just happened Bon Jovi was said I kind of registered that I don't yes yeah yeah powering up Bon Jovi war machine gearing up in three months we'll be doing some but you'll have decided and I like it and I like Bon Jovi and I got my daughter listening to the theme song to Hampton water hmm Hampton guzzling theme from Hampton water is that possible you gotta show her the family trail
Bon Jovi jr. married 11 from stranger that's true Jason knows that you know what is something worth talking about though that way to think well not I think we want to have time this holiday season but you know about John Bon Jovi's Christmas album right don't do I well yeah I have to lead a little bit more this was before he was John Bon Jovi his name was John Bon Jovi he had not split up the name at this time you know where I'm heading with this I don't think so he does all of the human singing on
the Star Wars holiday album Christmas in the stars I didn't know Christmas in the structures with the stars now is this album is separate from the holiday special it is confusingly yes there's the whole crazy holiday special but then there's also it's
Christmas in the stars it's the first professional recording of John Bon Jovi Wow I did not know this his songs are all very boring I will say no way as opposed to I mean because the money is
the song sung by C3PO Wow which is the title song Christmas in the stars Christmas in the stars I don't know this that's shocking Christmas in the stars I am very surprised but yeah yeah do you guys know real quick I mean we're all over the place do you guys know this the rock and toontown album with the guy was his name like Craig and Company yeah I'll do Craig and Company that was on the Disney Channel so much when I was a kid he did this he did a song called haircut that the Disney Channel really pushed
you like my haircut you need a haircut yeah I was a full toontown album that's yes Sky Selga told me about this because I had asked on that episode the parade episode what is this toontown song and then he texted me and he said that is from this album rock and toontown I know that there was a full concert special that aired on the Disney Channel which I have watched in the last two years you see we're not so different all of us we have we share
this so we come together for Christmas over the same bonds dumb bad Christmas special shit rock and toontown are we there yet I'm bored food for thought voice of the spirit younger kids stuff these are all tracks from this do bullies have mommies no that's why they're mad bullies are a different species right they're inhuman they're basically trolls this year you know I had this thought of this year I was like did we get through too much Eisner's I was like
are we burning too much Eisner this year because we really feel like a second half especially like hitting a bunch of weird Eisner stuff and I'm like no there is an unlimited room rock and toontown the rest of the goofy parade yeah so no I feel better about it but there was a couple weeks there
really to me his primary contribution slash the Michael Graves team Disney building in beautiful Burbank which we all call home the building held up by the dwarves right yeah there's you know we haven't even talked about we haven't really talked about his architectural footprint on this world which will maintain for thousands of years after we're all gone yeah aliens will come and dig up the wow this was a thoughtful species this building it's so clever little dwarves are holding it up
yeah well the the aliens that are here already are appreciating it I think the ones that are still there showing up it's another thing you didn't get out you didn't you didn't manage to get your alien talk out while I was gone there hasn't been any but there's been a lot of alien stuff that's happened lately too big hearing mm-hmm it's a whole weird just got an email about another feature this stuff is fucking weird though this stuff is legitimately interesting unlike the other stuff that you even you admit it's not well yeah no it's not and it's I said it on the episode I said on the points upside ago on its face you could go to a person on the street and go you know it's a big alien here
ring or a bunch of guys said a bunch of crazy stuff and somebody go oh that is interesting and then you go why would you like to hear about the Jersey Mike sub that I just had for free and they would say no but yes but that's a person on the street we are talking about people who listen to this podcast these are sickos these people who listen to us they're all this they're the sicko they're that that comic drawing of the second yes there are people Jason nice people I guess if they like the point yeah I saw some negative comments too
you don't know your points okay sincerely boy at this point we better not have more than 15 minutes about small world holiday I had a feeling there's gonna get well okay all right here let's let's actually like power it let's like we could preview for small world holiday next year I want to get a small world holiday to already snuck me into a sequel by even doing small world holiday
why not it's the same shit we need to do more everything more everything it's not the same because we do talk about different things in the you know for instance in your day we cover verandas and in your seven we cover how you tried to do a class to learn Shakespeare which you don't want to learn of course
different facets of the haunted mansion we could have that goal from every ride we could have we could find new different tangents in every single ride wow wall was right imagination truly is limitless I don't know if he said that he might have said it seems like you put it on a construction wall you gotta fill in some quotes I sincerely believe that we can get through small world holiday let's just okay let's reset it as if we could try would it help if we said we were like even there might be
no ad break when I do this but what if I bet this will help with energy what if I say and we'll be right back and when we're back we'll talk about it's a small world holiday all right so we're back and there may have been no ad in what you just
put an ad in there you can really fuck me up and put an ad in I'm gonna put an ad right when you're talking right now the next sentence you talk I'm putting it right yeah right there that's where it is oh damn it I mean I don't really know what happened because this
your only the listener can hear this but you did it didn't you yeah and it comes to be to be marketing I love I put two ads really close together son of a bitch this is because this is like this is like a video game weapon that you're
waiting like you're the ad splatter splat ads in the middle of any you like if the two of us say anything that you'd like if we started saying Mike I don't want to hear about alien stuff that's not kind of thing
yes shit he's right in an ad the ad splatter struck again is Jason there's something you want to say negative to Mike it's amazing just how many drugs hims.com has available the problem is we only have three ad breaks in a regular episode so I've used the ad breaks up and I'm going to let that last sentence play normally
that's a good structure though to like is you know instead of like the boring like it's roughly every word to just like jam all those ads I think that's what I've almost together but then with only three seconds of the podcast technically does come back but just for three and a half seconds
this is gonna make so many people mad cuz like I'm gonna have to do the bit now this is in here but people are gonna have like a full four minutes of ads I'm gonna be so mad some of them are already mad because I'm bad they're out there I see your little there's some there's a flavor for everyone on podcast the ride you know and that's what it's about like a holiday feast each of us brings a different flavor to the table
one of us brings wet walnuts the other brings warm walnuts my walnuts are warm and dry and Jason's are wet and cold geez I'm out of I didn't realize there was a I have no type of walnut fire roasted okay I like that
frozen walnut your walnuts are frozen just cracking some teeth yeah well that would get a bit would be a more exciting you didn't have teeth crackers growing up you would be able you put them in a nutcracker then that's an extra exciting crack cuz you're cracking the ice and the walnut shell you'd have a metal nutcracker though too we have to be cuz a wooden one from maybe would break I don't think nutcrackers crack nuts so good right like like practice like they're more
decorative I think it depends yeah yeah like certainly you should not Jason would you use a decorative walnut cracker no you would use a practical metal one yeah do you have one of those I don't think I think just ornaments that maybe they do the
metal nutcracker or of the wooden one the wooden soldier yeah I don't have I don't think I have any metal nutcrackers in the house I file away a wedding present I'm getting a big nutcracker
yeah his and her get recreations of Jason and Jane getting a getting him like a sexy lady for his bachelor party a sexy lady nutcracker yeah I think that'll be good right I don't know if you want your nuts cracked that's the last thing you want oh yeah we get
a bachelor party I don't know what do you think pal I don't know well I didn't I never had one either really yeah we team up where we going we think we're going down to Knott's Berry farm I actually did consider what do you think we're gonna
Burbank Sears we're gonna walk around the Burbank Sears yeah what do you think I have now been in the Burbank Zombie Sears oh I heard yeah I'm glad they got to this while I was gone I'm just making sure you remember I know you have a lot well you gotta engage your mere feet from it yeah that's true
all right what what time is it how long have we been going we've been going an hour we've been going time to talk about that they put Christmas lights on it's a small world I think we can do it I believe in us small you did some of the stuff 1996 since 1997 Walt Disney's it's a small world has transformed has been transformed from a World's Fair festivity to a to a holiday spectacle holiday light color you could imagine red green
even blue they put a big Santa hat on the clock face outside they sure do which is nice it is nice this small world holiday is better than regular small world I like this take better than regular small world I have to agree with you I really like this
I'm not a small world hater I like small world fine I don't go on it a lot I go to more now that I have a daughter yeah better so much better now what is it because I tend to agree with you what is your knee jerk as to what makes it better and anything you don't say I will try to throw in the outside looks awesome the outside rules it is full if you haven't seen it go online it's just tons of Christmas lights because people are poor friends in Orlando and I think all the other parks at this point various parks have flirted
with this tried it out but it didn't stick I really lands the only one that took it all the way I write they don't do this in Disney World do they am I way I'm not in Disney World they don't have a spectacular facade that's a real problem with the Disney World for that part of it yeah the Magic Kingdom small world is doesn't compare I would say kind of an indoor loading they also don't care about Disney World like they care about Disneyland what do you mean like imagine you're like it doesn't we get like Tiana's Bayou Adventure it was designed for Disneyland and then they shoved it into Disney World is that true that's
what I heard that's what I that's what I heard and like there's still I mean you can feel the philosophy like the Rivers of America gone Disney World they're like see you later cars are moving in and ours are like they paint I mean it's a few years ago already you got like historic landmarks right that's what that's so that they aren't yeah that's currently the philosophy and the proximity of the engineering headquarters being right up the highway go check on it yeah well that's look that's what the Lake Nona campus was supposed to it was and well hey maybe they were
turned to it I don't know they might yes I feel like if there's no what climate Florida will be in the future let me let me throw this in and go so because you mentioned Tiana it seems like we've closed out the year without doing Tiana I would really like to go I really you've done it I have not gotten to do it here's another thing that day that I just described day three of the shoot which was so harrowing for me in many different ways this was also the day that the magic key passes were going on sale yes and I was like there's no way I can be on this set and managing everything that I have
to manage and also be like one sec hang on the Pinocchio the Pinocchio thing is still loading his nose is getting shorter which means I'll be up and it'll be my sorry just hold the take hold the roll that was not gonna happen but I also I was doing some math the night before I'm like hmm if this NYT needle keeps going the way it seems to be going I think I'm gonna want a lot of Disneyland in my future and I haven't had a pass in a while basically I paid a friend to get it to be in the
queue for me and to get me so I'm back I'm back baby I needed it for that Trump cheer up for that post-shoot celebration so I will be I will go and oh and then and I got the lowest tier and in which then the shoots over and I'm like hell yeah I
you just finished your first movie what are you gonna do next I'm going to Disneyland look at calendar oh all of December's yeah fuck me January 8th you'll be back yeah so as soon as I can which will be the new year I will
go on Tiana yeah we'll do that maybe January or February so I guess you better pack some extra socks I hear the water has been like really hitting people it is so soaking people thank God and I guess Jason you better not pack extra socks because I know you're gonna want to get your soak on
colds not colds been a little unpleasant lately and I know Southern California people like well use cold lightly but it's like I'm a little sensitive to heat and cold nowadays more of a summer wet socks man I yeah you could pre soak your socks to get comfortable and then go on it oh you're like a
a trainer yeah so a training for yeah Tiana soak your socks in the bath the nearby bathroom so your socks wake up it's wake up at 655 get the virtual queue yeah shut out of it sitting there in my soaking wet socks practicing but you're still but you're still getting your reps in I like this I like practicing for that's what did and Ernest goes to splash it retains that tradition I am getting ready verne for my return for my
grand voyage on Tiana's at bayou adventure I am soaking my socks to the brim ice-cold temperatures watch this and then what he pro and then it's like then you see like they like turn his ankles blue with digital with an old analog effect with some hungry bear barbecue okay the next virtual queue is in two and a half hours the next ordering time that's available wait I have a question Jason when's the last
time you went to Disneyland I actually I was looking for is about to say this but I have not been in a theme park in over a year since we were in Orlando Wow I think since we were in Orlando yeah you haven't been in the parks but you have been looking up what aspects of going to the park are difficult
so that you can be mad about them from afar I like to keep abreast you know I like to keep updated it's our job Mike has also done a pretty good job at filling in you know he's outing Jason and I have a separate text chain of course about all these different details that's probably smart and now to exclude you're at it we've had a text date since 2009
feel free oh you would like to be excluded on some stuff well he doesn't care about the four different lemonades you can get at the hungry bear barbecue you and I want to talk about the different lemonades they now have at hungry bear barbecue jamboree and all these new water dispensers which as someone usually packs a metal water bottle
I ate there with the family we brought them all there mobile ordered the food we have to I just got an email we have to reshoot all that stuff from when the power went down they need me right now guys I'm sorry
well I guess what does that talk about the sauces but Scott your movie Red One already came out
Red Two it's Red Two I've been being modest of course I did Red One
I love Haunted Mansion Holiday and the average theme park goer loves it more than we do and we like it we're fine with it
I really like it I am not one of these haters of this thing
sure that's fine I would say that on a certain day maybe but I'm just saying like I don't know they could do it in Florida they do it in Japan so I'm just saying like it does feel like we do get special stuff still
yeah well here's also here's what I recall about Small World Holiday is that this ok 1997 it opens and this was this era where we've revisited this from time to time
this is when I started like being a little online about the parks this is where that turn happened and I'm getting on my little news groups and seeing how like oh things are getting a little chintzy maybe this park expansion is not going to be what we think it is
Main Street Electrical Parade is going away what are they replacing it with the worst parade ever made a lot of stuff like that is happening and New Tomorrowland was like so it was kind of it was a bummer of a time you know I've described it before it was a loss of innocence for me in terms of my pure park love and we weren't getting a lot of cool stuff
and what I remember is that okay they're okay let's see so they're doing a holiday they're doing a Christmas version of Small World well what if that what if they kind of crap out on that the way they've been crapping out on everything and sure enough it is just this modest little project that's really nice that stuck and that they've never stopped it was a bright light in sort of a grim budget crunched time for Disneyland specifically so I always have fond memories of it for that reason I'm glad it never dropped off I also remember you guys have
any memory of this or have you seen pictures of it that there was a time where It's a Small World did not have the glimmering white and gold color scheme they did this kind of pastel yeah yeah that was just not that good similar not nearly as egregious as the weird like forced copper paint job in Tomorrowland but it just wasn't as good it looked better pure white like the kind of perma 60s feel of the It's a Small World facade right it went away for a little bit but then they put Christmas lights all over it and it actually
the colors complimented that very well it like the Christmas lights kind of fixed the the aesthetic that It's a Small World fell into that wasn't as pleasant so so I have just very fond memories of when it started just like this is a nice thing it's such a layup and and they yeah they nailed it it's just a nice thing it's a nice thing and it's also like I'll just keep comparing a taunt of Manchala just because that's the closest thing I have to like an annual tradition of an overlay it is
it's nice because it doesn't change the right it's not they're not putting new characters it's not a different movie it's it's nice because and I did sound stupid when you say it it's nice because they put us other lights on it and they put Santa hats on things yeah and there's a slightly different soundtrack yeah yeah and and and it's like it's interesting because it's like I was thinking like Haunted Mansion what if they did a holiday Haunted Mansion but it wasn't Nightmare Before Christmas and you just put Santa hats on all the ghosts you change the
soundtrack fine but but fun still yeah yeah but I'm saying like it's an interesting it's a different thing than that because it's like you're just dressing up what's there already and I'm not saying it's a good or bad thing but it's interesting that like it maintains it maintains the spirit of it in a way obviously stronger than the Haunted Mansion holidays which changes the vibe of the ride well that that soundtrack elevation is definitely a big thing a lot of the feeling I get that I love about Haunted Mansion holidays being outside and that kind of
like that weird like shimmery unsettling score before that it's not even from the the Danny Elfman soundtrack and similar hearing a like big elevated version of obviously that the song changes the dolls all sing jingle bells and in some cases deck the halls but there's all there's still some it's a small world in there and the arrangement is really nice it's nice to hear kind of a 90s bigger better produced strings oriented
holiday infused version of the song I think I think the song it's a small world really shines limited capacity I agree and yeah version we're no small world song haters either that's right but it is you know I get it that it's very repetitive and it's a very simple type song but you do appreciate it more in between jingle bells or deck the halls when you get little breaks from it yes they're just varying it up at all makes you kind of miss and appreciate
yeah sort of like the simple earworm nature I think it's I think overall the song is an upgrade jingle bells I think it is too I mean I love Christmas carols so I have to agree with you like I'm a big Christmas guy so they play wonderful I have been now the last month I've been twice Disney to Disneyland's
oh great and there's a lot the family I got the I made the family get passes parents so like there's a there's different you do the whole yeah your folks go along with your daughter and yes there's different configurations you can have I can pull one family member I mean I am I brave enough to go with a two-year-old yes but I haven't done it yet like just you in here is scary a little bit but I would do universal first because we have done that yeah but it's it's just such a long car ride and if something
goes wrong so speaking of something going wrong last time I was there it's it's very hard sometimes to get her to nap at the right time because a lot of excitement going on so I was she's in the stroller still so I'm like okay if I push her in the stroller at the right time I can get her out and the time before that I was just walking around Star Wars land pushing her around and she was yelling and pointing a Grogu and then calling for her mother you're trying to get the naps to still happen while you're just walking around yes because she just gets
the day can last a little longer then okay yeah because she won't be so hard to deal with it seven eight nine o'clock whatever are you closing that stroller you trying to encourage kind of a relax it happens it's happened a lot so it's so like in the middle of the earlier in the day she'll go to sleep if she's in the stroller for an extended period of time and nothing is too distracting so the so in Galaxy's Edge she's running around and she was like so awake and I was like oh this ain't happening she saw Chewbacca she's never seen Chewbacca she's not seen Star Wars she's a Chewbacca it shocked the hell out
of her she quieted down I swear to God within two or three minutes she was out she was asleep it just like broke her from her pattern she liked seeing him and she's like I'll bring him up now and she knows what's going on but he broke her knee she went right to sleep it's like her brain couldn't process so she just like she just gave up like well right not for today yes that's tomorrow's work she was so up and pointing it like a Grogu backpack and pointing everything and I'm just like wheeling her around here I'm like she's gonna go to sleep and then Chewbacca did it so
then cut to the next week we went and I'm in the Esplanade I'm like getting her sleep I did it last time we can do it this time the Small World Holiday theme comes on in the Esplanade which is the full Jingle Bells Small World she is almost out I have leaned the stroller all the way back I can tell she's on her way out Small World Holiday comes on she loves both of these songs she starts singing and ruins the entire it ruins the entire nap she does not go to bed she is
in there I can see it she's lying down she's like is this Small World after and then sings right into Jingle Bells she's going back and forth nap ruined we couldn't go it ruined like it ruined from 5 p.m. on because she was so tired so you're trying to find Chewbacca now well I should have this very but getting from Esplanade to Galaxy's Edge it's a wild trip there with the stroller you can do it and it was such an infectious song she
couldn't stay asleep she needed to be awake to sing this thing and I yes I also get it I tried going walking around Grand Californian at that point with her just kind of in the back and it didn't work it really screwed me I'm amazed you try the naps even out on the road that's cool that it's worked it's just it's worked almost every time and it just extends our ability to be there without tantrums sure
yeah for a little longer you gotta appreciate what you got cuz I just Aaron and I just went backwards oh it's really because I was sort of gone I was like I was busy and grandma was helping and and now I'm like oh right a baby yeah yeah back at the front of the line oh boy you climbed the mountain once now you gotta climb it again yeah yeah at least I know I can but yeah so so so I was I but I was while this was going on I was like god damn this is a good version of this song I was cursing it and loving it at the same time it's
great that's great stuff in the day Jason you got something on the pie I do yeah right now well I I agree more Christmas hats that's my beat plus up like put a Christmas hat on every human and creature in the Santa hat it's not a Christmas hat but it would be some other type of am I hallucinating this we did an episode about
Santa Kong right I think we did I had a whole discussion of just that they put a Santa hat on King Kong we did do that right we did yeah that's a big one that's one of the best that you don't overthink it yeah yeah put a big hat on a big thing yeah so here is one of my favorite creatures in the
it's like this sea serpent has a Santa hat on and a wreath around their neck oh yeah yeah yeah and it's great and I was a little disappointed because some of the iconic creatures like the the gator with the or the crocodile with the umbrella or the pink hippo didn't have that much Christmas stuff going on
they're not all wearing this one this guy's decked out you know the umbrella the umbrella on the croc doesn't have like there's not like a candy cane pattern on that I might have just not noticed it I didn't see it this popped even just watching video this popped up like it's under the sea Ariel's next to them so there's also very cute I think it's the snake from Jungle Book
but it's in the Egypt sect is Ka Ka kind of like on a deconstructed Christmas tree yeah maybe let me I can describe the thing open here it is like right in front of the or to the side of the Sphinx so but it's like the opposite of the Indiana Jones snake which is scary this one is cute well I should hope so yeah a bit of that's right is a bit of a different tone it would have I mean to be very funny if right in the middle of
Small World there is some like terror the one of those after hours events they just made Small World scary they bring out slave Pinocchio from Hong Kong yeah yeah oof that was rough did you see that picture of him no I think you just tagged me and I still that's a sign to not look yeah that was a really scary picture that sounds very creepy in terms of scares in this thing I I was watching a horror movie and
I was watching a video of it and I didn't know from what year but keep in mind that there's a you know this is obviously largely about about Christmas and the holidays but then there's kind of a new year representation as well and there's always a part where the there's a flashing sign of that that has the you know next year the numbers of next year right written on it and in this case that just we round a corner and I wasn't expecting it and that all of a sudden we're in the new year
and then flashing on and off and lights is twenty twenty yeah and I when I didn't so I must have been watching a twenty nineteen one and not knowing that it's coming there's something about seeing twenty twenty and flashing lights it's it's like you're looking at the Confederate flag it's like it's a it's a hate crime to see the words to see the numbers twenty twenty like don't show that to me yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that video I should report it to YouTube get it yeah yeah you could probably get it they would understand I was watching I
did notice that because there's twenty the one I was watching was twenty twenty five so I did not have that same reaction that's gonna be the same situation in five years well yeah let's let's let's just hope that here's the hope we can put out into the world is the twenty twenty five is not a future notorious year well we'll see we'll see hopefully I don't even know what if it was Harrison Ford saying we'll see the Hulk but red
yeah he's he's bitter because people like people are gonna see me in that stupid red Hulk what do you mean another round of reshoots my friends are gonna see this they're gonna make fun of me if we reshoot it a twelfth time maybe it'll be good what do you mean you already put out the heavy meal toys what are my grandkids gonna get this right here is also the way we make yes and these wooden Santas are really fun oh yeah
they're kind of like Tiki Santas yeah but I mean it's like almost like a 2d wooden Santa and they're really stylized it's hard to track from year to like I mean I guess you could have track from year to year what they put up somebody must I'm sure there is like a running tally of like and this was new this year and this was new this year but it's all it's all kind of a wash to me nothing so insane has been added they put the snowman I believe at the end toward the end is new this year so this big if you've seen that which is a really cool giant snowman yes and the
I think it's his winter wonderland under him and the font is a little sinister but it's supposed to look like icicles sinister well hold on let me find it yeah yeah here here the snowman was added in 2011 was it really oh then I'm thinking of something else I'm thinking of something else yeah that's a little bit of a metal band font yeah I like it but yeah I feel like the lights outside the
lights on the building as like LED technology just keeps getting better and better I feel like they're more vivid all the time sparkles I feel like yeah it's straight lights like you'll get little like little like bright white sparkles sure and it feels like extra fun when the like it hits the top of the hour and is it every few minutes 15 every 15 minutes the little show yeah that goes on wait no okay let me admit I watched a ride through
but I don't know what happens to the little clock show I don't know how the clock show is different but it is different there's a first of all there's a hat on the clock as you said yeah but what else happens to that clock show do we know we need to just watch I think it's kind of standard the little guys come out and then they go back like there's nothing special it's not different for the holidays I I didn't really notice a difference that stuck out when I watched I admit to not watching the actual ceremony I watched the turning on the light ceremony which is just a very quick
thing they do that where they do almost like they do a California adventure at Halloween time it's an unspectacular ceremony but I do like the idea that you switch on like I wish there was a Guardians of the Galaxy when it's monsters after dark when they like counted down to like the thing turning yeah a different color yeah but no I don't actually don't know I should look that up yeah should look and see if there's a difference in the little clock show because yeah they it's every 15 you said it's usually like the toy soldiers
pretending that they don't know what happens to try to get small world holiday 2 to happen we have to we didn't know what happened to the clock show if it's happened in seven years that's fine we're on a good we're on a good precedent you may as well point I was reminded in the very
two of us all have quit by seven years from now there'll be one of us left I don't know who it is and is it a pure monologue or is the one do I don't want to suppose who it is but is the other is the one who's left doing it to like pillow versions of the others oh maybe yeah there's like it's
you're pretending they're there or it's they've been replaced by an AI we both we whoever we are who have been replaced by a eyes mmm yeah like James Earl Jones we have willingly submitted our voice to the AI the AI averse except we did not also die right but yeah it's
well he did it before he died yes you could so he got paid he had a lot of fucking bad bullshit with Darth Vader they can do whatever they want and his family gets paid which is nice I was reminded I was saying at the very beginning of the ride you kind of hear like a monologue from Santa but he's in his home yeah there's Santa house so you're all just kind of four years you're just kind of peeping on Santa it's just
like we're hearing his innermost thoughts we're hearing is his monologue talking to himself so he's thinking you're saying you think he's thinking that he's not saying it to us I think he's saying it but he's like talking to himself like if you talk out loud when you're like okay I gotta I gotta measure that I gotta do you know like well this is your read on it but this is the is this just a cousin of one of the some of the sexual things that we've learned about in the recent past this is this a fetish called like Christmas
voyeurism I don't think peeping I think peeping Tom is a universal reference I think voyeurism Tom can be a pervy thing of course it can say it is exclusively a non-pervy example of peeping Tom well you've just never been curious about how other people live when they think they're not being one I'm not saying it's me Jason's very online that's why he knows more about being a peeping Tom
he's read up on being a peeping Tom he knows all the ways you can be and it's not one thing being a peeping Tom can be many things yeah it could be you can peep on a lot of you can be a peeping Tom and peep on many different things or people yeah you know he's a college friend you may be Tom Ripley this guy I met and he seems really interested in my life I don't know what's going on literal peeping Tom yeah I don't know we're going out on a rowboat later just
check some stuff out so we'll see what happens there's that radio voice again it is the perfect amount of time this exists the perfect amount of time too it is like just long enough where you get a nice chunk like it but it's not doesn't overstay its welcome yeah so like sometimes some years you're gonna miss it which is nice again Haunted Mansion Holiday it's so long you're not missing Haunted Mansion Holiday if you're going a couple times a year
I like that thing I continue to agree it's it's a little bit long and yeah it feels a lot I think I like something that plays a little hard to get yes and then it's like if you can if not Monsters After Dark I feel like even runs longer than I feel like that runs closer to two months but this thing runs like a little over a month like it just it had just or it was just opening when I was there like mid-November so like it's like six weeks yeah mid-November
to what I think is when the holiday stuff wraps up does it go that long it probably ends of the day before our passes are good again yeah yeah yeah we are exactly boxed out of fuck with us you will not see this but you got to see you got to say with you you are in the yeah so I will get to at the end of yes you can do it it's I don't think there's anything we're barred from seeing the tree is up but we went twice and that second November trip was to make up for the December
trip we wouldn't be taking that is where they're headed you're gonna have to start doing like there'll be like certain price tiers like okay well with the with a magic key you don't get to look at the Matterhorn we've now we've written a scanned you have to have done a retina scan to get a magic key and like yeah no okay well like there look there are unfortunately blackout pirates there are a number of pirates throughout the attraction who you don't get to see but you get to see a few at the beginning
one in the middle and then a couple you know sixty percent into the right and then nothing for the last five minutes but the people with the top tier pass get to see all of them you're saying well yeah until the four hundred dollar written add-on yeah
because you're gonna want to guarantee your path to seeing every pirate yeah with the keys these I did you joke but these sort of thoughts I've been having a lot in the wake of the last few weeks as certain things
accelerate toward their inevitable end and that is where oh boy well that was a heavy way to put it swell that's all no we can't not an hour and a half I can't get into what I'm talking about I mean I you know what I'm talking about hey cheer up come on I was trying to say happy 2025 to y'all I'm it's me baby new year okay that's something that happens baby new year Jason's favorite character in fiction I would imagine
I'm changing from my long typical podcasting beard to my little Sash and Di-P the face Scott made when you said Di-P I'm back baby that is kind of a universal like the old year leaving the new year beginning Jason that was not what my harumph noise was about it was less about the concept of baby new year and more about the word Di-P
you're worried about the universality of my references I think I nailed this one yes that one not an issue yes certainly you're reacting to the reference to baby new year and not the joke about me stripping my clothes away in front of you and putting on a diaper little being said right before Di-P
no years of stage acting taught me to have one costume on under the other so the Di-P is ready to go so you're wearing it already yeah what he's this is a long way for him to tell us that he's currently wearing a little Di-P in all seriousness I think a thing that I
really like about this ride that I think works well on an attraction in Florida the Space Mountain at Christmas where they just they just pummel you with music and blinking green and red lights there's so much Christmas stuff in this and granted it's Christmas around the world but it's just like you're getting hit with Christmas carols and lights and decorations and stuff you're being pummeled you're being pummeled so like it's yeah you know what
I feel like it has just like I think it sort of filled a void the Disneyland had which is the need to just have Christmas the ride that's sort of what this is I guess that's true it just became like you know the like the dolls and everything in it like all work and it's all complimentary but what it really is about is just like taking a boat past a bunch of Christmas lights into a place to see more Christmas stuff yeah more winter stuff it's Christmas the ride that is like a really it's pretty simple
which in this and look in the spirit of holiday of forgiveness and and coming together this is something I haven't experienced this myself but you know I've I've been on the record about my feelings about living with the land but I like the feeling that I get from this Christmas version I think I would like that the Christmas version of living with the land because I think that would have the same thing of kind of being Christmas the ride it seems it seems neat to me I hope to do it in person at some point we really should fly
tomorrow or tonight to Orlando to do Pizza Rizzo and to do that living with the land clock is ticking do we know have any idea when it's going away I don't know but when they were talking about starting the monsters in construction it seemed fat like it seemed like that was on a faster track are we gonna have to do a Pizza Rizzo Pizza Rizzo episode without having eaten at Pizza Rizzo I'm worried that that might be the case I went I walked around I visited Malia I but I didn't get to I like the really if
really ultimately the food is part of it but maybe the food is not part of it I did like the little wedding banquet room a lot yeah I like things that I really like that yeah I mean it's to Mac or donut it's very the pizza I mean I bet I bet it's funny seeing stuff that I remember opening like 10 years ago like a Pizza Rizzo or like the Hello Kitty store get flipped to Monsters Inc. and the wicked like center
like it's very straight it's like I feel like they built that out so much and then they're like we're putting in new stuff they put all this money into transforming the space and now they aren't holding the space ironically I have if they said you'll have time to enjoy enjoy it in 2025 but I don't know will it last six months I don't know well all the more reason to light the fire to I was gonna say this at the wrap up
but my my New Year's resolution get down to Orlando we've talked about we talked about a couple episodes ago there's a lot of stuff happening this year there and of course I mean the opening of John Taffer's right Taffer's Tavern in the on in the I Drive area you think they would let us break a bottle of Taffer's brown butter bourbon on the building as it opens like it's the ship official inaugurator by the bottle too he doesn't have to pay for it
sure he's not going to so in late you said a bottle that's money out of my pocket we can do before like some cream soda in there you know we don't have to actually he just has to look like it was his bourbon doesn't actually I also think I could probably like you know buy some other I still I'm still carrying around that sticky bottle oh yeah exploded in Vegas that we offered to do that way I think we had with Griffin I offered it to James Zdomian who seemed rightfully disgusted
by the idea yeah it's still kicking around my house I'm gonna have to this is becoming a real I don't know that bourbon can turn like sandwiches but it is very much a Homer and the Big Sandwich situation this thing just gets grosser and grosser by the day but I could fill it up with other whiskey reseal it and use that to break the well on the second gate Jason has said he's he's not enjoying expired food like he used to well now you're great as
boys I know I've had to make a lot of lifestyle change in the last year plus we don't if you think that if you think that we're I'm gonna burn any time here on the getting the giant sandwich this is club three business that's gonna be on the paywall yeah I we have
others Christmas stuff because I have a little small world thing let's cover Chris it's not quite Christmas oriented that's why it's hard I wish there was like a comprehensive list of everything because I'm sure there's like
invisible stuff even I'm not noticing or making the lights brighter or more aggressively Christmas or holiday which 18 I felt like I would be like a week you could do this in a week right I don't know if there's other stuff I'm not even thinking about but I
think longer than I had for the movie I was gonna say yeah I hear 18 days my head spins I think the with this and on a mansion they had to preserve a lot of the original stuff is so old at this point you mean so they don't careful they got a
tiptoe that's why yeah they have to go do not knock the serpent so it's all doll number five in India you don't think somebody's falling over and crushed one of the dolls like oh no turn it around that face the wall and then like yeah they like just find like a
basketball or something and paint a face on it or a volleyball like Wilson they paint a volleyball stick it on the little kid's head and nobody's gonna notice it's a stylized face so we got any rides with pigs in it just grab a grab a pig paint it skin color and throw it on there 50,000 bulbs I saw yes yes that's another little fact more facts you remember any facts I don't have any more facts I kind of settle my facts I mean facts Christmas is beloved
all the world round yeah that is a fact yes Christmas is a Christmas season is a time for caring fact there was a weird thing that I was looking at some like website where they're like here's some 10 facts about haunted on a mission a small world holiday and like most of them aren't even facts just like it's good and you're like yeah that is I guess yeah that's a that's a trick listicle that's a trick stickle it is a trick yes it was a trick arbitrarily made into 10 it's like this is like number nine it's like it's all about the small details and one of the first rooms representing the northern region pay close attention to all the
subtle festival details again this isn't really a fact my favorite is the mailbox with letters to Santa and a silhouette of the man himself in the window situated behind a little furry friend with a paddle what what what yeah what do you guys know what that means and I'm gonna paddle some animal well or is the animal the one with a paddle I don't know wait say the sentence again let's really think about our conjugation here okay my favorite is the mailbox with letters to Santa and a silhouette of the man himself in the window
situated behind a little furry friend with a paddle behind he's so Santa's behind does the furry friend have the paddle pointed at Santa's front I or is it Santa who has the paddle and he is behind I thought it was the furry friend was in front of the house is how I took that a silhouette of the man himself in the window situated on him situated behind a little furry friend with a paddle what's the furry friend I what
kind of yeah is Santa have like a furry friend historically and I don't think so he has mrs. Claus he is Rudolph Rudolph isn't free though he's a reindeer and we're combining okay it's we're combining furries and paddles Jason I'm not online enough what is it I'm throwing is it is it just an Easter egg of tiptoe the blue reindeer the Macy's mascot but does tiptoe the blue reindeer from Macy's have a paddle does it wield a paddle it has a walking parade float
yeah but we don't we don't have it's a shame I think we already said our Christmas lineup but learning about the original character tiptoe the blue reindeer that they're trying to get inception into us that like this is a guy they did work you love it huh they
Incepted you I bring it up tiptoe on this I think I saw a lot of people going what the fuck is I didn't remember tiptoe yeah you go to sleep dreaming about tiptoe now and Macy's great stock and return policies well you always go to sleep thinking about Macy's return policy let's be honest
oh my god another reshoot on the movie guys I gotta get out of here oh let's just let me do my episode visions of hassle free returns floating in his head
okay I'm looking at a still from the video of this tiptoe I see no oh okay you wish no I see it's a silhouette of Santa and there's maybe like I don't see a paddle I don't know what's going on what's the paddle I don't know I see no furry friends
with a paddle do you see this is a Rorschach test now we're looking at a silhouette I don't see a furry friend in a paddle I guess this is an article from last year so I perhaps the paddles gone but what's to the left of Santa in that silhouette is that his hand or is that a candle it looks to me like he's holding a wishbone
is it a ping pong paddle is it a ping pong paddle is it a pickleball paddle I hear that's really growing in popularity is Santa playing pickleball up at the North Pole maybe are there enough human beings to play I guess he could play with the elves elves little friend with a paddle I mean what even character has a paddle
now I'm looking at 2023 I see no paddle what is this wait wait wait stop everything I got it this is what they mean there's a little it has nothing to do with Santa there's a little white cub some kind of like polar bear cub who is on a paddle as if on a kayak that's what it is the Santa thing was confusing
what we're looking at is Santa's house and then separately in front is a cute little bear in a kayak they are not in the same room Santa is not ominously hanging out behind you were trying to okay okay I was saying like oh look for this and then look behind it okay oh geez well I skipped too far ahead in the video yes alright because when you said that sentence I pictured that like I don't know some kind of a pest got into the house or that Santa has changed his mind about a pet
that he got once or is particularly mad at the reindeer this year yeah and he then so he is as we've said in the past he has come with a paddle for their ass right like Santa's gonna do something really bad with this paddle to a little furry creature who I don't think had it coming oh I thought the creature was gonna nail Santa with it oh you took it a whole other way yeah I took it the other way there's some kind of like revenge fantasy happening I thought that was gonna be the impetus for red one they have to rescue Santa from this unhinged
little creature who's taking him captive there's some sort of little gremlin or some kind of like freak reindeer went into the flying machine like some sort of freak creature yeah who has somehow gotten loose in Santa's house got a hold of a paddle and now he's gonna go buck wild on Santa's butt Jason what animal would you want to paddle get a paddle from who would you want to get hit with who which animal would you want to take a paddle to your ass are you saying do I want a strong animal or I want a weak animal
to run up to you I don't like a baby goat would probably be cute okay I'll try to manage a paddle anthropomorphic or regular with just a paddle in its mouth think either yeah but that's a big difference oh yeah anthropomorphic it can uh can really
curse at me and swing yeah well I didn't say that speak English swing I guess baby goat then okay that would just be cute it's kind of just like it'd be cute now I could put my hands on my hip and go like right come on really but I mean it look it wouldn't hurt too bad because you would have the diapy on yeah like a little padding yeah diapy provides padding that's what it is it's literally what it is it's padding yeah it's padding
so it meant to be padding for it's meant to be padding the other way not writing for a paddle right not paddle well WDW magazine is a written a confusing article let's just put it that way magic confusing clickbait trixticles coming from yeah online Disney well this is what got us into the mess of that Eisner is the golfer and then the still unproven fans thing I'd love to figure out the fans thing this year and I still can't find her next year 2025 I still can't find the thing that was new this year that was not the snowman so that is that's what
why we're gonna have to do another one I guess so I guess well here's what I'm
wondering is should I burn how deep are we in now what's that almost two hours
just a little under yeah I'll say I'll say it fast okay yeah because I was in
the small world holiday section of the Wikipedia which brought me towards the
bottom of the small world Wikipedia which had a little section about small world
in other media and it brought up in this section I saw a reference to a small
world movie that was planned but not made in the 1970s oh interesting and I'm gonna
read you this as copy pasted straight out of the Wikipedia okay although this this
might necessitate maybe we do need small small world holiday 2 or small world 3
whoa Raymond John Cassavetes was planning a devastating look into the
lives of the people around the world Disney was gonna finance a Cassavetes
that's pretty cool yeah no here we go in the 1970s a planned feature film was
going to be a Cold War tinged comedy adventure where the children of UN
leaders try to get their parents to stop squabbling through faking mass
kidnapping only for a war profiteer to try to take advantage of the fear and
start a mass conflict whoa what it's a small world the movie of a fake
kidnapping and war profiteering what the fuck what is he made movie no it wasn't
made but it was planned but Disney was going to make it I'm saying well I think
that might be too strong that might be further than it ever got here's here's
that I started exploring like what is the source on this and I clicked on the
source was Jim Hill media interesting this is a Jim Hill thing this is
something he published in 2003 and he published it because he seemingly knows
the person who had this idea this was a movie pitched by a guy named Larry
Pontius he was VP of marketing for the US parks in the 1970s and Jim Hill goes
into further detail about what this pitched 1970s it's a small world the
movie was going to be so let me weave the tale here really quick before we go
all right so to set the scene tensions are high internationally it was the
1970s you see only somewhat after the Cold War so a nine-year-old Russian boy
is captured and detained by the Chinese a Russian boy just goes into China just
to like look around and make some friends and China says no get out of here you
know flares up the conflicts between the countries big news story international
incident and this is the dream of a true villain named Alexander Bashillion he is
a despotic leader of a made-up country maybe Krakow from the terminal something
like that you know Russia esque and his sole export is munitions that's all
that's what he lives for is to sell weapons he Alexander Bashillion lives
for war you see so you know he's good he's gonna use this to stoke
international fears but there's one group of people who doesn't like any of
this and that is the kids of all the UN ambassadors because they all go together
to one UN elementary school you see and even the even yes you know the UN kids
all go to the same school huh yeah you got it you're with me and they all get
along great not like us adults with all of our weird fear mongering and over
thing you know kids speak the international language of love they all
get along so the kids of the UN ambassadors they all hatch a plan they
say I know how to make everybody get along in the world again we'll pretend
that we got kidnapped and then everybody will have to unite to come find us what
without why without us plucky kids what are we good like how can the UN possibly
move forward so they do that they go hide somewhere all the click one kid
from every nation Noah's Ark situation they all disappear and this becomes a
much bigger story than the one Russian boy who got captured so that story gets
wiped out mission accomplished so the kids have reminded everybody what's
important not so because evil Alexander Bashillion seizes on this and he says
all those kids who got kidnapped that was the fault of Russia and or China
they took them so now what we need to do we need to have a war and also I'm gonna
go kill all those kids that's the story of it's a small world the movie oh my
god a false kidnapping of one child from every country in the world all fake
kidnaps themselves and then a mean man sets out to murder them it's a small
world what the fuck what is this really I mean it's it's too specific it's got to
be real some yeah but when I say when when when you read Disney was developing
this were they really because think about the story that I just read now
now juxtapose that to what Disney live-action movies were like in the
1970s this would have come out right between you know cat from outer space
and candle shoe we would have had this movie about a false international
kidnapping incident you know Disney wanted just getting on the paranoid
thrillers of the seven parallax few three days of the condor and they're
like we want to get in on that money train Walker is wondering where's my
three days of the condor I don't this is such a bizarre I mean maybe it was
developed and written and then finally somebody went wait what because it was
the 70s they didn't quite know what they were supposed to be certainly yeah so
maybe it did get written or developed like it's possible well as as Jim tells
the story a treatment for this was drafted and shown to then head of Disney
card Walker the feedback apparently was he literally he wrote on the treatment
interesting and that might have been maybe that is what happened but my
question beyond that then is okay we're gonna do it's a small world the movie it
is gonna be a paranoia thriller made in the 1970s is would they have just done
this with a bunch of kind of like you know like a couple tears down from Jodie
Foster like kind of mophead kid actors like those kind of bad musketeers from
that 70s special oh yeah my god gee we got to kidnap ourselves but I got to get
home for dinner is it like to like a Billy Moomy would have been too elevated
for this maybe yeah too good yeah no this is like the third new Mickey Mouse
club I think so he's all playing kids around the world anonymous mop heads yeah who all have to learn some
accents that they probably can't soccer a blue Alexander but Chile on wants us
dead but then my but then my further question was and this is maybe still a
question if it was this or any story if you were gonna make it's a small world
the movie would you do it with the dolls you're saying me personally or just like
what you would have to do it with the dolls right well I don't know if you'd
have to it would be the scariest option but just imagine imagine a full movie
with puppeted dolls kind of in the vein of garbage pail kids oh well that's a
different story and it's genuinely scary it's like it's a living it's like you
know let's say Michael Caine is playing Alexander Bashillian like my way with
you I will see I was gonna say don knots is Alexander Bashillian well now
we're talking about Fred McMurray is the heroic American ambassador Tony is
important because there are old movies that are like light and fun but there if
you really analyze what's happening it's a shot attempted child kidnapping child
murder like there are I could maybe see this is a little heavier than normal
movie I'm talking about but well but like you know the the Beethoven films
exactly about because Disney staple Dean Jones is in them the first one is like a
bunch of needles are gonna go into a kidnapped dog and the next one Beethoven
rescues his owner from a rape situation yes this is some very heavy yes subject
matters right so yes it's maybe maybe maybe on paper they didn't think okay or
in in pitch they didn't think oh this may be a little too much but in the way
that some people say like oh the last unicorn or bed knobs and broomsticks
like there's some unsettling elements yeah this well they would have had to
you yeah with the 70s dolls though they would have had to use like 70s technology
to make puppet dolls that's what I'm if this is just imagine you know we've been
glorifying the Eisner era but if in that now that's where all the craziest stuff
came from but if this one is tweaked through wow yeah watch it's a small
world the movie and it's about like like a rifle is being held to the to the
temple of a little small world doll like there's like there's a little Russian
doll cowering next to a little a little Iceland imagine yeah please we speak but
don't you realize as much as we share it's time we're aware it's a small world
after all oh my god I never thought of it that way what have I become I'm a
munitions loving monster and then it takes his own life yeah splattering all
over all of the doll Don nuts geez I'm a monster I tell you I don't deserve to
live wait you can change you can change mr. nods and that's really if only we
can get a blu-ray that this holiday season could we get Jim just to like do
does he have like just a list of everything that was in development from
1970 to 19 just we imagine all and we just said and when Jess was on because
she was talking about various projects and development at Disney all the money
they've spent not making every ride oh sure into a movie or TV show I wonder
because there's probably been several rounds of every single one every single
one of them yeah yes and I would be interested is is it does it picked
probably picked up in the last 20 years but I bet still before that obviously we
hear small world in the 70s like this one right yeah it's new to me yeah in the
1970s they tried to develop the Main Street omnibus and then you read the
treatment page one the omnibus crashes glass flies everywhere no survivors the
omnibus at the time was carrying one child of everyone in the UN delegation a
child from every nation in the world was slaughtered at the hands of a broken
omnibus starring Donnats oh god I was too drunk to drive the omnibus someone
got the brakes well if only you know it's it's it's not a world where you have
a great film like that but it is a world where a podcast toast can come back from
a big crazy adventure and reconvene with his with his podcast pals it's been a
pleasure guys I like yes it's been nice to be back glad I got it in great to
have you yes thanks thanks welcome back again this may and again and this may
have already been said several times and that you may have already heard a future
welcoming but for now we all survived podcast the ride main feed 2024 what a
year a host departure all that d23 bedding and nonsense the the Orlando
Saga yeah yeah did we do that we did I believe we did it's hard to remember it
was several can I say a couple children ago for me in my mind since we did that
I was thinking like oh and that like I City Walk is gonna change so much in the
next five years I have a feeling we just I'm glad we did it to wrap up this
version of it I'm just saying but I in my mind since we finished that City Walk
shouldn't change it should stay the same as it was when we did the sagas yeah
okay and any respect for our our great classic work but I think it I think the
toll story of the podcast that's where I think yeah but no it's gonna change and
hotels will come and oh you're saying we're gonna know the hotels are very
exciting but I'm just like we're gonna have to cover it in some way I don't
know but it doesn't I didn't we say we did it already right it's not like it's
not up to us ultimately it's really a matter if we get contacted by a ghost or
by a guy who's out in the world who resembles a ghost well I don't know what
whatever strange mechanism will cause us to have to go review a cafe in a hotel
yeah I know well we'll see in what year will that occur I don't know but 2025 is
ahead of us I vow some fun stuff I vow some live stuff and I also vow that the
adventures will continue even through the holiday season even as we take a
little main feed break I don't remember how to read this anymore guys it's been
weeks a few fourths for three bonus crepe episodes shit I forgot how to say
the words okay for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride
the second gate where we will have new episodes even as we take a little main
feed hiatus or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three you
will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride and of course
coming soon the the audience requested official Scott response yeah the Scott
free era yeah buckle up we had a lot of points to go over gentlemen
points McDonald's points this has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Bohm Joe Cilio and
Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts calm
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get
your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on
Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook