Welcome to podcast the ride the second gate and happy holidays as today we're going to
be saying the names Tress McNeil Bill Farmer and Charles Fleischer a lot I'm Jason Sheridan
hi I'm Mike Carlson we're gonna be saying these names a lot I thought we would they're they're
notable in this special yeah I mean I think we will be saying those names but I just I
questioned the a lot I hate to I hate to start so combative here but I just think what do you
think a lot is well let's take a guess I'm not gonna not say their names now in a normal way I'm
just wondering let's guess what we would have done look it's probably just going to be a handful
of times but I think it's very funny to just list very specific people's names even though
you could argue these are like voice acting legends I think you would yes I don't think
there's an even an argument to be made I wouldn't argue with that they're legends well I think I'm
gonna let me see I'm gonna say the name Bill Farmer today I think maybe once I think I'll
say Bill Farmer once that's after this sort of preamble and I'll say Tress McNeil once and
maybe I'll say Jim Cummings 25 times that's maybe that's the one maybe I'll say Jim Cummings a few
times sure because who knows what the conversation about him where that could take us the freedom
fighter yeah I could see maybe that being the case but I just you know I'm calling I'm just
making my predictions ahead of today's episode you might have also latched on more to the original
human characters like their narrator the sad sack Conrad then the minis neighbor Tina sweet
hungry Tina yes yes so so yes today we're talking about it you've probably seen this in the title
we're talking about Mickey's Nutcracker which is a show that I kind of knew existed kind of it's
familiar we've talked about it there's a there's a musical number in it that is very familiar that
I think we have talked about before specifically one one that I feel like has maybe made the rounds
more the rest of it yeah but when I was going back through stuff to do for Christmas season I was
like oh Mickey's oh okay it was a special on TV and it was also something that was actually live
at Disneyland which was on the Videopolis stage yeah I think one in 1992 yeah it was on the
Videopolis stage and this special aired Christmas 92 I think a big thing that sticks out to me all
those voice actors these are like the real deal voice this is an off-brand Doc Brown this is an
off-brand that's true it's not off-brand mostly but Paul Winchell who was Tigger for many many
years was not Tigger in this it was Jim Cummings right so you would say maybe at the time people
would be like what is this bullshit where's my Paul Winchell Tigger this sucks fuck Jim Cummings
Paul Winchell forever they were okay with him doing the the offstage exterminator voice yes right
exactly because he does do other voice of other voice in the show yeah but yes so so mo from as
far as our childhood yes Jim Cummings Tigger is all we've really known as far as new poo in the
last I don't know so many years but for the time there probably were Tigger purists who were furious
where's Winchell yeah sucks where's Winchell Winchell lived I feel like he lived to like
2,000 or something crazy but I maybe I'm wrong maybe I'm getting my John Fiedler which I
mispronounced his name who was Piglet on an episode a few weeks ago this one I'm talking
about so many wonderful names Paul Winchell well yeah Paul Winchell 2005 okay because Paul
Winchell also I knew Paul Winchell because he was a ventriloquist he had a dummy you know what I'm
talking about kind of you weren't a Paul Winchell guy I don't know if I was a Paul Winchell guy I
don't know that I was ever much ventriloquist guy you never were a bit who's your favorite hey
wait let's go who's your favorite ventriloquist I don't know if I have one I think Slappy from
Goosebumps just scared me well he's a scary guy but do you think maybe I mean are you a Dunham
maybe you're a new ventriloquist guy maybe that's more of your style Terry Fader you love Vegas well
I I do love Vegas and you know I I just get a little started by those ones because I'm not
sure what's going to be coming out of those dummy's mouths well that's fair I mean Paul
Winchell had the like the Jerry Mahoney doll like that's what you know you hear that reference a
lot yeah um and it's a pretty like you here I have his pictures right here first of all Paul
Winchell kind of a hunk if you really look at him kind of a hunk and there he is with
with his dummy who looks like you know Slappy looks like Night of the Living yeah he look that's
like a classic ventriloquist and kind of has the same less handsome look but kind of looks like him
vaguely okay Paul Winchell with Jerry Mahoney and he had another character named Knucklehead
Smith oh I like that I want to see Knucklehead Smith well yeah there he is right there
M-S-M-I-F-F but this famous ventriloquist was Tigger's voice Knucklehead Smith is more put
together than I would have thought Smith it's M-I-F-F yeah he's got kind of like a track jacket on
and then Jerry Mahoney has kind of a James Bond like that white like suit jacket with the black
bow tie he looks very and they're both making eyes at Paul Winchell for a name uh a character
named Knucklehead he has an awfully like well put together turtleneck ensemble yeah I mean look we
can look into more into Knucklehead in the future because I don't I'll be honest I don't know a
ton about Knucklehead look at this top of the episode I was doubting you that we would say
names and you but if you had said Paul Winchell I would immediately have proven you right because
I've said Paul Winchell about 10 times by now I just for some reason I didn't think we were
gonna say Bill Farmer that much I don't know I just latched on that that one no I'm saying I'm more
for the audience I guess I'm totally wrong is what I'm saying I guess you would have been 100%
I'm apologizing I'm saying like 100 you would have been 100% right if you had said well say the
name Paul Winchell a million times or Knucklehead Smith which we've already said seven or eight
times oh man this episode of course is Scott Frey always oh is it I didn't notice he's not
not here he was just looking for a moment uh we're talking about the handsomeness of dummies oh I
guess Scott isn't here you're right I didn't notice that he wasn't oh I guess I forgot we're gonna
have to get him up to speed because the audience on club three voted they wanted to hear oh yes
they did yes check in they wanted to hear uh Papa Scott's feedback on the Scott Frey episode so now
we have we tell about uh Paul Winchell Jerry Mahoney Knucklehead Smith this is very exciting
well we tell them about the Paul Winchell and Jerry Mahoney show uh which was also sponsored by Tootsie
Roll you know or it had featured a clubhouse motif and a theme song co-written by Winchell
and his longtime bandleader and on-air sidekick Milton the Lug oh wow you say the best for last
Milton the Lug I'm gonna be spending the rest of the day looking up Milton the Lug yes uh so okay
let's pivot back to Mickey's Nutcracker yes which has a lot of the big voices that we recognize
Rucy Taylor Minnie Mouse up until a few years ago she did Minnie until she was like 90 or something
she's in this um but yeah they got it all there's no there's there's not many uh fake sounding
voices in this I'll say that yeah I mean it's crazy how much the company as a whole has memory
hold Roger Rabbit like Roger Rabbit used to be a heavy hitter oh yeah I know he used to be a main
eventer number they put him in the slot like the the main event slot up in up in like what a year
I guess when the movie came out it wasn't even a year late like he was just one of the big six seven
whatever we call it he was one of them yeah he probably was higher than Chippendale at the time
even though rescue rangers was happening but yeah he was everywhere uh and then yes they slowly got
rid of him I feel like he lasted into the 90s but he is yeah he has not been there and then there's
we've speculated on this before because there's been different like dialogue about why there's
not more Roger Rabbit going on I forget who somebody was pitching a show to Disney recently
and they tweeted this I think that they were like oh there's too many people that own the
rights to Roger Rabbit it's not something Disney outright owns yeah it's a legal quagmire between
right Disney and I guess Amblin or yeah something like yeah yeah right some sort of Katzenberg
Spielberg but then they were somebody was asking Robert Zemeckis about it and his answer was just
like yeah they're not going to use Jessica anymore did you see what they did to her at Disneyland
they put a coat on her yeah so he went more with that route and almost blamed it on that that like
Disney is afraid of Jessica Rabbit which is something I've heard uh lately or I guess in the
last few years and I guess it would it would back up what he's saying because they literally
threw a coat on her like they did throw a coat on her that's not making that up as if there's
not millions of styles of evening gowns but they are afraid of her ample bosom
like that's what Disney doesn't they're like worried about that I guess well wait but don't
you know she's not bad she's just drawn that way I know she said that so I guess maybe there's a
little bit of both still preventing Roger from having his big comeback yeah I think everybody
would like Roger to have a comeback but they kind of went separate paths almost because like Roger
Rapids in all these parades it's in all these state shows doesn't necessarily mean Jessica there
was there I mean Jessica so you want to get rid of your island you would get rid of Jessica in
a future Roger Rabbit project are you saying they could do it hypothetically uh no I don't
want to get rid of her at all oh you want to get rid of Roger and just have a sexy Jessica Rabbit
I'm just saying there was a point where like Jessica's was at Pleasure Island yes her kind
of own separate thing Roger Rap was doing stage shows baby Huey was hanging around
baby Huey was hanging around I feel like well remember there was going to be a baby Huey like
ride based on that one short that was oh you're talking about they were no no no not baby Huey
you're talking about the baby from oh baby oh god is it well I can't think of his name now
now all I can think of is baby Huey from Harvey comics is it baby Oscar what's his no that's baby
Oscar's from Ghostbusters 2 why can't I think of baby I all I can think of is what baby Huey
looks like in my head I have a complete block how how fast are you typing on an iPad I am looking
at baby why can't I think of his name I can see his baby face it's not boss baby it's not uh uh
Kenneth babyface Edmonds no that rmb legend singer producer that's not him who baby baby it's not
baby Sherman how is it taking you this long to google because I pulled up his wikipedia I'm
googling now and uh that's baby Herman baby Herman there we go I forgot there was like a bunch of I
couldn't pull it either I I forgot there was a bunch of books so then half the wikipedia you
started reading a book to try to find his name I was trying to scroll down to who framed Roger
Rabbit uh-huh oh god that's embarrassing I've embarrassed myself so many times on this episode
already I I squawked at the idea of saying names and then I couldn't find baby Herman's name in
my brain anyway yes you so you could split all three of them up and and do something with them
I mean they can get back together I mean that yeah the the uh Chippendale movie that went to
plus who we know friends of friends the writers of like that uh is like getting the gang back
together sure yeah which also another Tress McNeil project because she's gadget well she's in
everything she's in everything she's a legend always the voice of chip I don't think I ever
knew that oh uh what do you mean always uh good question uh maybe in the 80s or 90s she took over
yeah I I yeah it's interesting to see like when certain people took over then some people took
over like Jim Cummings some people would take over here and there they wouldn't take over
completely yeah there's always like a weird like it's it's there's starts and stops to some of the
people's voice so you are just dunking on my ass about how many times we're gonna say these names
I feel just humiliated now from I look I was just trying to have fun with it no no I'm your dunk I
mean you're low-key donkey you're not a cocky dunker like I would be if I had if I had proven
you wrong at the start I would just be like celebrating you're just low-keying it that you've
proven correct your assessment I I am trying oh you know and just a humble man I'm just a simple
man it's a man I much like the uh Nutcracker Mickey Nutcracker who comes to life he is not
you know uh let's talk about the Nutcracker real quick because I feel like I mean Nutcracker
people have had Nutcracker mania during Christmas season for many years but I feel like in our
childhood specifically I was just bombarded with Nutcracker we went to see uh like a local ballet
do Nutcracker we did too Philadelphia always did it every year I feel like just so much Nutcracker
and then obviously so much of the music especially Dance of the Sugarplum Fairies you know it's in a
Nestle commercial it's playing it's playing in a every Christmas commercial you were just
bombarded with it did you like the Nutcracker oh I loved it I did I think um catching bits and
bobs on tv of the actual story of the ballet element I would sometimes be very unnerved
or like I forgot there's a character called the Rat King and uh this one has a very happy ending
right I would say and I I couldn't really Mickey version yeah in the Mickey version
yeah yeah uh I I did not like the Nutcracker but I don't I did not appreciate it as a child
it didn't do so much for me as a child now obviously if I heard Rat King I wanted my
Ninja Turtles villain Rat King that's what I wanted yes so I was like who's this fucking
poser this isn't the Rat King sure the guy who lives under the sewer and terrorizes my friends
but obviously like in hindsight the music is is great is is great and I'm not really a good
assess I'm not good at assessing uh how good ballets are in general no ballets or opera
symphonies I can appreciate it as enjoyable but I I can't really track the like ah and that's
kind of a funny like that's uh you know that twinkling is a bit out of form like oh that
little look at that little comical twirl they did yeah I am chuckling to myself that's not the way
you'd normally twirl ha ha ha I mean this one uh jump to jump ahead a little this one is a little
funny because it's like oh the toy soldiers come out and they all start tap dancing well they they
popped I don't know what would I call it they modernized the Nutcracker and the music in a
lot of ways to certain levels of success I would say uh uh they did not just go with like traditional
arrangements of of the Nutcracker this was on the Videopolis stage it's about a half hour long it's
it's yeah 20 whatever it can air in a 30 minute block or whatever it's uh interesting it's an
interesting thing and it really feels like they went all out to promote it there's ads for it
there's I found merch I don't know if you found some merch there's oh I didn't see merch pins
there's an actual like little Mickey's Nutcracker thing here and some of it's hard to know because
because Mickey Nutcracker stuff is also just common I feel like around the holidays so it's
hard to tell if it's an actual tie-in to the Disneyland show or the special I believe there
was an animated short later on called Mickey's Nutcracker on one of the kind of the whole gang
seer Ludwig von Drake is as a short and then Mickey and then Goofy and Minnie and that's the
half hour yes um so I guess Mickey and Nutcracker have happened before and they will happen again
um but yeah so so your take before we even start talking about this did you like this
I did like this I was I felt a little silly early on because I was like who are all these original
human characters is the is the party going to be the full half hour and then they do Nutcracker
segments and then the humans get reused as like uh don't I know you it's like no I'm the mayor
of Candyland you know like right or Goofy and Pluto and Chip and Dale all show up in other roles
too right so because because the Nutcracker itself is like a child having a fantasy a dream
yes essentially where like a Nutcracker comes to life and then there's like a Rat King and bad guys
and this kind of transitions to dream like elements I mean I feel like Minnie never really
goes to sleep but a bunch of mystical creatures crash the after party basically yes yes um but
it basically yeah there's there's Minnie's having a party she has a bunch of strange human neighbors
and then she sees a Nutcracker that looks like Mickey and she's like this is a handsome
fucking Nutcracker yeah well it's gifted to her by the narrator yes um and she is she is sort of
blown away by his attractiveness um I guess yeah let's there is a narrator which I thought was
interesting because I feel like they wanted to fill in some gaps narratively especially for like
a theme park show where you'd have to be like all right and here's here's what's actually going on
and he's not totally in like an orb far away or whatever he pops into the show a few times
they're like hey mr narrator like yeah that's kind of fun as a kid I really liked when they
would break the fourth wall like that you know yes I also enjoyed fourth wall breaking um I
don't know I guess I play a clip of him just so you can get a vibe of the the narrator and
how this special works everyone and welcome to Mickey's Nutcracker our magical story begins here
once upon a time at Minnie's house on Christmas Eve Minnie was hosting an elegant ball and all
of her friends were there well that's Minnie in the beautiful blue gown hello she's with her dog
Pluto
and then there's more singing um so yeah you get the you get the gist of of how it goes um
the narrator yes he's very folksy and then here's what's interesting i also think they've sort of
retconned that pluto is minnie's dog that immediately had to pause it oh yeah wrote down
pluto is minnie's dog in this did you did that take you i kind of took me out of it as far as the
of the narrative well i figured it would be explained and then it dawned on me it was called
mickey's nutcracker and i'm like oh he doesn't live there he's the nutcracker right in this
well in this version mickey is doesn't exist no that's right mickey doesn't exist in this
universe minnie is the one who has pluto because pluto doesn't have an owner
yeah so really you're seeing a version this is in a sort of an else world story where
mickey is created with magic he's created from a wood is created with magic and i i thought of like
an old i was trying to think of it was more maywest or ethyl merman and will come into play
or uh like charles knows where i live like uh just like a woman she just wants to couple up
with their toys there is and then i that joke turned out to be very prescient uh yes yes there
this this guy has got is giving a big performance uh uh here and he's got a nice purple suit on
which i really like and it's interesting because i you don't see i don't know you don't see shows
like this again anymore as much like at the actual parks i feel like um no and especially
the human characters i was like oh are we gonna follow all these human characters and then of
course in its sense we do because they show up in sort of a wizard of odds setup yeah i mean you
see i mean okay i saw deadpool and wolverine's holiday show at disneyland a couple weeks ago
so they're doing little things like that but that's just a little backdrop and two performers
not a big wow stage show with a bunch of song and dance just some glib remarks and
yeah it's uh was it my favorite show i've ever seen it was not you know that was kind of a running
thread at this season as we're kind of uh re looking at christmas stuff yeah i was like will
you do that or we do jingle cruise or we do but then you've just been like knocking out of the
park finding these specials the thanksgiving special this special yes i've been knocking it
out of the park i agree um but yes so that was a yes there were other ideas there's always other
ideas for what we're episodes we're going to do there's plenty of other things i almost feel like
scott has sent me a file i think he kind of wanted to do this too um but we're still scott free so he
has sent me a file of something we will play a little bit later here oh that's nice i always
like when he does that he does yes he's he makes his presence felt he's here in spirit he's here
in spirits uh um but yes so so what i also like about this all the characters are dressed for a
party chip and dale have suits on with no pants chip and dale have like bow ties on and cummer
buns on but no pants and this just i don't know why this makes me happy i don't know why this was
the choice many years ago for cartoon characters i don't know yeah what cartoon character innovated
the formal wear but no pants i know there's so many examples of it so many i mean donald
yeah well when big bird dresses up he wears the little like dicky thing around his neck but he
doesn't want any pants he just wears the thing up on on the top and it really it looks to me it's
all it always just like looks kind of like if you were to put that on like a performer it would look
like a chip and dale's dancer or something did you see um there was an image going around the
internet of like i don't know if it's on streaming on 2b or if it's current crop of
looney toons collections on hbo max but they like they they doodled pants on porky pig
they doodled pants there's like photoshop pants oh right you're saying very odd looking you're
saying some uptight sensor drew pants on porky pig i guess so because they didn't want people
to be offended by seeing his like his smooth pig underside yeah he looked a little like the
la county fair mascot oh yeah that eva evan amy are we going to be able to think of the name of
the character no we're not are we not going to think of this character we're going to both
sit here and get frustrated not being able to think of the uh something bird the bird fulberg
what's his name thummer thummer oh i knew i had the th in there i had the th in there thummer yes
he does look like that so i don't know i think that is look you know what all these uh uh
conservatives complaining about cancel culture this i'll say this that's my line in the sand
you had porky pig with pants no way bullshit don't censor porky pig's butt or his smooth crotch
yeah i want to see it okay leave that alone if you're gonna put in like a flare let's see
that curly little tail so oh you're saying you're okay with the pants if you can see porky's curly
little tail poking out of a hole in the butt or like you had a like septum pier like i'm like
if porky pig had a septum piercing or a belly button ring i don't know if he was just trying
some stuff out an older age midlife crisis what can you get can you get a tail piercing if you're
a pig i mean i guess they probably tag pigs in real life but he could have like a tail piercing
or something have a tiny tail piercing of the red circles and it says that's all folks really small
okay like could he have like a big hoop earring on the back of his tail that would be kind of cool
sure or just on one of his ears so you're saying you would be comfortable with him wearing pants
as long as you could see his different piercings on his lower body no i'm not comfortable with the
pants at all i'm saying additive uh you want to see his naked lower half and you want to see where
he's pierced yeah okay i mean i can't argue with that i'm fine if they want to add piercings to
porky pig i'm comfortable with that but as far as the pants no that's where i draw the line i mean
nothing great not like a taint piercing or whatever or i wasn't gonna say taint piercing no you brought
it in well would you be offended if you got a tape taint piercing you know it's really not my
business i think i would be shocked initially but i'm like i guess live your life man you're
you're older now you know have some fun in your later years you're saying because he's an older
guy he's now experimenting with things maybe and that's okay you wouldn't judge him i mean he's not
like your kid or something where you're gonna say hey maybe you don't get your taint pierced
yeah yeah right but you're saying godspeed porky pierce that taint maybe start with a little stud
a little like harrison ford stud stud in his taint no it is here you said yes all right yeah is that
how you would get a taint piercing you would have a stud in your taint first and then you know we've
moved on from taint i was just saying no we have not moved on from taint i'm actually just asking
so i'm saying like but you you get a little tiny ear pierce that's how you when you pierce your ears
you start with a little thing you don't go with like that big hoop if you want to do that thing
where you get the big like kind of hole in your ear oh i don't work up to that i'm just saying
you gotta work up to that right so i would assume it would be the same with taint you would get a
little stud in your taint and then you would work up to a bigger item your bigger earring a taint
ring or whatever don't you think i guess so you wouldn't want to get some crazy taint ring no
that's that's advanced level yes because it would hurt you you would want to work up for sure yeah
yeah i think that's i know i'm staring at a picture of paul winchell in his dummy right now
that is not what i wanted to do uh oh are you staring at uh uh knucklehead or are you staring
at knucklehead smith yeah or jerry mahoney no i'm so well i was staring at jerry and paul
knucklehead is down you have to scroll down to get to knucklehead smith okay the other yeah uh no
okay i'm going back to mickey's nutcracker here i swear um yes so so let's go to let's like i
i when mickey shows up as a nutcracker they've they've made this little fun little mickey thing
and minnie brings him out and i guess i'll play well we've gotten all the character the humans
conrad is a lonely man he's a lonely uh man minnie's lonely friend conrad is what they say
yes and he's the one that goofy is consoling yeah basically and goofy's trying to get soul
and like tina just keeps taking any sweet she can yeah and etho seems like she's just like the party
yes and this dynamic i'm kind of like are they talking to tina like hey will you just
make out with conrad or just like just hold company like just hands he's gonna pass out
anyway you think they're gonna like etho did it last year you know it's do you think that they're
gonna try to talk one of the carrot of the female characters into just kissing yeah a pity kiss a
pity you mean just like a pack on the cheek you think a pack or like over the clothes stuff or
like you think goofy's gonna go oh gosh tina what'd you do over the clothes stuff with conrad
she's not gonna remember anyway you think bill farmer is gonna say that dialogue i don't know
the bill farmer well i don't think bill farmer is gonna say i'm not saying this this is dirty
stuff that's true goofy to say i'm just saying it would probably be like look this would be
less of a headache you know minnie is kind of focusing on herself right now we are we're a
little worried about conrad getting in cell vibes and it feels like a slippery slope so i don't know
i mean i think i mean goofy should just give him a hug or something goofy just give him a hug and
a kiss on the cheek and be like you're nice guy he could be just physically contact deprived
yeah right conrad here you go kiss if you focus on your interest and try stepping out of your
comfort zone volunteering or taking a cookie class you might meet someone conrad mentions that he's
very rich he talks about how much money he has but that says that does not apparently seem to help
him with his his romance yeah well then you got to worry it's like do they just like me for the
money are they just pretending goofy also seems like he's kind of like he feels bad for this guy
conrad now i don't know why they spend so much time flushing these human characters out because
no one gives a shit about them no offense no conrad and ethyl i their character gains come back
a little right but but we're all here we're here to hear the dance of the sugar plum fairies we're
here to see mickey come to life we're here to see mickey and minnie fall in love in this universe
yes and the humans are a lot more fun once they become like magical yes well sure i mean who isn't
going to become more fun when they're magical yeah honestly but you know they do so they do and
i mentioned this earlier they do like sort of number so i guess i don't know we could walk
through this more as it happens but yes they minnie is talking about mickey as the nutcracker and
he's just a little wooden doll and she's like oh this doll is so hot this doll is so attractive
thank you for coming merry christmas everyone according to the grandfather clock it was way
past minnie's bedtime but she was way too excited to sleep i'm much too excited to even think about
sleeping all i want to do is dance with my handsome nutcracker all night long so minnie has lost her
mind apparently at the end of this party all she wants to do is dance with the nutcracker
and again he's a wooden nutcracker he's not alive yet so what's going on with minnie
look he's he's handsome and he can't talk back it's an ideal situation are you doing are you
channeling the ghost of pauline tonight with with your retorts with your i think okay good he said
it changes i've forged in life so minnie is dancing with her little wooden boy
all night long as the clock strikes midnight and then struck 12 midnight something wonderfully
strange and magical happened
like stuff is like hatless the stage is kind of coming up it's like move
everything is moving up yeah uh and yeah minnie's like oh my god my house is coming apart
what the fuck is going on two bolts of purple lightning strike the nutcracker
scary kind of bolts like it almost like power rangers style boats bolts of electricity
shoot into this nutcracker and bring him to life minnie is not afraid at all she just goes
holy shit there's a hunk in my living room it's christmas time fucking as deadpool would say
let's let's fucking go yeah she's just totally on board right away um and mickey is wearing
uh a fun nutcracker outfit um blue red i don't know why i mean it's you know it's nutcracker
shit it looks like this and he kind of does a little nutcracker march as he walks into the
room um i i can't believe it why this is strange and magical you're alive you bet
why every christmas eve me and my friends come to life your friends you mean there's somebody with
uh-huh
mickey salutes uh as if his superior officer has just shown up and he explains that at midnight
he and his friends come to life every christmas and then a bunch of female toy soldiers come out
of a big present yeah and minnie is just happy she's happy to see these toy soldier ladies
i mean wouldn't fire minnie i feel like i'd want the nutcracker at all to myself bunch of show girls
just showed up this is what i'm getting at there's a bunch of show girls just entered the room and
you'd be like okay is mickey really that interested in me or does he want to have some sort of weird
party what is this all about yeah what is this guy but no she's she's sort of on board and she
she thinks it's fun and at this point like this is a point let me guess what scott would say scott
would say i don't necessarily like human beings being toy soldiers i just have a guess because
to me it feels adjacent to raggedy and raggedy andy it sort of feels in the same genre of like
painted face maybe big circles on the cheeks yeah there's obviously like it's just doll humans being
dolls or being toys and now they're big and i i don't totally disagree with him about that i
think he has more of a revulsion to that than i do but i'm i don't disagree what is your take on
when adults dress as like toys or dolls um i think i'm okay with it i grew up with some
toy soldier ornaments and some raggedy and andy but those are regular that's what they're supposed
to look like i'm saying a human being full-sized raggedy and raggedy i i often i don't know that
it lends itself to full-sized actor portraying so you're kind of agreeing on some level yeah i think
like fur quote unquote fur costume raggedy and andy a little more acceptable they look doll-like
so you're saying as long as not a human face you're more comfortable with it face
you know limber human body is that the term for what not you don't have a human face on
the costume a fur costume well i've always heard face character that's like walk around peter
peter panham fur character fur oh that's interesting i you know what i real quick real
quick tangent uh there's something called the doodah parade that happens in pasadena
yeah which you know you're familiar with this yeah it happens in ocean city new jersey too
oh it's a sister those are the two doodah so you do know about the do i do know and you gotta look
at the grand marshals of the ocean city one this year was just a guy from the fly who used to play
for the flyers i saw the doodah parade this year in pasadena for the first time ever and i was
very interested there were people there that were trying to make like serious political statements
there were there were furries marching it was a real interesting assortment of characters
but all the furry costumes were really nice they just like the furries had really good costumes
there are some very impressive fursuits out there for sure right and i just wonder yeah because like
fursona like i wonder i hear fur more now in in the in the furry like used with furries but when
you say face and fur characters i wonder when that started i wonder when that term started i don't
know i'm not sure but it sounds like you're sort of on the same page with us about like kind of
being it's off-putting to see like dull come-to-life people on stage for the nutcracker yeah i think if
they're standing far away in a parade float waving yeah i'm a little more okay with that
as long as you don't see the horror the facial horror i don't know if i want to see them doing
dialogue i don't know if i wouldn't see the one sitting at a kitchen table going
where were you you wait wait you weren't supposed to be up this late you wait you don't want to see
like raggedy ann being mad at you for staying out too late with the fellas i don't want to see cat on
the hot tin roof playing gary glenn ross raggedy so she's got like one arm in the air one arm down
and her eyes are like this and she's like jason where were you i waited up all night i'm worried
no one told you to do that who were you out with i was out with co-workers were you out with a sexy
nutcracker woman where do you get this stuff i just know that you work with that adult-sized
nutcracker at work and maybe you are out at the out having a drink with her there were other people
there jason you're drunk i would sing a song that raggedy ann and raggedy ann sang but i don't know
anything about them past uh what i've said on this show there were some i feel like there were
some cheapy world of deke grinded out cartoons oh there were plenty yeah yeah for sure so we'll get
into that too but i feel like i know more about paul winchell and jerry mahoney and knucklehead
smith than i do raggedy ann and raggedy ann let me play a clip from this song not that it's
anything that special but i'm just trying to give you a flavor of what this is what these songs are
like
so they've taken a classic song and they've desecrated it with some
bullshit they've jazzed up like they've jazzed it up they've added lyrics and i will say i think
it sucks i think i don't like i don't know i need the lyrics but i like a little jazzy i like a
little tap i was gonna say i don't think you can ever say you don't like something if there's a
little tap involved if there's some tap tap tapping with tap shoes i think you're gonna find something
to like about it i'm not anti-tap i just feel like i like the original versions of these songs a lot
and i feel like it wasn't necessarily a good idea to add lyrics and a tap routine in it but i don't
i understand they're trying to do something different with it i guess they do it in some
of the others but that's the most noticeable i feel like you mean other versions of nutcracker
in this show oh yes no they do they do yeah okay oh yeah there's other like modern quote-unquote
versions of tchaikovsky songs got what's his full name peter uh uh uh ilyich tchaikovsky i just
want to say his full name because it's fun to say i've got some background for you on the ocean
city dude oh go go for it please a build is a salute to humor and comedy thank you yeah
featuring impersonators of groucho marx charlie chaplin maryland mumrow of his presley abbott
and costello celebrity comedians and tv stars have served of grand marshals including uh jone
rivers yes joe franklin larry storch mickey rooney soupy sales were we talking about this
in relation to mickey rooney or was it a different parade that he was a grand marshal of that's when
we were talking about you being a grand marshal in a parade yeah yeah i don't know if it was a
doodop parade but it was another i mean mickey rooney being grand marshal maybe there was a
was it a super bowl halftime show i think so yeah i bet but how many times has mickey rooney been
a grand marshal in a parade i bet the answer is over 50 i think he's been the grand marshal
at the doodop parade multiple times i wouldn't be shocked um but yeah so there's as i said there
modern versions of things which i it's just a little too schmaltzy for me it's adding like
extra broadway crap on top of like uh great music great christmas music but i get that like some of
those songs are a little bit downbeat they're a little melancholy so you want to jazz them up
you want to do a little fun a fun thing um but let's get to uh uh the rats let's get to
the rats because there are many human zoobily zoo style rat characters in this yeah they're mouthy
they're got a bad attitude
oh yes this is my favorite part of the story these are the evil but not very bright hensch rats
what's happening look out here comes trouble
so you got the heavy metal version now of that song and up through the floor comes human
rat man and there with his rat henchmen also are coming up he looks like in some ways king
koopa from king koopa's cool cartoons which we talked about a year ago or something he's very
much in that like 80s 90s vibe of what it looks like when a human dresses up as an anthropomorphic
yeah animal uh but yeah i said zoobily zoo already which is what it makes me think of
which was a weird show i watched on pbs um but he comes up and he yes as you said he is mouthy
and he's a real wiseacre i would say he is a real uh wiseacre but they also in so many words warn
he is dumb as shit this is the evil rat king nice to meet you a long time ago a terrible
curse was placed on a handsome prince which turned him into the creature you see before you
now it says here that the only thing that can remove the curse is the very thing that
rat kings hate the most sugar hey what was that about sugar i was uh telling them how much you
don't like sugar that's right i don't like sugar he really does have like i guess he does have like
a rizzo the rat style voice which i find interesting rizzo the rat kind of buzz buzz
but meanie a little uh-huh but what is the first rat like when you this is the kind of voice yeah
you're here but when it was just the first vote like who did the first rat that sounded like that
was he just i always think of it as like the bad guy greasers heavy who's wearing 3d glasses all
the time well yeah and that's the back to the future yeah there's been plenty of characters
that have the voice that weren't rats i just wonder was there a specific rat maybe that was
given yeah i'm giving this voice i got this voice yeah i don't know i don't know the answer to it
but this i don't either this rat has the same sort of rizzo style obviously rizzo is a nice character
or he's a little you know he's a little shady but he's not a terrible guy or anything now i
i think i was chasing the dog around trying to get in calm down as this was playing but i
totally forgot i got really into the musical numbers and the classic music as he explained
okay he was a prince turned into a rat he doesn't like sugar because sugar can undo the like that's
a lot of backstory yes it is a lot of backstory especially for a theme park show i mean i guess
it's just like ah stay away from sugar like i guess that's really you just want the kids in the front
row to know oh this this character doesn't like sugar this will defeat but rats will eat anything
if you're gonna dissect the logic i agree like why would sugar be sugar should be like something
that he feeds he loves sugar yeah so it is weird i mean i guess they're saying like
sugar plum fairies i suppose they're trying to make those characters like the antithesis
of this i think so i suppose so this is almost like a version of like a usually when you would
see something as a kid at least us you would see like oh yeah like vegetables would defeat
the rats because vegetables are good and sugar is bad yeah it would be some sort of psa style
thing but that's not what's going on that the corn syrup lobby will make sure that it's not
portrayed as a bad guy well that's right let's we'll see what happens with corn syrup going
forward and then a future administration i'm not sure i'm skeptical but i'm not sure either
i've also been reading the nutrition it's talking about like doesn't really make a different like
refined sugar is bad my doctors are big on fruit like if you're making fruit smoothie
real fruit or frozen fruit they're like it's better than refined how is the fruit because
you've talked about this a couple times recently on the show how is your fruit smoothies go how
are they going they're going great you know almond milk what do you got what do you give me the
ingredients almond milk uh scoop of peanut butter yeah sure what kind of peanut butter
are we doing natural peanut butter are we doing i usually like skipping natural okay okay so
um uh i don't really like when the oil separates uh blueberries go to antioxidants frozen blueberries
use frozen fruits and vegetables cuts down on how much ice you need to put in well that's right
frozen spinach fresh or frozen kale yeah and like i just finished one uh right here it sounds like
you're on the right track i think so yeah the almond milk's unsweetened maybe a hint of vanilla
but no sugar okay and then so you're not leaving out that you put a box of sprees in there are you
i'm not no all right good i'm debating doing a protein powder but i don't i gotta find the right
like organic one with not a lot of sugar not a lot of fakie stuff yeah are you gonna put any
andrina chrome or anything in there or well no i usually take that at night before bed okay
okay ketamine or anything i know that's administered by the professionals
by the junkyard all right fine fair enough uh okay let me play a little more of this uh rat
segment what was that about sugar i was uh telling them how much you don't like sugar that's right
i don't like sugar i don't like children i don't like christmas and i don't like you
so you heard you heard maybe a beat almost kick in there yeah and this is where we get to probably
the highlight of the whole show rapping king rat rapping king rat yeah would you agree with that
this is this is the thing that you would want clipped and posted on whatever social media
instagram
And spice and everything nice so what do you what do you think immediately when you hear that like what is what comes to mind?
For you. I have my answer, but you did something feel right like what are damn beastie boys
Yeah, okay. Yeah, the beastie, but I mean right like maybe the king rat is like add rock or something
He's got a little more voice like this. Yeah. Yes. They're doing
Beastie boys, I'm guessing 1991 or whatever that came out 92 and beastie boys have been out for a while, but this is all sputique
90s is it the 80s? Yeah, I used to be a big pulse boutique. I mean, it's still really like I say what happened
well in college, I just got a hold of it and I was like, well, this is really good and I
It really like that instrumental album. They did it
89 is Paul's boutique or boutique. Some people say boutique when they're talking about the word boutique
Recorded not too far away, right and that water. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I forget what corner it is and what like drugstore or restaurant is there? I don't remember sure but it was yeah right there
So yeah, they have Beastie Boy rats
Basically in this show which I can't deny that. I don't like it. I don't know that it's the highest quality
I don't know that they can go toe-to-toe
with
MCA and rock and Mike D
I don't think so
But I appreciate the effort and I appreciate that they all are taking turns just like the Beastie Boys would
So so you gotta like yeah, I do like that that feels current and it feels we've talked about Disney
It is a little more current then usually Disney would go for it was pretty current and it is certainly not the worst
Like I'm rapping ready and I'm here to say, you know
Yeah, I mean the verse the last verse that he dropped it was the closest to being something good
But it is still pretty much like some old folks and the Disney company were like well, I can write a rap
I know that a rat's true. Yeah, so this gets me to the point where
Scott has sent something in and he told me to play this after
After the rap specifically, this is why I think he was like
Oh, I think he would have he would have liked to be here for the discussion of the rap
So I have it here and I'm gonna play it. Hey everybody just wanted to weigh in really quick
I was actually available to do this episode about Mickey's Nutcracker, but I
Elected not to come I elected not to participate and if you're wondering why well, it's because I
Don't like it
I
Wow, that's great so fiendish Wow, yeah, really do you think it took more time to record that let's
Do an episode with us?
No, because Scott can produce it something like that in I feel like he can do that while sleeping
Yeah, he's I mean, I know he could do it fatten and somewhat but could he do it in an hour?
Put that together in an hour easy. I think we could have done this. Maybe he did it at night though
Convenience schedule. I did it at a weird hour where the baby was awake. So he's like, I'm awake
I may as well distract myself, but that was great
That was very good. Yes, and he got I wonder where he got the did he sample this actually?
Did he did he already have a sample of Mickey's Nutcracker Rat King rap already on his computer?
Cuz I wouldn't put it past them to have that where he just had the sample from the music. Yes
But maybe not maybe he just he did a keyboard and they made I'd have to listen to the track again to figure out
If it was a sample of that one
instrumental from 99 problems
I don't think so. It sounded like the music from rap
Okay, yeah, but it is a kind of a comment does have that guitar
Which is similar does 99 problems sample from rat rap it could it's possible that that's where they got that
Jay-z got the best time for 99 problems right now. I'll tell you that it certainly is not he's got a hundred
I've seen you know what? I've seen a few people make that joke on social media. Oh
I'm so I thought you were making a joke because it was obvious. I well it was obvious
But I thought you thought your first one to mark it on it on that joke. I'm sorry to say
I'm so well, that's a whole nother. I don't know anything about that
So yeah, this is very shredder
Coming out of our shells very much turtles, of course around the same time
And shredder is I mean similar voice, let me see can I play a little bit more
This will become a horrible time of year from this visitation this mass migration this
Population this congregation this infestation of rats
So now the rats are terrorizing all the like Rockette Nutcracker ladies
Yeah, running around and then the metal like do you know me only you know is playing at that point now if I was a kid
In 1991 I'd be shitting in my pants in the audience. I would be so afraid of what's going on now
100% and it builds up to
Mickey whacking people with a mini whack people with like a
Ladle and I'm like, oh my god, please do it. Please take them all out
So you were terrifying me rooting for for muting for violence. Yeah. Yeah with her ladle
Which I guess is kind of a guess if it's a metal laid at ladle would be something that would be she would whack him
But she didn't go far enough. She didn't push in the bag that like George HW Bush
She didn't finish the job. I came back. So you're using the one that's ten years later
It was topical to the time. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's true. Yeah. Oh, you didn't mean to that
Just I didn't mean to you know making a
Commentary about the original George Bush and what he's yeah done. Just a little capital steps flavor
You know, yeah, one of your casual capital steps sort of references at the time
I I guess I was really giving you credit, but you just that's just the thing you say
Sure, the thing you say about George HW Bush
Yeah, I would this is a thing like with same with shredder where I would have been like, oh my god
We're all gonna get killed by these rats. These rat people will kill us
So
What happened there and you already said many many has her ladle as a weapon, but the rat king is about to impale Mickey
Yeah, he is a real big spike with a big railroad spike
he's about to
Should plunge a railroad spike through mickey's head the question does he carry that around or did many just have some conveniently close by
I don't know
I don't know if that's supposed to be something that like blew up big cuz it looks like it could be like a nail
or an icicle
Yeah, maybe a big icicle. Yeah, I don't know but this is a pretty violent thing to have in a Disneyland show
Sure where Mickey is about to get killed. I mean like you could pretend like all his hands
Shoot like his like little rays or something right? Yeah, but it hangs for a while
Yes, he hangs he's really threatening him with it
And again, I would be shitting in my pants cuz I'm like I'm about to watch Mickey his brains get shot all over the stage
After this railroad spike the super super big railroad spike goes through Mickey's little head
you know eventually I got precocious enough when I would look at the map and
Scheduled cuz you know, I was all over that map when I was I was Disneyland map. Yeah, Disney World
Any park I wanted to know the showtimes, right? I want to know everything. I mean like, okay, I guess this works out
There's five more shows today
Hmm. No, so you found where you talking about you actually looked at a map with this
No, no, I'm saying as a kid. I'd be like I'm scared right now, but this must be resolved
Because they have to do this again in an hour so you would put that logic to it like okay
Cuz you thought that would calm myself down from worry about Mickey
That's smart being murdered cuz I didn't put two and two together when I saw the Ninja Turtles on tour that like they got
Tour dates for another 30 days. I didn't know anything about that that it could have just come to a head
Well, I guess that's true
But the logic is but the but you were saying that made you feel like okay
This rat didn't go rogue in this one show and he's about to yeah, but to murder my hero and that's right for real
Okay, that's smart. I wish I had thought of something like that and been like they're not gonna shredders
Not gonna end this turtle world tour right now. They got other they got money to make. Yeah, this isn't real
So yeah at that point, I mean that's
Really the highlight but then there's a section where
Mickey and Minnie are on a like Santa's sleigh with Pluto
Yes pulling it as if it was the rain and there is an unnamed driver
There's a nameless driver with a steering wheel
Wearing nearly stage black like stage group blacks. So he right and they don't really acknowledge that he's there
No, they don't want yeah, they don't want you know, I mean, he's he's not wearing like a full suit like face covering or anything
He's got a top. No, it's kind of like a chauffeur's
Partial chauffeur's outfit. Do you think so? Do you think in the in the narrative of the show?
That he's not supposed to be there
No, I think he's supposed to be there. But I think like
It might be a subservient like that. Like he's not supposed to speak unless you're saying this
You're saying this like Minnie's butler
Yeah, and she treats I think it's Mickey's butler, but Mickey just came to life. Why would he have a butler?
He's got a magical sleigh
with a
Dog that looks suspiciously
Suspiciously like Pluto. So you think Mickey has a butler but he doesn't let the butler talk or make eye contact with him
I think he's just very strict as an employer
He's Mickey like a Steve Harvey like
Don't make eye contact with me. Is Steve Harvey like that? That's what there was a memo leaked
You got a wrap go yeah
Around the diet coke before he handed to them. They don't want their hands wet or cold
I mean, there's a lot of celebrities that that's happening, you know, don't look them in the eye
Here's what I'll say as long as family feud is that funny?
Don't look him in the eye respect Steve Harvey. That's what I say
Yeah, you know what I'm saying and Mickey I guess Mickey as well if he's like look you work for me
We don't have a personal relationship. I don't know your name. I don't know your kid's name
You know what? I don't give a fuck about it. I'm paying you you respect my wishes. Don't worry about it
You might think I'm intense
But there are hundreds of people counting on me and if I think about that pressure, I'll crack so I had to put up walls
I don't have time to write an autograph for you an autograph for your fucking nephew
I don't want to hear it. Okay to me. Your name is driver
Okay, I'm calling you driver and that's it you dress in black you wear a black top hat
I don't care if you're smiling and you're laughing
Stay straight ahead. I know I'm I turned to a New York guy all of a sudden and if I snap three times
Start killing rats and don't ask questions. I'm gonna give you a pistol
I want you to keep it in your holster by your ankle and I'm gonna keep talking New York like this for some reason
This is low caliber. It's a low caliber. You're not gonna kill me. So don't even think about it. I'm wearing a vest
Okay, I'm wearing a bulletproof vest
I got a vest take a shot of me right now. I'll prove it to you. You can't kill me. You're gonna carry a 22
I'm gonna carry a 45. So if you get any ideas, you're getting a whole
Okay, I can out draw you let's do a door right now you don't think you don't think I can out draw you
I've been shooting guns at cartoons for 60 years. I got a musket. I got a pistol. I hunted ghosts
What have you done with your life ever? What have you done? Nothing? He's old-fashioned. He's been around a long time
That's what the old fat. Yeah, he hasn't shaken some of those values the old-school guys
Yeah, I would do that with their assistance and Mickey has been around for a long time a hundred years. Okay, so let's get to this part
Are you ready?
And so with the reindeer leading the way many of the nutcracker began their long journey to Candyland
So this part's kind of just like that that's the real music that's the
Moment the rat king and the rat king number. There's a little flourish. That's like one of the big other songs
Yes, so at this point, they're going to the Candyland. They're going to Candyland. They do a little nose kiss at some point
But to say they do a little nose candy
They do do a nose
Snowflakes, what do you think those snowflakes are made of? I used to do this with a card Walker in the 70s
You know what it was like it was go go. Well, I guess the 80s too
Walt left a notepad that said Kurt Russell didn't explain that was code that Kurt Russell
Has my coke
Okay, so he died and then Kurt Russell
Just everyone went to eat took over. He has the coke now. He's got the coke now
So so I forgot like Candyland
Obviously the concept of Candyland has been around for a long time
But to me Candyland just is the board game, of course
Yeah, but Candyland is here and there's many candy lands in the history of entertainment
Oh boy might have to dive down the wormhole of the candyland of all the candy lands, you know
Yeah, cuz like I think as a kid it most kids are obsessed with candy lands
But they get to Candyland and I mean you what do you think in there goofy is?
Well, hold on
Snowflake see no, you're right. You're right, right
And this is where the the kind of I'm assuming that they named the character Ethel
You know not to like an Ethel Merman like a big personality showman. Hmm show woman tight
I guess so and she floats down on like a big candy bench a
big
Snowflake that's got a bench on it
Nowadays if you did that you'd be strapped into that thing six ways to Sunday
Let's go and fine. Okay. Yeah, so so so they may get to Candyland. They make it to Candyland and
Do you want to play anything like music wise or you want to go to goof?
I I you know, I get goofy excited. I get excited when I see goofy because goofy is my all-time favorite
Disney character. Yeah. Well, I
Can you do if goofy's intro mine? Yes. It is just very funny. Yes to hear
Nutcracker welcome home
Gores, who's the beautiful mouse maiden? She sure is birdie
This is Minnie why she saved me from the evil rap king
Well, don't see how I've been the mayor of Candyland my whole life
Gores, I'm at the citizens here would just love to meet many
Come on in join her Christmas
Celebration
So at this point they reveal on the set that they're in candy like it's a full Candyland sets
And people rush in with flags. It's a big reveal that they're in. It's great. There's a lot of candy buildings
Goofy has revealed himself as the mayor of Candyland is the mayor of Candyland. Yeah, which is fun
He's wearing like kind of a pink suit
And fun pants. He's got like kind of yellow and pink swirl pants
He's got a green hat and he's got a staff that looks like it could potentially be like one of those long suckers
like one of those kind of
Like I was gonna say phallic. I don't is there like they're a little phallic some of those long
Oh, I was gonna say is it like a peppermint stick a little it's probably a peppermint stick. It's probably not a phallic
sucker I
Mean, it was certainly like commenting on Minnie was very purdy
Are you saying he's a little horned up and maybe he's yeah, maybe well that sugar as I'm horned up
Is that something that happens to you sometimes when you get too much sugar not really yeah
But maybe the rat king doesn't like being that one. Maybe the sugar makes everyone too. Oh, yeah, too happy and horny
The rat king hates being happy and horny. That is yeah sure
So goofy is a mayor of Candyland. Do you would you rather be the mayor of Disneyland or the mayor of Candyland?
What do you think tough decision let's say it's the Candyland from the board game with Queen Frostine and grandma nut
You know all the all the loopy and gloopy. Is that his name? I thought that was
gloopy or gloppy I
Disneyland easy if it's oh, you're still saying Disneyland. There's too many personalities. There's too many
I kind of think I would rather be mayor of Candyland
Can you handle that? Can I handle it? I think I can I
Think it's just a lot that it's because there's quit. There's a queen
I mean obviously there's there's a monarchy going on in Candyland because there's Queen Frostine and and Lord licorice
so there's some sort of monarchy system happening in Candyland and mayor would would
Suggest that it's not like he's got some other position there
Well, his could be ceremonial or hers theirs could be ceremonial, right?
They could be more it's like an England thing where it's like
Prime minister has a real power but the Queen has to oversee a lot
Yeah, I like to think that Candyland has gotten more progressive over the years as far as its government
I would hope so, but that they still like the tradition of having a
Lord a lord and lady and a queen and I think it's just too many
Like cultures clash. I think it's like the 50 states. Yeah, it's like every state has its own identity
Its own politics its own graft and corruption, you know
Well, I could be I would also be okay being like Lord licorice
Like I could be a lord
We you would prefer the ceremonial. I think so. Yeah, I know. Okay mayor seems just like whatever
Were you a Downton Abbey guy? Have you watched much out? We did watch a lot of down. I haven't seen the last
Season or the there's two movies at this point. I'm a little bit
See like four seasons of Downton Abbey, that's about where I after the big death I kind of checked out
Well, there's a couple deaths or a couple like disappear. They're driving one. They're driving. We did we hung in for another season or two
Yeah, I went to spoiler alert when Dan Stevens dies. Yeah when Dan Stevens died, it wasn't anything specific
I just I think it took a little while to get the season after that on. Yeah, and I just kind of checked out
Hmm. Well, I want to be a lord
I want to be Lord licorice, but it sounds like you would still rather be mayor of Disneyland. I think so
Okay, this candy land looks pretty fun. Everything is made of candy
Everyone's seat seems harmonious. Everyone seems on the same page. There's kind of a candy utopia happening
Basically Chip and Dale introduce themselves. It's the candy masters
What does that mean to you when Chip and Dale who are wearing now again no pants
They're they have like a little like taffy striper kind of hats. What would you consider a more like Candyman style hats?
Yeah, like they make the candy
Yeah, or do they just know all the recipe like I watched I watched a video recently of a guy at an old candy store
He's like we've making these fresh candy canes same way
Hundred plus years hundred years. This is from the 30s. It's from the 50s same granite slab the whole time. I've watched
Probably the same video you're talking about watching a man make candy canes on the hundred-year-old slab of granite
And I grew up around a lot of the South Jersey a lot of those candy stores
Are well over a hundred years now, so would you go would you flock to see the candy the local candy caner?
We took some tours
We took some tours. How many how many tours you think in your life?
I think I got a little of Shriver's the big one in Ocean City
There was another one on Asbury Avenue kind of the main drag and Thursdays
Were family nights of the war walk and activities for kids
During the day downtown, so there'd be entertainers jugglers clowns and gazebos
The kid the one candy stores did tours. Yeah, there'd be like decorative gazebos
Oh, but they would just be temporary or would they just decorate a gazebo that was already there
No, it's just kind of a little entertainment kids that on the ground and
It's just interesting
Gazebos was presented as a like interesting thing as a good thing
Gazebos was presented as a like interesting thing as a
Now there's some photo. I they have a lifeguard boat
Santa takes a photo in the lifeguard rowboat downtown every year
So you would go see people make we would go and you would get free samples and be like this side with this in line
We make it and then here's a little paint. We place them in the papers and put them in the box
It seems like hard work making candy canes seems like a big pain in the ass candy game seems very hard
I think chocolates might actually be easier unless you're lucy and ethyl
Of course that was out of control. They were packaging chocolates
Yeah, they were sure they were putting them in a little like paper thing and putting them in the box
I had to tell you I knew
The son of the guy who owned you company
Called o'brien's irish potatoes. Hold on you got so excited. I haven't seen your face light up on this whole time
I've been talking to you other than just telling this story just now repeat that again for me
Okay, uh, it's a company that I knew a lot growing up because come st. Paddy's day
Yeah, these were everywhere outside of build up irish potatoes. No, it's a candy. It's like a fondant kind of
You speak in my language is fondant. Well, it's kind of like, um
A gooey candy filled with coconut and then it's rolled in sugar. So it looks like a little potato
Irish coconut. It's no, it's called an irish potato potato. Sorry, and so
I had no idea for years. This guy knew he's
A family owned the factory they owned the place and my friend erin was like one of his best friends
And she would work there around christmas time or the irish potato factory. Yeah, and I
Every year try to get in there. I'm like work. Yeah, I want to work at the irish potato factory
From what ages were you trying to get into the irish potato factory like
16 to 19
Really? I was like we're home for a month from school
Let me in there. Let me get because you imagine like some of these like one for them one for me
Like you would take one and eat one. I am sure there were some misshapens that you were coming home with
Oh my god, so wait and but you didn't find out that you had a direct connection to the irish potato factory
Well, I didn't really know him until like high school chemistry
But I was eating these irish potatoes for years and years and years. I had no idea. It was local local
You were like starstruck when you realized that this kid was
Absolutely was irish potato royalty and uh, erin's review was like I don't really like this job
And I'm really do with the job packing
Because you would do the lucy job of packing she would do it and she's like andy there are so many
Magnets and tin signs of lucy and eff and that fuck because I immediately she said
Oh, I got a job working irish potato factor for the you know, new year
It starts to really amp up production and I was like
I told her at like 18 19 like lucy and ethyl and she's like, I don't
When every year about clever i'd always been clever. She's like i'm just so fucking sick of your about lucy and ethyl
Because obviously, of course the older folks who work there
immediately were like
That's got to be the case with any company that has by hand
Candy packaging that they have a picture of lucy nether from the i love lucy show like
If we went to this there's a seize candy outlet in the burbank mall
Yes, so long time candy company. I really haven't had that it may have very many times
Um
But I bet if we went there and talked to the employees and I went
Do people talk about lucy and ethyl in the candy line a lot? They would be like
But is it yeah, you think there's a candy line in the back of the burbank seize candy
They're packing some stuff fresh. Oh, you do think I think there's some fresh
I don't think there's a lot but some of those calendars look pretty
In that small store. I don't I don't think it's a conveyor belt like there. I don't think it's a huge assembly line
But I think so. I don't think that's all driven in from a distributor. I feel like we've been recording for three hours. So
That so your friend you knew that worked in the irish potato factory
You would say I want a job and what does she say? I'm not are they hiring she's like
No, we have enough. I'm the seasonal hire like so she was keeping the job from you
basically
So they wouldn't hire more than one seasonal employee. That seems ridiculous. I don't think so, you know
We were probably too far out from the start of the rush season because I feel like college semesters
You start back up like mid-january 12 13th or something. So
Later, yeah time wasn't right
Wow, so so
This and you moved here shortly after
After college lived at home for a few months then moved out here, but did you ever try to get another candy factory job?
No
It's in my blood one
Grandpa Sheridan, I should have continued the family business and he had a candy factory
Well, no, he worked the um
He was like he ran the line
For which company we talked about this. I know we have I forgot a lot lately
I said, I don't know anything about you, but I have been forgetting whitman's was around phil and he worked the line
Uh, he ran the line. He tried to get poached. He almost got poached by hershey
and my
Uh graham graham was like i'm not moving to hershey pennsylvania
Wow, so she put a stop to it
Yeah, graham graham did graham graham did what was his name was his name grandpa grandpa grandpa
I feel like what was the other side's name? We just talked about mom mom and pop pop mom mom and pop mom and pop pop
Graham graham graham graham and graham pop
Pop or pa I feel like was interchangeable grandpa. I love grandpa
I had such a boring name grandma grandpa
I know you'd say maybe their first names if it was like the side of the family you didn't see as much
He would talk my dad. Oh, let's tell the story and I saw it once
They moved down to south jersey when they retired
And they moved in a little residential neighborhood that was next to a golf course
So we would go visit them walk around the neighborhood pick up straight golf balls, but he would go out for a walk every day
and he had this
homemade sap
Basically, he had like a chunk of metal wrapped in electrical tape. Oh sap like a like a old school police weapon
Yeah, and he would carry this with him when he would go for his walk and we're like
You were living on a quiet street next to a golf course
You don't need protection
So he was paranoid. He's a paranoid guy
Yeah, I mean they grew up they lived in the northeast of philadelphia for a long time and
I could care less about mickey's nutcracker right now. I don't give a fuck about mickey's nutcracker. I don't want to hear more about
grandpop
And the whitman's factory and the different candy factories you grew up around
That's really that's where my interests lie. I like mickey and minnie. I love goofy
I love all of it
But I want to hear more about this
Did he retire at the whitman's?
I think he retired from whitman's so he got like his pension or something from whitman's. I believe so
and they they always joke that like
they
They probably owed back like the money isn't in the walls and I never found that
Do you think they weren't using they weren't paying that was the urban legend around the family?
This is the side of the family his father ran a speakeasy for mayor nucky on the atlantic city borough
Mayor nucky played by steve buscemi and borough walk empire, right? Right, right
Um, so so so they never found a bunch of like cash in grandpop's walls
No, but that was always a joke, right? But so but you with some family member would have found it
Would have found it when they cleared out. Yeah
Yes, so so
You knew grandpop a little bit. I knew grandpop. Yeah growing up
So yeah, you're all both grandparents instead of grandparents were in life. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Everyone loved my pop-up
Yeah
And he was
I never knew him like as a mean drunk
I knew him when he ran the fan, uh, the city's a a print the town's a a program
Oh, so so a lot of people in the family knew him before that happened and he he had so many sponsors
He was sponsored for so many people
So many people came to his eat we had they had to have a night viewing
And the morning viewing before the funeral because there was just so many people he had touched their lives from a.a and stuff
Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's nice
Um, and so when you were a kid were you were you like was he like ah the whitman factory like was it candyman?
Like or willy wonka style when you were a kid you're like, oh my god
not really there was just always whitmans at christmas and stuff and
I think they're
one one of my aunts for uh christmas one year got like
Every household a giant whitman sampler box, right?
But you didn't imagine like grandpop driving like a big gumdrop to work or something
I didn't know because I didn't know he he did for a long time
I knew my pop-up for a while. It was like the security guard at a pencil factory
but I
There used to be a lot more factories
What pencil I don't know
I don't know if it was you gotta find out I gotta find out I gotta find out the name philadelphia
You just have a ton of factories. I mean tasty cakes. I think still is a big
Uh factory maybe down by the navy yard, but I don't know if like the battleships
It's been decommissioned. Was it like your grandfather's almost in the cia where you like find out later like he's a whitman's man
He didn't like to talk about it. He was in vietnam
I just didn't know I don't think I just thought like oh a child a kid won't be interested in all these and I'm like
I am more than interested. I will say I don't know if i've said this before on the show. I'm my grandfather
Uh one of my grandfather's, uh owned a bookstore
Yes called bookman's alley, which was a pretty cool spot
Uh that was in chicago
Uh, and he my grandfather is in the movie finding vivian meyer
Which is a movie about a woman who was a nanny in the suburbs and she also was a photographer
But they didn't find out that she was like a cool like a cool a good photographer until
Uh, these guys bought a bunch of photos at an estate sale
Um, and my grandfather was a little like enigmatic and just one day
It was like, oh they interviewed me for this movie and it was because vivian would come into the bookstore
But if you were around, I mean the store was there for decades at this point
Um, but to show you how dumb of a little boy I was I was like, yeah grandpa's got a bookstore
Yeah
We go there for a couple holidays and the thing I was most excited about
Was that he would have a big or not even that big of a dish. He would have a dish of gumdrops
Yeah, oh, yeah brother and I would go in there and it was an old
It was like a really old building and it was kind of falling apart in a fun way
And I would get very excited because I would go and get some gumdrops
And I was not so excited
I'd be like looking at the books like oh, yeah
All these old books all these old editions and all these like nooks and crannies in the store
But these gumdrops
And then my mom would be like these gumdrops have been sitting here for months
That didn't stop me because my mama had a candy dish very similar
By the way finding vivian meyer just watch points you at
Amc plus is where you can currently see that. Thank you. Yes
um, and uh rent on your normal
uh
apple tv
Um where else paramount google plus apple tv. My grandfather is in free on plex
Oh, yeah, my grandfather is in this movie. Is he gonna use bookstore documentary to or like a bookstore documentary?
That's a good question, but he is so
Honest to god, he might be and I don't remember or don't know because he wouldn't say he wouldn't talk about a lot of things
Uh, so so but that's how dumb a little kid is
I was but I think if I had a grandfather that worked in a candy factory in a gumdrop factory
I would be like holy shit. This is the coolest thing i've ever heard
They were a long retired by the time I ever knew them finding vivian meyer 2014
I remember this movie was very acclaimed. I feel like when it came out
Yes, I think it was nominated for an oscar and what what was your grandfather's name?
Because i'm gonna fire it up. I mean roger carlson is his name roger carlson great
You will see him in this movie. I never said that on the show
Uh, you maybe it's been a while. You've told me in conversation
Yeah, but I forgot it was about vivian meyer. I thought it was more about
So there's a lot of documentaries on the history of bookstores and stuff. Yes
um, oh what do
Okay
Is there any way we can get back to talking about the end of mickey's night? I mean, I think it wraps up pretty
Pretty nice. Oh, yeah. So so I mean I guess yeah, it wraps up pretty nicely
Obviously, they're gonna defeat the rat king roger rabbit sings a song about living
In the land of candy and the importance of dental care if you're eating that much sugar
Which I mean, I don't know how that how much that's you know stuck with kids
Um, they do like a country version of a song at this point too and at the end
Yes, which I mean look, I like there's some candy cowboys
There's candy cowboys, which I can't be mad at a candy cowboy
Because you know, I like in my later years. I like hillbilly nonsense
That's a big thing, but I don't know that I necessarily love like this version
Oh
All right, I take it back I do like that actually
That's a classic not nutcracker piece. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I mean that's yeah that's song fine
Yes, but i'm talking about this country version of it. Yes, but you're but I don't like all the newer versions
The the hipening versions of all the other songs, but this I do like I do like this
Uh, uh pretty good and tigger is dancing like line dancing
And you know pretty good
Pretty good pretty fun
um
My favorite line at the ending is when mickey turns to minnie and says
Minnie will you be my princess and stay with me here in candy land?
And i'm just imagining the bank
Going like did she abandon this house? She hasn't paid her mortgage a month like
Where is she you were just thinking of her old life that she left behind. Yeah, she
Conrad tina etho they've given yeah statements to the police, but they have no idea where she is
What if you fall asleep tonight?
And let's say like mrs. Taffy comes to you in a dream
And you and mrs. Taffy go off
Well, wait, is she with mr. Taffy or they separate it? No, she's having an affair
with you
But she says jason we're gonna live in in taffy land. Is it like a dead bedroom situation?
What is that? Oh, that's where like there's no physical intimate dead bedroom. They're not
Sleeping together anymore. They're more friends than anything
So well, how about this? I'm gonna make it as uncomfortable as possible. Mr
Taffy is in love with mrs. Taffy, but she's not interested in him anymore physically
I don't know if I want to get in the middle of this because I don't know if he's violent
I don't know. He is violent. Oh great. Yeah. No, i'm staying away from this
But mrs. Taffy says jason you and I can live in taffy land forever, but is he in taffy land?
Yeah, but you have to just carry a a candy sap on you at all times
But it's all the candy you can eat and because it's magic it's not caloric
It's a lot to consider
And
and
Mrs. Taffy also just looks like a big piece of taffy
I would hope yeah, I mean, she's not like a sexy lady taffy or anything. I we should say by the way that um
The end of this mickey hits the rat king with a big bag of sugar
And then it goes slow motion everyone danced around him and he's a handsome prince again
Which I totally forgot was set up early. I was like, okay
This kind of makes sense why he eats sugar, right?
But the narrator stuff that like it was a handsome prince
They got a curse turn to rat eat sugar because you break the cart and i'm like, doesn't everyone want to break the curse?
Yeah, you'd think so. Sorry. I started that
uh, yeah, you would think so, but I I also forgot the the handsome prince part of it, um, but
Overall, it's a pretty good show. And again, it's eisner era nonsense
And I like hillbilly nonsense nonsense
I like eisner era nonsense
And I wish they would do something like this where like oh you got to see this one show
It's only going to be this season or maybe two seasons. Yeah
Um, and it's you it's got its own narrative. It's obviously got some unique music
um, but
I don't it's never gonna happen again. Well, I appreciate the increase in uh
Producing and production values and obviously the singers and dancers in the parks still very talented
Well, I feel like every question. Yeah, I I feel like the behind the scenes stuff
There's so much of it has to be picture. Perfect has to convey this it has to fall
these are the
parameters
of
Whatever this guy's got to look like
I also want to make clear i'm lamenting the fact that they don't do this in the park or anything right now
Um, but I don't I didn't like this
Okay
So that's a principle of the thing basically. All right, I didn't like this but I have principles
And I want things like this that I don't like to be in the park
A man's got to have a code and I yes, I have a very strict code and I want I want more
Stuff I didn't like like this in the park
And versus stuff. I didn't like like wolverine and deadpool
Holiday show specifically holiday show because I feel like that original show that I didn't see in person
I liked the clips better
Than I saw this but I will also say this my daughter was very upset
During the show and I was trying to wrangle her in addition to watching and enjoying the laughs
Did the show make her upset or well she was just sort of in a mood?
She needed a nap
And then on top of that as soon as the show was over
Deadpool and wolverine left sort of toward the hyperion theater part in california venture that show I thought you meant this show
podcast the ride
No, no mickey's nightcracker. Oh, yeah. No i'm talking about deadpool wolverine
Sorry, and as soon as deadpool wolverine left and they were out of sight she goes
Hey, I want to meet them
I want to meet them and I go i'm sorry
They're not doing like because you know obviously all the other characters we got in line and we met them
Deadpool wolverine were not doing a meeting great. That's absurd
So she yelled I want to meet them and I had to explain to her like we they're not meetable
And she's like no I want to meet them and she like flipped out
So i'm dragging a two-year-old away from the front of this of the area where they did the show
And she's yelling that she wants to meet deadpool and wolverine. They should really be escorted by handlers to the side of the stage
Line up the audience and everyone it's a good point
Everyone wants to see deadpool and wolverine
Are you kidding me? It's a good point and I don't know why they didn't have a meet and greet
But they do have a show there and I again, I like the effort. I appreciate the effort. But anyway
I oh by the way, I have uh, I read an article about you know storm
Has her first solo comic in quite a while. Yes, and I read a big spoiler about the one that comes out
Today do you want to say it on here?
I don't want to say it on here because I don't want to ruin it people go and
Pick up their shot, but i'll tell you what I am excited
You seem as excited as when you said the irish potato story earlier in the episode. I well when
I tell you what it is. Uh, I think you will see why okay
Well, you'll tell me off mic because this is so I will tell you off mic
I can't stop thinking about the pencil factory that you're graham
I really don't know a lot about the pencil factory. You got to find out what brand of pencil
I feel like I was a ticonderoga kid
But I really like the ones that were yellow with silver
I think that was was that a ryan and I could never find them
I'm not sure what a ryan or a ticonderoga. I don't know the difference. I don't know. I was reading some
gloomy stuff recently about like
kids
High schoolers college students like they get an assignment and they just plug shit in the chat gpd
And they're turning in papers filled with
uh
What is it? Do they call it artifacts or they're?
Anomalies like no that didn't happen. That's not real
Shakespeare
Shakespeare did not write the play julius caesar to perform for
So you would say so they would be writing a paper about roger rabbit and they would say like, you know,
Baby, huey was the baby in roger rabbit and it's just because that information was incorrect somewhere
They heard it maybe on a podcast on the pocket with that. Yeah, and that's a folly of fact checking
Right. I mean I have seen there are still kids who like just thesaurus everything
And there was a really funny tweet going around about like yeah
I knew he had done that in this paper because it was about 1984 and he called big brother enormous sibling
And I was like, well, that's pretty funny. That is really funny. All right
Well, did we do did we do it?
I there's another episode where I feel like did we do the episode did it even happen?
Did it did we do we do a good job just so?
bamboozled by candy factories and I got I got so down yes, I was I just wanted to curl up sort of by the fire
And kind of just listen to stories
of candies and pencils
Great just wanted to hear that. So anyway, you've survived podcasts the ride, uh, the second gate mickey's nutcracker
scott free
Um, thank you for joining us
I hope
Tell us what your favorite pencil company was growing up. What pencils did you use?
I don't really remember. I honestly I was sort of bored by I like mechanical
Everyone you know, everyone just liked a toy to fiddle with I like to toy to fiddle with so you you contact family members
And let's find out what pencil factory
Yes, your grant your
What was it grandpa grandpa pop pop pop pop pop pop?
I like pup pup, which is what you said initially which does sound like mitts saying
Hood dog on no boys. Yeah, but I think I think pop hop or pup
I feel like it would be entertaining changeable. All right, well, we'll find out what pup pup did