Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the Second Gate's historic third Munster-based episode.
I am our grandpa, as established with costumes a while back,
and we've got Herman here, Mike Carlson.
I am Herman, hello.
Hello.
I guess.
Yeah, no, it's not. It's really a size-oriented thing and not a voice-oriented.
I mean, I could sort of maybe, I'm grandpa.
Yeah, I can only do Billy West's impression of grandpa, which is just like,
look what you did, you big jerk, you big dummy.
That's pretty good.
Pretty good.
We've got to switch it up then.
You can, look, if we have to do the voice at some point,
which means, so can I switch to Herman?
Can I like, maybe?
Yeah, maybe.
I think so.
I think we could be flexible in what we're doing.
I mean, there's the only two really that have such distinct voices.
Lily kind of, but then, you know, Eddie is just kind of a little boy's voice.
And Marilyn is certainly just, no, the rest just sort of talk.
Yes.
So you got nothing there.
Although even Fred Gwynn as Herman also just kind of talks, but just like,
very stiff and polite.
I don't know if that's not good either, but you know what I mean, right?
He does that and then he kind of has this low status thing he does that's really,
that's funny, but he's not doing such a voice like Al Lewis's.
Yeah, yeah.
But Al Lewis then is just that character all the time too, in real life.
No, it's not particularly a character.
So it's not a character, just because of his days in the vaudeville,
when he was in a vaudeville, as he says on the many interviews I've watched with him,
where he discusses his vaudeville training.
Wow, it's always vaudeville.
He calls it vaudeville.
Wow.
Yeah.
So.
Which then that is his vaudeville training.
Yeah.
Training step number one, pronounce it vaudeville.
Vaudeville, yeah.
So, but yeah, so he, no, he just seemed, I don't know, the monsters,
I love the monsters, but it is funny.
This is an interesting special because I feel like it takes the monsters out of the normal
context of the monsters to some degree.
Yes.
To some degree with the way, just the way that the show was shot.
They're kind of out in the world a little bit, but still, but only to a degree that is like
detrimental to the viewing experience.
What if the monsters was filmed badly?
That's true, yes.
It is filmed badly on like video tape I read.
Yeah.
And like bad work, like I don't know, is monsters on film probably?
Like everything was on film?
Yeah, I think so.
Probably.
That seems right.
As far as old sitcoms, yeah.
Oh, so that's the, yeah, because there's, this thing's full of like weird
flare outs or burn ins or seemingly just like digital weird jumps in restoring it.
It's a strange little piece of material, I'd say.
Yes, but they all, I will say they like, they don't phone it in, in a way I've seen sometimes.
Like, and I don't want to put him down, but you see the clip of Adam West where he's in Memphis
wrestling and it's a little while after the Batman show and he's still hilarious,
but he's like drunk and he's clearly just not quite in the zone like he used to be.
I was going to say, yeah, I'd pin that on being drunk.
It's very possible it's partly because he's drunk, but I'm just saying sometimes you see
some of these characters, these people out of context or out of their regular show,
and it loses the magic.
I would say it doesn't lose the magic, even though this might be a bad watch.
No, it's definitely, yeah, it's definitely them.
Well, because they were in the zone, as opposed to the Adam West thing you're
describing way after the fact, this was in the run.
That's true.
Between the two seasons.
So they're locked in.
They don't get like a summer break in which to lose Herman.
No, yeah, that's true.
And Rambo.
That's true.
To lose the character they developed.
Yeah.
That's such a hard character to do.
Highly specific.
Yeah, yeah.
No, with a long summer break, God, he might start pronouncing Vaudeville.
Vaudeville.
Right.
You would lose that character completely.
They say Seth MacFarlane goes into the booth sometimes, and they say,
oh, Seth's Stewie sounds a little weird right now, and he has to kind of readjust
because it's been a while since he did Stewie.
He does 30 other voices.
He's recorded three music albums in the interim.
So he's lost Stewie for a second, and now he has to get Stewie back.
No, it didn't have to do that.
Yeah.
Well, that's like, it takes Jason a second to fire up the stitch,
but you just have to key in on Ohana means family as the keyword,
and then out comes a perfect stitch.
That's a very good point.
Jason's not with us, by the way.
Yes, we've said that, yes.
Any of our Munster family is not with us.
But I'm not concerned about it because there will be
clearly at this rate many more opportunities to talk Munsters.
Yeah, we're up to three.
Right.
This franchise in the podcast, The Right Franchise,
will go as long as Fast and the Furious, I think.
Sure.
At least as long.
Which is what, did I mean 10?
Or I guess Hobbs and Shaw, I don't know if that counts as one of the 10.
Right.
Well, I guess The Right presents Munsters episodes, presents.
Yes, and there's more Munsters being made.
They're going to keep trying, too, which is what really is important.
They're going to crack at one of these days, yeah.
Yes.
They're going to finally bring the Munsters back.
After 60 years of remakes, remake attempts.
That's something I wanted to bring up was the kind of the age of the show.
In one of the times, I don't know if this was one of the Munsters-oriented episodes
or if this was just kind of a separate Munsters detour, which it very well could have been,
but at some point, I don't remember if it was you or Jason or the both of you,
there was discussion of, well, maybe we should get a hold of one of the Munsters writers,
either to ask them a question or for them to help us out with something
or to get their punch up on something.
And I responded, I don't know anything about anything,
but I would imagine that the majority of the Munsters writing staff is dead.
And I was thinking about that in this and while looking at some Munsters IMDB pages,
and I was like, can I figure that out officially?
Can I make the official call there?
And I got into a list.
I was like, all right, I'm going to click on every credited writer for the Munsters
and see where we get.
And there was a while there.
Basically, I made it 15 in and every single one I clicked on has been dead for some time.
In many cases, some have been dead for like 50 years.
Wow.
Some of the Munsters writers died 10 years after the show.
I believe one died like almost immediately after.
Maybe that was the tragic circumstances.
I don't know, but a lot were dead in the 70s
because a lot of the writers were born in the 1910s.
They were in their 50s writing.
Yeah, that's a good point.
So the notion that an original Munsters writer is still with us.
Now, I was like, oh my God, I'm going to be able to report in this episode
that every Munsters writer is dead.
And then I got to the last three, strangely coincidentally, and they were not listed as dead.
However, it does seem possible that maybe just the fine folks at IMDB have not been
notified of the passing of these three Munsters writers.
And I would still say, I think smart money's on every Munsters writer is dead.
But if you can just prove it out there, let us know.
And they're not, yeah, they're not like famous writers.
There wasn't a bigger credit maybe they had where they would have notoriety.
What's bigger than that?
What's bigger than the Munsters?
Where do you go from there?
I don't know, it's a good point.
I found also no information.
This started because I was looking up the writers of this,
who were not regular Munsters writers.
And that might, you know, if, this is an if, I don't know.
If there are any questions as to the quality of the special we're talking about
and it not matching the quality of the series.
Well, maybe the outside hires could be the issue there.
Yes.
I looked this up.
There was something like one of them had an Arthur Godfrey credit.
I forget which Arthur Godfrey show there was.
Oh, sure.
Uh-huh.
Viewboost staple, Arthur Godfrey.
Right.
Yes, exactly.
So there was some, yeah, older credits.
I see.
Than this special.
Yeah, I think mostly we are dealing with this.
Maybe they decided to go older this time.
Let's get people like, we've been given these young whippersnappers.
Too many breaks.
Let's get some writers who were born in the 1800s.
Yeah.
Well, that's the reason that they can't crack this Munsters reboot
is these people are too young.
Rob Zombie was 58 years old.
Yeah.
When he did this new Munsters, probably 57, whatever.
Ultimately, yeah.
It's just not, it's not really a thing that 1900s writers understand.
And that's too bad because I can't imagine that in the year 2025,
anyone is still alive from, well, I say, okay, you know, that was unfair.
I think anybody born past the 20s, it's true.
But there's probably some people still alive who were of Munsters writing age.
It's possible.
I mentioned this on the show before.
I go and see once in a while, Jimmy Angel, an 89-year-old rock and roll singer.
Yep.
He's the last of the 50s Bobcats.
Listeners, can you believe what Mike is telling you?
Does this seem strange?
He goes to see an old rock and roll singer.
There's a guy who I often see sitting and watching the show who is 104.
He's a World War II veteran.
Whoa.
So he's like, Jimmy's a young man to this guy.
And this guy still gets up and dances too, this 104-year-old.
Really?
So every other couple songs, he gets up with what I assume like is his young 87-year-old wife.
Because she looks younger.
Maybe I'm wrong, but she looks younger.
So I do sometimes, I do wonder, are any of the...
And believe it or not, an 89-year-old rock and roll singer attracts an older audience often.
Some months there will be a bunch of young people.
I don't know why.
Don't know what they've heard about it.
Sometimes you're at a couple tables where your hip youthfulness is matched.
Exactly.
But in many cases...
No, many cases it's old folks, a lot of old folks.
And I do often wonder, are there old sitcom writers here?
And I've never gone table to table, but I do have that thought that like,
maybe there's a Munster's writer among all these old people.
At least Adobe Gillis.
At the very least Adobe Gillis.
Or at the very, very least, someone whose memory has decayed so much
that they now believe they were a writer for Adobe Gillis.
Would be fine to talk to that person.
If they can give you a minute of details and like,
Yeah, my favorite driver was Mater G. Cribbs.
We'd laugh and laugh and we'd order sandwich after sandwich.
And you look it up and like, he didn't even...
He moved to Los Angeles nine months ago.
He was dumped here by his family.
They just dropped him off at the smokehouse.
They figure it out.
Ask some bartenders.
They'll find you somewhere to live.
My picture's on the wall over that booth over there.
And you're looking, it's like Jimmy Stewart.
That's not you, sir.
Yeah, it is.
I looked different when I was younger.
Maybe it's an eyesight thing.
I don't know.
But yeah, smokehouse.
Smokehouse is a time machine.
Yeah, yeah, in general.
Yeah, we've referred to this place.
I don't know if people know.
The restaurant that's across from the Warner Brothers lot,
where there's the rumor is that there's a tunnel
that takes you from the Warner Brothers lot to the restaurant.
That's the rumor.
Let's try to decipher that.
I don't know where that ends up.
God, if we could determine if that's real, that's an episode, I bet.
The smokehouse tunnel to the Warner Brothers studio.
Smokehouse, separate, tunnel, separate.
Weird poster on the wall for an independent short film
called Martinis at the Smokehouse, separate.
Which seems to be a, from what I can tell,
a Midnight in Paris type thing,
where all of the ghostly legends of smokehouse yore all come back.
Was that word right that I used?
I think so.
I didn't want to say lore.
I want to say yore.
Is that like the past yore?
Oh, yeah.
Days of yore.
That's usually how it's-
Yeah, there you go.
All right.
Days of yore, yeah.
Sometimes something comes out of your mouth.
I know.
And you don't.
I'm instantly feeling that in the two host format that you sort of,
because I think-
A little more pressure.
You know, now I know you had a bunch of episodes without me.
Just to keep the ball in the air.
You cannot take a break and pass it over to-
No, there's no, yeah, no.
It's not a triangle offense anymore.
There's a basketball term, triangle defense.
I don't know.
It's not that anymore.
I bet Jason would know because he's been trying to figure out the pop fly rule.
So if he's been trying to figure out that,
then he's probably like a few years from figuring out what the triangle offense is.
So the Munsters.
Today we are talking about the Munsters at Marineland.
And this has actually been on my to-do list for a little bit.
Not just the Munsters thing, but I've been wanting to talk about,
and maybe this is a good context to talk about before this special a little bit,
the park that this is filmed and set in, Marine Land of the Pacific.
And again, just to clarify, this is not an episode of the Munsters,
but like a summer special where they go to this theme park,
which is kind of a Sea World-esque aquarium type of theme park.
And Marine Land of the Pacific, I guess growing up around here,
I knew that there was such a place, but I didn't know where it was.
I didn't know anything about the history of it.
And this all kind of moved to top of mind for me last year because about a year ago,
Aaron and I got a little break from our then one kiddo.
And we got to spend the day kind of exploring Orange County in the South Bay
and just kind of like wandering around.
And so we were in Orange County and we're making our way up to like more kind of the
Marina Del Rey neck of the woods.
And we're like, what can we do in that?
Is there like a kind of a fancy bougie lunch we could do?
Is there like some weird hotel that we've never been to?
And we looked it up like, all right, what's along the coast?
There's something with a beach view.
And we found this place with this very odd name
that we're staring at, like, Tyrannia.
And it's turned at TerraNaea is how you say it.
You ever heard of TerraNaea Resort?
So this is in Rancho Palos Verdes.
So we got excited when we saw this, like, okay, what's the way the hell out there?
But we got the whole day to explore.
That sounds great.
It seems like there's tons of restaurants there.
And it's like big winding path, like takes forever.
And you're climbing and climbing and climbing up to like the top of like you're very it's ocean
front and it's cliff side and like such high dazzling cliffs with just shimmering infinite
ocean views as we climb and climb to this place.
It is crazy beautiful.
And like a type of beautiful, I don't usually ascribe to the LA area.
It's very like Hawaii.
And we're just like, who knew this was?
I mean, I guess we've been over there once, but like didn't really know the deal.
And when we get to this resort, especially and like this is insane.
It's just like it's like sprawling so many buildings, immaculate ocean views wherever
you go, it's fancy, it's marble, it's smooth jazz playing everywhere.
That's what we want.
You don't always have to stay at the fancy hotel to get a little taste of the fancy hotel.
And we're walking around and we're trying to figure it out.
And like, so why have we never heard of this place?
And then we get a little afraid.
We go, oh, is this Trump?
Is this a Trump resort?
I really hope it's not a Trump resort because he does have a golf course around there.
Look it up.
No, thank God.
All right.
This is a fairly new place.
This is maybe like 2009 on kind of new spot.
And in looking it up, we realized, oh my God, this is the spot where Marine land of the
Pacific was.
There was this massive 100 acre theme park property was here and has now been converted
into this bougie resort.
We keep going and we end up at a restaurant, which I'd recommend to any, if you're trying,
if you're wandering around this neck of the woods and want like a cool, not even break
the bank kind of restaurant, really great waterfront restaurant called Nelson's.
Nelson's, huh?
What does that name mean?
And then we're looking around and all of the art in the restaurant is devoted to one
really specific actor with a very memorable face and very memorable, intense eyes.
And that is Lloyd Bridges.
Everywhere we look, old photos of Lloyd Bridges who like, and Lloyd Bridges, what are his
big, he was in a lot of spoof movies.
Like that's kind of, he's been the most relevant to us for, what are they?
Is he hotshots and is he an airplane?
Seinfeld is the like intense.
Mantle bomb.
Yeah, yeah.
Is he a mantle bomb?
So like what's going on here?
Nelson's, and it turns out that this is a restaurant that acknowledges the Marine land
history because Lloyd Bridges played a character named Mike Nelson on a series called Seahunt.
You ever heard of Seahunt?
No.
I've never, in old TV wanderings, never run into Seahunt before.
Seahunt ran from 57 to 61.
Wow.
One of these like hundreds of episodes and still like how have I never come across this before.
Now this is a year ago that we went to this place and I've done a bad job of
looking into what's actually going on with Seahunt, but I just really liked the vibe.
Are you seeing anything interesting as you look up Seahunt?
Because I just loved, all the posters on the wall of this place were so great where it's
that he's just got these like beady, crazy guy and we think of him for the spoof movies.
We see Lloyd Bridges and we're kind of laughing already.
So seeing him in scuba gear and then it's like old pulpy magazine covers and it says
Mike Nelson loved danger and he found it deep down and he's looking at you like he's about
to snap. He's like, I'm going to have to go buck wild on an army of crabs.
I'm going to fight them all hand to hand combat.
And then like things like here's him on the rocks.
Every piece of art also seems to be him shirtless in tiny, tiny shorts.
And in this case, like another scuba guy is punching him in the face.
That looks awesome.
It looks so awesome. So Seahunt was filmed on this property.
Marineland was the like filming home of Seahunt.
Here's another one. Like this guy was fucking, he had one of those.
Oh yeah.
Just like, you know, like diver kind of bodies.
Here he is in even tinier shorts.
Like he looks like tanned up, greased up, holding a weird little machine gun in front of a sea cave.
Wow. Seahunt.
Seahunt.
Bring back Seahunt.
Oh, Leonard Nimoy was on it. Eight episodes.
Yes. Leonard Nimoy was on it. His kids were on it.
Jeff and Bo were on a bunch when they were really little.
One of Jack Nicholson's first TV credits.
Was on Seahunt.
I found a really great YouTube channel of like an old.
This guy befriends the Jimmy Angel.
This is like an old diver who's sitting in front of some film canisters.
And he's talking about all the stars of Seahunt, all the old actors.
And he frames it in the same way every time.
He kind of like daughters on and on.
He says, Leonard Nimoy was on it, you know?
And people didn't know who he was back then.
They'd say, who's that?
Oh, Leonard, he's just a nobody.
He's just a nobody getting his start.
And then before you know it,
he becomes one of the icons of American screens.
The one he's Leonard Nimoy as we know him today.
He says the same thing. Who's that?
Oh, that's this kid, Larry. Larry Hagman.
He's a nobody. He'll do Seahunt for us.
He needs it. He's hungry and desperate.
He'll come here anyway.
But now he's he's what's his name?
He played on the Sean and J.R. He's J.R. on the.
I was like, I was enamored.
I think it's not described in this old divers YouTube.
He's the guy who owns the most Seahunt
memorabilia in the world.
If that's not a YouTube channel you got to subscribe to.
I don't know what it is.
Seahunt memorabilia.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, he might own that gun.
He might own pieces of coral.
Where Lloyd Bridges got his head smashed in.
Wow. I wonder if they have like action figures
or something for Seahunt.
I don't know. It might not have been.
It was like syndicated.
I don't know if it made it to like,
I don't think it was one of the primary shows.
No.
Well, you know what it was.
Syndicated show with beefcakes on the beach.
This was the Baywatch of its time.
Right.
This was Baywatch before Baywatch.
So anyway, I've already let everybody down.
This has been a year and I've not done the deep dive on.
I haven't gotten greased up.
Wow.
Much more jacked and dove off the cliff and explored Seahunt.
But anyway.
Is Seahunt streaming anywhere?
Pluto TV.
It's a Pluto.
We got Pluto.
Hey, they got to flesh out these lineups with something.
Which by the way, the Munster special that we'll talk about
is pretty accessible.
I think 2B was one of them.
I think this is some real like streamer bait.
If you have a streamer and you're looking to populate it
with something, I think you can get Munster's Marine Land
Carnival pretty easy.
There was a show called The Aquanauts in 1960.
Ooh.
And then a show called Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea
and ran from 64 to 68.
So there were a lot of sea-based shows
that I really have never heard of or never seen.
Well, things maybe trying to tap into the Jacques Cousteau
thing.
Yeah, a little odd.
The sad thing is I started poking around.
I just got bored because I didn't immediately counter
Lloyd Bridges bludgeoning an octopus to death in scene one.
Like that's what I wanted to be.
I know.
I'm worried it's boring.
I think probably.
Well, and which is the magic of Baywatch for me,
that it is not boring for the most part.
Early on, it's when they were trying to be more of a real show.
Yeah.
But Sea Hunt didn't make it.
Sea Hunt didn't get to its shark-jumping sixth, seventh,
eighth seasons that just turn into long music videos
that Lloyd Bridges is doing, which is really a shame.
But yeah.
I want to see him getting electrocuted by an electric eel
and then he retains the electricity of the eel
and turns into kind of an evil electric Lloyd Bridges
and starts zapping his family and friends.
That's what I want the show to be.
And then Jack Nicholson's part of it
and he becomes some sort of electro figure alongside him.
That's what I want the show to be.
But you can't get everything.
Yeah.
You want it to be lost in space, Batman 60s mixed with Sea Hunt.
Not yeah.
But it sucks because often, and this isn't always the case,
but sometimes when I see old stuff I go,
there's probably a reason I haven't seen it yet.
Like no one's recommended Sea Hunt to me yet.
Because somebody would have championed it before.
I would love to be wrong, but I feel like it's probably kind of boring.
There's not an episode where Lloyd Bridges gets fooled
because a piece of trash draped onto the head of a walrus,
which made him believe it was a sexy lady
and then he married the walrus for a while.
Yeah.
Just like Lloyd Bridges going to the underwater kingdom of Atlantis,
like swimming down to Atlantis and seeing what a 60s Atlantis set is.
Yeah.
And him fighting like the king of Atlantis for the throne.
Like that's what I want.
Because he fell in love with the princess of Atlantis.
Of course, yeah.
He fell in love with his wife, stabs him with a trident.
Guy who has like a half bass head is like,
they're already engaged to be married and he has to punch his way to her heart.
Right.
And then, yes, he has kids that are half mer-baby, half Lloyd.
Well, we'll see.
But it's not that show.
Yeah, that already, that's what it could have become in season eight, I think,
is we have left, he's no longer a marine biologist or whatever the hell he is.
He's now the king of Atlantis.
Yes, exactly.
Yes.
Oh, why doesn't, oh my God.
My new goal needs to be like Trojan horsing a show.
It's just a relatable kind of like, you know,
and it's about three guys and they work at the post office,
but they're very different, but they make it all work and they,
and it's very refillable, you see, and every second of that,
I have the intention of turning the show in success to becoming about the king of Atlantis.
Yeah, of course, that is the dream.
I know, it's a bummer.
What if something like The Bear like eventually become like,
it's all a long con and like, no, no, no, the Chicago restaurant era is long over.
They've been in Atlantis for six seasons now.
Yeah, well, and as we've discussed, like they, the genres had to scatter from the network,
from the major networks too.
So it's like, they're even more adverse usually, unless it's like a drama now,
like they've put things in boxes.
I'm trying to think it wasn't the last like silly mainstream super,
like things with supernatural elements on like NBC or ABC.
I think you got to go back to the TGI.
You have to go back to waning TGI shows about like genies and angels,
but then those weren't, those weren't good either is the thing.
Right.
Super Teenage Witch, I think of some quality writers on it.
That was silly, but like those moved to like Nickelodeon more.
I guess there was like that DC, like superhero cleanup show,
but like no one, I don't know.
That's kind of like, there's some silly thing.
I don't know.
I just mean, there's not a high concept.
What show is that?
Wasn't Jenny Pearson on it?
The one that Jenny Pearson was on, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm just trying to, like if there's going to be a mainstream monsters TV show now,
it's got to be a drama for some reason.
I don't know why.
It is my hope.
I don't know.
With the state of the world as it is, that we can all just commit
to getting sillier and sillier.
That actually, I think I can kind of weave us back to-
Hold it.
Can I say my pitch again?
I've said it on the show before.
Southern Munsters.
That's my pitch.
You've said Southern Munsters on the show before?
I think so.
This is my pitch.
Southern Munsters.
It's like, I mean, Reba's on TV, but like Reba,
it's like Tim Blake Nelson dressed as a Frankenstein.
Sure.
Same thing as the Munsters.
There's not much to it.
Southern Munsters.
So kind of a Beverly Munsterbillies is what you're describing.
Sam Elliott's in there.
He's like grandpa, I guess.
That is a good one.
Also, because this is the thing, like kind of a new Trump era.
Right.
We think we got to be like all the streamers are going to be kind of like,
you know, desperately courting the red states again.
So that's a, yeah, yeah, you bring back Munsters, but then like-
Summer, some Southern Munsters.
You could call it Southern Munsters, I suppose.
You feel like Tyler Perry might go in on Munsters?
Sure.
Like kind of a Munsters with heart?
The only thing is he would just probably make his own
because he wouldn't get as much money because he has to split it with-
Oh, yeah.
What am I saying?
There's no IP going on.
Yeah.
Why would he?
He wouldn't waste his time.
He would do his own monster show.
Yeah.
Oh, a thousand percent.
So yeah, that's my pitch.
We're quickly understanding.
We're reminding ourselves the economics of Tyler Perry world.
But anyway, I just found all this interesting.
It was really nice being at that place.
And then I started discovering, okay, well, tons of stuff filmed around there.
Partridge Family, Mannix, The Six Million Dollar Man, The A-Team,
and why Batman 66, one of our favorite films, something filmed at Marine Land.
I'm not sure what, but you know, there's a bunch of,
because they're dealing with submarines and bat boats and stuff.
Not the dock though.
Not the famous bomb dock scene probably.
That is, ah, I always forget what that is.
It might be like Santa Barbara or Malibu.
I don't, yeah, it's not where Batman's running around with the big bomb.
Right.
One of the finest scenes in movie history.
This did remind me of the fact, and reminding myself of Munster's stuff,
Munster's mega hit, like huge, huge hit for two seasons.
It was only on for two seasons, but the seasons were all like north of 30 episodes.
60 episodes.
Yeah.
They jammed that all into two years.
And the special, we're talking about this Marine Land special,
was done between those two seasons.
I didn't realize, I did not know this chronology,
that Munster's huge hit season one, whichever other network,
I'm not even sure, ABC?
I don't know.
I don't know what was on what network, but the other networks,
like we got to bring Munster's down.
What do we do?
Hey, I got this new thing, Batman.
Let's get Munster's in the crosshairs, because I didn't know that.
Yeah, Batman killed off the Munster's.
Wow.
Isn't that disturbing that two of our favorite things were enemies,
that they were fighting so much of the same spirit?
It is true.
But then Batman kind of burns out quickly too,
in the way that they did that as well, where they,
it's like a ton of episodes in one season,
and then that's done after three years too.
And they're two episodes a week, so that they had every opportunity
to just like burn people through.
Yeah.
Right.
Flash phenomenon.
Someone might say that perhaps the Munster's had said all it had to say by year two.
I don't know that I'm saying that, but perhaps.
Worthy years.
Well, I mean, what it would have had to say around this time is like,
they would have had to address kind of like the Flower Generation,
and the Sunshine People.
Is there ever anything like that?
Do we know?
Does Herman put on long hair?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's one of them.
I feel like that is one of the episodes.
I know, I think so.
I mean, there's definitely, there's a Beatles stand-in episode,
there's a fake Beatles episode,
where they're even performing a Beatles song.
There's some dealing with youth culture.
Is it a made-up Beatles type band,
or isn't like a good band?
I want to say that one of these duo bands,
like Chad and Jeremy, or Peter and Gordon, were on the Munsters.
Chad and Jeremy were on the Munsters,
but I think it's a different...
Chad and Jeremy also on Dick Van Dyke's show,
I believe there's an episode.
But I believe there's a different episode I'm thinking about.
Beatles analoged Munsters.
I think they were...
Fifth Beatle Herman Munster, I forget.
Munsters, I don't know.
This is going to take more research to do it,
but I believe both existed.
I don't think that was the same episode that I'm talking about.
Well, because none of these episodes have been about the show.
One was about the Rob Zombie movie.
One was about his restaurant in New York,
in which I saw one ad in which Grandpa Munster calls himself Grandpa,
and I will never not call him Grandpa from now on.
And now they saw Marine Land Special,
people have recommended, I think, over the years,
or maybe it's snuck into the Club 3 suggestions,
but I figure this might be a fun time to do it.
I want to talk about my Marine Land stuff,
which I'll dovetail back around to that,
what happened to Marine Land and why
we have Terra Nega Resort and no Marine Land today.
But I guess let's focus on the special for now.
You're going to find it if you look it up on 2B or wherever else it is.
I think Munsters Marine Land is going to get it for you.
I think Munsters Marine Land Carnival is one of the names,
but when it was playing on 2B,
there was a huge block of text on the screen,
and I wrote it all down.
It said that what I was watching was called
Marine Land Carnival with the Munsters TV show cast members.
It's not a very economical use of words there.
Anyway, but don't bother typing all that.
That's a big effort.
Just put in Munsters Marine Land and you'll find it.
This was a special film in 1965,
which somehow has to bring together the family of monsters,
the family where there's a Frankenstein and several vampires and a wolf man,
and we have to get them to a park that is where you see dolphin races.
So I had the question going in,
how narratively do we tie all of this together?
Yeah.
I guess the overarching story here, the why,
is that they believe that they are at the world's largest pet store.
Fish store.
Fish store is what they say.
Okay, yeah, and that they are looking for a pet for Eddie,
their wolf man son.
So that maybe some of the more monstrous creatures
who you can see at Marine Land,
like walruses or electric eels,
might be suitable pets for Eddie to take home.
Right.
And this is the dense narrative web that is woven.
It's pretty good, honestly, as a premise for the Munsters.
It's a pretty good premise.
That's all I need.
And then I get to watch that crazy coach pull up
to between a bunch of fish tanks.
Sounds good to me.
Which looks dangerous.
The Munsters coach, not the Dracula,
the Munsters coach pulls up.
Just spelled with a K, is that how you make it scary?
The Munsters coach pulls up with Eddie, Marilyn, and grandpa on the back,
like on the chair where granny sits on the Beverly Hill billies,
like that elevated part of a car.
And it looks like, you got to hold on to that thing.
That doesn't look like it's so secure.
All these shows establish that the funniest place
for the oldest person to sit is up top on the perch,
but it's also the most dangerous place by far.
Yes, and they're right.
That is funny.
I don't know that they didn't lose a couple of grannies.
Possibly, yeah.
Although they all look the same.
There might have been several granny hillbillies.
Yes.
In my mind, their last name is Hillbilly.
What's their name?
Clamp it, I believe.
I'm not a big Beverly Hillbillies guy.
Though I do like Hillbilly nonsense,
so maybe I need to get into the Beverly Hillbillies.
Yeah, that's confusing.
I remember kind of enjoying the film with Jim Varney and Floris Leachman.
I remember, yeah, maybe I've only seen a little bit of the film,
but not 30 years ago.
I mean, I'm positive it's not good.
No, I don't think it's good.
I did like Green Acres okay, though.
Okay, sure.
I do like Green Acres to some degree.
It is probably for the best that you want,
because if you were more into these things,
like then we're fully edging out all of the theme parks
that are barely making it into the show these days.
If we have to devote ample time to Petticoat Junction,
like we're like, all right, sorry.
What have we not done yet?
Radiator Springs Racers.
Well, the only, like Radiator Springs Racers is lucky
that it's got a Hillbilly character in there.
That's true.
Because otherwise.
And Radiator Springs, sorry, I was going to cut you off,
but Radiator Springs Racers is partly why I started
really getting into the old Hillbilly nonsense
is because Roly Poly plays in the line.
Oh, that's right.
Radiator Springs Racers figured out what it was.
There was, I think in one of those Scott Free episodes,
I think Jason just like quoted something
that was like three verses deep into one of those songs.
And I'm just like lost.
I am beyond, he's like assuming knowledge of the deep,
like the third of five verses of Roly Poly.
Trying to remember what that is.
Daddy's little fatty.
Eating corn and taters.
I think something like, yeah, yeah.
It was a joke of the nature of like,
well, I'm always eating my corn and taters.
And even you were like, what's that now?
I don't remember.
Look, I don't remember it.
When you're doing two, I like,
I won't remember any of this later either.
When you're doing two, you got to be focused.
So I'm just, it's, I'm just having it happen to me.
And then it comes out.
No, it is interesting.
I mean, what we could do is just like,
kind of like take breathers here and there,
just like kind of both of us just drift,
allow our voices to break and then chop all those out.
Maybe that's what happened.
Maybe what you're listening.
Yeah, we could have done it.
Yeah.
I don't know though.
I think we've got to, we've got to become a rapid fire.
This is, you know, we got to,
we got to be a middle ditch in Schwartz.
You know, we got to be locked in rapid fire.
I know.
Guns blazing.
And this is the problem too,
because right now I'm like,
I cannot find confirmation that Chad and Jeremy were on Monster.
So maybe I'm wrong about that,
but I believe that the fake band is the Standells
who performed I Want to Hold Your Hand
in the Munsters living room.
They do I Want to Hold Your Hand.
They do I Want to Hold Your Hand, yes.
And I believe I said it on this show before.
I've mentioned that they do the actual Beatles song.
I fully, fully believe that.
I see no reason not to believe that.
Well, in this special, you have a real band,
a real great band, a wonderful band,
you know, kind of taking some of the work away from the Munsters.
The Munsters are the hosts and their little stories,
the wraparounds that take you into the different aquatic exhibits.
But as the beginning tells you,
you also are going to be getting a lot of musical treats
from the new Christy Minstrels.
Yes.
This, which is a new level of lame old reference even for us.
I don't think, I think somehow we've never talked about
the new Christy Minstrels.
I don't think so, yeah.
This is some real like up with people kind of,
I mean, clearly the basis for The Mighty Wind,
the new Main Street Singers,
the group with like way too many people.
And they're all the whitest people with the whitest smiles.
And I don't think I realized till watching this
how exactly right on that is.
The parody is perfect, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, it is precisely what this is.
So new Christy Minstrels are in this.
They, they perform, yes, some of the, you know,
the whitest music you've ever heard.
Got me wondering, what is the deal with this group?
And also like, okay, the new Christy Minstrels,
what were the old Christy Minstrels?
Quick check of a couple of links.
Uh-oh, real Minstrels.
Yeah.
Whoops.
I mean, I guess I should have known,
but you know, don't go looking into the old Christy Minstrels.
No.
The new Christy Minstrels improved on the model by, you know,
not doing that.
Somewhat upsettingly,
and I'm kind of glad Jason's not here to hear this,
that old, the old Minstrel tradition of this.
Apparently that group was the group that popularized
some of the biggest songs of the 1840s,
such as Camp Town Races and Swanee River,
very much in the Jason Sings the Old One's pocket.
Yeah.
And I'm just, I'm sorry that some of his Spotify raps,
six and seven of the year tied up into kind of an unsavory tradition.
Yes.
I will.
Well, we'll see.
Maybe.
I don't know, but we'll see what I look.
I'm still digging for his actual top 10.
You know, I dug, I dug last.
I want to find it.
I don't know where it last night.
Or I meant last episode.
I guess depending on when this comes out.
Are you hacking into his file?
Are you from afar?
That would be a little weird.
Trying to tap into his phone.
No, I haven't like, so like sat outside with some sort of equipment
trying to hack into his wifi.
Look, just to see what
just to see what the last five songs are.
The answer, the answer is going to be new pornographers.
The only band that he has enjoyed in the last 40 years.
There was a brief window of time where he was interested in new music.
He found that it closed that chapter.
No need to go back.
It's probably what it is, but I just think there's something in there.
That's fun.
I don't know.
I don't know why.
I don't know what I was drawing.
I just feel like there's going to be a song in there.
You go, whoa, what's that?
Yeah.
And then we got a whole, well, and then we're off to the races.
To the camp town races.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, I was trying to see if there was a cover of camp town races by Chapel Roan.
I'm just making sure that in Jason's absence, we still get our
every episode reference to Chapel Roan.
And I want to make sure we're still checking all the boxes.
Yeah.
So I could be wrong about Chad.
And Chad and Jeremy maybe didn't appear.
I can't get it confirmed.
And I'm saying that's the tricky thing about doing two people.
One episode, because I can't fully get that.
And I don't want to be wrong.
You can divet.
I can talk and you cannot listen.
Yeah.
But I like to listen.
It's more.
Listening is better.
It's certainly more awkward.
But Far Out Monsters is the rock and roll episode
where they're dealing with youth culture.
The 50-year-old writers are all figuring out what they think about these beetles.
I don't know about these beetles.
Well, you get a little bit of beetles reflected in this at some point.
You do, yes.
Hey, wait.
Look, why not?
I think what happens is, OK, so there's a lot of little vignettes
where the monsters pop around and see different types of fish.
And at some point, one of the more entertaining ones
is that they run into a wall-talking walrus.
And they say that the walruses want to break into show business.
Yeah.
And that they all, it's a tough road for them
because they are walruses, first of all.
And then, second of all, that they only speak blubberies.
Yeah.
And then they perform kind of like a jazz scat song for the monsters.
It's really weird.
So a bunch of walruses perform a jazz for an all-monster audience to hear.
And then when it's over, somebody says, well, it was better than the beetles.
Yeah.
Grandpa says it?
I think, yeah, sounds right.
It's better than the beetles.
And then because it's easier to understand what they're saying,
and they're much better looking.
Was that a big complaint that you couldn't understand the beetles?
I know, so like Bob Dylan, I guess, there's all been famous bands
where they're mumbly-mumbly.
I don't know.
But maybe the beetles, just because you would enunciate as a singer
up until that point, and then just like, I'm trying to think
of what the most mumbly beetle song even is.
I can't think.
The main music that I know from kind of the pre-beetles era is holiday music,
because it's when it kind of like grows its head again every year.
And then because all flash to like, I guess a hit song before the beetles was,
it's the holiday season, the holiday season.
And in that, that's not only one singer, but then more,
then like 20 more singers all come in, and they all super enunciate too.
Right.
So yeah, the beetles with their screaming.
There'll be a song where they just go, wah!
What did they even say?
It was just a scream.
Don't worry about it sometimes.
They didn't even say what season they were enjoying.
What holiday is this celebrating?
Nowhere in that scream did they say if they were excited that friends and family are near.
Rock and roll music is trash.
They all come from broken homes, and they're going to make new ones.
And they're ugly too.
So ugly.
Look at that hair.
That's another, yeah, they're ugly.
And then also like, they look like girls.
They look like beautiful girls who I can't take my eyes off of, but also they're ugly.
Every sitcom in these years had an episode like this,
where they would just make fun of the beetles' hair,
and they were too loud, and what they would do to the girls.
And it's just like every like old TV writer who was 38 probably,
was just like, what is this shit?
What is this fucking garbage?
I'm going to take them down a peg using the Beverly Hillbillies.
I have my pulpit.
My pulpit is a petticoat junction.
I'm going to show how foolish this rock music is once and for all.
Uncle Fester's going to put on a mop top wig,
and he's going to stick it to these beetles.
Go fuck yourself, beetles.
He's going to sing a song that's like what they do.
Here, listen to him.
Be-bop-a-doo.
Be-bop-a-doo-pee.
See, this is what you sound like, idiots.
You'll change your tune.
You get old like me.
I'm trying to think there is a Batman.
Batman is cool too.
He dances the Batusi, but I'm trying to think what that episode is.
There are relevant depictions of youth culture like the Batusi,
but they weren't always so on the mark.
Yeah, yeah.
Not perfect.
Well, look, I imagine the same people who programmed,
who like, well, let's make sure we get a lot of anti-beetles material in there,
are also kind of overseeing the new Christy Minstrel side of it,
where at some point they said, now here to perform one of their greatest hits,
and then they just do, this land is your land.
You're like, wait a minute.
I think they had a hit with it.
That's what I read.
That's not their song.
And it probably did.
The new Christy Minstrel's cover of This Land is Your Land,
I was going to say like beat out Sgt. Pepper for the Grammys.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But probably not even.
It probably like somehow beat out Run DMC for best hip hop performance in 1986.
Like revival of it in there.
Well, they didn't get enough Grammys when they were around,
so we slunk them into a category in 1987.
There's nine people in that group.
They require a lot of Grammys.
We're doing them a disservice by not shoveling Grammys their way every year.
And Kenny Rogers in the group here?
Is that right?
It says he's in the, on IMDB, he's in there,
and it does list that like his career was started with this band.
Is he one of these nine?
That's what I think.
That's what it suggests.
Wow, that's wild.
Yeah, I think, let me see, Munsters.
Yeah, I think on, well, he's for sure listed on IMDB.
And then on the Wikipedia, it says that this group launched his career.
So this is before New Edition, First Edition.
I mean, it was before New Edition.
Yes, but First Edition was the Kenny Rogers band.
Okay, I didn't know that.
Which is just stopped into check or whatever.
My condition is in from, people know it from Big Lebowski.
Oh, he's in that?
Yeah, that's him.
That's him.
So he had like a, he kind of had a trippy rock and roll band
before kind of just being like, you know, like the guy you'd see on infomercials.
And that's from a movie starring Jeff Bridges, Son of Siemens.
Right, there you go.
Son of Mike Nelson himself.
Now I can think of it.
I just dropped in to see what my condition, my condition is in.
Yeah.
Which is a cool song.
I know, it is.
Wow.
In fact, I didn't know.
So he's had a couple different phases.
Here's a really unconfirmed fact.
First of all, I think we've, we're so deep into the episode,
I don't want to veer us into this tangent too much.
But I do think that we've undermeditated on this crazy information that
Frank Marshall's dad, Jack Marshall, wrote the Munster's theme song.
That is wild, yeah.
I forget if we've even fully addressed that on the show.
Right.
Well, among the strange like connective tissue that is like, who gets,
we talk about Grandpa Munster a lot and then who gets cast to play him in the movie.
The guy who played Jay Leno in Wait, Shift.
Again, we talk about Frank Marshall a bunch,
then it turns out his dad wrote the Munster's theme.
But also then I was just watching this John Williams documentary on Disney Plus
and they bring up that, well, Frank Marshall is interviewed and he brings up how
his dad, Jack Marshall, writer of the Munster's theme,
was in the army band with John Williams.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, so they went way back.
So when Indiana Jones comes up, the opportunity to collaborate
and create an iconic score with his dad's cool friend was an incredible experience.
So there you go.
So there are interesting Frank Marshall stories out there.
They do exist.
He, to Frank's credit, there's a lot of interesting stuff about him that I don't talk about.
That's less interesting to me, even though I like the things he was involved in,
which is less interesting to me to talk about.
Sure.
To Frank's credit, there's plenty of interesting things he's been involved in in his life.
You just choose a deeper, a deeper cut of that's, you know,
if you're a purist and seeking information that is interesting.
This is a wrong podcast if that's what you're looking for.
Interesting information.
That's not this podcast.
But this one here, this one might be interesting.
All of that was a roundabout way to say, and this was only,
I only saw this in comments, so this is unconfirmed,
but in the Munsters theme song, before the electric guitar kicks in,
it kind of starts with a big ba-ba-bum, which is a timpani.
And there are people who believe that that timpani was played by John Williams' dad.
Really?
It was also a John Williams.
But that's a rumor.
Yes.
That's just a rumored, yeah.
We combine a lot of, okay, so is it interesting to hear
liner notes information about who played on what?
Possibly not.
But what if that information is not credible?
Now we're talking podcast the ride.
Yeah.
Podcast that was once about theme parks.
One, a long time, days of yore, when podcast the ride was about theme parks.
It feels like when the Munsters writers were still alive.
We are about theme parks, though, here, because this was filmed at Marine Land at the time.
At the time, this is filmed, one of the most thriving theme parks in the state, in Los Angeles.
Marine Land opened in 54, it got the jump on Disneyland.
I believe this site, according to that Disneyland coffee table book,
the site of Marine Land was once scouted by Walt for Disneyland.
This was one of the prime open areas where you could fit a big crazy theme park development.
But they grabbed it, and they were decently competitive, I'd say, with Disneyland for a
little while.
This special shows you a little bit of why.
You get to see what they had to offer that isn't just Munsters related.
Because, by the way, a lot of it is the Munsters drive around.
They talk about how they're going to try to find electric eels for Eddie.
And then you just kind of get to watch Eddie watch a bunch of shows.
There's so much watching Eddie watching shows in this.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, they cut to him once every 15 minutes.
And that is meant to sell that you are becoming Eddie.
You are Eddie's POV.
Like, OK, first, imagine there's a wolf man boy.
My god, what a terrifying, though.
Imagine the capers he would get into.
Well, yes, for example, sometimes he sits politely with his regular friend and watches
dolphins swim around.
Yes, he also doesn't seem that excited.
Most of the shots.
Yeah, he kind of just has a blank expression on his face.
He's tired.
He's like, why I don't get the summer off?
I just filmed 36 episodes in a row.
There's no laws yet.
Preventing illegal.
Well, all of it.
The orcas aren't going to be allowed to be here.
And I'm not going to be allowed to be here for 20 hours a day.
The legislation is on the president's desk currently.
This is going to be illegal soon.
Yeah, something that luckily Trump is going to turn it.
That's one of his.
That's in the first 100 days.
He's going to get kids back to work without breaks for school and sleep.
Anti-Jackie Coogan laws.
Repeal the Jackie Coogan laws.
Creepy Coogan, we say.
Children need to work harder.
He's depriving children of that.
Children want to be working in the mines and they want to be working in this.
Sometimes both at once.
We send them and they pick out some coal and they come out
and they do some mines for Disney Channel.
Manny on Modern Family would have been on more episodes when he was little.
We love Manny.
We would have had him more on those early seasons when he was so tiny and adorable.
We won't happen again.
When I was on set of Little Rascals, I said,
you're doing it all wrong.
You could be getting so many more hours out of bug hall.
Bug hall.
You're missing precious alfalfa.
You could be swallowing more bubbles.
This movie could be two and a half hours.
But they wouldn't let me direct.
I tried to take it over.
They said, do your lines, sir.
I'm trying to find this vintage.
You can buy vintage beetle wigs.
I found when I was looking for merchandise.
What does that mean?
Not as opposed to?
I don't know.
Authentic is authentic.
I guess it was actually a licensed product.
Oh, you're talking.
So in the like, in the actual phenomena,
which I can only assume there was no mechanism yet to get them any money.
No, there was no way to do that.
For this.
So whatever bizarre like Texas oil man who despised the Beatles,
who like prayed for them to fall down dead.
But he was willing to make a buck with their name.
This looks like what Jimmy Angel's hair looks like.
He bought one of those wigs and just kept it up.
Kept mothballs out of it.
Kept it from being devoured by silverfish for 60 years.
I was heading somewhere with this.
Oh, the kind of thing.
Now, here's OK.
As we said, this is not done with the film quality
that we expect of the Monsters television show.
It's kind of in this weird.
It's, you know, if you've ever seen the Disneyland opening special,
which we talked about a long time ago, it's kind of the like.
It's not done live, but it's done with kind of like
as good as cameras could shoot outdoors at that time.
So things like get all bright and flare and it'll look like somebody
like jumps five feet in one single frame.
Like odd little bugs happen all the time.
And I say all this because this is a special that is largely padded by
let's just watch the shows that happen, you know, let's watch seals do tricks
and let's watch dolphins swim around at marine land.
But just the quality of camera, the water is just too bright.
The water is just getting hit by the sun far too much.
And you just all you just can't see and it's and it's we aren't.
We haven't figured out like, you know, Super Bowl angles yet.
Like the cameras are further back than the spectators.
So you're watching like a thousand yard away
footage of two shimmery of SEAL shows.
You can't make this is not very interesting to watch.
I'm going to be honest.
Imagine it's on an old TV.
We're watching it on like amazing technology.
Anyone's ever seen Munster's.
Right.
No way you saw the seals on your old ass black and white TV 60 years ago.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
No, that I looked at.
I hit a couple zoom forwards on those seal parts.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah.
I said, let's get a little more grandpa.
I did.
I did technically make it all the way through as opposed to the last Munster's thing.
All right.
Yeah.
For you, the movie.
I heard there were parts I thought about fully.
I kind of undersold it in the club through you that we just put out the
when the medley of songs about bananas.
I really was almost like, is this Munster's two for me?
Do I have to stop watching this special?
I am being driven insane.
I think like, yes, we have no bananas.
Horrible.
Then it becomes that banana fana fofana.
Yeah.
This is this is too much friend Anna Carmen Miranda comes out.
Jason is like Jason's writing down his notes.
Delightful.
Stupendous.
The name game.
That's what you're missing on his Apple music.
Yeah.
It's just he just listened to name games for lots of.
Jane, Jane, Boba.
Just put in anyone he likes.
Chapel, Chapel, Boba Apple.
This is we're going to be missing.
We're going to be doing Jason fan fiction.
And I think a lot of the time, it's understandable.
Let me let's talk though about something that.
All right.
I'll speak for myself of a lot of things in this.
I thought that the weaving together of animal stuff,
monster stuff was sometimes done not so gracefully.
And I think they found themselves searching for.
OK, whatever entity forced the monsters to be here,
maybe they could never really figure out the why
and how are the monsters compellingly combined with what we have in Marine land.
Then it all changes because grandpa has to go fly to rescue something.
I don't remember what.
Yeah, he's got like the flag.
He's getting the flag.
He's just going to help with a flag problem.
Yeah, there's a flag problem.
So all right.
So grandpa flies.
All right.
Well, is this some kind of like George Reeves Superman sort of like,
do we cut to him in front of the footage of sky?
No, no, no.
Well, he just leaves or he just leaves frame.
I don't think he even jumps and he just walks away.
He walks away.
They're not going to make Al Lewis like jump two centimeters.
No, kill him.
My God.
He's barely, barely hanging together.
Uh, but, but so he just kind of disappears off camera and then it cuts to,
he is up at the top of what seems to be like 150 foot pole.
It's so big.
It's Paul.
Crazy eye.
And when it first cuts to it, you're like, okay, this is some weird illusion.
I'm looking at a Batman thing, the way they would crawl up the side of a building.
They just like painted a line and then had a guy just kind of like crawl,
but he's just crawling on his hands and knees.
But then it cuts wider and the pole is so high.
And then the pole starts wobbling back and forth wildly, wildly.
This was crazy.
And I'm getting my head around like, okay, this must just be like something they had.
This must've been part of their show is that they would send divers up or stunt people up
to go wobble around in this pole.
And in this case, they put somebody in grandpa Munster makeup and did it
because like, Jesus Christ, this was, I loved this.
Yeah, this is the best part.
Yeah.
Grandpa wobble on a pole.
It's not, yes, it's not Al Lewis.
You can tell it's not Al Lewis.
No, certainly not.
And it's, it looks, you know, sometimes you see something that's very dangerous
and people make it look effortless and it's still impressive and still cool to watch.
This does not look effortless.
This looks effortful.
There are such like long unbroken takes of just this performer trying to like,
like keep their body up.
I'm trying to describe it where they hold the pole with their two hands
and then stick their legs out in the air.
And it looks so difficult.
And there's points where like, it seems like maybe they got caught.
They get like kind of stuck with their legs moving around and like, you're like, oh God,
oh, I guess, okay, they're all right.
All right.
Like there's a little court, I think, tying the Al Lewis impersonator to the pole.
Should be a hell of a racket to get into these days.
It is, yes, it is crazy to watch this.
And then they have to be dressed as grandpa monster in addition to this.
They got a cape to deal with.
They got to figure out where that cape is going.
Yes, and the cape keeps getting in the way.
Yeah, you do sense the cape is actually a problem.
The person's annoyed with the cape because it's getting in the way
as they try to like turn over on a pole.
There are some on-frame like, yes, like exasperated movements.
You can watch the guy mouth like, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah, because I could die.
If this cape fucks with, I'm going to die.
I'm going to fall and kill myself.
His leg is just in some kind of like little invisible loop or something.
Something, yeah.
He's barely got anything going on there.
Yes, this is the best part of it for sure.
Yeah, and it lasts a long time.
Yeah, it goes and goes, but I was not complaining.
Not in a bad way.
I'm just saying it's like a long stunt.
This to me is the forefather of all of the TGAF shows going to Disney World and saying,
we're just going to do the full Indiana Jones.
Oh, you're right, right, right.
Stunt sequence of the boulder.
Like, let's just, let's give ourselves a break here.
We have built-in production value with the theme park we went to.
Let's just let this, let's all, let's take a writing breather.
Let's have a couple extra sandwiches today and take a long nap.
Is it too late to get this stunt into Mission Impossible 8 coming out this summer?
Tom can go on the top of a pole dressed as a vampire
and do all these tricks as the pole wobbles back and forth.
I think this would have certainly happened in Dark Universe.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
That would have been good.
Yeah, what are we going to do?
Like the, like there's a, there's a cursed amulet up at the top of that pole.
Yeah.
Hey, let's get the mummy to fly up there.
Yeah, mummy goes up the pole.
And then he's got built-in, he's got the bandages so he can, he can like,
rappel down at the very least, slide down with the bandages.
Yeah, yeah.
But if not, did he become a mummy?
I haven't seen the Tom Cruise mummy.
No, I mean neither.
I don't think he becomes a mummy at the end, which is what you would want.
He's not the mummy.
Or was he going to be the mummy?
Or is it just about the mummy?
I don't know.
Is he hurting the mummy?
This is something Jason would talk authoritatively about,
but then it revealed he doesn't even know it either.
He's a Brendan Fraser mummy guy.
What are you saying about Barbara Stanwyck?
He's exploring the works of Barbara Stanwyck.
I'm exploring the works of the Dark Universe.
You mean you looked at the mummy Wikipedia?
Yeah, yes.
So I would hope Tom Cruise would become the mummy, but I don't know.
I don't remember.
Yeah.
Also like did he not want to be covered, his face covered because like an actor thing.
Is there any possibility that the success of Epic Universe
propels the Dark Universe back into and that a Tom Cruise navigating a confused franchise
that had to decide that the next movie isn't a part two,
that he goes back to whatever the mummy plan was going to be?
I think that would be funny.
They're like Johnny Depp back.
Tom Cruise back because of the success of this theme park, but I don't think so.
I would hope so.
I didn't realize the two of these lands are Johnny Depp oriented.
Yeah, that's correct.
The picture in Fantastic Beasts.
Grindelwald and...
And I mean, I guess, you know, Dark Universe, not specifically, but it could be.
Yeah, well, it's vaguely associated because of the photo.
Because of a picture.
Because of a picture that they took to promote.
I guess it's a stretch, but yeah.
But it's not.
Well, he's got a lot of theme park.
I mean, pirates.
Is there another one?
Isn't there something else I'm missing?
Maybe not.
There's no Edward Scissorhands land, I guess.
I don't believe so.
No, they never built a ride that's like the Chocolate River from the...
You don't get to meet his.
Hi, I'm Willy Wonka.
Hey, Lello.
I'm Willy Wonka, the chocolate guy.
So much better.
Oh, see, yeah, that Gene Wilder.
What a piece of shit.
What a...
We got to do this thing right.
We got to do it the way Roald Dahl wanted.
All right, here it is.
I'm Willy Wonka.
I got a bob haircut, I'm Willy Wonka.
Can I bring up an actor that's in this?
Yeah, yeah.
Named Sid Gould.
Do you know who I'm talking about?
I don't.
And who was Sid Gould in this?
He's like a guard and it's just the same gag.
Every Monsters is basically the same gag where a human looks at the Monsters and goes,
what are you, excuse me, I'm scared.
And then they pass out because they're so scary.
They must have been afraid of something else because they don't think of themselves as scary.
Yes, and a big thing with Monsters is they're situationally stupid about a lot.
They never seem to learn that, oh yeah, our appearance is a little different than everyone
else's. They never learn that.
And then they're all idiots in this.
Would you want them to?
No, I don't want it.
Because then the show's over.
I would say that all the Monsters are stupid and think it's a fish store.
Not a single one is really like, this is kind of an amusement park.
I know you're Monsters, but you've been in a store before.
You know that there's a place where there's a cashier with a cash register.
And then they go, why would a bunch of people be in an audience at a fish store?
Right, and they think, and then there's a part where I forget if it's Herman or somebody,
they go like, look at all the fish in their stores.
I mean, it's the ocean.
And then Lily goes, oh yeah, look at all the people.
And she points to the people in the stands.
She goes, there must be a sale.
You're like, are the Monsters this stupid?
This is insane.
They're not, okay, I know that they are Monsters, but they aren't,
the backstory, as far as I know, is not that they landed from space.
They aren't Monsters also from Mars.
You know what the ocean is, right?
They had the ocean in, are the Monsters old?
They talk about this in the special.
They do.
They say, how old is your grandpa?
And then she says, he's like 62, give or take a thousand years.
And that's the joke.
Well, even that, they had the ocean a thousand years ago.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe there's some Bible timeline.
Maybe they're also fundamentalist Christians.
They'd make a joke about Jonah and the whale in this as well.
So they are.
All right.
So we learn.
But it's a joke.
This is another problem I have with it.
Sometimes with the writing of the Monsters is that grandpa goes,
I knew a guy who lives inside a whale and his name was Jonah.
And then Lily's like, oh, grandpa, you're joking.
And you're like, but sometimes he's not joking about knowing
like an old, some old thing, historical figure or whatever.
Like, so it's inconsistent.
Sometimes are they saying that the, that there were,
did they go back to the Bible times?
Well, grandpa might have the crucifixion of Christ.
Yes.
Grandpa Munster was at the crucifixion of Christ.
The rabbit.
That looks like it hurts.
Glad it's not me.
They've been for the grace of you know who.
Check, please.
They've been for the grace of his dad.
This is more Woody Allen.
Yeah, we're a lot more, I'm a lot more.
Yeah.
You're rearing me into Woody too.
I feel like, yeah, yeah, I don't know.
Maybe that's a Mel Gibson's passion of Christ too.
I guess they show the crucifixion of the first one.
Maybe there'll be a flashback.
Yeah, they blew all the good material.
Yeah.
Unless you do it as a sequel where it happens again.
Maybe, or you get flashbacks.
They're back for more.
This time it's personal.
You can do some good retcons when you flash back to the first movie
and then you show like in the crowd there was like,
grandpa Munster was there and you didn't show him in the first movie.
So you can kind of add things that way.
When he thought he saw the devil in the form of that creepy baby,
he was actually looking at grandpa Munster.
Yeah.
What are we here for, gladiator fights?
This guy's going to betray you, Jesus.
I'm telling you, three wooden tees.
He's up to no good.
Sid Gould.
Oh yeah.
He's the guard.
He's afraid of the Munsters.
So I'm looking, he's, you know, he's in stuff.
He's in love boat.
He's in all these different old things.
He was on police academy four was the last thing he had as a credit.
And then I scroll down and I see 44 episodes of here's Lucy.
And then I scroll down 49 episodes of the Lucy show.
Who is Sid Gould?
Man, I made it out of,
I didn't tell you that there's an episode of the Lucy show called Lucy at Marine land.
I was like, let me try to skate by this one.
No, no, here we are.
He is cousin by marriage to Lucille Ball.
His cousin, Gary Morton was Lucy's husband.
And so he was on all these little bit parts in the family.
He's in the family.
So he got all these little bit parts on all these different Lucy shows.
Wow.
Yes.
And if you want to drag the episode length out even more,
and I won't even get into more.
Hold on.
Now I got to find the exact year because I want to be.
I got to say, I'm really, I'm really happy that one thing in Jason's absence is that the
percentage of hosts uninterested in talking about Lucy all the goddamn time goes up to 50%.
As opposed to a mere 33.
It just really helps my numbers.
There's more pressure, right?
We're kind of at logger, it's kind of like, like we're at a perfect tie,
which presents its own conflict.
Well, wait till you hear this credit.
He played Zumba on the Paul Winchell show in 1953.
Zumba.
Zumba must have run into Jerry Mahoney.
And Knucklehead Smith.
Now what I realized by watching an episode,
scrolling through an episode of Paul Winchell show for the first time is that
Knucklehead Smith's voice very similar to Tigger.
It's almost the same thing.
It's basically the same thing.
So Tigger and Knucklehead Smith have the same voice.
That's a sort of interesting fact.
That's sort of an interesting thing.
If you know Tigger in the old days.
It's interesting assuming that you think anything about Knucklehead Smith is interesting.
Well, I think the audience thinks Knucklehead Smith is interesting.
I bet they like Knucklehead Smith a lot more than Madam.
I bet there's a lot more Knucklehead Smith fans out there.
I just don't know if Knucklehead Smith has been around and discussed enough.
I think people are less fine.
I think they like him initially more than Madam.
I do think there's a lot of hate for Madam.
We're still in only the third episode where Knucklehead Smith has come up.
One of them is Club 3.
People haven't heard that.
Yeah.
I don't like what's happening here.
I don't like that Knucklehead Smith is becoming a recurring presence on the show.
I'd like to try to turn this ship around if I could.
There's a section of the Paul Winchell show where Knucklehead Smith and Jerry Mahoney are
sitting at a talk show, like a late night talk show desk.
And it says Tootsie Roll on the front because I assume they were sponsoring them.
And then they interview people together.
Which I use pretty good.
I was enjoying watching this.
Now, you told me that, and then I thought there was more story to go.
So I just said, okay.
It's a ventriloquist talk show.
It's a kid's show.
It looks like the Bozo show with a big kid audience, but then they do little skits.
And they have human performers.
But then there's a part where the dummies interview people.
And again, I didn't present this as a big story.
I'm just explaining to you what the Paul Winchell show was like
because you'll need to know when we do future Paul Winchell show content.
This is we can't.
We're already we're already covered.
We already do too much of the of like famous old shows.
Now we're starting to delve into.
Look, I guess.
Okay.
Well, see, I know I brought up Sea Hunt, but I'm not saying that cleared out Sea Hunt for me.
I'm not saying we know we haven't investigated Sea Hunt.
That's true.
You think there's a Sea Hunt episode where there's a ventriloquist dummy?
I hope there's a haunted fish, like the ventriloquist dummy or like a merman.
If there was an episode where he like where Mike Nelson
shatters a ventriloquist dummy against a cave wall, then now I'm interested.
A ventriloquist dummy was used in the 1959 Sea Hunt episode
Monte Cristo to portray Mike Nelson when he was thrown into the sea.
Okay, we know that actors can't just be thrown into the sea.
So maybe you use a dummy, right?
But a dummy equals a six foot dummy.
Maybe not a little ventriloquist dummy.
That must be wrong.
They just tossed a little dummy.
That must just be a regular dummy.
Maybe it was a wide enough shot that they figured as long as something's going,
as long as you see limbs in a head, you're good to go.
That's so funny.
Before the development of stunt doubles that are the size of the actor.
This is cut to a dummy.
And this is the people, the thing one, viewers are idiots.
Thing two, no one will ever watch this again, do whatever the fuck gets it done.
This in the IMDb, it says it just refers to it as a dummy.
So when two crew members are throwing Mr. Nelson into the sea,
a dummy is obviously being used because Mr. Nelson hits some shallows before diving
and hitting an immovable object from a significant height,
which would otherwise result in injury or death.
And they just left it in a dummy hitting the rocks.
So this isn't, they are not trying to pass off a small ventriloquist,
they aren't trying to pass off a knucklehead Smith size dummy as hulking tan Lloyd Bridges.
If they really sculpted a ventriloquist dummy that was like jacked, like a shirtless dummy,
what if Jerry Mahoney was jacked?
Yeah, I don't know how many more just standard dummies I can look at and pretend to care,
but I would like a really ripped.
Who is the hunkiest dummy of all time?
That's a good question.
Is it probably a newer dummy, I'm guessing?
Because I don't think of any dummies as being big hunks.
Attractive ventriloquist dummy.
It's also, it's just filling in attractive ventriloquist,
which I believe there may be no results for as well.
Well, that's why they need to distract you whenever you look at something else.
Maybe a young Terry Fader.
What Terry Fader looked like when he was young.
Okay, so I Googled attractive ventriloquist dummy,
and now I'll turn around my laptop and show you Google results that are 30
of the most horrifying images I've ever seen.
And they aren't, none of them are what we're looking for, like cut.
It's all just a bunch of different types of scary fucking dummies.
Why? These results make no sense.
If we had a dummy final four in April.
No, no, some of this show has to be about theme parks, for God's sake.
April? April's a far, you're barely even, it's a timeline.
Is it the issue that that's not the issue?
I know you think it's too much dummy content, but I'm just saying like,
if we really, what if we determine the hunkiest dummies of all time?
Start with a field of 64.
When's Jason going to be back?
When can I get a movie going again?
By the way, I just clicked one of the results of this,
of attractive ventriloquist dummy.
Look at this eBay result.
Antique, 1938, Frank Marshall pro ventriloquist figured.
What do you mean?
Oh, Frank Marshall is a different, we looked, oh, I said this on the,
I said this one on your episodes, we went there.
Frank Marshall is a dummy maker, but not that Frank Marshall.
Oh, it's a brand.
It's a different Frank Marshall.
Okay.
Cause I was, I almost fell out of my chair too.
Cause I was like, oh my God, Frank Marshall from the age of five was making dummies or
something, but that is not the case.
The different Frank Marshall, who was a dummy maker.
If we have a new.
It's a new sounding Marshall.
Yeah, I think I might've listened to this and did one of my classic auto erase.
It was being erased as it was occurring.
Dummy.
Hoping that it would never come up again.
And here I walked right into it again.
Yeah, I know there's been, you know what?
There's been a lot of talk of making us as action figures on this show, which I
still would love to do one day.
But what if somebody were to make us as ventriloquist dummies?
What if somebody were to make you and Jason as ventriloquist dummies?
Do not, I don't care who you are.
I don't care if you're Frank Marshall.
I do not want to see myself.
If you're Frank Marshall himself, other one.
I don't want to see myself as a ventriloquist dummy.
Okay.
I guess not now, not in April.
What if you're Jack though?
All right.
Sharon, you sold me in one note.
You got me back on board.
What have we missed about this thing?
So we got to the poll.
I wrote down the phrase, maybe we can get a markdown whale.
The special is sponsored by Minute Maid and Hi-C.
I like at the beginning, we love our variety show intros.
Here's everybody who's going to be on the show.
The Monsters, the new Christy Minstrels.
But I like that there's nobody else.
So they just have to credit the animals.
Yes.
So then you just get big titles coming at you and it says,
Walruses.
Right.
Saw a fish.
And then one of them, it just says Monsters.
Yeah.
Huh?
That's a real insult to the kind of fish that it is.
I don't think it was just a monster.
No.
That's really insulting.
Yeah, somebody classified them as sea life if they're in marine land.
I get it, maybe if they were in the sea and they saw something
they never saw before, was never discovered.
I think whoever had to make that credit sequence just looked at it like,
just put Monsters.
Let's get this done, put Monsters.
We didn't talk about, they did the mermaids like Disneyland to some degree.
Oh, okay.
There's mermaids in there, but the mermaids were swimming under the water
because there's a part where they go and look at the sea life under,
like it's the living seas or something, or I don't know, an aquarium.
Doesn't have to be Disney.
And then there's mermaids where they have like a big air tank on the back
and they're swimming or whatever.
And then there's some joke, it's Marilyn and Eddie are watching them.
And then he said something about like, you wouldn't want these as a pet.
And Eddie's like, grandpa would like one of these as a pet or something.
Like, okay.
You.
Yeah.
And then grandpa would like to kidnap a mermaid.
Uh, and then, so I guess, yeah, I guess they had some like fantastical stuff
because he was just thinking of a Marine land.
It's very straight ad.
There's big fish tank seals.
There's fun, the shows, but there is not like an imaginative quality,
but like, this is like, at least there were mermaids here.
Yeah, that's pretty, that's pretty theme parky.
Yeah.
Right.
This is more theme parky than everything else.
Well, they kept going in this direction too,
because just a little other Marine land history,
it passed through a lot of owners and among the owners,
Hannah Barbera, it was Hannah Barbera's Marine land.
Right.
At one point.
So you could meet who's the shark, Jabberjaw.
Yeah.
I think there's a photo of some kid getting their face bitten off by Jabberjaw.
Yeah, that's really good.
You know, that's a big shark.
I don't want my head in its mouth.
So, you know, so yeah, it was not just like a clinical aquarium facility.
They had their fun.
Sure.
Especially that pole show.
My God.
Yeah, that pole show is interesting.
I wonder, I wonder if, I wonder what that is even called.
I wonder like, was it like one guy like that guy
who would get shot out of the rocket at Disneyland?
Oh, that's right.
I wonder if it was like a one person specialty.
Yeah, maybe.
Was doing pole shit, high up pole shit and then dressing up as a vampire.
Or it was a number of underpaid 19 year olds.
Could be.
Yes, they could send somebody up there one day.
Here's what you got to do.
We built that pole to pay for the pole costs.
Yeah.
We need constant 19 year olds up there.
They should have made Al do it.
He might have been able.
Well, he seemed to.
Well, as I said, he made it a long time.
Yeah.
He was 45.
He was like 45 years old here.
Oh, I'm fine.
Yeah.
You could climb up that pole.
I could climb up the pole.
I'm sure there was pole, like some sort of pole work in the vaudeville days.
Yeah.
Certainly something.
Probably.
Right?
That's why they built it into the special.
Right.
I heard that he had a vaudeville pole act.
And so we better devote a lot of real estate to that.
And then they got to the day and he chickened out.
Yeah.
Well, that's why his career never took off after.
Yep.
Yeah.
He was not a team player.
All downhill besides restaurant ownership.
That's a high, high.
What else?
Seal show that's hard to watch.
Yeah.
I mean, they eventually, oh, there's like a surfing dog.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
Probably dog didn't like it, but yeah, that's fun to watch.
I wrote down the phrase, idiots who dive badly.
I'm sure.
Yeah.
There's like a little like goofy show they do.
Like a bunch of knuckleheads who bump into each other.
Yes.
Yeah.
Which is fun.
Fools.
The new Christy Minstrel sing fake underwater in a fish tank.
Right.
Saturday night.
We'll get together on a Saturday night.
Again, things like this really make you understand why the Beatles were important.
There was a way to be filled of exciting music.
Yeah.
People with even 2% sex appeal.
That's true.
It's the most neutered, sprayed down people.
Yeah.
I've said this before, but there's these YouTube clips of just every song that was number one on
the charts, starting in whenever the charts.
So you just go through the 40s and it's like every time the song would change, it changes.
So you hear all the songs that were popular in America and man, is it dry up until the
Beatles show up.
Like once in a while you get a song and then obviously Elvis is there and then there's
some stuff you know, but man, there's some like, you're like, this was some song about
like a carnival we've never heard for 12 weeks on the charts.
This is 1948.
Now we're getting away with this because Jason would be livid.
Carnival caper.
It's been a year on the top of the charts.
By Slimmy Billy Morgan.
Yeah.
What was the number one song of 1946?
I mean, there is holiday stuff.
I don't want to know anymore about the song Dr. Lawyer Indian Chief.
Oh yeah.
And that happens a lot too where you go, I've never heard this song.
It's problematic.
I don't know why, but it is problematic.
And yeah, then the Beatles show up and you go, oh man, like they really changed the deal.
Obviously the people that influenced them really changed the deal, but they weren't
as popular sadly.
I'm like your Chuck Berry.
You know what I'm saying?
These girls who look like walruses, they need to cut it out.
I can't understand a word they're saying.
Can't they play good old fashioned music like Old Buttermilk Sky by Kay Kaiser and
his orchestra?
Yes.
What year?
With Michael Douglas and the Campus Kids.
That's the number one song in December 1946.
Yeah.
These are truly, that is a fun, like put it on.
These are long videos on YouTube and you just go through all these songs you've never heard of.
Old Buttermilk Sky was nominated for an Oscar too.
This was cleaned up.
Some of it's good.
I'm not saying it's all bad.
This was the, what's the Shallows of its day.
Yeah, yeah.
There's songs like, sometimes we'll come across things like this.
And I, you know, I think Jason enjoys the kind of the identity of the liking the old
timey stuff.
But I think if you like, if we made him sit down and listen to all of the number one songs
of 1946, I think by the time we made it to Old Buttermilk Sky, whatever that is, he'd
be like, fine, I don't like this.
You got me.
To prove it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'd break him down.
Here's what it actually was.
Or he comes out more.
Yeah, it could be either or.
It's a song that described my dreams.
Right.
Sometimes I hope I wake up and the whole sky's full of buttermilk.
Yeah.
It's probably that second one.
Yeah, I'm mortal.
All right.
Let me, let's, let's veer to the exit here a little bit with this.
So they, they end up, the monsters end up leaving because they, they don't want any
more fresh air and they drive away and they drive away in an unsafe manner where it seems
like Eddie's going to fall out of the car.
Yes.
There's a lot of unsafe driving.
And they don't get a second take of that.
Yeah.
And that's that.
But in case we never revisit Marine Land, do you know this, the end of the Marine Land
story?
I don't actually.
Do you know why it's not there anymore?
So they passed through a lot of different owners.
It was jointly owned by Taft, which owned all those Kings Island parks,
and that's why they had a rare thing.
And Kroger's Markets, they were together owned it.
20th Century Fox owned it at one point.
The people who owned Hollywood Park Racetrack owned it.
And you know, it like thrived decently in that time.
I think it fell by the time Disney was getting real solid with pirates and Haunted Mansion
and SeaWorld obviously really cut into its business whenever SeaWorld opened up.
So like on the decline, but they still did amazing.
They built this giant tower even higher than that pole.
A 240 foot observation tower, which must have been, again, having been on that property,
those views must have been unreal.
This is like, this is paradise.
This is so it's crazy.
Get down.
If you're ever wandering around, it's such a great place.
But anyways, and then they installed this thing called the Baja Reef Exhibit where you
could like snorkel and actually like go through, like they themed a little like rock environment.
So they're adding stuff and then and it's all kind of on the backs of
pre SeaWorld's two killer whales, Orky and Corky.
They're the stars of the show.
And eventually like laws are passed that you can't go capture any more of these whales.
So to see any in captivity becomes like such a rare commodity.
And the fact that they had them was such a big deal.
Right.
But then SeaWorld in like 87.
Well, I don't know.
Okay.
At some point, SeaWorld is taken over by a hardcore publishing new owner and they are
a lot more aggressive about the expansion of SeaWorld than whoever the previous owners were.
And they know that SeaWorld and opening new SeaWorlds is dependent on having
whales that you can call Shamu in any of their parks.
And now there's these laws in place, right?
They can't just go capture a new Shamu.
So they're looking around.
How are we going to get a Shamu?
Well, I got Corky and Orky over there.
Marineland.
Maybe we can go, let's see what we can hook up with them.
So they go to Marineland and they say, hey, we see you're struggling a little bit here.
Times have been better.
Would you be interested in maybe selling us Corky and Orky?
And they say, no, no, they're the fabric of this place.
That's why this place works and it's so important to us.
And we would never sell you Corky and Orky.
We would, however, sell you the entire park with Corky and Orky,
with the provision that Corky and Orky would stay here
because it's where they live and it's where they're comfortable.
And so would you, SeaWorld, want to buy all of Marineland?
And they said, sounds all right to us.
Very good.
And there was a little bit of concern about this plan
because this is a big tourist boon for the Rancho Palos Verdes area.
And it's a big centerpiece of why anybody would go there and spend money in that town.
So SeaWorld, you do promise to keep the park open and in good condition, right?
Yes, of course.
We are no nefarious whale purchasers, you can trust us.
We will keep it open and it'll be a vibrant part of the city forever.
One month later, oh, sorry, looked into it, closing it.
It's just going to be a lot of upkeep.
We're not going to do it.
We're closing up shop.
People were very, very mad about this news.
And then forgive me, I'm a little bit confused about the timeline here
because I know that they just immediately closed it.
But also something they did was in the middle of the night,
load up Corky and Orky and ship them out of there, send them over to SeaWorld.
They stole the whales.
SeaWorld bought Marineland and did a killer whale heist.
Holy shit.
Yeah, that's one of the most nefarious things I don't think we've ever run into
in theme park ownership.
So it was just a handshake deal, basically?
Because it would be a legal thing if they said, well,
this is what you have to do in order to buy it.
Or maybe it was kind of on paper, but there was some clause about,
as long as it's reasonably in good condition for you to even start repairing.
And they were like, it's not, can't do it, bye, sorry, whales are moving.
We got them.
And then not only that, they took, this is so crazy to me,
they poured concrete into the drains so that no one could ever open a new park there again.
They salted the earth.
Which nothing would grow.
Yes, yeah.
Wow.
This is crazy mob shit.
That's so brutal-y.
Yeah, I know in a new way that, I mean, it's only partially a new way because we, you know,
I guess stealing killer whales in the middle of the night seems far from the course for them.
But yeah, they concreted the land.
No water park can ever be here again.
And then they still had like a little bit of time to go before they were going to close it.
And people were so mad at them for all of this stuff, rightfully so,
like the community was really upset.
And then they were like, all right, we're just closing it now then,
like way earlier than they were going to.
And they said, why?
And they said, well, these angry, these residents, they're such animals.
They've been sending in bomb threats.
Whoa, whoa.
You got bomb threats here at Marine land?
Who do you think made the threats?
Don't worry about that.
We got them.
And we definitely got them.
They were real.
We got real bomb threats.
This is not an alibi to try to steal all the whales.
Nobody ever found out who made the threat.
So they stole whales, concrete in the drains, made up bomb threats in order to just like
scorch this place and never deal with it again.
That has to be the tip of the iceberg for like SeaWorld behave.
I mean, we know some of it, but like, I wonder if there's a whole like
shitty thing SeaWorld that episode.
I mean, I'm sure there is, but I'm worried.
Yeah, you know, we were in our SeaWorld episode.
We ran into things that we had to bleep because we found them so disturbing.
So disturbing.
Yeah.
So I think we might very well be.
Maybe that's too, too dark.
Could be.
Jesus, they salted the earth.
SeaWorld stole the whales.
Do we know how long the whales live?
Right into the eyes of the old owners.
So they could never, they put concrete in the, down the throats of the old owners.
I'm picturing like follow that bird too.
They're like, they like painted a blue, like big bird in a cage.
They weren't even black and white whales.
Right.
They had to put a bunch of paint on them.
They painted them like Shamu.
Do we know where they went?
I don't think one of them died kind of soon after horribly.
And, but one of them is one of them still alive.
Really?
It's all happened in 87, but either Corky or Orky is still one of the SeaWorld Shamus.
So there's still Shamu.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's interesting.
Because that's the deal with Shamu, right?
You just, there just won't be any new Shamus.
I think so.
Those old Shamus are grandfathered in.
Yeah.
But they really, their clock is ticking, I think.
Again.
How long do those?
Trump SeaWorld on the White House lawn.
Oh yeah.
Shamu will be back.
We're bringing America back into Shamu's doing flips in the.
He's going to be on the boat.
He's the new bald eagle.
Hunting for the new Shamus in a full captain's outfit.
Hey, I see one over there.
In a big, like the fisherman and the.
Yeah.
Or he's dressed like a sea hunt.
He's dressed like.
Oh yeah.
Kurt Douglas looking for Shamus.
Being president, more boring than I remembered.
I will be starring in a syndicated action show.
I will be shirtless.
Everything's on the table.
You never know.
Choppy seas await.
But anyway, that's what, so that place, it just, having been concreted, it just sat vacant
for like, from 87 to like 95 and they kept the tower up.
So imagine like that kind of tower that's at knots or magic mountain.
Yeah.
They're inaccessible, just rusting away.
You could just go into the Baja reef drained.
Like it's, you could just walk around and do graffiti and an empty aquarium.
And that's the sad.
Yeah.
Once a thriving hub of production, this place turned into a, into a real graveyard until
the fine people at Terra Naya took over who have merely been the target of a multimillion
dollar lawsuit by employees alleging misconduct and overworking.
Okay.
Any other things.
So besides that, so it's still not the due to the sea world stuff.
Terra Naya will never lawsuit or no lawsuit.
They'll never be responsible for all the worst things ever to happen on that land.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, I, you know, that might, we, maybe we won't do much more Marine land, but when you
did, you did say Lucy Marine land.
So I don't know.
We'll see.
You did say it.
I did.
I mean, I, I felt like, like, hopefully you ultimately regarded that as a show of good
faith that I can hide that information from you.
However, is my interest to do Lucy and Marine land very high?
I can't say that it is.
Is Sid Gould in it?
That's what I have to ask.
Is Sid Gould or her husband, Gary Martin involved?
Get me in.
I already did Munsters down there.
I know the directions.
You don't even have to send me a call sheet.
I'm well, I'm, I'm familiar.
I'll camp there.
I know a cave I can hide in.
There's a, there's a, they got a spare reef.
I can spend the night in.
Isn't that nice of Lucy to throw Gary's cousin a bone?
Yeah.
You know?
Shows you the kind of lady.
80 different episodes of like bit parts.
No one else wanted to hire poor Sid.
She's a classy dame.
Ah, Gary's annoying me about Sid again.
Just make him the postman.
Will it shut you up?
Gary.
Another Sid episode.
Fucking hack.
Whatever.
Untalented fuck.
If it prevents another Gary bitch fest.
Gary always whines in the worst way.
Gary, one of these days, I'm going to fill your lungs up with concrete.
At least Desi was a man.
He'd scream and be mean.
Gary just whimpers like a little dog.
It's pathetic.
He's more pet than husband.
All right.
Well, I, yeah, all right.
Lucy in Marineland to be negotiated.
But for now, you've heard about this.
Follow along with us.
Watch it on 2B or wherever the hell it is.
And hey, you survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
It's also where you can every month have the opportunity to suggest
even older television show topics, have them picked by Mike and then handily lose the bowl.
More if you want to pick Gary Morton as a topic.
That is now that we've talked about.
What's the one that can get less than 1% of the vote?
Gary Lucy's second husband, Gary Morton, who I think I'm the only one who's ever thought
that I think Lucy wasn't that thrilled with him.
And the thought of him is like, ah, he's fine.
Because of interviews I've seen with the two of them.
That might be originating for me.
You know why?
Because I stopped listening at the beginning of the sentence.
Well, if you want to hear more, Gary Morton vote for him as a topic for club three.
And let's see if we can get that to the world record of club three of zero
of the ocean where only Mike Nelson on a sea hunt could find it.