Five, four, three, two, one.
Dude, are we on? Dude, what the fuck? You're dropping shit? What's that? Are we on or not?
Come on, what's this fucking shit, man?
Dude, Mike, what the fuck? I don't know, cause I'm here like, am I fucking talking to Jason or am I talking to Stu?
What the fuck's going on?
We're on, we're on.
Which microphone?
All the microphones are on.
Any? Any of them?
Dude, tell me, point to the one I'm supposed to be fucking using.
The one in front of you.
Oh, okay, hey, all right, wait, we are here, it's January 1st, 2025, let's, fuck, oh, sorry, let's go, baby.
There's a little taste of, stylistically, I think we inhabited the genre very nicely there.
For this first episode of, hey, it's first night, second gate.
And if some people are hearing, if they have nothing else to do, if they don't have a New Year's party to go to, which would be me, what with a new baby, I won't be anywhere.
You weren't last night at Universal Studios Hollywood's New Year's celebration, Eve?
Well, we're recording this in the future, but I would put a lot of money at the Commerce Casino on me missing Eve.
I don't think I'm going to make it up to Eve.
Are you going to try to hit Eve?
You got an older kid, you could slip out to Eve.
I thought about, I think I even texted Evan Susser, I said, should we go to Eve this year?
The New Year's Eve celebration.
Ooh, a double daddy bash.
I thought though, I guess my pass isn't the best pass at Universal Studios, so it's not, it's blocked out on New Year's Eve.
And I was like, am I going to spend $200 to experience Eve?
And is Eve in the park or is Eve in City Walk?
In the park.
Okay. And what is Eve? Now Eve is in the past.
Sorry, Eve is happening.
Do you think maybe somebody's listening to this at Eve though?
Maybe they're at Eve, but on the way out they got us in the AirPods.
I don't know.
It's possible, yeah.
What possibly have you and Susser already, first of all, if you're there, look for them, but then...
I think that Eve is just that they set up a couple DJ booths at Universal Hollywood.
And then they do a countdown. I think that's it.
And how likely is it that they play the things that we always joke about them play? Do we think it's still Daddy Yankee?
Gasolina.
Oh yeah, it's Gasolina.
At this point I would hope it's Gasolina. I would go nuts for Gasolina.
They're kind of the theme songs. It's those in Hooray for Hollywood are the music of that and Happy.
I would hope they had the espresso radio at it.
Not the Baudier one, the radio at it.
Why that song?
Huh?
Why that song specifically?
That's a little current, Jason.
Do you think it's too current?
For Universal Studios? Yeah, I don't know. I think they're going to find out about espresso in about 11 years.
Oh, okay.
It's about Universal's pace.
Was that on your Spotify rap?
Yeah, it was number one.
I think it was.
Was it number one?
I don't use it a lot. I don't use Spotify a lot.
Okay, Apple Music more?
No, I don't have Apple Music.
I feel like my local music collection and YouTube, I feel like I just look up songs.
It's still local music? You still have files?
Yeah, I still have files. They're kind of spread out.
It's kind of a rarity.
How do you listen to them then on the phone?
Because my Apple Music will say you can search for just like the Apple Music catalog or you can go to your own files.
Are you using that on your phone if you're listening to your local file, your actual files?
No.
On your computer?
I downloaded albums, like purchased albums or files if I'm just playing it off my laptop.
Say you're trying to listen to a new pornographer's song right now on your phone.
What would you use to listen to it?
I have the albums all local on my phone.
Program is what I'm saying.
This is what we would have done in the old days when Scott wasn't here a month ago.
The Apple Music app.
I think I'm not here now.
It is Apple Music app.
Who was Apple Music?
iTunes. What you used to call iTunes. I don't know. I still call it iMessage when referring to texting.
Here's how I think it's going to go is that I did that Club 3 where I responded to everything and then that's going to swing it all the way back to the next month becomes like Mike and Jason discuss the file structures of where all of their personal assets are on their desktops.
Do you use Apple Music?
And you said, no, I don't have Apple Music.
And then we got to the point where you said, I am listening on Apple Music.
I thought you meant the subscriptions.
I don't have the subscription service.
The music app, I guess you say.
Yes.
And how's your storage doing?
How many?
Storage is OK.
Specific stats on that.
I don't want to take a lot of time, but like how many how many gigabytes could fit on your phone and how much currently is available?
I got a problem. I got storage problem.
Me too. That's kind of why I'm wondering.
Well, I'm I'm I'm careful with that nowadays.
I'm paying for Google Storage and Apple Storage.
I don't like it.
I avoided it for years.
But I just kind of have to because I I'm at texting.
It's like 10 or 20 gigs.
I feel like like the messages themselves.
The messages themselves.
Yeah, the messages.
Sure.
Between the messages themselves, years of messages and then photos and videos in there.
Yeah. Well, and I assume that you guys are both sending each other like daily updates on how much movie theater candy you're buying from CBS.
Like every day there's three photos.
Well, 4K video of it.
Like very good.
Yes.
Unboxing multiple gigabytes of the Twizzler boxes and the snow caps.
Yeah. Don't just send me a photo of the runs.
Send me the runs coming out of the box.
I want to see that pour out, baby.
Right. A selfie.
I take the selfie stick to the Burbank movie theater.
I buy a ticket that I don't use.
I go inside.
I buy multiple boxes of candy, giant sodas.
And then I take 4K video.
Well, if you're in downtown Burbank, you got to go to the bulk candy store.
Well, that's true.
If you have a movie ticket before or after, you get a discount.
Yeah.
That's a good tip.
I was worried that we would get 15 full minutes into the new year without you guys discussing specific Burbank area stores.
Thank God we're starting 2025 right.
You have emboldened.
I guess because of Scott Free Weeks, I think we've been emboldened in a lot of ways.
I'm experiencing a torrent already.
For example, there really wasn't an intro to this second gate.
We just started going.
You know, we just started that cursing at the top.
We kind of went in the club three minutes.
That's the kind of thing that never would have happened but two months ago.
Imagine starting the episode with a bit.
We're in a whole other universe now.
The possibilities have been unlocked.
We're through the matrix.
That's right.
We look at the whole new show.
That's the thing I did.
Wait, you're telling me we wouldn't have done the thing I started?
Did you get the question?
I actually didn't get the question.
You phrased it as confusingly as possible.
Jamie Kennedy knew your style a bit at the start of the episode, but then you said...
Yes, no, I got that.
We wouldn't have done the thing that I did.
I got the Jamie Kennedy bit and then I thought you were going to switch over to an actual like,
hey, I'm so and so and so and so and so and so.
So I missed.
I missed that.
It's the crazy electric energy of you guys talking about Burbank stores and being emboldened
that led to me not saying our names, which are Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson, and Jason Sheridan.
That's true.
You're right that I didn't say the names.
I'm as confused as the PA handling the Walkies on a Jamie Kennedy.
That's as confused as you can be.
That seems to be the crux of a lot of what went wrong with this broadcast,
is they claim they had walkie issues.
Yes.
Yeah.
There was a lot of blame to go around.
There was in the aftermath of what we're talking about today, there was simultaneous blame
and excuses of no, no, no, that was the plan.
That's what we wanted it to be.
But I guess before we can dissect what happened in the aftermath, we should talk about what this is,
which, by the way, I mean, we had just a brief text exchange that was like,
is there anything New Year's oriented to do and quickly realized that's kind of a finite area.
This episode's out on January 1st.
You want to do something?
And then I realized, wait a minute, what better way to kick off 2025
than with a horrible way to kick off 2013, which was this special, which is a very online thing.
There was a cut down that was on YouTube and then Twitter.
Oh, remember those days.
But this went around really quickly.
This was how January 1st, 2013 started.
And by January 4th, host Jamie Kennedy was in the New York Times explaining himself
and saying things like, I didn't stab anybody, OK?
What do you want?
Why are you mad at me?
What did I do?
I just tried to have some fun on TV.
Anyway, what this is, is this crazy special that aired heading into 2013
on Los Angeles local television called First Nights 2013 with Jamie Kennedy.
This was a Los Angeles local TV disaster.
It was on KDOC, which is just kind of regular ass TV.
Sort of not so much around or it's like format shifted today.
Specifically an Orange County based religious station.
It is today religious. It wasn't religious at the time.
OK, because I was watching this and I was like, this aired on a religious station?
So I think I missed the ownership changes.
It's not that crazy, yes, because that would be really insane
is if they went to kind of like, you know, Ma and Pa churchgoer and said,
we want to create a wholesome piece of entertainment that the whole family can enjoy.
Something to keep the kids up till midnight.
I think we'll do some Bible verses if we have time,
but we have already booked Bone Thugs in Harmony
and they do not intend on self censoring.
But no, it's not that crazy.
But anyway, just just to get out the full broad strokes of what this is.
I don't think a lot of people were paying attention to this as it was airing.
But like one person was and did a cut down that was online fairly quickly
because this was a live special that was fraught with technical errors
and dead air and profanities and absolutely bombed jokes
and off key music, very sloppy musical performances.
One techno crane really trying to hold down the fort,
trying to go back and forth in the six feet of range that it has,
like doing a lot of heavy lifting to prove that this thing has any production value.
Because otherwise I would say this is a 90 minute broadcast in which not one element worked.
I guess I agree.
There's not like a pleasant, oh good, they nailed that in the whole thing, in the whole 90 minutes.
No, it's down to like the frame rates are weird.
Like they throw to like little sketches and then those don't look right and they don't start right.
There's like black and glitching before they begin.
And then you're into the meat of the sketch and like a racist costume is being worn.
This is an absolute like content gutter situation,
which hey, well, let's start the year off right.
It seems like the way to begin.
We're starting the year off with a curse and not the profanity you would find in this special.
Literally like an Imhotep style curse.
Yes, both curses are definitely part of this.
Death is only the beginning of the year.
And we're here with Shannon Elizabeth, who you kissing at midnight.
And Shannon Elizabeth who tries to deflect to the many projects she has going on.
She a human being with interests and they're like, OK, cool, but let's talk about your boobies though.
Shannon Elizabeth who shows up for about 30 seconds and does not make any return appearances in this special.
I hope she was safe at home by midnight so she could not be accosted or slobbered on.
Yeah, I hope she was safe and guarded away from the premises.
Fingers crossed.
Bridget too from the girls next door as well.
I'm worried about all their safety.
I didn't look up if everyone involved in this is still alive.
Well, Bridget is.
I hope they survive the night.
Bridget is.
She's doing a podcast with Holly from Girls Next Door.
Yes, a theme park enthusiast.
Holly is a big theme park enthusiast.
Would she do this if she's got a podcast to promote?
I don't know, it's a good question.
Would she do it?
Probably.
Somebody told her.
Would it help if we told her that at this point every single episode has like 25 minutes of weird creepy sex talk?
Increasingly unhinged.
Yeah, but if we frame it in the right way that it's more about, again, it's band kid energy.
God, not even the confidence of theater kids.
No, not at all.
That's different.
Yeah, that metaphor doesn't work from the high school.
I went to because all the band kids were like cool and hooking up with each other.
The band kids were?
The tuba player and the timpani's are all.
I think the band kids were all smoking weed and playing a hacky sack and listening to Dave Matthews.
Damn.
That's one of the coolest kids I've ever heard.
I don't know that anyone in our high school band was smoking weed.
Maybe they were, although I was just maybe a little bit oblivious.
You were not invited to join to that.
Should we ask Mike?
Well, look at him.
He's busy with his practicing his solo, his trumpet solo.
I am assuming they were because I don't know how anyone was listening to that much DMV and playing hacky sack sober.
I don't know a lot of kids.
High school was high school though, you know?
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, we grew up in a time of sober DMV.
There's a lot of sober DMV in high school.
I like a little DMV.
Don't get me wrong.
What's your number one DMV?
What's your number one song?
Ants Marching?
Huh?
Probably.
It's probably something from the Crabbit Streets album.
I'm suspicious of that answer.
That answer was probably.
That makes me feel like he can't name a song.
I think that's right.
Wait, let's try.
Let's try.
I was going to let it go, but Scott's here and he wants to know.
I can't name anything except I remember one of the songs was the single of the soundtrack for Mr. Deeds.
Oh, what was this?
Was it Crash on Mr. Deeds?
What was the single?
No.
I think it was Crash.
It was not Crash.
It was much later.
I like Crash.
I was going to say Crash is like the big hit.
It's funny how Jason keeps sparking to the songs when other people say the title.
I was not a big DMV.
What about the song What Would You Say?
It's got a John Popper harmonica solo on it.
Pro.
Blues Traveler?
Were you a Blues Traveler kid?
I can't name any of it.
The singles?
Probably.
They're probably on the radio.
That's a strange answer.
I was probably a Blues Traveler kid.
Probably.
You have to be cool here.
If you played the singles, I'd probably go like, oh yeah, that was on the radio.
Stop everything.
We don't have to be cool here.
You don't have to pretend to be a Blues Traveler kid.
You don't have to.
That would make him cool.
In my eyes, of course.
No, I only know the single Blues Traveler singles.
Who was the one who went a little nuts and used to tweet Benghazi is not going away?
Was it John Popper?
It might have been John Popper.
I think John Popper might have gone a little crazy.
It might have been Macy Gray, honestly.
It could have been Macy Gray.
Macy Gray had some strange opinions.
Let's get to this particular area of shadiness.
It's a Jamie Kennedy hosted special.
Jamie Kennedy was a person who I never had a ton of opinions on.
Jamie Kennedy was just kind of in stuff.
He was good in good stuff.
The Scream movies, good.
Romeo and Juliet, both finger.
This was a strong career in which he had the goods.
I thought it was pretty great.
I never really thought much about him until then he starts doing his own vehicles.
He becomes a star and what does he choose to star in?
What chooses him to star in?
Things start getting a little dicey.
It's hard for me to not play a brief moment of this clip.
This is a real, this is a bug main classic.
This is something he would torture people with a lot when I met him.
It's the kind of thing people, I don't think a lot of people have actually watched Son of the Mask.
Has anyone ever sat down?
I have not tried, no.
I was wondering, is this going to be from Malibu's most wanted or Son of the Mask?
It's Son of the Mask.
Just before this plays, and this is not all his fault.
He was a hired gun to appear in this film.
However, just remember the star making moment of Jim Carrey at the nightclub
and how he made it look so easy.
He's this living cartoon and just the pure charisma of that musical performance.
And all the shapeshifting and the CGI.
You've never seen anything like this in 1994.
And then cut to the big music performance when Jamie is wearing the mask.
Listener, you'll be missing a lot of the visuals here.
He's at a nightclub watching some boring guy perform Can't Take My Eyes Off of You.
And then he does it a little bit more masky.
This informed a lot of bug mains.
One of the primary influences, yes.
I want to say 2002.
I'm not totally sure.
Does Bug like Son of the Mask?
I don't think so.
2005.
Jesus.
Wow.
But he does like the second Dumb and Dumber, I recall.
Does he?
Not the teenage one.
I don't think the teenage one.
I think the Dumb and Dumber two or whatever.
That's interesting.
I think that's what he said a couple years ago.
No, I think Son of the Mask is more of a like you must bear witness to this.
Don't just keep your life moving without putting your eyes on this.
You must know that many millions of dollars were spent to get to this.
Ten years later, ten years post-mask, they decided to direct it.
Was it in the theater?
That was in the theater.
God.
Yeah.
I don't really blame Jamie Kennedy for this, but I certainly noticed that as things start
to become Jamie Kennedy-driven projects that things are sort of weird.
And then not long after that, this is a story I've definitely told on the podcast before,
but I had this opportunity.
What an opportunity.
I had a meeting with somebody who worked for Jamie Kennedy.
And this is in like early YouTube days for me.
So anyone wanting to talk to me at all, like that's crazy.
Whoa.
What could this turn into?
Jamie Kennedy.
I guess I'm fine with Jamie Kennedy.
And then I go to like, it was like a meeting at night and it was just all very shady.
The place was shady and the guy was shady.
And then like, he's like, oh, hey, you got to meet Jamie.
Dude, you got to meet Jamie.
And then I'm brought back into this room.
This like very like, okay, you probably all in preparation for this, you may have seen
like a bunch of like art of Jamie Kennedy projects.
Just like the graphic design of like Malibu's most wanted type stuff.
So I walk into this room where every bare inch is covered in Jamie Kennedy giant posters,
just like the worst fonts and him just mugging.
And then he's in there and he stands up like, hey, dude, Jamie, this guy, Scott, he's coming up.
He's good.
And then he gives me the worst handshake I've ever received.
And I am not one of these people who, I'm not like our parents' generation.
I don't judge people on their handshakes, but I do when it's this weird.
It felt like three sardines just kind of slapping me.
Like it was so, it was weird, wet, not committed to.
He's not looking me in the eye.
He seems fucked up.
Just like, oh, what's going on?
Weird laugh like that.
Just like the sketchiest.
And ever since that moment, I've just been like, huh, Jamie Kennedy.
There's something off about Jamie Kennedy.
And that was about 2010.
So this is like, this is when I've got him kind of in my mental sites.
Like, okay, if you ever see him in anything, like pay attention because this might be strange.
And that's not long after that encounter that this occurs.
Like, oh, here it is, the full manifestation of the Jamie Kennedy shadiness.
I don't know what it is.
I don't want to go start making like accusations about what his deal is, but it's definitely I would put it in the Pauly Shore camp.
I'm just about to say that.
I don't want to start, I don't want to say specifics.
I wouldn't even know what makes you like that, but just kind of like weird, floaty, like, oh, yeah, dude.
Just messy.
Permanently like that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Have you checked in on his straight to camera broadcast?
Like his YouTube channel?
Yeah.
On his social media.
You know, I have weirdly because he did a reaction video to this.
I actually found his analysis of what happened to some of the mask kind of interesting.
But I do you got something in the pocket?
Do you experienced anything good from Jamie recently?
Well, there's one video I just saw.
It's a tweet and it just says Black Swan event incoming in three, two, one.
And then there was a video of him talking about it.
What year?
When was this posted?
Oh, in the last month or so.
Black Swan?
About the movie Black Swan?
No, no.
A Black Swan event is like a big like the Trump assassination.
It's like a big.
Well, like COVID would be a black swan.
The markets all tank.
It goes back to a very ancient history, I feel like, where they thought like, oh, God,
if you saw a swan, but it was black.
And then eventually explorers discovered like, oh, there are black swans.
Oh, it's not occur.
It's not a weird like Kraken creature that you have to be afraid of.
But then he posted another video where he's like, if your vote is still voting for the left,
you're either brainwashed, getting paid or a deviant.
And if you encounter, A is a good thing to remember going 2025.
You encounter anyone in your life or in social media who's talking about a deviance
or degenerates like immediately be skeptical of anything they're saying.
Because it's like the it's like some right wing madness.
Like it's the groomers and pedophiles right wing kook.
I didn't know these phrases were big phrases right now.
What if someone I know is talking about degenerates?
Ellen, is that OK?
Hey, and what if I am English woman?
Did I use any of those words when discussing Spencer's gifts a few weeks ago?
Well, let me check my transcript.
Well, they are.
And they're deviance and degenerates and they're getting away with it.
Because I don't know, maybe I said that.
I don't know what I maybe I'm slipping.
I don't know.
Can I say one more?
I left so much on the cutting room floor of the Scott Responds episode in that same episode
where there's a lot of like naughty things that Jason's naughty products he's describing.
And then Mike is responding.
The most pure Mike response that there ever could have been was Jason mentioned a sweater
that has a little beer koozie in it, like a little like spot where that is clearly made
for putting a little holster for like clearly beer cans or beer bottles.
Yeah.
And Mike is trying to wrap his head around it.
And then your response uncommented on by Jason is, oh, well, you could put figures in there.
Nothing could be more.
That is perfect writing for the Mike character that you see something shaped for beer cans
and you think, oh, Donatello.
I didn't respond because I was like, oh, yeah, that's something Mike would say.
Yes.
So yeah, true.
Almost in a way, not remarkable.
But in a way, the most remarkable pearl of that's all of that's Mike right there.
I don't remember.
I don't remember that part.
That's why I got to be here.
I got to underline things.
We don't like things.
Well, there's a brewing country.
I shouldn't even say this because because it's going to derail it.
But there's a brewing.
There's an episode where I recently I insisted that Jason said that he he was going to have a warm or wet walnut.
And I write and on the episode, which is a Spirit Halloween episode, I do make mention of a warm walnut,
but it seemingly comes out of nowhere.
And I feel that I had invented some sort of concept in my head that I was about to present.
And then we got the rail talking about the barrel of nuts.
And then later I said something about Jason having a warm walnut on the spirit episode.
And then that is now implanted itself as a memory of Jason saying he wanted to eat a warm walnut.
But Jason never came up in the first one where I was right.
But I don't think Jason ever said.
Wow.
In your defense, like I think it was just kind of common phrase it because it's like talking about a walnut barrel,
talking about wet walnuts, but at old fashioned ice cream parlors.
Well, you have said wet walnut before.
Yeah.
That is for sure happened before you have said wet walnuts.
My grandfather and my mom just like, oh, if you go to the ice, you know, we're getting ice cream to go.
It's like I would like sprinkles or hot fudge.
They liked wet walnuts on it, which is just walnuts and syrup.
There's a whole I'm sorry, Mike.
There's an entire Wikipedia of wet walnuts.
Jason's right on this one.
No, I agree.
Walnuts is an area.
I've heard him say what walnuts warm.
Warm walnut seems to be a style of finishing of wood.
So warm walnut is almost like it is a phrase, but it's more it's not a food phrase.
What walnut does seem to be a beautiful, great judge.
Very.
Jason.
I believe that's fair.
But what I believe happened, though, is that there was a series of things that happened on the Spirit Halloween episode that derailed me.
Christmas.
Spirit Halloween.
Spirit Christmas derailed me so thoroughly.
I had some sort of joke concept floating in my head, ready to go.
And then you hit me with three things that I wanted to explore.
And then at the end of that, I said something about you enjoying a warm walnut.
And it comes out of nowhere, seemingly.
I don't know where there wasn't a warm walnut said earlier.
Also, by the way, where is this controversy brewing?
In my own head as I edit the episode.
This isn't anything that anyone's commented on or noticed.
No, no one's probably said that thing about it.
Mike in his mind palace just has a fire going with multiple chestnuts roasting on an open fire become warm walnuts.
I did so much investigating yesterday of going back and trying to figure out where warm walnut came from.
Because by the time you presented to me, it was presented as fact.
Right. It was fact.
I mean, I am the episode in a similar to Marshall Gate.
At the end of the discussion, I said, maybe I'm wrong about this.
But I was trying to figure out where it came from.
And I think it was floating in my head.
And I said it in that episode.
But you never said warm walnuts.
Mike just turning over his memento polaroid saying, don't trust his lies.
This is the scariest thing about Mike ageing a bit, getting a little older, which is that he like finally there are lapses in his memory of everything Jason has ever said.
Well, that's what I guess I can.
I forgot. Look, I forgot that he used a little flashlight on the episode about the Disneyland app when he was a kid going on the dark rides.
A very cute and daring story.
Right. And I forgot that.
So I'm.
You just said about yourself.
Yeah.
While he's right.
Everyone.
Because I've told it multiple times to people in real life think, well, like, oh, that's sweet.
You know.
So you're just flashing the memories of being on the receiver.
You tell the story and then you getting these looks like Jason, Jason.
You light up my life.
You warm my life up like a warm walnut.
Well, a hot and wet walnut.
We're just trying.
We're patting this episode with nice stuff because the actual thing.
The thing is.
So I think that probably is what's happening.
Pleasant.
Let's hear.
We'll get we'll get back to it.
The OK.
You're right.
That there's maybe been a bit of a right wing turn.
Jamie was also embroiled in this.
He was in this situation where like he found much like the New York Times was quickly grilling him about this special.
He was also several days after a different release saying what I can't be in a conservative funded film called Roe versus Wade.
That's about the evils of that that decision.
I like I can't be in some.
I have to believe in what the movie.
It doesn't necessarily mean that that's what I think.
No, it's like I'm just in it.
It's me and John Voight and Robert Davi and Joey Lawrence.
And so and then like but I don't get down like those guys.
I'm just playing a doctor.
Actors do roles.
OK.
So he's there's just a world of Jamie Kennedy shadiness.
And what I've learned is that you can enter the world of Jamie Kennedy shadiness not just through very poor quality videos and copies of this on YouTube, but also in the way in the higher quality world of to be.
You can watch this special on TV where it's it's labeled as Jamie Kennedy New Year's Eve just without real reference to how it went or what it is.
This seems to be part of like an overall content deal with Jamie Kennedy Productions, who I'm sorry to say I did not have the pleasure of working with.
Despite a positive meeting, I did not go forward with any projects with J.K.P.
Did you meet with Robert Davi at all for like a spin off?
I'm still dreaming of it after his after his very memorable Funny or Die encounter where he hit on two directors girlfriends.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Well, he's never going to get music videos for his Sinatra record Sinatra covers that way.
No, but here you can watch like if you look up Jamie Kennedy on to be and this is why I was saying like I can if you want to see a digital wall of ugly Jamie Kennedy covers, you can look this so you can see Kennedy's court.
The unprecedented idea of a show where it's like two parties enter a courtroom to make it for a decision to be made and the judge Jamie Kennedy.
I feel like for there's so many garbage things like that.
Yeah, that's and that's like Teagan's court on late 2000s.
Have I talked I don't want to do it, but this is funny.
All right. Have I talked about when I worked in like reality and clip show TV?
But I talked about the pilot they made.
I'm not sure about called psychic court.
Not sure.
Go for it.
We don't know.
Okay.
Doesn't sound okay.
All of a sudden there was a guy hanging around.
Maybe it was the guy who created slam ball and he was helping produce a bunch of these other pilot ideas for this company.
I worked worked at and all of a sudden there was a thing in the like folder when I was editing called psychic court.
And I was like, oh my God, what is psychic court?
I'm so excited.
And and this other producer guy I know he was like, oh, yeah, that's something we're working on.
We're not sure.
Blah, blah, blah.
And I go, I think I know the door wasn't closed yet.
And I go, you know, what would be funny to get as the judge of psychic court?
Judge Larry from the Anna Nicole Smith trial.
Oh, yeah.
Larry was like a kind of he was crying when he was doing the like he was clearly making a play to get his own like judge show at that point.
Fred Armisen played him in a very like, you know, barely exaggerated.
Yes.
Impression.
And I was going on and on and I was telling him I told the producer like, you know, Judge, here's why it would be funny.
Get Judge Larry because it would be a trashy, funny, bad show, whatever.
He closes the door and he goes, we've got him.
That's who we hired.
We hired Judge Larry for it.
And I go, what?
So you're saying that you, Mike, were the psychic.
Yes, that is absolutely.
Because why would it?
That was crazy.
It was one of the craziest things because why would it be Judge Larry?
Other than he was in the news.
He wasn't a psychic judge or anything.
Wait, where's the psychic element?
There was a panel of psychics in the court.
What Judge Larry would then go to to advise him while he was making his psychic.
Psychic court really strongly implies that the judge is a psychic.
But no, the judge consults multiple.
Yes, the judge consults multiple psychics.
They shot it.
There was a pilot.
There's a pilot somewhere.
It's not online, but it was.
They did shoot it.
It seemingly was.
It was unwatchable.
I don't think I watched even all of it, but.
And obviously it never went anywhere.
This is 15 years ago, but.
Wow.
Judge Larry.
But that's around the same time.
I feel like of new judge shows.
Was there legal bearing?
If somebody, not that it was a case this severe.
I can't imagine it was.
All right.
The defendant did kill, did kill a dog.
Like that is the, and that is true.
But the psychics get like, I'm getting an energy.
This doesn't seem right.
I think we got to call mistrial.
Or actually, no, we think you, the owner, killed the dog.
You are sentenced to gavel gavel.
The psychics have spoken goodbye.
I mean, I don't know if they were like sentencing the guys behind Enron or like, I don't know how high level these crimes were.
No Supreme court level things.
Yeah, I don't know.
Murder trial decided by Judge Larry.
Roe v Wade was ultimately overturned by psychic court.
The Supreme court ran it through psychic court.
Murder trial determined by the Long Island medium.
I don't think, I don't think that's what they were going for.
I'm assuming it was small claims.
I saw a clip from a couples court show and when it cut to the judges, there were two judges.
Well, there's Hot Bench, which has a bunch of judges.
Well, this was two and I didn't quite understand.
Like, I'm like, are the judges also a couple?
Did they kiss?
No, but I'm just like, oh, that's a good idea.
Husband and wife or two partner, a partner.
Yeah, a judge show where they kind of like you get you learn about their relationship, but then they also sentence people.
They like go behind the wall of the courtroom and over there, there is a judge relationship counselor.
Everyone's in robes for this.
So most of the show is a husband and wife judge team proceeding over a trial.
But then in the middle, they go work out their personal differences with a judge who's also a counselor.
Right. This could be called Hot Bench too, depending, depending what the relationship like.
Bench of love.
This is really the game.
Love judges.
This is what Jamie Kennedy has figured out is the real money is in putting together bizarre shows that are sold to God knows where.
Right.
That somehow make more money than this podcast, mainly because the money is pocketed by three people only.
Even though unlike this podcast, which only has three people, these shows employ 200 and most of them lose money.
Except for the three.
Except for the two judges and judge counselor.
So 2B has like the best collection of classic film outside the criterion channel.
So it's total trash.
And then it's like, oh, all of Fritz Lang's movies when he came to America, he made.
That's why it's perfect.
It like represents American culture more.
It does.
More than anywhere. Yes.
Yes. It's the trash and the highest eyebrow.
Anyway, there's a lot of Jamie Kennedy on there, including this.
But I was like, even it's hard to know which version of this to watch, really, because there was there's a cleaned up version on 2B and then I watched a full hour and a half on YouTube.
But even that was missing some of the more profane things that this initial cut down did.
So if you aren't terribly interested in this, like in the whole thing, but you want to get a sense of it, what I would say still is look up the video.
KDOC's New Year's Eve show of fail.
Jamie Kennedy is our bizarre title from, as you noted, Jason.
I don't think this is who edited it, but it's from a channel called Yip Investing.
I think this is a pot like this popped up on somebody else's channel because the rest of the videos are like this is like prognose twenty twenty three investments and then something about Nazis.
I don't know. We're in a we're in a weird German German.
You'll come in, it says, yes, it's named Yip Investing, but it's unclear.
Nothing seems like investing like he certainly is not.
At least all it does is teach you not to invest in cheap New Year's Eve broadcast.
So there's two German videos of questionable content and then the Jamie Kennedy, which I strongly believe was not.
I believe Yip Investing is not the editor of this because the video is very funny and I could see why this it's it's spread.
I think Patton Oswalt, like, you know, popularized it in the in the days following the thing.
So I still feel like the best way to experience this is the cut down of like how this thing went.
And I'm going to play clips from that because again, I think basically KDOC airs this as we said today.
It's a religious channel at the time. I believe it was mainly known as L.A.'s home of Perry Mason.
Very straight lace channel does not want a lot of funny business.
It's Channel 56 in L.A. and somehow they got talked to.
They must have gotten stars in their eyes. Jamie Kennedy, he's in movies, right?
Yes. Yes, he is. Not was is.
You can get movie stars on your channel. He's promising Shannon Elizabeth.
Oh, I think I've heard of that. He's promising Mina Suvari, who spoiler is someone he asked to be in it, who then was there.
But the production was so confusing and she got tired of banging around.
So she left. So he bailed rightfully.
So anyway, they also aired the Sacramento My My Network TV affiliate KQCA.
OK, if you recall, if you read the if you remember, My Network TV was the networks when UPN and the WB merged.
So the CW would end up on one channel, but then that other channel needed something.
So My Network TV was a lot of syndication stuff. OK.
And then eventually went away. The Wikipedia for My Network TV is so confusing because it's like and now they're just like a content production company.
And it's like it's unclear what any of anything means.
It's unclear how anyone makes money and syndicated television nowadays.
Yeah, yeah. I don't know. See, it seems like a weird mess appropriately for what we're talking about.
Well, let me let me start setting the scene of how.
So somehow I think with like six weeks of like six weeks from soup to nuts, this thing came together.
Some producer, I don't know, like I don't know.
I don't know. It does. I guess the details of it don't matter.
But we end up at Jamie Kennedy hosting and producing this thing because he went and found all the sponsors.
Apparently, that's what his own money was put into this.
I think that's important to note.
But what it leads to is I will literally set the stage like the literal stage.
So we are on Hollywood Boulevard, L.A.'s Times Square, where it all happens.
We're in the courtyard of the Chinese theater, a place where there's nary a weekend where you don't find Jason and Mike and I.
That's always where we're hanging out, putting our hands in the concrete, sampling L.A.'s local wares,
enjoying the finest Hollywood has to offer.
Certainly not a place that we avoid like the plague end up at once every 11 years stops.
It's like such hell over there, truly.
And they have set up a stage and the stage has room for, I would say, comfortably eight people.
And at many points of this broadcast, it is asked to hold 35 people.
And then there is a screen behind them.
And what's on the screen?
Well, usually pictures of the Chinese theater, which again we are at already.
And then above that, the Carl's Jr. star.
Somehow they convinced Carl's Jr. to give money to this and to lend the star to this.
And there's something, again, I don't like hold the Chinese theater in such high esteem, but hey, it's in the parks, right?
That's the landmark of Hollywood studios.
So it is kind of disgusting to see the Carl's Jr. star in front of it.
I don't know why, maybe not to you guys.
It made me a little nauseous.
And then at midnight, like instead of, because there's no ball that drops at midnight.
Three, two, one.
And it zooms into the Carl's Jr. star.
Yeah, spoiler alert.
I want to talk about that because I was like, well, surely the star will drop if it's up there in the center.
It doesn't.
Like I like rewind it and I look and there's just two poles holding it up.
And I'm like, the star is not moving.
They just zoomed in on it.
Imagine the kind of mechanical wizard they would have to contract and make work on a holiday in order to make the star drop for 10 seconds.
They couldn't even, again, we can jump around.
It's a confusing mishmash anyway.
They couldn't afford a clock, let alone they get the countdown wrong.
When it hits midnight, midnight has already occurred and they are 10 seconds off.
And I think they say on Mike, like the clock guy left.
We couldn't hire the clock guy.
He wouldn't fix it.
The excuses on this, like the excuses of Jamie Kennedy afterwards going like, well, it's actually supposed to be an anti New Year's Eve thing.
And I'm like, that.
No.
Wrong, wrong.
And between that and then I have to say probably the worst film sketches I've ever seen.
Yes.
Probably.
It's got to be.
They're basically commercials for Commerce Casino, but they're not even solid commercial.
They fail in both aspects.
Well, they're referred to as short films.
At some point, the co-host of this, Stu Stone, who was from a rap thing with Jamie Kennedy called Blowing Up.
So he's in the.
That's not who I met.
I met someone else in the Jamie fold, but Stu Stone pops around.
He's at the Commerce.
That's so that's the sponsors of this.
Carl's Jr.
Pretty good.
Commerce Casino, which if you don't know it, that's on the way to Disneyland.
That's probably where we experience it the most is that like that middle zone between where we live and Disneyland where you're on the five and you're like, oh, God, traffic's not good today.
Yeah.
Damn it.
You're like losing morale a little bit.
And then you see this casino and you wonder what's going on over there.
Is that they having fun over there?
Nope.
It's one of those like scary, serious, joyless casinos.
Yeah.
Pure bedding.
That ain't the fun.
You've been you've been in.
I haven't been in.
I've been in the bicycle casino, which is also and it's a different way down to Orange County.
But I went in there.
I think I've talked about this before that I went in and just like nothing but glares as soon as I walked in the door.
It felt like the birds when the birds have overtaken.
You are not wanted here.
Have you been in the commerce casino?
I have never.
We got out of there quickly.
I remember you saying that many years ago.
And it's LA County.
I think it's just it's just table games and a sports book.
I believe.
Yes.
Right.
And it looks temporary.
All the tables were set up temporarily in this like lobby of a hotel.
And there's nothing fun and casino about it.
If you like, you know, lights color like obviously they're not doing slot machines or anything, but still we were like, oh, this is weird.
It's like a place like Artie Lang would go.
Yes.
For sure.
Artie would have.
The hotel is the is a is a crown.
Royal.
What's the name?
I don't know.
And it's huge.
I stayed at them before I stayed.
And some are pretty nice.
North Carolina and stayed at one of Philadelphia.
Did you see that the fuck hotel you were talking about is open still?
What's that?
People post that fuck hotel you talked about with the big wine with the big martini glass.
Oh, was it saved?
I don't know if it was saved.
Somebody just posted, I think, on our Patreon that it's open still.
You said it closed, but it's open, I guess.
I maybe it's set to close or maybe the owners change.
I don't know.
Can you go home during holiday?
Yeah.
How close are you to it?
The Poconos are probably like four hours away, three or four hours away.
That's not so bad.
Yeah.
Get over there.
Prone bone in the Poconos.
I would like to see my family.
Yeah, you will.
You're going to be there for a half day or so.
You'll be going to the big sex hotel.
Go to the sex hotel.
We'll do an episode on it.
Come on.
He's going to discover the exact perfect shape and type of reclining that you can do.
What his body has been needing for a long time is just one long sit in a champagne glass.
It's perfectly contoured.
That's perfect, yeah.
It never surprises me, but my body is doing great now.
One medical professional referred to neurological condition.
It's like you're in a car and you're getting to your destination,
but there's an insane wild passenger in the passenger seat that you have to calm sometimes.
So no doctor is prescribed buying a giant wine glass for the house.
Champagne flute on top.
Sorry, sorry.
Yeah, because that's too severe.
That's like the wildest.
Yeah, you're right.
Champagne flute has a more gradual angle.
I don't want you to inception any more false memories of my antics.
In myself.
Yeah.
It's up to us to do.
We need to buy him a Pocono style champagne.
What he needs in his house is a big animatronic tree from China and a giant champagne flute.
I didn't check in.
I don't know that there's any holiday sales on the industrial.
Trees.
The animatronic tree.
Yeah, Black Friday for, wow.
Now it's only $32,000.
I watched the whole recent Jamie Kennedy, not rebuttal, explanation of this special,
and he refers to the location of the casino as downtown commerce.
Beautiful downtown commerce.
I can't argue with that.
I don't really know what downtown commerce, but why wouldn't it be this?
Sort of an unremarkable area in my memory.
No, a bit.
So anyways, they're on board and there's a bunch of sketches.
They're referred to as short films.
We've got a lot of action happening here at the Commerce Casino, but Jamie Kennedy just
shot three short films for them.
So we're going to be checking in on those throughout the night.
And then yes, throughout the broadcast, you're treated to the worst sketches ever made, all
the way from incompetent to offensive, because one where he's a Mayan, because the Mayans
predicted things.
Yeah, because the 2012 prophecy had not come true.
And I believe also was debunked even then of like, well, that was just when the Mayans
switched to a different calendar system.
It was their Y2K.
It was just a switchover situation.
But they're all wearing headdresses.
It's a lot of white people wearing war paint and headdresses.
Yeah, and they don't look, why does Mayan culture force them to have to do that?
I would say it doesn't.
They're at least aware, even though they still do it, because in the sketch, they say, one
of them has a prediction, Jamie Kennedy never works again after this sketch.
So at least they know.
Somebody knew.
Yes, one punch up guy on the...
But yes, you're in these barely lit, barely decorated conference rooms at Commerce Casino.
And then there's a lot of at, like you're being made aware of poker tournaments and
stuff throughout.
But let me go back to the top.
Let's talk about his standup set at the beginning, because there's kind of not a lot of bombast.
You know, we love our specials, our Disney specials.
We're like, with Alan Thicke and with, who's the, God bless thee, Lee Greenwood.
Oh, yeah.
It's always Lee Greenwood.
We love our long lists of celebrities.
Sandy Patty.
Gospel singer, Sandy Patty.
Well, there might be that for this.
Actually, I think there is.
But basically, it just kind of kicks into like a, just a confusing, chaotic scene where
everyone's talking and like Jamie Kennedy only barely has volume over them because he
has a microphone, but an often malfunctioning microphone.
As you said, Jason, at the very beginning, apparently, it was like three, two, the walkies
aren't working.
Go.
So they, like the walkies went out as soon as the special began.
So there's a general lack of awareness of what to do, where to look.
You get 10 minutes of opening standup monologue and the amount of times just in that 10 minutes
that they don't have a shot of what they need to show.
It'll just cut to someone's back or someone's feet.
It's just, I know, I understand that they were like, it'll be drunk.
It'll be crazy.
And you know, like everybody drinks, like, cause it should be, TV should be chaos.
Yeah, but this someone, maybe the director needs to be not drunk.
Someone needs to, you need to, you need to be able to see the chaos to even register
that it is chaos.
There appears to be no director, no stage manager or production manager.
And it's just like, if you don't know anything about walkie talkies, you probably know they
are an idiot proof technology.
It's hard to fuck up.
You could be on the wrong channel, maybe, but it's like the armies use them for a reason.
The armies use them.
I'm sure they still use something, I think.
Well, I would hope they use something.
They do need something.
No, the armies are all on, they're all on Slack mainly.
Oh, okay.
It's like, all right.
So go into the sub group, go into the hashtag attack group.
Didn't they have like World War II, like walkie talkies and a television production in 2013.
That's true.
If walkie talkies can be the basis of an invasion, then why can they not work for first night
2013?
But man, this monologue is like seven or eight minutes long.
And it is so rough.
I'm trying to remember if I have, I wait.
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
So I got to, it's jokes like, hey, but good news.
Snooki gave birth to a beautiful six pound bottle of spray tan.
I'm just joking around.
It's things like, like, I don't know.
I can't go throwing shit.
I'm not a stand up.
I do know that probably if you're doing stand up in kind of a chaotic environment, just
tell the joke and see if it lands before you go like, what?
What?
Why are you mad?
He just like undercuts every single thing he says.
And I also know that stand up, you know, like a tweet, like a good little pearl observation.
There's an economy of words that's an important thing, I think, especially to a monologue joke
on television.
Pay attention to the very skillful economy of words here in this joke.
And very good voices going on, too.
When Kim announced that she was pregnant, Yeezy, that's her husband, Kanye, wasn't much help.
He interrupted her and he said, I quote, Kim, hold on a second.
I want to tell you, I'm really happy for our pregnancy, but I'm going to let you know right now,
before I let you finish, Beyonce had one of the best hip hop pregnancies of the year.
That was funnier than that.
That was funnier.
Funnier than what?
That was funnier than that, than itself.
You guys that know you should have laughed more because it was funnier than itself.
There was a, that was a quantum joke.
You'll get it in a million years.
So that he's just talking so much.
And, and I think his, his subjects very at the top go like Snooki, Honey Boo Boo, Lindsay
Lohan, Kim Kardashian.
It really seemed like he, he was about to say we're leaving women in 2012.
Like he's just planning on women until he gets to Gangnam style, which.
Well then you perked up.
Huh?
You perked up.
Jason's number two on his Spotify.
I love, I like it.
I think it's funny to still reference it.
But he says it in the most insane way I've ever, like.
The biggest song of the year.
Gangnam style?
What is it?
Gangnam?
Grannam?
Gunly?
It's, it's gang, it's not that complicated.
Yeah.
No.
The thing is all the topics you just mentioned, there's no doubt that Jeannie at California
Adventure in that year was using, was doing better jokes about all those topics.
Oh, a hundred percent.
Tighter.
Jokes.
The ramble of like, why was it, it didn't have to be hip hop pregnancy.
Take that one now.
Yeah, why is that in there now?
Too many.
I think, I think everybody's ahead of, people know that it's going to be a joke about interrupting
before it even begins.
So just like get to the, get to, I'm going to let you finish as fast as humanly possible.
And how is, I'm going to let you finish not about sex.
It should be about the impregnation, not that, that I have a lot of notes for this joke again.
He's done a lot more standup than me, however I do, it doesn't mean I don't have an outsider
perspective.
I'm also, I would never, I don't know if I've ever heard the phrase hip hop pregnancy.
Like, I don't, I think he's trying to say like a tabloid kind of thing.
It's unclear.
It's all unclear.
Well no, what he's trying to do is, as if, as if in the, in the Taylor Swift interruption,
if it had been, Beyonce had one of the best hip hop videos of all time, but he didn't
say that.
It wasn't hip, because it was a general, that was like a best female artist category.
Yeah.
He said a lot of words that aren't in what Kanye said.
There's a number of problems just within that minute.
A lot of the minutes of this have five problems.
Yeah.
And you add it all up and we are at a million problems.
He's crazy, he could have just had a career, all those movies he made, it's like, oh he
could have just been like the funny character actor.
I think so.
I feel like he was like on the precipice of doing that.
Supporting actor, you know?
But there's a thing like, there's like a youthful energy and Mr. Shore is a good example
of like, when you're in your twenties and you got something there and you, some people
put you in things and it's the right role, that works.
But as soon as the aging starts and they're like, I'm going to take some more control
over my, like.
But your persona is still like, Stone 17 year old.
Yeah.
But you're like, but the, just like the lot, and the, and also if you have like aged worse
than normal people due to how you live.
You're right.
So if you look, if you look 70 by way of 17.
Yeah.
But like Matthew Lillard, I think as he aged, changed, you know, what he was doing, his
persona.
Or your favorite, DJ Qualls.
DJ Qualls.
I was later, I was laying awake at night like, wow, where did it, Jason's worship of DJ Qualls.
I don't remember that at all.
I just.
Very interesting.
I just liked when he would pop up and things, but I really like Matthew Lillard as a performer.
There's a very funny, when I worked in post production, do you remember there was a short
live CIA show where Katherine Heigl was a CIA agent.
This lasted one season or like half a season.
And in one episode, like the head of the CIA get, has to resign and they have a temporary
head and it's Matthew Lillard.
And he just comes in and he's being such like an intense oddball.
It's like immediately, I was like, oh, this is, I had put a couple episodes on the background
as I was working.
I was like, oh, the show immediately got better when Matthew Lillard showed up.
Like he's Shaggy from now on and yeah, no, he's, yeah, you're right.
That's the path, I think, is to ride out the teeth.
Like you have to age your type up.
Yeah.
Yes.
But so also this, also this, you're right, is another setup I like.
How many guys here like your new technology products?
Yeah, that is really, this whole thing, this whole thing couldn't, like it does border
on purposeful, how bad everything is.
Yeah.
Like to the point where, yeah, you start, I start to question like, oh, is this, all
of this is done to be as awful as possible.
Yeah.
But that's what it feels like.
Because that is such a funny thing to say.
When you're, when you were starting to lose an audience, like what's the right, how do
we broaden out here?
You guys like touching things, right?
Who here likes jackets?
Can I say my other favorite one I wear down?
Yeah, yeah.
Percentages had a big year in 2012.
Percentage, the concept of percentage is to set up a cumbersome, like we are the 99 percent
Occupy Wall Street thing, but it's just the setup of percentages had a big year in 2012.
Percentages.
Yeah, these are some, I'm, you know what, I'm taking it best of my back.
These are some excellent lead-ins.
This is really good, yeah.
So years had a big year, right?
Like we're in one and then there's a whole other one coming up.
Give it up for years, everybody.
I'm just-
Brought to you by Carl's Jr.
I am curious now.
There is a full 52 minutes of Jamie Kennedy's stand-up, I'm not going to listen to it now,
but I am curious, is that the type of setup he does normally?
I don't know.
That's a, I'm curious about that.
Yeah, yeah.
No, just kind of like yelling general, to like-
Right.
Who here likes colors?
Do you like the light travels from the sun?
I-
From the spectrum.
One of the short films, it starts with him and I, this actually got me because it starts
with him like on stage at the Laugh Factory and then a dramatic sit-down where he's like,
I knew I was, when I was, I was born to be a stand-up and it is all a swerve to do a
Commerce Casino ad, but I was like, oh my God, don't tell me there's a dramatic like
the importance of the truth tellers video in this.
No, not that one.
The other thing about the stand-up set is that it's like non-stop, there are just very
angry guys moving equipment around the entire time, never ceasing, just like if they ever
look towards camera, they have so much hate in their hearts, it feels like they, it feels
like they're kind of a situation where like they needed to hire like 20 grips or roadies
or whatever, but 17 of them called out because they, like, what are they paying?
And it's on New Year's Eve?
No thanks, bye.
So the entire thing, like changing out the sets to be ready for Macy Gray is entirely
on three very pissed off guys' shoulders, sorry, can you hold, we're doing stand-up
right now, no, no we cannot, we are too understaffed to hold.
Can you do the, do it during the commercial break?
Listen, I don't know what show, what commercial break.
No one knows when those are.
I've just heard so much about energy efficiency in California and they're saying nothing.
Okay, well that's a good setup for my favorite guest who visits, like, so you get, we're
talking to, you know, we talk to Shannon Elizabeth and various people and then like Playboy Babes,
but then they talk to this woman and this is a, like, so guys, so Stu Stone is doing
this big wind-up about energy efficiency that clearly, someone in the general notion of
energy paid money to this project, so to where now they have to read all this mealy-mouthed
stuff and the host, Stu Stone, is doing that and behind him is just a party-goer who also
has eyes on the teleprompter who's just reading, mouthing the entire thing behind him, which
is the funniest thing that happens in the entire, much funnier than anything that the
so-called comedians do, so good job on that girl, but then, so he's setting up, this is
an energy person in the crowd who's gonna talk very casually about energy.
Foremost, how can we improve the energy efficiency in our homes?
Hi, Stu, it is a pleasure to meet you, and California homeowners could do different types
of energy-efficient type of projects to their homes, anything like changing out their windows
from single-pane to double-pane, insulating their home, improving their heating and AC
systems, and many more, and now we actually have a state-wide-
Well, Stu, who should we send to represent this cause?
How about someone who has never been on camera, who is petrified to be on camera, who needs
to memorize everything like a child in a pageant?
Hello, Stu, thank you for having me, it is a lovely evening, the weather is brisk but
comfortable, now on to energy.
It sounds like a robot.
She might have been a discrete robot, yes.
I wonder if this was, it seems like maybe a state program, they had a certain amount
of money they had to spend on marketing or advertising-
Oh, and it's the end of the year, so they can drain it all on the very last night, yeah.
Oh good, we won't get text at that higher rate if we just funnel money to Jamie Kennedy.
All right, it's New Year's Eve, the president doesn't want to do it, the vice president
doesn't want to do it, head of marketing, head of advertising is out.
Everyone's on vacation.
We've gone down a dozen people and it's like-
There's a lot of fun, there's a lot of fun folks who pop up in this, the host, there's
a, you know, she's relatively together, like everyone in this, everybody kind of gets progressively
drunker clearly as it goes, but you know, all together, all told she's pretty together,
somebody named Jessie Cruikshank who is the co-host and I was like where does she come
into the fold, cause Stu Stone's the Jamie Kennedy guy, oh, Jessie was his co-host on
an extreme musical chairs show that he hosted on the CW called Oh Sit.
Musical chairs, yeah, when I saw that I was just like, yeah, cause I was describing this
and she stopped me and I went, who is Jamie Kennedy and I'm like, she didn't, she missed
it and I was like-
But she knows like teen comedies of that era, right, she must have been on a radar.
I think we watched Scream and Romeo and Juliet, but I was just trying to describe like, do
you know Jamie Kennedy experiment or Malibu's Most Wanted, I also, I didn't like these,
like I didn't watch these-
No.
Malibu's Most Wanted?
Malibu's Most-
You didn't like Malibu's Most Wanted?
No, no.
Oh, huh.
I, well, and like there was a time where ext was sort of the like go-to terminology of print,
I feel like there was a brief window where like, am I getting ext right now, Jamie, where's
Jamie and then within a year it was, am I getting punked right now, where's Ashton?
Yeah, Jamie was before punked?
Think so, I could be wrong on that, but certainly within popular culture, I would say punked
has a much greater hold as the shorthand of pranking.
2002 Jamie Kennedy experiment.
It was right before, it kind of got, yeah, wow, got a little wiped out by punked I think.
Wow.
Anyway, then you get into, okay, when this cut down video blew up, there was a lot made
of the Macy Gray performance because she's very all over the map.
I would say when you watch the entire thing, it's like no more than anyone else, like everyone
is, it's just clearly the policy on this was just everyone would be drunk and it's fine.
She's definitely like meandering, it's not the finest performance you've ever seen, and
it has something that really blew me away, which is like, okay, I understand people being
amended by background singers or like giving kind of a solo to somebody, like now somebody
in my band is going to like carry this part, but she just is a true like pinch singer.
Like she kind of, like somebody else comes out and does all the vamping and she just
stands next to her and nods.
A much, much better singer.
I hope the much better singer found her way to a good career because she deserves, she
just like fully does it instead.
Doesn't have the personality though Macy Gray's voice does.
That's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Money can't buy personality.
I am also, again, to make me like feel like kind of crazy watching this whole thing, there's
not a single person who like kind of delivers in a traditional way.
You know what I mean?
Who does the entertainer task that is assigned to them?
That singer does it.
I guess you're right.
Someone whose name we don't know.
Performance as a whole, every element of this, that's what I'm like, well surely like one
of the musical performers just does a good job or it seems like a normal TV performance.
I don't know that any of the ones or like Jessie or Bridget from Girls Next Door, they
just seem like they are.
They seem scared.
Well, because the vibe just seems awful.
I don't think they were particularly set up for success, especially when the one has to
hold the Carl's Jr Turkey Burger, which looks nasty.
Oh yeah, and she's asked on, she's like, it's kind of a like scary little like shady audition,
but on camera.
We're like, no, eat it sexy though.
No, come on.
Can you like drip something?
Get something on your face though.
It's like, oh, okay.
That's a woman telling her to do this, by the way.
I forgot all about the Carl's Jr ads of the time.
That's what they're imitating.
They are so intense.
Mike, you might want to see if they still have this turkey, albino turkey burger.
It says only 400 calories, and I know you like to hack fast food.
I was thinking, the whole time that I'm watching people refer to this turkey jalapeno burger
as being healthy and low calorie, I'm like, I'm thinking about the two of you.
You floated into my brain like ghosts, because it's exactly the kind of thing they would
say.
Yeah, yeah.
The jalapenos actually can't go bad due to the hydrolyzation process.
Do they say that?
No, no.
The Carl's Jr app is the worst, at least the last time I checked, it was the worst app
in all of fast food.
Yeah, you know it's even worse, the food there.
Yeah, I don't really ever eat there.
Even I have my lines.
The one time that old Scott got a little chubs was due entirely to Carl's Jr. and Jack and
the Bucks.
I had a lot of ultimate cheeseburgers right when college started.
Oh, really?
That was your go-to?
I did a full freshman 15 for sure.
Wow, with Carl's Jr. specifically?
Yeah.
I don't know, you're free, you got a car for the first time so I can just go to the drive-thru
myself, but I'm not really drinking yet, so I'm not having a lot of like, what am I going
to use this freedom on?
Cheeseburgers I guess.
Sure.
But then that's how you guys eat today.
Well, it's funny to say that because I always remember my dad when I would talk to him on
Sundays.
I'd be like, yeah, I went to the dining hall, I got a slice of pizza, a pasta dish, tried
the cheesecake.
A tray of garlic bread.
And he's like, did you eat all that?
It's always the most insane combination, like oh, tomato soup and chicken figure.
I was like, oh no, I just kind of nibbled on everything, I wanted to try it.
So I want to try all this food, I'm going to be here for a few years.
You would just nibble on the different items?
I would try everything.
Wait, wait, wait.
But I wouldn't finish it.
What?
What a waste.
That's weird.
I don't know.
You're talking to Mr. Food Waste over here.
You've got to be crawling out of your skin, leaving just little nibbles like a pigeon
would do.
I mean, I would eat a good amount, first off, I was 17 or 18, okay, I didn't do this every
year.
Okay, but you just presented it as your dad would always question you.
He would always be like, that is a wide variety of food, like he's like, what are these combinations?
I have a question though within this.
Pizza and pasta, though, goes together?
Yes, yes, wild combination.
Well French fries and burger, and then oh, the vegan, I think I had a vegan station.
But this is, the thing that I really, what is the payment situation on this?
Because I can't imagine any age of you spending $35 on food.
What is the payment?
Just to nibble, yeah.
You swiped your student ID card.
That's what I was going to say.
Because in no other situation are you just buying six meals and not saving them for the
rest of the next two weeks.
No, I had like the 14 meal a week plan or whatever it was.
So like two meals a day and then I'd eat cereal in my dorm room or something.
But I put, I think I did put on some weight, but then I avoided it because Ithaca was all
hills.
So just walk into class, you're going up and down, and the campus is built into hills and
stairs and stuff.
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you think there's a record of, I mean there's not, but I would love to see a record of purchases
from your college days.
Do you think there's a, I mean that had to have been electronically.
As we head into year eight, this will turn into all of us reading our old receipts.
Yeah, right.
And I, because I had a similar system and I'm wondering now if I could log on to the
portal of ISU of Illinois State University and see what I was eating.
I think there's a subway in our lobby of the dorm, so maybe I ate a lot of subway.
I found all of Mike's purchase records from 2007 to 2008.
He bought hundreds of cock rings.
Here he is playing dumb about cock rings.
He knew this is, I knew that was, you doth protest too much.
Normal, the biggest cock ring store in normal Illinois.
I was always frequenting there.
Yes.
Normals normal shop, they call it.
Normals normal shop, that's right.
Ben Folds way to normal about normal Illinois.
How about that?
I guess that didn't occur to me.
That's about the place.
You kind of, I didn't catch that.
It was a little mush mouth.
What did you say?
Oh, a way, there's an album called way to normal, but Ben Folds, which I saw Ben Folds
perform.
Oh, a full album?
No, no, but he saw him perform in normal.
Oh, okay.
I don't know if it was the time.
Well, that must have been special.
I don't know if it was the time he thought of the album.
I'm not sure.
Wow.
I think he performed there a few times.
You might have watched the gears turn.
But it's possible.
About a neat title.
Let me, talking about great music performances, here you are saying, you might be taking
that back, what you just said about no entertainers delivering, because I'd like to play a little
bit of this performance by a band called DTK.
Oh God, DTK.
Come on, I want to see you guys dance.
Watch this in every move I make.
You don't want to make any mistakes.
Keep your words until they cause you to break.
You can keep on talking till you fall on your face.
Me, I'm just trying to survive.
This just fully sounds improvised.
It fully just sounds made up, off the top.
Just pretend you have a song.
I'm a guy and I'm living my life.
Like, just whatever the first thought is in his head.
Okay, we'll book you.
You do have songs, though, with lyrics and a plan, right?
Yeah, sure.
No, I got you, Jamie.
Of course.
Four albums worth.
Wait until you hear my great lyrics.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
What am I going to do?
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Your eyes are beautiful and I want to look into them tonight.
Look into my world of truth, but the truth hurts sometimes.
Look into my eyes.
What is that band?
I don't know.
There's enough bands called DTK that it's impossible to...
I know.
It's impossible to find it.
I really wanted to know what that...
I bet there's something interesting there if there was any record of them existing.
But there's not.
Stu Stone's nephew, he did some work on his patio, so he let him...
I was going to say they just started asking crew members who could play instruments that
they cobbled together with bands from that.
Does anyone have any vaguely attractive sons?
I need all the crews vaguely attractive sons.
We got one hair straight in there.
We'll bring their hair down in their face.
It'll look like hot bangs.
In the way that Jamie Kenney's stand-up goes on for too long, I feel like they do a number
of songs.
They get so many.
Technically, they start and stop and go into...
But it all feels like one song to me.
It all feels like a big song.
Oh, like a big jam sash?
Yeah.
Just one multi-part suite.
Yeah, yeah.
It's easier to delineate between the Bone Thugs and Harmony song.
Have we said that, that Bone Thugs and Harmony are on this?
Yes.
And that...
Because there's one that...
This song also to me, I certainly...
I like a lot of Bone Thugs and Harmony songs, but I guess I didn't care for the one where
they just keep saying, it's the first of the month.
It's the first of the month.
Maybe the recording of first of the month I might be fine with, but this is where...
It might be important to say that...
Because they were asked a lot of times, like, so did you guys rehearse this?
Did you plan it?
And they're like, no, because we wanted to be crazy psycho shit.
Did you sound check?
No, there was no sound check.
I don't think...
I think in any other setting...
Look, you can still be chaotic with a sound check, for God's sake.
I think that's something that you need for music to be performed on amplifiers.
I think that's right.
I think, yeah.
I know he...
Look, Jamie Kennedy embodies the punk rock spirit, but it's television and you have to...
People have to hear things and...
But people definitely did hear a lot of things, especially the viewers at home, in the performance
of the more well-known and a song I'd certainly like, which is Notorious Thugs.
Yeah.
And here now is...
Just keep an ear out for some words that you shouldn't be hearing here in Notorious Thugs.
Notorious Thugs.
So many.
That's really...
So many cursing.
That's nailed nicely in the cut down.
Yeah.
So many profanities.
And they're sort of aware.
They're like, oh, shoot.
There's a little energy there of like, oh, wait.
Okay.
Oh, there's also a guy...
This has to be narrated because the listener can't see it, but there's a guy who like, all
he's asked is, what's your name?
And then he says something you're not supposed to say.
And then he immediately makes a face like, oh, like he knew.
And Stu Stone has to go away from him very quickly.
Here's that.
I believe that's me.
Macy.
Here we go.
What's your name, sir?
Talon, motherfucking fool.
Hey, it is New Year's Eve 2013.
What is your name?
His mother.
Then what is your name?
It's Talon, motherfucker.
Check it in with Talon and his mom.
Mrs.
We're in with Talon and his motherfucking mom.
Mrs. Talon.
Yo, who'd you have to fuck to make Talon here?
I actually think, I think I will have the thought, again, it's in the past for listeners,
I think I will think as it hits midnight if I'm awake.
And the answer is I won't be.
But if I am, I will try to conjure the phrase heading into the year.
It's motherfucking Talon.
Talon is my, he's my patron saint of 2025.
So that happens.
Let me, in terms of, let me just play.
This is what I was alluding to with the opening bit here.
At some point it comes back from an ad and you get this.
Come on, man, don't fucking give me shit, dude.
I gotta have a camera.
There's no camera to work on the show.
He should be right here, roaming around here.
Where's our camera guy?
It's called Fairly Odd Christmas.
Okay.
That's a live action.
Where's our, where's our stage manager?
Amy, don't fuck into the mic.
There we go.
Alright, welcome back to 2013.
I was trying, I was like, do I cut this off?
I think we have to make the listener hear this as long as it played out.
That was just like 30 seconds of nothing and swing.
Yeah.
Boy.
Where's the stage manager?
Where is the sound guy?
Why is this going out live on the podcast?
Like, mute the mics, you know?
A lot of questions.
I don't know.
The guy who put this, the guy who was the director, like maybe, I don't know if you caught this, that Jamie,
because you watched his like excuse video recently.
Yes, yeah.
The director, he seemed to feel a little betrayed by what the director presented as his capabilities
because, and the director is a like wrestling league owner.
Is that a name you've ever heard?
Oh yeah, what was that name again?
I don't, I have to look it up.
David something.
Does that narrow it down?
He owns wrestling and he's a David.
Oh shoot, maybe I missed when he actually said, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
Is it, you said he was an owner?
Yeah, he owns a league and still to this day, but I don't, I don't have this,
it'll be forever of me Googling if I don't.
But anyway, I think he, Jamie seemed to imply that the director did not have his shit together as much.
There was some blame to go around, but then there was also this notion that like it's going to be crazy.
Like, you know what was in my head when I was, I was like, you know what I, you know what this like
common talking point is that I bet he will say is like the Dean Martin show,
Dean, you know, would just get drunk and he wouldn't even go into rehearsals.
And then, so then anything could happen.
And then once I heard his soundbites, it was close.
It wasn't that it was Jerry Lewis.
Oh wow.
He's like, I want it to be like Jerry Lewis Telethon where he's on the air for 24 hours.
And I'm like, the clips I've seen of the Jerry Lewis Telethon are a lot more buttoned up than this.
Yeah, of course.
And there's a lot of children around so you don't have bone thugs in harmony saying fucking shit over and over.
David Marquez.
That's it. There it is.
Yeah.
You ever come across this name or this league before?
Pro wrestling.
Oh yes, yes, I do know that.
I think that's like a really was like a really hardcore one.
He might have been the guy who there was a weird wrestling show on MTV for a very brief amount of time.
Oh, OK.
That he did.
David WXW maybe is known for championship wrestling.
Hmm. I'll look into it more.
The wrestling game clearly is to get all the letters as close as they can be to each other.
So maybe you get confused which one you're going to.
Right.
He's involved in MLW now.
So he's been involved in wrestling for a long time.
OK, OK.
So he betrayed Jamie Kennedy.
This is a smaller promotion with a television deal.
OK, yeah, yeah.
I guess that's what it.
But anyway, I think there was a feeling of like this guy doesn't have because we don't have the sound is bad and the walkies went out and then they didn't.
They say where's our clock so many times.
I would say this is how New Year's Eve viewing usually works for me.
Again, if I'm awake, I won't be.
I have a very new baby.
But usually it is like, OK, I'll put on whatever show just for the countdown.
So really, you know, we got all these bits with Anderson Cooper and Kathy Griffin and all that.
Who cares?
I don't watch any of that.
The only thing any of these places really owe is what countdown they only have to have their shit together for 60 seconds.
And this does not.
It's nowhere close.
The countdown is late.
The one thing they have to do, they don't do.
It's so wild.
I'm trying to think what else to hit.
I don't think I have to play the clip of him telling the heart disease people that he's made that they're making his heart do crazy things right now.
I think I could skip that.
You can imagine what that is.
There's a part where he says, is it weird being on stage with 14 year olds and champagne?
Yeah, if you have the question, it might be might be weird.
What else?
Oh, well, OK, where it culminates, obviously, because things are already chaotic.
We've already heard from Motherfucking Talon.
Yeah.
Phone Thugs and Harmony have sworn a lot like it's it's really going off the rails in that last half hour.
There's oh, oh, boy.
OK, here.
All right.
So then some kind of like, you know, non entertainers start making their way to the stage.
Just people who are around because they're trying to make this a Hollywood Boulevard block party and whatever.
And let's just the chaos is part of it.
So then Jamie ends up talking to this person.
Jamie Kennedy is with two of the biggest freaks in Hollywood right now.
OK, hold on.
I'm with my two lovely ladies girls.
What's your resolution for 20 years?
What's your resolution for 2013?
I'm just get rid of all my haters.
All your haters.
Can I ask you something?
Do you like white boys?
I love the hell out of some white people.
You love the hell.
You know what they say?
Is it true what they say?
You know, they say once you go black, you never go back.
Yeah.
Well, I'm saying you should try white because it'll keep your vagina very tight.
Bleep that, bleep that.
Give it up for the first night of the wedding.
He's been live on the air.
He's been planning this for six weeks.
He's live on the air.
I think you don't have regular audio, let alone bleep audio.
There's not a seven second.
Maybe there was, but no one's manning the seven second delay at that point.
Yes.
I think the person who was on the seven second delay button is the woman going, I want to get rid of my haters.
She was the bleeper.
There wasn't one live bleep.
No.
Which is part of why as soon as this aired, KDOC just ran.
They were like, no, we didn't know.
I think somebody hijacked our airwaves when that Max Headroom took over TV that one time.
You know that story?
That was pirate radio, I think.
We have never met Jamie Kennedy.
We don't know who that is.
They disavowed the entire thing, and in part of that, they used to really stay on it, deleting copies of this.
But now it's gotten away from them, and Jamie posted it on 2B.
But still, I think this one cut down is the only way that you see all of the fucks and all of how it actually, all of the worst of the errors.
I watched the full 90 minute broadcast that's on YouTube.
I don't know, don't.
It's really boring.
It isn't terminable.
It didn't add a lot to my, that's what I'm saying, just do the cut down.
This felt like a cousin of Six Flags Live to me in terms of content gutter, and where I had to keep, we had the idea.
That'll be fun.
And then I had to do it in four sittings.
Really, I had to like, come on, Scott, you could do this.
You're a man.
You've got two children.
You can make it to the end of Jamie Kennedy's first night.
Sit down and do it, motherfucker.
Last night, I was doing something, and then it was like 11 p.m., and my body shut itself down.
I was trying to finish this last night, and it would not allow it.
My eyes just were like, you are going to bed.
You cannot stay up to watch this.
I actually did feel, it's funny you say that, because coincidentally, I was feeling ill after watching it.
Like I just didn't sleep great.
Like every participant in the show.
Yeah, I wonder if the vibes were just leaking from the screen.
Maybe everyone, if anyone intends on watching this, they should do it at like 9 a.m.
They should have like a lot of time before bed is even in the picture.
There's a couple notes from Jamie I found interesting.
He believes that multiple parties owe him money still from this.
He believes $36,000 is owed to him from Carl's Jr.
Because he went to Carl's Jr. himself, he says, and got this deal, and then they never paid up.
He didn't even get a turkey jalapeno burger out of the deal.
He certainly believes a lot of things nowadays, it seems like.
He believes the Chinese theater owes him $15,000.
The theater itself?
I think they've changed owners so many times.
It's going to be hard to get that money, Jamie.
Just to get away from me.
Those were fake deals, just to not pay Jamie.
TCL, that's the name on your TV, and it's the name of the Chinese theater.
Can I at least get a TV now?
He praised the Commerce Casino as good people, though.
He said, I guess they paid up.
They're on the level.
They paid up, and he didn't have a beef with them.
And then I lost it all before I left the building.
He did not have a beef with them like he had with Carl's.
It feels like a real California split, like David Milch's luck kind of gambling, like hardcore gambling stuff.
Spending many hours.
Yeah.
Well, there's a part where they do a little skit there.
That's with a wrestler, too.
Is that a guy you guys have heard of?
I think the bit is that he's mad, but he does it so scary.
He's pounding on the table in a way that's extremely unsettling to the female card dealer.
Who is that?
Yeah, who was that?
Why, that's Scrap Iron Adam Pearce.
Where were we with Scrap Iron?
He's getting scrappy at the Commerce Casino?
Yeah, we know Adam Pearce.
He's the onscreen general manager of Monday Night Raw and WWE.
I haven't watched WWE in a long time. Is he smacking SmackDown?
Okay.
But maybe I'm wrong.
Nick Caldys is SmackDown, isn't he?
Oh, maybe I'm wrong. Yeah, maybe he's right. You're right. You're right.
I haven't watched Raw in a while.
He was in this.
Adam Pearce is in this.
Being pounding on a table to the point where it alarms the other people on camera.
Yeah.
Also, a very odd moment in one of the sketches where he approaches a table of Asian people and yells,
I don't speak Asian, and one of them responds, we're from Sherman Oaks.
That is the closest thing to comedy I get, the closest thing to a joke structure in this.
Well, also in the aftermath, the other guy, Stu, was on K-Rock after, and the guy's trying to get,
the K-Rock DJ is doing a good job holding him to the fire where he gives the same stock answer three times,
but like, look, we're trying to, you know, Jamie loves to go buck wild, okay?
And the DJ is like, did you memorize that answer? What are you doing? Answer my question.
There's no way you planned all this stuff.
And one of his sputterings in there is like, look, Jamie loves Andy Kaufman.
No.
He loves Monty Python. Oh, yeah. Oh, Monty Python.
It's because of a deep abiding love of Monty Python that you didn't have a clock.
That's very Python-esque. That's the sort of thing Terry Gilliam would do.
Surreal, you see. Anyway.
It is crazy this is 2013, though.
You mean it feels like it'll be older.
It feels like it'll be older, yeah.
I double-checked when Jamie Kennedy was dating Jennifer Love Hewitt, and it was a few years before this,
just because that's one of the main things I know about Jamie Kennedy, that he dated briefly Jennifer Love Hewitt.
And you put him on some sort of, you put him on a dart board, you got a Jamie.
Yeah, and I've hated him ever since.
He drew Xs over his eyes.
That's right.
Well, you're getting your revenge now with this long criticism of his work.
Finally.
Yeah, how dare you have your time with, what did people, did she have a nickname, was she like Love?
Was she J Love?
Oh, they called her Love.
Love.
I know that.
Anyway, the thing it really culminates in, which I guess our description of it should as well,
so that last clip gave you a taste of the kind of people who are on stage,
or at least their condition in this moment, and then things start getting a little while behind them.
It's been an unbelievable night.
We want to thank everyone who came out.
DTK, Macy Gray, Bulldogs, and ArgaMini.
Bulldogs and ArgaMini.
YingYum style.
Bulldogs and ArgaMini performing GongGong style.
Gongler's Casino.
And then, like, there's a lot of people who start to tell what's happening,
but you can start to see that people are getting shoved, and then it gets to this.
It's getting crazy here.
We also want to thank Carl's Jr.
God bless you, and we'll see you in 2024.
I don't like that.
That's too weird.
There's a fight.
It's ending with a fight.
You can't see the fight.
You can't really see that.
You really got to see through some people to see that there's a lot of shove,
and maybe even the people who we just saw laughing and talking into the microphone,
I think one of them is now just severe eyebrow.
Fuck you, motherfucker.
There is a very serious, angry fight going on on the air,
and then they cut the mics and just roll the credits over silence,
and that is the end of First Night.
When you said that Jamie Kennedy experiment was 2002 and this is 2013,
I'm like, I would have thought this was like, oh, he's on TV or he has a movie out,
so he's hosting this New Year's.
No.
Yeah, he is on TV.
This.
He's doing this, and a lot of things that won't be seen by humans
until they end up on 2B 12 years later.
2B paid for this.
Yeah, money was exchanged.
I would love to know how much.
Yeah, really.
What is that worth to them?
Right.
And how many people, and do they base their views on do you make it to the end?
Because if so, no one has.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think of anything else in his aftermath worth mentioning.
Again, he says to the New York Times, I didn't stab nobody.
I didn't shoot nobody.
I just made a New Year's Eve special.
Is that so bad?
Yeah, look, the answer is no.
He also said that why things are in a very defiant,
yes, we're doing Fire Festival again next year kind of move.
He says we're already doing it.
Commerce Casino is signed up for next year.
And I got a text from Marilyn Manson and says he wants to do it next year.
And I want to get Wu-Tang Clan.
I want to put people in that I like.
And Stu Stone in the K-Rock appearance reiterates the same.
It's exactly the same status.
Marilyn Manson in.
I would not help with a special today.
Wu-Tang Clan desired.
How do we feel on Wu-Tang Clan?
Are they in enough to get well?
I don't know.
We want them.
That's something.
We've announced a guest that we want.
That's like us.
All right.
Big 2025 for our Guest the Ride.
We got Marilyn Manson joining us as a guest.
And Michael Eisner.
And we want Michael Eisner.
OK, so a Big 2025 to come.
A Commerce Casino episode with Marilyn Manson coming up.
Yeah, well, that gets us there, I suppose.
You know, hey, starting the year with a little bit of chaos.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, I watched the cut down for sure.
And then, yeah, no, don't do the 90 minutes.
No, no, it didn't add anything.
The cut down is the way to go.
Have energy efficiency in Carl's Jr.
and Commerce Casino if you want to lose it all.
And be aware of hearts needing to be healthy in general.
Yeah, maybe we should.
I mean, Eve, Universal's Eve, their Universal New Year's.
Every year I get those promo emails and I'm like.
But maybe they should have.
Check out Eve.
Maybe they should have Jamie Kennedy host one of the areas,
just for old time's sake.
You know, just for if you know, you know, really.
Well, my my pitch to that would be yes.
But don't tell him that he's doing it until, let's say, 1110 p.m.
Right.
Just shake him out of wherever he is.
I would say sleeping.
There's no way.
Yeah, I was just going to say, though,
I think you're giving him too much credit for being prepared,
even in this day and age.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, like you'd be fine.
Like actually.
What am I saying?
Give him four months notice.
Right.
He'll still end up the same.
I think so.
All right.
Hey, we're here with Shrek.
Hey, let me suck your green dick.
Oh, shit.
Don't do it.
I can't say that.
Blip that.
Jamie, this isn't being broadcast.
There's no way to bleep it.
Blip it from reality.
Blip it from having happened.
It's like climbing down the hill by the roller coaster construction.
Hey, I'm lost.
Somebody tell me how to get back up there.
We're here with a coyote.
Oh, shit.
It's ending with a fight.
It's ending with me getting chewed by a coyote.
He's in the club scene in the Fast and Furious studio tour area.
There's a hologram of the rock here.
I'm going to hook up with a fucking hologram.
I'm in my hologram ho phase.
I'm going to get me HPV as a hologram.
I'm going to stand here, but not here.
Everyone's got to be in one little square.
Tidal safe square.
Oh, no.
I got hologram genital warts.
I need a hologram doctor to scrub them off.
He drowns in the flood area.
He's sitting there hosting, and then the flood comes and hits him.
And he has like two full minutes to watch the rain come down.
What's this?
Some kind of fucking flood?
I'm going to walk to high ground.
That shit saved me.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, no.
And I never even got to meet Wu-Tang Clan.
That's no context for War of the Worlds.
And he's like, what happened?
Is the world ending?
Oh, no.
For the Lord, the humanity.
This plane must have crashed into Kim Kardashian's butt.
That sounds good, honestly.
Yeah, I know.
I do want to say.
That's what I'm saying.
I think, look, this thing is like hateful and horrible, right?
However, who cares?
Do it every year.
If we had like lots of years of like, I want to see him do it as long as Jerry.
Get as crazy as Jerry.
But except for no good cause.
Helping no one.
Other than making you generally aware that you shouldn't hurt your heart.
But also turkey jalapeno burger.
Constant back and forth between gigantic sloppy burgers.
But mind your heart, though.
Did you guys, did you enjoy all your new technology products this year?
Yeah, very happy.
I had a very good Christmas in terms of new technology products.
Well, and hey, check out percentages did have a big 2024.
Yeah, I'm excited for percentages this year, too.
Hey, I hope that you subscribe to 100 percent of the great content that we have coming out here on this on the second gate.
I'm still in the mode.
I still want to wrap it up like that and go over to go over to club.
What?
I can't read that.
Three.
What the fuck is that?
I've never seen that before.
Club three.
Our VIP Patriot until we get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes out free.
This is chaotic.
I didn't say you survived.
Oh, yeah.
I guess the ride.
You slur.
I guess the fuck is the rub.