Let's talk about Madam in Manhattan.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, it's on my mind because Madam in Manhattan was the, uh, where did it land in the poll?
It's the, oh, the last, last place.
Uh, that makes the second to last, not the second to last, the second last place finish for Madam in one of these polls.
In this, in this case, uh, accidental PTR legend and completer, Griffin Newman, uh, made a plea for us to consider it rather than the
broader topic of, because it's too much to take on Whalen Flowers and Madam all at once that we should start piecing it off.
Right, right, right.
And doing smaller areas at a time of the, of the Madam universe.
And the, how, by the way, how the Club3 polling works, you know, sometimes we'll remind you to, to vote with your likes.
If you look at those, look, look at suggestions in the comments and hit like on it, if you, because we do pay attention to that.
That's what, uh, forms what we call the popular vote, the one that does well enough that, all right, well, that's the people's choice.
And, uh, we should put that into the poll and Griffin's plea won the popular vote.
Like, wow, people are maybe into, let's just, let's just do Madam in Manhattan, which seems to be a special from 1981.
Uh, and, uh, and I'm like, wow, geez, maybe Madam is, this is the way to, and with, with Griffin's endorsement, one of the strongest endorsements,
you can have over in Club3 and instead straight to the bottom, as soon as the poll went live, could not have been faster to the bottom.
Uh, and I guess what I'm getting at here is, and this is not, uh, you know, I don't, I don't like to say this, but I, I just, I'm just going to call it how I see it.
Yeah.
I don't believe that a puppet candidate can win the Club3 poll.
I don't think that the, the Club3 electorate is ever going to accept a puppet candidate.
And I don't know if that's, maybe that's not a good thing.
Maybe that's backwards.
Maybe we should be more free thinking, but I'm just like, you know, in our lifetime, in this, in this century, I don't know that we're going to see a puppet win the poll.
Okay.
That's a good question.
I mean, there has to be, there will be a puppet candidate that will win this poll.
I believe I'm an optimist.
Because I also, this isn't just Madam.
I'm going off of a lot of cold plays, weirdos came in with a lot of hype and then, uh, not, not the bottom.
That was like, that was strong showing four puppets, but, uh, uh, at this point, Madam has lost twice.
And so somehow Mike's excitement is toxic.
I don't get it.
Thank you for saying that.
You don't get it.
I appreciate that.
I like, you, you, you always take us on such fun rides.
So I'm willing to give it a shot.
Dummies, I mean, I guess dummies, dummies versus puppets also.
Cause I almost feel like Madam is more of a dummy than a puppet.
Weirdos are puppets more in the Jim Henson muppets variety, but Madam, I think, and maybe I'm not the expert on this.
Madam is closer to sort of like a knight of the living dummy, uh, you know, Charlie McCarthy, of course, the famous, the famous ventriloquist dummies.
Even, even like Terry fader or Jeff Dunham's puppets, um, what's the old man?
Jeff Dunham puppet.
Do you remember Walter?
Walter.
Thank you.
You are a puppet.
You're a puppet fan.
You're just fully a puppet guy.
I love, well, am I more of a puppet guy?
I mean, I am a puppet guy.
You're right about that, but I also dummy.
I like dumb.
There's something about dummies too.
Is the difference, does puppet maybe more connotate that I'm not sure that the lines here, this is, you know, I don't know exactly the rules much
like the rules between what makes a dildo and what makes a vibrator, but does, does puppet imply more that the, the operator is not seen?
Yeah, I think so.
Because if we know the name of the, and we see the person operating, does that put us more in the dummy territory?
Yeah, I think that's probably part of it as well.
There is an interesting culture around ventriloquists and dummies.
Yes.
That does, that does sound interesting and like an interesting area for a different podcast to pursue.
Oh, you don't like the museum they all go to when the ventriloquist dies and the dummy goes.
Oh God, that sounds very grim.
Where's that?
I forget, I forget.
There's at least one, if not more, resting places for the dummies.
You'll like it.
It's nice.
There's other dummies there.
You'll make a lot of, you know, these could be the golden years of your life.
You know, life without an operator, without a puppeteer can be the greatest life you've ever had.
Mike, you found, we were talking about on one of the Scott Free episodes, ventriloquist.
Your favorite new character you didn't know about, Knucklehead Smith.
Yeah.
Well, this is a whole other, okay, because like some behind the scenes, there's been some behind the scenes, puppets, dummies, discussions,
whatever you want to call it, in text message form.
And I was kind of wondering if it might go here because the reason why Knucklehead Smith came up.
Excuse me, Scott.
Smith, S-M-I-F-F.
Very good.
The reason why Knucklehead Smith came up is because you were talking about this show that had Tigger in it and thus the original voice of Tigger, Paul Winchell.
Yes.
And, oh, thank you.
Thank you for the visual.
Paul Winchell and Knucklehead Smith.
Oh, thank you.
Well, yes, of course, Jerry Mahoney, the very famous, the very famous reference that certainly you don't need someone on the episode to say, what the fuck is that?
Here's what happened.
We're still in Scott response territory a little bit.
I'm listening to this.
I contributed to that episode, but I wasn't on it.
And this just went by and this is, we plowed past this in the first four minutes that Mike said at some point, now Paul Winchell and his
dummy, of course, Jerry Mahoney.
And that's a reference you hear a lot.
And Jason said, and I went, I have never heard of this in my life.
Jerry, I'll reference you hear a lot.
So I started going at you in text message form about this and your proof that it is a reference made a lot is that it was referenced on a Seinfeld 30 years ago.
I've never, ever heard of it.
I feel like I heard it.
It's just a given that we barely even need to go over this, that Paul Winchell's dummy is Jerry Mahoney.
Yes, of course.
I look at my life.
I come across dummies more often.
I guess I did explain it.
I didn't just say, I, you know, if I didn't explain it, I think I would be on the hook here.
Were you scared and sloppy?
But you were explaining in that way of like, okay, I guess let's say it.
But of course, everybody knows Paul Winchell, Jerry Mahoney, he was done with that rushing through it air, which then Jason's like, Jason didn't fucking know.
He said he didn't know.
Yeah, I didn't know.
But when I saw him, I was like, oh, okay, I kind of recognize now partially because he looks like what all dummies look like.
In the mid 20th century, they look very similar.
I mostly associate it with this, with Slappy, the night of living dummy from Goose Bums, who I was scared of.
Well, right, he is scary.
That is part of my fascination with the dummy, I think, is that I'm scared of dummies.
And this is now and this came up in a recent episode that I think that we're trying to put this on that in that Chukko territory of like, is it is the fascination because of the fear?
And on my end, it's not fear.
It's it.
I don't like these things because they stink.
And I do believe that the I think the stats on Madam prove that ultimately people do not know what the fuck this is.
To allude to another another recent campaign in the last few months, I think that the Madam team has failed to tell the Madam story.
I think that ultimately they have not created a compelling story.
Yeah, well, that's a good point.
And it's that's on me to tell a more compelling Madam story.
I such as step one.
What the fuck is Madam?
You need like the oomph of like two storytellers, Vicki Lawrence and Mama.
No, no, no, we are not.
I'm not engaging any more with Vicki Lawrence and Mama.
Can I ask, do you know the the dummy that do you know?
I think it's Edgar Bergen's dummy.
Well, that was said earlier.
It's Charlie McCarty.
Yeah, I just had a conversation with friend of the show, Andrew Grissom, about this because Grissom watched whatever Disney movie.
One of those like war era Disney movies with the wraparounds are Edgar Bergen and his his dummies.
And he brought all this up to say, hey, I watched this this movie with these ventriloquist dummies in it.
I hated it.
I hated every second that these stupid dummies were in it.
And he didn't know the names.
He'd never heard of any of this before.
For the Disney fan out there, the famous the Mickey and the Beanstalk short was originally presented in this package where there were it was all narrated by.
Who is the other one?
I think I did. Is the other one Mortimer Snurd?
Yes.
OK, yes.
I do know my dummies, dummies.
But originally, if you watch Mickey and the Beanstalk, it was all narrated by these like, oh, what's he going to do?
And then they they did it in a more palatable packaging, which is how we saw it.
I think I think I'm right about all that.
Was it unpleasant?
Yeah, life on the home front was hard during the war.
Give him a pass.
Anything unpleasant from during the war?
It got very confusing when Charlie McCarthy was drafted, but not Edgar Bergen.
And so is it possible Mortimer Snurd's voice being annoying?
Is he ever thought about that?
Maybe it was due to shells going off.
Very possible. Yes.
That's ringing in his ears.
You need to talk normally if he could.
He recorded his audio in the Pacific Theater.
The look, I'm trying to think about my relationship with dummies in general, and it is something because, like, one of my favorite Batman villains is Scarface.
That's the name of the character.
Scarface and the Ventriloquist.
And and so that's like one of the only my Batman animated series figures are in a box except for that one.
OK, this is not on purpose.
This is just now that I'm thinking about it out loud that I must have something.
That's the one that you kept out of.
Well, it's just, yeah, it's out of the box and eventually they'll all be displayed, hopefully.
So he's watching you sleep on your nightstand.
Yes, correct.
Well, he's not in my nightstand.
And also, and just to do just to do further math, then you are at once the most out of the three of us concerned about seeming youthful and aware of new music.
Yes.
And also you are, as the years go by, becoming more of a Ventriloquist fan.
Do you feel you can reconcile these two things?
I was listening to M.J.
Lenderman today, his album from twenty twenty four.
That's a young man.
He's in his mid 20s.
Now, you surprise me there.
That's a name that I don't know.
And when you said that, I think what I went to was M.J.
Lenderman. Now meet my friend Skippy.
Hey, hey, M.J.
It is. It kind of sounds like a Ventriloquist.
It does sound like that.
But but in addition to that, then I also will watch a clip from Madam's Place.
The episode that I think is really the one I want to do is the one with the army clip.
I keep mentioning.
That's the thing that really started my love affair with wanting to talk about Madam.
So, yes, I got both.
I mean, look, I can't fight you on this.
I've mostly been exploring the works of
Barbara Stanwyck and exploring, you say?
Yeah, she made so many movies exploring me besides watching the movies.
Wait, hold on. I don't think he's watched them necessarily.
That's right. We might be reading with you.
Yeah, yeah. Wait a minute. Hold on.
No, I have been watching.
OK, how many? How many?
Uh, just a couple so far.
OK, so two. One and a half.
But I think the Lady Eve is like really funny, like really terrific.
It's a Preston Sturgis movie.
Now name a young person that you're interested in as well.
Give me the youngest person that you've interacted with their art in the last two weeks.
Sabrina Carpenter.
Sabrina. This is another thing that I have, by the way, is that all of our
that the desire to be relevant on this show, like like like.
Mitcham is the other very old actor I've really been.
I'm going to say that's the next youngest person you've been enjoying.
Being relevant on this show is completely hand in hand
with just knowing the names of the most popular singers in the world.
That's how that's how we get like how I'm relevant.
I know what this is.
I know about this artist who is big enough to play in arenas.
It's kind of like saying, I'm I'm hip.
I know who the Clippers are.
Well, that would make you at least, you know, sports, you know, if you do.
That's one of the that's one of the freshest teams on the scene.
I recognize Lucy Arnaz
within 10 seconds or getting out of a taxi cab.
Right. And that's cool.
Well, and we'll we'll start making our way that way.
But I do have to say that, look, you might not.
There's some listeners who might not like how these polls are going,
but it is democracy. There's a lot of people.
You can't you can't argue with the numbers here.
And look, Madame was dead last.
And what's second place? Let me check.
Oh, Bugman does whatever he wants.
Second place again.
Bug's numbers are growing.
Bug went from twenty one to twenty five to twenty six.
A certain presidential candidate every every election.
I will say bigger and bigger every time.
Jane was excited to be considered,
but not thrilled to lose third place to Bugman.
But I suppose that's just karma
because of how much of the
she's been playing the Bugman album around the house.
This is the fiction that people invent
because I'm seeing people say a vote for Jane is against Bugman.
And I'm like, Jane likes Bug. I know this.
I know this for a fact.
Yeah. Bug is a friend of all of us.
This is insane. The notion that this is a troll, a troll.
How could it be a troll?
Bug is one of my good, my dearest friends,
a close collaborator for nearly 15 years.
He was one of the groomsmen at my wedding.
This he's even he has grown into.
Yes, I'll say an uncle figure to my son.
He's Uncle Bug, don't you see?
This is a this is a dear friend and not you guys aren't as close,
but you're but you're you're friends and fans of this friend.
The notion that we are only doing this as some just to rile people up.
Is it is it a troll to invite one of your closest friends into your home?
Not not where I come from.
So what can I say?
I guess this month,
listeners, if you see it in your hearts, bring Uncle Bug home.
And with that
and also somebody made of I think I think Ryan was the user.
Somebody made the very good point.
Every time that Bugmane loses anybody's in second place,
we're going to have to do this again.
And the bug haters are going to hear this name and the name is too much.
Here, just Bugmane.
I just they all just shivered.
They all people are so upset at the mere mention of I.
So look, he keep it.
We're between a rock and hard place here.
He stayed. He's he's not moved from that second.
But we've been doing this in September.
I have a I don't even know. I want to say it.
I feel like there's only one way he wins.
And that's if you split up,
you split up maybe like the anti-bug vote in a perfect way.
I don't have the equation for it, but I almost feel like
he cannot win the way that the club three is gerrymandered.
It's like it doesn't.
I'm not sure. I think there's a way.
I think as long as I make a separate new emotional appeal
at the top of every episode, this one was shorter than last time.
No, it's help. Yes. Yeah.
Well, I'm trying to keep it tight.
I don't want to waste it because that's going to rile people up.
Yeah. But the more that I speak to this man
and what I think he's capable of and what I think he's going to bring to an episode,
the voting options were Bugmane does whatever he wants
and then four slots for the short lived Lucy Arnaz show on CBS
that aired the year Scott and I were born.
That might work. Yeah.
Or four different episodes of Madam's Place.
That sounds good to me. Well, let's lock that in.
Yeah, it'll all be it'll all be separate Lucy Arnaz votes versus Bug.
And just to see how that that makes things play out.
I think we'll be doing this for another five years.
Yeah, that's this might be a perennial aspect of Club 3.
Yeah, just always we have to by what we and this is not new.
We always talk about what is the runner up.
And if that's how it's going to if he's going to be the runner up
and he has the votes to at least be the runner up, I think every time.
Is there any do we want to amend the concept?
Like, is should there be a year limit on something like this?
Ooh, you know what I mean? I don't know.
I'm not saying I even believe it.
Well, I think that's something to consider the next time there's one of these.
Oh, OK. Like, I don't know.
I think Bug deserves it because that's a new rule.
And I don't think that's fair. Bug should be able to,
you know, let it play out as long as he wants.
But let's say there was some other topic that, I don't know, was kind of a
like, let's say there was, you know, something more unpleasant
and ball chinned that got stuck in that second slot for a long time.
Yeah, I think then you might want to start creating some term limits.
I understand what you're saying. There's no way that ever happens.
Yes, we are.
The Club 3 Constitution is protected against,
you know, a madam type zealot from rising up because Madam
loses every single time.
Yeah, for a split second, I went, is he talking about the movie 43?
Does someone have a ball chant in that?
Yeah, right in the first.
Might be Jackman.
Oh, OK. I forget.
It's you and I watched that.
Do not, if I have to hear you talk about what apartment you watched
movie 43 at again, how is this becoming a five timer?
Where we watched movie 43.
And that's today's topic, movie 43.
Is Barbara Stanwyck in movie 43?
She is not, and Robert Mitcham isn't either, unfortunately.
Which Barbara Stanwyck's movies have you watched of her?
Lady Eve, there's one.
Lady Eve, right. What's the other one?
I have to find the other one.
All right. Well, so let's move on to the Space Mountain
opening special, which is what won the poll,
what did end up winning the poll this month.
This is something from from 50 years ago this year.
Now that we are in 2025, which I didn't realize.
You know what? This very month is the month.
January 1975, 50 years ago is when Space Mountain opened.
Now, does that mean that this will be the year that we talk about
Space Mountain on the show?
My money's on. No.
We're not brave enough.
I don't know if we're ready.
I don't want to rule it out, but I don't know if we're ready.
There's quite a lot of them.
There are a lot of them being demolished as we speak.
That's true. Yes, that's true.
All right. New ones being rebuilt.
New times for Space Mountain.
But I would say then, if you find the name of the movie,
I just wanted to keep things, I just wanted to keep things moving.
No, I forget.
You didn't. There's no other movie.
I got to search my private letterbox.
You've been exploring the filmography.
I watched one movie.
Well, I certainly have read about both of them quite a lot.
Why? I've been exploring the Lyle Wagner filmography.
I watched one special and I for another one.
I think I forget.
I remembered the existence of the Linda Carter Wonder Woman.
Oh, that's right.
That was Lyle Wagner in his big role.
That and the Carol Burnett show, I think.
Yes. Yeah, Lyle Wagner, one of the hosts of this special,
has been on my radar not from watching anything,
but he's just kind of an interesting figure in Hollywood lore
because he apparently screen tested for Batman
and lost to Adam West, of course, and rightfully so.
But he ended up on Carol Burnett.
Thus, he was in kind of the like cool world of people
that P.T. Anderson's dad, Ernie Anderson, was in.
And because I'm interested in old Valley lore,
because I grew up in the Valley and licorice pizzas
set in the 70s and shot in the Valley,
all the scenes with Bradley Cooper as John Peters,
that's the guy's name, producer,
Robert Streisand's husband, the crazy Tudor style,
manor style house where all his scenes take place,
that is the former home of Lyle Wagner.
When he filmed this, that is where he lived.
He lived at that house. Wow.
Way up the hill in Encino,
and I know that because there's a really cool,
if you are into old San Fernando Valley stuff
or just licorice pizza, P.T. Anderson,
he did this great interview with a writer,
Esther Zuckerman, who wanted to talk to him
because that's the house she grew up in.
Her parents bought it from Lyle Wagner.
Oh, wow.
And then like, would he give me five minutes
to talk about this?
And he gave her half an hour.
And she started like,
no, I don't know if it was communicated to you why you were,
and he's like, no, no, no, I know.
Okay, so did you buy it from Lyle Wagner?
Like he just wanted to drive straight to it.
Love his old Valley shit.
That's cool.
And so this guy in the special, Lyle Wagner,
he left the Carol Burnett Show,
thus vacating the announcer spot,
which was taken over by Ernie Anderson,
P.T. Anderson's father.
The second Barbara Stanwyck movie is called
Sorry Wrong Number.
It was her fourth Academy Award nomination.
And the second lead in it is Burt Lancaster,
another great actor.
Yeah.
He is great.
Sweet Smell of Success, great movie.
Great.
I've never seen that.
Well, we got it.
You're gonna watch all four of those Oscar noms?
Let's make it true.
I don't know the other ones.
I should search them out.
You know, Tooby has quite a few classic movies.
Shout out to Tooby.
What about Jason takes us through the filmography
of Barbara Stanwyck as a club three suggestion?
Bugs shaking now.
You know what is very funny?
If you read the politics tab on her Wikipedia,
it is like the worst.
Like was anti-communist supported Dewey over Truman?
Like she kept picking losers.
Well, that'll be on the episode.
Yeah.
We'll explore it.
Explore her political leanings as well.
Okay, but to step back, the big stuff here.
This is an episode of The Wonderful World of Disney
that aired on March 23rd, 1975.
And though it ran through the poll
as the Space Mountain opening special,
and that is what it is,
and that's the thing that it leads to,
it is actually called Welcome to the World.
World is in quotes referring to Walt Disney World, you see.
So what this is is a special that is largely musical
in nature that runs throughout the vacation kingdom.
Those vibes are very strong.
That 70s leisure sports kind of vibe of early Disney World
because Disney World's only been open for,
not even for full years at the point that this is filmed.
Context, also the night that this aired,
March 23rd, 1975, this was on NBC.
On CBS, there was a new 60 Minutes,
an interview with Nixon Chief of Staff H.R. Haldeman,
then serving a prison sentence
for his role in the Watergate affair.
That is considered an early example.
I might've helped coin the term checkbook journalism,
where he was given a good degree of money
in order to do this interview.
And it's like, is that weird to be given money
to prisoners to talk about things?
But hey, you get the ratings.
Hey, look, Wonderful World of Disney
has Lucy Arnaz and Lyle Wagner.
We have Tommy Toon.
Holy shit.
Pay up to Haldeman.
Checkbook journalism, I think,
because I was always taught in college,
don't ever pay a subject.
Don't ever do this.
So I think it's paying the subject in general.
Now, jumping to Tommy Toon,
we said Mike knew something as just a reference.
Growing up, I always just knew Tommy Toon.
I feel like as a reference.
That's correct.
Any kid of our generation, if it's more than that,
there's something wrong.
It is a funny name.
You were raised correctly, is what that means.
Yeah, very acclaimed Broadway choreographer and dancer.
Yeah.
And one of the hosts of this,
it's a three-hander, right?
Lyle Wagner, as mentioned.
Tommy Toon, who's doing dance numbers throughout the thing,
who's, I don't think the only Disney special
with Tommy Toon in it, but a very lanky man,
the tallest man.
Very tall.
His Wikipedia online was talking about
how when he would go to auditions,
he would learn how to play, like bend a little
and like play down the stage.
So it looked like he was not that tall.
He's 6'6".
Yeah, wild.
Yeah, a 6'6 dancer feels weird.
That isn't common.
It feels like dancers are usually shorter.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe not.
I can't think of a very, very tall dancer.
No.
Look, not that I know a lot about dancers.
I don't have an encyclopedia of dancers in my head.
No, ventriloquist.
No, dummies, maybe.
Very tall ventriloquist.
I believe that height was difficult.
Like he had to learn to work around that height
as a dancer.
That's why I never got good at dancing,
because I'm 6'3".
You think without the height?
Without the height, I would have been on,
yeah, I would have been on Broadway.
I would have been in a ballet.
Who knows?
I was in a dance show in high school and I sucked.
I was bad.
And that's because of the height.
That's the only reason, the only reason.
Center of gravity weird.
Yep.
You were cursed with height.
Bad dancer.
But the third host of this,
and kind of the most present host in it,
I would say is Lucy Arnaz.
Oh my God, I forgot to do the thing
where I read the person's suggestion.
Oh, right, right.
I'll try to do that to make sure,
because that might also illuminate.
Here, I'll search for that.
Well, I'll search for that.
Well, I will give the floor to you guys,
because this seems like a good opportunity
for you to say a bunch of things about Lucy Arnaz
that are quickly proven untrue by our audience.
Well, this, Scott said this was a three-hander.
I think it becomes more of a one,
like there is a lot of Lucy Arnaz.
Lucy Arnaz is a star is what you're saying.
Yeah.
And Lucy Arnaz is the daughter of both Lucy and Desi.
And Desi, yes.
Not adopted by one, they, yeah, both of them.
Biological daughter.
Had a lot of projects, but my funny,
the funniest one I feel like is that Lucy Arnaz show
that aired in 1985, the New York Times Review said,
the always ingratiating Miss Arnaz as a psychologist
who not only writes an advice column,
but also takes calls from listeners
on her own radio program.
What?
That sounds like a show I've heard of before.
That's right.
What?
She did a Frasier before Frasier.
She did Frasier before Frasier.
Wow.
It's interesting with Lucy Arnaz.
I don't, did anything, did anything work necessarily?
Yeah, that's what I, yeah,
that's one of the things I wrote down.
It's like, what am I supposed to think about her?
Am I supposed to watch her and go very funny?
Or am I supposed to say, excellent singing?
He's not so.
Excellent dancing.
I don't know what my response to her is supposed to be.
None of it's bad.
Yeah, she's not bad.
She's like 24 years old in the special,
which is funny, cause she seems like she's 50.
I thought she was much older, yeah.
She's a good host.
I think she's a pretty good host.
She's got a very much like,
can you believe this guy?
Like that's sort of the delivery about with everything.
Yeah, yeah.
But certainly, you know,
was not even on my radar as a kid who knew about Lucy
growing up.
This was not present,
well, if I'm gonna be a fan of this,
then I have to know about what Lucy Arnaz is up to.
Right.
But that, I think I really learned about her
at the old Lucy museum.
Lucy Attribute.
Yeah, Lucy Attribute,
seeing the DVDs for sale for Here's Lucy.
And I'm like, what the hell is this?
This isn't I Love Lucy or the Lucy Show.
You said this, yeah.
We're talking about Here's Lucy.
And I'm like.
You were getting furious that you didn't know.
She had a show with the kids?
Yeah.
Like.
We talked about this in the Recently Unlocked episode.
So this is, we're in the middle of a five-timer right now.
We're in the middle of a new one, yeah.
And the story is you saw the show
and didn't know what it was.
Oh, yeah.
It was Gaston, it was Gaston episode
and you brought up the fact
that O.G. Simpson had just passed away.
And Jason and I were like,
duh, he was on Here's Lucy.
That's all we knew.
We didn't even know what happened
other than that he was on Here's Lucy once.
Who is the old movie star who's on Here's Lucy
and dances with Lucy and Lucy?
Ginger Rogers.
But you make a joke that that's the same episode
which I don't believe is the case.
It's not the same episode, no.
But you did say the same thing.
You went to Lucy's tribute and you said,
well, what the hell is this?
I've never heard of this before.
I was pretty intimidated.
That's strange, why are you mad?
I wasn't mad.
Something I don't know.
I was just shocked it never showed up in syndication.
The way you make it seem,
and you made it seem like this today
was that you were a little bit upset.
That's how I read to me, I agree.
I was a little upset that I didn't know about it.
Yeah.
Oh, you were mad at yourself for failing.
I already lived a Tommy Toon-less childhood.
Now here I am.
I've wasted years on this planet.
Punching yourself.
Not knowing about a show not good enough for syndication.
God, stupid Jason.
Tommy Toon, one of his big Broadway things,
he choreographed Nine,
which is the musical based on Fellini's Eight and a Half.
Okay.
And that's, Jane loves Nine and I love Eight and a Half.
And somehow we make it work.
That's a joke that Lucy Ernest would have done
on a special.
That's right.
Right.
Get out of here.
Somehow we make it work.
Let me read the thing now that I have it.
This is from Iceberg77779.
With Disney World Space Mountain turning 50 next month,
I think it's finally time
to cover the ride's opening day special.
This special features very little Space Mountain.
Ah, our ears have perked up.
Very little of the ride in the episode.
Sounds like a podcast the ride, doesn't it?
But it does have unsafe dancing,
a 10 minute banana themed musical number.
And I have to say, I wish I'd read that part
before I allowed this to be in the,
although this was the popular vote,
so it's in No Matter What.
And most importantly, Scratchy Voiced Mickey Mouse.
We'll make it to that.
Yeah.
A little later.
But yeah, so that is correct.
We, what we have, I feel like this might've like,
this might've fooled people in a way,
calling it the Space Mountain opening special,
because like, if we had to put a percentage on it,
what do you, Space Mountain content
in this Space Mountain special.
3%?
God, I was gonna go higher even,
but I think you're right.
I think it's, yeah.
So little.
Yeah, yeah.
And I both don't like it and like it.
Because like, do I wanna see Lucy Arnaz
in like some green, like early green screen space situation?
Yes.
Do I wanna see Tommy Toon dancing on the moon?
Yeah, it should've been more,
yeah, what they did, but more about space.
Right, so like that's where I'm upset by the lack of space.
But it's fine, it's good.
Yeah.
For what it is.
Well, let me play a little of what you do get.
This is a good, where like, what,
now you might wanna alter that 3%
because the song I'm gonna play
technically counts as Space Mountain content,
because they do say Space Mountain in it.
Okay, fair enough, fair enough.
But I think you'll find that it is not particularly on brand
with the Space Mountain that we know today.
We've been invited to Disney World
to see Space Mountain.
We're travel and life, we brought a smile,
a dance, a song.
I'd like to sing.
Fresh flowers?
A tub.
I'll need a key size bed.
That, by the way, they're all checking in
at registration desks.
They're checking in at the then three places
you could stay on Disney World property.
One's at Polynesian, one's at Contemporary,
and one is at, what is it,
I get the wildernesses, was it Fort Wilderness
at the time?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Seems like logistically terrible,
they'd probably put them all up
at the same place, but go on.
That's, yeah, yeah, true, yeah, yeah.
But they wanna feature the different places
and amenities and vibes, you see.
Well, you have to.
Did you say Space Mountain at Disney World?
Walt Disney World?
That's a frequent facet of this is ghostly applause
that comes from nowhere and often you're like,
what are you applauding for?
Yeah, laughter and clapping when they're outside
and there's no studio audience.
What I just showed you, why did they clap?
To signal to a viewer that this is over.
Because they walked away?
Well, they sang and then they finished it,
walked away, the song ended.
Somebody was watching it and went,
people are gonna be confused, where are they going?
Why are they leaving?
So clapping signifies that the number is over.
Because you have to check in
and then you drop your bags with the bellman.
What a hotel is.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, that is a weird,
that clapping is weird the whole time.
There's a lot of it and there's times where,
one thing that happens in this,
not to jump around too much, but we certainly get,
it's not like the plot is so confusing
that we can't jump around,
but Tommy Toon does dancing in a lot of odd places
in the park.
You know, he'll be, you'll see his feet
and then you'll see that he's on a boat.
And then you'll see his feet
and then you'll see that he's up high on a building.
And sometimes the reveal of where he is gets a laugh
and sometimes it gets a clap.
The claps are impressive and the laughs are funny.
And I don't, why is the boat a laugh?
But then he's like next to balloons and that's a clap.
It's a good question.
I actually didn't even think about that.
I feel like they may just wanted to have varied it up.
Cause it doesn't seem like it has too much.
I mean, I guess he shouldn't be dancing on the boat.
That's silly.
This must be the unsafe dancing
that the iceberg referred to.
Right.
Jason, what did you think of when Tommy Toon
was dancing on the boat?
Well, I thought it was very fun.
I assumed this was topic was picked
cause they're like, oh, this has vintage,
I love vacation kingdom Disney world.
Yeah.
And once I saw- You're saying it's for you,
it's picked for you.
Well, that part is for me,
but I think especially for you,
these very old now, or in some cases, dead actors.
Or for you-
In almost all cases, dead.
No, two of them are still alive.
Toon's alive.
Oh, of the people we're talking about.
Oh, I see.
Oh, you mean in this.
I just meant that Mike veers to dead actors in general.
Right.
Wagner has passed.
Winchell is dead.
Huh?
Paul Winchell is dead.
Winchell is dead.
And Jerry Mahoney, where's Jerry Mahoney?
Oh, good, good.
Remember we talked about this.
The kingdom is alive, and Wayland Flowers is dead.
What's that word?
And potentially staying in a home.
All right.
And Mama thriving.
Well, that's a whole different thing.
I disagree, disagree.
That's a whole different topic.
Not here, she's not.
But this just had so many,
and it had some little numbers.
I love that.
I love that number, the opening number was great.
I love the split screen.
That must've been very hard production wise,
but they got it done.
Well, here's what we're learning is that, so you,
all right, I think we're landing at Jason,
who loved it.
Mike?
Here's what happened.
Or here's what happened.
Okay.
So lately on the show,
I feel like anytime we watch something,
I will admit that Mickey's Nutcracker, Generation X,
I've been a little like,
eh, what are these things sometimes?
You know, I'm not so into it.
Jason loves everything.
That's just how it goes.
I'm like a child about to be handed a cotton candy thing,
and I'm just laughing.
Jason's into it all.
There's people on screen.
They're smiling and dancing in some cases.
It's late last night, and I'm like,
I have to finally watch the special,
and it's very late,
and I first watch Kenny Omega's Return to Wrestling
after diverticulitis.
I watch this live.
It's around 1130 or midnight.
That's a living person.
I don't know how I feel about this.
Yes, he's a living professional wrestler.
It's in a masterpiece.
It's 31 minutes.
Tanahashi, the president of New Japan,
is crying after the match.
They're in the Tokyo Dome.
Kenny's back after a year.
I'm like fucking psyched.
It's late, I'm exhausted, but I'm late,
and I go, now I gotta watch
the Space Mountain opening special.
You have to be welcome to the world.
Have to be welcome to the world.
And I think I was riding the high of this match
that as I'm watching Space Mountain opening
and Tommy Toon is dancing all along Walt Disney World,
I think I said to myself, I love this.
Oh, oh, I wasn't sure where this was going.
Wow.
I think I was in such a good mood
from this bloody match that I had just watched.
You're just like, wow, what the human body is capable of.
I was like, holy shit.
Vigorous wrestling to unexpected dancing.
Tommy Toon on the top of the riverboat,
and I'm like, this is pretty good.
I mean, the second half is less fun
than the first half of the special.
Yeah, that's where I struggle.
But the first half, I'm like, this is pretty good.
And then there would be segments where I'm like,
I don't know about this segment.
Then something would happen and I'd go,
this is a good segment.
Here come the country bears.
This is a good segment.
I love the country bears.
I was skeptical of the toy soldiers.
And then there was a lot of them
and they were all tapping and I liked it.
That's the one I didn't get.
There's like, they reveal, there's just two.
Lucy Hernandez is with two soldiers.
And then it cuts wide and it shows
that there's lots of soldiers
and that gets a big fake applause break.
And I was like, why?
Why is that gonna applause?
They're coordinating.
They're moving in unison, in patterns.
I like it.
It's cumbersome costumes.
I think the adrenaline started to wear off
by the time I got to the toy soldiers.
So you're gonna have my back in some of this.
I'm not trying to, by the way, this is me calibrating.
I'm like, oh, I don't wanna be doing like,
Scott's being a stick in the mud in an episode
where it seems like there's like half the room.
I also like plenty of this, by the way.
But it seems like, don't let me step on your joy here.
It's about halfway when like all the people are there
and it like changes tone that I started to go.
Not that it's such a dark tone or something, but.
The banana midway.
The banana, I'll be the downer here.
The banana is intolerable.
Oh, thank you, thanks.
That was my, thank you.
I don't like the banana.
I don't think Iceberg did either.
I thought that was gonna be a punchline
or like just a non sequitur.
Like they're just, when they were singing,
yes, we have no bananas.
And then it just kept going and going.
I like all the characters.
I like all the old characters.
When my brain slows down and goes,
is this Space Mountain special?
Yeah.
Cause even the first part I'm still like,
it's not Space Mountain special, but look at Tommy Goh.
Like it doesn't matter.
My brain is firing, it's happy.
But then at this point you're like, okay, I don't know.
I'm about ready for, because like a modern,
like maybe today they would blend it
and make it like a sneak preview.
But if they tell you at the beginning,
like a Galaxy's Edge opening special
is not gonna be like 80% dance numbers.
No.
And a song about like a sad song
about how you stayed too long at the fair.
Yeah.
What does that have to do with the songs?
Sobering, yeah, I had too much fun with those bananas.
And now look at me, a broken woman.
I will be very excited if the next Megatrader appearance,
she does the full trolley song
from Meet Me in St. Louis.
For which ride would that be?
What's the next ride opening?
Well, she'll just be riding the main street trolley
up and down.
I know, but would it be like an opening day special
for some new ride?
For the Avengers-y ticket.
The Avengers, yeah, that's a good one.
Yeah, like I'm Googling every song
and I'm like, what does this song have to do with,
because they do the, the next song is,
it's not where you start from the musical Seesaw.
Did you know this?
I have heard of the musical Seesaw,
but I don't really know it.
Yeah, I'm like, it's not where you start,
it's where you finish.
And you're like, okay.
That's what I didn't know if these were original songs
for this special.
This is like a somewhat popular at the time musical
called Seesaw, which you look up the original cast,
which included Tommy Toon,
and also included Giancarlo Esposito.
Really?
Yeah, which is 1973.
But then-
He was in shows with Tommy Toon in 73?
Yes, and he's at his peak today.
Oh my God.
Yes, it's wild.
He was at it for a long time.
But then when the Broadway run ended,
Tommy Toon went on the road with the traveling version
of the show with Lucy Arnaz.
Okay.
She says at one point we were in a Broadway show together.
That's what this is, and this is a nod to that show.
So they're doing songs from Seesaw,
because the viewers might know them
from Seesaw coming to their town.
It's possible the viewers know them from Seesaw.
Interesting.
So that inherent chemistry,
that crackle of Lucy and Toon.
So they were like, I don't know if they were like,
yeah, we'll do it, but we gotta do one of our songs
from the musical.
And what's happening in that song?
Do you remember what that's paired with visually?
Well, that's like, oh shoot,
that's when they're talking about how it's not,
she's going across the lawn of the Polynesian
at that point early on.
Is that when they're getting from their separate hotels
to the park? Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, and then they ended the different Main Street vehicles,
and then they all meet up in all of Main Street.
Well, I like that.
That all was fun enough.
And you're seeing those paddleboats
out in the Seven Seas Lagoon.
Oh, the coordinated paddleboats were very fun,
the putt-putt boats.
Yeah.
Tommy is wearing a wild outfit.
It looks like he's wearing a tank,
a long sleeve tank top or something,
or a V-neck long sleeve shirt that's pink,
an open blue denim shirt.
He's got chaps on, like a cowboy it looks like,
unless those are built into the pants,
and then jeans as well.
He's got this flowing long hair,
and he's 6'6", and he's on a miniature horse,
which is really interesting.
He's a very, he's a very 70s man.
The most 70s man I've ever seen, yes.
And he's riding a tiny horse that he is too big for.
I liked when he rode the tiny horse
and all the bicyclists showed up.
Yeah, and that's a laugh that you understand at least
why they added the fake laugh to it.
Yeah, some say, yeah, they aren't all confusing.
One thing I thought when I was watching this,
I was like, already he's on a train.
What the hell train is this?
This ain't the Disney World train.
This ain't the Magic Kingdom train.
This is a Four Wilderness train, is what this is.
I didn't know they had a train.
Yeah, I didn't either.
Did you know?
That yeah was all like, yeah, I know, I know.
I do know, yeah.
What else do you know about the train?
Is it operational?
That I don't know.
No, it was very briefly in the 70s.
It was just a couple years.
Because they get on it in a weird spot.
That's when I went, what is this?
Yeah, that's how I felt.
Yeah, we're in Disney World, this is a train,
but I've never seen this train before.
The train was apparently functional
and miles long of a track
because it was to get people from Four Wilderness
to just pretty far back there over to river country.
That was the need for that train.
But they stopped running it mid 70s
and today at least one of the engines
owned by John Lasseter
Well.
On the winery grounds.
There's a name I haven't heard in a long time.
Mm-hmm, the hug express he calls it today.
Choo-choo.
Choo-choo, he wants some of that huggy.
Is he still at Skydance Animation?
I believe so, yeah.
So we, oh, because that means
he would be involved in all the Paramount stuff.
Jason, I don't know anything about that.
I feel like people are worried like,
oh my God, is Lasseter about takeover Nickelodeon?
Oh, it's possible.
Anything's possible.
Now there is a song in this
that I was previously familiar with
from one of Doug Jones's great DVDs
and cut downs of Disney World specials.
I definitely knew from that,
he pulled out the song by the Rhodes kids.
At some point we go to a family band
that is so Osmonds, that's so Partridge,
that's so Brady's, I would say that's so Jackson's
except it's so white that you can't really say
it's so Jackson's.
The whitest family band,
the most 70s family band you've ever seen
because we're in full.
You know what, it actually reminded me of Lickersh Pizza
when Cooper is in the,
he's with the cast of Yours, Mine, and Ours.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With Lucy, they don't call Lucy
but on this variety show.
Because it's like a whole band of Danny Bonaducis.
It's all Bonaducis and they do,
they come out of what I recognized immediately
as the sunny eclipse spot.
I don't think I realized that the sunny eclipse spot
was a genuine bandstand area that did the Disneyland thing
where the stage rises up from the bottom.
I don't think I knew that.
So they rise up from the bottom
and perform a very groovy song called I Like You.
Yeah, that's what I wrote.
All right.
["I Like You"]
I like the summer when the sun is shining
You make me glad in the sun
And I like to get when the snow is falling
You make the moon light stay bright
I like being me
I like when I see
When I see you smile
There's something likable about this
in sort of a, like, I'd like to buy the world a Coke.
I tend to like corporate attempts at 70s music,
like written by some stiff man,
like yeah, we're gonna make a hit for the now generation.
Yeah, and it's late.
Even when it fails, I kinda like,
it still lands somewhere I like.
I like all the Partridge music.
Yeah, and Partridge Family, this is like, this is 75.
I don't know when that song was written,
but it feels a little late.
Yeah.
Maybe that's wrong, but Partridge Family starts in 1970.
So like, come on, get happy, around then.
By the way, all that Partridge music,
much better than what I just played,
but they got some bangers.
This feels very much like the Simpsons joke
of the hooray for everything.
Yeah, for sure, yes.
I know it reminds you that there was stuff
very much like that, yeah.
So they're so polyester and vests and matching pants,
and then they come strolling down
the main Tomorrowland thoroughfare, like arm in arm,
and that has a really inexplicable applause break
where the little one gets ahead of the group
and then realizes he has to run back.
Oh no, it gets a laugh, it gets a laugh.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're laughing at that fake audience?
We put in a laugh there?
The joke is that he didn't realize they were stopping,
and then they do like,
like, it almost looks like an improvised choreographed dance.
Yeah, yes, they're like.
They are not too on it, I think there's a reason
why we haven't heard of the Rhodes kids.
Yeah, I looked, there's not a lot of Rhodes kids material.
There's not a lot, did you find though,
there's almost only one thing you can find,
and it's from a Houston newspaper,
because they're from Houston,
or somewhere in Texas, I believe,
and they uncovered a very strange fact
about the Rhodes kids.
You might have a different thing,
I just saw that their mom was a pianist,
and their dad was a chemical engineer for Exxon.
It's not that, I guess the Exxon involvement is sort of dark.
No, no, no, it's crazy than that.
So they were on something called GRC Records,
and that was run out of Atlanta,
and it was run by Atlanta's biggest music impresario,
Michael Thevis.
Oh, I didn't see this.
And Michael Thevis, he,
not only was the credited executive producer,
and like the, you know, the head of the label,
he also put pen to paper,
and wrote a big old note in their Christmas album,
Rockin' Rhodes Christmas,
about like how he, it's not worth reading,
but just like it blew me away.
The house lights went down, the spots flashed up,
and pow, seven kids sang and played,
not with real pros.
And he's saying, I had jet lag and fatigue,
and I was in Vegas, and instead I was just,
I was with a bunch of pros.
The 10-year-old did an incredible imitation
of Tom Jones and demolished the,
literally demolished the hotel lobby.
That's one of those wrong,
you used to literally say Thevis,
but I get your point.
Anyway, this guy, if you look up his Wikipedia,
you will quickly find his nicknames,
the King of Pornography, the Sultan of Smut,
and the Scarface of Sex.
I thought those were Jason's nicknames.
He grabbed them in the art sale after Thevis is passing.
I'm no Thevis, but they were a real steal
when he got washed up.
No, this guy, he was like big in not,
I think, I mean, I think like pornographic films in general,
but like specifically peep machines,
like things where you gotta peer in and insert a coin,
and then you get to peep with some naked ladies.
And this special, this airs in 75,
and I think that's around when he wrote this note,
am I correct?
Or no, 72.
All right, what I just read,
he wrote their liner notes in 72.
By that point, he's writing that on a typewriter
or with a pen and paper with his hands,
his hands that had already been used to shoot
and kill a rival peep machine maker.
Oh my God.
Which he just fully got away with.
Oh wow.
It was a guy who used to work for him,
and then he started his own peep machine company.
And he said, would you mind coming to my office?
Okay, Thevis called me in, huh?
Maybe he wants to do a deal with me,
the new king of peep machines.
Hey, come in, pow, pow, pow.
I did not see this.
Kills him, wraps up his bloody body
in padding meant to transport peep machines.
This poses a body, this is still around.
Then a couple years later, blew up a guy with a pipe bomb.
And as always, this is all concurrent with,
and I got the Rhodes kids out there,
I put them on Welcome to the World.
In 78, he was finally caught, went to jail,
escaped jail,
thus putting him at that time
on the FBI's Ten Most Wanted list.
Oh my God.
He's a graduate of the Ten Most Wanted list,
died in jail in 2013.
He, like Lyle Waggoner,
owned a Tudor-style manor in Atlanta,
a 30-room mansion.
That's where he was doing all of this bidding.
The peeping.
And that mansion was purchased in the 90s
by Whitney Houston and Bobby Brown.
Wow.
Whitney Houston lived in this guy's,
in this crazy guy's house,
when I Will Always Love You was happening.
That's wild.
Yep, yeah.
Whoa.
So when you watch this cheery performance,
just imagine one peep machine
make her murdering another.
Did Lucy Arnaz live in a notable house, Scott?
You know, probably, I actually,
I genuinely believe that if you asked my dad this question,
he would know, because my dad,
I pick up some of this from my dad,
because he knows a lot of, like,
if you drive around in C&O and Sherman Oaks,
he knows a lot, like, oh, that's where this guy lived,
and that's where this guy lived.
Oh, wow.
He also, I remember him telling me
about Lyle Waggoner a long time ago,
because Lyle Waggoner is spelled with two Gs,
as is Star Wagon's, the trailers that you use
if you're in a movie or TV show,
and that's because that was a company started by him.
He diversified his business and started a,
he was working on, what was the,
it was the comic show, he was on Wonder Woman.
When he was working on that,
he was in some trailer, and he was like,
where'd this trailer come from?
Oh, they would, like, lease it from this guy,
and he's like, hmm, what if I could be that guy?
And he just bought trailers,
and now it's the main brand of trailers in the world.
That's crazy. Yeah, yeah.
This guy who makes almost no impression
in this special otherwise.
Yeah, no, he's not,
he's the least interesting of the three.
No, yeah, it's all off the page,
what's interesting about Waggoner.
I feel like they had him for a day, day and a half,
like, I feel like.
Yeah, less time than Tommy.
Get to show what he can do.
I feel like he probably wanted to get in and out.
I would say I have no sense of what he can do.
I don't know. It's just a guy,
he's a handsome guy.
Oh, yeah, I've seen a few Wonder Woman's,
not recently, but it's fine.
I don't really remember anything about him.
But I'd kill to go to a poker game at this guy's house.
I'd love to hang with him.
His mansion, yeah, yeah.
I mean, he's passed away, but I'd love to hang with him.
Playing Steve Trevor in Wonder Woman,
same character as Chris Pine.
Chris Pine.
Oh, oh, gotcha, oh, he's that character.
Okay, okay.
Anyway, well, that's, let's see, other stuff,
that covers a lot of those, that covers Rhodes,
that covers Theavis.
Scotty Plummer.
Scotty Plummer, would you care to explain Scotty Plummer?
Scotty Plummer, okay, so in the middle of this special,
Lucy Arnaz gets accosted on Main Street
by a kid who's like, I've loved you forever.
I'm 14.
And she's like, hey, wait a minute,
don't you dabble in music too?
And he's like, yeah, I'm Scotty Plummer.
He's a little 14-year-old boy.
It looks like he's wearing a plastic red wig.
He looks like he's a Lego piece or something.
He's got such a perfectly round head of red hair.
His pants, shirt, and belt also look molded.
It's the most 70s outfit you've ever seen.
Yes, he's a 70s red-haired little boy.
Yeah.
14-year-old boy.
Yet more, they aren't all in the Rhodes kids.
There's still more.
But there's different flavors of 70s kids.
Redheads, 70s redheads, yeah.
So they kind of run around Disney World
and do like a montage,
because Lucy's like, we've got so much to do.
We got to see everything.
And then after that, he's like, I'm worn out, Lucy.
Or he says, I think he says, I'm plum tuckered.
And then she says, everyone needs
their plum tuckered once in a while.
Dare you, Lucy.
He's 14.
She's 14 years old.
Yeah, I was conflicted,
because I'm like, that's a pretty good line.
But also, that's very weird to say to a 14-year-old.
Did you know that I was at Target,
and they sell a plum tucker in the pharmacy section.
Oh, yeah?
Bright purple.
That's right.
The wellness area?
That's right, yeah.
Yes, weird.
That's also one of the old days
where I feel like you would have asked them,
and she would be like, oh, that's just nothing.
They weren't even thinking
that I'm making a sex joke to a child.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, it just sounds like something.
It's just like a thing.
I've said this before.
You watch some old Bing Crosby stuff,
and sometimes there's just repeating the rhythm
of what should be a joke.
Not even really a joke, if you think about it.
It just moves fast enough
that you don't stop and question it.
Right. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there is a May-December vibe,
but not a two-hour heart-wrenching movie.
Between the two, you mean?
Between the two.
Oh, you got the vibe.
There is a week.
No, it's just that long.
It's an Anakin-Padme situation.
Oh, I guess so.
From Phantom Menace.
It's about the same age spread, I think.
I don't like getting my plum tuckered.
Well, no, it would be Jake Lloyd saying,
This is why we need Bugmane to clarify these things here,
and he would know.
You're not getting your plum tuckered, right?
Like the meme.
Yes.
So then Scotty does a little number,
because Scotty Plumber was a banjo prodigy.
Yes.
And he does a little dance, too.
He does a little tap.
He dances a little bit.
He dances. He plays the banjo.
He plays the banjo.
He has a hootenanny going on.
Yeah, the country bears show up for the hootenanny.
Seeing the suited country bears is always a delight.
This is another one where I was like,
okay, this section's okay, or whatever.
A little boy's dancing and playing the fucking banjo?
I'm back in.
Now I'm back in.
My adrenaline shoots again through the roof.
Now I know that you're all about hillbilly nonsense.
I'm a big hillbilly nonsense guy.
These things I learned.
Do you guys know who Billy Strings is?
That's a guy who plays the guitar.
He's a young man, 31.
I assumed that was your name when you...
Billy Strings?
Well, when you start out with the ventriloquist Ws,
because there's so many Strings.
Well, that's more of a Pinocchio.
Oh, that's a marionette.
We didn't even get into how marionettes are different.
Not a marionette guy.
Not a marionette person.
You're more of a marionette guy, I think, than I am.
Yeah, we've done some comedy
where you made me play with a little puppet boy before.
Yeah, we bought a marionette for you,
but it wasn't because I have a thing for marionettes.
I just think... You just know about them.
Well, I don't even want to say I know about them.
I don't know the history of marionettes.
I don't want to say something wrong here.
Okay.
Because there's probably marionette enthusiasts out there.
Well, anyway, I had a diversion
because I couldn't remember the last name,
and I saw Scottie Plummer did open for Liberace,
and I'm like, no way. Oh, yes, I saw that too.
This isn't the Scott, and then I confirmed that
Scott Thorson is not Scott Plummer,
or else Mike would have called or texted
if it had been Scott Thorson in the middle of a special.
Scott Thorson was playing the banjo
on a Disney World special.
I didn't.
I would have said we're doing the episode now.
Well, we would have done it five years ago, yeah.
Yeah. Right.
So I got a little caught up in that, just confirming that.
That's confusing, because he does like, yeah,
he has an affinity for Scots,
and he likes talented youngsters.
Surprised he didn't get the Rhodes kids.
They're the new generation, and I'm not just saying this
because Michael Thevis dangled me out a balcony window.
He was on a special that I've never seen,
Scottie Plummer was, called Lucy Moves to NBC,
which I wouldn't need to watch.
I did see that, yeah, because she used to be on CBS.
I don't know, there was something.
And they made a big deal out of it.
Tread lightly, guys.
You're gonna start getting your corrections.
I've got the question marks in there.
That's what J.T. Jason said it.
I think Lucy Arnaz got her show on CBS.
Well, I'm being very careful about it.
I didn't say anything untrue about marionettes or anything.
I just said, I don't know, it's not my business to say.
And I'm saying I don't know as well.
Okay, good, good.
Yeah, and Scottie Plummer passed away, sadly,
in the early 90s.
He got in an accident, so he did not live.
He's not currently alive.
So I guess that's another person who has passed away
that Jason was missing out on.
Yeah, I confuse that.
I thought he was still alive,
because he was so young.
Scott Thorson also passed away recently.
Have you seen Behind the Candelabra, Jason?
Not all of it.
Somehow I've never seen all of it.
That's my Scottie's favorite movie.
It's an HBO TV movie, right?
It's gotta be on Mac still, yeah.
It's meant for theatrical,
but it was too daring at the time.
Right, because Matt Damon Kisses, Matt Douglas,
Michael Douglas.
Well, it goes further than kissing, I would say.
Well, right, but I'm just saying.
Hand holding?
You don't see Michael Douglas' dick getting sucked,
and it doesn't happen.
No, not literally, no.
No, I'm just saying visually.
Yes, what they're implying, obviously,
is more than kissing.
Yeah, there's a big dance with soldiers.
Now, see, this is where we're very different,
because you were like, I love it,
and that's around where I wrote the word interminable.
Right, that was my reaction to the next number,
but I didn't like it when she was floating
with two immobile toy soldiers,
but then when they started moving
and all the other guys came out,
they had a big aerial shot.
I was like, okay, I like this now.
They were setting it up.
Okay, this pays off.
I think my interminable actually may have been
for the next thing, though,
because the next thing is where we get into
what Iceberg mentioned, which is the banana.
Do they clear out all of Adventureland?
Is that what we're looking at?
Yeah, I think so.
And it's just a big, big nightclub, basically,
in which the two boys, the goofs, Lyle and Tommy,
start with, yes, we have no bananas,
which I assume was number three on Jason's Spotify raps.
Only because he doesn't use it often.
Local files.
He has that on a local file he listens to more.
But then we're mixing all these banana songs.
This is, this is really, oh.
Can I real quick side note, just a quick question,
because we have this on the last second gate
that we recorded, or two ago.
You used Apple Music, we had a misunderstanding,
that you use Apple Music primarily to listen
to your albums that you have locally?
Yeah, I always forget it's not called.
Do you do it on your phone or your computer, generally?
And Shin, would this be a good time for me
to use the restroom?
If you want, I'm getting somewhere,
is that Apple Music also has a list
of most listened to songs for the year.
So potentially.
For locally downloaded songs?
That's what I wanna know.
If you have a list of what actually is your top 10 songs
listened to in the year.
I mean, you can take a look,
and we'll see if it has that.
I mean, I'll look now, any time I touch any tab
besides albums.
I can find it for you if you want,
but I'm just saying we will be able to see the actual list
if indeed it shows local files.
That's all I'm saying.
So we'll see truly if Sabrina Carpenter is number one.
He's not gonna, Andrew, you're gonna see tab after tab,
open tab after open tab of target sex toys.
And peep show machines.
Personal peep machines.
At home peep machines.
And Apple notes he's made to himself.
Start peep show machine business.
No, Thebes is dead.
There's a new Scarface of Sex in town.
And there's like a diagram he's drawn with his finger
on the Apple note of a new machine he's concocting.
Peep machines are back.
The kids like vinyl, and the kids like peep machines.
The only tabs I have are radio library.
I'm gonna have to, would you feel comfortable
sliding your phone to me?
No. I'm not going anywhere
other than if I promise you,
I will not look at your texts or anything.
Would you feel comfortable?
And I'm laughing, but I swear
I will not go through anything else.
I know on the air, you maybe would believe me off air
more than you would on air.
I do.
Okay, what if I come over?
I will take the microphone off the stand.
Yeah, do that.
And I will guide you and see if we find it.
Scott, you didn't like the toy soldiers?
No, I know.
I think we covered that.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I think we didn't talk enough
how good the Tommy Toon section is
where he's dancing on top of buildings.
Do we need to say more about that?
I think it's pretty good.
I say it's very good.
What do we do now?
Now that you guys are phone fiddling over there,
what am I supposed to do?
Well, what else?
By the end of the special, I'll tell you what I find funny.
The actual ceremony for Space Mountain.
Yes, we do get into it.
They introduce all these astronauts and scientists,
most of them just nod to the crowd.
Yes, just kind of angry looking.
This is important that they,
I think we all associate Space Mountain with space travel.
We certainly just don't think
it's a cool roller coaster in the dark.
It's like, this is a tribute to our brave astronauts.
So they must be here for the opening, right?
This is impossible to do because I'm talking to Jason.
We're trying to, but he's peering at his own phone
because he's afraid that you're gonna end up looking
at his like, save number for a prone boneologist.
I don't think there's any.
I've only been at Apple Music though.
I think, okay, what it is I think is Jason,
they don't have the tab because you're not subscribed,
but I do believe it would show up if you were subscribed.
They would have shown.
So if I wanted to pay $10,
I believe we could unlock it is what I'm saying.
I would be willing to pay $10 for Jason to unlock,
but we should do that off the air.
All right.
I'm not going in on this.
I don't need to know this.
I know one of his music lists.
I don't need the rest.
If the listeners want to go in on it, that's fine.
I do need the rest.
So should they Venmo you then for the 10?
If the listener wants to Venmo me.
I don't know how Apple Music also says Chappell Rhone
like everyone else, but it does.
This is what I'm saying.
Every week it's like, I am relevant.
Sabrina Carpenter, Chappell Rhone.
I said the names again.
We are not old.
We are not 40 or above it.
I could have gone through the list of albums
though he has in the library.
Maybe I should have done that now that I'm thinking about it
when I was over there.
Cause that does show up.
What is your end game here?
What are we trying to do to our friend here?
I'm just wondering if Sabrina Carpenter
would be number one there too.
That's what I'm saying.
I want to know because-
I don't use it that much.
Okay. You don't use Apple Music that much?
No.
Okay.
Well, I just want to see if they lined up.
Who's listening and going, thank God Mike kept,
we, they veered out of this territory
at space mountain speed before.
We need more of Jason, more haranguing Jason
about his track.
We have arrived at the entryway of space mountain
in the special.
I did have stuff to say before I let Scott talk about
off-brand Mickey.
Yeah. The scientists, you're right, Scott,
they mostly glower at the camera.
One of them says a brief introduction
and then they all clap that space mountain is open.
There is a marching band walking on the people movement track.
But at that time of day, it was mostly in shadows.
You could hear a marching band
and see shadowy figures walking on the track.
Yeah. They're behind rails and yeah,
nobody's got a good shot of them,
but they do cover that all.
It's interesting to see a bunch of people
walking on a track, 2000 member band.
You have to see how they did ride openings at this time.
They didn't have to get no fancy Hollywood stars.
They just needed fancy astronauts,
fancy guys who've been to the stars.
That's right.
They get Jim Irwin, the eighth man on the moon.
He's there.
They had 2000 marching band guys,
a pageant of nations is something they said happens.
And I don't remember really what that was comprised of.
I think they should have put the marching band
in people mover vehicles.
Like two to four in each vehicle
and then they're just running and playing their instruments.
I think that would have been fun.
I wonder if that would be less safe.
Yeah, possibly to have to operate and just tidy,
you gotta like space out those horns.
Yeah, probably not safe walking,
but maybe worse in the vehicles.
I mean, they don't let people have selfie sticks today,
much less a tuba.
I looked up these astronauts
and the reason I looked them up, as I said,
do any of these astronauts believe in UFOs?
You're trying anything you can to get your UFO.
We got a winner, folks.
Oh, man.
Gordon Cooper.
The first man to spend an entire day in space.
Gordon Cooper believes that the government
has been covering up UFOs.
He has testified this.
He says there's been hundreds of reports by people,
different pilots.
He did not see one in space,
but he saw one in a mission
when he was flying over West Germany in 1951.
So he is a guy, like many other people
who worked in the government,
who believe that UAP or UFOs are real.
So my guy here, I found an interview with him
where he seems like he never blinks
and it's kind of a scary interview.
Yeah.
Jesus, Gordon.
Appears to be at a funeral floral this week.
This is 1999.
The film quality is oddly eerie in some ways too
that makes it look like his skin
is like some sort of like puppet or plastic.
Like I'm just like,
there's a lot of things going on.
He looks like a damaged wax figure of Ed Harris.
Yes, that's a very good way to put it.
And it looks like he's,
the backdrop is like a Sears portrait studio or something,
like a red silk curtain is behind him.
So you're saying he believes the government
is covering up UFOs.
Yes, he's seen personally has seen something
like a saucer thing that flies in like inexplicable ways.
Isn't that a given?
Is that that unusual to think?
What do you mean?
Oh, I just thought that since I was a child,
the government was covering up UFOs.
Oh, well, some people would doubt you're serious.
I am serious, yeah.
Well, I think as a kid,
you're like, oh, probably the government,
it's a big coverup in Area 51.
And then as you get old,
this is my arc at least,
then as you get older, you go,
wow, that's all kind of nonsense or whatever.
But then slowly, especially in the last 10 years,
I do believe that they have been covering up.
Yes, I believe there's something going on.
I don't know that it's like green man.
It's like a fun Mars attacks situation.
But there's definitely a bunch of weird stuff
that no one can explain that some of it documented,
some of it not.
Why don't I care about this?
A lot of people don't care.
Do you find on the other end,
when you go into this, which I'm sure you do,
do you find a lot of on the other end,
just kind of like start to zone as I zone?
I'm not saying you're wrong or right.
But I think I am saying that deep into a podcast episode.
The majority of people don't care.
There's been a bunch of public hearings recently
where people say crazy stuff in the public hearing,
seemingly like reasonable seeming people who go,
there have been bodies recovered from craft.
People have been injured recovering bodies from craft.
We don't know what it is.
Like Boeing or other companies like retake technology,
they use it to make some crazy,
like there's all of these crazy statements saying,
this is nowhere near major headlines.
No one's talking about it.
No one gives a shit.
So you're not alone.
Most people are just like, yeah, that was weird.
Yeah, that's about all I can muster.
No disrespect to it.
I just go, oh really?
I just think it's, yeah.
So you're not wrong.
It's the majority of people right now.
They're like, I got bigger things to worry about.
Call me when the ET is on the TV.
Like that's the majority of people.
Put a camera in front of them
when they're ready to address me.
Call me when the ET is on the TV
and then I'll be interested.
But let me ask you this though.
What do you think about,
do you have any opinion on it in general?
Do you go, ah, that's weird, I don't know.
Is that your opinion? I'm about there.
I'm about there.
I'm similar to, I got nothing on ghosts.
I know there's a lot in podcast world
about like let's tell ghost stories
and you must have a ghost, I got nothing.
If that was posed to me on some show, I'd have zero.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe I'm not imaginative enough.
I'm not a ghost guy, I wouldn't say.
I'm not a ghost guy.
I'm not a Sasquatch guy.
It's just the same feeling from, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe, could be.
I also don't necessarily think that an alien is an alien.
It's interdimensional, like a crystal skull.
I'm not married to some sort of philosophy
that I have about it.
But I do find it fascinating
and I find that there's more information coming out
in very public places now.
I like looking at Jason with his iPad
with the Space Mountain sign on it,
just sitting and waiting.
When can I be in there?
Well, I'm also just like, how much do I chime in on this?
I don't, I- What do you think?
Yeah, chime in.
Well, I have not had many paranormal,
or any paranormal experiences, I feel like.
But I'm very superstitious.
So you more think like demons are real.
I don't know, I don't-
That was a big leap.
No, I didn't say that.
I just more like, I check my,
I check astrology or I check co-star every now and then.
He's worried that Barbara Stanwyck's gonna rise up
and get be mad at him
because he hasn't watched enough of her great films.
Yeah.
He's not going through the filmography fast enough.
Tarot cards, I like tarot cards.
I like all the like Ricky Jay stuff
that he was-
You're a magic, you're a fan of magicians.
I like magic, but I feel like there are things beyond
that we cannot comprehend.
There's no doubt there's things beyond
that we can't comprehend.
It's all interesting.
I mean, I'm more of like,
oh, it's like human beings in another dimension
or it's like me from a different dimension traveling.
Like I'm more, I don't know that I think it's like
Klingons coming from the planet.
I think it's actually something like,
I can't even like think about,
like your dumb brain can't even conceive of.
Anyway.
It's like abstract.
You know what, Gio, very interested too.
Gio and I talk about this a lot, so.
Well, let's get so-
Bring him on, yeah.
Yeah, bring him on, yeah.
Bring him on my way.
He's reading a book about, he's been one of these guys.
Yeah, when you're away, we'll do a whole alien episode.
I watched some of, oh, in Hulu,
there's a history channel show called Strangest Things,
which is like all objects from history
that they still don't quite know what they are.
They were involved in mysterious stuff.
And then I watched a few minutes of Dan Aykroyd's
as a history channel called Unexplained?
Something like that.
I'm gonna be honest with you right now.
I promised my family that I would hang out with them
this afternoon.
Yes.
If I leave, you guys can do this as long as you want.
Literally, I'm like, it's too late for Dan Aykroyd
and aliens to be in the picture.
You could go as long as you want.
But we are talking space, which is related to-
No, I know, I know.
I'm saying I will leave the floor.
I'm total, I'm done.
I was going to open up another inquiry
and just the sense of like,
you're a Space Mountain fan, obviously.
Were you a fan of anything?
Did you like the concept of space and aliens as a kid?
Even just like, was that a part of it?
Or was it just the colors and the traveling in a spaceship?
Yeah, I think it's dark and a good suspense.
Okay.
Sure, sure.
I don't wanna step on this being a thing
that is talked about.
In this hour that we're doing our second episode in a row,
I think I can't-
Look, Gordon Cooper, look,
I wouldn't have ham-fisted this into the episode
unless my man Gordon, who appears-
But what I'm saying,
you guys can leave the microphones on.
You can wrap up the episode.
I haven't really eaten lunch.
I don't need to go another 30 minutes.
Oh, great.
I'm just saying this is one of the guys.
I don't know that he thought about aliens
while he was sitting there watching Space Mountain be opened.
I don't know.
Or this was all very true.
The reason he was so angry, as Jason pointed out,
is that these guys glaring,
it's because he's like, he knows what he saw.
Right.
They aren't even gonna, I'm just brought here to,
they're just gonna do a parade of nations in front of me
and release balloons.
I watched an alien massacre.
I saw what they do to each other.
I saw, if they could do that to each other,
what will they do to us?
Yeah.
I blew an alien's gray, he was a big gray,
and I blew his brains out. I blew?
Oh, God, that was such a long one.
I fired, I got confused,
cause I was also- I blew an alien.
I, Gordon Cooper, blew an alien.
I blew his brains out, his head was real big.
I had to empty a whole magazine.
I emptied a whole, he emptied a whole magazine
into my mouth.
The Vintage Space Mountain sign.
We're gonna go back to an RCA sign after that.
Mike yelled, I emptied a magazine into his mouth,
and now we're gonna come back to RCA, good font.
You're the ones talking about peep machines and stuff.
Yeah, well, I think they would do a,
they would make a comeback.
You said come, and then it took a while to get back to it.
If I, yes, they would make a come back.
They would make anyone come.
If they, if you could look in a peep machine
and see a guy unloading,
see an astronaut and an alien together.
Maybe.
A lot of mob business around this,
coin operated, early pinball and video game machines.
You think the mob was involved
in the peep show machine business?
Oh, 100%.
I don't know about the mob, but maybe they were.
I literally talked about this 45 minutes ago.
I talked about a guy who was a mobbed up guy
with peep machines.
Did you say mobbed up, though?
I don't know, I assume.
Maybe he was just sort of a solo killer, though.
I don't know.
No, I think he is.
I'm pretty sure.
You think Gordon Cooper.
I didn't say it, you're right.
Do you think Gordon Cooper got confused
by anything at Disneyland,
thinking it was sort of a extraterrestrial phenomenon?
Do you think he was put up at the contemporary
and asked to move to the Polynesian,
because he's like,
I don't want to think about this future shit.
Oh, because of the architecture was so futuristic?
Well, and the monorail.
The monorail freaked him out.
Yeah, maybe he saw the five-legged goat,
and he's like, fuck that, now it's too close to the grave.
It's possible he wanted to go to the Polynesian.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
If Sonny Eclipse had been there then,
he would have been unable to keep.
Unloading a magazine.
He would have unloaded a magazine in Sonny Eclipse.
Anyway, there's about one minute of space mountain footage.
Less, less.
Yeah, well, and it's not even footage.
It's just weirdly comped, half-opaque ride going by.
Well, this is the biggest punishment for me,
is that I'm like, when are we gonna get to Space Mountain?
And then we do, and that's mostly represented
by Lucy Arnaz singing a song from the Peter Pan musical.
It's all said to I'm flying.
In which, and it's somebody in that thing that says,
Wizzin'.
But wait, that's all special for Space Mountain,
and now I gotta hear about Wizzin'.
Yeah, that really is, that is a letdown.
Yeah, now Space Mountain is a conundrum.
How do you film it?
They face this challenge to this day.
Now there's better low-light cameras, it's easier to do.
But at the time, that's why we have a mystery
that's much bigger and more important
than the mystery of are UFOs real?
Which is, are there fans in Space Mountain
that make you feel like it's going fast?
We still haven't had a definitive.
Someday, the truth is out there.
Yeah.
Can we ask Gordon Cooper, is he long dead?
He's dead, yeah.
He passed away.
Well, I'm glad we implied that this long dead man
had blue and alien.
Spit out my mouth.
That's good of us to do.
American hero.
That was not my intent, my intent was that he murdered
a gray alien called, what?
You were just trying to imply murder.
We were the ones who made it sexual.
You can't stop at blow and then doing a side
and then come back.
Yeah, yeah, that's what happened.
We got caught on blow.
Got caught on blow.
Yeah, yeah, it was going to happen.
Anyway, yeah, look, then, yeah, as Iceberg said,
this does, the riot is ultimately inaugurated by a,
look, I'm just going to do it.
I could play the clip, but why would I
when I know I want to talk like this?
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls,
we proudly present Space Mountain.
Done kind of like, done with that aggression, I would say.
It's always like aggressive.
Yeah, that's an aggressive,
that's where the voice comes from.
He sounds like our aggressive, violent Mickey impression.
That's why we do it, you see.
Because he's angry, yeah, that's the vibe.
But this one I'm saying really sounds like it.
This reading.
Let me get this straight, you make me wait
after 50 goddamn minutes of Tommy Tune?
That two bit hack?
I wait after Lucy Arnaz, huh?
Oh, why do we know her name?
Is it because of the last name?
Is it because of who mommy and daddy are?
Who are my mommy and daddy?
Nobody's, no one even, I don't even remember their names.
I'm Mickey fucking Mouse, is who I am.
I had to get up on top of the riverboat
and clean all the footprints off of it.
This fucking maniac dancing all over the diamond horseshoe.
You're not supposed to go up there.
We have rules about keep your hands and arms
inside the vehicle for a reason.
Cooper, I heard about your fucking request.
You're staying put in your hotel room, you son of a bitch.
Gordon Cooper, I know what you've been doing in your hotel.
I know what you've been doing behind closed doors.
You don't do that shit at Disney World.
You don't do it.
We had to clean up three dead bodies.
This is a family slap, friendly slap, place slap.
Who can't it you were in space?
But Nez, if you fuck around with those boots like that again,
I'll have you in jail.
That was a blatant violation of common sense maritime law.
And Waggoner, I've been in your trailers.
They stink.
I asked for my own.
And Plumber, you're the darkest person I've ever gazed upon.
I don't care how fucking old you are.
It's so good that Mickey, like he's just,
I feel like the newer Mickey cartoons
are closest to that Mickey, honestly.
They were really taking inspiration from this Mickey voice.
But not enough swearing and not enough violence.
Well, that's true.
And that's what we ask out of whatever
next official iteration of Mickey is out there.
But now that we've talked for a while
and done that voice at the end,
I feel like mine's shot, mine's gonna go in about three.
I feel like I just did two straight matinees of seesaw.
So I better wind it down.
I'd say you survived Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Thank you for the pitch.
Iceberg, that was a blast.
And yeah, your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
Bug Nation, I wish you luck in one more round.
May the putty sauce be with you.
We can do it.
Let's at least get the second again.