Guys, we have to keep it together.
We have to keep brave faces and be professionals.
And in light of the news from a few hours ago that the CityWalk Abercrombie is going
away.
All right.
I don't want to see any tears.
I don't want any attitude.
Like, look, I have a little bit of that just before we start recording.
I just wanted to say, like, we have to be professional here.
Even this.
That's what being broadcasters is all about.
No, no, none of that quiver.
You can't do that.
We owe these, these people pay for these episodes and we can't be doing that whining and moaning
Mike Carlson and you over there, Jason Sheridan.
I understand.
But we have to shed our tears in private, you see, Abercrombie and you're pointing
to Jason.
Jason's saying nothing.
I fucked this up before.
Haven't I?
I'm going to try.
Oh, this is another.
Is this a little quiet book?
It's a quiet one, but we haven't gone back to it.
Well, now hold on.
Well, I do want to preface this way.
I have never purchased an item.
Okay.
All right.
This defense is insane, Jason.
You can be aware of a brand without ever having purchased anything from the brand.
I'm just saying, I'm going to take this.
Okay.
Abercrombie and Finch?
No.
Is it Fitch?
In Jason's defense, I wasn't sure myself.
I was like, I'm going to look it up, but that would be cheating.
I think if you'd put it to me, I might've said Finch as well.
I changed it right at the last moment.
Because Finch is an animal in this world and Fitch is nothing.
Right.
Am I wrong?
No, you're not wrong.
Well, the reason it sticks out to me is that, and forgive me, someone animated this chunk
of our podcast from the original City Walk Saga.
Oh, really?
Where Jason says Abercrombie and Finch, and I casually just say Fitch, and it's animated.
This is why it sticks out of my brain.
I had rewatched a lot of stuff and relistened to stuff when we did last City Walk, so it's
fresher in my head.
Well, we need more stuff to get animated because it's going to help us remember things.
So audience, do us a solid and just animate everything we say from now on.
Could you be a deer and animate all the stuff we say?
There's probably going to be an app that will do that soon.
I was coming in so fresh, well rested from the holidays, you know, I made sure to have
a good breakfast and take all my medicine, and I was like, well, still getting my sleep
schedule and my medicine schedule, still trying to get it in order.
This medicine is going to help.
Remember to take this medicine every day, Jason, because it will help you recall one
letter differences in City Walk France.
But I just felt so composed, and I was like, nothing home plate, Mike just threw the craziest
curveball.
I don't really want to take any blame here because I was doing a separate bit, and then
you made it all finger pointing.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It just stuck out so vividly in my mind, but it's just because of this animation that was
done.
It actually threw me off to begin with unintentionally because I didn't know that one was closing.
Yeah, I thought that might be a way to, yeah, as we record this, everything is changing.
All the City Walk stuff's going away.
Sparkies went down.
Sparkies going down.
High fly today is the last day of operation, I believe.
Oh my God.
What are we doing here?
Right.
Let's get up.
to, you know, putt around and mostly fall an unpleasant, loud wind tunnel.
And we're here.
I don't know.
We're here working?
Audience, get off our backs, please.
You're taking us away from the things we love.
No, not our children.
From loud, loud wind tunnels.
Everything though, with Downtown Disney changing, new things are opening at Downtown Disney.
You can get like a slushy rosé at the top of Sip and Sonder, the new restaurant.
Yeah, I was reading that on the way here too, that you can get like $18 Lemonade.
An $18 Lemonade, yes, at Sip and Sonder.
At Sip and Sonder.
I got a pair.
I'm so excited to go to Sip and Sonder.
I'm the opposite.
Sip and Sonder seems like bad news to me.
I read a bad review of Sip and Sonder this very morning.
Is it about the chicken sandwich?
No, there's a couple different places in this one little complex that's opened.
That's what this whole, all this New Downtown Disney stuff, that's what it's all going to
be about, right?
Is like expensive, increasingly bad chicken sandwiches.
That's the entire game in all of these malls outside of theme parks.
I totally think I've seen Mike as happy in ages as he was to say Sip and Sonder like
three times in a row.
Let's put him on blast.
Is it an and or an ampersand or an N?
Let's play his game against him.
It's not the N.
It's not an N?
All right, we know that.
I don't know if it's an ampersand.
I think, oh, I think it's an ampersand.
Let's go with ampersand.
This guy, he's got to take his medicine.
Sip and Sonder, Sip and Sonder.
It is an ampersand.
It's an ampersand.
Okay.
I believe, unless it's a different Sip and Sonder.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, maybe it's a different Sip and Sonder than the one that exists, but I doubt it.
How different is Sip and Sonder is there?
Is this a brand that exists outside of this?
I thought it was a Disney created thing up until this moment.
But now I'm questioning that.
Huh.
Well, you're right.
I don't know what to make of all these changes.
I feel like these places are rapidly changing in this year.
We've said for years now, oh, Universal's getting rid of stuff.
They don't know, blah, blah, blah.
But it really feels like we're hitting a turning point in these last few months.
It is ramping up.
Ramping up.
It's ramping up.
You might say.
Very fast.
I need my medicine too.
Yeah.
But I feel, I don't know what to make of it.
I almost feel like the rift we healed in the City Walk saga has something to do with this
now.
Are they doing this just for, are they doing this for us, are they closing a bunch of things
and opening new things just because they want more, because they want another series?
Not a saga.
I don't know how we can do it though, but yes, it feels, to me, who's very full of himself
and egocentric, it feels like what we did caused a lot of this to happen.
The rumors of two new hotels at City Walk Hollywood, it's going to look so different
in a couple of years.
I can't think of what else might cause all these City Walk restaurants to close.
It must be us and certainly not the unbelievably terrible quality of said restaurants and that
they are never solicited by human beings.
But what they want to do is open more things like Toothsums.
That's true.
Toothsums is part of the new wave of bad stuff.
It seems like just an abject failure, just also this morning, I guess I was having a
theme parky morning.
I was having a text exchange with Dennis McNicholas who joined us a couple of years ago, who was
asking for like, so what is up with this Toothsum?
I'm seeing a movie.
Should I hit up Toothsum?
I said under no circumstances should you go to Toothsum and he said, well, I am just learning
about Jacques and Penelope.
He was having that discovery.
Oh, there's the characters and he sent a few photos and I was like, no joke, Jacques and
Penelope were cut for budget one week ago.
It's really all happening right now, isn't it?
It's all happening now.
We're in the deepest period of city walk change.
We did that entire series in a way of like, isn't this place weird that it never changed,
that it's been this odd way for the last five years, unchanging?
And now, boy, that's out the wind.
It's changing every day.
It's unrecognizable.
Now it's really going to be something.
Now Penelope's parents are never going to find her.
God, they might never close the loop on that.
We might never get an end to the story, at least for narrative purposes.
They have to keep those characters, don't they?
I think so.
What if they turn it back into a hard rock, but then brought Penelope there and she's
just managing the hard rock?
That's fine.
That's technically a story and Jacques is a robot, but he has a good guitar and he rocks
sometimes.
What if he is the guitar?
Oh, what do you mean?
What if he's playing himself?
Oh yeah, that's true.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
You can put that in, but he could be like a one man, but he could have a keyboard in
his tummy.
Oh, that'd be better.
Yeah.
So he could do a whole thing going on.
Trombone ears.
Yeah.
Little cymbals and balls, I don't know.
Your cymbals are little balls that clap together as our balls clap together when we walk.
Closing the loop may be a thing.
What if the evolution of City Walk is that circle is complete and stuff starts coming
back.
There's a wind up toy store.
There's Jody Moroney's Sausage Kingdom, which what would that just be called nowadays?
Jody's Place?
The Jody's Place.
Oh, I think it would be like Jody's.
It would be a simpler.
Is that what you're saying?
Jody's even simpler.
Yeah, yeah.
Like a new version.
Jody Moroney's Sausage Kingdom is too wordy potentially.
The rumor is Buka will close too.
Like, I think.
Really?
I think.
Wow.
That's why I saw a rumor, but also makes sense because it's not a universal own thing.
Yeah.
It sucks ass.
Julie, man.
But it's made it a long time while sucking ass.
Sucking ass does not mean that it should close because it's done so well.
As long as the Raiders store stays, store for a football team that is no longer in California
and is not even one, is certainly not one of the two teams in Los Angeles.
The absolute majority of its existence, it has not been, the entirety of its existence,
it has never been.
Wait, maybe the entirety, right?
I don't know my time.
No, they were in the Los Angeles.
Didn't they move after the earthquake?
But it was in the early 90s.
Yeah.
But that store was not open.
That part of CityWalk was not there at all.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Maybe it's never.
God, that's insane.
Has anyone in the last two or three weeks cracked open the Google Maps overhead view
of CityWalk like I have?
Yeah.
You have?
Because I was trying to place for these hotels that are getting rumored.
Because I'm very CityWalk minded lately with all these rumors and closings.
Yeah.
Because yeah, there's rumor two hotels, one goes by the entrance to Universal, one goes
where iFly is, that's the smaller one.
But it looks like it takes over the movie theater, I don't know what the geography of
that is.
All the things they could remove.
That would be the strangest CityWalk decision that the movie theater, the one thing anyone
uses and that doesn't fuck up what it does, unless I'm on, like I don't see movies there
a lot.
It's just to me, like you go in there expecting to see a movie and then you see a movie as
opposed to any CityWalk restaurant or store that finds a myriad of ways to fuck up what
is promoted as the task of the place.
You go in expecting pasta and they serve you diarrhea.
That's what happens often in CityWalk.
But yeah, movie, they'll show you the movie you bought a ticket for is what you're saying.
Someone sent us the tweet over the holidays.
The film critic for Variety was like, so wait, if you go to CityWalk, you pay for parking
and then the AMC still gives you dirty cash?
I do like that with everything changing that that has not, that they still just, they still
hand you dirty cash.
Well, if you use the AMC app, there's a way not to get the dirty cash, but that is still,
if you don't do it ahead of time, how you have to get your money back.
Can I, I want to shout out, this is, this is, I have this, you know, it happens to us
once in a while.
I'm driving up to CityWalk through two and a half weeks ago with my daughter.
I'm just going to, we're going to stroll around.
Weeks ago or hours ago?
No, not out.
We didn't have time today.
I almost, I almost did yesterday, but I hurt my toe and it was like hard to walk around
with my shoe on.
It's okay.
My toe is fine today though.
Don't worry about it.
If it had been at CityWalk, we could have gotten a lot of material.
That's true.
But I was just a stray toe hurt.
I had taken, I was taking her just up there.
We're going to go in the park for a second and then we're going to have something to eat
at the El Vivo, El Vivo Italian kitchen.
I feel like there's an eel in there.
What am I thinking of then?
What am I?
Isn't it an aisle?
Is it just Vivo?
I think so.
What am I thinking?
We would be the people to know.
Well, if anyone.
Well, that's my new buca di beppo is that I had an eel.
A stray eel.
He wasn't sure if it was an ant or an ampersand and he put an eel in there.
Oh no, I'm going to edit this out though.
So I'm going up there and I realized, cause I have a pass that has the parking, I realized,
oh shit, it's past six o'clock, which is by the way, this is some dumb policy of Universal
not to let you park for free.
If you have the free parking in your past after six o'clock, even though the park still
can be open till nine, like regular riffraff.
It's weird.
There's no annual passholder respect.
It's a bizarre policy that they need to change.
And I'm pulling up and I realize, oh my God, it's six 15 shit.
And I pull up and I really innocently, I wasn't trying to pull anything.
I go, Hey, I just realized this doesn't work right after six or whatever.
And the guy at the booth goes, don't worry.
I got you.
And I went, Oh, really?
Thank you so much.
That's really nice.
And he goes, you do podcast the ride, right?
Wow.
And I go, Oh, I do do podcast the ride and he goes, he goes, yeah, cool.
I think he said, I hope he's listening and I didn't get his name.
I should have gotten his name, but there's, you know, his name is hero.
And he said, I think he said, love that.
And then he gave me the parking and off we went into city.
You toil with no reward, with no light at the end of the tunnel, days and years of misery.
And then finally it all picks up.
And then I had to cause Noah was in the car.
I turned, I turned to my daughter and I go, daddy was just recognized and we got free.
I told her what had happened and she was, what did she say?
Oh my God.
She said, she made a noise or something.
I was going to say there was more than that.
You're lying.
No, no.
She said what she had been saying for like 20 minutes.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, honk shoe.
Me, me, me, me, me, me.
Was that us?
She's sleeping.
That's sleeping.
Yeah, she was dead asleep.
That's the second time that you've said honk shoe out loud and I had no idea what you were
talking about.
You don't know honk shoe?
I guess I don't know.
It makes sense to me as a, as a verbalization of the snore, but I hear it in and of itself
and I don't know what it means.
I never thought of that as that.
I always thought of it as like, that's always the noise I heard.
If I had to spell it out, I would say like, like snort and then like, few, I guess.
No, I think, I think making it the stiff phrase honk shoe is more confusing to me.
Who made that up?
I don't know.
I just spread it.
Another hero, a different hero.
So Charles Fleischer.
Oh, maybe I just, maybe it's from something.
I just didn't know.
One of the early Looney Tuts guys.
Well, I think it's time to unpack a topic that very well might make our listeners honk
shoe if we're not careful.
Or it's the, or this is an insanely dynamic topic.
I'm not sure.
I don't know how.
I can't tell.
My dry alert is going off.
However, I do find it to be genuinely interesting.
It is good.
I think it is interesting.
And that topic is go.com.
Go.com broad strokes.
This is Disney's failed internet portal from the like 99 2000 dot com boom.
And this is something, this has been in the works for a while.
We've wanted to do this for a while and it came up a little bit in the mobile app episode
as it did honk shoe.
Was that one where I was just listening?
Was that the episode?
Maybe.
I think Jess, I think it was.
I think Jess knew what you were talking about, but Jess knew that specific phrase.
It must have been nice in that time to have occasional people here who understood what
you were talking about.
As opposed to you got me here in this chair 90 percent of the time who doesn't back you
up.
I'm 50.
There's a chance with the other.
50-50 I'm with him though, I feel like.
Something like that.
Because like as soon as I, even though he's goofing on me for Sip and Saunders, you know
this man wants the Sip and Saunders, he loves Sip and Saunders.
You know that.
He's excited to go Sip and Saunders.
I'm excited to check out Sip and Saunders.
Right.
Of course.
I'm saying half the time I don't know what you're talking about and then the other half
I'm like right with you.
We have that hive mind.
Look, I will admit I don't know the dictionary definition of Saunder.
I looked this up yesterday.
Oh.
I think it's like.
You're on Google Maps for City Walk and you're looking up Saunder.
I think it's, let me read it or just a noun.
The feeling one has on realizing that every other individual one sees has a life as full
and real as one's own.
Okay.
I encountered that.
I was like, I encountered that like 10 minutes ago, five minutes ago, I looked it up and
I was like, that can't be right.
That can't be the name.
You looked it up five minutes ago.
So when we were talking, you were looking up the dictionary definition of Saunder?
Yeah.
Wow.
Because I didn't want to look stupid.
Jason, I called it Il Vivo.
I can't look dumber than that.
People are going to be roasting my ass for years.
We are having a very stupid January over here.
Vivo of course means live.
I looked that up too.
You're manning the dictionary over this whole time?
I do this every episode.
I look up stuff.
That you don't end up saying?
You're just like over there.
You just got dictionary.com open?
Yeah.
On background.
So Jason's got dictionary on background.
So you've got a complex now from doing the show where you're like, oh my God, they're
going to ask me what Saunder means.
Oh my God, they're going to ask me what Saunder means.
I need to know what Saunder is.
You're like, I'm going to look it up.
I'm going to play it cool.
If they ask me, I will know.
And then I'm going to do all that work and Mike's got to come out and go like, spell
Aero pastel.
You may as well.
A-E-R-O-S-T-A-L-E.
No, you missed a bunch of letters.
You missed a P, right?
You missed a lot of letters.
Oh well.
It just turned into an S really fast.
I mean, you spelled it right, but you just missed the middle I think.
I don't like curveballs.
I'd better go with Aero pastel.
Aero pastel.
I don't like curveballs.
I'd better with a sinker or right down the middle.
You just asked for it.
You're like, curveball me please.
Can I have a curveball, sir?
And I said it was going to be trouble.
This is how we're going to make it to the topic.
I don't know.
We should abort this episode.
Let me know.
No.
Okay.
We don't do that.
The InfoSeek heads want us to get to the top.
Yeah.
Shiver through the ghost of their body when we say InfoSeek.
Though this was on the docket on our end when I did a little, hey, what do you want next
year?
We did get a reminder.
The people once again demand go.com from the great Milschneff.
Thank you for reminding us to do it.
We were on the way here.
Now what this is, as I said pre the Aero pastel spelling.
This is this is kind of a relic of this was Disney trying to get in to the internet in
the ask Jeeves dot com era.
Yeah.
In the pets dot com era.
The first time that the internet was big money stock market wise and everybody all these
corporations are trying to figure out what their strategy is.
And this was their strategy.
And it was a weird flawed strategy as we will get into.
But I wanted to say all that really quick just to say.
All right.
Does this seem like kind of a weird relic?
Is this a thing from 25 years ago that we're talking about just arbitrarily?
And I would say no, because go dot com has a very day to day relevance.
And I will do a little exercise with the listener.
If you don't know this already, I would say to the listener, why don't you go to your
browser?
Why don't you type in Disneyland dot com or Disney world dot com and see what happens?
I'll wait to click the click.
You got to improve your Wi-Fi, but that's taken a while.
I'll sonder while you're having that page load.
You got to do that.
And remember that all of our listeners have their own internal lives that are bussing.
Every day I'm sondering.
Every day.
I'm sondering.
OK.
Now that you've sondered, people have maybe if they didn't already know this, realized
that in trying to type in the simple should be one of the most iconic URLs in the world.
Disneyland dot com and you have been rerouted to Disneyland dot Disney dot go dot com.
Right.
Now, I say this like this is new to some of the audience and maybe it is.
But if you're versed in these things, if you've tried to do any of the, you know, of getting
tickets and reservations or hotels or any of that, or even if you just been in the app,
you might have found yourself in Disneyland's mobile app and then you get sent far away
to the hinterlands of go dot com.
I love that.
It just remains this bizarre rerouting that is part of the Disney Internet experience.
Sorry, go ahead.
Oh, I was going to say, I just love, you know, we talked about on the app episode, but half
the features on the app just opens a mobile browser and sometimes you have to log in again.
Yeah.
Like, why didn't you just build this into a tab on the?
I don't know.
I don't know what the entirety of like how this is all 25 years ago.
This gets built even even older than like there's been ample opportunity for Disney
to like join the modern Internet and to like defang this strange like like this, this little
creature of go dot com, these two little letters that just like suck the life out of their
URLs.
Yeah.
I've never been able to do it.
It's strange.
Yeah.
I think probably it's one of those situations where every time they build something new,
it's like, well, the cost to completely revamp this is 100 million.
This is hypothetical, obviously, 100 million dollars.
But to just add this new thing on top of go, it's 10 million dollars.
So they keep making the decisions cheaper, which probably ultimately, if they had just
scrapped it 15, 20 years ago, they would have saved money, but they didn't.
And they refuse to at this point.
Well, it's kind of like, I mean, you hear about the Internet in general is like there's
stuff at the Internet online or at companies that's held together with tape and popsicles
or like, oh, this works because of Teddy and Teddy is retiring next year and no one else
knows how to do this.
Teddy's a guy.
Yeah, it's a guy.
I thought it was like a search engine or something.
No, no.
Just like so much is still done ad hoc.
So in that sense, Disney is on point.
Now, is this safe?
Is this smart?
I don't know about that.
Safe is an interesting quote.
You're saying like, is Disney more at risk of being hacked or we all, any of us who put
our information and dare I say, our credit cards on Disney's website?
Are you suggesting, Jason, that there might be that we're all at risk day to day due to
this go dot com?
Well, I just these holes on the Internet in general.
There's been so many data breaches at these big companies.
Credit cards get leaked.
The government gets breached sometimes.
Social Security numbers get leaked.
Yeah, I feel like once a month I get a letter of like, here's complimentary, you know, ID
theft tracking because like a gym you went to years ago got hacked.
Sure, sure.
Well, I you know, I can't speak to that.
I don't know, you know, is go dot com safe?
I don't know.
But was go dot com successful?
I would say no.
Was go dot com the path to Disney making a big splash on the Internet?
It absolutely was not.
No, it's a strange, odd history and which I guess we can sort of go through here.
I mean, to do this, you have to go back to a time and this might be a time before a lot
of listeners even remember.
And I don't know how well I'm going to explain this, but the word portal, I hadn't thought
about the word portal.
Oh, yeah.
But this was very this was, you know, when we were having our Internet awakenings, it
was always OK, we were aware of the Internet.
The Internet's here.
They had those those dial up sounds.
Those were crazy.
You pick up the phone and we're going, is there a monster in the phone?
What's this?
It was wild.
You had to be there.
Oh, you know, you're a 90s kid.
And anyways, like it seemed like a lot of the right.
There's money in the Internet.
So there's a there's a there's a gold rush here.
And a lot of it was like, could you be not a controller of the pipes?
But I still don't understand why this was the case, but like to get on to the Internet,
you probably went through some weird, I mean, these portals, although Yahoo is different
than like prodigy.
This is where it gets confusing for me, like because those are like programs.
Get on the Internet via prodigy, or AOL really won that.
But AOL is also considered a portal.
I don't know.
The point is there were these like four things that were like your first stop on the Internet
originally.
Yahoo was a big one that Disney tried to make a relationship with, but it kind of fell apart.
Yes.
Yeah.
So and this and I think that the notion was there's money in these because like, hey,
you got to start your Internet journey somewhere.
And if you start on one of these, whether it's a website or a full like program that
you enter, you know, it's your gateway to all of these like chat rooms and like little
subgroups.
And, you know, there's article, there's content in these places, but then also it's places
for advertisers to sell their wares and make it's like, how is anybody going to make money
off the Internet?
Well, through these portals, I guess, was the original idea.
Similar to now, things I think kind of ended up at like, if you're going to go online,
you're going to start at one of five programs or apps or whatever.
Right.
Kind of like went back to that.
But kind of before Google just sort of threw down, like, well, it's us.
I just remember when I was like, I like, Mom, Dad, did you know we don't need AOL to get
on the Internet?
I remember I had this conversation with my parents at one point.
Yeah.
Like that blew my mind.
You're paying $30 a month for CDs.
Right.
If we don't have this CD, we can't, then we don't pay this company to hear those sounds
because if we don't hear, you've got mail.
If we don't hear goodbye, that means we're still on the Internet.
Well, yeah, you are still on, you can always be on the Internet.
Even more specifically, you didn't need AOL to be on AOL Instant Messenger.
Well, yeah, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
That was the main, I feel like the main draw for me with AOL.
After like six months it was, because initially I was so excited about AOL.
You go in the DC portal, the Marvel portal, and you click on stuff.
I don't even know that it was anything that cool there.
It was just like, oh my God, you're loading photos of characters.
It was reduced color photos of Green Lantern.
Right.
It was a photo of Green Lantern that didn't have the bitmap data it needed to make the
green extra green.
Uh-huh.
And so, yeah, I don't remember why.
Maybe they like chats with the creators once in a while or something via that.
If you go on at a certain time.
But yeah, after a while somebody was like, hey, no, you don't have to have it anymore.
And I came home with this information and I presented it to my parents.
What are they saying?
I think they went with it.
I forget.
Yeah.
If it's a cost saver.
Well, that may be what pulled down AOL generally, because in all of that, what I was just doing
in painting the picture of the Internet era that we're talking about, there weren't a
lot of mics out there, enterprising mics figuring out that you don't need the CDs.
AOL was doing huge in the stock market.
Yahoo was huge in the stock market.
So for Disney, it became, how do we have more of a presence online than just Disney.com?
Do we have to partner with one of these places or should we build our own?
Yeah.
And from what I remember in the Disney war book, buying EBC, the network EBC, and buying
Infoseek, which would be a part of Go.com eventually, were sort of like the later Eisner
era, like everyone going like, oh God, what are we doing here?
But I think his instinct for we should have a portal was correct in a sense.
Yes.
And down the line, even more correct because like, well, Comcast owns television networks
and a movie studio and a theme park and this and that and the other thing.
AT&T used to own Warner Brothers and they became a lot more symbiotic.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, and he apparently, apparently Eisner once said, we'll never do cable.
We will never be part, that's never going to be part of our business.
And then they had to scramble and do cable.
So I think, so he didn't want that to happen again.
So like we have to have a solid internet presence, but how are we going to do it?
And thank you for name check.
So Disney war.
I want to just really quickly name check a couple of things because I have a bunch of
screenshots from books.
So if I just read passages, I'm not stealing it.
Disney war by James Stewart is one, if you want to read about this stuff without a bunch
of jokes in the way and a bunch of Abercrombie talk at the top, you can go to these books
in your local library.
The audio book of Disney war is very good if you would still like to listen to the dry
facts.
Great.
Uh, Disney war by James Stewart is one, uh, uh, keys to the kingdom.
How Michael Eisner lost his grip by Kim masters.
I mean, I have half a mind to burn.
I know.
It's upsetting.
I don't even lie.
I didn't like having it in my presence, but I washed my hands after turning every page.
But then, then now let's get back to bit.
Let's let's get back to, you know, wholesome good literature.
And I will occasionally reference Eisner's book himself, uh, work in progress camp, uh,
not camp.
Camp is a, we got to get to camp in 2025.
What have we, uh, year after year and we aren't making it to his book about his childhood
camp.
Uh, um, anyway, so, but I wanted to credit those books, uh, because I'll be reading little
passages from them here and there, uh, including this one from Disney war.
This is important backstory with the rise of personal computer and internet access.
Eisner had become a voracious user of email.
That's what I like about it.
He's on the cutting edge always.
This guy used email.
You think every seat, you think Sumner used email?
Uh, no, he was like, it was printed out for him and laid on, laid onto a naked woman's
body page by page and he would read as incentive for the pages to come off so he could look
at her, at her bare body, uh, but I assume, uh, uh, it's
speed and convenience perfectly fit his impulsive personality, especially when he was suffering
from insomnia.
So you see, I email for Eisner, this is, this gave him a way to work even more, to always
be, will always be tinkering with the Disney company.
Um, but what this led to was like, Disney needs to not only have an internet presence,
we have to like be the main internet presence.
So, uh, a bunch of people came on board to, to, uh, you know, consult on this situation
and they all told Eisner, what we should do is buy an existing website or partner with
one of the main, so like, like we would recommend Yahoo for the money that we have allotted
for this.
Uh, we, we think that we should partner with Yahoo, buy a big steak in Yahoo and that's
how we will have a big internet presence.
And Eisner said, no, we need our own.
Why would we do it from the ground up?
And what he would point to is, we didn't let Marriott, uh, you know, run all over Disney
world and build a bunch of hotels.
We built hotels our way.
We built the beautiful Swan and Dolphin and, uh, uh, we can't just do that on the internet.
We need the Swan and Dolphin of the internet.
Um, so lots of advisors, all Michael Graves in here.
Yeah.
Make him do it.
He can design a building.
He can design a webpage.
Um, anyway, uh, and sorry, I'm like, I'm ducking all around these new, I feel free to
interrupt with less dry things.
It just feels like the current situation with streamers, with, uh, streaming services where
every, every company made the same, well, we have to have our own.
And then it's just destroyed half of them.
Yes.
Yeah.
And what that led to in almost every case was like, we need our own.
It's got to have a name that's snappy, a simple, a name that the, that Gen Z will get by because
you see they stream, they don't even watch cable.
This is what a report that I read told me about them.
So here's $500 million to figure out what our name is.
And then it was just all plus and max everywhere I just landed on plus and max.
If you, uh, speaking of current things, like I would advise everyone, take a moment.
We already sent you to Disneyland, disneyworld.com type in go.com now and do that myself.
It is, um, it's hanging in there.
It is a long, like basic HTML list of, it's just text.
It's just text.
It's like a GeoCities website.
It'll say like endless scroll.
It's promoting projects from 2023, just text without a photo.
Loki season two, the God of mischief returns October 5th in season two, which picks up
in the F when Loki finds himself in a battle for the soul of the time variance authority.
No photo of what the time variance authority is.
Why would you need it?
It's just a text webs.
That's very strange.
Wow.
It's still hanging in there.
And like, I found this a few weeks ago and I was just like, the fuck is, why would you
the top?
They don't update it.
I don't think, because the top thing here at the top of 2025 under Walt Disney pictures
is wish, wish Asha, a sharp-witted idealist makes a wish so powerful.
That's it.
I still, I don't know what wish is.
What's about Asha?
It's about now.
Yes.
You're right.
I do know it's about Asha.
Haunted Mansion 2023 is at the top of, so go.com, the entire, it's all built around just like
a tree website.
That's just a list of things that they were doing in 2003.
Like why wouldn't you just put in a redirect to send you to Disney.com?
Like I don't know, this is strange.
And still all of their presence serves to send people to this.
It's kind of beautiful.
It's kind of a beautiful postcard from early internet, but with the content of two years
ago.
This is one of the most dynamic things I've ever seen on a corporate website.
20th century studios, enjoy all your favorite movies from 20th century studios.
This is, how much does that, how much did what I just read, how much does that cost
Disney every year?
10 million dollars.
You know, Disneystore.com though is not go Disney.
Interestingly enough.
Really?
So they are not every facet of the company is all tangled up.
Because shop Disney is now Disneystore.com.
Shop Disney is no more.
It's Disneystore.com, but not go.com.
This is now, all of this is pointless, right?
But isn't it ultimately, it's like, it's at least a job creator that like there's people
who've spent entire, their entire lives just like shuffling assets from here to there.
And is that a good job?
Is that a worthy job?
Maybe not, but it is a job and you know, and the cleaner these things get, then you don't
have people to be the janitors of the internet.
Just like pushing around assets with a broom, never landing them anywhere satisfying, never
fully getting them in a trash can.
I bet, I bet like major banks that everybody uses have similar infrastructure to this.
I get the sense that like, even like you would be shocked at like what old ass system banks
are built on top of.
If you just put, put the right code into bankofamerica.com, you'd go, oh, I have access to everyone's money.
Yes, it's possible.
Like I think hopefully it's better than go.com, but I think there's a lot of this going on
with stuff that was what internet 30 years ago, it's built on the top of it.
Let me go back to Eisner stuff.
I forgot about this.
So they said, why don't we just partner with Yahoo?
We'll buy a bunch of Yahoo and that'll be the strategy.
And he said, he not only rejected the Yahoo proposal, but also seemed annoyed by it.
Why do this with anyone else?
We'll do this ourselves.
He derided the person who presented that plan and his team as wimps.
Wimps.
Yeah, geez.
So not only, he's not only like doggedly determined, he's insulting anyone who says otherwise.
What a man.
Why don't you go home and fail to get it up to have sex with your wife?
That's clearly an idea from the brain of somebody who doesn't have what it takes to pleasure
the woman they love.
Doesn't have a thick, firm erection whenever he wants.
By the way, we shouldn't partner with Viagra.
Disney should have its own erectile dysfunction pill.
I'm trying to think which character is associated with that.
That occurred to me too.
I couldn't think of a good one.
The old mill.
It's got to be something strong and trustworthy and a brand that people remember.
Chernobog.
Side effects of Chernobog may include rage, calling people wimps in meetings.
Do not take Chernobog if you've experienced low blood pressure, heart conditions.
If you're allergic to hellfire, do not take Chernobog.
So anyways, then they do something called the Digital Future Summit.
Eisner listened to various strategies, including, hey, maybe you could buy one of the, how much
did that cost?
All right, here's a hundred million dollars to host the Digital Future Summit.
Hmm, very good.
No, I think you're all wimps.
I think we will still build our own.
Now they did own a stake in something called StarWave, because StarWave is how they built
the ESPN and ABC websites.
So then they combined StarWave with buying a bunch of, 43% of something called InfoSeq.
And they mashed up StarWave and InfoSeq, and instead of calling it StarSeq or InfoWave,
which would still be viable, we should buy those URLs if they don't already exist.
But that became, all right, we will technically, all right, we'll start with something.
We'll mash these websites together, but other than that, we'll build it from scratch.
InfoSeq apparently was the third most popular internet search engine after Yahoo and Excite.
There's one that's lost to the sands of time.
Yeah.
How the hell is Excite?
Created by a man who came on my radar during COVID.
Yeah, here we go.
You know what we're talking about?
Steve Kirch.
Steven Kirch.
Kirch.
The guy who did Excite?
InfoSeq.
Oh, oh yeah.
I missed this name.
He turned into a rabid anti-vaxxer and a guy who would challenge people on planes, would
post photos of himself on planes, challenging people on the internet to a vaccine contest
of some kind.
Vaccine contest.
Or data, I wouldn't say that, but data, and you'd look at some of the stuff, I'm so out
of my mind, I would fall, he would be in spaces on Twitter and he would be arguing with data
with doctors, and you're like, he clearly just lost his mind, and he's still going.
This is his number one pursuit right now is anti-vaxx.
Did you have to go into spaces to absorb this material?
Well, spaces, yeah, you'd have to click on listen to.
I would listen to it.
But you don't have to sign up for anything for spaces?
No.
You can just get out.
I still might say-
I don't think I've ever purposefully gone to spaces.
That's what I was going to say.
I think, Jason, if you agree with me, I think that even clicking on spaces once is indication
that Mike has lost his mind.
I have watched clips of spaces, and it's usually like, look at this dumbass, and it's Elon
or-
Well, it's his alter ego.
His alter ego, who is a guy, quote unquote.
I don't want to ask a guess, but HB1 is a guy named Adrian-
Adrian Ditman?
Yes, and Adrian Ditman will post like, man, Elon's kids must love him.
He'll post the saddest shit.
The most powerful people on earth all have false personas, like Trump's fake secretary.
Yes.
God.
The guy.
Steven Hirsch, notable, made a bunch of money selling Infoseek to Disney, is one of the
people credited with the invention of the optical mouse.
What's the optical mouse?
Not the ball mouse.
Not the ball.
Rich, because remember when you first had a mouse and it was like, you would get shit
in there, dirt, and you'd have to clean the mouse ball out?
Oh, sure, sure.
Oh.
Light, yeah, optical mouse, but other people were working on it, so it was like simultaneous
inventions.
Okay.
And then-
So does he make money when we buy an optical mouse or no?
Good question.
I don't know.
It's unclear.
There's a long interview with him from like 10 years ago on YouTube, but that would be
before all the COVID stuff.
It seemed like he started with good intentions with COVID.
He seems-
Bunch of money into research and other scientists and doctors, and then he started complaining
about like the vaccines will make you infertile.
Oh, and he's like a hydroxychloroquine guy.
Oh, boy.
He's got, let me just say this, bad vibes when you look at him.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
That's a, no, that's like a-
Snapped.
Yeah.
That's like you like have hypnotized somebody and then you like say the key word again and
marker, and then you say marker and snap your fingers.
Yeah.
And then the guy goes into that mode.
Oh, no.
So anyway, he got a lot of money from Disney.
He gave a woman on a first-class Delta flight a hundred grand to remove her mask for the
entire flight and she refused.
That's what I should have said.
Yes, yes.
Yes, that's right.
He was like challenging people to take their mask off.
I just like, I don't know.
So Disney essentially, Disney paid this person that hundred thousand dollars and then much
more.
Michael Eisner handed him a bag of cash.
And yet, as you guys might have bumped into, this might not be the worst person involved
in the creation of Go.com.
Sure, sure, sure.
We got a lot of folks to talk about.
Yeah, there's some troublemakers for sure.
That's one way to put it.
So to go back, so all right, we're going to mash these things together and then I don't
know where the name Go.com comes from, other than it's something basic that hasn't become
a website yet.
And this optimistic era of it's all still ahead of us, we are going to take over the
internet with Go.com and the Go Network.
They also call it the Go Network.
And this is the period in which Eisner writes his book, A Work in Progress.
And just to read a passage, this is where he was at at that point, what he was looking
forward to at this time.
As we envision it, Go Network will enrich people's lives in many ways.
Call up Go Talk, for example, and you'll be able to communicate in new ways, not just
by sending messages, but by actually talking with as many as half a dozen other people
who are online at the same time.
What does that mean?
So you can get...
So it's a chat room but out loud.
It's an out loud chat room is what Go is going to have.
That's like spaces.
It's like spaces.
Oh yeah, it's kind of the spaces of it's time.
Twitter spaces.
Well, this seems like a great opportunity for people of all types to enter a room and
then for one person to say like, let me see your dick, can I see your dick?
Eisner was not thinking of that at the time.
Anyone was.
They all get reports like, just so you know, everything we're talking about here, 89% of
it will be sex related uses.
What was ham radio like that in the old days?
Was CB radio like that, where like people would just say dirty stuff in the old days?
I feel like it feels cleaner because it was an old...
They would say dirty stuff, but after you said a bunch of like Delta, Delta, Niner.
Oh, okay.
Well, but yeah, it would be like penis, but it would be...
Delta, Delta, Niner, suck my balls.
Over and out.
Like penis had a code word maybe or something.
So everything just felt a little cleaner.
I don't know.
He had a CB.
I always thought, yeah, I always thought it was like hobby enthusiasts.
That's if we were doing this as a radio show 30 years ago, we'll see Jason knows he's on
ham radio.
Right.
He knows all the hip lingo, he's on ham radio.
Go Shop will be designed to search out the best products and the best deals on the internet
in any given category.
And also to hook you up to a professional web shopper who will find precisely what you're
looking for on the internet.
This is, I was glad to find this because I can't find any, I can't find any literature
that says why go.com is going to be any different than any other website.
Yeah.
They're here as specifics.
You can enter a room of six perverts and talk to them on the phone, on the not phone.
And you can get a personal shopper, which is what?
Is that a person in the world who go drives the stores for you?
Yeah.
Or is that entirely online?
And then, and do they just end up like, okay, very good.
Well, thank you for these parameters.
I'll talk to you again in an hour.
And then he comes back and then like, all right, I think I found what you wanted.
And then it's just a photo of his dick.
They essentially wanted to invent Twitter spaces and stitch fix like 15 or 20 years
ago.
Yeah.
Okay.
It is stuff.
That's also something is the internet is unfolded.
I found where it's like Twitter starts and Instagram starts and I go, well, Facebook
did all this already, but like, apparently that's not how people like to absorb things
all in one big like, cause it didn't make any sense to me why you would do Twitter
or Instagram at first.
Cause I went, well, it's like just being on Facebook, I guess, right?
Cause you can post a status in there and you can post your photos in there.
It's not how people like, people like it, you know, in one app dedicated to a thing
in general.
I feel like.
Well, and how many old photos do you have like with hipstamatic filters on them?
A lot.
Yeah.
I don't need Instagram.
I just bought hipstamatic.
Sure.
Yeah.
He also, uh, back to Disney war, this is actually, this is from his like letter to the Sherald.
This is, this in general, because we look, we do a lot of glorifying Eisner on the show.
Rightfully so.
Yes.
You might read what he's saying here, but the near future of the company and go, okay,
well, maybe there's trouble in paradise.
So this is, this is his outlook at the top of 2000 in January, there's Fantasia 2000,
a remarkable continuation of a distinct Disney legacy from Memorial Day weekend.
His dinosaur, which is truly like nothing you've ever seen before further down the road
kingdom of the sun, which will definitely be called that and not have a contentious
documentary made about it.
And Atlantis are looking to be wonderful additions to the Disney animation legacy on the internet.
Go.com is an exciting venture into, into an entirely new world of information and entertainment.
Can what dazzle?
It's a exciting world of information.
What does it mean?
I don't think there was ever a vision here.
And while he was right about most of that, while dinosaurs certainly is like nothing
I've ever seen before, it was much, much cuter than anything anyone's seen before or since.
Yeah, look, at least he never offered to pay a woman $100,000 on a plane to take a mask
off.
You know, maybe he was losing it a little bit, but maybe it didn't get that bad is what
I'm saying.
I agree on some level.
Yeah.
Whatever the, the Eisner's worst beliefs have not been on the record.
He keeps them private.
Can I just confirm kingdom of the sun became emperors new group?
That is when it was a much more austere sting, a sting based project before he got pushed
out of it.
And his wife made this documentary.
That's fantastic.
Sweat box.
You ever seen that?
I, I can't remember if I've seen it.
You know, Disney chases it down and deletes it at every turn, but it's so it's worth,
I've watched it like in a tiny box in another box and another box on YouTube and it still
is just as entertaining that way.
It's a really great look into a messy creative process.
That's funny because Disney plus has, I guess, waking sleeping beauty is reasonably positive.
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
They're all the documentaries are incredibly positive.
This is like, this is things wife, Trudy Styler, correct?
Making a documentary about part largely about how sting got screwed and like seeing it kind
of as it.
Have you seen it, Mike?
I haven't.
I highly recommend it.
Yeah, I don't know why that's future.
One of those where I go shit.
Yeah.
You again, you have to let you got to like search, you got to search for it and pounce
on it when there is a version on Vimeo or Dailymotion or something.
Right, right.
Because Disney wants to make sure no one ever sees this interesting look at what it's actually
like to make one of these.
Yeah.
It's not that bad.
Like you don't see, it's not like you see Disney executives like, you know, uh, uh,
using racial epithets in each other.
Yeah, it's not that bad, but their brand is just so like, you just can't even anyway.
It's good.
Um, so, uh, yeah, then it became, well, what are we, who's going to run this thing for
us?
Uh, and there's a guy, I forget his first name, but wine bomb is the last name.
This is the genius who's going to run go.com, but then he left all of a sudden to start
a new website, business.com, which is still, I assume what everyone does when it's time
to do business.
You go to business.com.
Business.com.
Yeah.
Did you go to it?
You go to it.
First, you go to tie.com collar.com cufflinks.com and then you're ready to go to business.com.
This is reminding me when I had to write papers in high school, like early high school, because
eventually Google slowly got dominance.
But I feel like early internet, I would immediately, I was like, all right, I'm going to open one
browser window that for Yahoo, one for SGS, one for like excite or something like that.
And then I'll search like the Odyssey, the Odyssey, the like on all of that, like whatever
the topic was.
So like the executive brain and like just to see like, well, something give me the secret
hidden website, you know, that does all your homework for you that would that helps at
least.
Sure.
Yeah.
So anyways, so this this guy goes and then a new guy named Patrick Norton comes in and
Patrick Norton is like enough.
He's one of the guys behind Java.
So he's an Internet, you know, like they ended up with him in the Starwave merger.
So here and Eisner likes this guy enough that he's touted in the book.
Here's why our Internet future is bright, because Patrick Norton is with us.
He got real estate in Eisner's book, and that's why Go.com will be a dazzling portal into
Internet, into information and words, things that are never fully explained.
Then this guy went into a chat room.
Or look, look, all right, he got he got to catch a predator.
This is what happened to this guy.
Like exactly that, he entered a chat room and talked to somebody who was actually an
FBI agent in disguise and there was a sting operation.
And this guy got obviously removed from the project.
What was notable to me about this is that it is public what screen name he used during
this, which was Hot Seattle.
I mean, it's interesting.
I mean, maybe Seattle's pretty breathtaking.
The Frazier guy, you know, he's just like when I hear Hot Seattle, yeah, trying to conjure
the image, you know, Seattle was hot at the time.
That's all I'm culturally is what I'm saying.
Right.
What do you think I meant more than that?
Not temperature, temperature wise.
I know, certainly not.
Cold up there.
That's what makes it an ironic joke.
That's another thing I was trying to do with the name.
Why?
It's you're the pervert reading into the name Hot Seattle.
Yeah, that's something, isn't it?
Also, way to out your location.
Maybe keep that quiet, not in your screen name.
Right.
There's not his address in there, I guess.
Yeah, yeah, at least you left that out.
Uh, so anyways, things are not, we're losing people left and right for various reasons.
I didn't even know this other guy you said was a bad dude.
Oh my God.
Uh, all right.
So, but then Isender finds somebody, uh, who did not end up in a shady chat room to put
in charge of this thing.
And he says, you're going to figure it out.
We are going to become the, the guy's name is Bornstein.
I'm sorry, I don't have the first name.
He says to Bornstein, we are going to become the number one portal.
And Bornstein's a TV guy, he's never done internet.
So he doesn't, he doesn't know because it's not his world.
But Isender's like, I trust you.
You're good on TV.
It'll, you'll be great.
And, uh, so we're going to be the number one portal.
Bornstein says, how?
Isender says, we're Disney, we're storytellers.
Is this the beginning of storytellers getting used as a deflection for any
criticism you might have?
Storytellers, storytellers, don't worry.
We'll sort it out.
Storytellers.
This is such a funny.
This is, is there any more bold example of like executive rich guy brain than
this of just like, I don't understand anything about this, but I will make
somebody else never encountered failure at all.
So all I have to do is say storytellers every meeting and it'll surely get
solved because like Walt, like it worked for Walt with Bob Gurr and creating
ride vehicles and it works in other ways with imagineering, but this is a
whole different concept.
Yes.
Because like, you're right.
That is a good thing to compare it to because like, and this is, look, there's
a lot of rich guys who just like point to a capable person and say, I believe
in you, figure it out.
And it's half motivational and half like, I don't know what I'm doing.
But in that case, you did have a guy who just like a clang around with
hammers and figure out a ride.
How do you like, we're deep into Yahoo again, to paint the picture by this
point, it was, it was on the table.
AOL called Isner and said, what if we buy Disney?
How about that?
And it wasn't that crazy of an idea.
That's how big AOL is.
Yahoo is gigantic.
Right.
How are the, how is Disney just from nowhere going to go get, you're
going to beat Yahoo years late?
Hubris.
Yeah, yeah.
Story, well, by telling a story.
The problem is you aren't thinking like a storyteller.
If we tell the story where we're successful, then the story will be true.
My favorite apocryphal like story about that of like Disney and tech is every
time these two companies fortune swap of like Disney is going to buy Apple.
And then Apple gets huge with the iPod and the iPhone and everything.
And it becomes Apple is going to buy Disney, which I feel like is the
drum beat I've heard the last few years.
Oh God, there was another, oh, the other one from this era is like the, the, who
knows how far it got, but the like, look, we have our own theme parks, our own
hotels, why do we have our own airline?
And then someone had to go like, look, that plane crashes in a cornfield in the
mid wet, like, and there was just a smoldering Mickey head.
We are screwed.
And I don't even know how true that it's just like a story.
I like that.
They're not concerned about the potential human beings.
No, that's not concerned about one piece of debris was burnt, but enough to
do where it kept a clean Mickey on it.
Storytelling has to have a happy ending, a positive, easy flight to Orlando.
That is every corporation.
That is really the calculation at the end of the day, the story telling as
Brooke, the idea of like, what is the story we're telling?
I don't know how many years ago at broke containment from Disney, but, but just
hearing about like a sandwich shop or like, oh, it's an app where we pick up
your dry, just hearing about whatever arbitrary thing is like, what is the
story we're telling?
It's like, I don't know, man, what do you do?
Just talk about what you do and just do a good job.
Please.
Everything's breaking and everything's expensive and horrible.
Yeah.
I, yeah, I don't know.
Well, he, so he was, this is another thing.
Eisner was a pioneer is just saying the word story and running out of the room.
Tell a story.
What he's gone.
Uh, it was so much more style than everyone else.
So when all of this, I still have never really now go.com does is built in all of
this time.
Yeah.
Did you guys have any sense of what the hell was going on on go.com?
Did you poke around any iteration of go.com?
I mean, very little at the time.
Yeah, I've seen the old versions.
Jane had a very positive memory of going to disney.co.com because like, I think the
top menu bar at the top of the web page was a little monorail doodle.
There was a little monorail graphic and then there was a game like you could play.
Uh, where stitch, oh no, where you would play and stitch would be making sandwiches.
And my old man, Jason was just like, you mean like burger time?
Oh yeah.
For the stitch made sandwiches.
You had to catch the sandwich ingredients or whatever.
And you didn't play this too wild to make a sandwich.
That seems like more patients.
Well, yeah, but he gets hungry.
You know?
Yeah.
But I was, I was stitched.
I just eat all the ingredients.
I can't picture him like, all right, then mayo and three leaves of lettuce.
What would it sound like if he was Jason?
Hand me that sourdough.
Yeah, that's right.
That was one of the better stitches.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
So, you know, so we've talked about hundreds of thousands or hundreds of
millions of dollars spent and the only positive thing anyone's had to say, or
any, even one specific memory is there is a flash game where stitch made sandwiches.
Right.
So that's good.
That's nice.
I did poke around.
I went to the old internet way back machine and I found some old iterations
of go.com and I was thinking like, well, I just want to see what it looked like.
And there was a weird, they were doing like just tortured, like, okay, like how
do they make it Disney?
How do they make it cute?
And it will be, it is like the go is done and like the Walt font.
Right.
Oh, that's probably because the original logo was like a green light, but then
they got sued by a different website called go to.com.
It's my favorite detail when someone like doesn't take the 10 minutes to double
check, like, Hey, before we go full steam ahead, let's make sure this doesn't
already exist.
Well, I, you know what?
I saw the diff, the logos I was watching.
So I forget what YouTube and I was like, it doesn't look so close to it.
Really?
Yeah.
It wasn't so I don't have an image of the original go.com logos.
I can't really place it.
All I know is that where they landed with this very Disney writing go and then
like a yellow circle around it and it's all on top of orange is very ugly.
Yeah, it's terrible.
Bad enough that I thought it was fan made.
I encountered it enough times where I was like, okay, I guess this is legitimate,
but I thought it was just a fan thing.
There's a good video on YouTube by Rob place that kind of sums this all up in a
few minutes.
I'll shout out this video by midway to main street, which I did not know this
channel, but this is the, this is the, the go network logo.
Uh, and then it's like a Sesame street.
I mean, I guess it's, I don't know.
It's a green, green circle.
Goto.com got there first.
Yeah, I guess, but it's not like I would have gone, Oh my God, they're ripping.
Other than the fact that it's just a stoplight or a gold light.
Excuse me.
Not a stoplight.
I just call it a stoplight.
Why do you, why do you call it a stoplight?
You know, cause you go with it, you yield as well.
No one calls it, he calls it a yield light.
Yeah.
Netflix, give me 50 million for some standup.
How about that?
Well, I think that would have been, that would have been a
standup special 45 years ago.
Well, there's a market for it.
I think for retro, retro standup special that I'm doing here.
Why not?
Uh, uh, well in, in my poking around this website, when I was like, okay,
when did, when were there photos taken of vintage go.com?
When could I look at, uh, how, how a sparkling this website was?
Well, keep in mind that the era that it was open, uh, was, uh, when it was up
and running and there were the most like safe screenshots of it was a particular
time, that time being late 2001 and all again, let's do a little Simpsons.
Come on, say it, Jason.
What was going on that you recall in late 2001?
It's very funny you said that.
Cause as we were talking about early internet, I flashed back to, uh, the
fall of 2001 where I, uh, was put in the, uh, elective class.
One of the options I chose was called internet one second half of the year.
I was in internet too.
Now internet too was like playing around with like whatever
Microsoft website designer.
But internet one was basically just sitting fucking around online for 45
minutes and occasionally starting a geo city, like, Oh, try making a geo cities
page and I mostly read like Marvel had a lot of free comp, like a weird
amount of free comics online and he's saying it.
So wait, wait, it's very specific.
I remember a boring morning in the second, uh, like second, third period of
the day, internet one, taking around all the internet and walking to government
class and in the time it took me to walk to government, the first tower of the
world trade center was hit and by the time I was in government class, the
second tower was hit and we saw it live in government class, government class,
which he usually had CNN on anyway.
So walking into that was a startling experience.
You think you're going to just see another hour about Brittany and the snake.
Sure enough.
Don't get me started on the snake.
That's the world we left.
Anyway, that is, that is what like, so a lot of go.com a lot of go.com is
thriving areas, them try to combine that they've committed to being a news
website with also promoting Disney stuff.
So like just a few clicks away, like, all right, they have to, there's a big banner
and the banner has big scary jets in it.
And it says America fights back news story.
U S raids can be round the clock.
Al Qaeda issues call to arms.
Then above that, check out the monster zinc movie trailer, then a few away from
that villains layer win a billion dollars.
If you dare enter the villains layer.
Meanwhile, just a few ticks over.
There is a literal villains layer and that's Osama's cave that
we're trying to locate.
Eisner was not like dictating headlines.
Was he?
I can't imagine.
Well, look, you know, go.com we have to do another nine 11 story.
Why can't we highlight the villains layer?
Did I, do I need to reiterate that you can win a billion dollars?
I need to be pushing the billion and let's call president Bush.
What if whoever finds Osama is awarded the ransom of a billion dollars?
I got it.
Who, who wants to be a billionaire?
Print it, print it on go.com.
This is where this is really, this is new mythology.
Ville that you could win a billion dollars.
What, what is a billion dollar?
What was that prize then?
And what is that worth today?
If you didn't spend your billion dollars in 2000, Oh, the inflation has
been brutal on a billion dollars.
Five billion, 10 billion, put all my money into villains.
The economy was in such a turmoil post nine 11.
I thought it'd be safer in villains.
Finally got my villains settled down and the housing market crashed.
Uh, I might, when I was looking on the way back machine, it, it snapped
to like 2006 and they were like a first look inside Narnia and it's like, oh
yeah, I guess, uh, the Chronicles of Narnia was coming out.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's not all bad news.
Well, look at this stolen fertilizer trailer found intact.
And that's, that's right under the headline.
Cheney war on terror on course, a dark time.
And yet even in that dark time, a stolen fertilizer trailer could be found.
Again, you could get Snow White on DVD.
The one that started at all.
Kind of topical as some kinds of fertilizer can be used in explosives.
Sure.
Oh, is that what it was for?
In fertilizer trailer found intact by Al Qaeda.
So anyways, look, this is a rough, this is a rough time in general for Disney.
And this is, again, it's, I hate to say it.
It is an era where maybe I can understand why people were reticent about, uh, more
Eisner and doubling down on more of the job it pains me to say, but like, I
understand, but they just had to give him a couple more years.
And I think he would have figured it out.
He would have sorted it out.
Yeah.
Well, then people start trying to help him figure out.
And this new guy, Bornstein, who he said, figured it out.
We're storytellers by February 2000.
Keep in mind, I just, I read that letter that was like, 2000 is going to be a
wonderful year.
We got Fantasia 2000 and then we got go.com in February 2000.
Bornstein gets everybody together and he says, yeah, we cannot compete and win.
This is the portal strategy is a failure.
We will lose.
He just threw it.
He threw up the white flag.
The portal strategy was a flawed objective carried out with a poor strategy.
He argued that we should instead just maintain websites of ABC, ESPN, the
Disney channel, all the things that we do.
Uh, but he knew this was corporate suicide.
He knew he was screwed by saying all the, although to that end, I think Eisner
did appreciate the honesty, uh, I think listened to it and did not fire this man.
Uh, I mean, there's no one else to put on it, but like that's, that's immediate.
That they barely made it into 2000 with a guy going, we lost 30 over.
We lost smart enough to know that the name that I encountered, I hadn't seen
in a while, uh, mixed in on all of this was Tom stags was tasked with some of
this.
And I'm, am I remembering correctly as Tom stags, the one who was in that
photo of groundbreaking at Pandora, like Navi, the big shovels shovels.
And then when they printed it out and put it in the restaurant, one of them had
been photoshopped out because he was left the company because he was a guy like
they were like, oh, he's going to be the next CEO for a while and then the stags
stags is missing from the photo.
I think that I know what you're saying.
I think that's right.
Look up.
Cause I, why I, why I, Nick Weiger was in the running and then secretly on the
board of directors, Bob Iger is not Nick Weiger, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, Iger
like kneecapped stags and forced him out of the company.
Cause that was the word on Iger is that he was like, he's a very like
politician, but he doesn't appear to be a guy who's scheming, but he is.
He's like a, he's like a Leno, I think in a way.
Just being like, uh, altering history, like photoshopping someone out of a
picture that's already photoshopped to put giant Navi in there.
Oh, you should find that.
I, it gives me the Willie.
You should see if you can find the, I think it was cause I think he was,
he was pushed out there.
I've seen his name pop up recently.
I forget where he is now, but I feel like his name has popped up recently
as a successor to Iger, like they're still floating the idea that Iger is
going to be gone in a couple of years.
Oh, right, right.
And that maybe he could come back.
I don't think it's going to happen, but I have seen his name pop up again.
He's not back with the company, but we'll see.
It's interesting.
When you talked about it, when you, when you say photoshopping out like dark
history and things that we don't want to acknowledge, that makes me flashed all
these photos of Walt clearly smoking a cigarette where they fomented his hand
to not be, and I wanted to, this has been on my, I've been wanting to
mention this for a long time.
This is something I observed last year, a long time ago, the last I went to
Disneyland, actually, uh, uh, that I discovered, and I'm going to issue this
little scavenger hunt to the listeners.
See if you can figure this out.
Uh, maybe you'll find something that isn't what I'm intending to, isn't what I
found, but I know from this Disneyland visit that there is somewhere on the
Disneyland park, in the parks, I won't even say it's hotel or anything.
It's in, in one of the parks, you can find a visual depiction of someone
smoking a cigarette.
Does anyone know, do you, do you have any idea where this might be, who it
might be, a real life person, a photo.
Oh, I don't want to comment.
Oh, interesting.
Interesting.
Okay.
There's a, a visual depiction of cigarette, of a cigarette being smoked.
If you know what it is, reply under the episodes or send it to us somehow.
This is a fun little Disney scavenger hunt, which I will reveal in a later
episode because I've been wanting to bring this up for a little bit.
Not a pipe.
No, cigarette.
Cause I know a pipe one.
There is a pipe.
Who's smoking a pipe?
I think in Pinocchio, I thought there was a pipe.
Oh, okay.
Uh, well, I don't know in the, in the, in the, but that's like, is that somebody
smoking a pipe as a, as in the little morality play, like it's bad that you're
smoking a pipe in scrubbing all the cigarettes, I do think they forgot one,
if not two, if you know what it is, I'm curious.
And yeah, thank you for refraining from guessing.
Is it at the cigarette stand?
Is there still a cigarette?
No, I wish.
Do you wish those crowded days?
Oh, you're just craving a parliament.
Are you still wanting to smoke a cigarette?
Not at all.
No.
How real that was.
Yeah.
When was the last cigarette you had?
I, it was like a year ago or something.
Okay.
It's pretty recent though.
Port of Entry is his.
Oh, right.
In Port of Entry.
Was that it?
Oh, I think right after Port of Entry, I finished the pack back in
California, like one or two.
Okay.
But you're done.
Yeah.
I don't, it makes me feel like shit.
Okay.
All right.
So anyway, I'm trying to figure out how to like, wrap up the tale
or have I missed anything?
Well, I think I'm, I'm lacking actually information of like when they, they just
pulled it other than this guy saying in February, we've already lost.
We got, we just have to like, let's just make corporate websites.
What are we doing?
We were never, we were never going to have a search engine.
Yeah.
I saw part, I mean, maybe we kind of talked about this, but like, there was
an idea that they were going to get InfoSeek and StarWave and
combine them to some degree.
Well, that is what happened.
Right.
But I mean, I mean, in the sense that this was going to work in the sense that
like, we'll take two totally different types of companies and merge them, which
was a bizarre idea spread across the country and vastly different, like cities
and headquarters, too many variables there for this.
This feels like a half-ass thinking too.
You're like, well, these two companies put them together and like, let's go.
And I was going to say StarWave made like CD-ROMs and stuff.
Oh, okay.
And they made, uh, uh, there's a Muppet game they made, which I think we
may have talked about before called Muppets Inside.
Is that the one with the really ugly, weird, like full body,
like the walk cycles are bizarre?
So, but there's a Doom parody called Kitchens of Doom, which is a Swedish
chef fighting giant vegetables, which is kind of fun.
Yeah.
I was like, Oh, this may be, I think feeling maybe mentioned, mentioned it,
but I didn't really remember.
Um, but there's a bunch of different weird stuff and it's like the
Muppets are caught in the computer.
And I'm like, Oh, that's maybe something we dig into later.
Oh, good cover.
I don't know this.
Yeah.
They also like this kind of like, uh, not smug, a satisfied Kermit.
And maybe we haven't.
I just, there's so much stuff we mentioned and I forget.
Uh, but, and then there's also another thing that StarWave made, which is
called, it's a Clint Eastwood CD-ROM, which was just like an IMDB for him
with like, that you would just get like, see his credits and I think maybe
he had a clips of his movies.
I, that's something I got to dig into too.
Clint Eastwood.
The CD-ROM.
This is like when his social media posts, like with the logo on the picture of
like, Clinton getting ready for a shoot day.
Uh, um, yeah.
So, Oh yeah.
I'm looking at a still from it.
That's just like, it's, it's, it's this bizarre graphic from Bridges of
Madison County where they're like, uh, Clinton and Merrill are
Photoshopped into the landscape.
Um, Francesca offers Robert a token of her love.
This was from that other video.
This, they, I'm winning.
I've, I have, uh, I have a hundred Francesca love tokens.
I'm winning Clint Eastwood the game.
Um, cause we, we, of course did the CD, whatever the CD, uh, the cyber
awards, uh, episode on the second game, but we really like, I was like, wow,
we got to get back into some CD-ROMs this year, maybe two, cause there's
so much funny shit that no one cares about there.
There's some really good emulators out there.
So some of these might be playable.
Some could be playable.
Some are even playable on the internet archive or at least saved and hosted there.
Yeah.
Um, Starwave also developed the first site and publishing system for Jim
Kramer, Mad Money's Jim Kramer.
Well, Starwave sounds good.
I'm, I'm pro everything Starwave is doing.
Yeah.
And apparently in 2004, Disney reactivated the Starwave identity as
Starwave mobile, which published casual games for mobile phones is on Wikipedia.
Wow.
With the mobile game, several Scarface licensed games.
Oh, I kind of remember these as you're saying this, I kind of
remember the mobile Scarface games.
You kind of remember the Scarface mobile game.
Well, I feel like that might be an offshoot of like after Grand Theft Auto
three and then vice city were big hits.
There were attempts to mimic the other world, some more successful than others.
Yeah.
Well, there's like, Scarface is funny too.
Cause like they, they made Godfather games and like those, they're just seemed
funny to me, um, but they did do it.
So I don't, I don't know if those are playable still on mobile.
There was a run of like, Oh, well, Grand Theft Auto is crime.
You know, what else is crime?
And everyone knows Scarface and the Godfather.
Yeah, those are crime.
Uh, here's a lie.
Here's a Tony line that's just written in text.
Hey frog face, you just messed up.
You steal from me.
You're dead.
That's something Tony Montana would say.
Yeah.
I didn't want to go.
So I'm like, yeah, well, you know, I'm in dicey territory.
If I'm doing a Scarface, Scott does funny stuff on the show.
He does this great Scarface impression.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, hello.
Maybe I'm just worried that I can't do it.
Maybe.
Yeah, it's a very obvious impression that I can't, when in doubt, throw it
at Jason frog face.
No, that was not good.
You also did the thing.
Wait, say it is, say it is stitched.
Hey, frog face, you just messed up.
That was good.
Yeah.
Frog face, a very funny and that's, that's the kind of thing.
Scarface is that like a classic Frenchman?
Take it from me.
Scarface.
You're a real frog.
I'm Scarface.
Ribbit ribbit.
Uh, have I said, have you, you guys seen Scarface?
I've said this on the show before, right?
What?
You've seen Scarface, right?
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever seen it all the way through.
It's so, it's great.
Um, but it's so funny cause I didn't see it until I was older too.
And I was like, everybody, like there's like posters of Scarface and like
rappers of Scarface or whatever.
He's the biggest fucking loser of all time.
He's a pathetic loser in love with his sister.
Oh, we've talked about this cause good fellas is very similar.
Like a lot of them are also huge losers who die or fail.
Eventually they all die, but there, there is more, I feel like chunks of them
looking awesome and good fellas.
Where they're like, cool.
But Scarface, I feel like he's just this pathetic loser of all time.
And it's hilarious.
It's so funny.
And it's such a weird movie, but like, it's so funny to come out of that
movie and going like, this guy's fucking rules.
I get it.
Maybe the art and the t-shirts are put up and worn by people who
have not seen the movie.
It's possible.
I just pay a lot of attention.
Yeah.
Very similar to like, like Sopranos is very funny.
Like the college dorm room posters, just black and white.
Everyone with their arms crossed, 10 bad asses.
That's my takeaway from the show.
Also fucking weird.
Like uncle Juder and the kids.
Anyway, recommend Scarface.
Great movie.
Well, look, you know, just as some of these characters have mixed ends, you
know, it's not so clean as being the hero or the villain or having a victory or a
loss that's sort of where Eisner lands in this, because you might hear everything
that we said and you might chalk this up as just a massive loss.
However, this is also from Disney war.
They point out that in, you know, not long after that guy said, Hey, we
have to stop doing this.
This was a disaster from the get-go.
The bottom fell out of the technology sector.
The dot-com boom went dot-com bust.
The internet segment in particular was, was hit hard.
AOL Time Warner was especially hit hard, fully vindicating Eisner's belief that
Time Warner had exchanged valuable hard assets for a grossly inflated stock.
And it's, and as the book says, a book that is largely critical of Eisner, they
say rebuffing an offer from AOL was arguably Eisner's best decision of the
decade since the consequences would have been ruinous.
Yeah.
So as much as it is embarrassing that whenever you want to go to Disneyland.com,
these two little letters appear that are like the ghosts of Michael Eisner's
failure.
You know, what's worse is that Time Warner became AOL Time Warner, and that seemed
incredibly foolish very, very quickly.
And Eisner had that opportunity and he said, no, he called the CEO of AOL.
And he said, he probably called him a wimp too.
He said, how dare you?
And isn't that better if it had ended up AOL Disney and then all of Disney's
built around AOL.com potentially worse.
Maybe we don't have the Disney company anymore.
Maybe go was the confusing mess that had to happen in order to retain this
company, retain these parks and let us do this podcast that we do.
He's a great man and we should never question him again.
Nothing will ever take away that opinion.
There's no story that we can dive into that will make me think otherwise.
He tried.
He put a Hillbillies rolling on logs in Disneyland's Lake.
He tried to build his own.
I find it confusing that you chalk that up as one of the craziest things he ever
did was a brief promotion where there was state fair stuff.
This guy was out of his mind.
He had Hillbillies guys on logs.
He was sick and twisted.
He would do anything.
He did balloon stuff.
Remember in state fair, he did balloon stuff with all of our friends, with the
guys, but these are all popular for deck and like log rolling.
Log rolling is popular.
I feel like at state fairs and stuff.
Yes.
Or like, this is what I do agree with Jason here that putting, taking, saying
we're going to do a state fair thing and then putting a state fair thing at it is
not particularly one of the most balls out decisions Eisner ever made.
This is counterculture shit.
This is fucking real counterculture shit.
Man, Eisner was punk.
Eisner is punk, bro.
The traveling inflatable thing.
If they had just included it for free, like with your fair admission or whatever,
probably would have worked.
Can I put you on finding a video of this fair, this fair show with the balloons?
Oh, the traveling.
We need to find that video of the show.
You guys said that it has to be a separate episode, but we need to find the video.
We need to find the video.
Well, I'll try.
And it's in, it's in Jason's best interest because otherwise that episode is
going to turn into nothing but talking about inflatable stuff.
Right.
Unless we have hard research materials to go off of.
There's no other way that episode can go.
But my hands, I've put my like, not on the, I'll look, I'll look the best I can.
I'm casking you with finding.
Yes.
Okay.
You're on this.
You're the reporter, the cub reporter.
There's something else that we got to do.
And I'm going to, I'm going to keep, uh, I'm going to spread this Eisner love
elsewhere in the Eisner family tree because I was, I was reading one of many
articles about go.com, shutting down, laying off a lot of people, them throwing
in the towel.
And at the end of the article, there was a little addendum and it said this.
Meanwhile, Eisner's son, Eric has changed his business plan at his own digital
entertainment site, the romp.com.
Is this anyone familiar with this?
No.
Oh boy.
I think we were planning another episode here.
Eisner juniors babes in animation site will begin charging a subscription
for premium users soon.
If you want the newest booty call cartoon, as soon as it comes out, you can pay
for it, said a romp spokeswoman.
Now I, this, everything connected for me here because I realized that, and forgive
me, I don't know the listener who put it, but we've gotten this suggested as a
club three topic before, and I was texted out of the blue a couple of months ago
by friend of the show, Joe Quazzala.
And he alerted me to a particular film and he led me down the rabbit hole here.
And I was like, why are you telling me about this?
And he said, well, you might be interested in who the director of this
film is one Eric Eisner.
And what he's talking about is a 2003 movie.
And this has been suggested for club three.
The movie is called Jake's booty call, otherwise known as national
lampoon presents Jake's booty call.
This is a flash animated based on an interactive game series for romp.com
turned into a feature film in 2003.
It's a series of 33 multi-plot animation games.
That was turned into a feature film, uh, written by and directed by Eric Eisner.
Eric Eisner made a flash animated sex comedy.
This is very small for you guys in my laptop across the room, but take a
look at the art that I give you a sense of, uh, you know, we're in leisure suit.
Larry, it's a rip off of Larry, but with less personality, but this is, I mean,
this era of home star runner, like flashed animation was he bombs world?
Like, yeah, it was in vogue.
Yes.
And Eisner and the Eisner's as they are on top of every wave, just as Eisner
knew that he, we, he, Eisner, the fan of email knew that they had to
have an internet presence.
So did Eric Eisner know that we need a animated film that's very cheap and
ugly with a lot of boobs in it.
We guys, whether club three or not, we've got to do Jake's booty call.
We have to, there's a whole, all of the love gets put on brick.
Yeah.
What we're giving.
No, I don't think I've, I mean, I knew there wasn't Eric Eisner, but I haven't
thought about him almost at all.
Eric Eisner, as much the filmmaker is his brother.
Michael created two great filmmakers, the body of work that will
resonate for decades to come.
I declare Jake's booty call.
Jason's birthday shot.
You're, you can't call my shot.
Why can't I?
I don't know.
That's a hell of a shot to call.
Your birthday is coming sooner.
You should call Jake's booty call.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
No, you should.
But parliamentarily parliamentary procedure.
You have to wait until your birthday and make your birthday shot, stealing
Jason's birthday shot and forcing him on his birthday to do Jake's booty.
Fine.
Yeah.
I was going to do a wholesome thing for my birthday.
No, you're not.
Show us boobs.
No, the rom.com right now is just a landing that says big news coming soon.
Stay tuned.
Leave your email to be notified.
So who knows what that is?
Jake back over 20 years later for another booty call.
He may have aged, but he's as horny as ever.
Wow.
Jason, could you do the voice of Jake?
Who did the voice of Jake?
I don't know anything about Jake.
You do know a lot about him already.
We're all learning together.
That's the point.
Uh, voice acting was provided by Jay Lerner and Julian Max Metter.
Okay.
Well, they're out.
Yeah, they're out.
Jason's in.
Jason Sheridan, who has a bigger fan base than them.
Yeah, this reminds me of another movie that we have not gotten to yet.
The, what is it called?
It's all the food mascots.
It's CG animated.
Oh, I know Charlie Tuna.
I've watched that too many times for my own health.
It's not sausage, but it's like a precursor to sausage.
Yeah.
It's like a less successful.
No.
And Charlie Sheen is a big dog man who kisses a human woman by Hilary Duff.
That's a, that's a, that's a rough go.
Yeah, that's bad, but you're correct.
We haven't done it.
We have not touched that.
Teen Creeps.
Did Teen Creeps do that with Oscar?
Maybe.
I don't remember.
I feel like maybe that's an Oscar.
Well, Eisner's ours.
No other podcast is going to claim the word of the filmography of Eric Eisner.
Step aside, blank check.
I'm afraid you'll never cover the $50,000 blank check that was used to make
the film Jake's Booty Call.
It's not even that much in terms of funding of film.
Well, I'm sure that created a real beautiful work and I can't wait to do it anyway.
So yes.
Hey, shots called right at the top as it should be.
And with that, you survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP page here on tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
If you want to throw Jake's booty call into there to like, help us get to it
faster, just to like kind of move it up to the top of the paper pile, you certainly
can cigarette scavenger hunt, please let us know if you can find a cigarette in
Disneyland, let us know there might be ones that I am not even thinking of.
Let's find all the cigarettes in Disneyland.
Um, I'd also like to say that I think I, my brain was thinking of ill Devo, the
international singing group, when I incorrectly called like one of those
things that the mom's like, I think I was also, I like, when you said the eel, I
was like, I've seen that eel.
Well, I freaked you out.
So you were ready to agree with me because you didn't want me to do anything.
You don't want me to put you on the spot.
I know I'm yeah, you were just like, I'm a little word, whatever you say, sir.
Please don't call me something.
You can mispronounce any of the different city walk.
Okay.
It's Abercrombie and oh, at the end of the episode, let's come on.
All right.
We're going to Fitch.
Wait, what'd you say?
Fitch.
Yes.
Good.
Yeah, we've learned that's an ampersand.
Oh, I, I don't know.
Is it an E doesn't matter.
They're shutting it down.
It's dead to us.
Okay.
Fucking care.
Take your ampersand and shit.
You're that ampersand is getting in the way of the future of the city walk.
Yeah.