Welcome to what I promise you will be the shittiest podcast,
the ride you've ever heard.
I'm Scott Gardner and I'm sorry in advance,
joined by Mike Carlson, who I assume is similarly contrite.
Oh yeah, I am contrite and I'm thinking about
what you just said and I guess that's true,
but I also, that gives me a freedom, you know?
When you say this is gonna be so bad,
I kind of actually relaxed for the first time ever
when I started doing like a recording.
So I go, wow, that's great.
Cause you've had the pressure of this could be the best one
or it could be the shittiest one if we aren't careful,
but no, this I feel, I think this is good
when we're looking for good news here
and I think this kind of like takes the pressure off
because there'll be that discussion as time goes on.
What was the worst episode of the show?
Let's just say it, it's this, it's gonna be this.
It's this one, we're doing it because it's gonna be,
there's a couple of things, it's gonna be short,
we are missing a host, it's on Zoom,
we've got bummer stuff to talk about
and I'm really confident a baby
is gonna start screaming soon.
And then, you know, there's a door here,
but I think that baby's gonna power over that door.
I think you are gonna hear the baby,
so I think it's good that I weren't.
Okay, yeah, well, let's see if the baby comes in on the mic.
It'll be interesting to know
cause that'll be baby's first podcast recording as well.
So it'll be something that'll be important
to capture as well, I think.
Yes, I think it'll be treasured by me and the listeners
when you hear just a faint, aah, aah.
But you'll bring that, yeah, you'll bring it up,
I'm saying like when the baby is older
and you'll say, look it,
this is the first time you ever podcast it.
That'll be nice.
I hope to God the last.
If I have anything to do, if I raise this kid right,
it's gonna be the last.
The only jobs left.
I can't control the tides of the business.
Yeah, 30 years from now,
that's the only job that's gonna be left as podcasters,
so I think we should just accept it right now.
Yeah, and everyone will need seven of them
to make ends meet as opposed to the mere six of currently.
Yeah, look, hey, I'm happy to be talking to you, Mike,
and we're just doing this as kind of a little check-in
to explain where we're at.
So, you know, we usually,
I specifically look forward to the first episode of the year
being like full of energy and well rested
and maybe like a big ride or a new ride, you know,
to come back guns blazing.
And right now I feel like, if I could talk about,
I believe this ride closed, Kingda Ka,
I think Kingda Ka is down,
the one that's just kind of, it's a launch in New Jersey,
and it's where you just go way up a big hump
and then down the other side.
You know how sometimes they'll launch that ride
and it won't make it,
and it just goes all the way back down to the station
and like, whoops, didn't, that's how I feel about,
the 2025 launch is a real Kingda Ka fail
on multiple levels to put it in,
I think we have to put it in roller coaster terms
so people understand.
Yeah, that's how our audience understands that kind of talk.
So that, thank you for doing that.
That's all they understand.
There's no other metaphor that would make sense
other than the very relatable Kingda Ka.
Right, right, of course.
Which RIP, Kingda Ka.
Anyway, that's a complicated and stupid way to say
that things are crazy, our city is on fire,
and that has kind of prevented us from doing things
the way that we'd like to be doing things.
Now the big headline is that the three of us
are all safe with all that.
Mike, you went down to San Diego,
not due to any particularly strong danger,
but just a precaution and a more comfortable place to be.
Is that a correct assessment?
That is a correct assessment.
We certainly live by a big bunch of mountains
and the air was bad, so we said, let's get out of here.
And we're very lucky.
Yeah, yeah, you've got a place to go, absolutely,
and yeah, because not everybody does
and to have family close, it's been really key.
So we're happy to say the three of us are safe.
When we just posted something, maybe on X,
it makes me nauseous still to say X.
We said something that maybe alluded
to how the week is going, and I just wanted to read this.
This is from the user Diddy Thump,
and I thought this was a pretty good little burn of us.
Looking forward to the presumably entirely normal
and uneventful evacuation process
that all three of you had.
Now, we did not really all evacuate,
so it's not necessarily accurate,
but this is a listener who's worried about us going to lunch
and I think correctly so.
He's heard the tales of woe just to go from a hotel
to a mall and what happens, but can we prove
Diddy Thump wrong though, or was it fairly orderly?
I mean, look, again, we were lucky.
We just sort of were getting out, so it wasn't anything.
There was people that had to leave at the drop of a hat,
so everything was fine.
I will say I stopped in Buena Park on the way down here,
which I think is actually smooth.
It's like, that's, again, that's a nice,
that's a luxury to be in Buena Park,
the greatest city in the world, and I ate a Portillo's.
Well, it's all under any circumstances, it's a luxury,
but especially now, now more than ever.
But I did eat a Portillo's,
and yes, I took all the essential stuff with me,
but I also did take belly bomb off of the shelf,
my prized NECA toy that I believe looks a little phallic.
Some people don't, but I do,
but he's one of the greatest figure.
That was like a,
that was a prized possession that you took was belly bomb?
I looked around the office and I said,
let me just take a couple things and throw it in the bag.
I didn't pack everything up, but I said, you know what?
I took the basics and I took the belly bomb
and I was right to do it.
Well, what are the, I think we've been seeing some stuff
about the six P's of evacuation.
There's passports and there's pets
and there's personal belongings,
but I think the seventh P is penis resembling toys.
I think that's right, yes.
I think that is correct, and I should make my own list.
To say, yeah, get a penis resembling toy
and then get a beef and cheddar croissant
if you can manage it in Buena Park.
Well, wait a minute, Portillo's.
Portillo's is the AC.
Damn, you're right. Wow, wow.
And ninth points, make sure that all of,
make sure that your points are safe.
Yes, yes.
Which I guess means bring any credit cards that contain,
I mean, the points really aren't on the card,
but just make sure that your points are in order,
because you might need them more than ever.
Right, now, and yeah, this digital age,
you don't necessarily need a card
that contains all your Landry's points
or your Jersey Shore points.
That's all on your phone usually,
but just make sure you have that in order.
Yes, that's important.
Yeah, oh, and if you don't, oh my God,
well, and again, a couple episodes ago,
I gave you guys Jersey Mike's gift cards,
which are physical items,
and now the fire has taught me,
don't ever do that again.
Make sure that it's only digital,
because what if those went?
What if the Jersey Mike's,
what if those are Shore points that are no more points?
That's very, yes, you're right.
I think I left the unused gift card at home,
now that I'm thinking about it.
You were mentioning your baby was gonna
make its presence known on your end.
My daughter is just trying to open the door
as if it's like a serial killer trying to get in the room,
like fighting for her.
It's a forensic raptor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think she was.
If it needs to happen, again,
that's why I wanted to take the pressure off.
If suddenly there is some Mike fumbling,
if she wants to come in and actually,
hey, look, everybody could use a cheer up.
If she wants to give her thoughts about belly bomb on Mike,
I think that would be a cheer up for everybody.
I think I made it through mine.
I believe the crying was distant enough,
and maybe he's gone.
Yeah, so that threat has passed, if not all have.
Okay, so keep your eyes on the door.
Here's the other theme parky thing I wanted to mention
as this is all going down,
is that again, I think probably we wanted,
the plan was like, well, you know what?
New year, new ride, we can come out with Tiana.
We could finally do Tiana,
and I had this cursed pass
that I've been blacked out on for a month,
but I'm like, okay, so the first,
you know what, I'm gonna schedule this for early January
when everything should be safe and fine and normal,
and I'll get down and do Tiana,
and then we could talk about Tiana,
and then the day that I had planned for months, of course,
is when all the shit went down.
So that blows that season premiere.
But Brightside, in the midst of darkness,
as we all know, Disneyland has the no-show policy.
You only get three no-shows,
and I wasn't sure enough if I was gonna do it
to cancel the night before,
because as far as we knew, it was like,
it's gonna be windy, get ready for some wind,
and nobody knew how crazy this was gonna get,
including apparently the mayor
and a lot of other important people
didn't seem to know or do anything.
So anyway, I was getting worried.
Obviously, my biggest fear in all this
was getting one of three no-shows,
which do you know the brackets on that?
How long is the no-show period?
Is it a month, or is it 90?
Well, you're saying between no-shows?
Because I understand it, and I may be wrong,
so somebody correct me.
My understanding is that you still just keep your no-shows,
and once you get three, then you're banned for 30 days.
Now, that could be wrong,
but this is off the top of my head.
I think that-
I got 90 in my head.
I think there's a 90 in there.
Maybe it's that you can't do it in 90 days,
and then you're banned for 30,
or is it you can't do it within 30,
and then you're banned for 90?
I don't think you're banned for 90,
but I could be wrong.
I should look that up.
That's tough.
That's a reasonable prison sentence.
It really is, yeah.
Yeah.
I guess I'll look, because I accidentally,
I even mentioned this in the show,
I've accidentally given my sister a second no-show.
I was supposed to cancel a reservation on a family trip,
and I forgot, or it didn't go through or something,
and she was like,
I don't want another no-show on my record,
and I remember looking in the morning,
and I still had her on there, and I went,
I fucked up, I screwed this up.
So now she has two, so she's close.
You inflicted a no-show onto your own family?
Yes.
This is, oh boy, how are you living with yourself?
I don't know, it's not easy, it's not easy,
but I'm doing my best.
I'm in a lot of therapy.
You'll reconcile with this in your autumn years.
This is gonna be more of an article search, I think,
to find out exactly the details on this.
Well, I'll say this while you're looking.
Here's the good news, is that for that stretch of time,
because so much of the city was on fire,
the Disney corporation was exceedingly generous,
and they overturned all of the no-shows
for at least a day or two.
So I do not, unlike your sister who is less fortunate,
I have zero of three right now,
and I just wanna say to the Disney company,
it's been a tough time, and I see you,
and I recognize what you did for me,
and there's that quote, Mr. Rogers, look for the helpers,
and I'm thinking about that more than ever.
Nothing helps me more than having a blemish removed
from my Disney permanent record, so thanks for the help.
Walt would be proud.
You have a clean record.
This is so hard to find.
I mean, I surely got it in an email,
because now you get it.
Like, okay, hey, welcome to your Disneyland trip awaits.
All your friends are gonna be there, Mickey and Minnie,
but do be aware that if you are a no-show,
Mickey will remember it, and he will mention it the next day.
If and when you were allowed to come back into the park,
Mickey will bring it up, he will whisper it into your ear,
it's like, hey, happy to have you,
but just so you know, we know.
Just so you know, we know, we remember.
You know what, I'm finding some interesting details here,
like adults must replace the photo
that's attached to their pass every 10 years.
So to make sure you have, yeah, so you have to-
Is it DMV aspect to it?
Yes, apparently, and you must replace
your child's photo every three years.
That's interesting.
I didn't know that before.
Kids grow, you know?
A three-year-old is not a six-year-old,
and they gotta keep tabs on them.
Right, interesting.
So 10 years, I think I've, yeah, I had a new,
I guess I got a new one in 2021, probably.
So 2031 is when I'm gonna have to,
I'm gonna really have to make sure, like,
I take care of myself so I look good
in my 2031 Disneyland annual pass.
Finally a motivator, oh my God.
I mean, now the thing is, I mean,
general fitness is gonna help you with that,
but really, you're kinda only dealing with it
in most shoulders and above.
So if you want your calves to get real flabby,
that's fine, you could gain 100 pounds if it's all leg,
but you're gonna wanna keep the shoulders and up look,
which means, like, which is also skincare,
it's exfoliating, it's trimming that beard.
Right.
It's really, it's all upper stuff.
Yeah, so maybe even if, maybe I could just wear, like,
a Mission Impossible mask in 2031, too,
if I'm not happy with how I look,
and it'll, like, a handsomer,
I guess I have to wear that then every time I go to the park,
so that wouldn't be a very smart thing to do,
but maybe I'll really-
Oh, to match every time they scan, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll get, like, a makeup artist, though,
to do something to my face before I get that photo taken,
just so I can look good in that photo,
because that's something I care about.
I cannot find the answer to this question.
I'm looking through these GD details,
and it's really hard to find.
I don't feel like doing it.
I don't feel like opening a tab, clicking around.
I don't feel like doing it either.
I wanna put it down.
Not having a third person, it's harder.
I'm happy, thank you for going for it.
Again, I look to the helpers,
thank you for helping trying to decipher the no-show policy,
but I don't think I'm gonna do it.
Although, as I said, shittiest episode ever.
If there was ever one to just go blank for four minutes,
it's just silence and then, like, click, click, click.
I don't know if you're getting that click on, Mike.
No, I don't think so.
No, okay, well, just like the baby.
Okay, well, maybe it's not the shittiest episode.
We're only recording what we need to be recording.
Yeah.
But here's the thing, though.
We wanted to have a little fun and goof around a little bit,
but there is, of course, like, you know, stuff is terrible.
It is tough in the city.
Everyone, we were saying before we started recording,
everyone at least is a friend of a friend of somebody
who has lost their home or evacuated.
Yeah, lost everything.
And everyone's just going through, yeah, yeah.
It's crazy.
Everybody's going through it.
It's all palpable and it's just, you know,
like the mood ain't great regardless of your situation.
If you are a person who has been struggling through this
or something terrible happened or you know somebody,
our hearts go out to you.
And if there's any way we can help or signal boost anything
anybody needs, please let us know.
I don't know what we can do.
I mean, we look forward to making you laugh in the near future,
but God knows if we can, like, use the socials to, you know,
to do any good or spread the word.
I want to put that out there if we could.
Here's the other thing.
And there is there's no easy way to transition into this.
But as all of this was going on unexpectedly,
and unfortunately, Jason's dad, Michael Sheridan, passed away.
And we don't want to say too much about that.
We'll leave it to Jason if he wants to address that any further
on the show at some point.
But mainly for now, we're heartbroken for him
and for the Sheridans and for Jane.
He's joined in the family and our hearts go out to them
and thoughts and condolences.
Anything you want to add to that, Mike?
You don't have to, but we're thinking about her, buddy.
That's exactly what you said.
And it's, as you said, heartbreaking.
And in the middle of all this chaos and sadness
that was happening already.
So, yeah, needless to say, Jason could take some time away
from the show and he will be back.
But, yeah, whenever he feels like he's ready to come back
and goof around, obviously he takes as much time as he wants
and we'll hopefully see him soon.
But, yeah.
Yeah, that's the point.
And hopefully, the thing we can offer
is goofing around with him again
because we'll miss it while we're not doing that with him.
And, I mean, all that being said,
let me just shift to here's the plan.
Here's what's going on in general.
You're right about Jason.
And with all this, I think we've conveyed
through all of this how nuts everything is.
And thus, here's what we've decided
and why we're checking in.
We are going to take the rest of January off
on the main feed.
Just collect ourselves, get back in the same place,
focus on our families, give Jason the space he needs.
We feel like we are not currently in a place
to do the quality of show that we want to be doing
and the quality of what the eight episodes a month
we end up doing that we want.
So we figure if we take a little time, we'll get there.
So that's the plan.
It is our hope and our goal to be back
on the main feed in February.
Things could change, but that's the hope
and this is what we're gonna try here.
So I guess we're asking for your patience
and your understanding as we navigate these choppy waters.
And it's unfortunate, we're sorry that it is this way
because we were just off for three weeks
and that we're extending it out.
But hey, we didn't expect any of this
and I don't know, hopefully you understand.
Yeah, and then we're still doing
the other Patreon episodes that are coming out.
There's an episode that we've already recorded
with Jason that's coming out.
Oh yes, the Club 3, yes, there's a very fun Club 3 episode
about the Space Mountain opening,
so that happened already.
And then you and I, yes, as far as Second Gate and Club 3,
we wanna make good on those commitments
to everybody who so kindly supports the show over there.
So you and I will figure out some stuff to do.
We'll screw around and do some low pressure fun.
Yeah, there's some fun ideas.
Keep the hits coming.
Yeah, there's some fun ideas happening.
We just have to reorganize and get it together
and then those will be out in January.
Yeah, yeah, right on.
So that's the thing, sorry.
So if you are missing us and you need a good boy fix,
things will still be happening on Second Gate and Club 3,
which is at patreon.com slash podcast the right.
As we said, Jason, probably out for a little bit.
We'll just, yeah, the door's open whenever he wishes.
We'll be looking forward to his return.
And just, also, I just thank you again,
anyone who's supported the show over the years.
That's just, and especially in times of crisis,
that is meaning very, really means a lot to us, I think.
More than one way.
No, I'm kidding.
I know, this is making me flash to the addressing.
So there's this pandemic that you might've heard.
There's a whole other thing that was probably us going,
so I guess we'll be on this Zoom thing for a few weeks
and then it ended up being a year and a half.
And many of the people listening right now
were with us through all of that
and were like a reason for us to goof around,
be creative, and have fun together,
even when things are crazy.
So I'm flashing all that.
I'm thankful for that.
I'm thankful for everybody now.
And that's a good opportunity to say that, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, we'll be having some fun there and we'll be back.
Fingers crossed we'll be back in the same city fairly soon.
And I don't know, I always thank the people working in LA
that are doing good work.
Thank you to those people.
I don't know, I just wanna, it's crazy watching it.
I'm sure everybody's watching videos of stuff.
People flying these helicopters,
I don't know if you've been watching this shit.
I'm obsessed with this,
the people doing drops with the water.
Have you seen this?
Well, yeah, there's these ones that are going around
that are like so ace-nailed and it feels incredible
to watch a raging fire just be done in two seconds,
because that's what we wanna see more of.
And boy, yeah, it's exciting to get a great feed of one.
It is crazy, these people are awesome doing this stuff.
So yeah, all of that is thank you to those people
and everyone else helping.
Does it qualify as a ride?
Do we, can we, does it qualify as a ride
if you're flying those helicopters
or just in the helicopters helping in some way
or is that too exciting and interesting?
Mm, it might be too exciting and interesting.
I guess I'm warning for future
if we were to have a helicopter flight,
like a firefighter, a helicopter firefighter
on the show at some point.
I think it's like in the same way that like,
if you go, man, I love the Mexico Pavilion at Epcot
and then somebody goes, yeah, but you go to Mexico
and you go, yeah, but that's too real.
I think maybe these are helicopter and plane flights
that put out fires.
They're too real, you know,
that's too legit to be a ride, I think.
But I'm thinking this all the time,
so somebody could prove me wrong.
Yeah, all right, yeah, so temper the excitement a little bit.
Yes, yeah, for sure.
Yeah, no, absolutely, though.
Thanks to everybody and hey, you know,
just thanks for the understanding.
Also thanks for the understanding of us
awkwardly poking around very special episodes.
I think this is a thing we are not good at doing.
I'll speak for myself.
It's something I don't feel good at doing.
We even had to do, like, I'm like,
we better try to say a bunch of funny things
in the beginning or I'm gonna be in trouble here.
That's all I know how to do.
My brain is broken.
How do you deal with serious things?
I know, anytime I ever do anything serious,
I like, I go, oh, I didn't say that right.
And then I, I told you, I said a couple weeks ago
how much I like, I stress out about just normal sentences
that I say week to week on the show.
But then when I have to say a serious sentence,
oh boy, does my anxiety shoot up.
I go, did I say that right?
People can understand what I meant.
So I hear you, I'm with you.
I would rather, I would be rather making jokes
about inflatable stuff, for sure.
That's my comfort zone.
That is the biggest thing that is gonna be off the table
for a little bit.
It's disgusting.
What has been my greatest joy?
It's really, you know, I think I have like a podcast
favorite toy for a while, like the dog chewed toy
that he just wants to attack and ruin.
And you're lucky that inflatable stuff came up
because that's my new favorite toy
that we're gonna have to set it aside for a while.
Because in the lead up to that,
it was definitely only listening to half
of Olivia Rodrigo's guts.
That was my, oh my God.
I was, the best toy I've had in a long time.
So you're very lucky.
So Olivia, half Olivia is getting eased off on
and maybe inflatable stuff too.
Okay, great.
Yeah, I hear you.
Well, we'll have to find new stuff,
which is I think is like, I was just,
I just discovered a couple of another Michael Eisner
like ideas the other day that I don't,
I forget if we've talked about like the wedding
of Mickey and Minnie, have we talked about that?
No, let's give people some hope into what we can talk
about soon, please.
Let's just, you know, let's open the doors
to the brainstorming process now.
For some better episodes to come.
Yeah, there was an idea that Michael Eisner
had of a year long celebration leading up
to the wedding of Mickey and Minnie.
I've never heard this, really?
Never heard it before, yeah.
So I was like, oh man, okay.
So that honestly, that was like a day or two ago.
Oh shoot, I forgot that guy.
I forget his channel.
This guy mentioned it on his channel.
I really should shout him out,
but I'll shout it out when we do the episode.
Here in LA, we've been in this realm
of the loud emergency alerts going off.
And I was watching the news when all the anchors got loud,
like somebody was on screen talking and then,
and then everybody off screen in waves.
Like there's the other anchors
and there's the camera people
and there's the people in the booth
and all the phones are going off.
It was wild to watch that happen on live TV,
especially because that's the one that was wrong
where they told, it was like everyone evacuate
and that was meant for only a specific area.
The people, everybody has some complaints
about how everything's going in LA right now.
In terms of the people who supposedly run the city.
But anyway, I say all that to say,
I wish to God that in a crazy emergency alert like that
would pop up on my phone.
And then I checked it and it said,
Michael Eisner once planned a year long ceremony
celebrating Mickey and Minnie's wedding.
That's the only thing.
And I would, if I got that alert at 4 a.m.,
I'd be happy I got it.
I wouldn't be mad that my sleep was interrupted.
If anything that crazy, call me about,
text me about, there's no time,
that's a bad time to hear about Mickey and Minnie's wedding.
I had a similar dopamine hit when I heard about this.
So yeah, it was very, very exciting.
That's right.
You know, I think we've talked about before,
but it just seems like a cousin of the,
and there's maybe not enough meat on the bone
for a full episode, but that whole,
the thing where he wanted to,
here in our neck of the woods, Burbank,
God bless Burbank, lately it's been nice and safe for us,
but that straddling riverside drive,
which currently, if you've ever been around the Disney lot,
there is like, there's ABCs on one side of the street
and then the main lot is on the other side.
And now there's a bridge that connects the two
and the animation's over there too.
But the idea was that for that, where that bridge is,
straddling the two sides of the lot
was gonna be a big hotel shaped like Mickey.
There's gonna be a big Mickey
in what very quickly leads to just an equestrian neighborhood.
It's just ranch style houses where people have,
you know, barn stables and stuff.
And that, so you would drive into your beautiful like ranch,
your 1940s ranch home under Mickey Mouse's legs.
And this was an Eisner plant.
This was Eisner trying to be bold and like,
I'm here, I'm new, this is the kind of shit I want.
I don't even know if I like it,
but I'm putting it on the table.
I mean, that would change the city for,
like if that was there,
if you were always driving under Mickey's crotch every day
to your home, to your horse.
I found, there's the video, I saw that information
which is from the YouTube channel Midway to Main Street.
And it's five abandoned Eisner era ideas.
And that is the Mickey hotel is in there.
Oh, okay.
Oh, so it's very related.
And it was like, I don't,
maybe we talked about this detail and I forgot,
but his idea was that the rooms would be in the legs.
We must have, we must,
because there's no way we haven't discussed it.
Like some room ultimately,
unless you like floor 13 it and just block the space up,
but some room is going to have to be Mickey's balls.
Yeah, of course.
That would be, I hope a suite at least.
That would be a bigger area to live in.
But yes, you would,
well, in the short-
What if also, what if also just kind of like
the rain gutter for the entire thing,
just like whatever, like the plumbing,
whatever like the vents,
that it does all lead ultimately to Mickey's asshole.
If you ever see like liquids or steam
coming out of the Mickey hotel,
it hills all right out of the boat.
Look, if I was planning it,
I would argue that the steam should be vented from the ears
to at least make him seem like he's mad sometimes,
but it might make more sense to vent it from his asshole.
So an engineer is somebody who would have to come up
with that, explain it to me why it has to be vented
from there, but I would try to get it out of his ears
to at least make it a fun thing
that like Mickey's upset today.
Like if the, you know, everybody's-
Well, you'd have to pitch it to Eisner.
Where's the steam?
We all know that hotels have to release steam
frequently, but what part of Mickey's body
is the steam gonna come out of?
Well, it could come out of his mouth
and people would think he's like blazing up.
Like you could like, like all of a sudden Mickey like
blows a big plume.
That's cool, man.
And a nice tribute to, you know,
Michael Eisner who must have been blazing up
to think of an idea like that.
He's so, yeah, he's so out there with his ideas.
Somebody commented on it.
We were talking about Eisner stuff
and I saw the comment like,
so he was doing buckets of cocaine, right?
And I'm like, that's a funny thing to say
about 80s executives and you know, maybe,
but like, is that his vibe?
Is this- No, I don't think so.
Because on TV, is the vibe of somebody
who does buckets of cocaine, hello?
I don't- I don't think so.
Yeah, yeah.
I think- You see, you can watch 80s footage.
You can watch people on talk shows and go,
there you go, there's one.
But I don't know if- Yeah.
Eisner strikes me and I don't know,
maybe he says this in any of his books,
but he strikes me as like a big coffee guy.
Like a guy who drinks like multiple pots
of coffee a day or something.
Like he does have that energy sometimes
when you see old clips of him,
but it doesn't feel like that druggy to me.
But I don't know. No.
I don't think so.
But it feels like he has an exuberance and an energy
and it feels like it would be just like,
like how Trump drinks 12 Diet Cokes a day or something.
Like it feels like it might be something like that.
Like a legal drink that has caffeine in it.
And just a terrible unending supply of it
that's terrible for you.
And yet you maintain well into your later life.
I don't know. There's no telling
what could happen, yeah.
Well, something we could explore in the near future
is what was Eisner on?
It's a great question.
We could- Was it drugs?
Was it just natural highs?
Was it just the magic of Disney?
At least that, that we know.
All I know is whatever he was on in the early 90s,
I'll have what he's having.
That's what I say. Oh boy.
We could use some of it right now.
I'll tell you that much.
Well, there's a little taste of A,
how we deal with serious things.
And B, what we'll try to do
while things are a little wonky here.
But boy, we'll miss Jason participating in that.
And hopefully he's back and hopefully
we're all back to normal as soon as we can.
So I guess for now, you survive podcast the ride.
And yeah, you know, it's just good to know.
Door closed on shittiest episode.
We never need to revisit this again.
Yeah, we have our answer.
No need to get into the debate.
I'm gonna cause the debate by saying that, ugh.
Well don't- Oh yeah, that's true.
Keep that amongst yourselves.
I don't wanna see a thing about it.
This is the worst episode.
You just heard it, we did it.
Yeah, text your friends if you wanna talk about
bad stuff, bad episodes we've done.
Because yeah, we don't need to read that.
We do not need to be, so look.
Not right now, please.
Not right now.
Everybody's dealing with a lot.
Sincerely, really hope everybody's safe.
And if you haven't been, that you're getting
the relief and the help you need,
let us know what you need.
And even if it's just making you laugh,
we'll certainly try to be doing that.
Thanks for your patience, everybody.
Appreciate it and have a good one.