Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
Some episodes and topics we pour over a little bit and we say, oh, is this the right time
or is there a better way to do that or is there a better guest for it or you know, like
how can we position that the best and you know, and we mull them over and make sure
that they get ripe and what have you.
Some topics are a text that are sent and we go, yep, put it in and there we are.
Sometimes it's just got to go straight wordlessly from episode to topic and I'm thrilled that
that is what has happened here.
I'm Scott Gardner, Jason Sheridan's over there and I am crediting Mike Carlson with a, that's
a grand slam out of the park with what you've texted us, which is what we're talking about.
Not dummy-related.
Yes, yeah, no, those are bunts that get caught and there's an out immediately.
This one to me, I mean, as soon as I actually, it took me actually watching it and maybe
it will for the listener too, but as soon as I saw any of it, I was like, oh yeah, alright,
here we go.
Yeah, we got a weird one.
This is a weird one.
It was something that just popped up because I've talked about this before, I don't really
use Facebook other than to just be a member of various different groups on it and I don't
even know if I'm part, there was a Back to the Future group and for whatever reason,
this just popped up and was suggested to me.
This wasn't even in like, it wasn't from, I assume it was like a YouTube algorithm theme
park stuff.
Maybe it's on some level, but it was just Back to the Future fans.
It was not theme park related and they were just saying, hey, there's like a Back to the
Future ride you should be aware of and that's really what it was.
Like Back to the Future, the ride is back, whoa, slow down.
Let me also say, if you are confused by what you're looking at, if you're looking at the
title of this episode, we haven't lost our minds, we didn't let AI write a title, this
is the actual name of a ride that exists and the name of the ride is, we are back, kids
from the future.
We are back, kids from the future, written in English on the sign.
In the Back to the Future font.
It's hypnotic, I've been saying it over and over to myself like a mantra, like maybe this
is my, I've been learning about, I was like, when David Lynch died, I was like, what actually
is Transcendental Meditation and will they give you a word and that is that you focus
on that word?
I'm like, maybe this is it for me, maybe there'll be inner peace if I just keep saying, we are
back, kids from the future.
We are back, not we're back, we are back, we are back, kids from the future is the name
of a ride.
It's like a poem.
Folks it's time to return to movie land.
Hooray!
So happy about, let's, so broader context here and maybe especially for newer listeners
because here we're referring to something that is five years old.
I remain very fond of the series that we did, Podcast the Red's European Vacation.
I thought we found so much interesting oddity and places that we may never go but that are
so fascinating to learn about and the euro of it all really appealed to me and honestly
this part might be one of my favorite things we've ever talked about.
I'm still, I can't speak to the quality of the episode but in terms of things I still
think about a lot.
It is that movie land, this was, I re-listened to some of the episode just to like remember
what we said and one thing that happened is that I said everyone say out loud what you
think the name of the park is and we all said different things because again what did you
just say?
Well I said movie land.
That's for sure.
The URL is canavaworld.it Yes, because it's part of like some broader kind of like family
of things infrastructure.
Vacation place in a place called Lake Garda but I've, sometimes it's movie land studios,
I've seen it as movie land the Hollywood park but we actually did all say different things.
That's how strange their branding is.
It opened in 2002 and it's yeah it's like a general tourist area, I don't know what part
of Italy, I don't know it well enough but broad strokes here, this park is just a full
tilt ripoff of Universal Studios at every turn from the outside, from the gate, ride
by ride, the characters who appear in it, the music that you hear, there is a fully
functioning knockoff of Universal Studios and it's not one of those things like oh in
China there's this weird decaying fake magic kingdom.
It's not that, it's open successful new rides, ride through videos, you know around the clock
this place is up and running that is a 100% knockoff, it's like the asylum studios of
parks.
It's so crazy.
It's right, it's like Doc Brown interacting with Spider-Man and interacting with I don't
know like not Lucille Ball but like.
Maybe.
Maybe Charlie.
They just don't call her that.
Right.
Yeah.
It feels like Hollywood.
Red haired glam queen, get out there.
It feels like Hollywood Boulevard where it's like there's Snoopy and Captain Jack Sparrow
together like just a mix of characters.
Maybe with costumes that aren't of the best care.
Intellectual property is not really concerned at this park.
Also artificial intelligence might be building some of this website now because these jumping
kids don't look quite right.
How many fingers on the jumping kids, that's always a tell of the AI.
Are we in a Willy Wonka touring show, Glasgow situation.
The fingers appear to be right but some of them are kind of fucked up looking.
Of course they do AI art for their website, of course.
Because that's the whole thing.
It's like and I said this in the episode that it's all using the right lenses you could
take photos that make it look like Universal Studios but if it's just unadorned YouTube
video it's just obvious like the materials of this are weird and it's all jammed together
and I surprised myself.
I heard myself say that they have a lights motors action show but that's like built into
an alley that's like a dangerous amount of space for cars to be doing stunts in front
of you.
Well a big thing we honed in on was the motor, the boat, the giant boat you could all get
in.
Yes.
That takes you into what is clearly the arena of a water world ripoff show that they don't
use anymore.
And that is a Knight Rider thing that's a boat.
So there's also a lot of like mashups of IP.
Well I have some good news.
It seems I've found some new stuff before we get to we're back.
Oh good.
We are back.
The Horror House.
The haunted house.
If you remember all the creature, all the like your favorite horror icons were there
has been updated.
And now it's the Horror House presents Holmes Hotel.
That's right.
H.H. Holmes.
What?
It's an H.H. Holmes Hotel.
Did you create this from your own imagination?
Do we have some listeners?
That's what you're that's one of your guys H.H. Holmes.
That's one of my guys.
You know I was talking about that.
I believe he is he was caught in Philadelphia I believe buried in Delaware County.
Wow.
You're a local hero.
You meet H.H. Holmes in Italy?
I think the heart needs to like oh this is like his haunted this is murder hotel that
he built in Chicago.
Wow.
To be fair to this place that seems kind of good.
Yeah that does seem cool.
The thing that confused me was this show just called USA Army Stunt Show and the tagline
is I am coming to get you.
The brand name is the US Army Stunt Show.
I am coming to get you.
That's a threat.
It's a stunt show.
That's the wall up on the that's on the receiving end of that is Greenland.
Yeah.
Right.
Canada and Greenland.
Oh yeah.
Canada too.
Yeah.
I you know it's a it's nice that I like that we've done so many of these episodes and some
of them are so long ago that I forget about them and it so to be re-listening and not
knowing what was coming around the corner and to hear because they also have a rip off
Hard Rock Cafe and that I loved like it's me talking but I don't remember what's coming
and what it was was I was it was like that they have like Rolling Stones ribs and stuff
right but then it gets then it gets to still makes me laugh so much.
Jackson Sandwich oh yeah yeah yeah yeah they have Jackson Sandwich there and what was that
I don't remember I remember what was in a Jackson I should I still have my I have all
my old notes and I should try to find it actually but the thing I the thing that you know go
re-learning about movie land the Hollywood Park made me realize like oh my god it's been
five years all those European parks might have new attractions yeah yeah even the good
one like Efteling redid that whole like haunted castle thing they had oh right right did we
find this because you did you found this like flash dance show you like put that was when
we were doing a sort of grab bag of shows yeah yeah that might have been the first time
we talked about it yeah yeah wait a minute now oh my god look I'm glad I checked the note do
you also does anyone remember Dakota stick no Dakota stick is a weird like corn dog looks like
a sausage with a roll at the bottom and then a little bit of stick coming out of the top that
looks like something it's going into your your your eat through it so it's scary and but then
also my notes are showing me I have no further information about Jackson sandwich but I wait
Jackson's I don't know Jackson sandwich has like they just like hard-boiled eggs in it that's
Jackson sandwich you see an egg salad sandwich oh yeah I got some pizzas there with all the hippo
gorilla yes that's right it's all animals that don't match the what the meat is it's so crazy
but yeah ripoff hemisphere dancer it's everything this place is just meant for us it's so crazy
rock and roll restaurant the margaritaville is called margaritas now my notes have really
thrown me for a loop because they've shown me that there already was kind of a ripoff back to
the future in a ride called magma 2.0 maybe I think it's called magma 2.0 still going strong
it has it is okay okay because apparently the pre-show of that is a yes yes okay so they still
have something with Doc Brown but that's not about time travel but they do now have thank
God a more fully committed ripoff back to the future ride but a little bit of story to share
there too I think that when we did this episode five years ago what they had maybe this had
initially it was something called Terminator 5d yeah which then became a weird melded game
attraction where a bunch of robots pop up and you blast them with lasers right and then it became
a Transformers ripoff called Android the final 3d battle and that from what I could tell has all the
same stuff that like it has the like part where you get whipped through the office building that
happens but it but it was also still kind of a Terminator ripoff because Terminator type robots
would pop up out of the ground and there were real flames in the room which is kind of cool but I
also don't really trust this place with flames no that's very alarming there's still some Terminator
stuff on the walls in the main show area too yes on the way out yeah there was a low when I was
watching it I was like oh look it's the Institute of Future Technology logo and then I thought no
that's cyberdine yeah that is yeah just kept it up this place rules sorry I I we don't have time
to get into the possibly unlicensed asterix and obelisk or the Fred Flintstone in the wrong
colors what but I have to say the ice cream place called ice stone creamery I ran into that late
it was late last night of the night before and I was laughing like a maniac to myself that Fred
is this horrible he's so huge he's either a messed up Fred or a messed up Barney either of them are
messed up he looks like you took a picture of Fred Flintstone yeah clone like stamped the or water
there bucketed the color wrong and then stretch it from a hundred percent to five hundred percent
with super stretch Fred Flintstone I yeah imagine a miniature golf obstacle and then make it much
bigger and put it on someone so anyways there is so they had this space that had it was it was kind
of a Terminator 2 3d ripoff and kind of a Transformers ripoff but also there was a chappy on the top and
then I was the ride was really hard to parse because it's all in Italian and that parts not
subtitled but I was like did they have Mike's favorite thing the moment of intimacy does it
have the I'm proud of you right from its prime moment and it does there is a part where a robot
at the end means down and talks to you and the thing that we say at the end of the club 3 your
bravery saved the planet but here a robot you don't know leans down and says good work guys
thanks to you the core is safe humans will have a future after all okay do you get anything from
that that a moment if it doesn't have the warmth of Peter Cullen I don't know but it's I like it I
like it's there yeah yeah at least they were if they're gonna do a beat-by-beat ripoff transformers
yeah that's an important part I'm impressed that they did it um but that was I guess I guess the
time for Android the final 3d battle had passed and they needed to step into the future with a
whole new concept we are back kids from the future yeah and I don't have myself but my big
question is can someone tell me what the hell is going on oh yes I think we will try I've never
been more confused with something that is so much exposition this might be I think we've always
reveled in sheer volumes of exposition and we were so delighted in a very genuine way I think our
feelings about the avatar flight of passage pre-show and the great David Danipour are very
clear like big info dumps can be extremely fun this might be the biggest one ever yeah it's much
longer than I think I understand it but it's a lot it's a lot and here's what I'm I hate to just
come in and say this is the order we must do it in but I feel that we should proceed in ride
reveal order and here's why because what this ride does is make some great leaps forward in terms of
the back to the future mythology yeah yeah he makes some assertions about what is now in the
world of these films bigger than now I don't keep up I don't know what the comic books are that Bob
Gale is doing I'm not familiar with the video games there might be like you know astounding
expansions of the world that would blow my mind but to me you know rides count the most right and
what this ride what movie land in Italy has declared is now part of the back to the future
franchise I'm blown away by and I give them a lot of credit yeah they took a big swing or many big
swings here and I applaud it yeah because we do like new mythology coming from a ride we've
always said that I think yes yeah it's the only ones I know I don't know you look I you guys like
comics to me it just doesn't get there's something about like the the visibility of the ride that
like because it's kind of where it's gonna like live in the public's hearts the most so if you say
guess what this now I think it counts more than anything yes and also yes you know depending on
choose your own choose your own mythology for a lot of this stuff now and when rides mean a lot
to you so you know that's why that's this is now canon in your back to the future is yeah and it's
and back to the future more than a lot you know it's a franchise with a hard cap on it this is not
how they do things anymore it's becoming a real relic the fact that it actually ended when the
creators of the franchise thought it should be ended and while that was great for everyone and
everything and we haven't had some fucking nightmare new CGI back to the future it does
yeah yes we are waiting on two people and that will be that but or if he's like if he's bummed
enough about how here went over maybe there's yeah start changing I think there's like certain
things a couple other movies you would sequel before yeah there's that's good news I think I
hope so Marwin too maybe welcome back to Marwin Pinocchio too but I was saying it does you know
unlike so many things that have added all of this like back to the future does end in 1990 and it
ends with Doc and Clara and but not anymore not anymore it's 2025 and everything has changed I
believe it ends with Doc and Clara and Jules and Vern and Einstein the dog doesn't it that's true
where we literally end is that way I mean look Marty and Jennifer are gonna go do what they're
gonna do but they're probably not gonna time travel anymore it depends on how much you want
to count the animated series as anything but you're right who's in the time vehicle is Doc
and Clara and Einstein and it's Jules and Vern very interesting and Jules and Vern have always
I guess been the key to is there more to the story yeah there was a cartoon that's what you
said yes cartoon that yep they are now like precocious little kids who sound like Tommy
Pickles and like all the kid voices all the time yeah and I don't really care for that I think
that's an ugly looking show looking show yeah don't I've never engaged with despite it having
extra Doc Brown shot by Peyton Reed it's still even that it's not really of interest did you
watch it as a kid no oh really I might have I think my back to the future fandom came later
like I was like 10 show was not I watched it I don't have any memory really of it but I also
think I really liked back to the future when I was a little older yeah yeah yeah that's where it
really came together for me but I guess like with the animated series is kind of like I had the
Burger King or McDonald's toys yeah I had Marty right those were cool those were cool yeah I you
know I joked I think I understand what's happening in this ride there was just so much of it by the
end oh yeah it's just like an assault it's but a very slow paced assault I know they aren't they
are not rushing through no that's for sure and there are some long shots it's five minutes of
content with one shot there are some moments like when you are shooting something in front of the
camera behind the camera you often will you know keep going what you're doing or like you paw like
something for the editors to cut around you know sure and this they left it all on the screen straight
yeah yeah but so you know if the key to expanding back to the future has been Jules and Vern maybe
this is why the door has been closed because this is a key that no one wants to use Jules and Vern
are not enticing to anyone I don't think maybe the animated show kind of got the job done but I for
one don't want to know anything more about Jules and Vern the children being raised in the Old West
in their starchy coats and I guess mainly I'm saying this because the children who were cast
in the film are the casting of those kids was the worst decision in the entire trilogy this is it is
a fumble right at the lot like it is it's a fumble at the one yard line they're almost out
perfect and then what the nice feelings that you're supposed to have at the end of three
wonderful inventive movies are it's all a little bit hurt by that like two of the weirdest little
froggiest little kids ever come out and one of them points at his wiener during the lesson of
the entire trilogy this weird we all know about this right yeah yeah this kid if you watch it bad
like it's but you know Doc bends down and the shots about him but the kid looks into camera and
points at his pants and it's the and he looks like he looks like a psycho he looks like he's
gonna go Chucky he's gonna leap up and start biting Christopher Lloyd's neck this isn't the
scariest shit ever so maybe there's not been a strong desire to like do the continuing adventures
of Jules and Vern yeah until now because we enter not the Institute of Future Technology but a new
related place Dr. Brown and Sons Enterprises and you immediately go okay well son like we are back
kids from the future of course it is it is Jules and Vern and then so you're going through the
hallway you see posters of an off-brand Doc Brown another episode that we did and then you're you're
going it's you know much like the ride you're trying to find like a lab you know to go get
more information interesting that this hallway kind of resembles an Instagram photo zone yes yes
it absolutely does oh it's got a selfie area with like a fake like green wall you have to have again
like I always say but the milkshake like a milkshake with rice Krispy Kreme on top that's gonna break
the internet if whoa how'd you get a picture in front of a neon sign and grass on a wall
grass on the ground not on a wall yeah Scott you forget the six years ago world of 2019 was a more
simple optimistic place you know experimenting we use the filters more we hadn't pivoted to video
you see um but yeah isn't it it's so cheapo it's so it's exactly what I'm illustrating about like
it's like technically it kind of has some of the feel of the back to the future ride but also it
kind of feels like you're like like walking through a doctor's office yeah it definitely yes it looks
like you're like a trendy like West Hollywood coffee shop or something that's what you're the
future technology yeah you're going to a bathroom you had to borrow a key to go to the bathroom in
a weird like where there's like yeah there's a boutique over here an expensive coffee place
over here and you got to get close to people's offices right to use the bathroom yeah I don't
that's what this queue feels like baffling choice really weird really weird there's like kind of
weird plants stuck on the other side of the hallway that like maybe you could like oh it's
an experiment or it's giving fresh oxygen oxygen or something but this clearly like the astroturf
wall is an instagram thing why would the why would Jules and Vern need that I don't know anyway
then you meet so then sure enough they introduce themselves I'm Dr. Jules Dr. Jules Brown
Vern Brown it hurts my brain to put brown after them yeah um and they so again immediately
important mythology they are they've followed in their father's footsteps they've gone into business
with it they too are time travel scientists and they still wear starchy coats I guess their
base of operations stayed in the old west I guess so but they can talk to us now using video and
they're what in their late 20s early 30s ish maybe I don't know for sure but they look like
they're in that zone yeah I think so yeah so they are grown so we are yes the kids from the future
have grown they are so that's interesting right away to see Jules and Vern at uh kind of Marty's
age or well I'm not quite I guess I don't know whatever uh but so they uh talk about their
experiments and stuff you kind of catch that one's like more straight-laced and one is kooky
yeah so they've divided that way they're not um going too hard either way on the delivery
of their dialogue it's accurate I'd say yeah I you're kind of you're sussing out those straight
laced and kooky based on one is glasses and one has a kind of a head cap thing I don't know how
to describe it accurate yes yes um this is all in Italian yeah and that kind of makes me I'm
actually like tracking I know that it's because it's a park in Italy but I'm also like you know
what maybe this is kind of cool like doc if you're time traveling parents like doc and Clara you can
raise your children anywhere and in any time so I choose to think that these boys were raised in
renaissance Italy oh interesting that's what I'm going with them on that and I think that is what
doc and Clara would do right uh you know wouldn't doc go try to get a hold of
DaVinci or something right yeah go try to be his friend freak DaVinci out yeah yeah
well he'd be quite cool he knows he doesn't want to cause a space-time continuum disturbance
so yeah that's what I think I think Leonardo DaVinci was like a babysitter for Jules and
Byrne and that helped that's smart yeah that's good yeah yeah could you imagine if like a
mid-century scientist like an archaeologist met like Archimedes or something or
you know they had the right kind of dial to go meet him yeah this would be everybody would
lose their minds probably not saying the right philosopher or mathematician we just don't know
what you're talking about yeah wait are you referencing I was referencing dial of Indiana
Jones oh there's your problem I never watched that fucking movie I watched it but I forgot
they eventually end up back in time spoiler alert oh oh yeah that is this wait yeah people
told I don't know I never saw it that sounds bad um so uh I was almost I was almost going like
is this is this like Peabody and Sherman what's he talking about um well yes I've just proven I
never saw that film I only I watched it a few months ago I finally finally uh caved and watched
it too and I was like I have been looking at this de-aged Harrison for yeah oh they get so
cocky with it it does work it definitely works and then you're 40 minutes in and you're like
doesn't work that well there's a reason why TV shows only do this for a scene at a time
they got so cocky about it and then they flash a flashlight on it in the dark and it's just like
the flashlights on and you're like why are you showing me the detail on this yeah don't you're
you're pushing your luck I know um so they explain why the lab is open to us the theme park
goers because they are opening a new era of tourism uh you where you can be part of the
greatest historical events and I'm parsing all of this via Italian video with um English subtitles
uh they have a new thing it's not a passenger DeLorean it's the time shuttle they invented the
time shuttle and it's interesting when you get in to the the the final room and see that the
time shuttle is a a bunch of fucking chairs it's the chairs in a big room it's just a very
it's very innovative all right the shuttle could be also a room the shuttle could be all room
yeah why not honestly it kind of reminded me of the massive factor ride you did not make it on
in great America oh that's right yeah that was big well I did get into the room the ride was
shut down once in the room okay yeah it was one of those where yeah you're you just have to go
with them that like it's 500 little vehicles and there's an actor yes they're doing a little bit
of sneaky business we do get we do get a stage actor who interacts with the film uh so they say
that we've invented the time shuttle and we will make our father's dream come true great scott
which is what the subtitles say but what they actually say out loud is like grande jove
they had to translate great scott
so then I don't want to just I don't want to do a recitation but then they say just a they say a
bunch of shit you don't need they talk for so long they're talking in front of a robotic arm
yeah they start going the lab set up some extras in there yeah they talk to some scientists and
then they pause for a while but there are like yeah they like like take a breath they like
collect themselves remember their lines they like keep patting the like good job
and then it freezes and it cuts to another shot just watching what they're doing keep it up
no notes they it's all nonsense too like we're solving the mathematical equation which allows
to split the impulses in the quantum tubes oh wow jules and verne you've really made something
of yourselves um then one some of this is just somebody didn't have good eyes on these translations
because what does this mean somebody comes in with a little bit of panic doctor electrolyte
is already reacting to electric shocks under one gigawatt electrolyte is that's not capitalized
that's not a person or a robot or anything doctor electrolyte is electing reacting to electric
shocks this does feel like ai wrote it ai probably did the translation we know from jason's proof
that they're in the ai business right yeah i it's just there's a lot of numbers being thrown around
and i am like kind of like i am forgetting the back to the few all i can remember is 88 miles
per hour but they're talking about the gigawatts and they're like oh we're not using uh hydrogen
and lightning like on the train that my father described we are using plutonium when we went
back to it and i'm like well that's one of my favorite they went back that's one of my favorite
things is that to be stolen from terrorists the first by the libyans it's plutonium and it's
dangerous and it's you know very dangerous material and then the upgrade of course is doc
so we can just do this out of uh garbage garbage but that wasn't enough for the show oh my god
it's so great and there's a big thing in this they make a big meal out of we're going back to
the bad stuff the plutonium this is trump era stuff this back to cool all that shit we did
back to square doing like we did it back scenes out they're building up hollywood they're making
epic again and it's going to be sylvester salone and mil gibson just two dying men two visibly
melting men and it's like they're going to make the movie industry huge again
they ran planet hollywood now they're running real hollywood all right yeah they're no we're
saying merry christmas again and we're using plutonium again it's yeah no we all right yeah
we can power things with trash but well they had a reason it was like hydrogen wasn't stable and
it causes explosions so we decided to bring back plutonium charge they want plutonium you want
plutonium they want nuclear reactions it's going to be better than just like your newspaper that's
so good such a funny choice to do that then why do they need to tell us this no it should make
another thing up doc didn't tell us any of this for he told us biff is here but he like i don't
need to know one bit of this to go get jostled around by the no why yeah why why or just like
make up a new element they need to get yeah we need a new thing and that's modern rare sure
yeah plutonium they also it is from the movie though i suppose and they i guess i yeah they
may as well just have used like we have an odd tanium wait a minute yeah yeah well that seems
like what they would do i mean there there's there is a part of this where i was watching
with erin and it cuts to a bunch of rocks and stuff and she said oh so now we're on pandora
so it's already it's i think it is almost in the avatar world anyway yeah uh but so yeah this is
maybe the best mishmash part because they also they they explained something i'm forgetting
another bit of justification they say our father designed a nuclear fusion system using garbage
that's news to me i thought mr fusion was something from the future that he oh that he took
yeah i didn't think because that's too like nice of a logo how do you like design that and stuff
right yeah i thought mr fusion is something that the world uses and he brought it back to us
i don't think yeah you're probably right i don't think doc invented mr fusion but the ride knows
better than i do the ride is the ride's real and i'm not because he didn't get like rich from doing
mr fusion or like there was never any oh my god yeah he'd be loaded right you invented a clean
burning you figured out how to make trash run a car right and why wouldn't he live in the future
then to reap the rewards made a bunch of money converting trash into gas why the fuck is he
helping marty mcfly jr not have to go to a party or whatever the fuck he comes back yeah it is a
very utopian idea that like in this set on a larger sense of like look the pizza
pizza you just they're real small and then they get real big you know it's like oh isn't the future
gonna be great although hill valley 2015 is kind of like shitty looking it's good yeah yeah but
it's a little busted just like 1985 and 1950 well it's kind of accurate to our future right yeah it's
the way like some of it's nice like the way if you go to tokyo you're like wow the future is
incredible and then you go almost anywhere else and you're like wow the future stinks
but so uh um something else is going on there oh that's oh sorry i was starting to say our father
designed that but unfortunately it turned out to be inefficient with time travels longer than 100
years okay even though in the ride we go to the the pat we go to the dinosaurs yeah but i don't
think the ride exists i think in this timeline biff didn't steal the eight passenger delorean
oh you think they're cutting that out from the actual universal ride yeah i think so i think this
is almost maybe entirely because also something else that is not mentioned is marty mcfly right
doesn't matter yeah that is confusing because you would think you would have at least nodded to it
in a weird let me say this i saw two comments two people try to claim that this was licensed
how how that's what i think what in the like the because the i mean let's here's one big thing is
that they use the font they use the music they use the music yeah throughout but why would it
why would universal i don't know why they just cut like is this just some weird little way to
launder money or i well that's what i was trying to figure out i was like is there some weird thing
where it's overseas and they sort of quietly take some money because because everybody's like well
why isn't why haven't this been shut down why isn't this everything in the park that is the
question yeah so i want because like marty isn't very active you don't see marty on the original
ride very like you don't hear references to him or anything like clips um but i was like i wonder
if there is some weird thing with this it still doesn't make any sense that it would be this
shitty yeah but still i would just it all i'll say is it left like a little question in my head
of like yeah that is weird that they're allowed to keep doing it do they just like look the other way
or i don't know it doesn't matter enough to them and they figure well it's not our branding it's
not a universal part so whatever but they also have i mean aren't they building in where are they
building there one uh england uh universal yeah right that seems to just get approved they're not
gonna want to i was gonna say it's like a different territory so who cares but if they're
gonna have a park in england they don't want we are back kids from the future you would think it
would be easy to stop we are back kids from the future if you were universal that it would be
pretty quick to get a lawyer on the phone and go you have to shut down we are back wait keep going
so you have to shut down we are back kids from the future immediately there's a problem i know
you're confused when i could it just be yeah what if it is like they pay a small licensing fee and
it's like how actors used to go do commercials in japan because they would uh make a bunch of
money and then never seeing them i wonder but it's still it's still not enough like could there be
limits could there be money exchanged and limits be placed some but some of it in the park seems
completely like devoid of any iconography or anything related other than just the concept of
big robots and then this has the font it's got the delorean it's got music it does say his name
what if late garter is some kind of dark zone that is copyright free maybe what if it's like
you know in the way like there's the laws don't apply in this part of the ocean yeah it's like
maybe there's so it is somehow a copyright dark spot i'm curious that's why this park was built
there well it's not this land of late garter it's not like italy has ever been associated with
craft or organized crime or nothing right that's what's happening like oh like oh your lawyers
are coming where all our lawyers are paying you a visit as well and then a bunch of mafia dudes
show up at the universal gates and just kind of like put their fist in their hands pow pow
and then they like oh okay whatever you say or a bunch of just a bunch of tommy guns we've got
some lawyers don't you dare try to shut down we are back kids from the future be real shameless
something happened to your globe here just because you got a problem with we are back
kids from the future like you sleep with the fishes for shutting down we are back kids from
the future you know you think we're scared of universal lawyers our lawyers are all our cousins
if you follow my drift a lot of sylvios if you follow my drift you fuck with we are back kids
from the future maybe you won't be back kids from the past so i don't know i just i was like
interesting if somebody out there can tell us i somebody knows i wonder if somebody out there
somebody obviously has to know but in our audience i mean well i also think that here's
i think somebody i know we have people who work in the people who listen to work in the universal
organization sanity if you know a legal if you know someone in the legal department ask them
ask if they know because what i don't want to like i want to i'm torn here i i in a way want to
protect movie land yes i do i love that it's this wonderful world of ripoffs that exists
but wouldn't i'd feel a little bit proud if the history of it became this park operated until
podcast the ride told someone about it and then it was sued into the ground i mean but then i'd
also kind of feel like uh when bart gets crusty in trouble with the rs yeah like i don't i don't
want to get congratulated for that and then go oh my god now i can't have a dakota stick anymore
but we don't see we don't see like the complete disney rip off like this brazenly right now
and universal and comcast are a big company they have to know yeah they have somebody has to know
they have to have known that there was doc brown on their old ride i think but maybe nobody told
maybe just somehow it's just like don't everybody forgot maybe it's just like yeah
it would cost more to go after them free marketing what are you gonna do
maybe anyway you know what all it's gonna do is remind people that there's a better park with
the same stuff that's better i do hope they're still doing that streetmasphere show bit uh or
little act based on the uh the artist the academy award winning yeah they just had the poster paint
at the side of the wall and they were just like doing the charleston and the jitterbug in front
of it it looks like movie land also the only place on earth where anyone remembers the artist
is that movie that that's french isn't it thanks yeah yeah okay uh oh yeah um uh another interesting
thing is that here's why plutonium is because day time shuttle doesn't do 1.21 gigawatts time
shuttle does 3.21 oh which that when i heard that that now it's 3.21 gigawatts that felt to me like
an indominus rex type i'm like if they did the jurassic world of back to the future that would
be one of the things they'd say is like actually for the fans pretty cool because now we're doing
3.21 gigawatts and half the fans would go oh that's so fucking cool dude whoa like actually
this thing might be pretty good i there is a bit of that in the first chris pratt movie
where the owner goes like i don't care how big and deadly it is the shareholders and the guests
demand new attractions and then his helicopter gets fucked up yeah yeah uh um i but that seems
doesn't that seem like the kind of like weak ass fan service that we'd expect they'd expect us all
the orgasm over yeah they'd reveal that like you'd be at comic con and they would say 3.21
on the screen right you're supposed to go yeah it would work but yeah that would happen yeah
would it work on you maybe yeah yeah it was if i was in the room i've said this before
if you're ever in those rooms you they'll get you to pop for almost anything you'll get so excited
at the littlest reveal i think you already pop for almost anything me
me depends it depends i i did see admittedly i watched the post credit sequence from captain
america brave new world and i was just sitting there going who the fuck is he talking to you
didn't know who is this man you know i can tell you i i think i put it together by some other
leaks online oh well he's a bad guy in the movie yeah it's not a big jules brown it's jules brown
dr jules brown dr jules brown doc brown's son is now the godfather of science jules are we still in
the first pre-show room not the second i think but yeah okay i got i know we got it we say we
keep this one short and look at us now uh so uh they they tell you that you know you could with
this you could do all kinds of things you could go see the signing of the declaration of independence
they spell like that yeah like uh that's the ai uh yeah uh um the yeah the you could be front row
and the eiffel tower is uh opened um you you will see when your favorite team will win the super bowl
or the football world cup the football the football world cup but the party you're not
supposed to do that you guys know more than anything right you're not supposed to do that
um and then uh they say we'll bring you to february 13th 1955 where the first oil wells
were built what why that doesn't come back no it doesn't why did they take us to the first oil
i don't know wait a minute there were oil wells before 1955 what are you talking about they built
in hill valley was that like a sea plot is it a poor translation of something else i don't know
and they didn't they didn't translate the date right the first oil wells in 1955 what's wrong
with this ride i don't know ride is broken um but then you're also going to go to the london expo
hold on to that that sounds like nothing but hold on to it london expo uh then they then things
start glitching and you gotta go and you don't you don't really know why then you go to another
room and it's them again and now they're in front of the time train they're in front of the train
that we saw them on when they were creepy little dick tugging kids and then uh they're talking for
a second and then they say something alarming which is that the pressure flow meter which is
all one word with no spaces is on red the pressure flow meter is on red and then it cuts out and
they're gone and then who appears on screen oh my god but a girl this popped me a young look i don't
like to say this stuff it popped me too a new a younger girl appears who we have never seen
before she looks a little bit kooky almost like the 2015 back to the future 2 style she's got like
a weird little hair uh she's got the vest and a vest she's got marty's marty's vest that's right
that actually did i do recognize i was like she's dressed like marty yes it's like well she's kind
of like marty jr because it's like like future neon and like like weird up ponytail and and she
says am i in am i in but zack are you there zack these who are these funky kids and they explain
that they are jesse brown and he is my cousin zack brown zack brown the zack brown i'm zack
the unused name zack brown uh and these are jules and verne brown's children we were wrong we are
back kids from the future jules and verne weren't the kids not the kids from the future they aren't
the kids there's still more kids from the future their kids are from the future their kids are no
no no uh well yes we are back from the future but it's our kids our kids are from the future
okay we are back doc faints now here's how i interpret this all you walk down a hallway
between the first pre-show room the second pre-show room stuff starts to act up i believe
there's neon lights on the ceiling between the two rooms and you hear a lot of like
like electrical sputtering yeah then you walk into a room what also has a delorean crash through a
wall oh right yes there was that yes that is not mentioned for a while is that they take that to
get to us okay so we have to watch three more minutes with jules and verne and then they're
back to us and i think they came in that delorean that is not mentioned for a while you might be
right that's just you figured it out oh wait the next line i'm looking at is we drove here in our
delorean and today brown enterprise's first time travel experiment should take place that's exactly
what happened they came here now is the day we have to drive we have to whatever it takes if it
takes driving into the building that's what we have to do another thing they say is we know it's hard
to believe but we come from 2055 that's when they are from jewel so that and they're cousins so
because it's separate they aren't so they aren't brother and sister one is jules right kid and one
is verne and the other is verne's kid yeah so cousins kids from the future we are back
and they drew they came they came here because the first experiment that's open to the public
with the time shuttle um then they proceed to tell you the most shit you've ever heard in your life
this goes on and on and on and on and i'm interested in all of it but i think there must
have been a way that it didn't have to be so much what are they doing are they covering that line
that ride doesn't seem that long no i have to do all this they have like they have diagrams they're
drawing on a whiteboard they have picked like documents like there's so much info they show
you a picture of the flux capacitor let me tell you i know i know that i don't know what you are
you're zach and jesse brown this whiteboard does not pay off uh no not really not really and
here's the other thing about it it is this is also a nod to the films because it shows you the
concept of here's a straight line and this is a timeline then this there's this juncture in time
where things skew into an alternate timeline and another one is created this is something
that i love when doc brown illustrates this in the future too so they do that again to show you
here's where we're from but they put too many dates on it it has more than docs in the movie
and you don't need all of them they you kind of understand what's happening from some of the
first things they say except not actually though there's a lot this is this becomes a soap opera
at this point yeah this be you know what they could have said i could have saved a lot of money
you cut the first pre-show you start with these two they explain what's going on it's half as long
you had to do as few there's a kurt vonnegut quote he said people ask him how do you start a book
he's like oh that's easy you write 15 pages and you throw the first 10 in the garbage there's
your start of the book those five so yeah he should have been consulting on we are back if
he was still alive and could have fixed all these problems quick we have to go back and get kurt
vonnegut to fix the copy of we are back kids from the future he was at look he shows up and back
to school around this time you know he himself is in back to school he says like uh rodney dangerfield
had a uh a test on kurt vonnegut and he's like i got a tutor and it's like and it's actually kurt
vonnegut maybe i'm did they not he was around they call him that i think i'm so uncultured i don't
know about that kurt vonnegut was in it um so uh all right what do they tell i'm i'm going to try
to only say what's important but i might i just started writing down every line so forgive me i'm
gonna go as fast as i can because i don't just to make can you just read all the lines as fast as
you could possibly do it right now well that's not true to the spirit but okay yeah they take their
time uh without correct data sent to the electric circuit which receives in turn impulses given by
the vehicle speed that 88 miles per hour combined with 1.21 gigawatts of electricity what in physics
is known as the breakdown of the time symmetry which would allow the opening of space time
which can't happen in the mechanism long story now that was probably confusing right but then
what it is is that uh uh zach is very mealy-mouthed long-winded jesse comes in and cuts through the
clutter so he says all that garbage she comes in and says long story short our parents can make
it work but we do great now i got it we have data and technology to solve bugs in the system
but it's still a big problem then they get a chart out they now they do the timeline today is the
date of the first listeners you're just gonna have to make a chart with us today is the date
of the first tourist trip through time so that's this that's 2025 uh on this day our parents did
a patrol around in the location we are going to visit using grandpa emmett's train zach and i
live here and then went to a year i don't think we didn't know where you live we didn't understand
what had happened to our fathers they had simply disappeared so when the red pressure flow meter
thing the last we saw jewels and verne that's today that's 2025 and then they disappeared
nobody knows what happens they had to come here and they found zach and jesse brown found a letter
left by their grandfather doc brown who died when we weren't born yet thanks to this letter we
discovered the position of an old garage where we found the remains of an old delorean and the
assembles the instructions to reassemble it meanwhile we picked up a signal from the past
in our laboratory the message is a distorted sos we had to recode dr jewels and dr verne are stuck
to ed in the year 1855 they reached that like don't you live there already what's the fucking
problem let them live there that's where they grew up who cares oh here's why because they
reached that date coming from today they they damaged the plutonium tank hitting a group of
rocks when they were a group this is family of rocks here's what happened okay let me cut
through the clutter i think okay i said earlier i'm sorry i was wrong earlier i referred to
they jewels and verne mentioned something called the london expo i think i was wrong that's different
than something else which is the science world congress the science world congress takes place
in the year 2030 and that is where on december 8th 2030 jewels and verne the brothers meet their
wives yes zach and jesse's mothers mothers and that's how zach and jesse come along
in 2030 yes different than the london expo london expo is nothing it didn't need to be said
science world congress is where jewels and verne meet separate eligible lady scientists to marry
and have children with and this happens in 2030 so if they're stuck in the past in 1855
they can't go forward and make zach and jesse their children so this is now you know what i
just realized why this is throwing me off is because zach rito and jess mckenna are oh and
i started getting weird at the same time because they're both from saved by the bell oh yeah dude
yeah yeah that too i was like why is this it was i know it was bugging me out in the same way it was
for two different reasons okay i think partly what's happening here i remember reading once
about like the way they translate french comic books or japanese manga sometimes is that there
is a translator who will write the raw translation of like here's what the story is here's the
dialogue and then there's someone who goes through and fine tunes it and changes all the the
characters into english language things about different context and that joke makes no sense
in this language so it's an equivalent yeah yeah yeah i think maybe what happened here is they
didn't do that step where someone fine tunes the translation for the subtitles that uh uh behind
the scenes story about my uh ongoing product tiny puppets i used to do it with google translate
yeah and then people would say i speak portuguese and this is fucking horseshit and which is fine
because whatever it's supposed to be a bad ripoff thing but then i started hiring translators to do
it and it got i'd say five percent better then the problem just became my pronunciation which
is and will always be dog shit uh my apologies uh so i've experienced this and i do the i think
we're in a google translate world or an ai but separate issue here now we're doing the we i won't
be born plot of back to the future one right using kids from the future we have been we here meet
zach and jesse make them be born because other characters you don't really know meet at science
world congress they have to go there you don't get to go there you have to go where they are
to find them so that they can still fuck our moms to make us it's pretty genius i'm gonna say as a
back this is like a real stab at what's back to the future four right it's about no it's it's about
your moms who we also don't see back the future four is about hooking up
our moms i'm just glad i mean look well you know hey the first little i think little verne was
horny to begin with well yeah i like skipping over jewels and verne as the real like stars of the
movie they're fake yeah they're fake out yeah you know i think i like that too because as i said i
don't want to hear more about jewels and verne they're from the past they stuck they're they're
creepy little kids i'm glad they do what their dad does but that's not different that's it's all
boring until some funky teens show up named jesse and zach and they throw the whole thing they they
bring a fresh hip energy that the franchise needs i got i was so excited when their kids showed up
i was like oh this is good now we're cooking that's like i remember yes i was like all right and
this if you i don't want to see they can make whoever they want jewels and verne but if this
is the path do they need to buy the rights to this yes and then this becomes like sydney sweeney
uh i don't know i don't i don't got a zach picked out i mean glenn powell these kids look younger
than sydney sweeney though these are you gotta get some tiktok stars yes yes i don't know i don't
know the young stars in there you might not even know the possible eligible i think the saturation
i feel like i have seen some funny like decent short sketches on instagram and tiktok i don't
remember any of the accounts but i'm like oh it might be getting saturated so much you start to
get some interesting weirdos ah like you end up you end up where you started where you essentially
have made like second city ucbio and people just figured out stuff on their own and they end up
like moldable anyway oh that's okay that's good all right well let's find the hottest tiktok stars
to play the plum rolls yeah of zach and jesse uh i mean i've i think i'm down i think we found her
four yeah as long as she's got a funky ponytail this is great sure um let's get bob gale on the
phone does he know about does bob gale know yeah that's a good question does he know i would
really love to know if he knows he's i mean look is he gettable yeah i think should we get him i
think he might know because he has like a google like right anything auto send about right movie
he's got to have a cease like a cease and desist ready to go um yeah you'd think yeah yeah because
he'd be mad if it wasn't money in his pocket but then isn't it like just to expand like do you think
uh like do you end up doing the same stuff like are jules and verne awkward with women is it the way
that like george has trouble connecting do you have to then go to 2030 and create the florence
nightingale effect to make the mod did like did that also happen like did the did jules and verne
get hurt which made two women say we'll take care of you and that's why they fell in love
right you're honing in on that but remember it is a thing that young boys do when they're nervous
like mike's karaoke holding his crotch oh yes point to your but is it point do they get point
to their penis when they're nervous or they put their hand over it i mean i when i was yeah i was
just full on put my hand in my pants i would yeah i did a lot of that too yeah yeah but i'm saying
pointing it seems different actually it seems more aggressive no it's weirder like right here
right here baby like a nerd like a nasty kid like a yeah it's like a nasty kid behavior
behavior baby yeah you're saying are you going to see actually the because because in the original
back the future it's like you know george that has to that moment where he punches biff has to
happen there's no shot you'll ever like george because he's such a loser i think you have to do
this but with two characters now who were both on both have women that they're trying to hook up
with so wait so zach and jesse have to separately be marty one has to go into one car and try to
right hand like get handy with their own mom and then they're not the right yeah but no but if but
if jesse's if jesse brown's mom is bi then it's fine then you can do it i don't know the math on
wait math on that i don't know the social worries of 2030 jason do you have a good pitch because i
have a good pitch i think i have a solve here i don't have a good pitch okay i mean i'm confused
myself too but i think you see what i'm saying though i know you're saying jesse brown has to
be marty so that means she has to try to fake get handsy with her own mother yeah but she's like
14 but marty was marty was yeah but they were the same age yes oh well yeah wait oh wait how well
how old were the moms at the science world congress that's a good question i guess we
haven't established that they might have been they might have been 17 i guess that's possible
so it's okay if jesse brown's mom is bi and so i see we're gonna need a whiteboard to figure the
math on this out let's find one this is we need to figure it out so then so she's pretending to be a
butch femme but then we get a femme man and uh is this allowed should we be doing this on this
chalkboard uh i was gonna pitch she just builds a robot i'm gonna a handsy robot oh yes she's
probably an inventor type this is what kids from the future bring to the table i'm so uncomfortable
for marty to have to make moves on his own mother so instead you send a robot to do a rapist's work
that's correct so that i think solves all the problems and then you get a fun robot in there
and the robot she'd have to program an evil robot but still well but she'd have to program
if the robot hits someone she'd have to program the robot like don't kill them so that'd be a fun
scene in the thing where like the robot like punches through the wall it's like oh tomb was
too strong oh yeah yeah no it's just got to like jostle a little bit right so you can't yeah yeah
yeah you can't smash the entire car sorry megan you're just too strong for this job
no yeah megan level strength would not work no 3.21 gigawatts is too much to power the
the assault bot yeah yeah so i mean i guess it doesn't have to be an assault it could be also
a different thing they could figure i'm just going by what i know i know you're trying to go one to
one from the perspective because the movie is all about mirroring which is also why i believe
that all of this needs to happen before the big science world congress conclusion enchantment
under the sea dance every year side the science world congress ends in a big dance where all the
scientists have to do couples slow dances i and if you're left alone well sorry you gotta go back
to your country or time after a three hour presentation on deep sea fish well in 2025
why did that anglerfish come up to the surface they're still asking uh uh it's an interesting
congress besides all of this yeah have i brought this up before there's a youtube channel i watch
sometimes that's that i'll talk about like movies that were never made like back man five or like
the stuff superman lives or whatever the cover smith version of it but there's a bat back to
the future 2 the original version of back to the future 2 have you seen any of this or i've never
heard any of this um is this where it was the 60s was the 60s and then marty was gonna like his
his conception was the thing in this the original version oh no yes so he had to make them like okay
they are together and in love but now they have to have sex at the right moment because it wouldn't
be marty if it doesn't happen at that right moment they have to have unprotected sex at just this
moment so it's marty not craig yes exactly like just another god like right would be a different
look a little different or whatever yeah yes but it was in the 60s but it's unlike the original
version of back to the future was completely the mapped they like their original their first
thought was just like well let's do the exact same thing but now instead of getting together
it was their conception so the absence of george and chrispon actually made them have to get
creative which maybe results in the skewing as you know an alternate timeline where it's the
big confusing movie that i love today yes that's what it sounded like that sounds like dog shit
they didn't want to make it they they put the thing at the end of the first one is like a joke
and then they got threatened that somebody else would make it or something so i guess we got to
make it oh just to like land grab so we gotta do something so let's just do woodstock so it's
gonna be that like that uh uh what george and lorraine they get like they like as we all know
they got really randy during uh you know country joe's performance at woodstock uh-huh and they
went and fucked in the mud george how marty was born they already have two children so
them two parents uh already have to go to woodstock i don't know if i'm making up woodstock but i think
there was something like that i think it was something i think it was that lorraine is like
a revolutionary or some shit yeah yeah it's something like that george really wanted to
watch so they couldn't do it then but then you get like back to the future this is like sleazy
back to the future one where they were going to be smoking weed and selling illegal videotapes or
whatever what's that in the first what are you talking there was an early script to back to the
future where they were gonna be they were like marty and doc were dirtbag like they were smoking
they were copying movies of vhs's and reselling them whoa i don't know that i don't think this
ever got very far they were doing a be kind rewind i know there were different like yeah
incarnations of like what their relationship was yeah like it was but i actually don't i don't know
what strap this is i just heard like oh there's a sleazier idea for this that's really weird like
closer to like more in the bill and ted uh uh wow geez well we're learning a lot is this like my
aunt who would give us like here's a lion king of vhs or here's sleepless in seattle and vhs
add a homemade label and she's like oh no my friend he's allowed to go in the theater and
tape these oh wow really you had somebody who really wow you got stolen we got handed well you
got like a true bootleg of like somebody with a camcorder in a movie theater yeah we had some
bootleg i thought what you meant was just like oh they taped like because sometimes you'd have like
the vhs machines where you could do too and you would take from a blockbuster but you're talking
about true blue i think with bootlegs it didn't seem like copy that is tremendous i don't think
i ever had a bootleg from a movie theater tape growing up you're like why it's like i like the
song of kuna matata but why is it so shaky it was and i was like i gotta wait him for christmas
man king this rules i've never heard this before this is some great jason mythology wow wow i i
think um he's allowed i think the same he's monitoring screen quality he's allowed and we're
all like license an operating license the vhs i think that same on went to a taping in new york
of the rose o donald show and there there we got borrowed vhs they were giving out freebies that
and i think it was was a i think we got mission impossible because she loved tom cruise and that
was in a real and that was one of the options mission impossible or wow i was gonna say now
see i don't understand there's these there's this moment that's so tense but why does somebody just
start coughing when he's trying to diffuse the god starts coughing at a certain point why don't all
these blurry figures walk in front of tom cruise they're so shaken by the coughing and there's a
part where just the uh you can't see the screen where someone's going to the bathroom
i didn't understand the cinematography the cinematographer's choice to leave tom walk
into a lobby stand in front of the urinal when he's hanging on the cable what falls off him is
it a knife oh that's in the trailer for the new one too it kind of i know all about but it's like
oh the knife just startled that person so much they started coughing the knife falls on the desk
right as he's leaving yeah and then the guy does see the knife there right yes um i the we've
we gotta wrap this up but i but i really just you know and here's what i'm gonna say i don't
really have a lot to say about the ride everything i had to say was about this yeah and i will not
stop anyone from getting their ride thoughts out i just the fact that it is such a mythology
expander that is so bold just to quote them officially um it what does this mean it means
that our parents are never going to meet which will activate a new timeline in which my cousin
and i don't exist which will create a space time imbalance other person says long story short all
of you will end existing too so we have to hurry up that's why we need our parents to meet at the
science congress but also you're all gonna die so all of that at once and that is all the back
story on which you go into a really mediocre simulator ride that looks like old video games
but i'm this blew my mind and is i think actually kind of a funny plausible premise
at least one i just i do wish i would like to hand this to ai like make make zach and jesse
back to the future 4 for me don't waste anyone's time don't bother christopher loyd and michael j
fox their health is not great don't you dare make them come be part of this make ai do the work on
this shit but i just want to know what the insane rest of that story would be uh i will say the
it's okay so the ride room has some weird stuff in it too one there's someone in the yellow hazmat
suit obviously obscuring their face so it can be a man or a woman they i guess get the plutonium
briefly take it off stage on screen it sure enough it is basically worse simulator footage
than the back to the future ride because it goes in prehistoric times it goes to the future
it's all the same stuff it's all the same stuff and then it ends at 1855 and everyone is so far
away from the camera there there's no subtitles at this point and they just have like emotionless
conversation the hazmat person walks on screen for a second i believe to give them the plutonium
and then maybe take the bad one back they walk off screen then they walk into the audience again and
they walk back and the other the guys go like i guess they go like let's get out of let's get to
the conference and then it it closes like a fake shutter and it says to be continued
but i don't and then immediately after exit and an arrow of where you have to exit so i guess it's
continued in that oh jules and verne can go have sex at a conference now they can meet wives
separate that also the idea of two brothers going to the science world congress and both of them
meeting their wives wait okay and when you have you do have to ask the question
did it all happen in the same room was the was this a was this a double brother
you have no wait a minute we're messing up the time okay so they go to the science conference in
2030 but jesse and zach come back and say they're from 2055 correct but they appear to only be
15 yeah they're not 25 years old so that means jules and verne have to meet the mother they both
spend about 10 years together oh right good point then they have the kids yeah oh yeah so
it's not necessary that they have sex at the congress it depends on their degree of comfort
with the women that they meet uh maybe jules takes his time maybe he does it on the 10th date
but verne i know from his weird little dick points is getting on right away he cannot wait
verne is pouncing on his wife they don't they don't say if they have any other siblings either
though uh no i bet the older ones yeah and if they don't is it just are they just lazy
or not scientists they're not scientists yeah like like can you take care of it
no can you go help me still be born thank you yeah it's really something uh the dinosaur can
i talk about yes yes of course there's a dinosaur that attacks the time uh time room the time shuttle
and this dinosaur looks like it's from like a windows 96 screensaver it is so funny it's i
mean it's very much in the mold of jurassic park classic t-rex that just bites into the into a
delorean and shakes it around like a dog it's a playstation 1 graphics nintendo 64 graphics
the jump in like frame rate it takes a bite toward you and it looks like it's it like you
missed three seconds of movement it goes from like 50 yards away to 10 yards away in a jolt
you're like wait wait wait hold on it looks so funny and bad it is a 3d movie and we're watching
it around and his big goofy teeth are right in your face it like there is i will say i actually
like i'm happy that it looks bad it looks like it's funny bad yeah it looks charming yeah it gets
the geography incredibly correct because they go to they call it the lone pine mall yes and i've
been to this mall and i'm like oh this is exactly this is exactly the space of that and then they
recreate it is perfectly the back lot it's perfectly courthouse square yes and then they
turn left and i'm like oh they go over there they show us what the movie doesn't show us
that's kind of cool but yeah it's it is just extremely video gamey back to the future stuff
and then yeah that ending that might be the most anticlimactic right ending i've ever seen
the ending is crazy you just the ride stops moving you just stare at a still shot of a very
snail paced plutonium exchange and nobody celebrates or says thanks you did it but thanks to you
we get to go make a family and the future is what you make of it they just they don't even
include us in it they could have said like you don't understand i'm your kid from the future
it's your parents you have to go back to the future like they could have just done that and
cut away really quick with the done done done you also never see zack and jesse again never yeah
yeah it's not like they get reunited like they're just like completely divorced from what part of
that we are back kids from the future don't they understand when you show us kids from the future
i expect them to be back and stay back we are back indicates that they're back they've been
there before we are we are back we are back but if it's 2025 and they need their parents to meet in
20 they ever been here well you know you know who's getting google alerts about this ride
is the writer of the children's storybook and the screenwriter of we're back a dinosaur story
surely they put in we're back we are back that's probably why it is we are back they had to avoid
that yeah right too many lawsuits going right um well let's talk this out it's called back to the
future wait no okay that is him going back i was gonna say when marty goes to 1955 that's not back
because he's never been there he's going back home for 1985 yeah you have found one and only one
logical hell yeah entire operation we are back kids from the future the kids have never been
to the present as far as we know or they have and there was an that was an important detail to tell
us right maybe they have been yeah we are back because like back to the future is pushing it
because look back to the future i guess it's a it does make sense but really it should be the
title probably should be more about going to the past that is what most of the but it's about
him getting back to the future it's kind of the goal of the movie yeah that's true but the mission
takes place in the ride is this track then we are back kids from the future so they're well i think
it does because the goal is for them to keep being kids from the future right that's true if their
parents still meet they won't be kids they won't be anything i'm awfully tuggered out i could really
go for some ice stone ice stone ice stone ice stone creamery or would you rather go to rock
and roll restaurant and get a jackson sandwich here's probably some real food here's where i go
crazy on the ice stone one of the things that has really not happened from doing the show that i
thought would happen is that someone would reach out at any place theme park company place around
the world this is what i wanted they would ask us to help write a ride and now that i think about
it the place i would want to make a ride the most is movie land you're right because it's
totally open canvas of anything you ever wanted to yeah right that's where you do that's where
back that's where we could really happens as a ride they should give us a whole land we should
each have our own ride your script for minecraft meets roblox yeah sure we can have anybody william
frolly can show up on where we are back kids from the future it doesn't matter anything goes
at this place it's lawless and truly there's no place i would rather write dialogue for a ride
than this place i you could have more right you could have et doc brent i'm sorry i'm not even
fuck doc fuck doc i'm not even using him zach and jesse brown are going to take et and robocop back
to dinosaur times and make them joust on velociraptor sure great and it's going to look
like that t-rex in the video it's going to be top of the line quality for 2001 yes uh i was
thinking chris for loyd got me thinking about the movie nobody because he has cameo in that
well not more than a cameo well yeah i don't want to spoil it but he's in it he's one of the actors
in the film i'm spoiling this five six year old movie so we've got loyd and we've got rizza we
got odinkirk but i bet odinkirk and rizza's grandfather william frolly would love to help
them out wait so your choice of all the ip in the world you were pitching the unauthorized ride of
nobody in which william in which is exactly the same except william frolly's and it's and it's a
ride that's different no you're right like hey you have your own ride to do this is great wait jason
go nuts put dj quals in there okay all my character actor papers yeah i mean and look anything
anything goes here i guess you know if now that jason's put that out there you know what if we
just um let's say we do the teenage moon ninja turtles but uh grandpa monster now is their mentor
instead of splinter oh man great why not like just we can do anything we want now the turtles
are not raised by splinter they were raised by a vampire uh and it's hell louis and but then you
then it has to also become a ride so just make that that also you go through the sewers in indiana
jones jeeps that don't work very well right yes that's true and then um my name is earl is there
he's also hanging out with the turtles and he's got to make good on all of the problem
oh i think she's done wrong just making sure everything's safe right yeah you guys good you
need anything i want a beer my name is earl what are you doing here imagine you're on indiana jones
jeep then you go spinning out and suddenly where are you pointing my name is earl yeah
hey your brain your bravery saved the sewer thanks well done freedom fighters thanks my name
is earl thanks my name is earl we're back my name is earl's kids from the future whoa and then right
at the end ant man jumped out of his mouth yeah anything goes wow wow that's why we need to get
in touch beauty of the i the intellectual property theft dark spot that is lake garda this is a
precious place forget what i said don't ever tell universal studios about this place don't tell us
we need to get there we need to make our things we need to crash our car into the walls must like
much like it was really important for jesse and zach to do let's send an email that's been
translated from our english to italian we won't double check it we'll send it to the company that
owns this place greetings fellow mister and pitch and pitch ourselves how is your acquaintance day
we'll pitch ourselves as writers who have a very popular podcast in america that we would love
big you know kiss kiss bang bang we'll say that we'll say that jason we are show business titanians
right yeah we'll send a picture of you and chris pratt jason uh we'll really try to like play it
up that this would be a big get for them to have us work on their future rides and let's again not
double check the translation but we'll send it out there with just mostly pictures of jason and famous
people mike mitchell griffin newman yep that's all we need three those three hollywood legends
will give you much love and money explosion right uh hell yeah we're getting there we belong there
we should be so lucky to be there where the the true theme park innovation is happening thank you
godspeed makers of we are back kids from the future oh my god you survived podcast the ride
thanks for subscribing to the second gate if you want to dig even deeper join us in our vap patreon
tier club three where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad
free i don't want to undersell the deeper tier of the patreon but you know who's not there kids
from the future it's just fucking us there's no kids from the future and they are not back
we gotta work on that we'll fix it