Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, you've got questions.
We've got answers.
Mike and Scott mail bag.
Let's go, go, go.
On with the show.
Hey, great.
All right, great.
Is that a new song for these?
Only if I can remember that later.
I mean, there's a recorded track of it,
so I could remember it.
Yeah, yeah.
I think riffing it every time, then it can evolve,
like jazz, you see.
I just wanted to start things on an exciting note, if we could.
Sure, and that was exciting.
Yeah, I think mission accomplished.
Thank you all for sending us a bunch of questions
directed at Mike and I, specifically, an opportunity
to do a different little slice of this three man operation.
And I noticed people kind of searching for themes
and going, well, what's up with Scott and Mike,
as opposed to Jason?
So I guess less in the way of Barbara Stanwyck questions
and more in the way of a parent question.
I think people put together, which almost I didn't,
like, oh, that's right.
It's the dads.
It's the Disney daddies.
Dads is good angle.
And I did notice a little handful of those
were worth acknowledging.
I don't know if I might have an answer that doesn't answer any
of them specifically, but I have some kid things to talk about.
Here's Gina Boliega.
As a first time parent to a one-year-old,
I just want all the parenthood content, LOL.
Amelia, same.
I've got a three-month-old.
And in keeping with that, Ariel Vento.
Which theme park that you visited with your kids
has been the most friendly and fun for three years old
and under kiddos?
And while, obviously, we've both had a lot of great times
at Disneyland and Notts and Universal and the big ones,
in terms of specific to that age and great for little kids
and something I'd never heard of before,
I've been wanting to talk about and hype up
this really cute little thing in the Long Beach area
called El Dorado Frontier.
I've now been twice and never had a good opportunity
to talk about it on the show.
Basically, it's in one of these parks
where you have to pay just to go in or to park in there.
Big sprawling park in the Long Beach area.
But then you keep driving and driving and driving,
and you end up in this little sliver that's
this little train-based park that
is so adorable and thoughtfully designed.
I think it was, at one point, just a train and that's it.
And it was getting run down and was going to close.
And then some people bought it who
were actual Hollywood set designers, art decorators,
and who were big Disneyland nerds.
And they thought maybe with just a little bit of money and care
and love, we could give this thing a little bit more charm
than it had before.
So it's ended up as this great little J. Ward type.
It's kind of like a Dudley Do-Right type,
like jagged font, tilted letter sort of thing.
Kind of like this fractured fairy tale vibe
and cute cartoony colors.
But there's not a ton there.
It's a train, and it's panning for gold and a merry-go-round.
But all done surprisingly, thoughtfully cool.
And I've been twice in the Christmas season,
and this time around with my new son.
And everybody loved it.
We used it as our Santa photo.
They do Santa photos there.
A great place to meet Santa.
Santa's hanging around.
You wait around for constant, every five minute,
real foamy snow blasts, foamy fake snow blasts.
You've got to love that.
Fomier than a Disney or an Americana fake snow
is what you're saying.
Boy, you know, amazingly, I don't really
go to the Americana fake snows.
I don't know why I haven't.
I think the kids would love it.
So I can't really compare the foamiest.
Yes, the outdoor Glendale mall.
The very stylized Disney-esque Glendale outdoor mall,
home to a friend of the show, Buzz Buzz.
Yes.
Be cool in the comments.
But anyway, this thing was just, like, so delightful.
Really surprised me.
Just if you're in that area, if you're
like a parent in the South Bay or Orange County
or around there, really charming holiday time.
And it also has this little type of ride that the kids,
it's like a little, like a caboose kind of car
that kids have to pump themselves.
It's like a little simple track, and they have to do it.
So like when the hobos used to ride the rails,
essentially that car, I don't know the name of it.
Yeah, where like the two people in the silent films
would like, you know, manically chase the big train
and, you know, to try to catch up or climb a board
or, you know, or like they're the damsel in distress
that is on the train and they got to catch up real fast.
It's like that.
It's one of those for little kids.
There used to be a thing like this at Knott's Camp Snoopy.
It was called Huff and Puff and it closed recently
to make way for the new Camp Snoopy things,
which are delightful, but it's this great little thing,
like for a very little kid to be able
to actually control it themselves.
And it's a little bit easier than like a little car would be.
And if you don't have the strength
and you can't really muster your energy all the way
that we're on the track, a teenager will come
with a broom pole and just push you the whole way.
So anyways, El Dorado Frontier, just,
I've been wanting to just earnestly give a recommendation
of this cute thing for a long time.
So I'll use this data to do so.
Oh wait, and I forgot the real reason
I've been wanting to bring it up.
Great train ride, like which scared the hell out
of my three month olds, but besides that,
screeching the entire way all the way around the track
and it's a long track.
So that was a lot to get through,
but worth it because like cute, fun, well decorated,
but among the like knickknacks they have out there
decorating the train path, an old McDonald's apple pie tree.
Oh wow, really?
They found one of those somewhere.
So you can see an authentical thing from our childhood
mixed in with old West stuff.
It was nice to see that mildly creepy smiling face.
Mildly, yeah.
That's interesting because that would be a perfect place
because we want to buy old McDonaldland stuff like that,
but like nobody has a mansion here.
So if you were to decorate like some sort of a fun center,
theme park, whatever you call it,
that would be a good spot.
That's a great, and like current kids
don't know what that is.
They don't know from McDonaldland.
It's kind of sad to think about
that any kid past like 2008 just thinks of McDonald's
as oh, that boring place.
That place with the white walls and nothing cool to do.
So nice that there's these remnants of, oh, what we had.
Oh, when there were little tiny Disneyland's
at basically every McDonald's location.
Yeah, well, there should be an executive order
that says we're gonna start teaching
McDonaldland in schools.
That's what I think.
So kids really need to learn about this,
especially the old like Officer Big Mac
and some of the characters that weren't even that common
when we were growing up,
maybe they were represented in the play area,
but they weren't so much on the TV.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's time to teach kids about the true history
of our military industrial complex
of when we had firm authority figures
who not only believed in strong prisons,
but they themselves were the prisons.
Their mouth.
Go into my head.
Yeah.
You commit a crime, you stay there, I eat you.
You don't eat me, I eat you.
That was a great time to be alive.
It really was.
And all we can do is try to pass it to ours.
I have a question for the nation of America.
Oh, everybody?
Yeah, a question unrelated to what we were just talking about.
I've noticed in Burbank and around here,
there are a lot of sort of family fun center type things
like low, I guess Chuck E. Cheese
because they would have play areas, but discovery zones.
There are so many different seemingly independent run
children's play things, play areas.
I don't even know what you call them, fun centers, whatever.
Balls, you know, something to climb on, a slide.
Maybe a trampoline component.
Yes, I've become familiar with this thing, Billy Bees,
which is at the Anaheim Garden Walk,
which my son loves very much.
And is it chain?
There's one in Santa Clarita.
Yes, correct.
But then there's a place called Rockin' Kids in Burbank.
And then there's another coming soon area that's called,
let's say it's called Candyland coming across the way.
There is something called Candyland in Sherman Oaks.
Are you making up Candyland or?
Because there is a Candyland.
I wanna say maybe it's the same thing.
I don't know, because it's like this weird like bad,
a lesser Lisa Frank looking art on the wall
in the Burbank mall.
But there's so many.
There's one just around the corner
where we live by a bakery.
I can't tell if there have always been as many of these.
That's my question.
Or if we're only noticing because we're new parents,
or is this kind of like how they're jamming escape rooms
in everywhere?
Is it like a reasonable way to fill a bunch of retail space
that is there, like something's gotta go in there.
And you might as well just fill it with a bunch of stuff
for kids.
That's my theory.
It does seem like it's quietly come back.
Like we're always going, oh, remember Chuck E. Cheese?
Remember Discovery Zone?
And they are back just in this kind of odd haphazard.
Sometimes, and there's varying degrees of shadiness.
Some are incredibly well done.
Some are pretty chintzy.
I mean, we found ourselves in a ball pit with,
or not a ball pit, but one of those blaster zones
with cannons up above.
And then there's air jets shooting foam balls up.
And you're like, so I'm digging through foam balls
to throw at my oldest.
And then you'll just find a chip bag in there.
Like, oh no.
Uh-huh.
So that's unpleasant.
But yeah, they're around.
They're everywhere.
They're really around.
There were two others.
There's two others right by us.
And I wonder if this is happening across the country.
I suspect what you're saying is right
that this is a smart way to fill retail space
as more stores go away.
So we can just like, kids don't care.
I've talked about this before.
The budget of a place is not important to a child.
Absolutely.
No, not extreme shade being thrown at rockin' kids
in Burbank, but it's not exactly
they have some sort of cohesive thing
other than they bought a bunch of Fisher Price stuff,
bought some wooden playground equipment,
and then just have a bounce house
in the corner of this place.
I will say rockin' kids sounds particularly chintzy.
I don't even want to group Billy Bees in,
although Billy Bees is the one
where I found the chip bag and the foam balls.
So that's minus points for Billy Bees.
But Billy Bees does have like custom builds.
Like they have like plastic shaped big scary bee heads,
which is scary and unpleasant, yes,
but custom theming.
And they did pick a theme.
And the characters have names.
There's characters, they have names, and that's all.
Yes, that's true.
They've got a little universe going.
You gotta appreciate that.
We'll get into Billy Bees down the road, I imagine.
Rockin' kids is fun, but yes, for the adult,
the kind of sewer of these places perhaps doesn't hold up.
Yeah, because we're McDonaldland kids,
so we set the bar extremely high.
There was never a better amount of theming and mythology.
So yeah, you just put a minion
that you don't have the rights to up on the wall,
and then maybe a Hello Kitty,
and you're like, well, those don't go together.
No. What is this?
What's happening?
Right, now, my daughter, I've never seen her more fun
than Rockin' Kids.
I've never seen a child of two and a half,
basically, hurl her body with such reckless abandon
in a bounce house, over and over,
cackling like she lost her mind.
I'm trying to tell her, maybe don't do that,
because dad doesn't wanna go home
with you with like a dislocated shoulder.
The way in which she was doing it though
was so much more violent
than the five-year-old boys that were in there.
She was hurl, she would fold herself like an accordion,
and I'm just sitting there going, I think she'll be fine,
but that's making me uncomfortable.
All I can say, I hate to say it,
but when you're telling me that, and what I'm hearing is,
and you know, you wouldn't believe what my son did,
he had paper towel beds for his Ghostbusters.
Well. That's a fire hazard.
That could be a fire hazard.
Yeah, I'm not saying it's not in the family of concern,
but I think if you had a video,
you would be like, I don't know about that.
Okay. Curl, folding herself up.
The video would have to be, is this regular kid stuff,
or is this particular Carlson-based concern?
It's regular kid stuff, what she's doing,
but the way in which she's doing this on a bounce house
was a little aggressive.
And then I was legitimately concerned
because it has this weird like tall slide
that's attached to the bounce house,
and it's as tall as me, but it's not a controlled slide
that has like, you know, it's a foot wide,
two feet wide or whatever.
It's a big wide thing.
So however you slide.
You're talking Billy Bees,
you got some of the widest slides I've ever seen.
And it's not even like plastic,
it's just material with air in it.
Okay. So there's a lot of variables.
So when she sees other kids doing stuff,
she just wants to do it.
Doesn't matter if the kid's eight, 10, doesn't matter.
She's wanting to do it too.
Wow.
So she's trying to climb up to do the slide,
and I'm like, you are not doing this slide.
I don't know how your body's going to fly.
I see a six, seven year old girl go up there.
She tries to go down the slide.
She flips in one of the most violent ways.
She eats shit so hard.
I believe the wind gets knocked out of her
because she doesn't even,
she kind of just pops over the slide,
lands on this thing and just like a little cough
and then runs right to mom.
She wasn't crying, but you could tell she was shaking up.
So I'm like, I was right.
You are not going down this.
Luckily it was a little too steep for her to climb herself
because she's too little.
But I can't, for me, if you went there
and you showed me what's physically happening,
I might go, okay, I understand.
Yeah.
Boy, having listened to a lot of your mom's stories,
I really wonder.
I need to see some photographic evidence.
Here's what I think.
I am leaving out the things that made me uncomfortable
that I know in hindsight for sure were fine.
There were five other things I could tell you right now
that stressed me out that I know were fine.
I'm only saying the two-
You're telling me, oh wow,
but you're leaving out things
that are perfectly normal things.
Well, this is, you're censoring, your mom's censoring.
Yes.
Wow, you could easily provide the mom analog material.
Right, I have self-awareness.
There was just a regular kind of tube slide
that she was going down.
It's such an angle with her holding her hands up
that I was like,
you're gonna get your hands caught on something.
I know that was fine,
but it was stressing me out in the moment.
I think even rockin' kids thought of that.
I don't think they put things out
that your hands could get caught on.
I don't know if it was anything jagged or anything.
I'm just saying-
It's not like the knots, or not the knots,
the Six Flags flume ride that I went on
where there was just an open,
like two turning wheels that were super thick with grease
that I could have just stuck my hand into
before going down the ride.
Yeah, it was not that bad,
but again, that's what I'm saying.
There were things I know were fine,
but I'm like, this was just like,
I don't know if that's okay.
And then, of course, my daughter has stolen a lot of stuff
from Muffin, the Bluey character,
who is the most petulant,
including saying like,
uh, no, I don't want to,
which is something that Muffin says.
So I now hear Muffin coming out of her.
Bluey's a bad influence.
And then she is funny too.
I say, uh, we went to the Bounce House today,
and she goes, yeah, and daddy tried to pull me out.
I feel like something's happening here, Mike.
I could be wrong.
I'm not denying it.
Wow.
Isn't that, like, isn't that odd to be,
we've heard tale after tale of overprotective mom woe
and look at you now.
Yeah, I said I was gonna be a helicopter parent,
and it's coming true.
Did you announce that if you knew it?
I mean, I've said it in private at the very least.
Okay, I don't know if you said it to our audio.
I wanted to make sure it's been said out loud.
I didn't know if you said that in the,
like, you were having a daughter episode.
Well, maybe.
She's here, excited,
and these helicopter blades are flying and flying.
May they ever spin.
Yeah.
Well, no, I, there's, yeah, I know it.
I'm aware of it, and I'm trying to check it,
but this particular thing felt very intense.
That's all. And it might be.
I'd have to look at, I'd have to check the footage.
Let me do another parent question for Marnie.
Sure.
Was there anything that you were surprised to find
that your kids didn't like about a particular theme park?
Something you assumed they'd love,
but they in fact hated or didn't give a shit about?
And how about vice versa,
something innocuous or second rate
that they unexpectedly adore?
And I picked that because I do have a question
for that more of the second part.
And this is kind of a general thing, I'd say.
My oldest is getting pretty accustomed to rides.
We just had a really productive universal trip
where we blasted through a bunch of things
that have been on the to-do list for a long time
that he used to be scared of.
Minion Mayhem happened.
Simpsons ride happened three times in a row.
So proud of him, like leaps and bounds
in terms of ride comfort.
And yet what he remains loving,
and I'm curious if other parents out there
have experienced this too,
like one of the biggest secret theme park attractions
that you never think about is just some parked vehicle
that you can climb in.
It is like the biggest, and Universal has like
Italian little scooters
and then other types of motorcycles.
Like they're just a big row of those.
An area that we think of as just like
somewhere that you pass through
to get from one thing to the other,
like the French Moulin Rouge area.
But my son could spend an hour there easily.
Like we don't even go to the bottom.
Escalators, that's a big old hassle.
We stay, we get on all of those little motorcycles.
We honk, we rev.
That's like all they, that's all they wanna do.
It's really, like if I was involved
in the planning of a theme park,
my first move at this point would be
a bunch of weird little vehicles that kids can climb on.
It might be more important,
at least to that age group, than actual rides.
Yes, I agree.
I mean, it doesn't even matter yet if it moves.
I mean, we were outside rocking kids
and there's just a horse that you put a quarter in
and it moves.
We didn't have to pay the quarter.
She just was thrilled to be on the horse.
Same thing at the Burbank Mall.
We never pay for it.
Doesn't matter.
Sorry that we're cheap skates.
Sorry we're not giving our well-earned quarters
over to these machines.
But yeah, he just cycles through.
Doesn't want them to move, specifically.
No movement.
Let me sit in a still spaceship.
That's what I want.
And that dovetails into another thing
I wanna talk about, and this is maybe a good story
about my oldest starting to become me.
We had a Knott's Day that was so delightful
and we're hitting all that aforementioned
newish camp snoopy stuff.
Made it onto Pig Pen's Mud Buggies.
That was a good leap forward.
That's a very bouncy ride and he was nervous about that.
But ended up doing it, wanted to do it immediately again.
The wanting to do a ride again instantly
has been a wonderful thing to witness.
And yes, he still has to deal with me, the dad,
who does not like cues, who does not.
I will say yes as long as that line
is not completely insane,
which it wasn't for all of these things.
I mean, I'd wait in whatever for him,
but I'd prefer it and not.
But anyways, the thing though, at some point I asked,
what's your favorite ride here?
And he said, Flower Train.
And I said, oh yeah, well the train.
We did the, we're gonna do that.
And he said, no, no, the other train, the Flower Train.
And I had to think and like,
oh, you're talking about a not actual ride.
You are talking about something in the ghost town.
There is just a still parked train
that he calls Flower Train,
because all of the carriages now are filled
with nice winter or spring flowers,
depending on when you're there.
And it's just a little train compartment
that you climb up in, doesn't do anything.
It's called Old Betsy.
And again, all he wants to do,
there is a train that moves and shows you stuff,
much less cool than the one.
I mean, understandably than the one
where you can get up in it,
you're piloting it yourself.
So blasted Old Betsy.
We're having a fight, like I'm not alone.
Like there's a line of kids trying
to just get on Old Betsy for a second.
This is huge.
Stationary ride vehicles.
Biggest thing I didn't realize till I was a parent.
Has a blast there.
Then this was on December 31st.
And I was, I kind of said a couple of times,
I think we're gonna,
this will be the last time that we go to nots,
because next year we're gonna have Universal.
Like we're trying to trade up the annual passes.
And, or change up, sorry.
And he was cool with that until we were leaving.
And then just burst into tears, sobbing.
Oh my God, what's going on?
What's up?
How can I help?
And he says, I would just miss Knott's Berry Farm so much.
And then we had to go back in.
We spent some more time on Flower Train.
I mean, it was really, I felt for him,
but I was also like, oh my God, he's me.
This is exactly me at the Orlando airport.
It's happening just due to even the vague mention
that we won't be doing nots this year.
And probably that plan is,
I think we're gonna have to do nots this year.
And then here's the part that really kicks it over into me.
And to answer somebody else's question,
Shannon asked about like PTR things that your kid's like,
here's one that then later that week,
he's like, I miss Knott's Berry Farm.
He's inconsolable about missing nots.
And I thought, oh, you know what you might like?
There's this song about Knott's Berry Farm.
And this is something, I don't know that this is like
landed especially hard with the audience,
but when we talked to Rachel Bloom a little while back,
I brought in a handful of odd old nots clips.
And there was this documentary from 1984
that was made in New Zealand
with this Knott's Berry Farm song at the end.
That's the most like emotive, beautiful thing I've ever heard
that also was like really like of the moment,
like excellent kind of like 70s power pop.
I mean, it's a little late for that,
but it's this song,
I don't know if you remember the song at all.
Vaguely, yeah.
It's like Shades of McCartney and 10CC and Emmett Rhodes.
It's like,
Knott's Berry Farm,
no mistakes, no regrets,
together we can make it all the way.
Like why this song be so emotional about Knott's?
And I was like, maybe this will help you out.
And now he's singing that song
when he needs a hit of Knott's, we play.
And what could be more of me
than like passing on to my son,
like clips, weird old clips recorded off TV
of theme parks from before I was born.
And those are songs that mean a lot to him.
Right.
It's just been a very nice,
just earnest experience watching him like truly
fall in love with these places
and with the song that he'll never encounter anyone
who knows it.
Right.
Yeah.
I would say my daughter really,
a lot of the stuff I was hoping she would like,
she likes,
but then it is always really funny
to see what she like takes to.
She loves the Pirates of the Caribbean song.
She'd been on the ride twice, I think, at this point.
She likes the song though,
cause it's dark on that ride.
I think she gets a little uncomfortable by it.
But then like we were leaving Universal,
like we popped into,
look, you go up there, you have a little pizza,
you go see the Grinch,
and then you leave.
That's what you do when you're a dad
taking your daughter somewhere.
It's a really good kind of two hour place.
And in the two hour version, no lower lot.
That takes too long.
We haven't even done it.
We haven't done a lower lot together, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But there's a new thing coming in at CityWalk.
There's a new store.
One of the rare things coming to CityWalk,
not the things going.
Not leaving, yeah.
But they're characters from South Korea
that I had never heard of called the Line Friends.
Oh, I don't know about this.
They're just cute little characters,
the Sanrio-ish or whatever.
And we're leaving and she was in the stroller for this.
And she all of a sudden sees these friends,
these Line friends on a wall,
a construction wall basically.
And they have five, six characters.
And she demands I stop.
She's like, but there's plenty of characters everywhere.
She's never really done this with like pictures on a wall.
She demands we stop.
And then she sits and demands that we take photos
of her and each Line friend.
Wow.
So I have a full photo shoot of her in the stroller.
These characters you do not know.
These characters we don't know.
She doesn't know them.
She is so elated in these photos.
She's just like exploding with delight.
And then we do all the photos
and then she just goes again, again,
which is a thing she says often.
I'm like more photos.
We took them.
We have to leave.
You have to go to bed.
It's already too late.
So I'm like, that's better.
I go, but remember we saw the Grinch
and he was dancing and it was all show.
She's like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But like these still characters on a wall
that she just glanced at.
And so it's bizarre seeing like weird stuff that resonates.
It's funny.
You were saying they're wanting to do a ride again
when she was 18 months.
She went on the mater junkyard jamboree
or whatever it's called.
And she, I didn't, I always thought she was going to cry
because she was scared on a ride,
but she cried because we couldn't go ride it immediately.
Again, we had to wait.
See, there's a tough one.
You can't, that's a different thing.
That's a long wait to get back in.
Not like those mud bogeys.
Yeah, 20 minutes.
Yeah.
20 is reasonable.
Depends what it is.
Yeah, it depends what time of day.
But that was something I was not,
we were like all set for her to cry on something
or seeing something.
But then she cried because we couldn't just stick on there
because she loved, she loves just getting whipped around,
which is something that I guess will be good
when we get to like bigger rides.
Sure.
Yeah.
But it's interesting.
It's fun.
Like having it all scrambled up, you know,
we were getting set in our theme park ways.
Here's the things that we do
and here's the things that we don't do.
And then you bring kids into the picture
and like suddenly this big area is completely weighted
and you gotta carve out a bunch of time for this.
Yes.
And it's fun.
And she loves Tiki Room too.
She likes the song or whatever,
and we've done it once or twice.
And then we were trying, it was just got very,
I think I said this on the show already,
it was very stressful day.
And she knew where we were in Disneyland,
like last time we were there.
Because she goes, Tiki Room?
She started pointing at it and I went, oh, she knows.
She knows where we are now.
Because before, I mean, my mom doesn't know where we are
when we're at Disneyland.
She like knows Disney World okay,
but hasn't been there in a while,
but she's like, well, where is it?
To the left of the hub, daddy.
Right.
So we were like right there and she saw it from afar
and she goes, Tiki Room?
Tiki Room?
Wow.
And I go, oh, wow.
You're doing a good job.
So she really, yeah.
Wow.
Wow, knows her way around, knows what Tiki Room is
and mainly likes an animatronic show
from close to 70 years ago.
Yes, yeah.
So me forcing her to learn the map every night before bed
is really paying off.
Running drills.
Yep.
You got anything?
I mean, I got a bunch loaded up, but.
Yeah, I can.
Oh, you know what?
You actually, here, this one dovetails into kids.
I'll answer it quickly.
This is from DRC.
We know Mike's love of Ninja Turtles,
but what were the key toys of Scott's childhood?
Oh, that's a good question.
I, what's nice is the key toys are the ones
that have stuck around and that have just been
in my childhood bedroom unmoved for a long time
just because I didn't have the heart to get rid of them,
but luckily now they are beloved toys to my son
and it's really great to see
and that helps me them be immediately accessible to me.
I mean, I love Ninja Turtles too.
I don't have a lot of them left,
but my favorites are also the Kinects Roller Coaster
was one.
Don't have that anymore,
but that was a really cherished Christmas.
If you remember Kinects, not Legos,
but those like the long pieces that you're there
and that was an incredible thing where you like
could actually build the chain and it worked
and it would take cars up and then like
do a big route with it,
but the ones that I'm so excited my son is using
the Batman Returns playset where you fold it out
and some of it is Wayne Manor and some of it is Batcave
and some of it is Penguin's Lair
and there's a part where you can put Bruce Wayne
into a chamber and then spin him around
and leave a Batman back there
so that he can seamlessly behind a door
turn from one to the other
and I still have a lot of Penguins
and their little like Penguin missile packs left as well.
Real animal Penguins.
Yeah, not just multiple villain Penguins.
Yes, I don't know if I even have an action figure
of Danny DeVito Penguin.
I have that weird Robin that people think is Marlon Wayans.
I have one of those still around.
Because he was gonna be Robin.
They made the toys in advance, that's that story
and then Robin did not end up in Returns
so they had to just like, all right,
well what if Robin was in Returns?
He might look a little something like this.
Yeah, that's the place that I think
I've sent you this before where they did four versions
of the exact same mold for the different movies.
Yeah, you told me that what in this version represents
the Penguin's lair is what?
It's also Mr. Freeze.
Yeah, something like that where they just really painted
it a different color and would use the same molds.
Oh, okay.
Used it for years and I think,
I forget maybe even a non-Batman thing used it
like late 90s which is always funny stuff.
Like I didn't realize that as a kid
that like they would reuse molds and vehicles.
Like you'll find like Ninja Turtle vehicles
but they're a different,
it's a totally different like property.
That's smart, I mean that makes sense to do.
The other one I really love, there is a game,
do you have this game?
There's a game called Crash Canyon.
It was a board game.
Oh, I know what you're talking about but I didn't have it.
Off-road type vehicles and when you rolled the die
you would fill the whole thing up with water
and then if you might land on a spot
that was not a spot that your car could stay on
so it would tumble into the water.
So it was very, it had splash zones.
It was like just a very like cool interactive,
there's a precarious bridge on it like Indiana Jones
and I love that he loves it and I always loved it
because in the days before you could just watch
theme park videos all the time,
it was like a little taste of,
oh this is the vibe of Big Thunder or of Indiana Jones
what with a wobbly bridge and what with fake rock molding.
I mean it's very like Radiator Springs before its time.
I've been loving seeing Crash Canyon around.
It's not a thing I hear about a ton.
Like you remember it but I've never caught a lot of
nostalgia for Crash Canyon out there.
I'm just, I'm so glad I got mine.
He's loving it.
That's cool.
Just you saying that I remember any board game
that was sort of three-dimensional,
even like the game of life,
you would put those little mountains that popped out of the.
Yes, hills and bridges.
Yeah, yeah.
I like that more because then the game is very dry.
The game is very adult oriented.
Yeah, I love the game but it's boring.
Yeah, but then the wheel extremely satisfying.
I felt the same way, just like placing the hills.
I found, it was like a,
it's almost like a model railroad situation
that only takes 10 seconds to assemble instead of a year.
Yes, yes.
So any game like that. Landscaping.
And then I loved Mouse Trap
but Mouse Trap never worked.
Never worked, more fun in theory.
But I would never do what it's supposed to do.
Yeah, totally.
I would be more likely to like,
well, let me just like take the individual traps
and make like one at a time work
because the entire Rube Goldberg is never gonna.
Right.
Run smoothly all the way through.
There's a half of this that's for you.
Oh.
Favorite, I think I might know that.
Oh, maybe I don't know the answer.
What's your favorite Ninja Turtle knockoff?
Barnyard Commandos, Cowboys of Mu Mesa,
Biker Mice from Mars.
Mu Mesa.
Mu Mesa, I think I've heard that before.
Okay.
For whatever reason,
because there were some Archie published comics also
in addition to the cartoon of Mu Mesa.
And Mu Mesa is by like a turtle guy as well.
And I have watched Mu Mesa recently
and I don't know that the show is really funny.
And I don't know if I've said this on the mic here
but the show is really funny
because it isn't even having that much fun
with them being cows and cowboys.
It's pretty much straight ahead.
It's like you're watching like a G-rated Deadwood
but they're cows.
It's just about like, you owe me $300.
Yeah.
It's not like that.
Then they don't say, that's a lot of moolah.
There's a little of that.
But then there's just like, there's clearly a brothel.
It's a cow brothel, but like they just drink sarsaparilla.
Like it's not, no one's drinking alcohol.
But there again, this is one of your,
you who claim to be the most puritanical
are imagining, how do you know it's a brothel?
What's the proof that it's a brothel?
Because she's dressed, the woman who runs it.
Miss Lily.
She's dressed like.
But she's dressed like the character.
If you've ever watched Deadwood, you know one-to-one.
She has like a speakeasy brothel.
It looks just like that.
There weren't speakeasies where people wore revealing clothes
that weren't brothels?
Perhaps in the old west, there was like one building.
I'm not even saying in the old west.
I'm saying in Moo Mesa.
Could there not be, are these cowboys
all just trying to get their udders wet?
Is that all it is?
And yes, I believe an udder is a cow's penis.
That is what I think.
Okay, well, as far as I know, that's what it is too.
But I guess what I'm saying is that
it's almost like one-to-one old west stories.
And it's not even like,
there's not even that much fantastical stuff happening.
They're just cows and they're having like normal like,
oh, the mayor's a little corrupt.
Oh, we exposed them.
And there's nothing like crazy turtle.
Showdown at noon.
Like the craziest thing I even found was just like
in the comic, there's a dinosaur.
And I was like, well, that's like the craziest thing
that's happened in a Moo Mesa story.
Then it's off.
How do you end up at dinosaur
without previously exhausting all of the cow fun
you can have?
Although is there a lot of cow fun you can have?
Cows are kind of a limited theme ultimately, aren't they?
They're a limited theme.
The origin of Moo Mesa is that a comet hit a Mesa
and then the cows around it became anthropomorphic.
So I think it's modern day,
but there's a very tall Mesa
where there's all these anthropomorphic cows
and other animals are just reliving our old West.
How do they know about that?
How do they know how to act and talk?
I don't know.
Do they do like Pat Butchram stuff?
Well, how do they know that?
I don't know.
We did also, did you say asteroid or comet or what was it?
Comet I think. Comet.
They also scatter a bunch of the old tapes their way.
Right, they were watching Green Acres episodes
and then episodes of Gunsmoke.
Yeah, yeah.
And then they figured, they were like,
well, let's live like this.
It taught them English, yeah.
But for whatever reason, I think a lot of stuff
comes down to character design for whatever reason.
When you're a kid, if it looks kind of cool,
that's what you need as opposed to actual quality.
Certainly, then you have the rest of your life
to pick apart all the plot holes.
Exactly, which I will continue to do.
Which is some of what we do here.
That being said, I do like Barnyard Commandos
and Biker Mice from Mars, don't worry.
Close seconds.
I have more of a traditional theme park question
if that would be okay.
Yeah, yeah, why not?
Hold on, my phone is blown up the question.
Matt Valdez asks, Disney reportedly has been surveying
guests about adding The Simpsons to Disney parks.
If that were to happen,
what would you want the land or rides to be?
Which park would you want it in?
This is an interesting question to me
as I really thought about it.
What do I want in the year 2025
with The Simpsons and a Disney park?
Does it even fit?
Yes.
Do I want it there?
It's not a giant priority to me,
I have to say. It's not for me,
neither me. This is probably properties
I'd be more excited about.
I agree, but I'm like, I guess I would take it
over other stuff.
Yes.
It just doesn't feel so urgent to me to put it somewhere,
nor do I feel it fits anywhere in,
or at least the California parks thematically.
But my answer would be,
if they actually do Itchy and Scratchy land,
that's the way to do it different.
I think we have talked a little bit about that.
Yeah.
About a real parents island and all that stuff.
But yeah, if there was a new ride
that was like the full journey and that let you,
because obviously you can't do the ride
where the log is cut down the middle.
You can't do some of the more dangerous things
or Bart and Lisa like exploding off,
jumping off the land mines.
But you could do a simulator
that takes you through all that stuff.
And you could build, I mean,
it'd be pretty exciting to arrive at a Disney park
and see a big stone Itchy and Scratchy
in a cliff wall.
And if you did have to take,
if there was a separate helicopter ride
that was the way that you got there.
That would be, yes, fantastic.
But where does that go?
Is it extra, let's well,
since I guess Monsters Inc was not an important enough
project to blow up the very important,
vibrant Star Wars launch bay area.
Maybe that would be a good place
to finally get rid of our beloved,
whatever the fuck is there
and build a specific slice of Simpsons.
Yeah.
Hollywood Studios is the only place
that is such a mishmash in parks
that that would actually feel like
you could do something there.
Which you kind of, I don't,
I think maybe theme parks,
maybe Disney parks need their mishmash.
Islands of Adventure is also a mishmash.
I think all the theme park brands need
what is their mishmash brand to be a thin excuse
to throw this thing in, which would make it DCA here.
But DCA space seems like more at a premium
than Disneyland space.
Like all of the most recent announcements were DCA.
People still tripping over themselves
trying to figure out where's Coco, where's Avatar.
I don't, I can't pretend to guess on either of those.
Yeah.
Would we blow up some of Tomorrowland for,
the current Tomorrowland for Simpsons stuff?
I guess.
Only if they were like,
we truly don't have any other ideas.
Yeah.
Is there anything at Disneyland
that you would get rid of?
For the Simpsons?
As much as I love the good Simpsons.
Just get rid of the, I mean, if I had to,
I don't really feel, I don't know.
I like Disneyland.
Maybe I'd say no.
If you wanted to, I don't really see the shows
over in the Fantasyland theater.
If you wanted to jam a little bit of Simpsons in there,
maybe there's kind of a relationship
with Toontown that makes sense.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I think that's weird.
I think it's a little weird.
Because they start in 2025 and then, so at Disney space,
2032, the new Simpsons experience.
I think really why I want it,
I think maybe now that I'm thinking about it,
the reason this question called to me
is that I wouldn't make the call to put the Simpsons
in a theme park right now.
It wouldn't either.
It wouldn't be on my top 10 list.
No.
And again, it's hard.
I don't think that the current Simpsons situation
has been lacking.
I think it's a great, that's the Simpsons in the park.
I think it's great.
I've gotten to, I took my son on the ride.
He got to, he's really into the Trias of Horror
where all of the characters blow up,
the like nuisance side of the road,
like the pet boys and the donut guy blow up really big.
And then they need Paul Anko to help write a jingle
and just don't look and all that.
So he loves that episode and then I got to take him
and there is the real lard lad.
And he got to eat one of those donuts.
And like, I don't know.
I just don't know what you're not getting
from the current one.
But you wouldn't want to just rebuild the current one.
Right.
And that's going away.
I mean, this question is because that's going to go away.
But ultimately, yeah, it makes me sad.
I don't know.
I guess I shouldn't have picked this question
because I guess it's a bummer
now that I think about the answer.
Here's what I think.
I love the Simpsons.
Like nothing could be more in my bone marrow
than the Simpsons is what like taught us
to have like more mature comedy taste.
There's still things from those early seasons
that make me like laugh till I can't breathe.
However, we've had a lot of Simpsons.
It's been a long time.
Wait, hold on a second.
Are you saying that in this culture,
we should let something die?
Maybe.
We shouldn't inject formaldehyde into its veins
to keep it perfect as the same as it's always been?
There used to be a thing
where when things ran their creative course,
they were finally set free.
I want every cast member of the show to be in their 90s
to be wheezing their lines, their lines of dialogue.
I want to hear the pain from the elderly cast members,
which they are at this point.
It's just, it's crazy.
Yeah.
So.
Well, at least they've kept the quality up.
You know, well, okay.
The only thing that intrigues me
and I don't even have a good pitch for it.
If it's full like Fox animation land
and you get your family guy and your Bob's Burgers
all in a little bit.
I think it would have to be that.
And that seems crazy that I would pick that.
Right, because I don't like big.
I like Bob's Burgers.
I've never really been a family guy person.
I'm not anti-family guy,
but I think I would pick that because it's new.
Yeah, I agree.
Before I would pick.
It's interesting.
It's more interesting and just a quick idea of it.
Yeah, yeah.
For some reason.
And all the new ones, of course.
Universal basic guys.
Well, of course, yes.
I'm talking about that too.
They'll always have a little room
for a new thing like that.
Yes.
That everyone knows.
The new generation of animation domination.
Is it still on?
I think.
Who knows?
There's no way to know.
No one has prime time television to be able to check.
Right.
There was a lot of activity on this one.
So I feel like I have a duty to answer it.
Yeah.
Aaron Abolt.
WTF does Scott eat?
I feel like we know so much about
Mike and Jason's eating habits.
And we also know Scott sometimes finds their ways absurd.
But if it's not too personal, can we get more details?
This question has been burning a hole in my chest.
Literally because I'm approaching 40
and acid reflux is kicking my ass.
Please help.
Apologies, Aaron.
Yeah.
Well, my dry meter is going off because like,
yeah, I don't, I do eat a little bit boring.
I don't dislike what I eat.
I'm like, I'm satisfied by my meals all the time,
but I don't, it's true.
I don't do the food indulgences that you and Jason do.
Right.
I think this makes me kind of lacking
in character for the show.
I think people find their way in,
in terms of choosing who's my guy.
Right.
In your guy's love of sweets and taco bell and the like.
But I think some of it is,
I've been with Aaron for so long now
and Aaron, Aaron like truly eats the same salad
every single day.
Yeah.
And I think it's, some of it's just force of habit
and some of it's health and some of it's like
anti-inflammatory, like chasing that
for the sake of her body.
And I think she's rubbed off on me in the food taste
where I'm like, yeah, I just don't eat like crazy
stuff all the time.
Like what did you eat today?
We did make it out to lunch today.
So it was a little bit different.
But I, but at like a typical, it is, okay.
None, no cereals for me.
It's not cereals.
That's like a big round of starch and stuff.
I do eat a lot of like bread and carbs.
I don't, I don't consider myself in like
great health, great shape, but I will say
I don't have the tummy troubles that y'all seem to have
or the weird other bits of fallout from it.
To be fair, mine is all stress related.
Oh, okay.
Anxiety.
Yours is different.
Yeah, guess your stomach started hurting
after three fucking weeks of fire.
Yeah.
After seeing your daughter bend in a weird way
at the fun playground.
Well, that helped, that helped,
but it wasn't the main cause.
I think, I feel like I try to do like a lot of fats
that are like natural and good for you.
It's eggs and avocado on toast every day.
It's then a lot of like, like protein and rice.
That's what like it'll be.
It'll be tofu on rice or it'll be poke.
I guess a lot of fish is in there.
Like turkey sandwiches happen a lot,
but then, but like done with like,
you know what I really try to avoid is like crazy sauces.
I really like the Jersey Mike's method
of like olive oil vinegar.
You know, that feels like nice and natural and simple.
Again, I'm maybe boring myself as I say this,
but I want to answer this question
and figure out what it is.
I think like ultimately,
I think you got to chase your indulgence, right?
You got to, there's like the thing
that you know you got to carve out.
And for me, that is admittedly not dessert.
I do not have the strongest sweet tooth.
I eat plenty of dessert, but it's not a like must for me.
But what is like, at least like the indulgence I know
that I'd like to carve out is drinking.
It's like, which isn't much at this point.
It's like, I'd like a beer or a glass of wine
or a cocktail most days, I would say.
So I try, so knowing that and knowing myself
and knowing that that's what I want,
I think I try to keep the food sort of reasonable
and boring so that that's not like extra calories
on top of an already gigantic calorie day.
Does that make sense?
Is it interesting at all?
Well, I don't want to put you on the spot about that.
I don't want to put you in a position to say no.
No, I wouldn't, I won't comment.
I won't say no comment on it.
But for the purposes of a haywalled episode
about the hosts where they're getting asked questions.
Why not get to know us?
I think really the difference of the three,
I believe maybe this is, maybe I'm patting myself
on the back too much.
I believe it's a Venn diagram and I am right in the middle
because like, for instance, what I have had to eat today
is some chocolate chip cookies.
I have had a wild cherry like cream soda zero soda.
See, that's another thing.
And no, I don't mean to, well, look, in this case,
I don't mean to shade.
Throughout the City Walk saga, I meant a lot of shade
because y'all learn nothing.
But that is, for myself, I don't do sodas
and I don't do like sugary milkshake coffee drinks.
It's only coffee in the morning and tea in the afternoon.
That's it.
That's the lowest calorie you can do.
And I'm really regular about that.
I need to do that at the time that I do it
or I will be off.
So like very, very, like really routine oriented.
But also today, I had a almost exclusively vegetable smoothie
and a kale salad.
So I feel like I'm in the middle.
I take wild, so the reason Jason and I get along with her
because we both like the same junk food,
but I do think I also can,
you'll find a real food item once in a while in there.
But I mean, there's gonna be days
when I indulge more than not.
But I like-
I'll say this, I think in the same run,
and this might've been the points episode,
which got into a lot of food stuff as well.
You got into a big run about like using the Taco Bell app
to calorie count.
Yes, yes, very exciting.
Mike, Mike.
Yes, go ahead.
You're an adult.
You know Taco Bell's not good for you.
You think you can Taco Bell your way to health?
I put, well, health is a different story
than just losing weight.
Okay.
You're losing weight though?
100%, if you calorie count works for most people,
whether that's the healthiest way to lose weight or not.
Okay.
A different debate, but absolutely,
if we wanna get in, maybe this is too dry,
but you can put in your height and weight
and you can roughly calculate how many calories
you should be eating a day.
But isn't there any, and I'm no expert in this,
isn't there also something to like calories
that are helpful to your body?
Again, health-
That aren't like trash?
Health and weight are two different things.
Okay.
So I'm just saying-
You are only arguing for the weight thing.
Right.
So I'm just saying that-
You do know that Taco Bell is dog shit for you, correct?
Yeah, but like, yes, of course.
But it's worse than like some like shitty
store-bought chicken McNuggets or chicken nuggets.
I don't know.
It's both, they're both bad.
That sounds bad too.
Yeah.
So, but no, no, I'm just talking about calorie counting
if you're trying to lose weight.
You know, fast food wise, I will,
the one, if I let myself start to dip,
I will like chicken tenders, chicken sandwiches,
the like Chick-fil-A side of things,
I will start going that way for sure.
I have to like make that a wall that I don't start,
you know, then that becomes that I do that all the time.
Right.
Yeah, no, so I'm not, health and weight is different
because you can be really skinny, but unhealthy.
That is, that is true.
Yes.
I've had periods of that.
Yeah, when I was a teenager,
I was just like weight fishly thin,
but you could like, the breeze would knock me over.
Right.
That was not a good way to be.
Yeah, no.
I've like been in better shape with more weight for sure.
But I would argue if you're having,
if you're like doing that,
you could still have Taco Bell once in a while
and be like calculated about it and still have your fun.
And we, as Jason, I said, still have your goo,
which is really what you go to Taco Bell for is the goo.
Well, it's what I was saying.
I don't do a lot of goos, I think.
Right, you're not a goo guy.
The sauces are really where-
Jason are big goo guys, we love goo.
Yeah.
All the different kinds of goo.
I also think, and this is what I'm saying,
like is where I have to just stay out of a lot of food
things because I do think it makes you guys lovable to be.
It makes you like, I'm not a good guest for dough boys
in a way for like, because I don't like do a lot of that.
Right.
And I'm not trying to be like pretentious or like,
and I don't even think I eat that great,
but I just, I know what I do,
and maybe now I'm going back to CityWalk stuff,
if something makes me feel bad, I never do it again.
And that is not, that's not you guys.
It's clearly not Weiger.
No, no, no, no.
Which makes you more fun characters to hear
the travails of.
But then there's like, I will be,
the problem is sometimes you're just so validated.
Like I had wanted Chili's for months.
I just, cause there's not a Chili's around here.
And I went to Chili's with my friends a couple of weeks ago
and that meal was fantastic.
It was so delicious.
Well, has Chili's turned a corner?
Is that what we're catching?
Is Chili's is the quality?
It's been on an upswing for a while,
but it's all still frozen food that they put in a microwave
in the back for, but for whatever reason,
their shitty frozen food really microwaves well,
or at least the plate I got.
So once.
That's strange to, I mean, you enjoyed it
and I can't take it away from you,
but the idea of like, this is a,
hey, my compliments to the chef.
He really microwaved it well.
Right.
The microwave. Excellent chef's kiss, microwaving.
Maybe they call it head microwaver
and it's not even a chef.
Maybe there's not qualification.
Like they don't need that qualification
to work in some of these chain restaurants.
They just need to be a whiz at the microwave.
They just know which setting.
Gotta know your numbers.
Which power level, right.
To microwave the ribs at.
They might even like not even like,
let's get, let's get having to know math out of there.
Just like make your own set of Chili's buttons.
Just put ribs on this one, burger on this one.
I hope they're not just microwaving the burger, but maybe.
They might be.
Some places might, you would be shocked probably
on what some places do.
I mean, we're five years away from a robot cooking
all the chain restaurant meals anyway, I think.
Five to 10 years.
They're trying really hard.
AI and robots just will shit out delicious Chili's ribs.
No one will notice, sadly.
AI will make the Chili's ribs and AI will produce
the voices of Mr. Burns, Smithers, and Principal Skinner.
I was just talking to a friend of the show, Nick Mundy,
on the phone today and I said that very thing.
I said, I wonder why it hasn't happened yet.
Yeah, yeah.
But maybe they had it there.
But you know it is being worked on.
I don't think there's, I think there's no question
they are exploring this.
These are some older.
Yes.
Can I stay on the name that you just said and say,
because there's also questions I would put in the,
well, this is a dad question too.
And there's also kind of a show business question.
Sure.
Not like Ethel Merman, show business,
a business of our show.
Of course, yeah.
Kevin De La Rosa, as a fellow girl dad,
will Mike ever give us a Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique review?
And I don't believe that you've been, from what I've heard,
and she's maybe a little young for that,
but I think we've talked about doing
Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique with Nick Mundy,
because he has been, because he is also a girl dad.
We did.
He has asked if he could do Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique.
So that's a possibility of all the guests.
Boy, you think you know a guy, huh?
You think he's a tough guy, bully, mean man, bad man?
Then he shows up, does Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique.
Unbelievable.
Yeah, I forgot about that too.
I think he did it last year, which I was at,
I went to visit him at Disneyland.
Here's another, this is like an internal show thing,
but why the hell not?
Luis Miziara.
Both of you guys have produced great music for the show.
What software do you guys use?
I'm assuming Logic Pro X.
Are there any virtual instruments,
including VSTs, plugins, or sample libraries
that you prefer?
Andrew Coth, the musician, seconds this.
I'll show my cards and say that, clearly not,
because I don't know what some of those words are.
I don't really know what a VST is.
I recently did, see now, I have contributed
a lot of songs to the show,
but it's usually like an existing karaoke track,
not something built from the ground up,
which does hurt the, you know,
an eventual vinyl release of PTR music.
I did send you guys that Beastie Boys-esque song
from Mickey's Nutcracker,
where I had the idea late at night,
I'm like, how can I crank this out?
Maybe I could, and that was just all,
that I did like, I did like musical typing on GarageBand.
I like found some GarageBand beat,
just like kind of mixed it to seem more like that track.
I like played a bad guitar, just using like,
just pressing the keyboard FFFD,
and somehow like threw some filters on it
until it didn't sound like shit.
So that was a rare from the ground up,
but that was just like cruddy GarageBand,
because I don't know what the hell I'm doing.
Mike, the actual musician, who's done our theme songs,
and then a bunch of other stuff,
the McGruff stuff, and then other things here and there.
The custom themes, when we do a theme,
they're always so delightful.
Hey, why not pat yourself on the back,
since it was asked anyway,
you wanna take us into your musical process.
I am just, I do a lot of things, like I do like,
when it comes to technical things,
I don't really know what I'm doing,
when it comes to like editing the actual show,
editing music.
I am using Logic, that is correct,
or sometimes GarageBand, but generally Logic for Apple.
And obviously I know kind of what I'm doing,
but I'm like, when it comes to like mastering or mixing,
I am still, I just, I should have somebody
who's a professional do any of this.
People like with, you know, it needs to,
that's like a PhD level thing to truly understand.
The McGruff songs that I made, they killed me.
I was trying to listen to them in the car,
to try to figure out like,
cause stuff sounds different.
Like when you're, what I understand is
when you're trying to mix or master things,
you're supposed to do it in a studio with big speakers.
You're not supposed to do in your headphones,
cause that's a different sound.
You're supposed to like mix or master things.
So they sound good coming out of two big speakers.
I didn't have that.
Like I didn't even have two big speakers.
So I was doing it wrong.
I was like mixing headphones and I was like, all right,
well, what did I try to make in the car?
And I'm like messing with the levels and you truly,
you really can lose your mind
when you don't know what you're doing,
which I still do not know what I'm doing.
So.
But virtual instruments and stuff.
That's a good question.
Cause you've ended up producing some sounds
that are like not like an instrument that you own.
You've covered a lot of genres
between all of these little custom themes.
Well, I can play, I can play the guitar.
I can play, I mean, I know chords on a piano,
so I can play little stuff.
Generally what I do is like if it's guitar,
I'm just playing it.
I didn't play the little fast Mighty Morphin Power Rangers,
like on the downtown Disney.
I cheated and used the keyboard for that.
Cause you can control it.
You can move, you can slide those notes around.
Exactly.
So anytime I'm doing the keyboard,
I will like do a little fix.
You do a little fix.
Cause you can drag those notes
to make them a little bit more in time.
Sure.
But like the McGruff,
like I'm usually if it's a guitar and playing it,
there's a pretty, I'm pretty proud of the guitar solo.
If you haven't heard my McGruff song on the apps,
the hookup app song.
I have to remind myself.
I have to admit, I don't offhand know
that I wish I could compliment you
on the specific guitar tone.
That's the slow jammy McGruff song.
I'm very proud of the baseline on that song.
I'm very proud of the guitar solo on that.
The baseline is just from the keyboard.
So I kind of just made that up on the keyboard
and then did a couple fixes on it.
You know what I enjoyed was giving you
a little musical note on the theme
of the City Walk Orlando saga.
Because I was like,
it should be like elevated from the first one.
Cause it's a song that we've used before.
So they're their little plus ups
that kind of like kick it into over to,
which Zach himself did.
Like you were already like producing it higher.
I was like, there should be some little bat,
quick dumb little guitar line,
which I thought because I really like
how my heart will go on,
has exactly one guitar part only.
And it's just the one thing it's like,
this ridiculous song also has a guitar part,
even though that's not the musical palette
of the rest of it.
I've always loved it.
So thank you for taking that note.
I felt like I got to contribute
and you played it well.
It's funny cause you just said that
and I completely forgot that's in there.
But I now remember what you're talking about.
And a lot of the vocal stuff, Zach just,
Zach is like, as far as just anything
Zach's ever been involved in musically,
whether the McGruff songs or that song,
he does it in seven minutes.
Wow.
I mean, he's the only person I know
who claims he does no inner monologue,
who has no actual voice in his head of self doubt.
Really?
That's what he's saying.
Yeah, that's right.
And most people have some voice going like,
don't do this man.
So literally sometimes you like send,
I go, hey, could you help me out with this?
Yeah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, 10 minutes later it comes back
and you're like, whoa, okay.
Damn, well that's very musician, I think.
To like just kind of go off instinct
and yeah, cause he just like sent you the parts
you didn't even like record with him, huh?
Like, that's very classic.
I'm surprised how much stuff I read about
where like, oh, they didn't even,
those guys never met.
They just like sent parts around.
I always think that's cool
that we're at that point technologically.
It's all, it's interesting
cause like you hear even old songs
where like Springsteen or whatever,
they all have like parts hanging around for songs.
They have just like pieces,
like they have a bridge, they have a chorus
and then they're just like plugging and playing things.
Yeah.
And that's obviously before they had things saved
to like logic or whatever,
but you'd have like little pieces of it.
Some little idea that maybe doesn't pay off for 10 years.
Yeah, so, and which I do have a bunch of things
like that from decades.
It's like us with the episodes.
It's pretty much as cool as like,
Bruce had this lick, sit around.
It's like, you know, Joe Walsh just started playing
let this lick and then it became Life in the Fast Lane.
And that's like how we just like said the phrase
Harbor Hoedown and then maybe someday
do Harbor, actual Harbor Hoedown.
Yeah, we are a lot like Joe Walsh.
I have to, any amount of comparing yourselves to musicians
I have to soften our coolness.
You have to admit, it's funny what you're saying
and I agree we should be self-deprecating
but you are serious.
It's true.
I mean, yes, you could take everything I said
and say it and not that voice.
You're doing a lot of that too where you're like,
actually what I'm saying, I believe.
I'm not saying it's as important as Life in the Fast Lane
is to American culture.
We probably all have a lot of like wanting to,
and I'm flattered, some of these questions,
I don't know if we'll make it to all of them,
but some are about like creative process
and the stuff that we do.
And there's always a part of me that wants to answer
and then there's a part that feels like it's indulgent
but the fact that we got the question,
this also reminds me in terms of like comparing ourselves
to other art forms, I saw this question.
Michael Hillman, have any of you guys considered
becoming stand-up comedians?
You guys are all so funny and have great comedic timing
and that's a nice thing to say but I do find stand-up
to be like pretty different than, you know,
probably like maybe both of us being interested in comedy
in high school or whatever, maybe we thought stand-up
but it's, you know, we went in pretty different.
That's just not, that's a very specific mindset to be in
but I bring that up less to say that and more to say,
I guarantee, if we read this question and Jason was here,
Jason would say, well, stand-ups are America's truth teller
because he says it every time.
If we talk about stand-up, that's one of those.
Yes, yeah.
Well, no, yeah, because it like pissed him off years ago
that people were saying that in like early Trump era
and now he says it every single time.
Audience, be on the lookout for some of those always,
Jason's, that's one and another one is
Manchurian candidate activation.
Yes, that is one.
He said that.
You could build the Jason AI right now.
You could build Jason AI.
It's even easier than Mr. Burns as long as you.
And then how do you fire that AI up
maybe with a Manchurian candidate activation.
That's right.
Is there anything, I think you might've been right about
that we should make sure we do theme park oriented things
as much as I am veering to,
oh, wait, this is theme park, but it's also us.
Unless you have one that you're excited about.
You know what, I have like a quick one
maybe for the end if you wanna do that.
Maybe you do your theme park one.
Unless it's the same one.
Well, it's also, I mean, it's kind of yours.
It's also about you, Matt.
I recently went to Disneyland for the first time
since 2019, meaning I finally got to ride
Rise of the Resistance and Runaway Railway.
And I have to say, I felt very sufficiently jostled.
Runaway Railway even literally fucked up my hip
lining up with Mike's wish to be fucked up by the rides.
So how much more can he really want these rides
to jerk us around to the point where he has to mention
it every time either ride comes up?
Also, I'm a decade younger than Mike,
but maybe this just shows how youthful he is.
Well, you got some compliments in the mix there.
This is true.
I have discovered as you've brought this up over the years
that people do seem to have trouble wrapping their heads
around your desire to be.
And if I could say it the way that you say it,
because it's not quite, I think so you get some Chicago
out in that it's always like fucked up
because I want to be fucked up.
I want to be fucked up by these rides.
Yeah, I do find this to be an odd opinion
and I agree with it.
I do sometimes go on these rides and I'm like,
yeah, I'm fine with that level of, but it's,
that's my taste and that's Matt's taste.
I don't know.
I don't know what question I'm posing
besides his questions, I guess.
Maybe I've, I don't guess I don't need to be fucked up
on Mickey and Minnie's runaway railway.
Let me be clear.
I don't think, I mean, maybe I've suggested some plus up
that would like move me around, jostle me more on that,
but that's not my primary concern on that ride.
I don't need to come out with a concussion
when I'm in Daisy's dance class.
That is though the most aggressive part of the ride
because that's probably where the hip.
It's shocking.
Well, there's other, I think you get like blown around
a little bit and you do kind of a whirlwind, you know.
But like you really like jerk hard to the left and right
and that could knock your hip out of place.
I feel like when you're doing that.
Yeah.
So yeah, I don't know.
Rise and Resist, I just, I like the feeling
of being under duress on some of these rides.
And so you're already a person who stresses your own body
into like weird welts popping up.
Right.
And yet be in on top of that, you need to like,
the ride needs to like bear down on you with stress.
Well, I think maybe I've said this before on the show,
forgive me if I have,
but I think it comes back to like certain properties,
certain movies, things I like.
When you would play with the figures as kids,
you like Star Wars figures, you'd have two figures
and you'd go, you'd like kind of close your mouth.
You kind of would almost play in a way
that you would make yourself a little delirious
or disoriented.
Like I used to love either playing with figures
or just pretending I was in a movie or TV show
where like, oh my God, we got to get out of here.
We're getting to the ship, we're getting to this
and like hurl myself on the bed.
Now I guess I'm a lot, this is where my daughter
is becoming me as well.
And what would your mom say when you did that?
Well, she wouldn't see, she would be out of the room.
And do it behind closed doors.
Yeah, and I would like jump on the bed.
I loved, I would get scared when like,
I've said this before, like a base would become under siege,
like, oh no, Shredder's in the sewer or something.
We got to get out of here before like the first turtle movie,
they get invaded by the Foot Clan.
So I always like, I think there was a visceral thing
that would accompany me liking Star Wars
or other TV and movies I like.
And Mickey and Minnie weren't necessarily
one of these properties that I wanted to feel like,
oh my God, we got to get out of here or we're going to die.
But Star Wars is.
But Star Wars is, Turtles is,
Indiana Jones is, so I think specifically when I say
I want it to fuck me up, I do mean like,
I'm missing that like action figure feeling,
that playing, jumping around, getting jostled.
It doesn't need to be like Indiana Jones or Transformers
where I don't need to vibrate.
So I guess I shouldn't always just say fucked up
when I'm calling for something different.
I should say though, I want to feel like some more
kind of thrill on it.
I want to feel, I love a feeling of thrill,
like it's a little out of control.
Sure.
But does not the drop, the drop.
I listened to the episode with Jess
where she was saying exactly this.
And she said, what about the drop?
And you were like, yeah, it was the most deflated yeah.
I'm not that, the drop is fine.
I don't hate the drop.
I enjoy going to drop.
Drop doesn't do much for me.
Wow.
Because I do, Guardians is a drop, that's a drop.
This is like four feet.
But I think the surprise, I mean,
you only get the surprise the first time.
It's fun.
But I still get a little rush.
I forget that you got to go up on that elevator by the.
It's not as big as the Hagrid's drop.
It's not as big as Guardians, obviously, or Tower of Terror.
But I think it's a move that you don't think
this ride vehicle has in its arsenal.
It is fun.
It's very quick.
It's just, if it was a longer, if it took longer,
I'm not saying it's bad.
I'm just saying that's not going to do it for me
as far as giving me that thing.
And I've said before, it could completely convince me
of its great, it is great, right?
But it could completely make me love it
if it had more warm moments, Star Wars moments.
Like that thing that never got built
with the Yoda and Dagobah, then you take off.
Stuff like that.
Like things that give me a different feeling.
I don't need just a thrill.
I also need love.
I need a feeling of love.
Well, that makes this other question extremely related.
Teddy K, hello to two of my three best boys.
Thank you.
I have an FMK for Mike with regards
to qualities of a ride.
So fwock, marry, kill.
Seeing your friends, fwocking you up, intimacy.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, these are wildly.
It's kind of confusing.
Three qualities that you love and need in rides.
Seeing your friends, fwocking you up, intimacy.
But you gotta kill one, you gotta fwock one,
you gotta marry one.
Oh my God, this is a wild question.
Who asked this?
Teddy K.
Teddy Maniac.
Let's see, pure thrills I love.
I mean, Velocicoaster I go on and on about.
So I do love pure thrills.
That means fwocking you up, I guess.
But seeing my friends and intimacy.
Intimacy, of course, the optimist prime moment
is what that's referencing.
All three of these take place, of course, in Transformers.
We get to see your friend Bumblebee.
And those friends are primarily from the ride.
I never watched the cartoon as a kid.
Didn't have many toys of Transformers.
And then I've seen the first movie.
So seeing your friends counts even if it's not friends
from any other media.
Yeah, they're my friends because of the ride.
That's my favorite Transformers thing, is the ride.
But then why can't the Rise of the Resistance characters
be your friends?
They're in a ride.
They are, but they're not.
It's Kylo Ren and you see Finn from a distance.
And again, for whatever criticism I level
against newer Star Wars, I like almost all the characters.
But it's just not, I mean, you see them in the pre-shows
and I like all that stuff.
But they're kind of far away.
I mean, all right, it's a monitor.
I guess a monitor with Poe Dameron
is not gonna do anything for you.
It doesn't do as much for me.
So Beck is your friend?
Yeah, I love Beck.
I've talked about Beck in my favorite, my...
Just figuring out the rules.
So Finn is not a friend
because Finn's on a screen that's far away.
Well, but he's like a head is on a stick far away
because you see him in the big AT-AT room.
But if he was closer, he'd be your friend?
If there was a room where Finn was like closer
and he was like, get in here and like the door closed
and like Finn is kind of right on top of you
like Optimus Prime was,
and he gives you some sort of instruction or whatever.
It's the being on top of that's required.
Or underneath, they could be on the side
as long as they're closer underneath you.
That's actual, I'm just saying
as long as there's something to the closeness.
We all were dealing with six feet,
the six feet rule during COVID.
Is it also the six feet rule of friendship?
If he's within six feet, is he your friend?
Yeah, I think that's pretty good.
I would love closer.
Like when I go on Snow White at Disneyland,
those dwarves are like two feet.
I could really mess up that ride if I wanted to.
Anybody could.
If you have long enough arms,
you really could just smack stuff, knock things over.
You have so much power
and everyone has so much respect for Disneyland
that they don't ruin those dark rides.
It's kind of blows my mind
that people don't just try to rip things off the wall
when they're on those dark rides.
That's true, yeah, yeah.
So yeah, the closer the better when it comes to that stuff.
It helps.
It helps forge friendships if you're within six feet.
Well, let's answer this question though,
because this is tough.
You gotta kill one.
These are three qualities you love.
These three qualities I love.
I guess I gotta kill, oh, I hate to say it.
I guess I gotta kill intimacy.
And I got to marry my friends
and I've got to F thrills, you know?
You've gotta fuck fucking you up.
I have to fuck fucking me up.
Because that's still a part of it
is getting to have your body experience something
that it doesn't get to experience in regular life.
So I think that's my answer.
Wow, there you go.
I'm glad you stuck to one.
That's a very tough one, the teddy.
I don't like it.
It makes me uncomfortable to answer it.
Do you want to?
I got something, okay.
So Michelle asks if you could replace one song
on Cosmic Rewind, which one are you removing
and what are you replacing it with?
What are all six of them?
Okay, so the question.
On Cosmic Rewind, not the other one,
not Mission Break again.
Right, Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind in Epcot.
There are what, six songs?
Or September, everybody wants to rule the world
one way or another, Konga, I Ran,
By Flock of Seagulls, Disco Inferno.
Oh, and the Eternal Dance?
Or is that, that's all of them, I think?
Eternal Dance.
No, this AI shit is giving me the wrong, I think.
Why do we, we used to have, you would search.
They would just come to the top,
like why is this AI crap on the top?
Just you would search something
and then you would get one set of results.
Now you get two sets of results and one sucks.
And that's the one, that's the one that's claimed
that on Sea Hunt, they had used a ventriloquist dummy.
That's what fucked you up with that?
I think, cause the stupid.
These AI searches.
Bullshit, wait, okay, so it's I Ran, Disco Inferno, Konga,
everybody wants to rule the world
one way or another in September.
Those are the songs.
I haven't gotten to do it, I've only done it
with one of these, I've only done it with Konga.
As far as, I just find like Disco Inferno
to be maybe the most like, maybe too obvious
of a song or something or like a two wedding of a song.
But then what do I replace it with that?
Yeah.
I mean, this can be a very indulgent answer, I think.
Like I'm not gonna, we could try to think of
what would appeal to everyone and what is like high energy.
I think it has to just be us, yes.
Well, I mean, my knee jerk is because I'm a yacht guy.
So I don't know, is this song more energetic
than Disco Inferno?
Possibly not, but I just want a yacht coaster.
So my temptation is to say Ride Like the Wind.
That would be cool.
I think it'd be good on a coaster.
I think that would be also kind of a crowd pleaser
actually, in addition to.
I think that would fit in that lineup of songs.
I think people would be,
oh, I got it with Ride Like the Wind.
Yeah.
No, and that wouldn't be so out of place either,
I feel like too.
So I think you actually did a pretty good
universal job of choosing.
Yeah.
Or what about, you know, like maybe a second place
is like Saucudio.
Saucudio would be pretty good.
Yeah.
That would be good.
Yeah, it would get fired up for Saucudio, I think.
Right.
I'm trying to think of something that like,
I like, I am trying to break your heart by Wilco
would be really interesting.
Cause again, I want to feel like sad and strange,
which is why I'm so like, I'm so like,
next time we're in Florida, I am,
my big goal is to get everybody wants to rule the world.
Just cause I want to feel the moodiness.
So I want to feel like strange, I want to like,
that song, if you haven't heard it is very like,
that's a very headphone song,
where like a lot of instruments kind of come in and out,
and there's like kind of unique one-off
little things happening, this alarm clock at the start of it.
I just want to like, kind of like zone out while I'm on this
ride.
It's like, I don't know,
can you be able to zone out?
No, I guess.
And it's like, you'll miss some of the,
you'll miss some of the subtle instrumentation of that song.
But I'm trying to think of there's,
there's another song by LCD sound system.
I would like, called losing my edge that I really like
from their first album or second album.
Does it resonate with you for some reason?
Yes, it's always has.
It's like eight minutes long though.
So they'd have to cut it.
It'd be a big radio.
But yes, it is a song about a guy who is losing his edge,
who feels the kids are coming up from behind.
And he's like saying all the stuff he's seen and done
that he like to give himself credit.
It's a funny song also, the credibility.
He had at one point, he even says,
James Murphy says in the song, he says like,
I have all the good Beach Boys records, like he explains.
So he's like kind of losing his mind to explain.
And I'm like, this is, it's a very like,
it's kind of the same groove for eight minutes,
but it's a funny song.
So like one of those, cause that's sort of very hip.
It's a very hypnotic beat too.
So I just like, I'm really want somebody to put songs
on roller coasters now that are like,
that really change the mood from just like high energy
or something.
That's becoming more intriguing to me.
You're trying to get,
you're trying to get a thinky roller coaster.
A thinky, yeah.
Maybe these aren't the right songs.
So if it's not gonna, if it's not gonna fork you up
and you want it to fork you up emotionally.
I would love it to do that.
Yeah.
Like maybe like a, dude, was there a,
there wasn't a Pink Floyd coaster at Hard Rock Park, right?
Was Pink Floyd in there anywhere?
I don't know.
And I'm not a big Pink Floyd guy.
I'm just trying to think of like something universally
or like very popular that's kind of trippy or weird.
I feel like Knights in White Sadden might be the most,
like the headiest song, like pop song ever used in a.
Probably.
Yeah.
But yeah, one of those, I would really,
I would really do it, it would be indulgent
and people would be confused.
Yeah. Yeah.
That would be.
Yeah, but poorly attended ride.
Poor, yeah, we'll close very soon.
But yeah, I am trying to break your heart, Wilco Coaster.
I mean, there's high energy.
LCD sound blaster.
Well, Jason could get in on this
because this is like some of the same popular
during his New Pornographers era,
which I also am a big fan of.
From the 10 months where he paid attention to music
until he got a fiance who pays attention
to current pop music.
If we could open it way back up.
If we could add like an early to mid 2000s era
Hard Rock Park, Strokes, like Spoon, College Rock,
Hold Steady, all these bands.
I think that would be,
I think we could flush something out there.
Yeah.
We've been threatening to get John Minkowski
on the show for years, but this is, this would be.
We did get a question about that,
about what Hard Rock Park and the, yeah.
Well, that's a good, I mean, that's a good land.
I think you could fit it all in there,
but yeah, early 2000s land.
Yes.
You know, MTV2 land, you might think of it.
Yeah.
Wow, I got pretty fucked up on the Ted Leo coaster.
That was from Cody, credit to Cody on that question.
Yeah, there would be, yeah.
Who suggested the John Resnick slide in that area
and the tunnel of Mike Love.
Oh yeah, that would be perfect.
Hey, sign me up, good vibrations.
Maybe a quick one on the way out the door.
Yeah, yeah, go for it.
Robert Warner, will you make it to Pizza Rizzo
before it shuts down in May?
And I want to answer this because maybe it'll hold us
to doing it because we've.
All right, I'll let you say it.
Yes.
I think we gotta do it.
We're gonna try.
I think we're gonna try.
It is a goal to try.
It makes sense, you know, it's closing
in the similar neck of the woods
to when another big theme park development is opening.
Uh-huh.
Which is obviously much less of a priority
than Pizza Rizzo.
And I've recently declared all the things
I hope stay open for us to get to Orlando,
and I think maybe they're all gonna be open.
They might all still be there.
We will get to do before they go away, so.
I figure if we just like, if we, you know,
it's hard for me to just say it
with a lot of, you know, assuredness,
but we'd like to, we'd like to.
Robert.
Wouldn't that be, wouldn't that be good?
At last, the Pizza Rizzo episode.
Wouldn't that be good to do?
Wouldn't that be their last day?
Have you ever been to a last day of a ride?
I'm sure I've asked this before, but.
I don't think I have.
We did Great Movie Ride last day.
Just by happenstance.
Wow, I forgot that.
We were just, we had booked a trip,
and then they announced it was the last day,
so we got to go like 11 a.m., the day of the last,
the last day of Great Movie Ride, and it was really fun.
Everybody was really excited.
Motion's gotta be high for that, yeah.
I watched videos of the last ride,
and it's kinda interesting to like,
drift off the feeling of that.
It's an interesting vibe, and I assume Muppets
would be even stronger, and an even more interesting vibe
at Pizza Rizzo and at the actual Muppets 3D.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I don't know, we'll see.
Okay, hope to be there at Pizza Rizzo
while there is still a Pizza Rizzo.
Yeah.
I think with that, you survived podcast The Ride.
Scott and Mike runnin' the post office.
Thanks for subscribing.
If you wanna dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month,
and our regular episodes ad free.
Hey, and why not?
I'm also gonna throw in,
because this will encourage me to finish this thing.
James McKinnon, can we get a session
of the previously teased infinite playlist feature,
hoping for some banger AOR,
or GRP passport jazz type wrecks from Scott,
and I don't know, Olivia Rodriguez,
or something equally hip from Mike.
Well, that's one thing Mike can tell you
with certainty, is that it's Rodrigo.
And as for me, this did encourage,
basically, I have to finish it,
but by the time you're hearing this click in the show notes,
if you think you align with my music taste,
like the aforementioned Ride Like the Wind,
I put together a playlist called Yacht by Ski-Yacht.
I'm still shaping,
I wanna keep it a reasonable amount of tracks,
like 11 to 13, something like that,
but of lesser known non-hit yacht rock songs
that I think prove why I love the genre,
and why I think there's a lot of emotion,
and feel, and why it's resonated with me.
As Weezer would say,
I put a lot of my heart songs on here.
They're all very important to me.
It's still in progress,
but James, if you wanna hear it, or anybody else,
I mean, look, I got Mark Jordan on there.
I got Pages on there.
I got Larson Featon Band.
Is Homie and Jarvis gonna stay?
I gotta decide.
These are the things that'll be weighing on me
before you end up hearing this episode,
but if you wanna hear the kinda bullshit I like.
If I remember, I'll make a playlist too.
I love making playlists.
What do you think's on there?
God, it depends what mood it is.
I mean, I could, at this point,
make an old Hillbilly Nonsense playlist too,
like with Hawk Shaw Hawkins.
I believe that's the gentleman
who does the song Rattlesnake and Daddy,
so I could do an old Hillbilly Nonsense playlist.
It's really a pick your poison.
Do you want the host,
do you want the host who knows some songs from right now
because of who he's engaged to?
Or do you want the host who mainly likes music
from before he was born,
but he's perfectly comfortable with that?
I've been fake-and-pilled for so long,
I have no desire to fight it.
Or do you want the host who likes a lot
of Hillbilly Nonsense songs from 100 years ago?
Right, if it's an older, yeah.
There's a lot of different things.
Yeah, I saw somebody tweet that like,
because I mentioned MJ Lenderman recently,
and somebody has drawn the parallel of like,
all the Wilco dads have switched to MJ Lenderman.
Oh, I see.
And then somebody was like, yeah, I thought,
well, I think he sounds more like the drive-by truckers
or pavement.
And I was like, mm-hmm, he does do that too.
This is what I'm saying.
I think we don't have to be so sweaty
in liking what the kids like
because they make new music for us.
No, they do, I listen to all of it.
If you're fake-and-pilled, you move to Benny Sings
or a myriad of other, Young Gun Silver Fox
or a bunch of things of that nature.
There's new music for us.
When that guy came up, something you said was like,
and he's, I think, 23 years old.
You were excited by his age.
You don't have to care about what age the person is.
This is my persona.
This is my persona on the show.
You meet me in real life.
I'm just like, MJ Lenderman is cool, man.
I'm gonna go there.
My dad likes him.
My sister likes him.
We're gonna go see the show.
I'm so much cooler in real life.
On the show, this is all this character I play.
You know what I'm saying?
But then that tone you went into felt so natural, so cool,
not like a character or a choice at all.
No, that was my real self.
Yeah, real Mike's like, no, I'm not even like that.
Honestly, I don't even remember how old he is.
Is he 25 in six months?
Is he 25 in one month?
I don't even know.
That's not what, it's about the music to me.
You ever listen to the band Mannequin Pussy?
I do.
It's rock and roll.
It's all the same to me, man.
I'm comfortable saying pussy.
I'll say it all day.
I say pussy off the show all the time.
I love it, man.
I'll go fuck some pussy, dude.
I mean, I don't say that as much.
I just say it like if it's a name of a band I like,
but I still am comfortable saying it, no problem.
I don't know why it got higher there.
Keep going.
Ah, ah, ah.
I don't know, I like band Mannequin Pussy.