FOREVER!
DOG!
In 2003,
filmmaker-actor-auteur Tommy
Wiseau released his directorial debut,
The Room. The landscape
of cinema was forever changed,
as was the life of eventual podcast
The Ride host, Scott Gertner.
The linchpin in this tale? Today's
guest, who starred in the cult
classic and helped Wiseau chase his dream.
And the best part? This guy
loves theme parks.
If you know and love The Room, you're in for a treat.
If you don't, stay tuned
for a big old Disney World nerd out.
It's all HyParks
with The Room's Greg Sestero
on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast
The Ride, where we believe
if a lot of people love theme
parks, the world would be
a better place to live.
I'm Scott Gertner. Everybody
betray me. I'm fed up with Disney
World. But I'm
so happy I have you as my co-host.
It seems to me like you're a theme
park expert, Mike!
Oh, thank you. Yeah. You know, whatever
it's interesting what you're doing.
You're channeling something.
Do I sound a little different or something?
A little bit, but not much. Not much, but a little bit.
There's some indiscernible
accent, unplaceable, no particular
like the kind of accent
where, you know, the person
would not ever answer what the accent
is or where it came from. Not important.
No, no, no. Doesn't matter. The mystery is
part of it. Yeah.
Well, look, I will open up a little
to anyone who doesn't understand any of what I
was just saying and why.
And say that if you don't know
what any of that was, then you
are clearly not familiar with Tommy
Wiseau's 2003 feature film
The Room. It is a
eternal
tale of love, lust, and betrayal
that I believe has
rightfully taken the mantle of
the most deliriously fun bad
movie ever made.
I believe it rose to number one.
Anybody tried
to dethrone it. I don't
think you could. Mike, you know that
I'm very passionate about this film. Of course.
Yeah. I think we've talked about it before.
There's a long history with me
and this film, which is why I've
been so excited for this
episode for a long time.
Been trying to put together for
forever. And I'm so happy we're
here finally because we are today
joined by one of the
key figures in the story of
The Room, Johnny's best friend
Mark himself, the writer
of an amazing book about his experience called
A Disaster Artist, which was turned into a Golden Globe
winning feature film.
But for you, the podcast,
The Ride Listener, what does all of this mean
to you if you don't know The Room? Well, I'm
thrilled to say that our guest is also
one of the biggest Disney Parks fans
I've ever run into.
So there is a ton to talk about and a ton
to do with our guest today. Greg Sestero.
Yeah. Oh, hi, Scott.
Yay.
I mean, yeah, this episode
is 20,
over 20 years in the making. We've known each other.
We officially met
in February of 2004.
God, yeah, you knew the you knew the month
even. You remember the specific screening
where you finally where you like joined
the fray of all
of the weirdos making their way to
your film on the other side
after I'm sure what must have been
like a strange period after the
completion of the movie.
I think with any actor, writer,
you always remember the first time you've
been in something that
like has a fan.
And I remember, so I'd been in
a movie called Retro Puppet Master.
So really, maybe without you, Scott,
that's all I would have is Retro Puppet Master.
Wow. And you'd be you'd be dependent
on some weird nerdy
mega fan base of Retro Puppet
Master, which there must be that at some
point. I think there is, but there's something about
The Room like coming to that screening
and seeing you
guys quote it.
Like I, again, I like I was telling you earlier, I saw
myself in you
because when I was 19 and I saw Tommy
perform in acting class,
I was quoting him.
We talked on the phone for hours because I just
loved hearing him talk and say things.
You might have been 19? You were that young?
Oh, wow, yeah.
July 11, 1998,
I saw him perform Shakespeare.
And I was like, this is, man, this is
so much, this is more fun than I've ever had in acting class.
Like I don't really care about doing
David Mamet or any of this crap they're pushing on us.
This guy is like
where it's at. And so I approached
him to do a scene together and we
like get this really weird reaction.
He's like, what does this guy want with me?
No one in the class wants to even be
around him. He's like, yeah,
we can do a scene together, but I warn
you, we need to rehearse.
I'm a very serious
actor. And I was like,
hell yeah, let's do it. He's like, well,
I have a busy schedule, okay? So we
meet, you know, Bank of America, 3 p.m.,
Market Street, and don't be late.
Bank of America.
I was like, does he work at Bank of America?
I gotta see this guy in action.
So I go to Bank of America, of course, there's nobody there.
And so I'm sitting
outside Bank of America
on Market Street holding my soccer
ball because I'd go to Golden Gate
Park and play soccer in the summer.
And I was like 99% sure he wouldn't show up.
And then I was like, now it's 20 minutes.
And I was like, okay, do I just start walking?
But then I was like, I just want to see what kind
of car this guy drives.
If he showed up, would it be a hearse?
I picture him in like an ice cream
truck and can't turn off the siren.
This is a person, as we've said,
if you're viewing the film for the first
time, you can't put
Tommy Wiseau in a box. You've never
seen anyone like this. You can't go,
he's this type of person, this type of person.
Is he gothic?
Is he undead?
What type of person am I looking at?
Visually, when I saw him come up on stage,
he had like a vampire Michael Jackson thing
going on.
So like you just said,
what does he show up in?
A brand new Mercedes.
So I get
in and I'm like, oh, nice car. And he's like,
look, don't talk about me.
He's like, in class, people talk, you know
what I'm saying? And I was like, oh yeah,
no problem. And so he
got like a little strange and I was like looking
and analyzing him. And then I see this like Burger King
crab thing attached to his
air conditioner. Like something like a
Transformers discount
Happy Meal toy.
Any familiar, you don't recognize this line?
I'm just trying to think, like there was the McDonald's
ones that like would transform from a burger to a robot
or something? Is it something like that? But this was like, this was
its own thing because it wasn't attached to any
franchise. It was like just
enough to be better than Happy Meal, but like
I didn't know what the hell it was.
And so I was like looking at it and
he's like, don't stare too long, he
may bite you.
So I'm sitting there in the car going like, okay, why
did I think this would be fun?
And then he's like, I need to
eat right now because I get cranky
if I don't eat. I'm sorry.
Don't worry, I pay. I'm like
alright, so we go
to this pasta pomodoro
on like, I don't know,
Mission Street or something. Immediately after the bank's
not part of it. He just picked you up and immediately
went somewhere else. And it wasn't like, it wasn't
the ideal place to pick up. There's a lot of people
honking in traffic. So
now we're in near Golden Gate Park
and we go to this restaurant and he orders
like all these dishes.
And so he pulls out
the play and hands me the scene. He's like
let's start reading the scene.
And so I was like, okay,
what scene? And I start reading and he's like, your
voice is too low.
You need to go up.
It's monotone. You know what this means?
And I was like, yeah.
So he's like pushing
it and he's like, it's still
too low.
And so I remember we finish
the lunch
and we finish the scene and I was like, okay,
maybe this isn't what I expected. Maybe it's
time to go to the park or do
something. And he's like, hey, wait. I see
you have this ball.
This ball. You want
to play, huh? I'm so jealous
you got so much extra time with this
man. All we get is the movie and the
interviews. You have this whole wealth of
years with the strangest
man anyone's ever seen. And so he's like,
let's go play soccer. And so we go
play soccer. He's dressed in like black
dress pants and like a white button down.
And he's doing his best. He's chasing
the ball and we're playing. And we're in Golden Gate
Park. The fog in
the summer is like, you can barely
see each other. It's like just us there.
And he's like, hey, come here. You're a good
spore. I have a secret for you. I was like,
yeah, sure. Go ahead. He's like, closer.
There's nobody there. We're in the middle of this
like huge soccer field.
Come closer. I was like, yeah.
I have a secret. Guess what?
I was like, what? Come closer.
Vampire live here.
Whoa.
Really? He's like, yeah, but not just
any vampire. Vampire from
Alcatraz.
I was like, it's him, isn't it?
So that's how it's
started. And he
he became more and more like
charming as time went on. Like he was
a tough read. Sure. But the quotes
were coming. He's like, let's go play soccer.
Let's go. Let's go
eat, huh? We'd go and so we just
said all that stuff. Yeah. Wow. And we'd
rehearse. And then I remember
it was like we did one more rehearsal
and then we went to this Chinese restaurant
on Sansom Street in San
Francisco. And we were sitting there talking
and he's like, I have I have dream.
And I'm like, OK.
I want to have my own planet.
And he starts
describing what he wants.
And I remember staring at him and
I got these goosebumps and I was like,
something big is going to happen
with this man. I was like, no,
there's no rhyme or reason to it. I just looked at him
and I got these like chills.
This is going to be an important
factor. I don't know what it is. And I was at
a super low point because
the week before I met him, I had gone
on these bunch of auditions
living in San Francisco. It's hard to get films
because they weren't really filming up there.
It was a movie called Wildflowers
with Eric Roberts, which at the time
was a big deal. Yeah. Oh, sure.
Yeah. And so it was
he's still he's still kicking, right?
Nobody works more than Eric Roberts.
That's true. So I went to three
callbacks, played this bad boy boyfriend
opposite Clea Duvall,
who I didn't know at the time.
I worked with her. That's funny.
Yeah. And so I went back
for the third callback
and it was like my agent told me, like, you're on
hold. You're going to get it. And I remember
getting the call that Monday that
I got released. And it was like
the worst feeling because I was like, now
what? Now what do I do? Yeah.
I've done a few commercials
like back then moving to L.A. was a lot more challenging.
And then I meet Tom.
That sort of led me to Tom. That was like
I met Tommy that next
that night. This is so cinematic.
The down and out.
You're at what could be your lowest.
Which puts you in like a fuck it
state. I was in a total fuck it
state. I had no answer. I had no agent.
I had no plan.
It was like get that role and then that was
going to like jump start you.
And I remember just being like
do I just give up? And then it was like
then I met Tommy. It was crazy.
Crazy timing. Wow. All of these.
Oh my god. I could hear these quotes from this man
forever. But I guess what I should drive to
is the how does
this coalesce into
and some of this is obviously
portrayed in a movie
which was created. Congrats on that.
But like in terms of Cliftonets
how does it become
this guy reveals that he has this
cinematic dream and then you help him
shepherd it along and appear in it
yourself. So we connected like tight
in those few weeks during the acting
class. And we were on a road
trip. We were lost.
And he asked me you know class is
over. What do you like to do? And I was like
I mean I want to
go to L.A. But it's tough.
You know I've been working like a bunch of jobs trying to put
money aside. But like where do I start?
He's like why you tell me I have a place
in Los Angeles?
And I was like a place. Yeah
I have an apartment. I can rent you $200
a month. Wow. Geez.
And I remember I was driving. We were lost. There was no
GPS. I don't know where the hell we were but I'm like
holy crap. This is this was
that's why I didn't get that part.
I knew it was like this was the freaking answer. So
we go I go back home that night
all of a sudden I was like he's like yeah I have to go
next week. You can check out place. It's yours.
And I was like
sure. And so then I had to explain
this to my mom and my mom had seen
a picture of Tommy and thought like
there's no way you're going to associate with this guy.
Like he looks like he's been through the ringer.
So he comes
to pick me up at Walnut Creek Bar station
and my mom has to come meet him. That's the
rule. We go up and Tommy
looks like he's been doing meth for like 60 hours
like exhausted. She's like she
has an accent too. She's a French accent. But she's like
hey you know how old are you? And he's like
oh Greg's age.
Twenty eight.
And she's like
sure. And what do you want with Greg? Like what's
your what's your draw? And she's like he's a cool guy.
And she was like I was like
mom we got to go. Like he's got a meeting. She's like what
meeting? Oh I do business.
It's the movie. Oh my god.
No answers. And then finally
she says to him Tommy
no sex. And I thought like
ooh he's just going to shrug it off. But he goes
well we all do.
So anyway we had she lets me go.
We make it to LA.
And we pull up. It's on Crescent Heights and
Fountain. I was
expecting the worst. We show up. It's like a nice place.
The security.
He can't get into the security gate because he's like I
can't remember code. What is code?
And then he pulls out these crumpled pieces of paper and the
code was one two three four.
So we get in.
And the play there's no
furniture in this place. There's one bed.
And like
there's a bunch of Hollywood reporters thrown all over.
Years before.
It felt like Sunset Boulevard.
I always whenever I see Sunset Boulevard
I think of the first night with Tommy.
There's Hollywood reporters everywhere.
And he's like don't rush you.
You can take if you like. I was like this is actually this could
work. So I remember I sleep on the floor
and he's in the
shower singing
A Whole New World from Aladdin.
Whoa. Wow.
That ties it to us. Oh my god.
Which he was singing by the way
in general. I don't know if I've heard it.
Does he sing? Yeah he started to sing
more. Oh really? Oh interesting.
Is this available anywhere? Is there an album?
Yeah please. I'll send you. I got a link to
like a Christmas song that he sang. Whoa.
Wow.
So he's singing A Whole New World.
I'm sleeping on the floor and then he gets out
and he sleeps in the bed.
It's a small
studio. Yeah.
So the bed's like right there and the door's somewhat closed
and I'm like kind of half asleep and I hear
somebody's chicken.
Oh my god. Oh no.
And so I just thought like oh just Tommy
being Tommy but yeah I think I am a chicken
I'm gonna fall asleep. So I fell asleep.
I end up convincing
my mom that I'm gonna take the apartment.
So I move down
to, I drive down
in my crappy car
that barely works. September 18th
1998. Drive down
to San Francisco. No plan.
I'm just going and I had the key.
Drive down, get to Hollywood around
1.30 in the morning. I pull up to the apartment.
I go up to the place.
You know a lot of emotions
going on. You're like is this gonna work? What am I thinking?
I didn't really pack much.
Go to open the door.
The key doesn't work. So now I'm stranded
in Hollywood. Now you live in your car.
Yeah now I'm stranded in Hollywood.
The strange man you followed didn't make
good. My mom told me
don't like don't do this. Big mistake.
I'm like is she right?
So I go to the Chevron on
Creston Heights and Sunset. I'm trying to collect
call. And he's like hi
I'm listening. And I'm like your key doesn't work.
Oh yes it does. You just don't know how to
do it. And I was like okay
I need to find it's 2.30 in the morning now and
I drive down Sunset Boulevard and
there's like it's so intimidating. There's like the
strip clubs packed with people.
I have like little
to no cash and I pull up to a place called the
Saharan Motel.
And the guy's like screaming at me your
car doesn't fit in here. Yelling.
I ended up staying in there
that night and there was like at that point it was like a
stripper like hotel. Just like walking
in and out. So that's where I spent my first
night in Hollywood. A stripper motel.
What a deep end of Hollywood.
I ended up getting the door
open eventually. And
I got, I landed Iris
Burton agency who represented
like Joaquin Phoenix, River Phoenix.
And on my fourth audition
I
booked the lead in
Retro Puppemaster. Wow. Wow.
And I just couldn't believe it was like such a crazy
turn of events. So I
go and I tell Tommy I go to San Francisco
and I say you're not going to believe this Tommy
but like thanks to you
I booked the lead in this film.
And his reaction you
start screaming oh my god I need
candy.
And he's like starts eating all
these chocolates and stuff so
so anyway I film
Retro Puppemaster in Bucharest
Romania. Wow.
Straight from San Francisco to Hollywood
to Romania. Wow. Which was yeah
which was out there. And then so when I move back
to LA, when I come back to LA
Tommy's now living in the apartment.
Oh good. Good news. He's like
oh yeah if you can do it I can
do it too. So all of a sudden. You gotta be
glad to have him there just to ensure that you
don't become a chicken. True. True.
Keep your chicken meter up.
So
now we're roommates.
And he's going hardcore at Hollywood.
He is sending his headshots out.
He's going like all out.
He's trying to audition. He's doing what you're doing.
Yeah. So when I first got in
I mailed out all my headshots with
the Iris Byrne agency logo. And I got a meeting
at Disney Studios like a general meeting
because they're like oh she represents
Joaquin Phoenix or River Phoenix
or Kirsten Dunst like this she must
but it wasn't her sending out the headshots
it was me. Sure. So they're like
Iris believes in this guy. She's like oh I just
signed him like he seems
like a cool kid. Like can he act?
A lot of good early buzz
from Retro Puppemaster. Yeah.
That was a tough one. One of the best Puppemaster films.
So Tommy
goes hardcore. It's a really toxic
living situation.
For many reasons he's up till
5 a.m. My agent
can't call because he'll pick up and be like
don't call here it's too early. Hang up.
So it was not going well.
And then I remember it was the Night of the Golden
Globes that year. Talented Mr.
Ripley was nominated. I took him to see it.
And he's like he
watches the film. He really gets
into it. And he tells me
after. He's like you know Hollywood think this is
drama. Well I'm sorry. They have surprise
coming. I will write a movie
and when people see my movie they will
not sleep for two weeks.
I was like alright.
He's called the room. He knew
that already. He's called the room.
It all takes place in one room.
I will play Johnny. Sort of.
It was
supposed to be an early idea.
Like a theatrical play initially.
He's saying you will play Mark like
this guy Mark Damon.
Mark's last name is
Damon?
It was supposed to be based on
Matt Damon. But because of
Talented Mr. Ripley he's trying to like
re-imagine the story.
Wow that's interesting.
But he called him Mark Damon so that's why it's Mark.
Mark Damon is a misremembering.
Whoa that's incredible mythology.
So he's like that's what's going to happen. So he starts
writing the script while we're roommates.
And he's now separated the apartment.
So now he's got the living room
locked off with these
black curtains. I have the bedroom now.
So now he's the chicken.
And so he's typing and typing
and he'd yell out like Greg how long is movie
script? How do you format? He'd ask me all
these questions. And so this
goes on for a few months and then
remember he was taking acting
classes on Brian Reese
studio like cold reading classes.
And he just tells me one night like I just don't think
like I fit in here and I think I'm going to take a break.
And he like disappears
for nine months. I don't know where he went.
I get these cryptic phone calls.
It's got to be a relief on some
level. You get nine months to yourself.
I was kind of worried like where
did he go? Because he was so big on
the acting thing. Big on the script and he just disappeared.
And then it was
so that but nine
months later I had like moved
I was living across the street. A buddy of mine
moved to London to do like tech
stuff at the time. It was like 2000. So
that was booming. So I wasn't even
living in that apartment. And then Tommy
comes back. I remember the day May 7th
2001. He says
I'm coming back from San Francisco. I want to see you.
So I go back over to the apartment
and he hands me a script
called The Room.
He's like I want you to read this here. You can't
take home. Like when you meet
on a marvel. Yeah right.
Christopher Nolan.
And so I sit there initially thinking
he's going to sort of reveal what's happened to him
in the last nine months.
And so I start reading it and I'm just
like this is my favorite thing ever. Every
character sounds like Tommy.
I'm very busy. I'm very busy. You're my
best friend. Peter you're my best friend.
Everyone coming and going all the time.
Everyone has somewhere to be. Enters
rooms. Immediately leaves rooms. No matter what
your age is you always have
somewhere else you have to go goodbye.
It was always like hello how are you today? Peter's like
did you get any clients Lisa?
No I didn't. Maybe tomorrow will be your
lucky day. It was like AI before
AI. And also
well to speak to our you know like Mike's
improv history the thing they tell
you like don't just have characters introduce
themselves to each other. Come in say
hello and then get like it
is like it violates all these like rules
of what make interesting scenes you know.
Yeah and it was just so him
and he's like so what do you think?
You see reflections of your life?
And I was like I do I do.
And that's how like it
started. He's like we need to make this
this film. We need to make this.
A few weird
things went down where he was like
wanted me to help him cast it and then
my girlfriend at the time read
it and some of the dialogue
she read out loud and it was one of the funniest
scenes. I wish it was in the film but it ended up
getting changed but it's like Michelle tells
Lisa oh I thought the wedding was all
playing with Johnny. How was Mark in bed?
It was like out of nowhere
out of nowhere and so she reads it she's like you're not
doing this.
So like there's this fallout because Tommy's
like you believe girl over me
and my god. Was it hard also
to now you're like you're eschewing
important people in your life to follow
this man. And I was telling her at the time that
Tommy was my cousin.
I knew she wouldn't get it.
I knew she would think like this is
If this is a person you can leave
at any time why would you not leave him?
Yeah exactly and so she didn't understand we had
like a bond starting from the acting class
like we both really wanted to make
movies and she would I knew she wouldn't get that.
So we had we had kind of like a little break
and then
it was August it was August
of 2002 he tells
me Greg I will give
you one job because we're going to move into this other
apartment I was trying to figure out what I was going to do.
I offer you a hundred dollars
come over 3 p.m. So I go over to
his apartment and he's got like five thousand
headshots because he put an ad
for Backstage West for the room.
He's like open headshot
pay you a hundred dollars. So I was like oh okay.
So I start opening headshots
and I was like
this is really therapeutic because now I'm
seeing what other
people are seeing behind the scenes
casting and all that. So I start opening all these
headshots and I all of a sudden
instantly become like the casting director
for the room.
And Tommy's got these HD cameras
like bought all the equipment. So I
go with him and I set up the
cameras and I call in all these
actors and honestly
watching Tommy audition
actors was the funniest thing
I've ever seen. Because people come in
and they're like
hey do you have a script? No
get in front of camera. They're like whoa
okay oh just up on your feet.
Okay you just won one million dollars
and they're like
so cut
where is acting?
And this
went on for weeks. It was the greatest
time ever. So that's
how it all started.
I wasn't going to be Mark
because I was like I don't think I should be in this.
At this point you're like
does this do me any good
to have my face in this movie?
Might be a big detriment in fact.
And back then it was a lot tighter. Indie film wasn't
something that was thriving
the way it is now. So it was like I was auditioning
for Terminator 3.
I had done Days of Our Lives so
this was something that
I was still aspiring
was something that like
more like would never go anywhere
because of the way the situation was set up.
You would imagine. You're like this is cool.
You're going to make a movie. What is that?
This odd guy wants to make a movie.
What could possibly become of that?
Yeah and I figured okay it's something he wanted to do
but he was taking it so seriously. But I was
sort of the glue
that was holding it all together. I was the one that they would come to
and be like is this legit?
You seem cool. What are you doing here?
And they'd be like is this really going to happen?
So I was sort of the one keeping it together
but what I will say is
making The Room was the best
film school because
so much was on my back to produce it and keep
it going that I realized how
the general sense
of producing a movie goes.
And it was like dealing with people
and the DP and what they need
and the morale on a set.
So it was such a crazy experience
and it opened me up to not just wanting
to like act but also
be involved in behind the scenes
writing, producing.
It was such a crazy
gift to go through that
and see how it works
on the other side. And in some cases
like the worst case
scenario. Yeah it was like how important
collaboration is.
Because it was like
it was Tommy's vision and then
the actors didn't have a script. So they're like
wow. You know so it was
he had this vision
that no one else. That could not be strayed from
seemingly. That's what's odd is everybody
you feel everybody like stuck
doing precisely the
strange specific words
of this guy. But
you feel everybody like
trying to like break out and find
meaning in these phrases that like seem
like nothing just on their
face. It's the most like auteur
driven movie.
Like one single vision.
Yes. Because even even the greatest
directors there's plenty of people they rely
on. But this does feel like everyone's coming
came together to try to channel this
one man's brain. And
then that also it also taught me how
important it is to have a vision.
Sure. You know because it's like
if he just kind
of went and improv'd it and whatever he wouldn't have
that intense
emotional strange charm.
Oh sure. It has to be plotted out
to some extent. Yeah. Yeah. Because if you just
if they just like literally improvise the whole
thing. I think the thing that's so hypnotic
about it is that everything like
it seems every line feels like it
should have like meaning
or something behind it. But what
does it mean? Why does everybody just come in
and then leave immediately and like
all these odd phrases and we see
you should not think too much.
It may not come out right. What is this?
Why does this have scary music behind it?
Why are they on a rooftop?
Why do people keep falling? It's just
an endless series of lies
that 20 years later
there's still no real answer for most of
them. Yeah. It's like these things that
could almost work like randomly
Denny looks at Mark
and they have a moment it's like oh did he
look at him because like the drugs are on the roof
or there's just all these questions
that sort of line up. And I think it all
came down to
you know the earnest
creative expression, the frustration
of whatever Tommy had gone through in life
was just represented
in that film. Geez. Yeah. So Mission
Accomplished. Well so that's alright
to start bringing it into the
well 2003 where our paths
merge finally.
So this
you make the film, you finish
the film and you get like
miraculously a little like theatrical
run. You get to what it's two
theaters in Los Angeles for
two weeks and you did
a screening, you did a premiere.
Am I correct that there were
spotlights during the day
at the premiere? Yes. Yep.
Those were Tommy's spotlights that he brought out.
He owned them? Yeah.
God the mystery
of this guy. How do you own spotlights?
He would use them at his stores in
retail stores in San Francisco. I helped him a few
nights on Haight Street and he'd put the Sky
Trackers on Haight Street.
Really? Wow. People were like, sale let's all
go. So I think he again he utilized
a lot of those marketing skills. And that's what some of
it is. He owned all these weird stores in San
Francisco. I mean you get into some of
this in the book and the way you go to San Francisco with him
and he just has a key for everything.
Just a
enigma. It's so fascinating.
But so at this
juncture there's a premiere
it's going to
be in theaters for two weeks. Do you have
any sense of
what did you think was going to happen at that
point? Nothing.
I just remember I went to the premier
I was moving places in LA
and I just
had given so much of my life to helping
Tommy getting the film done.
Five years?
You give him five years of your life.
Yeah it had been
quite a journey especially
producing the room. I was there through the whole
thing and helped him with post and
I think I was like yeah okay
you put the billboard up, the premiere
and that was it. I figured I would just move on
the project was done
so I went to the premiere
and it was really funny to finally
have an audience watch it that had no idea
what was going on.
I remember these two critics in the lobby talking
like they walked out like ten minutes in
and the one guy said to his buddy I'll never get
hard again.
So that was funny
but I thought
If you haven't seen the room, and by the way
big encouragement to any of our audience
to see the room if you haven't seen the room
but the treat of Tommy
with his naked backside
which isn't even, you see his butt
during the sex scenes
but then you really see it when he just
gets up to go to the bathroom
and that's another why.
All nudity in film has some
intention, either it's for
sensual purposes
or it's to show somebody's vulnerability
and this is just like I'm going to go to Cannes
and you just follow him naked for no
what does that do other than
making the audience all yell and recoil?
You know what he told me right before that?
He said Greg I have to do it.
I was like
what now?
I have to show my ass to sell this movie.
He's like you know Brando would do it
and I was like
yeah it's true but I thought that was it
and then he literally went out and straight
up did it.
So maybe that was the most calculated
thing of like this is going to help
sell it. Like he literally
a little nudity is making him
titillate people and make them excited
to see it. Yeah mission accomplished.
I also think it was
his chance to be
Brando, James Dean leading man
and he was just going to go all out for it
and I think he had no idea
what it was going to turn into so he was truly
that's what's so authentic about it. You're seeing
a guy who's really shooting for the stars.
Wow. Yeah and you feel
his influences. He wears those
on his sleeve in such a beautiful
way. But I guess
okay so at this point
I thought that was it.
I thought it would show for two weeks and
it's hard to get even
good films traction right?
Movies come out and then they have a LA
premiere and they're good and then that's
it so I thought for sure this was going to be
like he did his thing and now it's time
to move on. Did you maybe
want no one to see it just in case
because you are in these odd sex
scenes? I did laugh
when because with the premiere he had
a few people review it so I
did kind of in a sick way want that
review where people were like what
in the hell did happen
and so in the review somebody
called my character something really funny so I
laughed about it but I just
did not think it could ever gain traction
in a serious way. I thought a few people
would see it and I really wanted
that cringe that audience to
experience the cringe but that was about
it. Sure sure just like alright
well I saw this through this has been an interesting
experience so I guess
now cut to
17 year old Scott Gardner
the summer between
high school and college
and I am bored
also I'm not
doing much kind of a listless time
for me and an angsty
time being in that like that middle
gap and college nerds and I
I just
remember watching TV
like kind of like some
local channel and then seeing an ad
for this movie
which mainly just
struck me as like it probably was barely
holding my attention just like okay
so this is some like odd pretentious
little like independent drama or
something until
Tom Uso yells you're
tearing me apart Lisa and
that was this instant
earworm there's just this like
you know there's just such a
call from that
like you can't forget it so it stuck in my head
I'm like that's interesting okay let me
file that away just like maybe I'll
mention this to somebody some day and then
a week
or so later I'm in the car
with my friends David Nelson
and Michael Rousselet
Michael Rousselet later of if any
listeners have ever seen five second films
of the movie Dude Bro Party Massacre 3
which you are in Greg
a great guy so
we're just like tooling around
the valley board
trying to think of some way to kill the day
and I'm like
hey has anybody seen this weird
ad where this guy yells you're tearing me
apart and I will never forget
the look on Mike's face where he
spins around with just
like bloodshot intensity in his
eyes and he says yes
what the hell is that
like he'd also been thinking about it for a week
but nobody to share it with and it's pre
not pre internet but pre YouTube instead
so like there's no way to like now there might be a way
to like track that and what was that
but it's just been like gnawing
at him and me too and then like
oh my god that yeah well what is
that we gotta figure out what that is and we went
searching I think one of us remembered the name of the movie
and god is there any way we could see that oh that's
what we should do we should go see that movie
well how do we see it oh my god
it is playing at the literal closest
movie theater to us
what are the odds of that so we
just get so punch
drunk on this idea that we could
like oh we're gonna do it we're gonna go watch
it but assuming that we would encounter
something that is like vaguely
funny three times because
this is the thing when you're fishing with kind
of crazy bad movies is like
the death of it
is always boring like a bunch
just a big murk which is what
you know most are honestly
that's what I expected
maybe there'll be some weird hidden treasure
in this we walk up to the
box office of the Lemley
Fallbrook 7 and we
have shading and grins on our faces
and we say three for the room
please and the person
behind the counter smirks
and just like has to stifle laughter
and then like
do her job
his job I forget who it was but the but
this person then puts their
just like breaks a little
bit gets themselves together
and then says would you like to see
a review
of the room yes we would
that sounds great puts a review
up that is printed out puts
it up to the window of the box
office and immediately there's that
line this film is like getting stabbed in
the head and now
we're like hang on we are in for a lot
more than I think we anticipated
that we ever would be
then this person
immediately like stifles a little more laughter
and would you like a copy of the soundtrack
of the room what sound
tracks are but I'm getting presents
from this movie what have we entered
here so like we're only getting
more giggly as we as we walk in
the lights go down
with so films big ostentatious
logo oh my god there's
a production company behind this credit
start you know just
pretty like sincere seeming film the only odd
thing is that his name is almost every
credit but we are still
just kind of like giggly where's this going
and then he opens the door a moment
I will never ever forget in
my life is the first time hearing him
open the door and say hi
babe and we
it's just euphoria
like we've never like
the tension was building and building
and then just erupted there was something orgasmic
about this experience honestly
not to be uncomfortable but just
the but but truly where it's
just like full body and then
everything he says is in that tone
and then his scenes and then a odd
man child comes in a kid who they live
with Denny who's this and then every other
scene is a sexy and I don't need to recap the
whole movie but just the point is we were
so just like this
delivered out of the gate
in a bigger way than we'd ever imagined
the thing I always say about it like
every every it is
as funny
as often as a sitcom is supposed
to be you know like the way like a sitcom
they're like checking the jokes
off like okay five per page
that was this like I've just never
seen anything like it so
we stay in the theater
the credits start rolling and we're like boy
that boy that was something all right well you want to go
Michael Russoley says no
we're not leaving we are
I'm calling every let's we all
have to do it we all have to call everyone
in our phone and get them to come here
right now we're rolling this into
the next screening wow
I didn't realize that right now and I
can't argue against that because like that's insane
what do you mean
did you have to pay for it again
well the dicey thing we know
we just rolled through nobody asked about
it some people came in and paid
other people were like
what are you talking about I don't want to do that that sounds like shit
and Mike said we will open
the theater doors and sneak you in
go into the alley so apologies
for cutting into the box office
back then but it seems like everything worked out
how many people were in the theater first that screening
the first one oh good question
so it was just me and my friends David
and Mike and then
a couple pockets there was a group of
two and a group of two and this was part
of the like strange like
you know just
full body shivers of the whole thing is that
we were trying to stifle laughter
but it was impossible because we were like who are
those people and did they work on the movie
or something and then
two of them left
midway through so few okay so they're
said two of them stayed
and then we asked like
did you have anything to do with that or whatever
and one of them just said worst
goddamn movie I've ever seen in my life and then kept walking
so we're fine we're fine
so the next screening I think we're clear we'll just
load this up with people
I think like ten people came the next night
we went back probably like
twenty to thirty people
the next night which was the final night of the run
I think sixty people
now we're like passing booze around we're all just like
disgustingly sharing like one
giant glass bottle of smirnoff
that's just like going down the road
so it's just it's becoming a fucking party
I think that bottle shattered it's just like
it's a big fucking mess of
a party
and then it ended and we thought well
that was that we got to experience this
thing but we may never see this again
did you know any of that was going on during
that wow wow geez crazy
because I think there was us and then the other one
was in like mid-wilshire
kind of neck of woods and I think a little group
might have found it there so then it became
this odd thing of like stalking the
movie like are we ever going to get the chance
to see this thing again and
we were worried it would never happen and then
I'm checking the website every day
these are my strongest memories of the beginning
of college I should have been partying
I should have been trying to get laid I wasn't
doing any of this so much room
and then the room ended up being like this
big ice breaker for me it became like the way
that I like here I have a personality
I know about this weird movie you have to come see it
they're showing it at this office building so anyway
we're and then finally you guys
start somebody start showing it
oh you were saying the son
of Carl Lemley founder of
Universal Studios see there is theme park
talk in this you'll see and more and more
to come we'll get into it with Greg cause there's a lot to talk about
but that was a mind blower
that Carl Lemley's son
starts putting screenings together
so it becomes a once a month
thing yeah I would show it the Lemley Sunset 5
last Saturday of every month
and I would do the voice recording
on the machine
that Tommy had on the billboard he had a phone number
which used to be my home phone number
oh yes I would call that number wow
that was you that used to be my own and then so I
he would have me do the recording like hey
come see the room last Saturday
of every month well that sounds familiar cause
you're trying to unravel the mystery like it's the billboard
has a number to call and then you call it
and it's mark answers
that's wild yeah
what's happening so we all are like
what is happening on the other side of this
and then I imagine at some point it happened to you
too that like wait people are coming
to this like there is a weird little audience
so speaking of icebreakers
it's funny it did the same thing for me cause
now we're now we're 2005
and it's the last Saturday of every month for free
and so I'd be going around LA
driving meeting people and I have the room postcards
in my car and so I'd be like hey
I see this girl or whatever I'd be like hey
hey what's up what's up you got this
this going on I did this you know movie or whatever
and then be like an icebreaker
hopefully at that time I was like hoping they'd never
show up but I remember there's this
girl from South Africa I was talking to her at Starbucks
and then she called me later she's like
you know in her accent she said I don't mean to be mean but this movie
looks like shite
she's like you're in this
so I remember I was doing that
and then I went to a couple screenings
in like 2005
I think I remember you guys
were there and it was like a group of like
40 sure and the spoons were
starting oh boy great and so
this is a whole wait let me say that
really quickly that again if you
might be very lost if you don't know the movie just watch the movie
it's wonderful it's such a rewarding
treasure of a movie get the where do people
watch it now is it still DVD the main way to
Blu-ray and Blu-ray I
I owe a purchase of the Blu-ray I gotta
see what's up with the Blu-ray but
one of the odd aspects of it
is that there is a framed photo
of a spoon that's visible in many
shots which I remember the discovery
of that probably in the third time that we watched it
whereas I think Michael Risalea yelled
there's a picture of a spoon up there
and then like it was so lit up about it so then
the next night he's like
here's an idea got
an idea this is what's going to make
it rocky horror we should bring
plastic spoons and throw them at the screen
and my now wife Aaron
was part of our like so the group
that was like starting to see this in these early
days and she discouraged
this from happening she
was like you cannot do that that's going to make
such a mess all these theater employees
are going to have to clean those things up you gotta think about that
so she almost killed you
well now you've seen like what it like
she probably could have saved
in her success she could have saved a lot of
cleanup around the world like I've been
oh wow yeah people come armed
with spoons like around the world
that's the biggest mind-blower to me
the movie for sure but specifically
the spoon thing being there for
like remembering someone
having that idea and now knowing
that spoons are thrown
in Russia all over the world
where have you because and this is a whole other
thing you like traveled the world
showing this movie now and
this documentary piece that you made
to promote your book which I'm in
it was the last we saw each other but like
yeah what's the crazy where have you been with this movie
I mean really like everywhere
all over Europe every state
jeez
I've been to Russia
Estonia
Estonia everywhere
Finland Denmark Sweden
like they're like they throw so
many spoons in Sweden did you ever did you go back
to Romania oh yeah
oh good ass
oh dude double feature with the retro
public
it's in Japan it's in China
I got stopped by
and I was in London fans
fans from China
and obviously we're gonna head into
music parks up but I've been stopped at
Disneyland Disney World like
the employees oh hi Mark
oh wow everybody like
a stormtrooper or Kylo
you ever got like somebody in character
did I send you the video wait I saw
you post it I didn't want to put the sound on
opposite and I think it was the guy
who was playing Kylo is friends
with somebody from Alan the draft house who
recognized came up and I was like
this is weird you don't really try to get their
attention but they totally trolled me
and the stormtrooper was like what have you done
with the wookie and I was like
everyone stared at me I was like I think
he's that way
but the no the spoon thing
is like you guys are like the fact
that you guys discovered that and it's become
a worldwide like that's what everybody
thought the publisher when I wrote disaster
is wanted the cover of the book
to be a spoon wow
wow oh my god it's the icon
of the whole well this is the whole
I mean like basically
the like the
at least my personal journey
through this movie has always
been so like positive
and magical and like
you know just like we said like it being
this icebreaker and then like getting to the other
side and like meeting you and the other people
who are part of it like oh my god everybody's
everybody's like cool and excited
about it and like deriving positivity from
it and then watching that honestly that
that spoon that watching that
grow from like I remember somebody having that idea
to it happens all over the world the fact
that I encountered the movie
on the way to film school basically
in a very like precarious
summer in a summer of a lot of fear and like I'm
gonna go chase my dream
but is there any chance that I would ever
do anything that anyone would ever see
or that would spread or that anyone
would ever respond to
the room and the spoons
and all of it always was this like
beacon of hope for like wow
if that can happen what else can happen
if you just like make something
that you try to do sincerely
and try to have a vision for
as you were saying so honestly
let me just say sincerely like
how inspiring the whole thing
has been for me and like everything I've gotten
to do since all the videos I've made this podcast
it just like it like
all provided an example of
like you can start
something with no audience and
have it grow and have like tons
of strangers be into it and be excited about it
with no budget or
that's another important thing yes
as all things start as
this podcast started as well
it's just the power of getting started
people wait for the perfect time
or the perfect project and it's like
you just gotta get out there and try
and I think what comes with that may not be
the first time maybe you meet somebody
on the second project and you find your voice
but it's really one of those things
like I didn't expect anything
from the room of anything I've ever done in my
entire life it was the last
thing that I thought would ever connect
with people and it's just
so fascinating it's like such a great lesson
with film never look down upon
something never think something is
you just don't know and
what's so interesting is like hearing
your story I mean I've told your story
to audiences for years
watching this film like getting stabbed
in the head that you guys saw
I imagine I said all that when
you interviewed me 10 years ago
but what I'm wondering
like do you think there's some sort
of destiny like there's
something there
with the room like you guys were sort of the
voice of that generation
do you know what I mean like
that's a weighty thing too
I don't know if I can speak to that
I don't know if that's my mantle to take
I think about it I think where you were at
in your guys' life
like the openness and maybe you guys were
kind of that first audience that
was could get
like your minds were in a place
where you could get it I don't think
my parents didn't get it like my mom said
oh hi Mark so I was in it but you
guys were really the first audience that could
sit there and
be like
digested the way it was meant to be
digested
I hope so that's an honor if you're saying that and by the way
you legitimized
it has always meant a lot to me that you
put credit Mike
and I in the book and as a picture
of us in your but like it has always felt
wonderful to like because you know sometimes you can feel
like you know a hipster like oh I was
there like yeah you're trying to like
insert yourself as a I knew about this
thing before but you like giving us any
sort of credit for that has always been very
meaningful but I
yeah I mean I think what
I think hopefully what we all
love about and what continues to resonate about it for us
is the like the psychology at
play you're not just watching the movie
you know that there's a story here
and that it all stems from the
odd psychology of Tommy and as
you were saying Mike he really does get like
has anyone
like put their unique
brain into a
movie more successfully
I don't that somebody I was literally watching
a video this morning about Stephen Soderbergh and somebody's
like you know he does all the things himself
and he edits while he's going and I'm like yeah
that's true that like that is kind of rare because most
you know big people yeah they they have
other people they rely on to do a few
of the things and they get the input but this
the way especially hearing you describe it I'm like
oh it's like he literally
shaped it
all directly
yeah yeah I got a crazy
story about you bring up Stephen Soderbergh
I mean this is just like hard hitting
but Simon Schuster
sent a copy of my book The Disaster Artist
to David Fincher yeah David
Fincher received it and looked at it and
said oh the
room my friend Stephen Soderbergh
is obsessed with this film wow
and like hearing David
Fincher say that I was
like yeah oh
my god wow
I mean you're talking about like our and then
another crazy story I was at the Palm
Spring Film Festival when The Disaster Artist came out
and Paul Thomas Anderson was there for Phantom Threat
and he was standing alone at the bar
and I thought I'm just going to
go up and I was sitting with the organizer of the festival
and I went up to him and I said hey
your films Boogie Nights and The Master
really inspired me when I was writing The Disaster Artist
and he just like shook my hand and said oh thank you
and then I walked away and I was like oh my god
I shook like Paul Thomas and I'm talking
to Jen who was like one of the PR
people and so he walked away
and went to the other organizer
and said oh my
I'm a little starstruck I met the guy from The Room
and so I thought
like
what is this like yeah
crazy world we're living in
where somehow that
movie has tapped into all the people
you would have dreamt of working with
in like such a twisted
strange way I would like
you know what you could have ever, as a struggling actor
you missed a part in this movie like how could you
have ever imagined like on the others
in 20 years this is your path
to all of cinemas greats
yeah it's so it's such a
twisted joke how
you know and I used to always say out of the room
like it's so bad I don't watch it but then like
once anything
any art has traveled for
20 years and people still talk about
it and watch it and it's been through generations
like you guys were the first one that's now
in 2025
I can't really like
judge it that way because it's like any
film I ever do or make or
like I would hope that like
the dream is that people still consume it
20 years later like it still works
like something timeless
and I'm like damn how did like
how did it pull it off the strangest possible
path there ever could have been to
one of those well let me let me bring
let me bring things of you know into our
territory here a little bit and say so here's another
so we hadn't I don't think we hadn't
spoken since I you interviewed
me for the this video that you've been
showing when you tour the movie
you show this little documentary you did about it
and then you and then you show the film
and you were showing it at this
venue in Pittsburgh
that we would really love to
play at some point Bottle Rock at Social Hall
Chris Copen is the owner's name
and I
think so he was
he was hosting you for your
tour and the video
before it comes up and I'm in it
and he approaches you after and says
wait a minute you know Scott Garner wait why is
Scott Garner in this what's going on here yeah he's like
how did you get Scott Garner in here
and I was like oh he's like one of the original
who launched the room he's like no he
has oh he's like I know you love
Disney you're always a Disney world like
he has the best podcast
about like music you gotta listen
to it I'm like of course Scott does
so that morning I
reached out to Scott and I started listening
to podcasts right all the way
driving like across
which then
has caused a bunch of discussion
for a while between you and
I which has been such a delight the discovery
that with all the okay there's
that whole shared odd history that we
have and the weird way that we met and now
on top of it you are a mega
Disney parks person a mega
Disney world person I don't even
know where to begin exactly
with all of this other than I think when you first brought it
up you really threw it all out there and
said that you were you didn't even say
I go to Disney world all the time you framed
it as I've been living in
Disney world four chunks at a
time do you want you want to speak to that or what you're
especially recent Disney sure
yeah a quick so super quick backstory
at the age of twelve
I went to Disney world for the first
time and
I didn't know it at the time but
there's something called Disney depression
you're probably gonna be like what the hell
you know I've never heard that coin but I know what you're talking
about because you're immersed
you're immersed in this world every decision
you're making is based on fun excitement
nothing counts
you're walking so much food food calories
don't count right right everything
it takes away all your problems
and then you leave and it's like really
hard especially world because you're
in the world like everywhere you go
it's Disney the music that you're seeing
there's probably no more
core memory for me
and my parents still bring it up all the time
than leaving Disney world from our
first trip when I was seven and that
I was just like balling
the entire time from the
cab the airport I
like it's it's among my earliest
memories which are interesting things to be
earliest memories because it's full of joy
but also but the deep set
and I think my parents knew then like this is a sadness
that isn't just like we'll
come back next year and they're like
I think a personality is forming
and perhaps a podcast in many years
but anyway I know exactly so this
so it was 12 for you yeah and so I left
and I was just um
yeah I was just like down I didn't want to go back
to school it was like a late summer trip
I went to the water parks I met
this girl who we kept in touch like
writing letters and I
we talk about this all the time we always
thought on a vacation we could like form
new identities right like if I'm really
confident at Blizzard Beach just
askew everything I am back in Woodland
well for me it was if I'm really
confident a girl will come up
and do all of the work as far as
introducing herself to me
then saying like hey let me show you how to
kiss for the first time but that did not
happen you actually had to talk to people
to make that go down but I did not
do it
just these incredible memories I was
kind of depressed to go back to school I wasn't
a great student and I just wanted
to find my way back to Disney World
obviously being back in California
that was a long way and then Christmas
I saw the movie Home Alone
and I
I don't know what came over me
but after I saw the movie
Home Alone I started I've never written anything
before I took a pencil
and a notepad and I literally
hand wrote a 78
page script Home Alone
Lost in Disney World a secret
which is
a good idea
if they had somehow pulled that together
then that's a that's a money prayer
as the third movie yeah and so I
and get this and I'm not
making it up I wrote a part for myself
that Kevin McAllister
now had a buddy in Disney
World to fight off the bandits who
are now janitors
were there to rob Cinderella's jewels
and they called themselves the bling bandits
wow
Cinderella's jewels that's so good you're not going to believe
what I called my character in
1990 oh god not Mark Dan
what what it was
I called myself
Mark that's insane
insane so that's also insane that you didn't
just say great that gets me great
oh yeah yeah you're right you weren't so
egotistical in your 12 year old writing
just a tad um so I
wrote a part for myself and I
hand wrote the script to 78 pages
and I wasn't doing homework I was
just writing nonstop and researching back then
it was really hard you had to get the newspaper you had to like
I looked at Home Alone photos
and then I convinced my parents to get me a video
writer I mean this was so
archaic it was like a floppy disc
and a little mini cursor with
like it looked like old space invaders
like 1960s style
I wrote out the script
drew a poster for it printed
it went to Kinko's got on
411 called 20th Century Fox
found
they're like you can't send it here you got to find
John Hughes' production company we don't
produce Home Alone
found John Hughes' production company in Lake
Forest Illinois went to FedEx
mailed the package my mom thought like
I'm not putting any money in this like you're insane
and I mailed the script out with
a cover letter and in my cover letter I was telling
John Hughes that combining the
Home Alone story with the Disney franchise
would be an incredible marketing
tool this is like 1991 I was like
you were an executive
it took me over
I was like my life was this
so I mailed it to John Hughes
week goes by and I'm like I so
believed this was going to happen
I stopped like studying
I didn't care about school
and I was like a week's gone by I haven't heard from John Hughes
two weeks go by
my mom comes back from the mail and says
there's a package for you from
from Hughes Productions and I was like
wow oh damn yeah
okay here we go it's a go yeah we're
making it next week yeah and so I
open it and
my script is in there and then there's
a handwritten note that says like how impressed
John Hughes was that I found him that I did this
and that like keep believing
in yourself and follow your dreams and I was like
oh my god so
what about the movie
straight to the negative
let's get this moment moving here
and so it hit me pretty
hard we didn't make it I couldn't watch Home Alone for a
while but I knew there
like that's what I wanted to do
is I wanted to tell
stories I like so now
let's cut to
late 2023
I take a
young family member
to Disney World for the first time
and I get to and I'd been
a few times been to Disneyland I'd always had
a good time but this is like July
of 2023 and
I see Disney World
through her eyes
and just have this incredible
time and then I start
to discover sort of what Disney World is now
you have the resorts
you have the extended
hours
and the magic bands and all this stuff
and all of a sudden like
I get like
I get hit the way I did when I was 12
wow oh so you were like you were
into it never like fully bailed out
but you were like fully reactivated
yeah totally reactivated
and I sort of like
there's a new draw as an adult
so for me I
haven't seen a lot of the films like I just this last
year watched Moana like I haven't seen a lot of
films what drew me in was
the imagineering and the park and
the just the whole feeling
you are when you go
and so we went back
for Christmas
and it was incredible I sent you
photos stay at the Grand Floridian the
gingerbread house oh yeah
it was just like this whole I was like okay now
I'm back to where I was 12
and I was like I gotta go back
and revisit what I
did and so I went back
to it and I said you know what
now I'm an adult
I think I can
do something with this now
I'm gonna take this story and I'm gonna
turn it into something and so
for the past year
I've basically like I said
so my character in the story the script
that I wrote lives at Disney
World right he was
where you live
he was related to Walt
Disney oh he was trying
to defend the vision of Walt
but like it had been taken
over so he was like
living in the underground like
parts of the park
tunnels below the tunnels
the secret little caverns that Walt
built he was living he had
keys to Walt's apartment like he had
he had like the little underground
magic that nobody else had and so he
helps Kevin so
I so he's the bird
lady of like yeah
totally I do have someone
on my side in this crazy place and
so I
just got fully back
and so when I go
like I send you that list I've been to all the
resorts I've gone to all
the different I don't think I realized that that
was because you've basically you've stayed
everywhere but
you're only missing two and
I think I thought that was more of a like last five
years or lifetime thing that's since
that's only from 2023
yeah that's starting 2023
to wow to
October of last year holy shit wow
and that's the okay what
what are you missing well let's go by what you were missing
because otherwise you've been to every did
you say Yachton Beach Club I haven't done
Yachton Beach Club I haven't done Boardwalk
so
those two but everywhere else you
stayed at wow and for like
big stretches like average
of like three to five wow
so fourth of July
at Epcot is the
best party like that is
never done that no we've never done that it's an incredible
time they have live music firework show
is like the best I've seen so
fourth of July is a really great way
to kick it off and what's awesome is if you're staying
near Epcot at Swann or Yachton
Beach Club or any of those like you just walk in
right oh yeah sure yeah and
and then for contemporary
is one of the best spots
because if you have a resort view you
literally go on your balcony I think I
sent you the video where you just look out
and you see Magic Kingdom right you
see the Grand Floridian you
can just see everything from your balcony it's almost like
I don't I don't need to go
and so there's just
yeah certain parts of the
park that are just have this
like I don't know when you when you're at Disney World
everything your whole mood is
different and I hadn't
I hadn't you know
I'd been back before
but rediscovering
the magic in a different way
has really plugged me into the creation of
it like how like
riding Tron I sent you those
those videos like just going
into how they take the movie and how they take one
idea and build it
and like the joy
it brings to to so many people
it just
I've rediscovered so much of it and I
went actually to Marceline
Missouri which is where
Walt was from
Oh yes the basis of Main Street
yeah yeah yeah that was a mind blow
when you were yeah when you were giving me
your stats and I was like I don't know we talked
to anybody who's been to Marceline Missouri
it's a tough one to get to I've been to Kansas
City and it's just
far enough to where you know you're going somewhere
else and so this last time I was in
Omaha Nebraska
and I was like you know what
it's only two and something hours away screw I'm going
like I'm not going to wait for the next chance and
so I pull pull into Marceline
Missouri and it was so
eerie and cool
because it feels like you're on Main Street
there's nobody there
and you pull up and there's like
the old theater and they have like the
railroad that Walt used to like
would inspire him to do all the railroads
you go into
some of the restaurants and they have some of the drinks
from Disney World like Boathouse they have like
really oh hey now we're talking
wow
you guys won me over here this is cool
yeah yeah and then just getting to walk
around the town at night and hear the
railroad and then go to the museum
I went to the old wishing barn
oh yes now this was because we talk
a lot about kind of odd Walt mythology
and it's sudden like because
it feels like things come up like oh he's got the
lamp above the fire station
and we're like I never heard of this lamp before
and you're telling me now there's a whole other I
didn't know about the barn and the tree
there's a lot there's all these wishing things
that yeah yeah I
so I walked up to the wishing barn
and it was so bizarre
because this the cutest cat
followed me around
for an hour and 20 minutes
like a real life figaro
is it figaro
yeah he literally and I kept videoing him and he was
like followed me and would rub
up against me and then I went into the wishing barn
he just sat outside the door and looked at me and meowed
the entire time and just sat there
it would come out it was like it was I was like
is this Walt?
reincarnated
the Walt's ghost is rubbing people
before they go in the barn
pretty magical right
come to my parts
bunny in the pockets of my ancestors
or my relatives
but it was it was if anybody
is a Disney fan it was a great
pilgrimage rolling in there at night
and they have the old main street music playing
really?
which is like what turn of the century kind of
yeah it's sort of like what you hear at the parks
and I try to get a video for you
like just to scroll
over and see what it's like but it felt like
you're on main street yeah yeah
there was an odd like specific magic too that wasn't just
like you know regular
main drag small town like there's
something to it was there a lot of people
were there a lot of tourists there? there was nobody there
nobody okay I was the only one walking
around really huh
I guess because it's kind of out of the way
it's like two hours
going each way and it's like unless
you really lined it up and I'm so glad
I went during the winter
it was like a lot cooler
and it just had yeah
and then not far from
there is Hannibal, Missouri
which is where Mark Twain is from
which is where he got the idea to
do the Mark Twain boat
at Disneyland the Tom Sawyer Island
I went to like that's only an hour and a half Tom Sawyer
Island is all near there
so you could see the influences of
the parks so clearly
jeez jeez like true
Americana that's great so it's you
recommend it as a pilgrimage but it's kind of a
you don't stay at the there's not some magical
Marceline hotel you sort of gotta
like pop in yeah
oh they should why don't they do it
there is a cute little motel there that has
the old Disney posters like the
old Monorail posters the old Pirates
of the Caribbean so there is a cute
little hotel in town like a mile out
sure sure yeah they have no
deluxe resorts there yet yeah yeah yeah
it sounds like they haven't monetized this
to the degree they could it sounds
like they you know you in some ways you'd
imagine like it's the Wisconsin Dells when there's just
a bunch of shitty t-shirt stores
being like Disney was here like
it seems classier than it does that's what
I liked about it yeah I felt like you were just in some
small small town you could really get a feel
of what you experience
really cute little museum there
that's very well done has a lot of artifacts
some really great
like 3D Disney art
but again very subtle
wow that sounds lovely
so you're a
Disney World hotels aficionado
particularly
let me I guess let me ask is there
if you had to commit
to one you can only stay
at one from here on out
which one we talk about great question
I was in so one of the most
insane Disney things I've ever done
is I went to
the Grand Floridian for the 4th of July
because we talk about like investigating
Disney depression right when you leave
you just feel like you're going back to the real world
and it's still there in a different way
so this time I thought I'm going to try to
to test it so I was at the Grand
Floridian for 4th of July
my birthday flew to
Alani in Hawaii wow
which is incredible Disney's worth
they have all the characters
and then from Alani
flew straight back to the Disney World
to the Polynesian for my
family's birthday damn
so I tested to see which is Hawaii
just totally insane
but when I was in Alani
I got pulled aside
and they're like have you heard of like DVC
Disney Vacation Club of course yeah
and they're like yeah
so they start saying you can like
buy into a resort it's your home resort
and when they're asking that question it made me think about it all
and they were telling me like Revere is available
or this is available
and I would say for me probably
my favorite that feels the most
timeless is the Grand Floridian
I love the idea of the monorail
coming into the hotel
picking you up
taking you to the park it's those little things when you
get older where it's like you've done
the rides it's those little
touches that like that's
what gets you I think as you get older so I think Grand Floridian
was incredible and then
during the holidays
at Christmas time the Wilderness
Lodge is
spectacular they have one of the best
trees I've ever seen it's like huge right
yeah you walk in it's like a woodsy
cabin feel and you
look up and the tree is
really anybody who hasn't done
it during the holidays it's an incredible resort
that's the thing I remember my parents carving
out time to do and even in our
childhood trips was like this
day no parks or maybe we'll pop into one
later in the day but today we're just
going to go or we're just going to
look at Christmas decorations
in these hotels and look at those gingerbread
yeah they knew how to do it
I don't know how they even knew that that was an
aspect of it but they were
that part of it had a
giant influence on me and the fact that I
still try to spend as much time as I can in hotel
lobbies still where I go to
to write and relax and get away
always chasing that vibe
living at living at Disney where like I
anytime I had a booking
or something I'd always
if there's in between week or
I'd always be I was at Disney
World for 36
36 days
and it was like again
the fact if you have the annual pass thing
it's fun because you have like
the magic band and you can go in and do
whatever you want but it was chilling
in the resort going
for a walk just the freedom to
explore and then I found this
like super cool
experience that I did not know was possible
if you're staying at the contemporary
they actually rent boats
yes I've done this yes
and you can go and go
cruise around the seven seas lagoon
it's like I was the only person out there
and it was the other one was
the sheriff like the just waiting
I was literally cruising through the Polynesian
and it was like there's just so many cool
things you can do and if you're doing something creative
or want to get your mind off stuff
like just that low stress
being around creativity
that's also what I love is like how
they schedule those midday parades
and you see people given they're all
the dancers the emcees
you're just around like happiness
and creativity that it just
it's such a good place to be
just for that
this is what people don't
I mean people that are listening to this
understand it but regular
people don't understand when you're like well
you go to disneyland a lot it's like yeah
I do and then you will you go to all the rides
every no no no no no no no no no
you drive down you get a little
meal you can do some work
near it and
you'll hear the music you'll
smell the smells and then
so much is just vibes and I
go maybe I'll go on one ride and then I'll come
back and then they just look at you like you're insane
but you're like no no no come with me
come with me and I will convert you I think
I think if you were spending every day just like
bouncing around the fantasy land
dark rides and that is it
if you're just around like carousel
calliope there's something there's something
odd about that I can see the lack of appeal
yeah I think so yeah just around
loud sounds and kids and
and rides where things jump out at you but
I do think that's one of the
biggest like gulfs in trying
to like convey any of this to anybody is like
is the disney serenity
because it's definitely there you've for sure experienced
joy instead of the like I think every hotel
has its version of just like
oh it's so still and either people
are already back from the parks or they're still at
the parks so you kind of got this the fact
that you could just like I got the boardwalk to myself
how is that even possible
just crickets chirping and water shimmer
and it's like it is it's
magical to think about it is it's just
built to like experience
joy like I was staying at the swan
hotel and I walked out and there's like the white
sand yes water there
and there's a hammock in between two palm trees
and I just like sat
on it for a little bit I was like looking up and I was like
you know you could be
in so many different places but disney's
found a way to take
what you would feel in
all these other countries that would take you so
long to get there passports and
like difficulties and they've brought it
to you yeah that's what I think
if you have the imagination you can
go there and escape into
kind of whatever you want it to do and that's also
why Epcot's become one of my
favorite parks too is because
they've just found a way
to bring you safety fun
adventure and it's just
all handed to you and like and just like
like big strolls
I feel like a friend of the
show Jason Walliner was just there and I
was like I feel like the big thing about
Epcot is just is just being
there it's just taking a walk it's just
like lagoon it's looking at that architecture
even if you don't go do anything in
the world showcase pavilions just
like passing by and then this music gives
way to that music and like I really
think especially Epcot I think number one attraction
is just is just
vibe well I also think of boardwalk and
everything as part of Epcot like the attraction
wise I'm like well at night
we're going to go to abracadabra
and we're going to do this and yes if
jelly rolls was still there if I mean it is still there
right now but for me I would be like
well we're doing jelly rolls that's part of Epcot in my
mind so that's all rolls into one
for me 100% right yeah I
always think Epcot is like its own its own
world yeah and then you can just literally
walk over to Hollywood Studios
yeah yeah right or a little boat
or you do your little yeah yeah your little
skyliner now yeah
that's so much yeah that that aspect
I had like true
serenity in that zone
you're describing Greg with the like
when these guys I did not I
it was a long day around the drinking
around the world food and wine I
did not have it in me to go to a dueling
piano bar yeah at the very end
of the long day even
though they did and had a wonderful time but I
was like I know what I need I know what my
spirit needs so badly which
is to just walk that
the Michael Graves Causeway between
the swan and the dolphin and then
just kind of like go sit on the grass
and just like put my feet out watch
the water and it like
it's just funny that it gives it gives you any if
you're in the mood for dueling piano
covers of give me one
what did they play oh well they
played like moving right along
I think from the Muppet movie but then they you know I
don't do they do don't stop believing it feels
right if they didn't seems like if you want to hear some
dueling piano journey you want but if you if you
want just like peace
you can get that to that's still what I'm dreaming because
I'm coming off a crazy run like a big project
that was very involved and then having a second
child and really my happy place in
the I was like and I still haven't gotten there but I will
and when I'm there hey maybe when we're all over
live show or something but the I'm like
I'm going to get to one I'm getting balcony
at whichever one has a balcony
swan dolphin I like both
swan to me I think is
is better got better views like I did
dolphin the first time it's good
but swan's just got a better vibe and then I
really like swan reserve swan
reserve because it has the top
level you can take it up and you
literally go up there and you have a view of the
entire Epcot it's one of the best
views I would like to see that
swan reserves got great restaurants it's
it's newer it's like a newer DVC
resort so it doesn't feel like hardcore
Disney it's just like a really nice resort
but I think yes
swan is great too yeah yeah
in terms of
this has been a long time
with no like real specific ride talk
but let's do a little
of that what is
first of all Epcot well what's your
what's your Epcot what's like the
big things you got to hit in a big
Epcot so Epcot what you said
as well the vibe is great drinking around
the world is so much fun yeah
one of the things I did
was sort of a ritual is
kind of backwards but you go to the Rosenkrant
bar in England you
do a few whiskey shots there okay
okay and then if you're still feeling
like risky get one
more drink and
go ride guardians
so riding guardians
with that sort of like wild buzz
you're not worried about nausea come back
because people get nauseous even sober on that
baby that's what I was gonna say so when I first
did guardians
I had a little bit you kind of
hit me a little weird yeah and then
I did the whiskey thing and
since then it's been one of my favorites
it's just you're just in the right
mindset and you don't get affected
by the turn so
I love doing that having a couple
shots of whiskey go to guardians
damn I've never done that bar I gotta
I will do this next time yeah I don't
know if I can handle several shots anymore
good for you
maybe it's the kids thing
something about that makes it
tougher but yeah guardians
is definitely
is definitely really up there love test track
it's down right now oh right yeah
are you hopeful for the new one
I mean I really enjoyed it
I'm sure they'll add a nice nice twist to it
I felt it felt a little 90s
it's getting janky yeah
a little tired yeah
they'll do something cool and what I again what I love is
when you have the extended hours at Epcot you get to
stay till 11 okay and if you time
it right you can get on your last ride at 11
be there almost till midnight oh geez
and then you're like if you're at like the opposite end of the park
and then you can just like walk out
slowly by yourself all things
just shimmer and sparkle
that's the best way to time is when you sort of walk
out and you have the park to yourself one thing that
happened that was crazy
actually last summer is I don't know if you guys ever done
this but you can eat dinner in the
in Cinderella's castle I have never
done it I know you've been doing this
yeah yeah so the
hack with that is if you go you get
the last reservation
you have dinner it's great um
super cool experience and then you are
escorted out as the last
patron in the park oh really
so I literally
got to walk around Magic Kingdom
as the last person and just hang
that's a great hack that's a great
tip it was you could just sit there
and just take it all in they don't rush you
super cool um like Kevin the
Callister but without the stress
of being a child alone
yeah and no bandits not that
not that I saw yeah thank god
you were there for one of those incidents right
wasn't there some like scary people thought it was gunshots
it was one of those nights I was in the castle
um and we missed the whole
thing people were writing me like hey are you alright
I was like yeah I've got wine
and I'm in the castle yeah
I think I'm good and they're like oh there was some
incident that went down I saw these videos
just missed the whole thing
and then that was one of the nights getting escorted
out being the last people in the park and I got a ton
of photos with it empty
as inspiration for
what the park would look like
in the story oh sure yeah yeah yeah
wow wow
that also if we're
Kevin's at Grand Floridian is that the like
cause that's very that's very much in that like
plaza and all the nice food
and then like they did the
like Rockefeller Center and the tree
that is pretty that is I can feel
that Home Alone magic maybe John
Hughes did read the script and used it for
Home Alone lots of music oh maybe yeah
just like fused it all into uh huh
yeah oh and speaking
of Home Alone get this you're going to
love this at the 2018
Independent Spirit Awards wow Tommy
and I were there for the Disaster Artist
and the award show's
over and we go outside and
Chris Columbus and his family
comes up and says how
much he loves the room
and the Disaster Artist and I'm like
and I'm like wow Chris Columbus
and he's like yeah I was like
oh my god like I could not
and then he was he was obsessed why
Tommy wanted to move him here
for the photo and so
it was like he got he got lost in that
I'm like no no I want to talk to you about Home Alone
yeah yeah
so the fact that like Chris Columbus and I asked
and I was like you've seen the disaster he's like oh we saw
it like four times and I
was just like Chris and Tommy had no idea who
Chris Columbus was oh my god
he checked out after Rubble without a cause
that's the only thing he knows about I feel like I have
to ask do you have any
is there ever been any discussion or proof
of Tommy Wiseau going to
a Disney park oh my god I have the perfect story
for you oh great oh thank god
I thought of it I thought of it a very interesting
story Mark I thought of it
on the way here and I'm so glad
I jogged all my memories
because
I booked some convention
in Orlando and I hadn't
been in years to Disney World
so he kind of tagged along
I did the convention and we went
to Magic Kingdom
so we're in line for Splash Mountain
and
two really weird things happen so we're in line
just getting to the corridor where
you're starting to go down
to where you're going to get on the ride
and he and I were like just talking
and there was a woman in front of us who was blind
and she turned straight
to me and said
you have a lot to offer
but you don't believe in yourself
and I was like oh my
god she's like I can hear it in your voice
and I remember just like this
woman with glasses staring at me
like staring through me
and I was like okay
cool shook that off
we get on the ride Tommy and I are going through Splash Mountain
we're having a good time
we're going like
getting towards where we're about to rise
and the person in front of me
has the biggest wasp
on their back that you've ever seen
so I'm looking at it and I'm like
oh no
and I like tap Tommy and he goes
don't say
don't tell her
because she will freak out it will come straight on you
and I'm like oh no
oh my god so we're going up
up to go
to go on the fall
and I'm staring at this wasp
and he's like wait that's right after the bee
part of the ride too
oh my god
and so it goes down I duck
into a wasp so a very Tommy
way to ride Splash Mountain he's like I told
you
so that was the Disney
experience
you have a bib wasp comes on you
you know good thing happen bad thing happen
that's life
there's so many
things like I quote it all the time
and I think it's so quotable because that's
one aspect of it is that like I don't think
you could quote a movie so many
bad movies are about like some crazy
monster or something so how do you
like it's about creatures and how do you fold
that into your life there's so much the fact that the room
is just about people and stuff
and there's all these anonymous phrases
that just like like Darren and I cannot
cannot say if one of us says
oh we'll see we have to say ah
we see
don't plan too much
you should not plan too much it may not come
out right is that
good or bad advice Disney
worldwide or are you a super
planner should you plan too much or
may it come out right
great question now I've had the luxury of going
a lot and knowing that I'm going a lot right
so so you can pace it people that
like go for the first time with their kids
they want to just do it's a small world
they want to like fit everything in something's
twice yeah I for me
I really enjoy
depends on weather let's say it's like a nice day
I really enjoy getting to the park
a bit later I think the
afternoons and the evenings are the best times
to ride things and see things so I'm like
a two thirty
three p.m. nice
stroll in and just take your time
I think having
a loose plan maybe having like a cool dinner reservation
yeah cause in Disney World there's
so many places to try you have all the
Epcot restaurants one of my favorites
is Steakhouse 71 at Contemporary
it's an incredible restaurant I haven't done it
oh you told me about California Grill
you haven't done California Grill?
which I tried and it was great
you got a little shit from Matt Cardona
he's like there's a wrestler he's a big
Disney World fan who comes on the show
he was mad that I only had pizza in the
lounge at the California Grill
so you haven't been?
it was on Zoom
so I wasn't as scared as I would have been in real life
but yeah he thought that was sort of
when I said I had been there
he felt that was not legitimate
that was not a claim
I don't know that's a very judgmental
way to view things though although I
don't want shit from him
cause you align with him on a lot of things
I know I do
you know what I can't help but ask
living with the land
I've done it a couple times
where do you land?
what's your feeling?
there's some rides that you go
and just sort of like
it's like a mood
I'll jump back on that again and take it in
it's not like one that you're
it's not like a soren where
it takes you on an escape
and you're like oh I'm gonna start with that one
it's a mood one sort of like
the figment ride
if you're playful
or spaceship earth
it's a mood
it's a mood alright
I think it puts me in a bad mood
no I have this whole
I just fully don't like
or get living with the land and this has been a battle
for me on the show
for years and years and I want to get it
but yeah Cardona backs me up on it
the thing that's so crazy is everybody's arguments
for why I should like it
I'm like I know that is what I like
about a lot of things but it's
what makes me like the Mexico boat ride
the three caviaros ride
that one has like I don't know
everyone's arguments about living with the land
I just apply to other things
I think it's Q based honestly and you've talked about it before
but I think it's that unpleasant
cafeteria feeling
that bottom floor of the land for all the magical places
at Epcot especially
I think it's just like crowded, stressful
a lot of traffic, people coming out of bathrooms
a lot of people trying to get to Soarin
and a busy like really quick service restaurant
I bet it's that
I think so yeah
as opposed to like entering this
beautiful lobby with the
Joe Roady mural and like atmosphere
and dim
you get such a great pre-show
I would say going into that thing
as opposed to just like I don't know it's like kind of yellow
and angry
I was saying I was in the Cardona last one
about Tower of Terror where like
I didn't go to the Tower of Terror in California Adventure
that much even though we love
that ride
but it's set back and forward
the Q and placement of ride seems to
matter and then there are rides on each coast
that are more popular than
the other and I do think it's like ride
placement and then Q
has a lot to do
with popularity
well honestly that's a great point because if you
look at like Soarin
which is in the bottom of that cafeteria
and you go to
California Adventure
it's placed in like this redwood
area that feels so much
more exciting
to go into
I love that zone man that's the last
I got to end my day there the other day and I just like
I was ending a little early and I was still like
you know what I think I'm good I get to soak this
up and like oh man yeah
yeah yeah instead of like you go into a
tiny lobby on a bottom floor and then
get squeezed through that's an unfortunate
thing about that Soarin. It's so hard to find too
it's like we're Soarin. Yeah
another ride I want to ask
you guys about
the Finding Nemo at Epcot
which
so I went on for the first
time it's newer and they have real dolphins
in that
I mean I'm going through Nemo
and I see like a dolphin swim by
and I'm like damn that looked really good
and it was like that was
a dolphin and then you go up and they have
this whole aquarium and they have
such an impressive collection
like and there's dolphins
like swimming in there so the dolphins are part of it
I recall seeing dolphins there maybe I just am I crazy
do you have dolphins in the actual urban seas
yeah yeah well they have
what manatees yeah
manatees actually but the dolphins are swimming
in like you're going through
you're seeing the graphics of
Nemo but there's actually dolphins
coming through that are part of it
not every time but the time I caught it
and then they had Mickey scuba diving
oh right I've never seen that in person
either that was a very like
if you go there in a TGIF episode
maybe there's a character snorkeling like
scuba down there but that's cool
so again the queue for that is not bad
but I was really impressed when I tried
the Nemo at Disneyland for the first time
the submarine yeah again
the queue is super cool you don't know where you're getting into
it feels authentic so
I think there's just something
special off of retry
but I'm with you living with the land is not something
I'm going to seek out because
it's sort of buried in a way
that's not I don't know
if it had a killer queue
you'd give it more of a chance yeah
yeah there might be something to that
yeah maybe I have to like see past
the queue I again say
to listeners I want to get it
I'm not trying to be a hater yeah
and there's some things that are
like a one time thing and you
get it like I did space 2020
the restaurant
we haven't talked about this much have you been there Mike
no I've never been I forgot
about it last time we were there we meant to
do it we meant to do it we own an episode
on that yeah what do you think I think it makes it really hard
because it's booked out so far in advance but I got
a reservation
really the experience is really cool the whole
setting is cool they have
incredible carrot cake
okay it's like
I don't know if it's a vegan carrot cake
carrot cake was phenomenal but
again it's one of those things enjoyed it
super cool but it's not one
that I would be like we got to book that again and again
and again it's one of those things you
that's what's so cool about Disney World there's so
many first things to try
some of you might love and become
may become a mainstay but
it's just worth it to give it a shot
once have you been there recently when this
new cake shop has opened up
on the boardwalk that everyone's talking about
you know what I'm talking about I don't know about the cake shop
it's a very expensive cake
shop oh I saw the
construction of it every time I walk by for
like weeks but I have not okay
been in there because I am fascinated
there's a lot of discourse I think they lowered
the prices of the cake okay after
opening because the cake was like thirty dollars for
a slice or something for a slice really
maybe it was twenty five or something but I think it's a little
lower but then some some people went
and like ordered every piece because all the
vloggers the vlogger community there
I just am impressed with how big
it's growing every day but there's I've watched
multiple vlogs now
of people trying all the cakes
it does seem like they like the cakes
seems like cakes are good but okay I am
excited it's a treat it's worth treating yourself
some type of that's yeah that's a crazy price so I'm
excited I don't know maybe
there's a eighteen dollar cake
I forget what the lowest
yes
I think the restaurants that I've really
enjoyed the most at Epcot are
Le Selye in Canada
it's a great setting
phenomenal food
and then the Mexico restaurant
we should do the ride after
I haven't sat down there I've only done the bar
yeah the bar is wonderful
yeah I mean you gotta like that's crowd
you gotta like get in and get out immediately
yeah drink it outside
yeah yes but like but as I've said
before like like downing
downing a margarita really fast
like to try to time it till right when you jump
on that boat ride oh my god that's the greatest
and it's a great atmosphere before
the ride that's a lot of it
that's perfect it's a perfect place to walk
around yeah the vibes in there are
perfect yeah it's that escape
like when you get on that ride you feel
like you're in some little
area in Mexico yeah you know you've got
the people playing it's just again
it's not like a rollercoaster or anything it's just a vibe
that is pleasant yeah boy
I love the way you do that I love
the way you go there I love that it's about
kind of like taking your time and it's
hotel oriented
I'm trying to think
anything else why would like is it
anything that you're like
anything that you would
hasn't been doing it for you that you want to change
or like it's something that they've closed
that you're like
or like any of these like recently
announced things that you're particularly excited
about I think so Cars Land
I think is one of the best creations
that they have at either park in
Disneyland I think Cars Land is
phenomenal and I think
Disneyland you can
tell how handcrafted it was
the theming is incredible
and I think the Mark Twain boat
fits there
you know because you have New Orleans
the Tom Sawyer Islands great the railroad
the way it all works together
so I totally get that and then in World
it's a little bit more forced it doesn't
quite have that charm that
land does so I think
what they're trying to do because
with with land they expanded
with the Star Wars world which is
which is great you have everything right there
and I think they're worried with Magic Kingdom
that nobody's really doing the
Mark Twain boat because it doesn't really have the
space and I think they know they
can spice it up by doing cars there
right right this is good as it being said
without Jason here I think Jason might be
livid at any discussion that taking away the boat
but it's funny can any of us even name
which boat that is?
because it's weirdly not Mark Twain
it's some weird other name
I can't remember what it is
so you're maybe positive
on this change happening that's interesting
yeah I mean again I love
having the old school feeling it's a nice
breather but when I
went to land I just saw
how well done that was and how well it works
for Fantasmic at land
because Fantasmic in
world is at Hollywood Studios and it's in a whole
amphitheater and it's really laid out
it's got its corner but in land they work it
into the with the Peter Pan boat coming
in so land just has its fixture
but I think that area
in world could I
don't think people will miss it within a year
I think once Cars Land is up it's got a
new vibe I was
surprised because I do love keeping
the OG but I really
think worlds a different
Magic Kingdom it's a different
beast than Disneyland yes like it's got
the bigger castle it's just it's
so I think it could use a little bit
innovation and I think if it's done right
I think people will be happy with it
wow that's a cool positive opinion
to hear because I feel like I don't think we've like
particularly weighed in either way
on that but for sure like the
vlogger I think Disney
online is like furious about
the Cars Land and the river and there's
there's kind of the worst of it I think
you'll still wait oh so there's going to be like cars zooming by
just right by
we have a bet
will you be able to hear engine noise
from Haunted Mansion and Disney
oh right
right so we're like okay
if they can block it out
it's a success I forget who has the bet with
one and who I don't remember who bet on what
yeah yeah but I am more of the mind
with Mater farting maybe
will you be able to hear Mater fart from the Haunted Mansion
that assumes that Mater farts anywhere
because I don't think he doesn't in the existing
Radiator Springs racers so
does he wait a minute somebody farts
when the big the tractors
when they go tractor tipping the tractors fart
the tractors fart yes because my son's
obsessed with this right now
and you know what he used to be very afraid of it
and now he's now it's his favorite scene
nice to know that kids
can overcome these fears that's what
the parks are all about but yeah I think
people are like it's just going to be like
hamfisted in there and they're just putting it in for
merch and I'm a little bit of the mind of like
let's see what Imagineers can pull off
and how they weave it all together I think if they do it right
I think it'll bring some excitement
to that area because Haunted Mansion
it's more of like an East Coast theme it doesn't have
the New Orleans vibe
so I think there's some theming there that
they can work with I will say
I'm not sure about
Rock and Roller Coaster I'm not sure how that becomes
the Muppets yeah yes because
just the vibe of
Rock and Roller Coaster next to
Tower of Terror it's got a nice
feel to it so the Muppets I'm yeah
that'll be a little
confusing I think I'm not sure how
that's going to be my favorite choice
yeah it's interesting it's like
a lot of weight I think
becomes on that pre-show
on the former Steven Tyler
and Leonna Douglas I think it's like to make
that's going to have to tie a lot together
because I think you were saying Mike and they said it wasn't
on like how does it it's not
a ride where you can like do too much like
you're passing you pass through like a big
oh like it has to be so broad strokes
so how do you get Muppets
are all about like details and small
things so how does that work as a
yeah I agree there's a little skepticism
so that's that's tricky because it's an exciting
like
blasting ride and it works with
the concert and it works with Aerosmith
you know if you look at Splash
Mountain and then became Tiana's
that that theming
you know it doesn't have Splash
Mountain had a villain and it had a goal
but the theming with Tiana still works
it's still charming it still has a
musical element to it
if you like that ride I don't think you
you come away like
that discerned but
going from Aerosmith to
the Muppets with you know
I don't know are you going to how do
you feel about Aerosmith are you going to miss Aerosmith because Mike's
a big Aerosmith guy I think you're
like I don't think that's all I don't think your
feelings are 100 percent because you're
sad Aerosmith's going away I think you have other
concerns but that seems like part of it right
like well it's part of it it just
yeah I don't I can't it's the ride
is so fast it feels
right yes like
I don't know it could be like I
would honestly if they said like it was going to be Metallica
and it's called like ride the lightning
oh okay
that'd be that'd be bad because Metallica
is one of my favorite bands but like
something that's literally the speed
and rock and roll are my
concerns and I'm like the Muppets are
rather than animal pretty gentle
like it doesn't I don't know
because the feeling of the
ride is so much for me of like
what about can you picture
that is a fast song
yeah but not really
I feel like what I like about rock and roll
I mean that's not
yeah I'm just
trying to think of anything I'm not against the Muppets
I'm just saying I think I feel like somebody
was saying like what is it going to be like rainbow connection
well no first of all that's not a Dr. Teeth
song and second of all but it's not going to be
I don't think it's going to be Dr. Teeth and I don't even know that
they're going to stick to Muppet songs
because it says other music
they like teased other music acts as
well oh that's a little scary
so it could be non Muppets
it could be Aerosmith songs sung by
Miss Piggy and Meghan Trainor that's what
I said and guys joked but might not
be far off is that you'll
have like six new Muppet
songs that could be other
songs I am nervous given the
the kind of performers who do the Christmas
specials
are you into the Christmas specials do you watch
those like on ABC to try to like
get your Disney Christmas magic
I haven't seen too many I did
do the when I was at the parks I did do
the Mickey's Christmas night
and that is a really cool experience
because they leave the lights on
in Space Mountain oh yes I yes I want
to do this so bad
with Christmas lights
it's really cool I want to see this
and then another thing I was going to
mention is on the not so scary
Halloween party they have live
actors like on Pirates of the Caribbean
the Pirates come alive
and Haunted Mansion you have ghosts
like people like with the tombstones
which is a good one
but I have not yeah I haven't seen too many
of the ABC specials I did love
Mickey's Christmas Carol growing
up
my guy Billy Corgan now
is back in the
not back now in the Disney family he did the
last Christmas special so if you do
a Billy Corgan
collaboration with one of the Muppets
you think maybe this may be a
Smashing Pumpkins is coming?
I'm just saying
it's hard to look
of all the bands you talk about
I can certainly handle
Smashing Pumpkins and Tonight Tonight
on a coaster would be pretty
moving right awesome yeah it'd be like
going on the moon trip that they
go on in the video that's maybe actually
fuck the Muppets let's Smashing Pumpkins
on Rock and Roller Coaster
what I like about the Rock and Roller Coaster is
the versatility of it yeah
it's like it's a cool fit it's like not something
I would have like guessed but it's a really cool fit
and then the Monsters Inc
I think could be
unique in that area
yeah it's gonna be good it's just
a bummer that what had to
what had to go to make it happen
you mean Rock and Roller Coaster not Monsters Inc
I mean the Muppets
yeah I think the Monsters Inc
will be good to great
I'm not worried about that being good
it's just like yeah couldn't you put it somewhere else
you ever been to the restaurant Pizza Rizzo
Muppet what do you think about
this here's another big debate on the show
I won't even lead you to it
because we haven't actually eaten the food there
any opinions about Pizza Rizzo
which will presumably be going away
with the Muppet Courier going away
I thought it was good
the ones that have stood out to me
at Hollywood Studios
the Sci-Fi Dine-In
oh yeah
the theming is awesome
I haven't done that in forever
I know it was still there
wow really
I think I realized it a year or two
when we were doing the show
the Roundup Barbecue
Woody's Roundup Barbecue
is surprisingly fantastic
and then there's another hack
I think is great that a lot of
I found out about it recently
but if you go to like
Brown Derby which is like their nice
kind of old Hollywood school restaurant
you can get a VIP pass
to watch Fantasmic
and sit in the front
all you gotta do is just go to one of those restaurants
and have the receipt and you can go
see Fantasmic like VIP seating
this is good to have you in general
because we are so Disneyland
oriented and I'm sure there's a lot
of people who are frustrated by like
the giant swaths of things we've never talked about
because you're naming restaurant after restaurant
that I'm like ultimately I have
I've only been to
Disney World way more than most people I know
but still not enough to like
we're missing out on a lot
all these steak houses
there's so much on the list
that we have like a plan
and when we go to do and then
we do 20% of it
we gotta go for two weeks
that's what I'm saying you just run out of time
even I haven't tried
like so many different things because you're like next time
next time and then
but at least you get to like build that list up
forever
here's what I'm thinking if we end up around the time
of Epic Universe opening up
I'd like to make that a win instead of an F
there's been a few things happening in Los Angeles
I have a new little baby
lots going on
so
what I'm hoping is by the time we get
there that we will still be able to and some of it
is confirmed be able to do rip ride rocket
because I keep chickening out every time I go
and I want to do this shitty coaster that
no one likes before they close it
that hurts me I will do it
I hate the thing I hate the way it goes
up I will do it
are you a universal person or are you mainly Disney?
I've gone there several times
Pizza Rizzo I don't know
there's been no announcement of closure
as far as I know that we'll be able to do Pizza Rizzo
Muppets
one last time and jelly rolls
jelly rolls supposedly closing as well
now just don't make me do it at the end
of the night because at the end of the night I need
my little swan dolphin nap and knowing
that I'm staying there next time
I'm sure of this I've been dreaming of this for
months it's been a beacon it's been my
lighthouse during a very insane time
of my life so you gotta really
keep me on the hook because I might just drift
to sleep
if it's one Bon Jovi cover
too many I'm like guys
I got serenity ahead of me
which if you had to hear one Bon Jovi
cover what song would you want?
Oh Runaway I like Runaway
yes that one I can
that's got a good that's got that like
cool 80s
what is on your list
next time you go what's strongest
on your list either that you haven't done or that you're dying
to do again what's number one?
the next one is I want to
eat at the Moroccan restaurant in Morocco
God I've eaten at a Moroccan
Moroccan restaurant there is there
is there only one or is there
there's two there's the one that's
on the water that sort of like sit down like
pick up like more snacky and then there's the
Marrakesh which is deep in Morocco
okay I have done that for lunch and I
remember being pretty surprised at the
quality I thought that was pretty top notch but I bet
is it even is dinner even
nicer yeah I think it's more like yeah it's like
a sit down they do a different menu and then there's a
secret pop up where
Aladdin and Jasmine will appear in the
back room with these like lit up lanterns
you know these hacks
they do like a secret photo thing
it's like really really cool
yeah
so next up is the beach club
okay oh great
I gotta cross that one off that was my second
trip of my life such fond
memory like sand pool might be my favorite
could be my favorite yes and that oh
my god the shipwreck pool
how have we never done an episode
just the shipwreck pool
I'll be the least articulate I've ever been in my life
to say that it's cool and then you go inside and it goes all
the way across the walkway
such a little kid energy for me and they have one of the
coolest little like old
school restaurants called Beaches and Cream
yeah yeah of course which is
a really good one I haven't been Jason's
I've been yeah those signs
also the signage has never changed
around it is such late 80s
perfection just like that's what I love
about Swan and Dolphin it's just like it is
1988 it's the way I saw
the first time I went to Disney World like has not changed
yeah and it's got the most like
impactful you see those swans
from so far away I was gonna ask you guys
is there a ride
that you just like
secretly avoid or like slightly
afraid of or is like intimidated
rip ride other than rip ride rocket
that you just hope doesn't come
up yeah I don't I'm
not dying to do like full
centrifuge mission space
yeah I don't like mission space
I used to be such a
it's been a whole thing I used to be such a wimp
about like maybe the group just won't want to go on
Splash Mountain like the drop was too much
for me at one point and I'm happy to say now
I've done Tiana Tiana coming
it rolls off my back
my back now I'm fine on that
now but
yeah what I'm sure there's a big
one I just haven't even
Everest oh I love Everest
I loved Everest but I'd
be I'd be nervous getting on it again
it was like maybe it was maybe like one percent
out of my comfort zone
in a good way I mean I loved it but
I'd be I will be sitting in that chair again
kind of with heart pounding for sure
it's weird it's like mine is like
goofy sky school
or the yeah good choice
ferris wheel like
oh ferris wheel I've never done the ferris wheel
I haven't done the one that like
the cars that slide and even I went in the
regular one and like slow heights
is kind of a weird thing for me so like
when the goofy sky school is like
it's on the edge slow and on the edge like
that starts making me go in
a way that when you're going fast on a coaster
it doesn't that's in the same way like
um uh rip ride
rocket going up like that which
I've done it once at this other
similar coaster it nots
that freaks me out like
I just kind of panic a little bit on the way
up so that's those are more
of what I get freaked out by
yeah and I like I'll
guess we have to do the swinging
cars eventually you'll be
okay I think you'll be okay you can you can zen
your way through that probably but I truly
kind of had a little panic attack doing the
regular car I kind of disassociate
like I disassociated for like 20 seconds maybe you wouldn't
like that look you don't need to you
owe this audience nothing you owe the show
I owe them everything
oh well that's a but now I look bad
that's a much better quote
my body is theirs I put my life
on the line wrap a go pro to me and I'll
do it is there anything you avoid
so I was
terrified of velocity coaster
so every time I was there
I'd be a group and like this is the best freaking
ride oh my god you leave your
soul behind you got to do it and I kept thinking like
every time
it broke down and I'm like
yes next time
finally I had to face
going on and I couldn't back
out tried the whiskey thing
okay so I had
that liquid courage going in
it's still terrified the hell out of me
like you're going so fast
and you are like out of your seat for
part of it it's and so I'm like
closing my eyes and like
so I did it once and it's
still knocked me out so
that's one that I'm like
tentative on okay
okay wow didn't you still yeah
that doesn't help that doesn't help my cause
I don't know I know I got to
it's fast like it's like Tron is like
57 miles an hour Tron
is nothing compared to I know
it's not I can tell yeah
Velocicoaster they said is like 75
but it feels like 30 miles
an hour faster it's I think
about it I love I did it three times
last time really yeah and it's my like my
favorite thing I couldn't stop
talking about it for months after we did it
I was like I take it back to the Velocicoaster
I wish I could be like you and it doesn't affect me
it's crazy cause I was
I'm not such a crazy coaster guy
but for whatever
like I felt like this euphoria came
over me it's a great ride I mean it's a great ride
it just hits like it's so smooth
is the thing too cause like Hulk I
understand if you go come on Hulk
and Hulk rattles your skull
that sounds terrible to me Hulk rattles
your skull so thoroughly
Velocicoaster is fast but
it's smooth you're like floating
the whole time and I was just like laughing
like a madman like
you know what I think it's one of the
best rides at any of these parks
is Hagrid's yeah
absolutely no I'm a big Hagrid's fan
that I can handle that's like right
that's intense but that's an intensity I can
do and it doesn't do like the
move you know we're not like
there's not inversion it's that bit you know what it is
the what are they cause they call it the top hat
on Velocicoaster I'm so scared of the top hat
I don't know if I can do the top hat
I don't fear anything
while I'm on the Velocicoaster
for some strange reason and I fear everything
in my regular life yeah I was going to say
all your fears go away
that's for me wow I fear everything
24 7 except when I'm on
Velocicoaster I love how you can do like the toughest
ride and be like oh for whatever
reason yeah you're routed in an interesting
way I sure am
listeners of this show know that
you've been listening long enough
for a while I avoided Space
Mountain in Orlando
I don't know why like as a kid
my first time going I could go on it back to
back to back yeah and then one of those times
I just felt kind of like shaken
which luckily
went away but I will say
the Space Mountain at land
I think is a better ride
yeah well it also feels
rickety in Florida
it feels old and like it's similar to the Matterhorn
out here it feels like a 70's
this feels old
so I think in that way it's charming
and you feel like the old school
Disneyland but the last
time I went on the Matterhorn
I mean it's a it's a rough ride but I
was like joking with my
friend and like the way I leaned up
the bar hit my knee
oh yeah and I was like blinding
pain I was like take
a break from Matterhorn yeah I might
be done with Matterhorn until I
do something yeah I don't need it doesn't give
me anything that outweighs the
bad stuff yeah the only
thing they're gonna do is implode it like there's
no way that they're gonna fix the problem
because it's impossible to fix the problems
with it because I feel like
constructed I do love how Disneyland
stays authentic to a lot
the best way that it can but
Matterhorn I know there's a better
ride that could be in there
sure yeah but you're right
so we know like the next level yeah they gotta
rebuild it though that's the thing and supposedly
of course somebody I've said this on the show before is
a fact I read that they need to
rebuild it within 25 years just
because it is falling apart the structure is
falling apart so like they will have
to do something to it within
let's say 20 25 years unless
there's a horrible day where the Matterhorn
topples over it's possible just
tips yeah oh we would all
we all have children and all of us
are inner children would all weep
well but maybe if people were under they could catch
it and they could push it back up save it heroically
right when you guys go to world
what are you excited
because you guys you guys go to land frequently
what are you excited to see what are you excited
to like oh I mean
it is like Disney World
is becoming like me trying
to tap into the 90s a lot which
is why it's like mundane stuff like
people mover and
country bears that
Sunny Eclipse hasn't changed
I love that you knew who Sunny Eclipse was
we're big Sunny Eclipse heads yeah going on the monorail
hanging in the Polynesian
lobby it's a lot of like nostalgia
just walking around contemporary
but then other hotel stuff
that I haven't done because we didn't
get much of a chance to do that last trip
yeah so like some other
going to some other hotels Hooptie
do review I've never done and I meant
to do that last time and that's still on the list
for sure yeah and that's been going forever
but it's nice to have guardians now as a like
that's not nostalgia that is a
current cutting edge thing that kicks
ass that's like you know because
you start to fear that like is Universal
getting the upper hand and Disney isn't
producing at the
volume that that Universal is but
but guardians is you were the one
that made me go back
and get back into guardians because I did it
the first time kind of made me uncomfortable and I was
like huge into Tron and you're like
no guardians number one Tron
too and I'm like oh it's like okay let me
go back and give it a shot and I went back I
got conga oh great
that really did it for me for
whatever reason so I have my favorite song in
the world I just like I don't know it's made
for that ride yeah yeah it really works
for me yeah and I caught it I'm like
okay I get I get what he's saying wow
oh great I'm glad I was part of that I let
the fear like the fear go and I just
and it was like now it's
a brilliant it's a brilliant fantastic and I like
your whiskey plan that's good stuff
I feel like you wind it down I'm so
happy you've you've you've talked to us for
for so long here and just to get to talk
Disney with you after talking room
with you the thing that's echoing in my head
really to tie it all together is just that
I wish the great movie ride was still
there and that they would do some kind
of redo and acknowledge one of the most
prominent films I feel of
the 21st century if only there was
a room sequence in
the great movie ride that I think
it deserves it very badly
yeah I think
I think there's a number I think you could it could
be all animatronics but also you know it could
be one of the things where the the gangster
or the cowboy get on the car with I think if
I think if Chris R got
in the car with you and threatened
you like asked for your money the
guests money I like that
yeah yeah I think that's that's as strong
as old west bandits
and it's it's funny you say that because I was
on I was at the man's Chinese
there where it's now Mickey's runaway yeah
yeah and I was in line with my family
and these two guys
come up and they're like
Greg Sestero wow oh
my god we get a photo and
I just thought to myself like
12 year old me would saw
this would be like holy crap oh man
I had no idea like
what what what did you do I was like you
can't see that movie yet
you gotta be 18
it pains me that I like you know like
we've talked about Aaron
my wife and we were both like at those screenings
together and then we started dating after that now we've
made two children together and we're like oh it'd be great
to like share a movie that helped us get
together no maybe not till
you're no maybe maybe they'll never be an age
where I want to watch the very
awkward sex scenes in this film with our sons
but we'll see we'll see
yeah they'll find it eventually
but that was the fact that you
you've told this story now of like
arriving in Hollywood with
a dream to go live at a weird apartment
and your key doesn't work and you gotta
go to a Sunset Boulevard shady
motel and now you're at
man's Chinese theater
the fake version in Florida and
you are the star being recognized
this is a beautiful
what a roller coaster ride
pun intended
that's beautiful
well look thank you for
talking with us for a long time thank you
for making for pushing
the room into existence
and clearly you must be
at this point that like look the joy
I've gotten from it
clearly the joy you've gotten from it
traveling the world in this Disney
world existence it's just so like
it's been a beacon of joy for me
like the goddamn Disney parks are
and I hope it's the same for you too
I mean it really gave us like
so much in such a
weird way that's I mean it's what you'd hope
you know if you made Back
to the Future a movie that classically
worked you know it's somehow
roundabout hit a home run in the opposite
direction
to the degree where like every moment of Back to the
Future works every moment in the room
doesn't work but in a way that I want
to experience again and again
it's really it just it delivers
I think I mean it shows with you
and I think with my
experience is like if you have the right mindset
you can turn any situation
into something that will work
for the best and I think that's what
you had the sense of humor
to like give this crazy
trailer that you saw a shot
and like root for something
that didn't make didn't work
or nobody else got at the time
Tommy called to me like he called to you in reality
yeah it's a wonder there was there's just something
I guess I chased what you were chasing
in this weird other way yeah
yeah more today than ever I
really feel like something out there
there's a cinematic god that like
dots connect and
like Tinkerbell put some dust out there
and you grabbed it and we're like
oh man oh geez I'm
happy to with health to be part of the story at all
is an honor and I'm glad you're part of the podcast
the ride story Greg Sestero
you survived podcast the ride this is
a blast so happy to have you let's exit
through the gift shop is there anything
you would like to plug
so I am I am gonna
make Home Alone Lost
in Disney will be right it'll be an animated
graphic novel wow
I'm gonna hope to do something
with that whether it's like an animated movie
or something with it to bring
it into existence for my passion for movies
and for Disney and then I'm making
a UFO abduction movie that I'm
that I'm writing and directing called Forbidden Sky
wow wow fantastic
geez geez that's so exciting
and that like that you're like writing
side got lit up and you're doing you're doing all these great
things with it also I mean
I gotta recommend the disaster artist pick
it up if if you see it
go buy it or just like
grab it at a bookstore there was the coolest thing for me
ever to be like that I could go to a bookstore find that
wow great book about the movie and then
there's a picture of me in the book in
so many Barnes and Nobles there's a photo of
me I like
just fantastic disaster artist
the book's wonderful
your shows how do people
if people want to see you in their
town because you do a lot of touring
how do they keep track of that stuff
so on social media I'm at Greg
Sestero on Instagram and Facebook
and Twitter great great
yeah well go see Greg if he
comes to a town near you
as for us for three bonus episodes every
month check out podcast the ride the second gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP
tier club three you'll find all of that at
patreon.com slash podcast the ride
we'll be back with something else soon hopefully
back again with Jason soon god
it's just sucks to be without Jason
you know you are part of my life I could
not go on without you you are
tearing me apart Jason
forever
dog
this has been a forever
dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson Jason
Sheridan Scott Gardner
Brett Baum Joe
Cilio and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts
please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe
to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you
get your podcasts keep up with
the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team
and liking our page on Facebook