FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcasts may contain moments of Father Serenity,
Poncho Gifting,
Frog Love,
Cold Place History of Coolness,
and we finally take a ride on Tiana's Bayou Adventure.
Hey, we gotta get to the party!
It's podcast, The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast, The Ride, where we will do an episode about this ride,
even though we started so many Change.org petitions to stop it.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hi, yes, mask off.
We've been fighting so hard to change this ride back.
We just finally feel comfortable to tell you.
Is it like, do you try to get more signatures into one,
or do you try to get 50 separate petitions all with a good amount of signatures,
which is what we ended up electing to do?
I mean, we were using every email address to start as many different Change.org accounts as we could,
and they still built this thing.
Yeah, it's weird.
I mean, I drew a lot of pictures of me smiling going on the original ride,
and I sent them to everyone's homes, the Imagineers' homes, the executives' homes,
and that didn't work either.
You want to take this away from me?
You want to wipe this smile from Young Me's memory face?
This is what it is.
Now it is frown.
Now you have turned smile into frown, which is upside down.
That's right.
I wrote, now you have turned smile into frown on every photo.
In blood.
Yeah.
Welcome.
Hey, returning triumphantly to the main feed.
It's Jason Sheridan.
Hi, I'm back.
Hey, welcome back, my friend.
Thank you.
Good to have you here.
Welcome back.
Although people may have heard you on Club 3,
where we talked about the sweat box in the recent past fun episode.
Check it out at www.patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
But glad to have you back, buddy.
Thank you so much.
And look at that hat.
You got that hot stuff hat.
I got this hot stuff.
He's got a hot stuff hat, yeah.
Scott got me.
Up at CityWalk, up at the construction site that is modern CityWalk.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, right.
Something's going to have to happen with that soon.
Otherwise, it's going to leak into every other episode.
I know, because that's all we want to talk about, really.
Again, it's all changing so quickly.
At the time that I went up there, it was much less the case
to where recently other people have gone and said,
anybody been lately?
And we're like, yeah.
And they said, it's grim up here.
It's not looking good up here.
People don't like it up here.
So every week, it's worse and worse.
But it must be all in service of getting it better and better.
You would think.
But look, Slice House Pizza is going where the Sparkies went.
Oh, by Tony Geminini?
Is that his name, Geminini?
No, I'm not saying that right.
I call him Tony G from where I'm from.
And this is something last night when I was discussing with my family,
and my sister said, oh, yeah, Tony G?
You mean Tony G from Slice House?
And I go, yeah, of course, Tony G.
So you're on a nov of shorthand with Tony G.
Yes.
But is this also, with apologies, Jason, and happy or beg,
but is this a Jason-esque Beppo Pepo ploy where you're faking familiarity
so that you don't have to attempt to pronounce the name?
Oh, I actually don't know the name.
I'm not pretending to not know.
You'll just admit that you don't know the name.
I don't know the name, yes.
I'm going to take Jason's word for it.
You took the biggest stab of it than any of us have.
I'm not tracking the Slice House enough to know.
I can just picture the logo and promotional photo in my head,
like I saw it yesterday.
But I...
Geminini or Geminani, which I don't think is right.
So Geminani seems right.
I think Doughboys have covered Slice House.
I believe with maybe Susser or somebody, yeah.
Did they cover it? And apologies, I didn't hear the episode.
Did they cover it because it took over the space
that was not Shake...
What the hell is the one?
Steak and Shake.
Yes.
Which also had a buy.
That is taken by Big Laurie.
Right.
And now it's Slice House by Jim Mignani.
Which is going...
Which despite having a location in the Burbank area,
is now getting a separate city walk.
Exactly, yeah.
Okay.
And you spoke highly of this place.
This seems to resemble a restaurant that people like,
which is a rarity for the city walk area.
Right.
Are you against it then for that reason?
Well, it's a good question.
If it was up at City Food and they declared
they would make it 25% worse,
it would make me more comfortable.
I mean, they're not going to declare it,
but it will be 25% worse.
Well, let's see.
But Sparky's is prime real estate.
Terrible spot for wines.
That's, I feel like, so cramped down there.
Well, that's a good point.
I don't know what the setup will be
because there's a lot of room in that store.
So you could potentially have part of a line
snaking around there unless they...
I think we're in line territory?
I feel like I've never seen a line.
Well, because you can buy slices.
So if there is a high traffic point or a time of day,
then perhaps there would be a line for slices.
But I don't know.
We'll see.
We don't know yet.
But aren't people, you go all the way up there,
don't you want to get some of the delicious slice pizza
available in the park?
Yeah.
I can't even, as I say that, I can't even conjure.
I mean, I know it's there.
Yeah.
I know there's some bad Italian place
kind of in the streets of the world area.
Right.
There's probably,
nobody's ever had slices of pizza at Universal Studios.
Do they have a chain in there even?
I don't think so.
Is there like a...
Well, there's a Simpsons pizza.
Isn't there?
I think.
Like in Luigi kind of?
Yeah, I think so.
I've never had it, but there's Simpsons pizza.
Do they have like a little mini pizza hut
or something in there anywhere?
What you're thinking of,
it used to be Pizza Hut down on the lower lot.
Yes, that is what I'm thinking of.
Yeah.
Pizza Hut and Panda Express combo,
and then I think it's in Jurassic Cafe.
And that's cool too,
because like Pizza Hut and Panda Express,
25% worse at City Walk,
then you move it all the way down to lower lot
where it gathers another 25, 35.
How many more percentages do we lose?
There is a math equation to do how bad a chain will get
depending on its location at Universal Studios.
I don't know the numbers.
We'd have to talk to somebody that's a real expert in it.
And how you calibrate that.
This seems like touring plans as Len Testa,
who's like a computer scientist,
would have an equation to work out exactly.
Okay, so you take say McDonald's.
You move McDonald's to the lower lot.
It's going to get 17% worse,
which means that the burger will be 31% colder,
and the cheese will be the same,
which will still give a good taste,
but the goo will be 12% less salty,
which makes its taste.
Like, he'll know all of that.
He could probably figure it out.
Len Testa at a X-ray machine,
just staring at the rumble of a tummy.
Just watching somebody who has eaten
theme park Panda Express,
how it passes through them, how it liquefies,
how it turns into just like black bile in their stomach,
and then writing down, very good, okay, I see.
Like, Jason and I in the Star Wars
Bacta Tank looking thing where we're in liquid,
and Len is just looking at our bodies
as we digest the McDonald's food
at the Universal Studios or the Pizza Hut,
and then he's looking at the levels
and how much we're enjoying it.
And then he takes all the equipment off,
like, all right, you're free to go.
You guys look at each other.
Well, want to go back to pizza?
Yeah, sounds good.
Sounds good.
See, with fast food in a theme park, though,
I thought you were going to go with the more upsetting
visual image of the precogs
and the goo in Minority Report.
Oh, that works, too.
Because some of that food has definitely
caused me to fucking freak out.
Well, that's me.
I'm a precog.
Right.
I shake around.
You're the one that they get out.
I get a vision.
Jason and Mike will have upset tummies,
and then I pass back out again,
and you guys again look at each other and say,
well, pizza?
Yeah, that reminds me, pizza.
Step over your body to get a chalupa.
Do you sometimes, when you're navigating different apps
and checking and stuff, do you imagine that you're doing it
like Tom Cruise in Minority Report?
Oh, with the ball?
In the air, yeah.
The carving ball?
I mean, like, up at the future screen
where you're sliding everything around.
Like, you see through the matrix,
and you move 20 things around in two seconds.
I think it certainly looks that cool.
I think it definitely makes me look cool.
Like it does Tom Cruise in Minority Report.
So, Scott, you're Colin Farrell at the wooden ball
going like, how is my tummy going to hurt today?
It's like, okay, constipated, but painful.
Probably one of the worst options you can get.
Constipated, but painful.
That's a horrifying phrase.
You can't do it.
You're trying, but you can't do anything.
You'd think being stuck would stop the pain.
It would think, yeah.
Well, this is for, yeah, we do have to figure out
how to address City Walk and stuff,
which is always more of a priority for us
than new theme park attractions,
which miraculously is something
that we are talking about today.
And I know you're trying to move on,
but I will have to say I do have
an Insomnia Cookies story from college.
Oh, Insomnia Cookies is moving into City Walk 2,
City Walk Hollywood as well.
Oh, I see.
I sent you a picture.
Sorry to cut you off, Scott, but it was necessary.
I was almost to the end.
I had said T on, and then I was stopped
to talk about cookies.
I sent Jason a picture.
I ate an Insomnia Cookie in San Diego
like a month and a half ago or a month ago.
I'm not up on things enough to know
that Insomnia Cookies is something that's coming.
Yes, that is coming, and it's coming
in where Mini Monster was.
And Mini Monster is no more.
Mini Monster is gone.
Mini Monster is gone, yeah.
Geez, boy, it's all changing so quickly.
Do you want to tell your Insomnia Cookies story?
No, no.
That's to say.
That's the sense of tease.
All right, get everybody.
Everyone's mouths are watering now
thinking about your cookie story, right?
My rival, like, every time I look at it.
Oh, it's a negative story.
It's bad.
Well, it's bad because I did it to my side.
It seems like a fine establishment.
Oh.
This is, again, we're right back in City Walk
Saga territory where you're blaming yourselves
instead of the establishment.
It is time for you to stop blaming the mirror
and look at the world and see what the world
is doing to your body.
It's the Radiohead song Just, right?
Do it to yourself, you do.
That's what you do to no one else.
I did it to myself, I did.
That's Jason's anthem for.
And not, not, to some in chocolate and pouring.
I'll be back real soon.
All right, let me finish the title.
Right.
Uz by U Adventure.
That is the attraction that we are talking about.
In my head, a new attraction as I stare at my notes
that tell me that it has been running since June
in the Magic Kingdom.
Yeah, it is an old attraction at this point.
It is.
Only November 2024 in Disneyland.
As has been discussed, a cursed time
and a difficult time to get there.
We still all haven't been, but close enough,
close enough to actually talk about a fairly
recent ride.
Yes.
And maybe not a full, you know, it's, look,
it's not a fully new attraction, as you know.
It is a bit of a reskin, a bit of a re-theme.
But, you know, a lot going on there.
And, yeah, here we are.
Specifically, you've been, Mike.
I have, yes.
I've been.
Jason, you've not.
I have not been.
Sure.
Well, I hope you don't mind us,
I hope you don't mind listening
or chip in based on if you watch
ride throughs, do you know?
Oh, I've watched a lot of ride throughs.
Do you know the names of some of the furry friends?
I did at one, I don't know, I always forget them.
But I like the furry friends.
I do too, but what would be the way that you would
even retain the names of the furry friends
besides looking them up?
You'd have to look them up?
Yeah, because is there ever, like,
is there spot these friends in the queue?
Is there any, because, like, the names aren't really.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
They don't have name placards once you're in the thing.
No, no, and there's, yeah, because there's, like,
original ride characters, but they don't seem to,
yeah, explain their names very well.
Maybe, I don't know, maybe there's, I have actually,
now that I think about it, I don't know if there's
gift shops that have the characters,
maybe there's some of that going on.
There is a little, like, they did raise berets,
and there is a little theme in there, but yes,
I don't know that the characters are so publicized,
what it would explain.
They're kind of, it's like it was leaked in a post,
not leaked, but, like, given to us, the nerds,
to, like, here, and just so you know,
this is the name of the possum.
Yes, Bo.
Yeah.
Bo.
Bo the opossum.
You know, see, this is good.
I'm gonna have to stare at notes.
Bo is kind of a sleeper.
He doesn't move a lot, and he's in a couple,
I think he's in a couple spots.
Well, a lot of these characters have moments
of not moving a lot.
Well, yes, if you're talking about limited motion, yes,
and also if they're broken half a day, yes.
Yes, yeah, yeah, which does seem to be the situation.
Which is often happening, yes.
I think we, I'm not sure in what order to attack this exactly.
We could talk about a little bit of the history.
I will really quickly say that after some of the travails,
which I've told the audience about,
I was finally able to make it down there
and go on this ride, which was a nice thing.
Magic Key finally got it up and running.
I didn't realize until I was about to do it
that my trip to do this ride was my first time
in Disneyland Park in two years.
Wow, is it that long?
I don't know.
Yes, I had done one California adventure
because that has become Aaron and I's priority,
even though we did that with our oldest.
So, you know, we'd been there, and I've done, oh, my God,
a couple of paradise just me and my son Trader Sam's
drinking a ZIPA.
Just me and my boy at 12 o'clock.
Oh, those goods are so much easier to drink.
You must be loving those.
Yeah, well, it's like medicine has to be fruit flavored
for him to understand.
You get maybe a little bit of a citrus,
so it helps it go down.
Yeah, a little fruit in there.
Yeah, and you throw it in a sippy cup,
and he's none the wiser.
Just falls asleep in the car, that's all.
Anyway, all this to say, here's a recommendation.
Go to Disneyland Park.
It was nice.
I forgot.
I forgot that I like Disneyland.
It was a nice thing to do.
I will say that I went solo because I have a new baby at home,
and I was a lot of guilt on my part
because there's been a lot going on,
and Aaron was like man in the hatches, both kids.
I felt kind of ridiculous saying I'm going to Disneyland for work,
but this was also part of your genius plan
in starting this podcast, thinking many steps ahead
and that we would have to go to theme parks for work,
so I thank you for that plan.
Now it really paid off.
That said, two kids, very difficult.
I felt really bad about it.
I still made it back for bedtime
because that's a process with two.
That's what I've learned,
and I don't want to tuck them in and everything,
but mainly though it was very nice to do,
and I was like I'm here.
I'm going to do all the stuff,
but the calculation I did was I haven't been to Disneyland
as opposed to DCA in a while.
I'm going to do Disneyland specifically
and focus on that partially because I haven't in a while
and partially because if I go down here
and mostly hang out in DCA,
I will feel like I am cheating on Aaron.
I think it will feel like I am out with another woman.
Yeah, because that's a lot of the fondness.
You put fondnesses on these places
based on memories and who you did it with,
and California Adventure is absolutely 20s, 30s,
dating, falling deeper in love.
I was just like I can't cut loose and just be here
while she's sweating it out with the kids,
so I did make that choice.
I will spend the vast majority of the day.
Sitting and drinking a Carthay Manhattan solo,
worse than making out with another lady, I think.
So I didn't do that.
Aaron, I have something to tell you.
Yeah.
Really bad.
Oh my God, what is it?
I don't want to have mince words.
It's really bad.
I had an $18 cocktail.
In the longitude and latitude of the place we go.
I didn't talk to anybody.
I just ordered it.
I didn't talk to the bartender.
I found it miserable.
I tried to spit up in my mouth so that it was mixed
with saliva and I didn't enjoy the taste
while it was going down.
Because I love you.
I do even though I've done what I've done.
You do have to, I don't know,
there's I'm sure like the 100 hacky stand up bits
about this.
Sometimes if you do do a solo trip
because you have to go for work,
I do kind of downplay how much.
I was fine, you know.
I just kind of was in and out.
That's a smart.
You know?
Yeah.
I'm just, I'm not lying, but I'm not being like,
it was great.
I was alone.
I was drinking a beer now.
Watching the Mark Twain go around,
like you dump.
The way all moments have some Simpsons analog,
it's Lisa Comes Back for Mitchie.
Yes, there you go.
That's it.
Which Bart can't see.
How was it?
It was all right.
Beyond this.
It was the greatest movie I've ever seen.
And that's definitely true.
Well, I know you want to try all those sauces
at the country bear barbecue.
Yes.
Well, actually that would have been,
that's something where I could have pointed to
and said, Aaron, it was not so great.
I had to sit and track a bunch of sauces.
Oh, yeah.
That would have actually,
that would have felt the best.
But you're right.
That is probably a way to play it.
And Aaron, if you're listening,
there is something that I played down.
I don't think I really talked about this
when I came home,
because it's a long day.
You don't want to rub it in.
But here, I will say this.
Round three, I do migrate over to California Adventure.
I, just backstory, I've been in a state
called eye-bleedingly busy
since the birth of my son in September.
It's been, I've been at a pitch.
It's been fucking nuts.
So to, in that state,
sit and have an IPA
and a Ghirardelli Sunday
in the Sonoma, which I went and got,
and then brought over to the Sonoma Terrace area
so that I could listen to a wonderful soundtrack
of what I refer to as crap jazz,
early 2000s acoustic guitar jazz
that even I can't defend,
but that I love with every fiber of my being,
because it relaxes me so much.
This, the beer plus the Sunday,
after the way it's been lately,
this was a borderline psychedelic experience.
I was texting people that I honestly feel
like I'm tripping right now.
I feel like I am floating off the ground.
Wow.
It was so crazy and great.
I'm sorry, Aaron, we'll get to,
we will do it as soon as we can.
I wish I didn't know what you were talking about,
but I do know what you're talking about.
You've been there?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I was texting you guys.
Did you have an equivalent?
Yeah, yeah.
I was texting you guys
because I didn't realize you could just have a beer
at one of the, not the quick service restaurants,
but one of the sit-down restaurants
around the Rivers of America and Disneyland.
Not the new, not Tiana's Palace.
Is it a palace or a place?
I forget every time what restaurant I was eating at.
I don't know if it is.
I feel like it might be Palace.
I don't know.
We should know that too.
So I was just sitting there.
I think it's Palace.
Oh, it is Palace.
I mean, that makes sense.
Confusing because place sounds more like a restaurant,
but it's Palace.
They do refer to it as Princess Tiana.
Google, why is it Tiana's Palace and not Tiana's Place?
It's because it's, wait, what?
In the restaurant it is?
Well, no, wait, okay.
You got to do that minus AI search.
No, I don't know if this is AI.
Look, point is it's Palace.
I'm sorry.
You were saying, though, it's not there.
It's another one of those New Orleans Square restaurants
where you didn't know until you got there
that alcohol is available.
Yeah, I forgot because you can get one now on Main Street
and it's all the places that you can't just pick one up and go.
It's the Main Street spot?
It's Carnation, right?
And Carnation's not the, that's...
Carnation, like halfway down Main Street.
Left or right if you're looking at the castle.
On the left side if you're looking at the castle.
Yeah, Carnation Cafe.
Which one is the chicken?
Oh, is that to the, that's the one to the right.
It's an inn.
It's not Jolly Holiday, it's the Plaza Inn, yes.
There you go, okay.
That's the Plaza Inn.
And then, yeah, so I just didn't realize that.
So I had been texting you guys, I remember.
I'm like, I had this big, giant vegetable salad
and some drink and I'm sitting alone and just the calm.
Yeah.
I experienced that, I experienced that
because, you know, having a, we're not,
I'm not nearly as busy as you are,
but just, you know, having a child day to day
and trying to do other stuff.
The bass is still very, yes, of course.
There's a lot of stuff going on.
So when you have sort of these times to yourself,
sometimes it can feel like otherworldly.
Like, I've seen LCD sound system before,
but I saw them whenever in October
and I just had like a drink.
I was alone in the back of the floor
and I felt like I was floating.
Like the beat, the groove was just like taking me over
and I'm sure it was embarrassing to watch if you saw like,
oh, that dad is really feeling himself.
But I know what you're talking about.
What's to say people weren't saying
that very youthful man over there
is feeling himself to an appropriate youthful degree.
Thank you for saying it
because that's what I wanted to say,
but I was trying to be humble about it.
But yeah, some people are like, what's that young man,
what's that young man doing at this show?
This is sort of a band from 20 years ago.
Is he even allowed to drink in here?
Yeah, let me card him.
Police, police, right this way.
You do a lot of like hushed, like if I,
you go to a bouncer or something with a dollar,
with like, with a 20 or more.
And it's like, you know, there's admission.
You don't have to bribe me to get it.
No, no, no, it's not that.
Will you just card me in front of a lot of people?
You just like.
Card me.
Just say I'm a college junior.
I actually did not have my driver's license on me.
And I went to a different show.
I was at a different rock and roll show this week.
And for a second, I was like really thinking to myself,
oh my God, they're gonna card me when I get a drink.
And then there was no question on the bartender's face.
And I'm like, yeah, what are you thinking, man?
Yeah.
You wish.
Yeah, how's the rock and roll show?
Oh, it was great.
It was the guy I kept talking about, M.J. Lenderman.
M.J. Lenderman.
Yeah.
Oh, I listened to it, but you know what?
On the Patreon, we both put up playlists.
And I can't make heads or tails of your hillbilly nonsense.
But your half, if you don't know,
on the second gate, we made playlists.
So I put up a yacht rock thing and Mike put up something
that's half hillbilly nonsense,
half music by people under 35 to prove that you're with it.
And that said music, I listened to a number of those.
There's a lot of good stuff.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, I have not listened to yours.
Or I listened to something a while ago that you made.
I don't forget if it's the same list.
Look, if you've been confused
any time I've talked about yacht rock and you're like,
what, so the Pina Colada song?
No, no, no.
It's none of that shit.
Oh, the yacht that's out there.
Oh, it's a heavenly world.
Hey.
Come with me.
Take a journey with me.
Let me ask, because people are speaking so favorably of it.
Molly Lambert, I think, was talking head on.
Did you like that yacht rock documentary
that came out a few months ago?
Oh, I did indeed.
Yes, HBO Yacht Rock.
Yes, which Molly Lambert is in.
The people who do that yacht rock podcast are in,
who coined the term Hollywood Steve and JD Riznar.
And it is an assessment of the yacht rock world
and story that I sign off on, I agree, with great music,
great artists shout it out.
And the spoiler alert at the end when it's a genius moment
when they call Donald Fagan from Steely Dan and say,
do you want to be part of the yacht rock documentary?
And he says, go fuck yourself.
Right.
Or he leads them on.
And what style of music is that?
What are we talking about?
Oh, yacht rock.
Go fuck yourself.
Hang up.
That's why I love them.
That's why I love them, baby.
That's great.
Anyways, let's veer out of that.
So I just had to share that lame dad tripping situation.
Oh, yeah.
But it was nice.
Great excuse to go.
Thank you, audience, for providing an excuse for us
to go to these places.
In terms of what we're dealing with here, fun fact,
did you know this was not always Tiana's Bayou Adventure?
This was once an attraction called Splash Mountain,
an attraction that opened in 1989.
I was aware of it, but I'm not sure.
You might be interested in Twitter trending topic
I got last night.
That said Splash Mountain told me as much.
So did you.
Why was that?
I mean, some of it, once I saw it,
was just rides where if you could wave a magic wand,
you'd bring it back.
So I'd see Horizons is one and Splash Mountain is one.
Yes.
I would bring back Horizons over Splash Mountain.
No offense to the Splash people, I guess.
Yes, because you essentially have Splash Mountain.
Anyway, go ahead.
I always bring back one that literally no fighter of it exists.
There's nothing there of it.
And I would bring back Create Movie Ride over Horizons,
going to the other one.
Really?
I think so.
Oh, that's a great answer.
I think I would go Horizons.
Someone had like four different things located.
But people were unironically doing like,
let's petition, let's get it back.
These are great questions.
And that is a little incoherent.
I don't know if that's going to happen.
I know what's crazy is I still think, my heart tells me,
unless, well, no.
I mean, I'd love to get E.T. Adventure back in Hollywood.
But it's weirder to say that because you can go to Florida
and experience it.
My knee-jerk is still Maelstrom, even though I don't have
any hate in my heart for Frozen.
I still just, I want to see that mural.
I want to see those unpleasant...
I want to see everybody who yells at you
and tells you not to go to Norway after you've been told
that Norway is pleasant and wonderful.
No, stop!
Get out of Norway!
It's definitely Maelstrom.
The oil rigs in the North Sea.
The proud people of Norway.
Back!
Oh, and the movie.
Look, I'm somebody who rushed through the movie before.
I'd sit in the theater and watch that movie five times,
if I could.
The boring movie with the boring chopping of wood.
It was on my list for like,
hey, let's do this at the beginning of the year.
And then it quickly became like,
hey, need to wait on this one.
Figured out.
Maelstrom's a priority.
I'm physically touching my heart when I talk about it.
It's in all our hearts, just like the spirit
of the people of Norway.
Full of adventure.
Danger, sure, but also pleasant for tourism, you see.
I love it.
Fuck.
But Splash Man.
Splash Man, Disney's first log flume attraction,
a Tony Baxter creation,
imbued with Tony Baxter creativity and magic,
opened in Disneyland Park in 1989,
opened in Disney World and Tokyo Disney
not too long after that.
Initially, the beneficiary of the biggest promotional blitz
in Disneyland history.
We have gone through many different specials
with musical numbers and skits
and things that acknowledge it and earnest
and like different styles of McDonald's tie-ins.
I mean, this might have been the most famous ride on Earth
when it opened.
Yeah, you couldn't avoid it.
Yeah.
It, I would say, proved the marketing might
of the Eisner machine at its peak,
but also the poor impulses of that same machine
to open a ride based on Song of the South in the 80s.
Uh-huh.
You know, 40 years after the film was released
and was controversial then.
Yeah, so it wasn't a retroactive...
Strange.
Oh, you know that scene
in that movie now that we're looking back upon it.
We have reevaluated Song of the South.
No, it was evaluated.
It had been evaluated.
A movie that was protested by the NAACP in 1946.
And yet, as we've been through,
the strangest fact ever to me,
that they did a re-release in the 80s still,
there's like a trial balloon for this.
Yeah, yeah.
Do we get away with this?
Now, I remain no expert in this
and with no desire to keep talking about it, frankly.
No.
Just interesting context for sure.
I have never seen this film,
and I could be wrong and, you know,
be gentle with me for suggesting this,
but my theory has always been that it's less than anything
in the ride was problematic
and more that it causes anyone to have to go,
what's this based on now?
Well, that's what I said.
And that's an uncomfortable question
that has been only mounting and mounting for Disney since 1989.
There's a couple of things on Splash Mountain
where, like, they've changed,
I guess whitewash is the word,
like, changed things around where, like,
that's a scene that would be problematic in the movie,
but they've changed things about it,
or they changed Uncle Remus' character
to the Brayer Frog character,
which was created for the ride.
So there's, like, stuff in there where you're like,
just, like, they've changed it to hide.
And you're not saying change while the ride was open.
But in making it a ride,
they've lost this element, that element.
So this is, you know, and, you know,
God knows, I don't want to say this
and then find that people were, like,
were offended by aspects of Splash Mountain.
I think it's just, it's the association more than anything.
Well, right, this is my big argument.
You go home and you're like, hey, that's cool, what movie is that?
And you Google it and you're like, song of the,
like, oh, that's, I don't know, that sucks.
To me, it feels like it sucks.
Well, and you know there's a problem because, like,
at some point, the literature became,
like, join us on a great log flume adventure,
as opposed to when it opened, like,
based on Disney's beloved classic,
Song of the South.
Like, that's completely how it was positioned then.
And you know something's up if they have to start going,
hey, hey, ask that part of the copy.
Yeah.
And, like, I look, I know we've watched,
I've watched plenty of Tony Baxter interviews
where, like, it seemed like they put an effort forth
to not make it a fence,
like, to try to take the bad stuff out of it.
Yeah, yeah.
But at the end of the day, it's a 20,
whatever, it's 2020,
at the end of the day, you're like, do we really need
a Song of the South ride in our park?
And I would say, like, ah, we should get around
to changing that.
Also, the more that theme parks become representations
of the biggest IPs on Earth.
Of course, theme parks have Star Wars
and Harry Potter and Indiana Jones
and Song of the South, of course.
Must get some real estate.
It's very strange.
Yes, and I'm sure I'm repeating myself,
like, yeah, okay, like, there's plenty of stuff
in the movies where, like, oh, this scene now
in hindsight is bad, or, and then, you know,
the Peter Pan depiction of Native Americans,
yeah, like, just change it on the ride.
Now, Disney is now changing the warning
in front of these movies,
which is a whole other weird thing
that's going on in the recent,
related to the recent administration.
We are sorry, but one of the characters
in this film
once thought about smoking a cigarette.
We want to get ahead of it,
and please go to Disney.com slash let's talk about it
to assuage everyone's fears.
Right.
Well, now, Trump mandated
that Disney just writes, we stand by
everything we've ever done, and it's perfect
before you watch something in Disney Plus.
He's going to make Iger go in front of it,
say, I'm Robert Iger, and I approve
everything in this, which he'll
happily do, by the way.
Seemingly, yeah. These CEOs are just
licking their lips.
We either, whatever, we condemn
this man. How much money do you want?
We hope that he is locked up as soon as we won.
Well, we love you. How much money, Mr.
Trump, do you want? We're staying out of politics.
We're staying out of politics.
We were
thinking about going
woke, and then we thought, no, we're going to
go broke.
There was an Axios article
about all this stuff.
You know, and they mention
they took away
those, you know,
helpful warnings of
those contextual
warnings that lasted
maybe 20 seconds in front
of a movie, and it's like,
you are disparaging the We Are
Siamese song. Take that
out.
Oh, my God, right.
Yikes. That was what I
got to post these.
If you look on YouTube,
that is on
some of the Rockin' Disney
compilations from the 2000s.
Oh, yeah, well, and everything, all of
this, of course, Zippity Doodahs in the
sing-a-long song. These are the
most. It's all out there.
But did you hear Hilary Duff
sing We Are Siamese, if
you please? Was it?
I think it was her. Did she have a sister?
No. Hayley Duff, of course.
Is there a Duff version?
I think that's
her sister is Hayley. I know that. I know Hayley
Duff. I look, sue me. But there's
another one.
What's the problem?
I was concerned about the age.
We acknowledge the American classic
Material Girls. There were a few cover versions
of it. It's very weird. There's
an Axios article where they explain
they were taking out those contextualized
things. Jesus, you're right,
Jason. What the fuck? Yeah, it's
the Duffs, and then there's like another
Disney-made rock band. Oh, my God.
Why would they do that?
What year are we talking?
Why would that happen? Also, what shade
to credit it to Hillary Duff
featuring Hayley Duff?
What a spin. That's rough.
Look, who do I
acknowledge more in terms of cultural
impact? Why, of course, Hillary.
I'm with Hillary.
Let's not.
They're both on the song. I'm with Hayley.
And Mike is with Hayley.
Oh,
God. Yeah, so
there's another
band that does it, like fakey Disney
band, I think. Anyway, what I was
getting at, there's this Axios article
and the part I screengrab,
Disney is changing its diversity,
equity, and inclusion programs
to focus more closely on
business outcomes.
Notes sent to employees to stay
and obtained by Axios.
What outcome do they want?
Up, better business, or lower business?
I wonder what outcome they want. I don't know.
I'm confused, too. Yeah, I screengrab
it because I thought it would be a dunk on a weird
company and then I'm like, wait, this is
Jipper. What are they saying?
What are they talking about? Like
all of this stuff, it's nonsense.
Yeah, I don't know. This current
this is all we can do with
everything all of us are dealing with. It's just like
it's everything we can do to
and Trump, let's move that
to the back of our brains as best as
we can just to not
fall apart during the day. But I
believe in the span of just a few weeks,
Disney
is doing
all that. They sent out that weird
survey to vacation club members
going like, hey, any of you fuckers
dying soon and you're getting an inheritance?
Oh, yeah, because that's how people have to pay.
Yeah, because that's how people have to afford
their vacations as they
get an inheritance.
Disney vacations now must be inherited.
Seemingly.
Must be passed down. Well, the vacation club
is because it's a timeshare. The idea
is you pass it down.
You keep it going.
But then also, so all
of this weird stuff and then
they're like the Captain America
movie. Everyone says it's a mess.
And then like
also, we're putting in the
final verse for
Small World. Oh, yeah.
Richard Sherman's verse
about understanding each other and
living together. So
Oh, yes. No, several
different philosophies going on
at the company right there.
I'm sure the verse is very
nice. I'm sure whoever
wanted to put the verse in
is nice and doing it for nice reasons.
You just wish that the rest of the company
would match the
feelings.
Well, we'll have to go check out that verse.
The episode of the verse
coming soon. We will do the verse, yeah.
The verse, the Walt
Robot. The verse and the Walt Robot are the big
50s. Well, dude, of course, Walt
Robot. Walt Robot is going to be
three hours. That's a big deal
for it. Yeah.
Anyways, what ends
up with all of this backstory
and contentiousness, if you don't recall
the history, how it ends up playing
out is that there's a long ambience
I'm sure we talked about in the show, just like
when is this going to get addressed? Then
a lot is going on in June
2020. It is post George
Floyd protests are raging.
If you can imagine a time when companies
were doubling down on
diversity and inclusion.
Was this 90
years ago? What was this?
But in this climate,
it was very obvious that something had to happen.
There were internet discussions
of, well, you know what you
could do, maybe based on
or there were rumors of, you know, I hear internally
they're thinking about doing this.
There were like
pitches of here's how it
could go and this would be a good property for it
potentially. And then all of a sudden one day
Disney is like, yes, we
were actually going to do that. That's actually why we
were thinking exactly what we were thinking and now we are.
We're waiting for a chance to tell
you, but it's totally
and we date stamped it all.
We wrote
down Princess and the Frog Ride, mailed it
to ourselves and that was in
2018 actually. So
we're way ahead of you. We're just going
to tell you all right now when
regardless of political strut, you
are all feeling the most insane.
Yes,
we're waiting for
the craziest
time possibly in human history.
And we'll drop it then.
So
yeah,
a weird surprise,
but a good surprise. I think we all felt like,
okay, pretty good. And then as the like,
but what this has also done is created
this long because what that is
is five years ago, Jesus Christ.
So nearly
so, you know, for them
to announce something that early
and we know the speed at which they build things.
It is not the speed at which Universal builds things.
So it's been on them to like,
let's release droplets
of information every nine months
because it's they create
an awkward situation for themselves like we're
doing it. Oh, they are. And then for
years you're going to Disneyland and still
you're like, so
and the company's having financial problems
during this time.
Oh, that's true. So like, there's a lot of speculation.
Well, I mean, the sense that like,
they're not like flushed with quote unquote
cash like Tom Cast is.
We run theme parks and theme parks
are closed for a year.
Okay, I understand that.
Let's not also forget the the
shortage of building material.
Every time someone go like,
well, it's taking a lot of awfully
long time to open this new ride or this
new Moana walk through and stuff.
People go like, there's a rebar
shortage. Don't you know that?
And it's like, I do not know that. I am
sorry.
It's the great American screw
loss. Listen,
capital is telling us they don't
have enough money and we need to be respectful
of that. We take them
at their word. I take capital at their word
every day and I thank them for it.
Another funny thing that happened
in all this was like
they're like, you know, announcing
like the minds who will bring us
this and that the original cast of Princess
the Frog will be back because that's somehow the first
I've said Princess and the Frog in this story.
This is based on
the Princess and the Frog was
am I correct? The like revival of
hand drawn animation after
a long after it was kind of like, hey, we're back
a little bit. Yeah, yeah.
And very charming for those reasons.
So, you know, it's all right.
Original voice cast is back and then and of course
Tony Baxter will be advising
and making sure that we do
that. And then that one went away.
That one's there.
That one's there. He's still
in her contracts. You got to get a little bit of like
he's involved. Don't worry. He's going to walk
down the hall. Don't look at some
interviews that have had 500 views
where he's like seemingly
salty about it.
Well, let's
also say like
if people have memory hold this,
at least it is a land
for a lot of years Splash
was kind of in rough shape.
Stuff not working.
Maybe I perhaps
have myself memory hold it. What do you
again? I also don't know the ride as well
because I was not going on the ride for some
time until Mr. Baxter himself
helped me figure out how to go on it.
So what were issues
with the ride? It was just I feel
like it was down a lot. Stuff
animatronics were not working.
Show elements were not working. Stuff would be
dark and you're like is that supposed to be
darker? Can I just not see it?
It would give it a weird. It was
always a trippy ride.
But then some stuff would be broken and I'm like is that
on purpose to make me
messed? I don't know.
It's an incredibly hard ride
to maintain.
I'll say it seems like of all
these rides to ever have to re-theme
might be the hardest. Maybe the biggest
most daunting task in the world
because of just like I felt like
it was harder to fix it with Splash
Mountain and it's so long
as well. Well I think
the thing. Yeah it's very long.
I was trying to figure out like oh pirates
I feel like they
don't have as much trouble and I'm like oh
pirates isn't fighting the
elements.
The animatronics have a lot of
space. There's not the intimacy
you wouldn't say.
There are sort of here's show scenes
and sure it's all next to water but it's
all in kind of a big like sound
stage isn't the word but it's more of like
here's the facility.
Which I guess is I mean you go into
a show building at some point during
Splash Mountain but the part I was
really thinking about in comparing the two
is that like just when you're kind
of in the deepest part when you're between
like drops two and three
it's so claustrophobic
like it's like it's really tight
spaces and I think like
redoing all the you know
another thing like there's no real like ceiling per se
to something like Pirates as opposed to
Splash Mountain the ceiling is right there
you're seeing everything around you
there in one of the great most
charming aspects of the whole thing
is the you know the tightness
and everything being right there but like I imagine
it makes it daunting that like you know
there's nowhere to hide stuff
in the show scenes.
Yes absolutely like
I mean I guess we could there's so much to talk
about but like just even talking about the
idea of re-themes like to me
Guardians of the Galaxy is the
Mission Breakout is the gold standard
for a complete
re-theme where you take the whole like the property
is different.
But that's to me easier
that seems a lot easier to do
versus this
which is just less ground to cover
and I'm trying to think what are the other examples.
They did it so fast which makes you think
it must have been easier.
Well right there's not as much
acreage to cover as well
and that means money can go farther
probably in addition to that.
I'm just in a basic
dumb person sense like
water makes it hard I bet.
I bet it does.
It's got to be musty in there.
Robots do not need water as far as I know.
Robots and water
are mixed. That's what I learned when I was a kid.
That's bad.
Unless there's certain
robot water
water robots excuse me.
I mean there are
mechanical specialists
who are also like scuba certified
and obviously pirates
there's a lot more waterway
and deeper water.
But like even in this you either have to drain
all the water to work on stuff
or someone has to like go down with
a tank of oxygen and a blow torch
or a soldering iron.
And then also
did they end up redoing logs
or refurbishing them?
They refurbished them but they're pretty much the same
logs I'm pretty sure.
Because it's not
it's not like they went to the double seating
which is in Florida.
That would be so expensive I think
to widen the track like it is in Florida.
Oh they're able to do that because it's wider?
To do double seating?
Yes.
I mean I think that it wouldn't be able to fit that way.
Is Florida longer of a ride too?
Yes.
Florida's long because like the word is
and again we don't have any good this is one of those rides
that's new and we only can hear like rumors
so we don't have that like good behind the scenes
of what's going on necessarily.
The rumor is that they designed it for Disneyland
so it fits in a nicer way
because we haven't been on the Disney World version.
But people say oh the Disney World version
feels like emptier it feels
I've been catching that.
That's what people have been saying and they feel like
they designed it for Disneyland and then they just stretched out
the show elements on Disney World
because it's like a longer track.
Well they also had further to go right?
I got curious about because
you know not to jump around too much
but I think a big concern was like
okay this is a ride that is teeming
with animatronics and are they going to be able to recreate
that vibe and I tried to not watch
a ride through just to experience it
and I'm like it's something I was worried about
because it's going to be so screen oriented
or mist oriented or whatever
that it doesn't because you need that feel
you know it at least has to feel
like a part of a Knott's one.
That's a lot of the thrill is like
I'm moving so fast and every second there's so many animatronics.
They landed at 48.
There's 48.
Disney World
and I was like what did it have before?
Disney World actually you know
this is the opposite of what I was saying.
Disney World had 68 Splash Mountain.
Disneyland had 103.
Yeah because those were the America Sings
robots specifically.
They had all the real original ones.
Which is funny they had to then in the 90s
recreate 70s robots.
So actually forget what I was saying
it's almost like they had further to go
in Disneyland.
Well as far as yeah just repopulating
or making it feel full like it did.
But there was less space?
Yes because I would just double check
duration of Splash in Disneyland
is 9 minutes 18 seconds
and Magic Kingdom is 11 minutes
45 seconds.
That's significant ride time.
We've done full two hour
episodes about rides that are like a minute and a half.
So a minute and a half in
within two versions of a ride is huge.
Yeah correct me if I'm wrong I think it's a little
slower in Disney World too.
But I could be wrong. I know it's for sure
longer but I can't remember if it actually for some reason
runs a little slower.
But yeah that's a long
that's a long two minutes probably.
Some rides are two minutes.
Besides the stuff with the ride
itself.
There were a lot of steps to this.
You understand why it took a long time because
there's the interior
there is the exterior
there is the land itself.
The land changed from critter country
to bayou country.
Part of this is that Tiana's palace
not place apparently
and the internet doesn't know why
either. Is that what it is in the movie?
Is that what it is? I guess.
I think it's right at the end when she
does she finally open up
a spot. Yeah.
I like this movie too.
I like this movie. I did see some
complaints of this.
I appreciate it's a new story
after the movie.
But I saw people saying like
a lot of the characters from the movie are not
in this or like
they're just in it at the end waving
you know or smiling
and not really moving.
Is it by the way sorry really quick is it Tiana's
it's she does she like has her
dream art of Tiana's place in the movie
but does it end up being palace because
she is a princess?
That is probably the logic.
Maybe that's the logic.
Who are we?
Ron Clements, John Musker and
Randy Newman the
creative minds behind this movie.
Who are we?
We are not them no.
We are sweat boxing.
We are sweat boxing this 2009
film.
Two of the great yeah it's a Musker
Clements and it shows they're two of the greatest
who ever did it and you get look
you can't complain about more Randy Newman
in the parks. This is a good thing. Sure.
We love Randy Newman. Randy Newman if you when you add it up
especially with this and between
like so much of the Pixar music
being in the parks in terms of
like you don't have to do the count but
has their
fingerprints on theme parks the most.
It's probably John Williams
between both Disney and Universal
but then there's Sherman Brothers
obviously but Randy Newman may be a third.
There's a lot. Maybe that is for
solid third. Which is great because it's
Americana and it's catchy and
there's heart to it and like what a great
person to be the soundtrack of theme parks.
And that always blows my mind because there's such
he has such a different writing style
for his solo work.
It's not like the Sherman Brothers are writing these
bizarre or
angry or
very
political songs. Sherman Brothers
were all happy days unless they have like a bunch
of secret stuff and like maybe there's a
Sherman Brothers vault like the Prince Vault
where they were really like giving
it to the current administration. Just 12
minute free flowing
nine minute
trumpet solos
and a lot of
like moaning like really
they got their girlfriends to come and
get freaky on the
trail.
Here a similar connection
to that. Jennifer Lewis
long tenured performer
and singer. Voice of Mama
Odie in this ride. I forgot
she is also the voice of
flow in cars.
So that means Jennifer Lewis
characters technically have a ride
and a diner
in these two parks.
I did not realize that
either. Flow is good.
That movie's on all the time in my house. I like flow.
Then they do the last song on the
ride also is written by not by Randy
Newman. The original
like it's the instrumentals of a
lot of the down in New Orleans and
Diggle Deeper and stuff.
Special Spice is the name.
Which takes the place I'd say
of Zippity Doo Da as the finale
song. Because I'm assuming they were like
well there's a lot of white people that made this movie
about a black princess so we should probably
have a black person write the song.
Well now that we do have in common with Ron
Clements, John Musker and Randy Newman.
Well that's true. We are that.
What guys talking about it?
So I assume that's why that's
the big show stopping finale.
And you know who that is? What do you mean?
Who wrote the song? P.J. Morton.
Do you know who P.J. Morton is
in terms of other musical output?
Oh I didn't realize this.
Maroon 5's keyboardist.
Is that right? I didn't know that.
Wow okay.
Was that a spark of
surprise or excitement over the
spectacular
I am excited to learn that.
I can't explain it to you why I was
so excited to learn that. I mean I was excited enough to say it.
I just don't know where you land on Maroon 5.
How long do we have to talk
about Maroon 5?
Do you not think it's going to take a while to sort it out?
You know what I like? I like that
song Sugar by Maroon 5 I think.
I think that one's pretty good.
I will say I could
enjoy Moves Like Jagger if it was
playing somewhere but it's not a song I like.
But I don't go very hard.
I have the first Maroon 5 album
that came out where everyone was like
you know there's that time when those albums come out and you're
not sure where a band will land.
And they were like maybe halfway between.
They weren't like lame
out of the gate. Exactly.
They were in this other
it was previously something
called Kara's Flowers. Yes.
Slightly reconfigured and that was more of a power
pop band which is a genre I like
a lot. So I remember finding them as like
oh yeah that's kind of in that zone
so kind of
horrifying that they became like kids bop
music. Yeah it's weird because like Harder
to Breathe came out which I didn't like and then the other
songs I did like
and then they eventually
like completely switched genres and went
like really chased like
whatever current pop music sound is
to some degree of success
with me personally.
But it's also like Coldplay were cool
for two albums. Coldplay were
cool. They were pitch four cool though.
They were like Rush of Blood did that
whether you think they were cool or not. Yeah I like Rush of Blood.
Well you can say you like it.
It was this cool.
But I'm saying they were like ten
like nine point five pitch four
rated which in that way I'm saying
they were cool. Yeah. And then
all of a sudden or whatever over the
next few albums it was like your mom
likes Coldplay. Never mind.
Oh yeah. God I mean suddenly a band starts
turning with puppets and people start saying they're lame.
Well yeah that's when it had this turn really happen.
What did Pitchfork give
the weirdos?
Is it a different scale when it's puppets?
Yeah I don't know. Two questions.
Mike has a big city walk sometimes.
He saves a while to see if the
weirdos are going to show up on that big TV
on that big screen.
I was reading the reissue of Wilco's A Ghost
Is Born on like a Pitchfork review of it like
last week and the reviewer was like
when I was in high school and I heard
this album I'm like God what
is this shit? High school? You shouldn't be
writing for Pitchfork. Wait wait well when
is the album from? 2003?
No no 2005.
But isn't that close to our age?
It's pretty close. What are you? Why are you trying to
talk this guy out of a job? I think he shouldn't
have a job. Anyone of any age has any right
to have any job they want to have. I'll read his name
here and I want him fired. Mike's
starting older millennial younger
millennial wars. I'm switching to
savesplashmountainchange.org
position to fire this young
man from reviewing Wilco music.
That's what I believe.
Our children when
they were born their years of
birth will barely overlap with the output
of Wilco. Are you to say they are not
to be gainfully employed? They need to
have been born in 1984 later
or else they cannot
understand. The only good ages.
That's right. Anyway
that's who did the song.
I was heading to this other area which is
because you know there's a little bit
of like a change of the of the landscape
and whether I don't know if
we could address the exterior
here or also just like the park in general
but like what do we think of the flow
what do we think of what it did to
the areas of Disneyland Park that
were affected like like like
you know Bayou country the flow
in the poo hungry bear
you know now we got like now we got Tiana's
palace with New Orleans stuff
how are we feeling about this this
neck of the woods? In some ways
I almost feel that the new
exterior is almost
more seamless in some ways.
Now I'm not saying I
necessarily prefer the exterior
but in some ways it really blends
well from New Orleans Square
to whatever
I guess it's Bayou country but I which
doesn't make sense because poo's over there but whatever
in some ways I almost feel like. It's
got critters why is it not just keep
a critter. I don't think critters.
Yes I agree I don't know that seems like over
think to me but. However it's still
a nice sign and I think
the sign is nice. The entrance
as far as it like coexisting
with poo and exit
and gift shop and everything I think it's wonderful.
I think it looks great over there. I agree.
I think the drooping
you know a lot of it fake
foliage
but mansion
the Haunted Mansion area
has a lot of kind of drooping
plants. So
in terms of transition
droopy plants. What are those drooping
trees? Different varieties
but I saw a short
video of like imagineering
members ride Tiana's
and one of the factoids
was a lot of the stuff
in the water out here as you're
starting the ride is
metal developed for outdoor
for water rides.
So it won't age. Oh
and it wasn't before? I
it might
have been but or they were specifically
saying maybe it was a newer iteration
or. Interesting. Maybe something.
I haven't seen the open Haunted
Mansion gift shop yet to know exactly how
this transition out because there's I've heard a lot
of discourse about this gift shop. Was it
open when you were there? It was probably right.
You might say I didn't
make it a priority to go to the gift shop.
What? Sorry to say
this. That's going to be the whole episode this year
about the Haunted Mansion gift shop.
And how it floods. How they have to
put sandbags out in front of the entrance when
it rains because they didn't figure that
out I guess. Because it floods
the store unless they do that.
When store doors flood.
Uh huh.
I didn't do that down on Melrose.
Oh I don't.
I hear you.
It keeps flooding down by La Brea.
So actually I do think
it looks pretty good. Now the question of
is it as striking? Is it as
specific and unique as
the old exterior of Splash Mountain?
That is a different question. But I do kind
of like the way it looks
and blends now. Yeah as far as
the campus. I think it's
never looked better in that
in Disneyland's little
corner. In Disneyland's little dead end.
I think it's great. I didn't
really get to see it at night. I would
be curious there.
Yeah god I don't know if I have
a real take on
better or worse exterior.
I like the
like whatever
the plants and the moss
or whatever you want. Like the green
that now kind of overtakes
the
hit. Well let's
get into it. It's a
ride is now. It's not a hill anymore.
It is a salt dome.
It's a salt dome.
We know this. We know that New Orleans
has salt domes.
Of course. Of course we pay
tribute to their cloud. Their wonderful
salt domes. And she set
up her like a place
where a bunch of people work in a
salt dome. It makes it weird when
you're you're past the kind of
the first lift. And then there's like a sign
that points you different directions. And one is like break
room. There's a break
room in the salt dome. It's
kind of strange. I mean I get look
hey if I could work at it. Look I'd like to work out of a
tree house more than I'd like to work out of some
WeWork. That's true. It is a good. It probably
is a really nice place to work. Tiana's
Food's probably a good deal. Yeah.
I saw the fake
the sign at the meeting in the queue.
Beignet Wednesdays. Tiana's Street.
Does it say that?
Yeah it does. Wow.
You're into it. Yeah I'm in.
Look this is part
of the plot of it also
is that she has the restaurant so you can go
the goal in the movie is achieved. She
has a restaurant. But how is she going to source
all the food for the restaurant. She has Tiana's foods.
This is its own operation. It's kind of like a farm
but kind of like a farm built into a
salt dome. I believe it's co-op.
It is a co-op. It's a co-op.
Good job if you can get it. If you end up
you can yeah. Work our own. You're part of
yeah yeah yeah. You own it
and you're getting free beignets
every Wednesday. Good deal. I think
Tabasco
is maybe the main
production headquarter where they grow
the peppers by a salt dome.
Is that it? In Louisiana. I saw that
somewhere when I was reading a little about
salt domes.
This was one of the
craziest
crazy person reactions I saw
about this ride. It's like salt
domes. That's some sleaziest
work there. So this ride is actually
more racist.
That was a safe splash person making
that argument. Yeah yeah.
Some kook.
It wasn't one of us.
That's what we're saying. It wasn't one of us.
The idea of like
that it's going to open instead
of and I'm just going to like I'm going to
search high and low for every reason
why this one's worse.
I'm going to prove it in court
that they made a more problematic ride.
What a good way to spend
your life and time
that you don't get paid for. There are accounts
still tweeting about it and it's really
interesting. I mean also like I guess there's a lot
of accounts that tweet about
like there's still people that are really
rooting for the Superman movie to
fail this James Gunn Superman movie because
of Snyder stuff. I literally don't know why
it's because oh because because it all
got taken away. That plan got
aborted. Yeah I think it's because
and if you look into it generally the people that are so
aggressively posting are like still upset
about Snyder stuff. So like
people are very relentless.
Hasn't Zack Snyder moved on to a
different movie studio and made like three
or four movies? I don't know if he's made
that many but he's made his
Netflix thing that I can't think of the name
of. He may have moved on but his posters
have not. So I'm saying
that people have. And they never have. Keep posting
Snyder people. People have stamina
is what I'm saying when it comes to
posting to try to get something overturned
or changed or root for some
failure. I guess I should be
I'm saying like I was surprised for a second and then I realized
I see this all the time. Yeah well I've
noticed in the clip three polls. Well
sure. There's a
stamp. People have stamina. People
can last. Post your way
to victory. You know what I think
with the exterior and I don't even like
I've already I think I kind of just said I like
this right also. I said it on the just you don't
have to. Scott you can just keep your reveal.
I'll keep too myself. Let us know.
I think I said I liked it. Yeah
dub your brow with that American flag
bandana you're wearing.
So don't misunderstand me but
I think what happened with that exterior
is that I saw that promo art
that art they released quickly in 2020.
Yes. And I had been hanging
on to that for a long time.
And it has a big
tree where that like stump used to
be on Splash Mountain and it has a boat
in there and the
art looked awesome.
And it doesn't the way
that it has come out they don't have that tree
they don't have a boat up there.
It does not. Is there a big boat?
Quite look as cool and
maybe the whole concept. Oh my god
I forgot this there was a boat. There was a boat
stuck in the lagoon in the tree
and I don't know
if this was a completely different concept
to me that looks expensive to put
that up there and the way they did it
looks less expensive. It was a wow
well this isn't a salt dome is it?
This is a big tree at the top
worthy of avatar
or of animal kingdom tree of life.
Yes. That you
this is the problem is that
this is kind of now every
time I look at the new Tiana exterior
I think of ah but the tree
like that to me equals
the iconic
ness of Splash Mountain's exterior.
And as opposed to because
the dome just does yes
I of course like that Splash Mountain has this
peak. It was really notable
and so scary to me in a way that's haunted me
forever and this yeah
the fact that it's just kind of. This is what
alright here you go it's a little. Right and again
I almost think it sort of blends like the old Splash
Mountain kind of was like oh and now we're in this
kind of different landscape and
now we're into Pooh Bear now we're into Bear Country
or whatever but like I'm like oh
this looks amazing and that's
why I keep thinking money wise
is that I think
they did the best
possible job they could do with this and there's
really some good to great stuff
but there's like things from like I'm like
I bet that was another 30
million dollars or something.
50 million dollars. That could just be
brain drain like clearly
they had people who knew how to put a
boat on top of a mountain. We've all been to
Typhoon Lagoon. They might all
retired. It's like how they say no one can do
Technicolor chemical processing anymore.
You think like nobody can put boats.
Everyone's retired. All the boat guys
retired. All the boat and tree guys had
retired. Yeah.
Wow. Yeah. Yes.
People who put boats in high places they
can't do it anymore. It looks great
at night like it's like purpley at night.
Well here's the question because I would love to see
it. Sorry to interrupt but I like in this
concept art I'm seeing it's also like
and they embellish stuff in concept art
but like there is this very like
it's like fireflies flickering
this thing. Does any
of what's going on at night have
any of this magic that kind of sparkles?
It has magic but it doesn't quite look like this
but I do think there's like the
lights are really cool. There's a
little more like color variation
in parts I think too.
It gets a little purpley it looks like. It gets purple. Yes
and I love I'm a big purple. My favorite
light I've said this before my favorite
like light setup is California Adventure
Halloween Time.
That purple light on
in like the Hollywood area and like
the in the old time
whatever Carthay area
that is my favorite mood
you know maybe any theme park
I've ever been to is that purple
Halloween light. You know what I'm talking about. I know what you're talking about.
This guy knows what I'm talking about. This guy knows a
lot of shadows and stuff. Yeah
but so yeah so there's
like purple light on this and it looks really
nice so yeah don't get me wrong
that I think this looks bad or anything.
Well and all the plant like look it's
it's great plant work. It's great rock work.
Yeah that's the thing like
you like one issue is
Splash Mountain versus
Tiana but then like on
top of that there is Disney versus
itself you know what I mean. Yeah yeah.
Like well-meaning Imagineers whose budget
clearly gets cut and then they can't do this cool thing
and that cool thing. Yeah and it's over the year and over
the years too it will be interesting to see how
you feel about the ride because
like initially
all you're going to be doing is going okay
does this feel like Splash Mountain like
and that's I think with the success
of Guardians to me is that I
don't think about Tower
of Terror almost ever and I feel
like quickly it went out of my head. I'm not
thinking about it when I'm on that ride.
And also though there is the benefit to
the superior
version always was elsewhere and it still
is. Yes of course that's definitely part
of it but I'm just like so so it's
interesting because yeah I'm doing your
there's a couple different calculations you're doing
these first few
rides on the ride. Yeah yeah
but it's very loaded for a theme park fan
in a way that it won't be for just
you know a kid going on this
ride. Yeah of course because the kid walks by it and goes
oh that's cool it's a big what they won't know
Salt Dome probably unless daddy explains it
which he will don't worry daddy will explain
it. But yeah yeah they go
it's cool big big thing falling
out of it. I do think also
that you don't
feel like it's quite as tall
without a big thing sticking out
of the top. Yeah. And that's
maybe a bigger bummer to
me. It's like an optical illusion. It's an optical
it was an old optical illusion. It's like if you cut the tops
off a main street you'd realize oh these
buildings aren't you know that that's what
three quarter not three quarter
is it three quarter? I forget the scale.
But yeah that's yeah
yeah that was an extra optical illusion.
So I'm sure that's why in the concept
art they were like well let's put something to
match sort of that whatever
stump on top of Splash Mountain just to
give it that illusion.
So some of some of my
complaints about it was that they've gotten
rid of some of the stuff that scared
you as a kid or as a teen
or as an early 20s. Well I would say a lot of I mean
the vibe of it is so so different
for sure. And
you know I would actually
just to like do
the cliff notes
of the story
there's just less peril
in the entire
notion of it. I think Splash Mountain
always had you're going to get thrown
down in the Briar Patch and that's all that's the arc
of it but then things ended happy.
In this it is all about a
big celebration that Tiana is going to
have. They are missing a band
and you need to help gather
critters
critter musicians. This is great.
To do yes along with
Louie the alligator
so that a big
you know Tiana's
food celebration can't occur.
Great. Simple.
We're putting the band together.
It's really cute now are these
musician animals
in the musician's union.
Well they'll have to deal with that.
The other thing is like there
were no human music. I know it says it was
carnival season you know.
And I'm sure they're busy but surely
you get some young hungry
up and coming musicians. Oh you're saying the humans are
in the band. The human musicians I guess
are all booked but there would be some old
veterans who would just play the show hopped up
on like
beignets and chicory coffee.
Hopped up on beignets.
When was the last time you were
hopped up on a beignet.
Well it brings you back to life.
You get a beignet at the what
do they call it now the coastal jazz.
Ralph Brennan's on the way out.
They call it looks like shit.
Downtown Disney's
destroyed
desecrated Ralph Brennan's. We do gotta get Jason
hopped up on beignets.
Get you sniffing a line of that sugar. That's a lot of sugar
but I don't how do you
even if you try you're gonna
get some on your shirt. Yeah.
That's true. It's part of the fun.
I think
I had a filled beignet
at Tiana's
palace.
Filled with what? Like a
custard or like a lemon
filling. Are there options? There are different
types of filling there? I think there was. I was there
right after it opened. And they're usually
not filled. It's like it is
the sugar. It's usually just fried and powdered sugar.
It's usually plain.
But yeah.
Just animals. Just cute animals.
Just cute animals. Well until the
there's like a kid drummer
at the end. Yeah who's that kid? Who's that
fucking kid? I don't know. Is that supposed
to be Tiana Naveen's like child?
Oh that's a good question. I don't know.
I'm not sure. Is that a character in the movie?
I don't know. I think
they just went happily ever after
in the movie. I don't know.
And it's not answered by the
it feels like an eventual
episode or club three or something that we
gotta do. Oh I think I put it in the
poll I believe.
At Eisner's pitch for Fantasia 2000
that you meet. There's a
procession to pomp and circumstance of all
the princesses and princes
and they present their
children. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah. Here's Cinderella.
Here's little
here's Dylan Charming.
Oh I would love that.
Here's
Breck Bellbeast. I don't
know their last name. They hyphenated.
God there's enough much children
at this point they'd be able to do a procession
and just them.
The greatest kids in the world.
Anyways but yeah so you were on
the hunt for musicians.
What a great way to then go
you know just get a bunch of critters
playing music. I mean they're like
I have to move elsewhere for my
ride notes but
is this a good chance to talk about some of these
animatronics and these do
they stand
out and do they
which one
of these these musician critters
do we like? Well I like all
of them. I've seen some
complaints yeah
they're limited some of them are limited
in movement but I think all of
them really pop and
some of I've seen
some people complain like some parts of the ride
are much darker than Splash
Mountain but I do think that
highlights the show scenes where you do
see some of the robots with the animals.
So I don't know I'm a
big do you want to start shouting out? I got my
list of names here. Yeah sure yeah
yeah well I don't
you know I like kind of the there's a
lot of good like woodland ones
but my favorite animatronics I think in general
are the big frogs
or to spoiler and to jump
around that you are
you get shrunk
in this and the ones that really
pop to me are the frogs
that are presumably your size. That's
the idea there that you are getting turned
frog-sized. Yes.
To resemble what happens
in Princess and the Frog. In the like laughing
place part of Splash Mountain they've
changed it now to where you get shrunk
down and you see a big
like you see Tiana like on
a screen like her head is big like she's
regular size appearing in
but you're in this same and
that's the closest to like yeah like kind of
an ode to the psychedelic nature of the
original ride too in some ways
because there's a little more color in that
section as well. Yeah it matches that
and it feels like if
they're following the format of Splash Mountain
that there needs to
be like a big tonal shift
post that second drop. I think
that is achieved very well.
Yes. Yes. I think that's a
very successful part
and those frogs are really fun.
Yeah. They stand out the most as
like personality.
Yes. To me. Like as a kid like
just like your kid brain goes oh yeah I would be
like oh we're in the frog part and
there's like kind of like glow there's like
a big bottle that you see pretty quickly
I think that's kind of glowing.
It felt very Alice in Wonderland.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Peering into
and seeing the fireflies through the bottles and stuff.
Yeah. That's all a lot of fun. And there's some griping
about the CGI Tiana because she doesn't
look quite like the robot Tiana
or the hand drum but like I don't know.
Yeah that's
just watching videos. That was the thing
that stuck out to me were those
where they're like, it's just kind of basic CG animation
to make it match the animatronics.
And I think the Mama Odie animatronic is really good.
Yeah, I think so.
There's a few of them.
But that said, in terms of match,
the original movie I thought was unique
in that it was 2D animation with like CG elements.
And it gave it a very interesting look.
It gave it a very unique look.
And I wish they could have gotten that
in those little screen moments.
That's true, and especially given
that it's an important film in that respect,
that it was a return to the hand-drawn form.
Right, but that actually might be a brain drain.
Or like, oh, we can't, this was kind of experiment-y,
and these computers have been replaced three times.
Like, we can't do this as easily.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, I think also there is,
sometimes it's like logic-wise.
They're like, well, if it's hand-drawn,
it's not gonna match the robots.
Some of that is a little too, I don't know.
It's in the same way that the timeline
in Galaxy's Edge stuff where you're like,
what's cooler or more fun versus what has to completely
follow iron-clad logic?
Maybe it's that, maybe it's not,
maybe it's just cheaper to do CGI.
This especially, it's like, well, that's true,
but also, magic is involved.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So this is kind of a disappointment, for sure.
So they looked a little stranger to you,
that would kind of explain that a way.
Right, and I also, maybe somebody would say,
well, the reason there's no tree and waterfall
is because Louisiana's flat, and they do have salt mines,
and they don't really have waterfalls,
but I would say to that, who cares?
Yes, yeah.
I would say, that's fun, though.
1000%, yeah.
Let me say that I think they pulled in
the correct New Orleans elements.
Yeah, oh, absolutely.
If there's that thing of let's actually
tribute the city and the culture,
the murals and the hand-drawn nature and stuff,
so true, yeah, yeah.
And the way in Florida, too, the Disney,
they're slightly different.
Yeah, there's this big wall in the Florida one
early on in a lift hill that's super charming.
And I was like, what was that before?
And it was just like a blank wall.
So any notion, I think people are being the,
if you can imagine certain YouTubers
being particularly angry about certain things,
there's something about, you see a lot of,
it's just empty, it feels empty,
and then you look at side by sides,
and you're like, this has color, and it didn't before.
Literally, there was no animatronic in this hill,
and now there's a Tiana.
Maybe other parts don't satisfy you on that level,
but the side by side is pretty,
I don't know, it's an endorsement, I think,
for the new one.
Yeah, I agree.
Oh, God, I wish I remembered the exact specifics.
I swear one of the complaints I saw was
someone said, huh, a 1930s promotional painted mural
in a ride that takes place in the 1940s,
or it was something that small,
or it's like a 1910s mural in a ride
that takes place in the 30s,
where it's just like, why, no one will,
they will just go, it is the past.
Hello, mural police, I have a major crime to report.
You'll wanna be sitting.
But no, I agree with you, Scott,
I appreciate how much they did research,
and got the vibe right, and the cuisine right,
and the chefs.
I think that stuff probably paid off better
than it often does, and I know there's a lot
of research trips involved, we just found that
on Sweatbox, and that always happens,
and I think it really shows here.
There's a different and authentic feel, absolutely,
to the new, and it's a different slice of New Orleans
than New Orleans Square, which has been in the park
since the 60s, so it's nice that there's a whole new
area of it that's being acknowledged.
I would say, I guess I can't keep comparing,
but I would say this first part of the queue,
the exterior part of that queue with the murals,
and with her office, I think is better than Splash Mountain.
I think it's a lot more fun.
Office is very nice, yeah.
Let me admit, I did not wait in the line.
I did not feel the need to like.
How did you do, I guess it was open by the time you went?
Oh yeah, yes, no, for me it was past any virtual queue
and all that nonsense.
It was pretty, if I'd gotten in,
this is the only part where I told Aaron,
sucks, you should be glad you didn't go,
was just that security took.
It's like fucking, by the time you're in the car line,
then in the tram line, it took an hour and a half
to even be in the park, and in that time,
the Tiana wait went from 10 minutes to 35,
and I'm like, brr, brr, brr,
and then the rest of it, that was awesome,
but what I ended up doing, Single Rider,
the app doesn't say, they're actually kind of bad about,
I've walked up to rides that say that they have Single Rider
and they go, no, and then this has one
and it's not listed on the website as having one,
and it's a very efficient one
for the Single Riders out there.
Don't miss it, jump in, do it.
You might wait with three other people
outside the facility entirely,
and then just be led 10 feet away from the logs.
It's really great.
When they were doing Virtual Queue,
I struck out like two or three times
when I would wake up at 7 a.m. in the morning
to get the Virtual Queue reservation.
The problem was is that it would be screwing you
because you had to have a reservation for the park
that you couldn't cancel once.
Oh, so you end up with your three strikes.
So the first time, I just went down anyway,
hoping that I would get it at noon.
I did not get it at noon and did not get to ride it.
The second time, I ate the strike.
I have a penalty now on my account.
You have a, ah!
I have one strike on my Magic Key Pass
Disneyland account. You have a scarlet pea?
That's right.
And then the third time,
which I feel like it was two weeks later
after they had started doing it,
I finally got it in the morning, went down solo,
and then just had a decent day
and walked basically right on when the Virtual Queue started.
And I was walking in to the queue and was handed a punch.
We'll get to this later,
but it was handed a poncho by some nice strangers.
Really?
Like, do you want this?
Yes, grabbed it, took it, wiped,
or just shook it to get the water off,
and then took that on,
and then paid that forward as I got off
and gave another stranger.
Is this a little thing that's forming
in the Disneyland community?
Is passing off the ponchos?
I don't know,
but I don't know if it's been happening recently,
but it was happening that day.
It's a good thing because that's waste.
That's like, you buy an expensive,
and also bad poncho to be immediately thrown away.
Well, the other, the thing I had learned
is if you really want a poncho for water rides,
go into Amazon and buy a pack.
They're like $2.
Yeah, yeah.
They're like $1 for five or 10.
They'll get you in an airport way.
They'll be able to pay like 20 bucks for one.
So certainly pay it forward if you have a pack, you know?
Get a pack.
I think we bought one at Disney World
when it was raining at Animal Kingdom,
and the plastic smell was so brutal.
It felt, it really felt like it was giving me a headache.
Like we were, I had just like freshly put it on,
and this one actually smelled similarly.
So I wonder if they had bought it at Disney that day,
and Disney just has thick, smelly plastic
that gets in your brain.
The microplastic's invading my brain.
That does feel, yeah, you're not crazy there.
It feels, and it feels like it's getting hot.
It feels like it's like fusing into you,
as if you're getting like a,
you're getting some kind of like skin graft or something.
It's weird.
Is it supposed to be this hot?
Yes, that means it's working.
They never, they changed it,
because for many years it was those iconic yellow ponchos,
and then they changed it because it's like,
oh, you know what these are also great for?
Shoplifting.
Ah!
So they changed it to a more opaque.
That's why clear?
Yeah, that's why clear.
But I love that they keep the smelly, hot plastic part.
They didn't adjust that.
It feels like the thickness of a clear,
the piece of plastic you put on your office floor
so you can wheel your office chair on it.
It feels like that thick of plastic and that opaque.
That's the kind of plastic that breaks within three weeks.
Yeah, and that's what it feels like
you're wearing with these ponchos.
And that is the kind of poncho I had.
Spiky floor plastic.
Smelly, spiky floor plastic that you're wearing
to protect you from the rain or from a water ride.
Yeah.
So I wore it.
So I put that on, but it was fun.
It was a fun exchange.
It was fun to be like, you want it?
Yes, I want it.
And then I did the same thing leaving.
So that's a good tip if you want to pay it forward.
If we're sort of going in order, though,
anything else you want to shout out about the queue?
Because it does seem, there's good food representations,
and then we're kind of going,
let's just go back and order the ride.
That's what I'm thinking.
No, I mean, just to look,
there's a ton to look at in the queue.
I felt like I hung back and let people go ahead of me,
but there's just a lot of fun little things and details
just like any other Everest
or when you see people's desks and rides.
I guess that is a common thing.
I like ride offices.
Ride offices. I really like that.
Yeah, I mean, from Spider-Man and Islands of Adventure,
there's an office, like fake offices.
Fake office, Final Four?
Oh.
We don't have one.
There it is, listeners.
You think it's maybe?
There it is.
It has a nice fit.
Men in Black Alien Attack.
That's it.
There's good office.
Oh, and there's a lot to assess there.
Do you want to work there,
but it could be a good representation of an office
that would be bad to work in.
Right?
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay. You did it.
Well, just tell us if you hate that, but I like.
No, I really like that.
That sounds pretty immediate from the three of us.
I think that's it.
Okay, wow.
You did it, yeah.
Oh, Discovery.
We took one off last year.
Jason's back.
We're figuring out our strategy for the next two.
This is good stuff.
Thank God you said that,
because I remember I had pitched
Ventriloquist's dummy Final Four, too.
So you just saved us.
Oh, but he was on to think.
You know, there's the kind of like,
don't say no to a pitch
unless you can think of a better one.
Well, Scott, we just learned about little Jeff, though.
You mean Jeff Dunham?
Oh, right.
Yeah, Jeff Dunham's, you can learn.
This was in a text thread, not on the show, right?
Yeah, this was on a group text.
We learned about little Jeff, the practice dummy,
but also Peanut's dummy of Jeff Dunham,
I believe, is the full stack.
Jeff Dunham's dummy Peanut
has a little dummy of Jeff Dunham.
Little Jeff.
Oh, that's what it is.
The dummy operates a dummy.
I believe that.
Well, that's what he was saying.
Well, yes, and then I believe you can buy little Jeff
and Instructional DD.
You can buy little Jeff, yes.
So you can learn how to Ventriloquist.
So you've avoided it.
You picked or you found a good one.
No, I was gonna say,
I believe you can buy little Jeff,
and I believe that I can turn my car on in the garage
and for long enough that I can go to sleep
and not do this episode.
You can smother yourself with a thick plastic poncho.
You know that they can't.
They like hand out implements
that you could kill yourself with.
You could, yes.
Sorry, Scott.
Just spin that baby around,
like hole up in a bathroom stall
where it gets hot and musty
and you'll be out in half an hour.
Yeah, but if you do either one of those,
you know who's gonna appear in front of you?
Little Jeff.
Is that who you see
before you enter whatever afterlife is meant for you?
The pearly gates, yeah, I know.
Hey there.
I'm little Jeff.
You can go to heaven,
but it's nothing but Ventriloquist dummies up here.
All the ones in the-
Send me to hell, send me to hell.
All the ones in the museum.
Okay, well, wow, fake office Final Four.
That is good, yeah.
And then, you know, the actual like,
back me up if I missed anything,
but the actual boarding zone is really similar, I'd say.
Very similar, yeah.
So like, if there's any like,
plusing up of like the actual,
the non-office part of it, I'm like,
could they have done anything to this zone?
Because basically, it's supposed to be a salt mine now.
So they kind of just like,
to me it looks like the walls are a little dirty or something.
Like it just kind of like splashes of like,
maybe more like white color
and I don't know even how to describe it really.
But I'm like, ah, it's kind of just,
this is more, this is sort of just the Splash Mountain Q,
which is fine.
This is, these are minor gripes at the end of the day.
Really, look, just to tell you,
I wrote down fake office Final Four,
not that we'll forget, but even in,
then I was like, oh man.
You were zoning out while I was just talking.
Indie's office.
I think I'm just dreaming of it.
It's just a good.
It's a really good one, yeah.
Because I'm so fond of all those.
I like, yeah, Tiana's little office is one of the best
things and then.
Yeah, the office is one of the best.
The big question is going to be,
is it little offices or big offices?
Oh, the collector's office is great too.
Or is one size, yeah, absolutely.
And do you even do a face-off,
are the haves big office and little office?
Good question.
Or you thrust them next to each other.
Different categories.
Is it conferences?
If you, if we can find enough in both categories.
Yeah, oh, we have to talk about this.
I guess we have to like make the list to be able to tell.
Yes, I think that's right.
This is, but there's a lot, yeah.
Good work ahead of us.
There's going to be a lot too,
because we're going to have to,
we're going to have to really find good 4K video
so we can tell the details on the desks.
I know, because some of them are offices we can't go to.
Some of these offices might be in Japan.
We can't exactly go and hang out in the queue
and let people move past us.
Harrison and Hightower's office.
Oh man.
Yeah.
We also, though, have to like create a firm divide
between like dens.
We have to discuss our dens offices.
Oh, okay, yeah.
But you can do office type things in a den.
Yeah.
So it depends.
Mickey, I mean, Mickey's den.
Oh, is the den, is the den an office?
Oh, that's where he makes his calls.
There's a lot to talk about.
I think you have to see if 16 spots are filled up
by proper offices.
Okay.
Before you can, and if they aren't,
then dens are in the picture.
Yeah.
Maybe we can, I don't know, we can discuss the rules.
We'll have to discuss the rules, yeah.
Really on the air, too.
Maybe that's a preview, that's a Patreon episode
where we discuss the rules of the office and den.
Simulations of all his things, yeah.
And we argue, basically, of what should be.
And figuring it out.
I might argue, well, I don't even want to, yeah.
So maybe it's an episode where we argue the rules.
Sure.
Are you getting us all the way back?
Did you say 16?
He said 16.
Oh, okay.
16, because that's how many we've had competing.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I might argue for 32.
Okay.
32?
Have we done a 32?
Was the vehicle one 32?
I don't know, was it?
I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
Well, we'll have to, well, then maybe it's entire divisions
and it's little offices and it's dens and it's,
in 32, dens are in the picture for sure.
But now we're in a four-hour episode territory.
Yeah, that's true.
So that's gonna have to be,
but if we add plus the rules as its own episode,
on patreon.com slash podcast at the right, the rules.
If we just did that every year and don't say what it means,
there's an episode just comes out called The Rules.
Yeah.
All right, lots to discuss.
Anyway, yeah, Boarding Area, Charming Zephyr,
are we on the ride now?
Thanks, yeah, we can go on the ride.
You know what I like, obviously, all right,
so there's like a, Tiana's food sign's nicely done,
Tiana animatronic, you get an animatronic earlier.
I think Disney World removed like a frog or something
and people don't like, I think you got an animatronic
much earlier in Magic Kingdom and that's gone
and it's just an empty space.
And that's not a good, you can't replace an animatronic
with nothing, but we don't have that effect in Disneyland.
So to me, I'm like, wow, animatronic in this little barn
kind of thing, that's good.
My opinions on living with the land have been gone over
and gone over and gone over.
Let me say this, I loved being a slow moving log
passing by little signs for fake food.
Oh, interesting.
I don't know what it is, this was great to me.
I like seeing little okra and gator peppers.
It's the queue, you were delighted by the queue.
This is my big hypothesis for you in living with the land,
is that unpleasant interior in queue area.
That's also maybe an area, what are the most unpleasant
parts of Disney parks?
That's very funny.
Can we find the worst room in any theme park?
Because I really do think, yeah, I think I'm always
carrying a lot of that annoyance into that ride with me.
I will say, I walk into the land and when you're looking
down at everything, looking at everything, I'm like,
oh, so nice, and the balloons, whatever's still there.
Yes, that's what I'm saying, in 1982 it was glorious
in there, that was one of the best rooms in Disney parks.
And when you could just walk on to living with the land,
ah, what nice paintings.
Now I'll hop right on the ride.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's sew with switchbacks.
Yeah, right.
But I do like those fake scenes, those fake different
climates at the beginning of living with the land.
I like those too, that's some of my problem,
is that there's not more stuff like that.
Okay, fair.
But I don't know what, I guess in the same way that we,
we are more interested in fake nature than we are
interested in real nature.
Yeah.
And it's just similar, I just like seeing okra squash.
Purple pod beans, and then there's a big gator,
like Lewis made out of squash, and that's,
yeah, that's clever.
I don't know, give me these fake plants.
I think I like it more in that pre-indoor section
than I used, I think Instrumentals great out there,
I think they did a really nice job in everything
before you're indoors.
Yes, I agree, and I think all that, like,
I'm delighted by all the additions leading up
to the first drop indoors, like as far as just the vibe
of like the fake green, greenage, whatever,
in the vegetables.
Yeah, Lewis's little bottom.
Yes, that's right, really early on, yeah.
No, yeah, okay, you know, exterior pre-first drop,
cause that's right, that's the first drop, right?
It's the small one, but the-
Yeah.
Although-
Did you drop into the ride?
Real soaker, real pants super.
That's a whole thing with this ride.
Did it get worse somehow?
Yes, I don't know if it's right now is worse,
but I've never gotten, that's why people I think
were really worried about having a poncho
is because for whatever reason,
it feels like this thing is drenching you.
I always got nailed on those first, those little ones.
Well, the first, the little ones were always worse
than the big ones.
Yeah.
In general, but it definitely felt like all of them
were just nailing us left and right.
Yeah.
And yeah, that would like, either the first one
or the second one would like, the boats would,
or the logs would overflow with water.
Yeah, you were getting suit pants for sure.
Right, you would, the log would just go,
submerge into the water and just throw water on you
versus just getting splashed.
Like-
And even I will admit that being soaked in pitch black
is an unnerving sensation.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This reminded me, I forgot, I was just searching
for my notes that I took while doing it,
because I ended up doing this ride twice,
which is maybe an indicator of my enjoyment of it
and maybe an indicator of the ease of getting on it
at this point, at least on a random day during the week.
The first, I was just thinking about the like,
how soaked did I get?
And I didn't do a poncho, but I just wore a jacket
over the clothes I actually wanted to be wearing
and that took the brunt of it.
Yeah.
Definitely got more soaked the second time.
I think I was all the way in the back the first time
and something about that helped.
Like I could just kind of-
The back is always-
You have room to like manipulate.
You can kind of like lift yourself up
and fully get your legs off the ground.
In the second one, I was up further
and I definitely got it worse.
And behind me were a mother and kid.
And I forgot like, oh, you can just fit two,
you can fit a parents and a child in the same-
Just a little section, yeah.
It's kind of weird.
And we got real soaked on that first drop,
which seems like nothing.
And the kid was so, so upset at that one.
And I'm like, where is the rest of this?
This is going to be really unpleasant.
And sure enough, by the end, just like, you know,
I mean, it's exactly what my son would do.
It's exactly what I did when I was 13, honestly.
Like I was, obviously I was like a baby about this, right?
Anyway, they calculated it wrong,
but I also bring all that up to say,
I wrote down the quote that she really miscalculated.
This is not a kid who wants to be on this ride.
If the first one was that bad for him.
And then also he's in like a bad mood,
but they're trying to get selfies
and he's shifting around.
And then I hear her say,
hey, smile for grandpa or no Sprite.
Had to pass that one along.
As much as things change, some things stay the same.
Threat of withholding soda.
That's the only way to keep a ship right.
Is both a reliable punishment and also like,
when you get older, you're going to be glad
you don't have that soda.
I'll have to keep that phrase in mind
as a disciplinary tactic myself.
I got two of these guys now.
That's so funny.
Anyways.
Mike jolted in his chair when you said,
just the threat, no Sprite.
I didn't like that.
It's if I need to keep you in line.
I'll be defiant though.
I'll go buy my own Sprite.
We share a Patreon.
I have access.
You don't control how many Sprites I get.
So, but yeah, you know what?
That outdoor great.
First drop, great as ever.
Although apparently wetter or something.
Then you're cruising into that first room
and you're in there and you're like,
well, this just is as good, if not better.
I think at that point, there's no question.
You're immediately like, wow, critters,
Lewis, Tiana, every, so many.
It's, there are screens, but they aren't crazy.
I don't think that there's anything particularly effective
or memorable about the kind of the little magic dust
that's flying everywhere.
I don't know that that's.
I don't know if it works.
They want it to.
No, that makes me feel like it's,
that makes me glad they haven't done
the Spaceship Earth redo because I feel like it'd be.
They might do that.
It'd be like, wow, and then when you see
that spirit flying around and then they do it,
it's like.
It didn't, yeah.
Oh, the spirit of storytelling?
Yeah, yeah, the old spirit of storytelling
I never got to do.
I think it would just be like,
I just feel like I'm watching a DVD menu.
This isn't anything.
Yeah, yeah.
But besides that, I don't mind screens in this.
I love where both Disney and Universal are landing
in terms of screens kind of augment and support
and don't, aren't meant to be the main attraction.
So everything up until second drop, hell yeah.
I'm like, it's still critters playing music.
The music's really charming.
I think you'd really be grasping for straws
if you were like, this is not remotely what.
Right, it's animals playing music
and you get to see them
and they're big and fun and colorful.
Yeah.
And you're at a speed that's kind of like,
I don't even have time to take it all in.
I gotta go on this again.
Yeah. It's everything.
It has so much of the,
it retains a lot of what worked about Splash Mountain,
I think. Yes, I agree.
I think that the only thought I would have is that
I almost in a way felt like the ride was quicker
and maybe it's just because it's such so much new stuff,
but I was like, oh, is it because of just like
kind of highlighting little show scenes
versus feeling like, I don't know,
like it's sort of what we talk about where it's like pirates,
there's just a ton going on and it feels like you're,
you're not being directed where to look.
I'm not sure if that's kind of why it felt shorter.
Everything felt like shorter.
Obviously it doesn't go faster or anything,
but you are just being directed to little certain show scenes
from one to the next versus like,
there's so much stuff around you.
Now, is there really so much more stuff around you in Splash?
I don't think so.
It's just that because that was such an open room,
you're looking all around going, where are we?
Where are we going?
And I think maybe that led to some of my feeling of like,
like I got off of this version of the ride
and I was like, oh, that all feels a little,
like it felt shorter and it felt like smaller.
In my brain going on Splash Mountain,
sometimes I'm like, I'm confused where I am,
where we came in.
And now it's a much clearer picture of like,
I'm looking here and I'm looking here.
Oh, sure.
We're onto another ride.
And I don't know if that's a bad thing.
It was just a difference in the way I process this track,
this flume ride, I don't know.
It's interesting.
I guess it is a little more,
being that there is like kind of more,
here's dialogue to pay attention to
that explains what's going on.
It's a little more, I guess,
show scene and less atmosphere.
It felt like more, my brain made it,
it felt more linear versus chaotic.
Which again, is not a bad thing
because it was all really cute or good animatronics
and good music.
Then you get into, yeah,
what used to be Bear Bear's Butt is now a screen
for Mama Odie who shrinks you.
And then that gives way to this new sequence
where there are lots of giant things
rather than tons of small critters.
Yeah.
I think this is all pretty delightful
and a fun surprise if you don't know it's coming.
Like, oh, that's a step.
And it's a way to like, you know,
create a whole, give it a dull new act
with new moves and stuff.
And it's the way to do the thing from the movie.
Yeah, yes.
What not have Tiana have to be a frog?
Yes, not like arbitrarily.
A lot of the fur in the movie.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Criticism of it.
So to not, you know, make it where it's just,
oh, the thing that happened in the first movie
is happening again, but you're here.
It's a little bit different.
My only question is, why?
Why do you get shrunk?
Oh, you mean like a narrative reason, you're saying?
Yeah.
Hmm, it's a good question.
I've been thinking about this a lot.
It's like, time to get small.
Why?
That bottle is there.
I don't know if that suggests we drank from that bottle.
Is that, how did, do you remember?
I know that I'm thinking about it.
Does she drink from something and turn into a frog?
Or is it just a spell?
Oh, I forget.
I forget too.
No, she in the, it's, I watched the trailer,
the original trailer, and she kisses him,
like the classic Prince and the Frog.
If you kiss me, I'll turn into a handsome prince,
and that turns her into a frog.
So we should have gotten a big smooch
from some character.
That would be the note.
That we get a big smooch. Giant lips.
Yeah.
Giant, like the Rolling Stones logo.
The scariest mouth.
Yeah, you go through it.
You go through giant lips, and once you pass through,
I guess that would take me to the body.
I mean, that would also, that would be very unnerving,
and scary, and gross.
I did see one of the things mentioned about this ride
is, in terms of characters not in it,
Dr. Facilier, the villain in the movie is not in it.
Well, this is all speculation too,
because of like, Dr. Facilier is in other things in Parks.
Well, that's what I was gonna say.
I thought, oh, did they think that was too much
of a MacGuffin, like voodoo is used like.
Well, that's what people have said online,
where like, that sort of.
Fortunetelling and Romani is used for magic.
Right.
But, Dr. Facilier has been in like,
two Oogie Boogie Passes in the 2020s.
Disney is not completely clear on exactly why.
In the narrative of Princess and the Frog,
he's like, dead, but.
Oh, that's right, I was just wondering.
But friends on the other side,
like you could bring him back too.
This might be, and we've been going for a little bit,
so it might be a good time to get into this discussion,
because I think this is the discussion,
is the drop, and the feeling of the drop.
Because I, if that was the calculation,
if it's that we wanna get away from voodoo,
or we can't do Facilier.
Therefore, if you haven't been on it,
the vibe of the lift hill and then the drop is kind of a,
it's kind of now not scary, but celebratory.
And there's a party waiting for you,
and we'll get you there in a minute.
And maybe it's also kind of like,
that's the passage to make you not small anymore.
Right.
Like the drop is supposed to be the transformation.
And I get all that.
I'm just not sure that it works for me,
that there's no build of tension and fear.
It's the one thing I would want changed.
Yeah.
Even as much as little things I have here and there
about it, that's the one thing.
I just, I don't think it works.
It doesn't do it.
Yeah.
The fear, especially when I was a kid,
that you would feel going up that lift hill,
was so strong and made the drop so much cooler.
Yeah.
And now it's sort of just a very tone.
The shadows are will like,
are seared into me forever.
Yeah.
Not the silhouettes I'm saying.
Like seared into me.
Vultures, oh my God.
Thunder, lightning.
And I think it all also really fits with it ultimately,
that all lift hills before big plume drops
feel like industrial, scary, clanky.
Yeah, yeah.
You're going up a big belt.
It's like the end of Toy Story 3.
It's like I'm heading, there's light up there,
but I don't think that's good light.
I think I'm going to hell right now.
And it is what the ride mechanism feels like.
It makes what is ultimately not that bad
so much scarier to me.
You all know about my journey with this.
So much of it was psychological from the way it was treated.
So I don't know if it really works to have it be like,
hey, you'll be at a party in 20 seconds, get ready.
I saw some Imagineers say kind of contradictory things
of we want to scale back on the peril,
but, and then it was also,
we recognize that conquering the big drop on this ride
is a rite of passage for a lot of kids.
So it's like, well, those sound like contradictory goals.
I mean, I think we've been on the record
as being like, yeah, it's good when children's entertainment
has scary stuff.
It's good to have some scares.
Toy Story 3, a great example.
But yeah, I don't know.
I think they were trying to have it both ways.
Keep the drop, keep the rite of passage,
but scale back on the sinister nature of it.
This is a whole nother conversation probably,
but I do sense overthink, I would say,
in some aspects of Disney.
Like the new bride I have not seen on Haunted Mansion,
we've all read the Kim Irvine article,
and Kim is the daughter of Leota Toombs.
She's done a lot of great stuff at Disney.
She said they took the old bride out
because they didn't want to celebrate ax murdering,
and look, it's a haunted house ride full of-
Celebrate?
Having it isn't necessarily celebration.
There feels to be some sort of overthink happening.
And also, by the way, if you listen to,
if you go through year by year on a Haunted Mansion,
I cited that as the thing I,
one of my strongest dislikes in Haunted Mansion.
And the new version looks better.
Is it better?
And the version on video I've seen looks better.
That's good, that's good.
But it's just like, I'm just like,
I feel like that's kind of an overthinky.
There's ghosts shooting each other
with muskets on this ride.
Portraying something isn't celebrating.
So right, I'm just saying that feels like a very overthink,
and I think a lot of it's coming from a good place.
I'm just saying there seems to be some overthink
in that regard.
So I don't know if they're like,
we don't want to scare kids,
but I'm like, kids like to be scared.
Again, we don't have a concrete reason
why this lift hill has nothing to be scary in it,
but we're speculating.
Yeah, no, I think over,
modern Disney overthink is right.
And then it's like, well, why,
shouldn't this be the same logic of,
couldn't we take a drop tower ride
and make it fun and silly and celebratory
instead of just scary?
And that is so successful in that whole demonstration
of it's like throwing a baby up and down a little bit.
Like, so you'd think, well, that could work,
but I think clearly Guardians works
and this does not really work.
It's a different thing though, too.
Yeah. It's a different,
because like that, the Tower of Terror,
that was always the end, that was the climax,
and now they're taking the Tower of Terror ride system,
and that's going to be the whole ride basically
versus before where the lead up is a big part
of almost half the ride.
Oh, you're right.
That is a significant aspect of the change.
They're completely taking just the climax of the ride
and using that ride system to make a whole nother ride.
And then they're seeing like, okay,
can we just make a different vibe?
And it's very successful.
And then they change the music, which doesn't,
I mean, the different songs change the vibe a little bit,
and especially Monsters After Dark changes the vibe.
So you do a variation just in ride.
But when you're talking about a ride that's this long,
and I've talked about this before,
a good ride often does need, I think, tone shifts,
little tone shifts.
Which is why I like the shrinking,
why I like everything's big now.
Right, tone shifts, Star Tours is the moment
where he said we've just joined the Rebel Alliance
or whatever like that, little stuff like that.
So this is very similar tonally for nine minutes.
That's the problem.
It needs a new app.
We just need a little change up,
and it doesn't even, if somebody can argue
why it could have a different emotion on the lift hill,
maybe, I don't know what it is.
But Scary sure seems to follow, doesn't it?
But Scary sure seems to make the most sense.
Well, the stuff we mentioned earlier about,
they went to New Orleans, they did all this research,
they met with all these people,
they studied all this architecture and the landscapes,
blah, blah, blah.
I think they got most of it.
Missing a big puzzle piece here,
which is New Orleans is one of the most
haunted places in America, I feel like.
It is so, so much, so much history.
What if there were ghost projections in there?
Again, I don't know exactly what it is,
and I don't know the world of the film enough
to know what to pull from.
But if there's that calculation of no voodoo
or we don't wanna do Facilier,
why couldn't it be that Mama Odie's magic
is going haywire?
Sure.
You don't need a villain for that to happen.
I think there's plenty of theme park situations
of the well-meaning scientist or whatever.
Uh-oh, I lost control.
Isn't there a way that it can be chaos in there,
but it's still her who means well?
Some lightly sinister song with a big, heavy,
upright bass part in it,
just really building up some cool visuals.
Couldn't it still be Friends on the Other Side
without a rearranged version that's not, yeah.
They're halfway there.
We need to find some musicians.
Where's the easiest place to find music?
Oh, you sell your soul to the devil at the crossroads?
Well, sure.
Oh, dude.
Well, that's pretty.
Well, I would argue for that, but.
That's probably too.
Man, Jason, that's a good pitch.
But it's so not current, isn't it?
It's so like.
It's not.
But they would've done it back,
they would've done it in the 80s, for sure.
Even in 2009, in that original trailer,
they show the scene where there's a gag
where Lewis just wants to play trumpet
with the real musician,
and he hops on a riverboat and does a trumpet solo,
and everyone is horrified looking to him,
and then it's kind of a classic visual gag,
cuts to a wide shot of the riverboat,
he jumps out of the boat,
and then there's just a barrage of gunfire after him.
Oh, wow.
So that's a go-to cartoon gag,
but it's like, yeah, you're not gonna do that gag
at 2025, maybe, but.
Yeah, but there's options.
Besides, there's options.
You can't overthink yourself
out of just the basic way things need to go,
and it's basically, because I just don't even know,
in my head, there's no even musical shift there.
To me, it's just like.
No, there's not.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, it's just more of what you,
and it's a point where you need build and escalation
for what was a particularly great build and escalation,
and it's also just the way these things go.
It's like the, you know, the knots one gets scary.
Yeah.
Like, it's just, I, yeah, ah, it's a bar.
If it feel, if you were listening the whole episode,
and you're like, ah, it seems like, I don't know,
is there a full, this is the big issue
I think we have with it.
This is it, really.
Obviously, yeah, little stuff,
but it feels like this is the thing,
as a kid, you remember so vividly,
and again, even just as an adult, you're going up,
and that's like, this is the whole thing
you were gonna conquer this,
and now it just, it doesn't feel totally different,
and you're not as scared,
and I guess, if you've seen the exterior now,
it doesn't look like the mountain is as tall.
It doesn't look like the drop is as bad.
So now you're not psychologically going, I'm in this.
I'm gonna be thrown out of this.
But it does feel like modern Disney now wanting to scare,
like it does, Snow White still has some scary stuff,
but getting rid of Snow White's scary adventure,
which, again, I think is better.
I do think that's a plus up from the old ride.
Yes, and there's a lot of this that I think is a plus up,
and don't let this confuse.
That my final review pretty much is,
I like Tionis by Adventure.
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, it's really good.
It's really good, yeah.
But this one air element.
But it could be like.
Amazing.
Yeah, it could be literally unquestionably better
than Splash Mountain.
I think if you put so much.
With this, I just don't know.
If you put so much work into this,
not so much work, just like some elements,
I feel like you'd be like, holy shit.
If anything had to get topped,
I think they thought a lot about changing
out properties, and they thought about a lot of things
that needed to be thought about,
and they needed to think about carefully,
and a lot of it is really victorious.
But I think they lost sight of,
also, this is our chance to do Splash Mountain 2.0,
and to make it way better.
Or they had ideas, and I bet it's also
that Imagineers meant well, and then it was like,
what if there's just some lights and stuff?
Maybe.
Because that's all they could afford.
I am sorry if I came up with an alternate ride
where Princess Diana needs a band for her party.
Naveen, who is kind of a cad in the beginning of the movie,
kind of a scoundrel, sells his soul
to learn how to play an instrument,
and then you have to get his soul back.
That's a little more scary.
That's a little more intense.
Pretty good.
And when it involves him,
who otherwise is not particularly in the ride.
I think they put, they were really concerned
with making the final show scene after the drop
as big and spectacular as the riverboat
with all the dancing animals.
And I think Mission accomplished on that.
Me too.
The final scene on this. Great job.
So much stuff to look at.
I wish there was a restaurant we could sit
and watch all that stuff, because it goes by too fast.
Yeah, really.
Well, you'll get the train back.
You'll be able to see it from there.
That's true.
You'll get the train back.
I think there's, isn't there more stuff?
There's a nice little kind of glowy city at the end.
Yes, there's stuff.
Mama Odie, I think it's, yeah, I think it's an improved.
I think it's, I will say, I think it's better.
I love the riverboat with America Sings characters,
but I don't know, it's kind of better.
Moodier, more depth, well-used screens.
Easter eggs of Ray and Evangeline are twinkling stars
at the one night time.
Ray's the Jim Cummings Firefly who dies in the movie.
He's always talking about loving Evangeline,
who's a twinkling star, and then the end of the movie,
the two stars are next to each other.
He's not right, that's great.
And you can see that in a moment towards now.
I think they put all of the,
oh, no, they put a lot of effort in all of it,
but that was the thing, like, we gotta nail that.
It has to be this big spectacular thing.
I think everybody was scared that that would somehow get,
because you're like, modern Disney's not doing
a ton of animatronics as a finale, but they did it.
They nailed that.
With good humans, besides, you know, good humans.
Good human animatronics, they're new animatronics,
not the frozen ones from 10 years ago.
No glowy faces.
But I do think they didn't think hard enough about the,
I think they put, they're like, okay, good,
we gotta nail this.
This is okay, but the drop is really the fun.
It's like, not the drop, it's the anticipation of the drop.
The drop is scarier if you,
the way that a pre-show affects the ride itself,
for the build-up to the drop affects the drop.
Man, I know.
But it's like a step below because of the fear factor.
I mean, I think a lot of people agree on this.
Yes, I don't think that's a controversial opinion.
It's a swing, but I think...
We're six months late to this opinion.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right, yes.
And it's also not an opinion that makes me say,
don't go on the ride.
No, go on, it's fun.
Why do they do this?
They must bring back Mr. Trump, I demand that you.
I mean, that will happen by the,
Elon will petition and they will go back to Splash Mountain.
But I'm not in support of that.
I like what they did here.
It's just, you just wish that you could come out raving.
And it's not a rave, I mean, I went,
I was like really itching to go on it again.
And I've kept watching ride throughs, it stuck with me.
I think about being in the small zone.
It was like, yeah, the overall tone that you're left with,
I think is victorious.
I just, and then thank God the ending
because that's like the final taste in your mouth.
Because if it was, if it ended with that drop,
it'd be like, what did we do?
And I am looking for, I mean,
the only reason I've gotten down there
is because cooler weather makes me so stiff
and also going to Dizzy Lake with a scooter or a wheelchair
as I'm sure people know is a lot more work
and a lot more planning and it just.
And other stuff coming on too, so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And hey, you should get down there.
We recommend it to you.
I think you'll be, it is overall.
I'm sure I'll love it.
It's just, yeah, boy, you wish, it's a weird,
but isn't it also the thing that you could have seen,
if, is there any version where this works?
What do you mean?
Where it is not a scary drop, it's a celebratory drop.
I think that light show has to be like way, way better.
I think you gotta be, you have to be,
it has to be psychedelic in that whole.
If you like, yeah, change the lighting package
or whatever you call it, like change the lighting,
change the music, make it louder.
I think maybe you could change it
to have the frog scenes like spookier.
It wouldn't be, it wouldn't be as successful
as making that lift so scary.
I feel like it needs to be scary, but.
Wait, something should try to get you.
Something, like now you're, that's, yes.
All you do, you get small and then you have fun
with frogs playing leaf drums,
but there's never anything where a big animal
now can eat you.
That would be cool. Right.
Cause at the very least you could change,
that could be a tonal change there and then.
Yes, and then it becomes like, I gotta save you.
There's this urgency to Mama Odie.
Yeah, but even like.
Even if it's just like, oh, he's old,
he's blind, he's a bat, sorry about that.
Like the big animal tries to get you
and then someone goes like. Oh, sure.
Oh, he's a sweetheart. Oh, you're saying
getting rid of the danger.
He just spooked him, like he didn't know what you were.
That's interesting.
Even like just like a fun,
like maybe it's like completely pitch black
and like they do something like screens opening up
and like just a little bit of like dark,
some element that's still like, oh my gosh, fun,
I'm so excited to do it, but.
If you compare it to, think about this comparison.
Splash Mountain to Tiana, the drop,
versus Jurassic Park to Jurassic World, the drop,
where they added dinosaurs, there's more dinosaurs,
it's scarier now and now this is like,
get ready, get your party streamers out.
Well, that's a thing where you,
like with Jurassic World's drop,
you can make the argument that that whole section
is a little less scary because it's not
in the dark anymore, but there's a ton of new robots.
There's two giant dinosaurs.
T-Rex still comes out of the wall.
And Raptor heads, Raptor ain't nothing.
And Raptor, right, yes.
So you could at least argue like, well,
maybe you don't get that complete crazy jump scare
of T-Rex at the end of the ride,
but there's so much cool stuff to see on Jurassic World
that at least it's different and better in a different way.
Did something surprise you or something?
I hear it.
Here's something that we haven't mentioned.
On the lift hill, the fireflies, the projection,
the footage of the fireflies going by
and they get kind of warped in the glass bottle.
Oh yeah.
Cover the tunnel in fireflies.
Sure, that's really fun.
Or make it like it's like this really magical lift hill.
Yeah.
Like there's just like this weird sereneness
or like nice magic quality to it.
Like the lift hill on the Maelstrom,
where you're hypnotized by that light
and that scary face and stuff.
Yeah.
That's like, I mean, it's scary,
but there's an odd serenity, like you're just kind of like,
yeah, yeah, it's hypnotic.
Right, if you could do that tone.
That's what I thought from the concept art
that that light was gonna be,
that it would just kind of like,
you know, there'd be like a mini,
like the avalanche thing in Universal,
you know what I mean?
Oh yeah, maybe.
Like you're just caught in this tunnel
and they're just blasting me with stuff.
What if there was mist at the end or something?
So then maybe you don't know until you go through that.
Oh my God, now I'm peering down to,
I'm looking at the edge of a gosh darn salt mine.
Sure, yeah.
Well, the other thing is operationally,
the way Disney sometimes operates,
water rides nowadays,
those logs are going up nearly back to back.
They're spaced out enough to be safe,
but you see all of them, which is fine,
but you're starting and you're stopping,
you're heart breaking.
This is worse on Pirates of the Caribbean, awful at this.
Yeah.
But it's like, well that takes away a little
of whatever story they're trying to tell it that little too.
Yeah, yeah, it decreases like tension and stuff.
Why don't they use the salt?
There's, oh, there's a darn salt avalanche.
The salt's shaking everywhere.
We gotta get you out of here.
Keep your tongue in your mouth unless you love salt.
Yeah.
Let's use, I don't think they even say salt mine.
I don't think so, yeah.
Why, the answer is salt avalanche.
Yeah, I think so.
I thought it was just background information.
I didn't realize that's what the top of this
was supposed to be, the salt dome.
I guess so, yeah, you're at the peak of the salt dome.
Imagine what could go,
if you were a miner in a salt dome,
you're trying to carve out that tunnel,
the likelihood of salt avalanche is extremely strong.
Extremely strong.
And then you get in your eyes, you can't see it.
There should be a thin mist that Mama Odie tells you
is actually micro salt, so watch your eyes.
Yeah, be careful.
What do you guys think the abbreviation of this
will be by guest?
Because Splash Mountain, it's like,
you wanna go in Splash?
Do you wanna go in Splash Mountain?
Tiana?
Will people just, yeah, I feel like it's called Tiana's.
Or it'll be called Splash Mountain.
Or that, yeah, that's what I was getting at.
Are people just gonna say Tiana's
or just keep saying Splash Mountain?
I don't think I'm gonna overhear a lot of families go like,
do you wanna go down and ride Tiana's Bayou adventure?
It's just one of those long, modern names.
But I had a family out here visiting once
and I said, oh, we're at Tiana's palace.
And they're like, listen, everywhere I look,
there are signs that say Tiana's.
I need you to be more specific.
Because at the time, it was still under construction
and they were coming from Galaxy's Edge.
And so there were signs for it everywhere.
And I'm like, oh, I did not think about this.
Well, I mean, people, if they had nailed the ending
and done the right ending, everybody would say,
so what do you, let's see, let's do Haunted Mansion
and then you wanna hit Salt Avalanche?
Yeah.
They just couldn't get the Tabasco.
They tried to get the Tabasco license
and they just couldn't.
Tabasco folks don't play ball.
They didn't play ball.
Yeah.
You guys ever thought about that Nabisco
is a shortening of, that that's like a,
I think, am I right about that?
I don't know, I don't know that.
I say it just because it's a similar word.
Nabisco is, means National Biscuit Company.
Biscuit Company, yeah.
I didn't realize.
I've thought about Nabisco my whole life.
I've never, my buddy Andy Maxwell I'm working with
put a light on that.
I was like, I've never thought about,
Nabisco is just a word to me.
So when you've been saying Tabasco,
I keep, I've been tripping out like,
oh yeah, what's Tabasco short for again?
Nothing, it's not that, it's Nabisco.
Wow.
Yeah.
File that away.
I think that shows up in one of my favorite TV shows,
The Food That Built America,
with my favorite non-union actor performances
of like Marjorie Post going,
I will crush the Kellogg's brothers.
Do they do, are there little scenes in that show?
Oh, there's little scenes of like Colonel Sanders
getting his shotgun to go like shoot a rival.
A rival chicken operator.
And they're done like real cheap?
I, they're very heightened.
At some point they start to get,
at some point like in the later seasons,
I saw an episode where Campbell Scott is credited.
I'm like, oh, I guess they started ponying up.
Oh, wow.
Buddy.
So it was like, it's a non-comedic drunk history.
It's, yeah, that is exactly what's going on.
Wow, interesting.
It's very like, it's very melodramatic,
but it's like Campbell's canned soup is never gonna work.
Wow, that sounds good.
It is good.
It's great.
It's great hotel TV.
It's perfect hotel TV.
Mr. Hines, that fool.
You think he could make a ketchup, a cat soup?
Is that?
That would take over the,
that would capture the imagination of the nation?
The Hines and Hershey episodes are really intense.
Is that your birthday shot this year?
Oh, I didn't even think about that.
That's an idea.
You got time to think about it.
Could be.
Well, this has been a useful episode.
We've learned a lot of things.
Oh, yeah.
We came up with a good episode idea.
Any like parting, oh, look, we can't go out,
I don't think without bringing up the,
this is, you do have to take points away
from the spate of broken animatronic,
that how often this thing seemingly shuts down
and how often the animatronic,
I think maybe both times I went on it
on the day that I went,
Tiana was frozen as if seeing a ghost.
She heard the centerpiece of a big ruckus celebration
at the end.
Tiana was in a mode that I'm gonna call hostage Tiana.
It's so creepy the way she is perfectly still
and just eyes moving to where you wanna ask, are you okay?
Is there a pistol trained on you that we can't see?
There's no red dot on your forehead,
but I'm worried about you, Tiana.
No, she just laid down roots
in the most haunted city in America.
Of course she's so ghost.
She's scared, yeah.
She's trying to put on a brave face and perform,
but she's looking at a Madison Square Garden
size audience of ghosts.
She's like stealing herself where she's like,
I'm gonna have to take out Marjorie Post,
I'm gonna have to take out Hines, Campbell, Hershey,
all these fuckers.
Yeah, that's right.
Is that where Tiana,
in the real Tiana timeline,
does she go from employee-owned co-op fun
to disgusting international corporation
that crushes the competition?
The food hasn't tasted good for years.
Tiana's sold out hard.
Oh no, she sold, Tiana's food is owned by BlackRock now.
It's owned by private equity.
Oh no, like Jersey Mike's.
Or it's not her, it's like terrible,
it's that fucking drummer kid.
The drummer kid stops fucking around on the drums
and decides to make some goddamn money,
and he destroys the spirit
that made Tiana's food what it was.
Here's one I learned from the show.
One of the Post estates,
a little property called Mar-a-Lago.
Really?
Yeah.
Wait, what do you mean Post estate?
The Post family owned it?
The Post family owned it, I believe.
Before Trump.
Initially, yeah, maybe built it.
Interesting.
Wow, wow.
Well, that'll be your birthday show.
So the Post owned it, yeah, Mar-a-Lago,
just as a place, yeah.
Oh, some of that bad food.
Now he's throwing bad food parties.
It's not creating Carter anymore.
You see pictures of the food at Mar-a-Lago, it's nasty.
I haven't seen pictures of the food at Mar-a-Lago.
Oh, it's bad.
That's it.
Well, I'll have to look into it.
Yeah, yeah, no, it's the fartiest building in America.
Well, that's true, that's no doubt about that.
Bowen will be really apologetic.
No, we're not taking sides.
We are not saying we endorse the president
and what he's doing.
We are talking about it as a place, okay?
It is a building, is it not?
Buildings aren't politicized, are they?
We're talking about the railings, okay?
Well, today was the start of our move to the right,
our soft move to the right,
so because of the lift-till criticism.
But no, yeah, we'll eventually get to the
defending our Mar-a-Lago episode.
I guess the ride eviscerates.
You know what I was gonna say about the animatronics though?
I'm heartened by the,
obviously this is still a new ride,
so there's a lot of problems usually with big new rides.
But the cannon's working on Rise of the Resistance,
and then did you see that today or something
that was posted that there's a water leak effect
that's been restored on the Tower of Terror
in Hollywood Studios after 25 years.
There's a water dripping effect.
I don't even know about this,
I don't know if you can see that from here,
but there's this water dripping effect
that happens in the queue
that's been restored after 25 years.
Wow.
So I'm like, what's going on?
What is this?
Who's giving budgets and stuff?
So I'm like, I wonder if things are gonna get fixed,
and maybe there's a renewed interest
in just keeping everything working,
and we'll see, I don't know.
Interesting.
I did see someone saying,
because Epcot, the new Epcot,
a lot of the lighting's been plagued with issues,
and someone's like, oh yeah,
any time something like that gets fixed,
it's like one guy.
Yes, there's probably what you would think.
They probably keep firing the guy.
You know what?
There's also, I think, I forget who to put this,
there's the people that look through the patents
or permits and stuff.
I think there's some rumor
that they're gonna fix the moving rooms in Indiana Jones
because of some sort of permit.
Whoa.
Like those things will move again.
So stuff like that, maybe there's a big push
to get everything working, I hope.
There's so little, but there's so big.
They really, these things really do add up,
and when you have parks that are,
there's a long list of things like this.
Yeah.
I will say they should put at the top of the list
forever fixing the animatronic of the star
of their new ride.
I would agree that should be a priority.
I mean, I love my drips, but God,
if there's any drips in Disneyland
that we've been missing out on,
let's fix those drips.
Fake drip final forms.
Fake drips.
I don't know, I don't know if this was.
You're lucky if you get the four,
I feel like, with that one.
I don't know if this was a rumor
or I don't remember my source here,
but I'll just say it, that some of the motions,
like it's hard because the logs themselves
trigger some of the motions on the robots,
so that's different than just having everything
kind of moving, and that has been a problem, maybe,
as far as running these.
So it's fixing the sensors more than it's fixing.
Certain sensors, now maybe she's just frozen
but it's not a sensor issue, I don't know.
But I'm just saying that maybe it's set up differently
because everything's like lit the same on,
or was lit the same on Splash Mountain,
so it just can be running indefinitely
versus this has set show scenes
that have to be triggered when a log goes by.
I don't know if that's true or not, but again.
So we gotta fix these sensors,
and if it is, in fact, ghosts,
we gotta get a priest in there.
You might have to have a priest in there, yeah.
Get Lana Del Rey's new husband, the fanboat captain.
Well Jason, you and I have not discussed this off the air,
but we both know about the fanboat captain
that's now married to Lana Del Rey.
We both know about Lana Del Rey's new
fanboat captain.
I did not choose marrying this gentleman at first,
but then they did get married.
Yes, so.
Fanboat captain where?
Can we take his fanboat?
Oh, well hopefully she upgrades,
I mean maybe he likes doing it so he's kept the job,
but I feel like Lana would be able to upgrade his lifestyle.
Louisiana.
Well how about it?
What?
Jeff, forget his name.
Jeffrey Dufresne.
By Jeffrey Dufresne runs the fanboats around here.
Yeah.
Jeffrey Del Rey now, I think he would take her name.
You're talking about Mr. Del Rey?
Well to me, he'll always be Jeffrey Dufresne.
To appeal to the Trump White House,
Disney has added a Jeffrey Dufresne animatronic.
Deanna's value adventure.
Yeah, this value adventure.
This is relate, we're kind of on topic
because it's Louisiana and he is a singer
and alligator tour guide first met back in 2019.
You know, for all of the weird husbands and shit
that you guys get obsessed with.
We love husbands.
That I can't follow you on, I do like fanboats.
I do like, I guess airboat is what I,
fanboat, is a fanboat an airboat?
Mainly, you know, if I was shaky here,
you had me at alligator tour.
Yeah, yeah, he's particularly fascinating.
I just want to, if he's still doing it,
we gotta go do his, that's a ride.
We can review that, yeah.
Yeah, wow.
Well see you soon Mr. Dufresne,
get your boat aired up for us.
Jason and I have fast food in common,
the Marvel Universe in common,
and Jeffrey Dufresne in common,
and we didn't even know it.
Do you like Lana Del Rey or just Jeffrey Dufresne?
Oh, I'm more of a Jeffrey Dufresne fan.
And you shouldn't choose,
because they're a marriage, and both have equal merit.
But no, I'm more Dufresne.
I'm more of a Dufresne guy.
I like that first album,
I like the song from The Great Gatsby,
but I really like fanboats.
I would like, you know, her music, you know,
for what it is, is like stark and heavy and powerful,
if now she just is so in love with Jeffrey Dufresne
that it becomes like,
don't want to see the gator,
they're gonna have a real fun time,
climbing onto his airboat.
Yeah, that's all that is, man.
She can do some hillbilly nonsense type music,
that would be good.
Yeah.
She looks at clips of her old performances like,
what was I, ugh.
This is too moody, yeah.
Ugh, take a chill pill, old Lana.
You could put one of her old songs
on the lift hill on Tiana's.
That's kind of a spooky vibe.
It needs something to like,
yeah, just like phase you out.
Yeah.
Make you depressed.
Like, this is what you want for all rides lately,
is for them to-
I do want to feel depressed on a ride, yeah.
Music that bums you out.
Spooky, haunted, dig a little deeper, Lana Del Rey cover.
Sure.
That sounds good to me.
All right, well, a lot accomplished here.
Fake Office Final Four.
Jeff, Jeffrey, Jeremy Dufresne.
Jeremy? Jeremy.
I get, wait.
You've been saying Jeffrey.
I had been?
Yeah.
I think I was misreading it the whole time.
Well, we obviously didn't know his real name.
Did I always say Jeffrey?
I think you did.
It is Jeremy, and I was staring at it,
and still saying Jeffrey.
Well, I was saying Jeffrey once you said it, so.
Well, look, we're learning together.
We have learned that Jeffrey Dufresne is Jeremy Dufresne.
I learned by reading more carefully.
I'm afraid, I'm a fan of Jeremy Dufresne,
not Jeffrey Dufresne.
That's in case there's some real shitty
Jeffrey Dufresne out there.
Jeffrey Dufresne commits multiple child murder.
No, we love Jeremy, we love Jeremy Dufresne,
and you survived Podcast The Ride.
If you want to dig a little deeper.
No, there's a bad guy with that name.
What's that?
There's a bad guy with that name.
Oh no, what did he do?
Jeffrey Dufresne.
I don't wanna talk about him.
Everybody's gonna pull quote us as that we're right winged
because we didn't like one part of the ride,
and then they're gonna take the,
the host who went on to say,
to speak of their adoring fandom of Jeffrey Dufresne.
Stop saying it.
Can you not say, is it so bad you can't say it?
I don't know, it's confusing.
I don't wanna read the article, it seems depressing.
Jeffrey Dufresne Epstein, the New York financier.
Jeffrey Dufresne, you have no place on this podcast.
Jeremy Dufresne, we're gonna talk about you
pretty much every episode from now on.
For three bonus episodes, every month,
check out Podcast The Ride at the second gate,
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Thank you for listening.
Smile for grandpa, or no Sprite.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com,
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.