FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcast may contain
A mysterious Main Street address situation
Anxiety inducing Ninja Turtle scenarios
Professional dog petters
And Handstand ET?
All this plus a grab bag of rides about firefighters
Hey, we're back on the main feed! It's Podcast The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, today a tribute to First Responders by us, the worst responders,
to conflict, stress, or faint interest from the opposite sex.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Oh, I'm here, yes, and the way I respond is bad.
No matter what kind of thing is happening, it's bad.
Sometimes it'll be bad and people won't even notice.
It'll just be like destroying my insides bad.
My stress response will be internal, and that's bad too in a different way.
It does. I can only imagine, yes, what we don't know about what you internalize.
Yes, my stomach kind of hurts recently, and it's definitely because of stress.
Why? How come? What's been going on?
I don't know, some stuff has been, you know, fleeing.
Yes, wild stuff, and as you may know from a little check-in,
we kind of delayed the proper start of the main feed here for 2025 due to a bunch of stuff.
Again, we are all safe, though cub reporter Jason Sheridan is out on assignment.
We eerily await his return.
But generally, kind of, we are back here on the main feed, ready to kick off 2025,
if with calcified internalized stress deposits forming all over.
There's no telling what's going on in there.
We would need a full, like, scan, futuristic scan, I don't know.
That's a real theme park journey to go, like, you know, in a body wars fashion.
If we could do body wars.
Who crystallized stress deposits?
Would it be more fun going to the doctor if it was a body war situation,
where they shrunk down a little ship and a team of people were to investigate you,
versus just, like, the boring doctor looks in your eyes, looks in your ears, snooze.
If they were to shrink, I guess it maybe would take longer.
For every little thing.
I mean, you've got to be selective.
Are you saying just any doctor visit equals a miniature team is dispatched?
Yes, but you know what it could also be is that they just, like, a miniature team is dispatched,
and then you go about your day, like, normally, and they go through and they check everything thoroughly.
And that way, they're really getting a good look inside of you.
Oh, they actually, they live there.
They get to see your body is at home, so they get a sense of it.
Yeah, they live there for, like, a week or something.
So that's your physical.
Your yearly physical is that the body wars team goes into your body in a tiny ship.
And then there's just a couple things you probably can't do.
You can't, like, they got to figure out where to go so you don't poop them out or pee them out.
That's the biggest thing.
Well, because in that ride, the ship would get caught in currents,
and suddenly you're in an out-of-control blood flow.
And that would be the toughest if you're anywhere near one of the exits of the body.
Right, so they would be worried.
Yeah, so they would tell you, like, different things not to do.
And then, yes, they could go and check, and they'd be like,
oh, Mike, you're from the stress of the last few weeks.
You've developed a kidney stone, but don't worry.
We blasted it with our lasers on the ship.
Don't worry about it.
It seems more fun and thorough, fun and thorough.
Mm-hmm.
Well, it would have improved the ride for sure if the ride was a week long.
Well, that's true.
That would be more accurate.
And to live in a body for all that time.
Yeah, yeah.
But also, like, in your case, they blast a stress kidney stone, great,
but then another one forms because you, like,
missed out on a, like, X-Men branded Flamin' Hot Cheetos deal.
Yes, that's...
They're never going to make Wolverine Strikes Men Flamin' Hots again.
X-Men character Pyro is featured on the Flamin' Hots,
and I, there's a limited time drop, and I missed it
because I was picking up a drop for Batman Oreos,
Batman villain Oreos that I had procured,
and I missed the Flamin' Hot Cheetos.
It's two-faced Oreos.
You know, we all like to take the Oreos apart,
but in this case, you take them apart,
and there's two types of cream in there,
and do you want it to be good cream or evil cream?
Right.
Perfect.
That's a pretty good snack idea, actually.
Yeah, they did that with Star Wars,
with the dark and the light side.
Oh, was it Oreos?
It was Oreos.
Oh, a couple months ago.
And was it the cookie or was it the cream?
The cream, it was the cream.
Okay.
Yeah, so it was blue or red Oreo.
Now, it tastes the same.
Does that line up with lightsaber colors?
Is that the idea?
The red's usually the bad.
I don't know if there's an exception,
but yeah, red is the bad, is the Sith.
Is it the First Order?
Okay.
I mean, it's the Sith.
The First Order is the government part of it,
the army part of it.
Sith is the Jedi specials.
You know what I'm saying.
I know I don't, actually.
I've watched all the movies,
and I don't know the boundaries.
I don't care.
The Sith is aligned with the Empire,
but the Empire is just the government
and the army, basically,
and the Sith is this extra thousand-year-old,
multiple thousands of year old,
like kind of magical, evil entity
that is the counterbalance to the Force,
the light side, the Jedi.
So it's like the relationship
between the government and the Meta.
Yes, to some degree, yes, you're correct.
And Tesla.
They technically are separate entities,
but they move in the same stream, certainly.
Yeah, well, look, we are kicking it off here, finally,
and of course, we're sort of getting our bearings
from the crazy time that we've had in Los Angeles,
and after everything that our city went through in January,
we have, of course, been extremely thankful
to the incredible firefighters
who have stopped all these fires from becoming much worse.
It's been wonderful to watch.
As we talked about in our little check-in episode,
just knowing how bad they can get
if they're able to get bad very quickly.
There was a Hollywood Hills one,
and one out in the valley by where my folks are,
and getting to watch the planes do these drops
and snuff them out has been amazing to watch
and heartening amidst a bunch of situations
that didn't go that way.
Yeah, well, past guest Justin Donaldson,
literally on the news,
watched his apartment get dusted with pink flame retardant.
He watched the drop of pink.
Yes, he saw his apartment get hit
because the fire literally was just feet away,
tens of feet, hundreds of feet away.
My God.
Just got dusted with pink flame retardant.
Well, he got driven out with barely enough time
by other past guest, Matt Mazzani.
Well, that's a whole nother story, yes.
Matt Mazzani saved him.
Guest Parvius the Ride guests
are saving other podcasts the Ride guests.
That's the month we're coming out of.
Yes, and then Justin stayed in my house
for a week.
It didn't occur to me we could talk about this stuff
on the show.
Yes, I don't think they're going to be.
Because you went to San Diego,
and again, you were never really in danger,
but that left an empty house,
and Justin had to vacate his premises
because it got pinked.
It got pinked, yeah.
And there was all these just movements of like,
my mom and my sisters dated our house that night
because their power went out,
so I got family in my house,
and then they leave,
then all of a sudden I'm getting multiple texts
from a friend of the show, Andrew Grissom.
Is there a place to put Justin?
Mazzani's on the way.
I'm trying to take a nap.
Oh, he was part of this coordination, too?
Grissom was part of it.
My God.
So I'm directing traffic now from San Diego.
From another city.
To try to figure out,
okay, I guess we can put him in there.
Justin's got a big dog.
So this is a little behind the scenes,
and again, we're very lucky.
Don't mean to bother you, Mike.
I know you've got a family to worry about,
but is there any way that from afar
you could use, I don't know,
some kind of mobile device
and check if there is a way to keep your friends safe?
Do you think this is a task for you?
Yes, I rose to the occasion.
Civaco, I did it.
Everyone's had to Civaco.
And yes, another friend of mine had to evacuate,
and then I'm calling him.
Yes, so again, we were very lucky.
Our stuff was not in direct danger or anything,
but then yes, there was just a lot of figuring out
if everyone was okay,
trying to figure out if everyone has a place to go.
That's just great.
The non-specific tragic version of this
is still a lot of hassle for everybody,
and kids out of school and everything's changing,
and the situation's different day to day,
even if something obviously much worse doesn't happen,
which is far worse than anything
that we all had to go through.
But it's been, yeah, varying degrees of difficulty
and craziness and luckily kept at bay
by firefighters and first responders
and everybody who's helped keep the city safe.
So much respect for what they do.
My brother-in-law is a firefighter out in Santa Barbara,
which itself is an extremely dicey area with wildfire.
They've had massive, awful situations,
and it's very difficult.
The work they do that isn't,
the firefighting is incredibly hard.
Just rescues and their day to day calls
are far more difficult than anything you or I deal with.
Not to play down the work of theme park podcasting.
Okay, all right, you don't have to.
You're right, I don't have to beat us up
in order to make them look good.
That's true, yeah.
They look good already, physically.
They're in much better shape than us as well.
Yeah, and then obviously they're very strong,
they can hold the hose,
and then the people are in the pilots,
they dump water from helicopters and stuff,
but can any of these guys nail a reference
to Lucy's second husband, Gary Morton,
like we can?
I don't think so, that's all I'm saying.
It's just different skills, different skills.
Different types of heroes.
Equally talented, different types of heroes.
Mm-hmm, well, it's the hero you need
in any given situation.
We try to be the heroes you need,
listeners in those ways,
but today we're triveting the other kind,
because also in the little check-in episode that we did,
at some point while talking about all the serious things
going on, we were saying,
wait, is it like when they do the helicopter rides
and dump all the water, does that count as a ride?
Is that something we could talk about?
And at least one listener pointed out that,
while that is maybe stupid,
there are a number of rides that are about firefighters
and that pay homage to this process,
to that experience, to the work that they do.
This is an odd little subgenre.
There's a good amount of theme park real estate
across the country internationally.
I don't even know, I didn't even get into that.
But I know that in America,
there is a firefighter presence at theme parks,
which makes sense, because there's a couple things going on.
A couple things we'll talk about today
have old timey fire engines, and that's always interesting.
It's interesting if you're into history.
It's interesting for a little kid
to be able to climb on those things.
And then fire engines in general
are more dazzling to a young child like mine
than a lot of the stuff you're going to see at Disneyland.
You put it all together, you get the fire truck
in Radiator Springs riding around.
Oh, right.
Well, that's all of it.
That's the interest in big vehicles
and rescue vehicles merging with the silly stuff that we like.
All of that to say,
we just thought that maybe an appropriate way
to start our late start in 2025 would be this,
collecting the rides that we could find
that are rides about firefighters.
Yeah.
Can I ask, does your son like
the Main Street Fire Department at Disneyland?
Not sure that we've done it.
I thought about this because
I finally made it out to Disneyland for a minute,
and we'd had this idea, and I was like,
well, I should go poke around there.
We haven't been to Disneyland together in a minute.
I'm sure that he would.
I also saw kids climbing on the fire wagon in there,
and I don't think I realized that you could.
I assume that was a very bolted down, which it is.
You can't even do the Morse code tapper.
There's not a lot of interactivity
in that Main Street Fire Station,
but kids can climb on that thing.
But yeah, you're right.
You flash to theme parks and fire department.
That's one of the first things you see
when you enter Disneyland off on the left
in Main Street is the fire station.
It is interesting, because yeah,
that is the one realistic store
you would have to have in a town square.
I mean, like a city hall too.
I would hope if your town has the budget for it.
But not a theater with Abe Lincoln, necessarily.
That's more fantastical.
But yeah, I don't spend a lot of time in there either,
but I'm like, I guess I should,
especially because kids seem to like it.
It's a little bit unexplored in my mind.
Well, I don't know.
Yeah, it is, but I walked in there.
I mean, I think we're eating up a half hour in there
with my son for sure.
But for me, without a kid in my prayer,
because I was there solo, as we do,
I looked around.
You got an old stove.
That's good.
You got a checkerboard built into a table
that you can't fold down.
You got buckets that you can't take down.
You got an axe that you can't remove.
And you got pictures of very angry-looking men
with fine mustaches,
real tombstone Doc Holliday in there.
So if you feel like you've been missing out
on the Disneyland Fire Department,
you are missing the angry faces of at least four men.
It's, of course, under Walt's apartment in Disneyland.
Yeah, he picked as his residence to be above.
Was there ever a time when he could jump on the fire pole
and write it down?
That's a great question.
I don't think so, but it seems perfect
and seems like what he would want.
I mean, I would want that if I had my own apartment
in Disneyland.
If you were designing an apartment from scratch,
much less in Disneyland, yes, the fire pole,
though do you trust yourself on a fire pole?
Because I think it's pretty easy to get hurt on those things.
You think so?
I think probably.
I think that seems like one of those things
that's harder than you imagine.
I'm imagining Dan Aykroyd sliding down in a Ghostbusters
when he runs into the firehouse for the first time.
I think I'd be fine on the pole.
You're fine on the pole.
I think so.
When was the last time you went down a pole, a fire pole?
I don't think I've ever been down a fire pole.
Well, even at a playground or something.
Oh.
That's a similar thing.
I'm not sure.
I do end up on the playground equipment a lot with my son,
but I don't think I've done a pole slide.
But I'm worried about that.
I'm worried about that friction.
I think it depends.
I think I got to be like ...
You go like this.
Yeah, Aykroyd goes like this.
He kind of tucks his arm in, I think, in that.
Well, it's not a bear arm, right?
I don't think so.
You need fabric to soften that blow.
Yeah.
What's the nearest fire pole here?
I mean, how quickly could we slide down it?
Well, I think there's a lot of fire poles around.
I don't know that they're going to let us on,
especially not right now.
Well, yeah, I guess I'm not going to barge into a fire department right now
and ask to use a pole.
Also, they're up high.
We toured the Burbank fire station as part of some community event,
and you peer down that, and it's higher up than you think.
I think the Disneyland one we can do no problem,
because that's a little two-story.
But I think your average fire station pole, I think, is a little more ...
I think you'd have a little bit of the hesitation.
You'd get some kidney stones peering down.
I think you're probably right, but I think if all of a sudden you were like,
oh, there's a fire pole in the room next door, I think I'd run in there and do it.
But now that I have time to ruminate on it, maybe I would get a little more scared.
If you were just jumping and you didn't look at what was ...
If you just went straight for it, maybe you're fine.
But if you have time to peer, then you're getting nervous.
Yeah, I guess.
In my mind, you always just grab the pole.
Yeah, that would hurt a little bit, so you would want to tuck your arm.
I think you'd want to think your way around the physicality in general
instead of just jumping and hoping for the best.
Well, this is the kind of thing.
This is why we are respectful of their work.
And before we get too far, I also want to say,
we figured if we were going to do an episode in this area,
we should also try to do some good related to these fires
and try to help out Los Angeles and California.
So that's why in this episode, we are going to be raising money
for the California Community Foundation.
This foundation focuses on the long-term fallout of disasters like this one.
They help rebuild homes, provide mental health support,
and build up infrastructure to tackle future emergencies of this nature.
So the California Community Foundation, there is a link in the show notes.
But if you'd rather just hear a link out loud the way we do our Patreon link,
then let me say, if that's what you're used to,
then I would say go to pledge.to slash PTR.
Nice, convenient, short URL, but it's in the show notes too.
Donate if you can.
Let's see if the good boys and the Cliffords together
can't unite and do a little bit of good.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
So if you want to reach out and do something,
and thank you to the George Lucas Talk Show boys
for identifying this great cause.
So click on that link.
I'll try to remind you throughout the episode.
So there you go.
But yeah, the Disneyland Fire Station right at the front.
Yeah, can I ask, it has an actual address, the fire station.
And my question is, do all the stores on Main Street have addresses in Disneyland?
Because I see 105 Town Square on Main Street, USA and Disneyland.
Do all the stores have addresses to all the different places?
Don't know that.
Is there some technicality?
Does like the Temple of Mara have an address?
Yeah, that's a good question.
It is some weird code that technically the haunted mansion,
you do have to be able to, if it's a structure in California,
you have to be able to send it mail.
Yeah, maybe.
Not sure.
I don't know. That's interesting.
Let's go digging.
And if we can find all those addresses, then we can read them out loud.
Oh my God, I'm so excited to read them if there are more addresses.
Reciting numbers and street names.
Sounds like a blast.
Let me ask you, I mean, I have sort of a sense of an order
that we could go in terms of fire-related attractions,
but when I brought this up, when I said,
what if we corralled all the rides about firefighters,
did you flash to anything in particular?
Well, you kind of walked me into it, but yes,
it was the ride I went on as a little kid, the Santa's Village,
which was a local park in Illinois,
where you would put out a fire at Santa's house in the middle of the summer
with real water, and it wasn't a real fire,
but it would be like a little whatever, you know, torch or something.
Yeah, how are they representing it?
Because this is something to talk about too,
is the representation of fires in theme parks,
because in some of the attractions we'll talk about today,
you get very much the Pirates of the Caribbean thing,
you get the fans blowing on the fabric on the like bright lit fabric,
and that is a cool effect, but in something like that,
where it's got to be kid safe, what is that fire?
What are you fighting?
It was real fire.
What?
It was just probably, yes, it was real fire,
and it to this day remains real fire.
What?
It was real fire.
I'm shocked by that.
I'm walking, I thought you were going to tell me that it was just like
a clip art of a flame and it kind of spins around.
Nope.
So you were fighting a real fire when you were...
Well, when I say like it was like a torch in the same way,
like a torch blows fire and then you would shoot water at it,
but you weren't actually putting it out.
The torch would just turn off.
Okay.
Now...
Do you think, and is somebody operating that or is like how are...
I mean, I don't know if it's, I would assume there's a man,
maybe the person on the...
So basically what you would do is you would go around
and there would be like almost like the universal tram kind of a situation
where there's like little, it's like little different cars all being pulled,
and you would get these little like fire hoses that dribble water to start.
Mike, this is blowing my mind what you're showing me because I pictured...
First of all, you said ride,
and I assumed that was a catch-all for like any attraction.
I didn't think it actually was a ride.
It is a ride, yeah.
You're on a big long truck and there's so many hoses to choose from.
Yes.
You're riding past real like chain link fences with barbed wire at the top,
and then it just landed at a real fire on top of a house.
So what's interesting about this...
This ride's crazy.
What's interesting about this, and maybe you define interesting, but...
It is.
It used to be...
It's so...
Because I'll describe what I was...
I got to do something that's chintzy or like what I was imagining this was
for all these years.
So what actually, that's a newer version of this ride.
This Santa's Village closed for a little while
and then opened up as like Santa's Village's Zoosment Park,
which they added like animals or something,
and I haven't been there since that happened.
Love a good word that your mouth rejects while you're saying it.
Yeah.
Zoosment.
But that is a new Santa's house that just looks like a shed now.
Okay.
Santa's house used to be that there would be the fire inside.
So there would be, in my mind, and I cannot find a good video of this.
I have been looking and I cannot find a good video of what it used to look like,
but it was probably like, let's say like a dog house for a St. Bernard
or something size Santa's house, and there'd be one or two windows,
and then the fire would start in one of the windows,
and you'd all sort of shoot the water, the real water into that window.
And then at a certain point, when I got older,
I noticed at a certain point the flame would just go out.
So when I was young, I thought we were putting it out for real,
but it was pretty clear then it would just sort of turn off,
and they go, oh, you saved Santa's house.
Because also this is what we've encountered with escape rooms,
like the city walk escape room where ultimately they got to get groups through.
If they're dependent on a bunch of children to actually put the fire out,
then the capacity is going way down on this baby.
Yeah, and also that's dangerous.
Yeah, yes, that too.
Uh-oh, it's spread for real.
So now what it is is that they constructed a big shed
that doesn't really look like Santa's house or anything to me.
You could buy this at Lowe's, I'd say.
And I think maybe that it's not themed to Santa's house anymore is what the situation is,
because it's called just Santa's, or wait, what is it called here?
Santa's man cave.
That's where he practices the base.
Uh-huh, but I think you're just putting out a fire and it's no longer Santa's house.
That's what I get from this, because it's just a shed.
It's not themed at all.
It's not like a quaint little cut.
It's just a big shed.
And then they have this fire thing at the top
that's almost like you see at the Waterworld stunt show when fire appears.
You can tell it's on a track of some kind.
Yes, it's very controlled, right.
Right, so then the water comes out of the hoses.
These hoses are getting nowhere close, and it's not really the kids' fault either.
That was a real sputter.
Oh, wait, oh, no, no, no.
They get a little bit, yeah, this is...
How much, do you know how much control you have over the hoses?
You mean direction-wise or like strength-wise?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because the stronger it is,
like a kid's not going to be able to keep that thing, you know, it's going to go...
I see it's kind of a short length.
What I recall is that you would be driving in this car
and that they would start to just dribble, the water would start out dribbling.
So you couldn't shoot water constantly.
And then as soon as you pulled up to Santa's house, the pressure would turn on
and it would shoot pretty hard.
And it would get in the window of Santa's house.
I can't tell from these videos if you're getting anywhere close to that fire,
but they would turn the water on just for that moment.
And then that was it.
But you didn't have like a gun like when you're doing those carnival games
and you shoot water at the target.
It wasn't like that.
So they would turn it on and off.
But as a kid, you're still like, that's real fire.
I'm shooting real water.
It's a pretty impressive ride for a little kid.
I am blown away by the scale of what you're showing me.
Low's shed or no low's shed.
And this is probably the most tangible way to act out this child dream job
of any of the things we'll talk about in this episode.
Yes.
So it was interesting too because it's another one of those things
that you don't question that hard as a kid.
Because in the actual amusement park, you could go to Santa's house.
And there was a building.
And then you'd go here and it was Santa's house.
And you're like, when was Santa's house over there?
I was there already.
I met Santa.
This is his house too?
And then you wouldn't question that like it's in the middle of the summer
and it's not like there's no ice around and we're not at the North Pole.
And I think there was some logic to like this is Santa's summer home.
He lives here part of the year.
And then it was right next to a place called the Polar Dome,
which is an ice skating rink.
Yeah.
Which I sat and watched many boring sister recital along whatever they call them
where they cram about 200 kids into a full show, four hour show.
Oh my God.
And everyone gets a turn.
Yeah.
Every group gets a turn and you're sitting there going, oh my gosh.
I know it, you know, and it's something I've been worried about as a parent
of having to sit through things like this.
However, I think in the last few months,
I got to go to my first little show that my son was in.
Oh yeah.
Which was a delight, a triumph.
I couldn't believe how tight they kept it.
This was a TV level of stage management.
I can't believe how well the groups came in and out.
And it was space themed.
So my little boy's up there dancing to Fly Me to the Moon.
Wow.
And then the other ones were all like, you know, like space oriented,
like Levitating was one of them, or like Men in Black and Space Jam.
I like, my son was up first.
We were like, okay, well, he'll go and then we'll leave.
Right.
We were so captivated by all the rest of the space performances,
by all the other grades.
Like, no way I'm leaving this.
So I'm pretty high on the kid shows.
But, you know, again, this was like a tight 45.
It doesn't sound like the ice shows you were seeing.
No.
And I was also a child as well.
So that wasn't, I think as a kid, as an adult,
I will be much more interested in watching kids perform than as a other fellow kid.
I guess, yeah.
And you're more invested if one of the 200 children is a child that you made.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I'm very invested in that.
You physically produced.
Yes.
Can we call a shot later for just doing this collection of Santa's villages?
Absolutely.
If, you know, I had the concern.
Oh, yeah.
And there's only so many Christmas things, honestly, that we can do.
So I would love to.
We had one in San Bernardino or kind of Lake Errehead, right?
Yeah.
There's so many of those.
I was almost concerned about taking this material away by pulling it into the fire episode.
Yeah.
It's okay.
But I'm glad you did because those are very real flames the kid gets to fight.
And the notion of having to save Santa Claus' real house,
especially given that, you know, now that we're on this, like, we're all on the watch duty app.
You're looking up like, oh, it's North Pole's in the red zone.
Uh-oh.
Right.
Doesn't Santa live?
Yeah, geez.
If this house goes up where Christmas is not happening this year.
That's extreme pressure.
Yeah.
Right.
I did feel pressure.
The app shows you, do I get presents this year?
Because it also tracks naughty and nice.
And like, oh, my God, I do have presents from Santa and they're in the house.
The house is in level two.
God forbid it gets to level one.
The only other game, I'll call this a game because there was some element of it, it was a game,
that was as stressful was the underwater level in the first Ninja Turtles game for Nintendo,
which I just, I have such a clear memory of just going, oh, my God, I have to do this.
I have to do this. I have to do like, I have to win.
It's so disastrous if I lose.
And it's a similar thing with Santa.
Because your friends would drown?
Yes, even though they would drown often with that turtles game because you would switch between turtles.
So sometimes I'd lose three turtles, but beat the level at least.
But you watch their corpses just float up to the top.
Yes. And do you know what I'm talking about this level?
No.
This level is the first Ninja Turtle game for the Nintendo.
This game is, this is the ultimate, I've played it a thousand times,
but just the first level and then didn't put in more coins.
Well, no, no, not the arcade.
Not the arcade.
Nintendo game.
Yes, this was different because those were, yeah, those were different games.
I don't think I own the Nintendo game somehow.
It's a bad game. It's hard to play.
Okay.
The controls are bad. I've never beaten it either.
But like the third, fourth level is an underwater like sewer level where there's all these different like vines that you can't touch when you're underwater.
Let's call them vines. I don't know what they are.
And like you would hit it like and you'd be like swimming through narrow thing like vines on the ceiling, vines on the floor.
And you got to swim through this narrow path.
And then you have to defuse bombs and there's a timer.
So you have like 90 seconds, let's say to beat the level and you have to defuse 10 bombs and you have to swim through these precarious situations.
And just as a five year old, six year old, whatever I was, I just was white knuckling that Nintendo controller because of this.
And then like when I would win, it would just be like euphoria.
Yeah.
And it's still, I can feel it.
And so you would win. I mean, that's good.
I have beaten the level plenty of times, but I would lose and you would cycle between all four.
Like sometimes I would, yeah, three turtles would die and I would get on the fourth one.
Like Michelangelo would survive with like a little health left, but I beat the level.
And it was fully, they float up to the top.
Then it fully cuts cut scene of splinter at the funeral.
They take you fully out of the level and throw you back in and you're right next to a vine.
You can't even think about that.
You can't even think about leaping splinter.
Right.
And then, yeah, it's a whole, the funeral is in real time on the Nintendo.
You'd have to watch it an hour.
Michelangelo was a, above all, a crying turtle.
Honestly, it's like kind of the plot.
A turtle of faith.
Wants to search every Sunday.
The plot of the last Ronin comic book, honestly.
It is.
Michelangelo is the only surviving turtle.
His brothers are dead and they appear to him as ghosts.
I don't know.
And then the rest of the game is just.
Well, that's a comic, but yeah, that's, they're going to make, I don't know.
They said they're going to make a movie, but I don't know.
Of a story where the turtles are, most of the turtles are dead.
Three of them.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Wow.
That's what they said.
I don't know.
But then they also said that Colin Jost and his brother were making a turtle movie and
that's not happening.
So who knows what's going on?
And I can only assume they've announced a Josh Gad turtles.
Well, here it is.
I see it's been announced an hour ago.
Yes.
If it is, if it is a property from before the year 2009, Josh Gad has been attached
at some point.
That's right.
This is all, I think all of the emotions that every emotions stress, everything that you
contain.
I think everything that you shove deep down only to come out as kidney stones.
I think you see a movie where the Ninja turtles all die and you're crying for a month and
a half.
I think that is how all of it, it all just gushes out of you.
You're an entire life's worth of stress and trauma.
Right.
I agree with you.
You need this movie.
I think this I need it as a catharsis.
And then, yes, there's so many different traumatic, like when I saw the mighty mutanimals die
in the comic book series, the mighty mutanimals, the friends of the turtles, I saw them gun
down in a horrifying issue of an Archie comic book completely out of nowhere.
Are you just at like high school?
You're just in Riverdale and then they come and then they publish by Archie.
Okay.
Though they did cross over a little bit.
You think it's about like, oh, do I ask Veronica to the dance and then the mutanimals suddenly
show they're brought to Riverdale to be executed?
No, it was not that.
Although there is an Archie Punisher issue that's kind of like a tongue in cheek funny.
Punisher comes to Riverdale to solve a problem.
I forget what the plot is.
Oh, wow.
You can trace my anxiety to just things that happened to the turtles and their friends
when I was little.
And so, yeah, you're seeing some, if I see something as an adult, it'll be good for me.
You see all of the stresses in your life as big sharp guys charging at you.
Big sharp guys.
There were big sharp guys that took down the mutanimals, so you're all right about that.
Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse, basically.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, sometimes the problems of the world are more complicated than a big sharp guy,
but I don't know.
Maybe someday we will face big sharp guys, too.
My daughter runs around now yelling, I'm craying.
And then I have to run away from her.
Cool.
And then she goes, you're craying.
And then I'm craying and I run after her.
That's a good one.
That's pretty good.
And she loves in the picture.
Little stuffed craying she's got.
She's like, craying.
She's hugging it this morning.
It's all happening for you.
It really is.
Yeah.
You can let it all melt away.
I'm a lucky guy.
You get to live craying in your home.
I'm craying.
And then she'll go, it's only me to make me know that it's not really craying.
Let me bring this into another memory with my son, which is that I got to do a little
firefighting attraction when we went to Legoland, San Diego early last year.
We did this thing.
I had to look up what the name was.
Legoland is the Funtown Police and Fire Academy, which in and of itself.
That's good, yeah.
Funtown.
But you still do need law and order even in Funtown.
Why yes, we face the threat of burns here in Funtown.
Anyway, you go to Funtown, you help out Funtown.
What this thing was, truly, I've always been imagining your Santa's Village thing as a
kind of a cutesy pretend sort of situation like this was.
This is a very unique attraction where there's four or five vehicles all lined up.
And this is a family attraction.
Everybody does it together.
And I think it's probably optimal for there to be little kids to do some of it and then
grownups to do some of it and the bigger, heavier lifting.
Because you have to get on a vehicle and you have to pump it and pump your way all the
way across a little tarmac or something.
And when you get to the end, as fast as you can, you got to jump out safely, still hold
the kids hands.
Don't want anybody tripping and falling.
Don't want actual emergency.
Don't want them to have to go to the Funtown emergency room.
But you get down, you got to get to a fire hydrant, you got to start fighting a little
fire.
In our case, we had a little blaze to put out at the Funtown post office.
We had to save the Funtown post office.
And then put it out as quickly as you can and then jump back on, pump your way back
to the starting point.
And it's like four or five cars, families all facing off against each other.
And this was pretty fun.
This was like a family double dare kind of situation.
I don't think we've been in something like this where the three of us all together have
to solve a little problem.
It was pretty neat.
Very worried the entire queue, however, that we would end up dead last.
And this was my feeling the whole time is that there would be, hey, I don't even want
to put it entirely on our son.
I don't have the strongest belief in my own physical capabilities.
This could be a referendum on all of the Gardiners if we come in.
And like markedly, if we are last so much so that it slows the entire experience down
for everybody.
And the feeling of coming in third in the...
Being third in the Funtown Fire Rally to me felt more victorious, I think, than winning
a gold medal in the Olympics.
The relief of our family together not being the dead last family, which I think is my
philosophy in general.
I don't, you know what?
I'm not going to require perfectionism out of my son academically, athletically, if
I already don't got a good feeling about that.
But that's not what the Gardiners are about.
But the lack of dead last, I think that's my...
Just not last is my parenting philosophy.
If we can...
Second to last, fine.
Second to last, love it.
Amen.
I remember feeling that way all the time growing up with contests like that.
As long as I'm not last, you just beg not to be last to God, to your whatever, whoever
you believed in.
Please don't make me last.
But then, of course, I've said I was last picked in a basketball draft in seventh grade.
Oh, man.
And my dad's...
Despite your height.
And I know that because my friend's dad was really a jerk and told me.
Oh, God.
That could have escaped you entirely.
Yeah, I wouldn't have to know.
Fuck.
Why did he tell me?
I don't know.
Jerky thing to do.
I should just say his name here.
Just try...
Would there be any real percussion against...
I don't think so.
Saying the dad's name.
No, he's not hearing this.
It's up to you.
No, it's fine.
It's so tempting just to hear some boring name.
Some guy's name.
His name's kind of interesting, actually.
Oh, really?
He won't say it.
Eddie, can you say half of it?
If my friend is listening...
My friend that I talk to still, if he's listening, I don't want to, like...
I don't want to do it.
I guess it's better.
We know our listener.
Our listeners are going to go to your hometown and they're going to let this guy down like
a dog.
They would find...
Yeah, you could do it pretty quick.
Figure it out.
Please, listeners, no more killings of vengeance in our names.
No, please.
We've appreciated the first few, but come on.
We're going to end up in trouble at some point.
Right.
Well, in terms of bigger attractions to talk about, the thing that I flashed to that I
was aware of in realizing, oh, there are rides about firefighting, what I flashed to is an
attraction at Dollywood because I remember them opening this, and I assumed this was
about a few years ago, but in fact, this ride has been open since 2014.
They put in a coaster called the Fire Chaser Express.
First things first, while I would like to talk about this Dollywood ride, I would also
like to say we've got to get our asses to Dollywood.
We've got to figure it out, come hell or high water.
If this podcast reaches a so-called conclusion and we have not made it to Dollywood, then
what was it all even for?
Why did we do it?
Well, it's not.
We're going to be replacing ourselves with different hosts.
It'll never end.
That's the first thing, but second of all, yes, you're correct.
I think maybe what we should do, and I guess I'm spitballing on the ear here, is that we
should probably a year out announce we're going to Dollywood.
That's the only way.
We're doing whatever, two shows, give everyone plenty of time, because I have a feeling that
the audience there would be more of a show of people coming in from out of town.
I don't know that the Pigeon Forge population is such a big podcast of ride listeners.
I don't know that there are so many locals.
There might be a few, or do you do it in Nashville and then, you know.
Could do something like that.
I don't know.
I'd be curious, listeners, strategies, is anybody out there?
Have you seen a podcast like ours in your area, and how did they do it?
We're flying, but we got no tour manager.
We're figuring this shit out ourselves.
We would love to do it.
Every reason on earth is getting in the way of us coming to your town, but God knows we
would love to come to your town, and if your town is Nashville, or even Pigeon Forge, put
some help in the comments.
We'd appreciate it.
Would we be allowed to swear in a live show at Pigeon Forge?
Are there some rules on the books?
I think those aspects of Pigeon Forge are exaggerated, because I once thought it was
a dry town, and that's not correct.
I don't know.
Swearing may be another.
That might be a Dollywood thing.
That might be Dolly herself's preference of gosh and dag gum, which I would accept and
honor.
Right.
I mean, yeah, I don't have to swear.
You don't have to talk about 30.
We can talk about innuendos.
Dolly is fine with an innuendo.
Probably.
I've seen her make plenty of innuendos.
I mean, maybe she's not uncomfortable with us doing it, but she does it.
So I'm just saying, if that's the level of-
Because y'all don't own it.
You seem nervous.
That's fair.
She's right about that.
No, she doesn't.
But yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if there's a venue for us in Pigeon Forge, if they could stop running that
Civil War medieval time show.
I know they've changed it.
But Dolly's Dixie Stampede has been changed.
Yes.
Yeah, I think it's not called that now.
But could we perform there?
I don't know.
I mean, it would be really fun to perform in an area of dirt or gravel meant for horses.
That would be great.
And also having to divide people into, you know, they only- all right, now this side
only laughs at Mike and this side only laughs at Jason.
Yeah, that'd be fun.
Cheer on, your host.
Anyway, all this to say, we're gonna talk about Dollywood ride, doesn't mean we're closing
out Dollywood.
You know, I don't even like talking about rides where it's all my intention to go there.
And in looking into these attractions, because there are multiple, it's only further whetted
my appetite to get down there because these look like a real blast.
Air Chaser Express is what they call the first dual launch family coaster.
So it's kind of tame enough, the whole family can do it, but it does one forwards, one backwards.
It's like, you know, a little bit of Hagrid's kind of stuff, but not so extreme, even to
where there are like little show scenes.
This ride seems like a lot of fun.
Dollywood in general seems like a lot of fun, especially because at least at this point,
they got a big new ride.
She's coming out and doing a little, I watched the opening ceremony, which starts with her.
She comes out in a fire uniform, looks incredible, obviously.
She performs great balls of fire.
Delightful.
From her rock and roll album that she's recently put out, because she was inducted in the Rock
and Roll Hall of Fame and felt that she owed it to getting in the, well, remember she
turned down the Hall of Fame initially.
And then they're like, no, you're in whether you want it or not.
And then she was like, well, I'm not a rock and I don't do rock and roll as much.
But then she like performed an original song about rock and rolling at the Rock and Roll
Hall of Fame and then put out this album of rock and roll songs.
This seems, this is delightful, but seems needless.
I don't think she had to prove herself in this area.
I agree with that.
Yeah.
I think she doesn't like, it's an interesting track, it's like, this might not be it, but
Hey Jude with Paul McCartney or something.
Like, there's something like that where you're like, wait, what?
But yeah.
Rock star.
Oh my God.
This cover.
Oh, we're in like Angeline territory.
This is insane.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Anne Wilson's on there.
Linda Perry.
Oh, a new version of hey, hey, hey.
Kid Rock in there in the mix.
All the best rockers.
Joan Jett.
I hate myself for loving you.
I think I tried listening to this and it wasn't necessarily my favorite album.
Okay.
Yeah.
It wasn't awful.
It wasn't, I like a lot of Dolly Parton stuff.
But yeah, anyway.
So wait a minute.
There's, wait, there's 30 tracks on this album.
It's let it be with Paul McCartney.
There's 30 songs on this?
A lot of songs.
One of the densest works.
Yeah.
Wow.
She really like, I don't know why she's.
There's been 29 tracks and then she does Freebird, an 11 minute Freebird.
I don't know why.
She put the work in.
She felt so insecure about getting into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
Wow.
Like who cares Dolly?
Purple Rain?
Just go take the.
This album is 141 minutes.
Yeah.
This is like, this is getting close to a brutalist.
So you need an intermission on this.
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
Well, didn't know any of this.
I'll try to reserve several days to listen to Rockstar, but anyway, I really liked her
great Balls of Fire and then she comes out and does like folksy jokes and she talks about
we're investing, we're investing $300 million into the park.
I got most of it in my back pocket.
There's a, they, they perform a bucket brigade and she says that she loves the firefighters
and they're on her bucket lists.
It's nice.
I think from Bruce Valanche's recent WTF interview, he discusses being like a ghost writer, like
writing her banter.
Right.
I think that's still kind of a big, I think that's a good like ghost writer area in general
is if they're the kinds of artists who, I think like a Lionel Richie, I think there's
people who do still commission jokes from the boys and get their banter jokes, but I
think that was, yeah, pretty, you know, Valanche was in the Dolly mines.
I've seen Elvis Sastello a couple of times and sometimes I go, it feels like he has a
bunch of little jokes written.
I can't tell if they're him.
I can't tell.
Could be him though.
But sometimes I suspect there's different, different, there is different.
That's a whole episode of a show that I don't do about the different banter between songs
for different bands and artists I like, go see.
So that's a different show, but you insisted Lucy is ours.
Lucy is a podcast, a ride thing, but do you want to hear like how I think, like what I
think Jeff Tweedie's humor style is when he's doing a solo acoustic show versus think
so.
We might be kind of Lucy territory here.
I think it's funny.
I'm just telling you, that's a different show.
Lucy is different.
But yeah, that's, oh, my sister saw Bruce Valanche somewhere like a week ago and I was
like, should I just walking around or watching a show, he's watching a show and I was like,
should I have her ask Bruce to be on this show?
I didn't, I didn't make her do that.
Got a book to promote, I think maybe, maybe a podcast, I think, maybe a podcast.
You know what?
Let me send an email.
Yeah, that's that.
I should, I really need to do that.
Ooh, a Valanche.
You know what?
Feel free to tune out right now.
You could do that right now if you want.
I want, we want that to get done.
That's more important than you saying anything here.
You know what?
Actually here, you write the email and I will read, I'm going to write an email on the air.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah.
Just bring the mic close to your, that's, you know, that's actually not a good idea
because I, if you weren't listening to this, then we'll be in deep shit because it's,
what I'm going to do is I'm going to read the narrative of the ride, Fire Chaser Express.
Yeah.
And I need somebody to be hearing this.
Oh yeah, I'm present.
Because, you know, it's a little bit, just to try to track what's, what's going on.
Again, I think you can go on this ride just thinking, okay, I'm a volunteer firefighter
and I'm going to go on a little adventure.
I don't think you need to know any of this, but I want to pay homage to this because I
don't think I knew there was this degree of mythology in Dollywood Attractions and
I'm impressed.
Please go ahead.
So, the ride is themed around the fictional volunteer fire station Seven and its fire
chief, Pete Embers.
Great.
Pete, love that.
Pete Embers is a man of considerable patience and he's always more than happy to let sleeping
dogs lie.
Okay?
Okay.
They convey that in a cue.
I'm like, maybe there's a sleeping dog in there and he's like, eh, fine.
He's conflict-averse, I guess.
Like me.
Except, except, when the great beautiful smoky mountains and their forests are in danger.
That's Pete Embers' home and lately, he's had to deal with this local businessman and
eccentric fireworks enthusiast, Crazy Charlie Cherry Bomb and his, I didn't, you know what?
That was hiding in plain sight.
I copy pasted the phrase Cherubom written and it didn't even occur to me until I said
it out loud that his last name is Cherry Bomb.
They got it.
Does Dolly do that song on Rockstar?
Cherry Bomb.
I don't think so.
So Crazy Charlie Cherry Bomb and his gas station and fireworks emporium.
Love that.
Combo, gas station, fireworks place.
That's funny.
Crazy Charlie's asking for trouble.
Because of an increase in dry lightning in the area, Charlie has been calling the fire
station on a daily basis.
If he sees the slightest hint of smoke, he says, get out here and help me.
So to deal with Charlie while leaving his regular volunteers available to deal with
real emergencies, Chief Embers has decided to deputize almost everyone in town to keep
an eye on Charlie and his latest creation, the Big Bertha Firecracker.
So what we are now is like all of the, we're through the regular firefighters and we're
through even the regular volunteer firefighters.
We, the riders of this ride are the riffraff.
We qualify just by like having human bodies.
We technically have limbs.
So close enough.
You can deal with this idiot.
You go help Charlie out.
If he.
I guess that's what Fire Marshal Embers has to do.
What is his first name again?
Pete Embers.
The original Dollywood creation, Pete Embers has asked you to help him help out a nuisance
in town who distracts from real emergencies.
Wow.
It shows the respect.
I mean, this is a very smart plan, but I guess I'm a little insulted that Pete Embers puts
me in the F pile.
He's just a no.
I mean, it sounds like he might not be very good at his job.
I mean, I don't know what the size of the fire force is at Dollywood, but maybe that's
the best way to do it.
Maybe that's the only thing they can do.
You don't want Charlie Cherrybaum taking all the attention.
Yeah.
It makes sense.
He's just a nosy neighbor or something, but I think then you go on the ride and you determine
that maybe they should have paid more attention to Charlie the whole time because now he's
got Big Bertha, which is a very big firework.
And when you're on the ride, first the ride's just going and you're just kind of riding
through the great smokeys.
But then you enter the fabled gas station and fireworks emporium and then things start
going off.
Real fire.
You're right next to it.
And then Big Bertha points at you and you're launched backwards and you propel out of there.
That's really, yes.
That's fine.
It's so similar to like the Big Thunder redo 10 years ago in a lot of ways, like stuff's
blowing up and you got to get out of here.
Yeah.
It's cool that they have things of that production value.
I think the equivalent, which is like Grizzly Mountain or something in Hong Kong, I think
is kind of this structure.
I think you get cornered, you do a backwards launch, track changes, but it's kind of like
Everest too.
In that case, I think there is a bear chewing on a cord that you need to keep you safe.
I don't know if you've watched that ride through.
That's a fun looking ride.
I haven't.
Anytime there's an animal chewing through something on a theme park ride, like the beaver
chewing through the train tracks at Disneyland, which is a newer thing.
Really good.
Pete Embers, I always, it's interesting because sometimes Pete fights Embers, shouldn't it
be like Pete Firehose or Pete Firehydrant, Pete Hydrant?
Pete Pole.
Pete Pole, Pete Truck, you know what I'm saying?
Why would his last name be something he's fighting?
I don't know.
I guess it depends.
But then he cuts in his blood.
He comes from it.
Yeah, I guess so.
He's of the Embers.
It does feel like a 90s, 80s action movie character would be called Pete Embers because
I've mentioned this before that Arnold Schwarzenegger in Commando is John Matrix and then I was
just watching Demolition Man last week.
The only person left alone is John Spartan in that.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Detective John Spartan.
Oh, Demolition Man's up there.
You just named my two favorites.
I think Commando, my favorite Schwarzenegger, and Demolition Man, my favorite.
Which stands, I just watched Cliffhanger and I enjoyed Cliffhanger, but it's no Demolition
Man to me because they don't show you the future of what Taco Bell will be like.
Yes.
And you remember Wesley Snipes' character's name in Demolition Man?
Simon Phoenix.
Fantastic.
God, hell yeah.
Masterpiece.
And I'm not going to do this to torture you, but I didn't realize this until last week
and I almost fell out of my chair.
Don't tell me Gail Gordon's in Demolition Man, for God's sake.
Well, Podcast the Ride character, or person that comes up once in a while, it plays the
warden at the start and is killed by Simon Phoenix.
Who's that?
Andre Gregory.
Oh.
From My Dinner with Andre.
Really?
Yes.
Oh.
I'm watching this.
Wow.
Wait, what the fuck?
My Dinner with Andre?
Of course, with the story, you've heard the story on Podcast the Ride, but yes, he gets
killed pretty early in the movie, like he gouges his eyes out.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Wow.
It's an all-star cast.
Geez.
Well, it's also the dystopian future with big scary buildings as portrayed by the San
Diego Convention Center and this one office park in Westlake Village.
It's right next to a Caruso property.
Yeah.
Anyway, do yourself a favor.
Take yourself on the Demolition Man locations tour.
You'll see a lot of nice stuff.
I was just there last week.
That's the thing about not swearing, also, like we were just talking about.
Wow.
That ties it all together.
It is a Pigeon Forge world in which swearing is not allowed, which makes Simon Phoenix
all the more abrasive.
Right.
So anyways, yeah, I don't know, I love Pete Emmer's, I love Charlie Cherry Bomb, yeah,
you get in there, things start going off, Big Bertha tips at you.
I just love that there's a show scene in a Dollywood attraction.
I didn't know the degree of theming there and it looks great.
It looks like a lot of fun.
There is another fire themed attraction, but it sort of ties into the other big one that
I want to talk about.
So maybe I'll kind of like move along in that order, because one's sort of like a cousin
of the other one.
And as we transition from thing to thing, I will remind you that in this episode, we
are raising money for the California Community Foundation.
That's at pledge.to slash PTR.
Link in the show notes.
There we go.
All right.
I'm doing my hosting here.
Professionally done.
Yeah.
The park drops.
Wow.
Mid episode.
Didn't even call any attention to it.
Just kept moving.
Casual.
Yeah.
Casual is all I'll get out of it.
Didn't make a meal out of it.
It was more of a snack.
Quick snack.
Well as we get to the main course in my estimation, because this ride I was not previously familiar
with and now I am dying to get there and go on it.
Another place that I, you know, I don't even know that this park was on a list of places
I was especially dying to go, but I am now because we're talking about a ride called
Fire in the Hole.
This is at Silver Dollar City in Branson, Missouri.
Here's another thing.
That's another place.
If we're like planning flags for future things, I feel like if we made it to Branson and we
like really planned it in Branson, I think we could become an all Branson podcast for
a year.
100%.
I watched a Club 3 loser at one point was a Branson, it was, I think it was called Lights
Camera Branson or something.
And it was, it was like a promotional video hosted by Willie Ames, who played Bible man,
of course, more famously from Charlie and Charlie and Charles in Charge.
I got old Charlie Cherry bomb in my head, you see.
He's never in charge.
Shouldn't be.
But so anyway, I, that was just like suggested as a maybe Club 3 and I'll like, I'm like,
I'll watch it.
I'll do it.
It was so fun.
I'm like, Oh my God, Branson.
I mean, it seems like it might be like maddening to be there too.
I can't tell.
But because it seems like it's all just on one big street, just like one long highway
you drive down.
It's just theater after theater after theater.
But also this theme park, Silver Dollar City, and I will be honest, I've never looked into
anything at Silver Dollar City and I am so surprised and delighted by fire in the hole
because what we have here built in 1972, this is, I think lays claim to be the first
indoor dark ride roller coaster, right?
I think it is the first ride with coaster elements where it does speed up and get fast
and his lift hills and drops, but there's also animatronics and sets and show scenes.
And when you add all that, I mean, this is like this today remains one of the most challenging
genres of ride.
And when they open, you know, it's it's it's gigantic news.
I mean, this this genre is this is this is Guardians of the Galaxy, Cosmic Rewind.
This is Gringotts.
This is like, you might say Journey to the Center of the Earth in Tokyo, Disney.
See, it's just a hard thing to do to get animatronics along.
And they they were doing it in this crazy homespun dressed up mannequin kind of way
back in the early 70s.
It's crazy.
Yeah. Some version of this ride system is probably my preference for ride system.
I don't like if I had to design a ride, I want some thrills.
I want something exciting.
But obviously, we want the show scenes.
We want the robots.
So like, that's the tricky thing.
I mean, I guess Indiana Jones ride vehicle is close.
Yeah, it could be exciting without a coaster proper.
I don't require, but it certainly is.
But it's cool to combo coaster and show scenes.
Mummy, I guess, is one that's for mummy.
And like Gringotts, in my mind, Gringotts never fully that first part of Gringotts
when you kind of dip down, you do the drop.
They're exciting.
I go, holy shit.
And then the rest of it is like fine to fun.
I guess it gets a little more like anonymous screen.
Yeah, it gets a lot of spinning in your eye.
It's not quite.
It never gets the high of that opening thing.
I like Hagrid's better.
Yes, I guess, obviously.
But yeah, but even with Hagrid's, it's still like tricky because it's like some of the
stuff you see too fast.
It's like you wouldn't always time out, right?
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Not that I still I think it's pretty great in a lot of ways.
But yeah, it's the ability to speed up and slow down, which I don't know that they
particularly had that ability on this or it was just like a gradual lift hill that
you don't even it's so gradual you don't realize it's happening.
Yeah, I frankly don't know how they did.
And this is before Space Mountain, even right.
And it's like that's when we were talking about that initial idea for Star Wars in
the Disney Disneyland with the like track like decision point.
Yeah, essentially, it looks like it would have been like this.
Yeah. And then like they had other ambitious things like the scene.
I guess it wasn't that ambitious.
The scene would kind of lift or raise.
I forget you'd be in Dagobah with Yoda at the start of the ride, I think.
And then it would lift you up.
Yoda lift you up.
But I think what it'll be just the scene, the whole scene would lower or raise up.
Oh, it might be like an optical illusion like Haunted Mansion.
Right, right, right. Gotcha.
But yes, that's in my this is this is the feeling I've always want.
I always want from rides is like the ability to see robots, but then go really fast.
Yeah, that's what you want.
It's actually sort of a rare combo.
Yes. Right. Because you want to like, you know, we love pirates and we love Haunted
Mansion. These are these are rides where you have all the time and we slow down to
appreciate the robots.
But something that lets you do that to some extent, but then also keeps going.
Now, here's another I think we're very fond of these Knott's Berry Farm,
the Calico set of rides of Calico Mine Ride and the log flume.
But those are sometimes in that log flume, you rip it through and you can't see all of
you can't see how poorly articulated the electronics are.
You can't see how scary their faces are.
Yes. Other side of the coin on the Calico Mine Ride, it's so slow that you have nothing
but time to see the sad, sad faces of all the miners and maybe get a little bit depressed.
This is a ride I've been very hesitant to take my son on who is obsessed with trains.
But and like, that's the train ride.
But then I'm like, you get on it and it's so dark and it's so claustrophobic.
And the the sound of it is just like, oh, it's like, yeah, it is.
Yeah, yeah, I am really worried my boy would would freak out trains or no trains.
So you're not now that's not look, we love the creakiness.
We I think in general, all of that to say, I think we love scary,
limited animatronics or not animatronics or just like, you know,
mannequins with old timey costumes on them, it's like it's an area
that seems synonymous with theme parks is is like
like cowboys go, well, well, fancy seeing you here.
But it's actually it's actually a little hard to think of tons of examples
of that kind of thing, of unmoving, weird looking characters
who talk to you in folksy voices.
And this is the mother lode fire in the hole.
This is exactly what you want.
Yes. Yeah, yeah.
I mean, we were spoiled, I guess, by having knots here,
because there is a lot of kooky old timey guy.
Yeah. It's like three rides, I guess, with that actual like figures.
Maybe more. You know, it's weird.
It's like less the I wouldn't really call the raft ride that
because those are kind of these like charming, realistic bears.
There's one guy with a musket.
OK. Oh, is there? Yeah.
There's one like musket guy.
And you used to have Mystery Lodge, which is not was not a animatronic.
That was a guy in a costume and a mask who would talk about the Raven.
Oh, the Raven.
And it's it feels like kind of related to that.
But like, anyway, I like it just it seems like you're always.
I'm always chasing a weird old weird creepy cowboys.
Yeah. Well, I park attractions.
But where do you where do you really get them?
And you certainly get them here.
Yes. This is you get. Yes.
You feel fills the promise of the idea, because even it feels like
you would get more of it at Disneyland, but you don't really anymore.
I mean, there's not really that many cowboy performers.
Golden Horseshoe is not running.
Yeah. You hear the prospect, your voice on Big Thunder.
Yeah. So, yeah, it's becoming a little bit.
Does anything at Disney in any of the parks fit the bill here?
I mean, like you've got Carousel of Progress, but that's a different
that's old timey, but kind of a different.
I mean, like for specifically for cowboys or. Yeah.
I don't know.
Where they're creepy.
The Hooptie Do review or there are cowboys in that in Disney World.
I mean, I think I think it's in that vibe.
Yeah. I don't know if there's like scary,
you know, figures whose mouths don't move.
No. Yeah, that's that's what I want.
I want it just.
Yeah. The creepy off putting soot covered faces.
Yeah. And this is wonderful.
It's wonderful. So so the to tell the story of this,
this is all based on real local legend and lore.
Again, volunteer firefighters, which this system is flawed to me.
I mean, this is, I guess, the way they get you to be part of the experience
is that you're a volunteer firefighter.
Having been through a bunch of fires in our city,
I don't want I don't want no Scott and Mike fighting these fires.
I hope we're not doing volunteer firefighters.
I've learned a lot.
Now, there's not the podcast to discuss all the different people
fighting the fires at the same time.
But it's interesting because, yeah, there are volunteers.
There are people that are serving time fighting the fires.
Yes, that's terrible.
But I think if we and I were fighting the fires,
they would give us an easier job.
Like somebody needs to keep an eye on the keys
and the ignition of the firetruck while we fight the fire.
So I feel like there's Dalmatian jobs.
Sure, we could keep that Dalmatian calm, make sure to check everyone's
like pants to make sure they're not falling down while they're fighting
the fire and you like I run up behind a firefighter and pull their pants up,
make sure their suspenders are or are tightened,
whatever you call them overall.
Cook up a giant vat of chili for when the boys come home.
I don't know about that.
I wouldn't be good at that either.
Yeah, that would be good for me.
I could technically I could read technically get like physical food
I would get something that resembles the ingredients of chili in a pot.
It'd be the worst chili you've ever had.
But yeah, I look, I'd fill that vat with something.
Yeah, I could take I could take all the firefighters Taco Bell order.
That's a good idea.
And I could really like what in the middle I could get really figure out down to like,
OK, Brian doesn't want lettuce.
OK, and I can do that in the app and a whole light light sour cream.
Is that right, Leroy? OK, got it.
Ben's going to need extra beans after all that effort.
Right. So I could do that.
That's too bad.
You know, I like what we're donating to the California Community Fund,
but I do wish that we could also just get a just get everybody to chip
in on a really good Taco Bell order for some local firefighters.
That would be fun. Yeah.
I might as well.
I'll repeat a joke that was from a text thread that we're on.
There's this app that we've been looking at,
you know, showing like are these fires spreading and what's in level one
and what's in level two, but it also shows food distribution centers
for first responders and people helping out places that are giving out food
for free. And I saw on the map like, oh, they're giving out food
at the the Hollywood Boulevard Hard Rock Cafe,
to which I thought, haven't these people struggled enough?
This is how we treat the best among us.
I mean, I guess no firefighters at CityWalk.
I'm banning them for we need to let's let's raise them up.
Well, I mean, there's no way to eat at CityWalk anymore.
There's no restaurants other than Toothsome.
That's right. It's all going.
Oh, that too. Yes.
Thanks for really letting it being respectful of our time off
as we cope with every single CityWalk establishment going away.
We're feeling it's a whole other episode is like, which we could do.
It's just like, what do we think's happening?
I really didn't want to do any more CityWalk content for a while.
But I feel like we got it.
I guess we got to do something we can give that we can, you know.
It's not going to be like a saga.
Stephen Kempner is living his life.
I don't know what's the thing.
This is just about podcast, the right.
It's still our right to talk about.
And I remember we're the only people who can make heads or tails of this.
Well, we'll see if we're called into duty as time goes on.
Anyway, I think a firefighter deserves a great big firehouse sub.
But just don't go don't go to the CityWalk one
because you're going to end up with plastic in there, which Jason called.
What? It's just a little oh, it's just a little nub and little nub.
Yeah, my God.
I love you can get away with anything
by just doing that little he's forgiving a place that put plastic in the sandwich.
I mean, they're twice.
I mean, they're twice since Jason got the little nub.
I like firehouse.
And I even I'm so I'm hungry right now worried about nubs with every bite.
You might have eaten nubs.
I do. You're worried about microplastics.
And then you're getting those.
Yeah, I know. I'm eating those.
I'm for sure eating those, depending on what the wrapper is made of.
Yeah, you're going to get mega plastics in those.
I made this joke already. I think I did.
Yeah. You know what?
We're all in a blur here. Right.
I do a quick check to make sure there's not a piece of plastic in there.
And then there's usually not.
I bet Jason would enjoy if you made a fire.
If you got him up in that on a second level firehouse subs,
make a sub as long as a fire pole.
Oh, yeah. Cover it in giant nubs just to like make it like stay solid for a while.
But then right before it's time to go, remove the giant nub
and and just let him slide down it and eat as he goes.
Oh, yeah, that'd be fun.
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh huh. So I'm going to draw that Jason was going to get executed.
I think we should arrange for that to be his final meal.
Execution by Hoagie.
Well, who could complain about that?
No. All right.
Look, fire in the hole.
This attraction, you're in an old minor town.
You're in the town of Marmaros.
And you are, you know, in the town's businesses,
harvesting guano, you know, bat shit.
Yeah. So you life's good.
You work in a bat shit mine.
But there's some no good nicks who make your paradise
a little less great than it could be. Yeah.
And they are called the bald knobbers.
The bald knobbers are a group of vigilantes.
And they are starting to burn down the town.
Now, I get into this.
I'm like, OK, so what are they?
They're weird vigilantes.
Yeah. The 1800s.
And they wear weird masks and hoods. Go ahead.
I'm nervous about what's going on with these.
And it's a real thing.
So I don't know. I'm like, I'm oh, yeah.
What are these bald knobbers?
Would you call these bald bald knobbers, you know, kind of a clan with their
they sort of together? Do they all form a clan?
Sure. Good question.
You look it up and I guess not.
I was a little lost in the literature.
Yeah. About the bald knobbers.
If anything, it seemed like they were sympathizers of the union.
Really? I think so.
OK. The enemies in this riot are on the union side.
Interesting. I guess I'd rather not ask any more questions about what's going on
here and just focus on that. It's fun animatronics.
OK, all right.
Anyway, but I try to dive in a little bit.
So you've got to watch out for the bald knobbers.
They're trying to turn.
They're trying to burn down the fine homes of all the best batshit harvesters.
This side of the Ozarks.
And that's real, too.
People were harvesting batshit.
Yeah. OK, I guess is used as fertilizer.
Like there's there is need for specifically batshit, though.
Yeah. Just a funny joke.
I guess so.
OK. I mean, I guess batshit crazy comes from somewhere.
Some somebody snuffed a bunch of guano.
Right. Guano would make give you some sort of madness.
And that's why that's why that phrase exists.
I don't know. I think you go up to that pinks hot dogs at City Walk.
I think those I think those wieners are made out of guano.
That's probably true.
I don't cut to you up there as soon as we're done recording.
You say firehouse subs in my mouth waters.
You say pinks hot dogs and it dries up.
I swear. OK. All right.
There are still there are still rules and there's the right.
Aren't so guano crazy in this world.
No, I get my my tummy rumbles for firehouse subs, but not pinks.
Thanks. Yeah. In general, so it's like a rough brand.
City food, though, there's no rumored closings.
If we should say at City Walk.
Well, yeah, I've got my theory.
I think that zone is safe.
I think the closer to the parking garage as you are, you're safe.
I think that I think but I think we're going to see an entire building
go and replaced by a new hotel or by some kind of talk.
Yeah, we have talk about speculation in this.
But it seems like there's the least funny episode you've ever heard.
We'll just we're going to get our maps out.
We're going to send you your maps.
We're going to. Yeah.
Speculation and four and a half hours. Yeah.
But it's no concrete facts of any kind.
No, nothing entirely guessing.
Just like the three differently universal accounts to post all the time
that post these things that in my mind have popped up in the last six months.
Yeah, I know there wasn't this.
There wasn't so much universal Twitter.
Yes, there's like three or four.
Universal High, Universal High with fires and five fires.
Five fires doing streams now.
I don't know anything about him other than I see some on streams.
He goes to Disneyland sometimes.
Yeah. But then there's another like universal account.
I forget the name of it that's posting like these are the rumored closings.
And it's like Margaritaville's on the list.
It's that whole section over there.
But then they're also building escapology,
which is not a universal owned escape room.
It's a different company.
Because I think that building is safe, too.
That's my theory. I think it's structure by structure.
Well, that's the only because it's connected to Toothsome.
Yeah, but it's too.
But Toothsome seems like as failing as a business could possibly be.
No one was. And what else is in that building?
It's just it's a Wetzel's right.
The Wetzel's is there. Mm hmm.
But then everything other than that and city food.
Yeah. Who knows? Mm hmm.
I guess Vivo is safe.
I don't know, though.
I think a lot of its neighbors are going away.
Right. Can't tell.
I don't know. It's another.
I'm just glad it's going.
I'm glad that the fires spared the universal hills
and that all these buildings and businesses can go out on their own terms.
We got to do this next week.
Maybe so. I got to get up there.
And we should probably just do with this episode.
Measure, spy, get up as high as we can.
Look down at construction sites, see if anyone dropped any permits.
Yes. Let's see what we can do.
I'm going to do. Yeah.
Reconnaissance.
Yeah, we'll try. Well, without without our cub reporter,
we will try to do our best.
Barrel ahead as best as we can. Yeah.
Anyway, so this this just becomes like,
all right, fires are breaking out in the city.
We're trying. I think we're trying to help.
I think firefighters are part of it, but mainly just like trying
to navigate all of the craziness as it starts breaking out.
And what you end up with is just it's just this like very
charming homespun ride that has a lot of great and memorable scenes
that seem like these are these clearly are the equivalent of like
the dynamite goat if you are a lifetime silver dollar city person. Right.
Like if you've been going here forever,
then you then you might you would just toss off casually a reference to
why, of course, Red Flanders and his missing pants.
Yeah, yeah.
There is a bald knobber trying to climb up into a window
and steal a guy's pants.
And his name is Red Flanders, not Ned Flanders, Red Flanders.
So you got that.
You got a collapsing bridge scene.
This is really cool and clever, especially for 72. Right.
That it's a situation sort of like it is really
a predecessor, I would say, to the Indiana Jones adventure
where you're heading for the boulder and then where do you go?
You go down under it into the darkness.
Similarly, the drop on the Jurassic Park ride,
Jurassic Park River adventure, whatever you want to call it.
The threat is looming. How do you escape?
You escape down below it. In this case,
you are you you approach a burning bridge
and you see it the whole length of it burning.
Then you come around and you come around a turn and realize,
oh, I'm going in there.
I've seen that's on fire. Now I'm in it.
You go in all the woods ablaze, then it all drops down on you
right as you hit an invisible drop in the dark.
This must have been so killer in 1972
when Imagineering has not necessarily gotten to this point on on a lot of attractions.
Yeah, it's interesting.
I wonder like it feels like 72.
It's like what else?
Disney didn't have anything that would like a blow my mind that much in that way.
Back then, I guess.
Well, you've got pirates and you've got Haunted Mansion,
but you don't have the thrills combined with it.
Yeah, I mean, it's the drop of the water drop on pirates in the dark.
Sure, sure. But the coordination.
Yeah, this was more intricate.
This feels like like an illusion that would belong on the Universal Studio tour.
This is like the coordination of it.
Looks like you're you're spinning in the, you know, infinite looping tunnel
or it looks like or, you know, or the track is shaking.
So you think earthquakes happening to you.
This this is like it's really it feels very universal ahead of Universal.
Yes. And I also thought that it's an interesting genre of ride,
of like natural disaster ride, like, oh, right.
Yeah, isn't also very universal, which is universal.
But then like, yeah, with Twister or Backdraft, it's tied to a movie as well.
But they are rides about awful stuff that happens in real life.
Yeah. And in these cases that paid tribute to local legend and things
that really happened.
And this is all referencing like stuff that happened in the Marvel
cave and the ball knobbers put people in the cave.
And so you can understand why these be so beloved that, you know,
because to get anything even remotely Disney-esque around there.
And then it's about like the stuff you grow up learning about.
It's it's it's cool.
I really like this. That's right.
What is the most like close to real life ride at Disneyland?
Is there anything is like knots in this ride real that is closer to like knots?
It's a mining. It's a it's logging industry rides.
It's like but Disney's everything is pretty elevated.
It's still fantastical.
And I'm trying to think, is there a good exam?
Big Thunder, I guess, but it's still like runaway railroad.
Like that's still like most people don't experience that.
That's kind of a fan.
Not it's not fantastical, but it's it's a pretty crazy scenario.
The canoes are canoes that are real canoes that you have to row
the way real people row real canoes.
Yeah. So it could be that you might say.
Is it maybe mission space at Epcot?
Like we're like, this is just this is how it is.
You go to space. Yeah, it's pretty dry.
You're in a real machine and you get real nauseous.
Right. This is like this is that's even closer to real
life than seeing a bunch of people being sad while they mine.
Yeah. Yeah. Like that's that's as close as it gets.
Well, the ultimate example might be the proto, the early DCA attraction,
Bountiful Valley Farm. Oh, right.
Where you just are on farming again.
You know what? A ride that my son today would love.
Yeah. Ride. It's a bit.
Let me be clear. It's not a ride.
It's tractors that you can briefly sit on. Right.
But this is so up his alley, more so than a lot of the things
you can actually do at Disneyland.
Do you think if Michael Eisner appeared in front of us
and we said Bountiful Valley Farm, would he know what we're talking about?
Hmm. Yeah, I do, because he I think that was a passion project.
He might not remember the name.
He might just go like, yeah, the farm, you know, the California.
Yeah. Yeah. He knows.
That's his baby. You remember your baby's name.
You remember Breck and you remember Bountiful Valley Farm.
Right.
Now, it gets a little confusing here because we get into things
that two attractions do.
Here's some history that I did not know is that Dollywood before it was Dollywood,
which is a switch over that happened around like 86, I want to say.
Before that, it was Silver Dollar City, Tennessee.
It was in the same family tree of theme parks.
And that is why they got a really similar attraction called Blazing Fury,
nearly identical.
And a lot of the same gags happen.
And even though those parks aren't related anymore, they share this.
They have joint custody over this type of ride.
And so and a lot of the same beats occur, including
you run into a train like Mr.
Toad, like you're heading down a path and then you get
smacked by a big bright light and honk and you're barreling into a train.
And once again, then you do a little dip after that.
I think I think you get you end up in a dynamite storage shack.
And so another good thing is that that's a great thing
always to happen in a fire-oriented ride.
Dynamites got to be stored somewhere.
Fireworks have to be stored somewhere.
You can end up in those places.
What else?
I think it may be only the Dollywood one has
is a woman who's trying to jump onto a trampoline,
but the firefighter says, wait, because he's got a bad back.
And the voices on this, by the way,
my buddy, Andy Maxwell, has been on this and he was telling me about it.
And he said his main memory was like, oh, those that is
the voices on that ride is like, that's fair.
There was a little boy.
It is definitely this is a musty, very musty attractions.
But I think that's got to add to that.
You've got like Boomhauer voice on an old radio, basically.
That's the audio system.
You know what? If I can hear it, I'm upset.
Yeah, you want to hear it like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't want one actual word poking through because it opens it up to everybody.
Then if you speak another language, it doesn't matter
if you don't understand what they're saying.
Yeah, yeah, I want it.
Yeah, I guess.
I feel like when I'm on the not rides, sometimes you can hear things clear.
It's almost like some of the speakers have been replaced and some haven't.
That's something I'm making up, probably.
But like you do want to hear like you want to feel like
you're hearing the ghost of the person or something.
You want to hear some ghostly version.
Sure. Hearing everything crystal clear would not be right.
Yeah. For those rides.
Yeah, because it adds to the it feels like traveling into the past.
Right. And like, I don't know, there's a weird charm to it's like drive in speakers.
You know, we're all right crackly, which I think they did a good job.
I think those the new animatronics, which are this point,
some of them are over 10 years old.
Yeah. When they've put new reinstalled animatronics into the Natsukaliko
attractions, they move, but they're still.
Yeah. I don't want a bunch of Navi Shaman a song, you know, flailing around.
I want I want I crave limited movement on old west attractions.
Yes. No, you don't want.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of a newer kind like Kylo or those
Beauty and the Beast ones from Japan.
No, thanks. Yeah. Yeah.
I would like a blink.
I would like, you know, let's think about that.
What do you actually what do you need out of the robot
when it comes to these old creaky like minor types?
Well, I'll tell you, as far as fire in the hole is concerned,
I don't need them to do anything.
Yeah, they can they can not move whatsoever.
They can be wax figures.
But if they're going to move, I'd say like a light arm.
Let's let's go like five degrees on the arm.
Let's go. Let's let's like if the arm is pointed at five o'clock,
let's get it to four. Right. No more. OK.
I would say like a slight lean forward.
That's what I want.
Well, that's a little scary, too, because you think I might lean all the way.
Yeah, but they're not going there.
They're going to lean like, oh, wait, it's going to be an inch difference.
You know, what else is this?
OK, that's fine. That's great.
I mean, because you know what?
The one of our fundamental favorites, the adventure.
Yeah, those cops, they don't move one bit.
Yeah. Yeah, those are truly very static.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
Well, what did we just find out from one of these universal accounts?
I didn't know this.
There's a there was a different E.T.
on his head in the universal out here.
Standy handstand, which you can see when Spielberg goes on the ride
with a Bradley and 60 minutes. Right. Yeah.
Did you know that that was different?
I mean, standing on the head felt familiar to me.
It definitely feels like in the, you know, in the world of artwork
I've seen or promotional photos, but I've never really tracked
the individual E.T.'s too much. Wow.
I know this all these good information coming from these different accounts.
Yeah. Yeah. There's you know what? Good work, everybody.
Good, recent big crop of new universal information.
You keep sending all these great like universal shows
that are barely documented. Never heard of these.
Yeah. There's a land before time live show.
This is something I want to I want to figure out.
There was something.
Oh, this is also something I wanted to propose to you was
there was some summer show that was there
attempted a phantasmic kind of thing called Spectra Blast.
Yes, we just I sent that to you. You sent spectrum.
OK, I found the audio of Spectra Blast, like what the show is comprised of.
I'm pretty interested in Spectra Blast.
We got to do Spectra Blast for sure.
But they all I asked one of these accounts, I said,
is there any more information on Womp Hoppers?
And that's all they could give me was that's out there, basically.
Wow. OK, all right.
Geez. So really not well documented.
You're the only person in this.
No one gives a fuck about Womp Hoppers.
Yeah. Yep.
What about the future?
What if there's what if there's what if they're bringing?
What if there's Womps to be hopped in the future?
Wow. Well, we deal with that.
What if there's Womp Hoppers?
What if Womp Hoppers is coming back?
That's why all the restaurants are closing.
Yeah, they're building the they're building a Womp Hoppers three times bigger.
I would love a wizard's back wizard's wizard's back.
Holy shit. They're not going to do anything fun, but we need it.
If anyone from Universal is listening, you know what the city's been through.
You know the morale right now.
You know that we need a five room
magic restaurant now more than ever.
I am so I would cry if they announced either of those being opened again.
It's very emotional. Yeah. Yeah.
Like, oh, my God.
And the and the heads of Comcast would also cry,
knowing the profits that would be funneling out the door.
What if I can I sneak my way to a meeting and propose
that they just change tooths into Womp Hoppers?
Because why not?
Doesn't matter. No one goes to this restaurant anyway.
That is so true.
It's a yeah. Look, it's dying.
And yeah, it is. Yes.
They can't get it to work.
Do you have to lose? Right.
Just change the sign. Yeah.
And it's still like a way.
It's still like, oh, he's Womp Hoppers back and he has a robot sidekick.
Yeah. Yeah. And then and then you just change all the like,
you know, it's I'm always at Knott's Berry Farm and I see the word a say.
Yeah. I was like, what's a say again?
Well, in this case, it doesn't matter.
You just call it a say salmon.
It's all the same. It's the same shit.
You ate a flounder, a flounder, a salmon Dean.
Wow. This is the best old West themed salmon I've ever had.
Yeah. Like caught by a bear.
Why a bar reached in himself and pulled that out with his mouth.
And we stole it from him.
He didn't get to eat his dinner, but you get it.
That's fine.
Who cares? Let me change it.
I'll draw a salmon from a crick.
I'll run this restaurant.
That would drop everything to run Womp Hoppers.
Wizards and Womp Hoppers.
I mean, there's no there's no way it's happening.
They're not going to make it through the opportunity to dream.
After a grim January, you deserve to be able to that's what I think.
To fantasy, to live in the realm of fantasy where anything's possible.
Did I do we get to anything?
I mean, we got to miss anything here.
There's plenty of stuff to dig in.
But like, you know, we've hit some of the big stuff.
Oh, well, I mean, the big thing to say, I've been talking.
OK, so Blazing Fury is there in Dollywood and has been there since 78.
But fire in the hole
ran from 72 and went down in 2023.
Silver Dollar City closed it.
Fire in the hole. No more. Yeah.
But replaced by a brand spanking new fire in the hole.
Brand new for 2024.
They respect their legacy, unlike Universal, that callously
rips out Womp Hopper after Womp Hopper.
They they just put in a new fire.
This is like it's the heart of the park, clearly.
This this story, this experience, this innovative type of ride
and these creepy, creepy dummies.
And I've watched the new one and they didn't go that much.
I think they like enhanced it to the point where now it's like safe,
but yeah, still creepy as hell.
That's what we want.
Thank you, Silver Dollar City.
This this in this delve of research and doing this episode
just served as an advertisement for myself to go to Silver Dollar City.
I really want to.
This is one of our sampler episodes.
Yeah, I would consider it like a sample.
You would get a Womp Hoppers, mozzarella sticks or or a planks
mozzarella planks, as Jason would call them.
Yes. You know what?
Real quick, I forgot I wanted to mention this.
There's another Santa's Village called.
There's a ride called Hot Shots Fire Brigade at Santa's Village.
They got more fires.
And it's it's you go in a circle on these fire engines
and then they raise up and down and then you shoot into these little holes.
And the kids are just standing like on crane buckets.
Yes, it's really interesting.
It's like you're in like a whatever.
You're fixing the electrical wires or something that's interesting.
Wow. It's an interesting.
I've never seen like a ride like that.
Wow. But we'll we'll, you know, we'll get to that.
You're fixing downed power poles. Right.
Which is amazing.
Yeah, which is another
that's another sort of slice of life ride.
You know, well, this is what when you're.
Yeah, you're you're asking what are like rides about real stuff
and real heroes because we needn't go,
you know, experience the tales of Finn and Ray to hear stories of heroes.
Of course, real life heroes all around us.
And they say of Los Angeles and and we appreciate it.
And these are a good excuse to talk about this silly stuff.
And boy, does it plant a flag.
Oh, I want to get to these places.
Wait, you know what?
Let me do a little taste of just really quick.
The all right.
You know, I have to admit, they kind of you might be OK with this.
There is a fire in the whole theme song.
And they did a new one, which is kind of like more current country tone.
And that's less up my alley.
But I do I do prefer the original.
It's the same song.
They just did it with kind of more current production.
But here's the old fire in the whole song.
Oh, that was something I realized that with this Chipper song,
everybody's heart is filled with fear.
That's what I was going in my head last week.
But you tried to make it a little hoedown for yourself to try to keep morale high.
Yes. Well, your belongings in the car going for a drive real far.
That's all we can do is to try to turn our fears into a into a fiddle jam.
Yeah. But anyways, this is great.
Would would love to go.
And I guess with that, you survived finally.
The first podcast, the main feed of twenty twenty five.
Yeah. For three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcasts throughout the second gate or get one more bonus episode
on our VIP to your club three.
But once again, I will make the primary plug of this episode,
the California Community Foundation pledge dot to slash PTR.
Link in the show notes.
Let's help out this great city, this great state.
And, you know, we'll make that the main the main cause here
as opposed to the usual main cause, which is us.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.