Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate where we don't acknowledge any musical genre
as legitimate until it's been performed by a duck.
I'm Scott Gardner, over there is Mike Carlson.
Hi, I'm here.
And yes, I would say even multiple ducks, multiple different ducks.
I will technically take one, but it really, because we are dealing with a genre that has
been handled by multiple ducks.
Three, are you thinking of three different ducks?
You have to three?
Three?
Disco ducks?
Three disco ducks.
Okay.
Geez, well we're going to have to do this.
We'll have to get into it because I remembered something that was just put on my desk two
weeks ago.
In relation to ducks and disco.
Now if I'm correct in the timeline, two weeks ago was before we were even talking about
doing this.
Correct.
So unrelatedly, a disco duck came across your disco duck desk.
A new disco duck was presented to me two weeks ago, two or three weeks ago.
Maybe this is pre, maybe three weeks ago because of fire, like fire time.
Taking off my glasses like Walter Cronkite.
Many albums.
But whoa.
Multiple albums from 30 or 40 years ago.
I would say, I think more than one song would really throw me for a loop.
You're telling me there's a disco duck with multiple albums?
Yeah, I mean, now we've said it too many.
Well, it could be the closer.
Is it the closer?
If it's the closer, it's the closer.
I don't know if it's a closer because I don't know that the music is very good.
Well, I don't know if the music or the main thing is very good either.
That's what we're going to assess today.
Well, we will assess it, but it might be better than what I'm talking about.
But the character is great.
Okay.
I'm a big fan of the character.
Well, should we address it?
Should we do this in order?
How do you want to do it?
First of all, while we're really going in order,
cub reporter Jason Sheridan is out on assignment.
But that has left us to do a little bit of musical cleanup work.
And I think this is a, you know, I'll explain a little bit about what this is
and what we're doing.
It's why it's Mickey Mouse Disco today.
And this occurred to me because I finally made it
to Disneyland for the first time in a while.
I'm in the queue for Mickey and Minnie's Runaway Railway.
A wonderful queue.
There was ever unskippable queue out there.
And thankfully now that it's reasonable.
Now, that's a pretty, I was also very much, she'll be proud.
I was very much like app checking a glue to that.
And there's a world of difference on that ride, especially.
I was like, sometimes I'm seeing it 45.
Sometimes I'm seeing it 20.
I see it 20.
I make a mad dash.
20.
That's really closer to like 12 minutes or something.
And you're right.
They're all over, you know, we've talked about that lately,
but I haven't been in the parks much.
And I was really feeling that inflation throughout.
That was really on my side all day, knowing like that's not going to be that.
And it was not, yeah, now that I love the moment, by the way,
of any ride that starts in this like big e-ticket, tough to get on,
virtual queue, stress hassle.
When it becomes just part of the fabric of the park and you can just go
and it's not a big deal and not a stress.
And the queue is like kind of what it's meant to be for the level of ride.
It's, oh, it's just the best when it's like actually been, you know,
absolved into the park experience.
I guess absolved.
No, I think absolved is not right.
Absorbed, I guess.
Absorbed is right.
Yes, I was going to say dissolved, but that's not right.
The ride's there.
It wasn't absolved.
Quite the opposite.
Some sort of layer, like new layer has been dissolved and then it is.
My layer of stress has been dissolved.
And I feel absolved of the stress that it's been in my head about going on the right.
I agree.
I think also that's probably when you really assess how good it is as well.
You really get a clear picture now that the hype is gone.
What is your desire to get on it?
Then you start adding up because every ride, there's a different calculation you make for
wait times.
Yeah.
Obviously, what's worth it?
What's worth that amount of time?
Yeah.
You really have to like pair it correctly.
Will I do that with a 45?
Yes, worth it to me.
Will I do that for a two hour?
I don't know.
Yeah.
And Mickey Mini holds up.
Mickey Mini's Runaway Railway holds up.
I know it's kind of controversial, but I think it holds up.
With who?
I don't know.
There's some people that seem like cranky about it.
Well, there's people that are cranky about it.
It's true, but I mean, it's not some widely hated rider or whatever, but I feel it holds up.
This is it.
Have I said this thought that's been on my mind for a while on the show out loud,
which is that sometimes we get pinned with the phrase, cynical, and understandably,
because we'll be cranky about various things.
And we aren't just gung-ho.
Everything that the parks do is perfect.
But I'm really like, if you think that we podcast the ride or cynical,
you have not watched enough Disney YouTubers.
Oh, yeah.
My God.
Some of these people where you'll see a thumbnail that's like,
the destruction of Epcot as we know it.
And it's a video about guardians of the galaxy of an incredible ride, an immaculate ride.
I'm like, I think we are not that degree of unreasonable.
No, I don't think so.
It's dark out there.
And I've said this before, the change from when we started doing this to now,
as far as the different vloggers and the different YouTube content,
it feels like it's exploded.
And now it has all the different bad avenues that every other topic that gets covered like this has.
Yes, you're right.
All the different political lanes, all the way up through, of course,
extremely hateful borderline hate group.
And then it also never fails to surprise me.
There's an account I follow that is so aggressively anti-Tiana.
And I'm like, oh, God, this account or whatever.
But then the account literally is not political.
It started posting mean things about Republicans.
And I'm like, this is wild.
Because most of the people that are still upset about it
seem to have a very specific political leaning.
Not this account.
The only politics this one account has is that they want Splash Mountain back.
And I'm like, whoa, that's because every other thing I see,
I go, well, this obviously correlates to their political leanings and blah, blah, blah.
No, not this one account that I've had pegged wrong.
No politics, no worldview other than I want to go on Splash Mountain.
And you ask them, and they're not even aware of Song of the South.
Right, maybe not.
I like the bees.
Maybe not.
And this happened a couple of weeks ago, too, where I was just like,
wow, you are not political at all.
You just want Splash Mountain back.
It takes all kinds to make theme park media.
I think the really the way what you were just saying that it
like the explosion in theme park media since we started,
it's really it's especially evident in that
that some of the earliest and strongest freakouts by any of us
during the course of the show were Jason in response to us saying,
what if we recorded audio of ourselves in the theme parks?
Just like the hugest spike of and now like you don't walk through
the park without somebody recording.
Right on a selfie stick or especially in Florida.
But yes, in Disneyland, you see it all the time.
And yeah, Universal, I guess, a little less.
But and I guess City Walk, even less, even less potentially,
which is what we were talking about.
But I am.
Yeah, I am grateful for that.
That climate, because it did result in counterpoint.
You were wrong.
It also resulted in the one where he out of no
but because I said we should record at the top of the City
Walk parking garage within two exchanges, he was yelling,
you don't even go on the rides.
You just drink the wine one.
I will remember on my own.
Yeah, that is him saying you just drink the wine.
You don't even.
Yeah, I remember.
I shouldn't do.
He's not here to defend.
No, I know.
Well, I don't think you would defend that.
I mean, or you would defend it.
I know he would.
We know exactly how he would defend it,
which is he would say something like, I'm just a little guy.
That's right.
That's the smoke bomb he uses to walk out of anything.
He would do that thing where he digs like the top part of his toe
into the ground and like shakes it around and like kind of looks coy.
Gee, did I was I would pull out his big lolly, take a couple licks.
Yeah, take pull his pockets out to show he has no money and just a moth comes out.
You want it.
I'm just a little urchin.
And it would work.
And it went.
Our hearts would be melted.
That's right.
OK, well, this is a good sign.
We got caught in a tangent in the first, the first line of my notes.
Team Park related?
Yes.
Yeah, you should be happy because the rest of it won't be.
The rest is going to be about an album from almost 50 years ago.
So I was in the very excellent room, very excellent queue,
and I turned a corner into what is an especially great room or part of the queue,
which I would call the retro room or the retro zone.
Yeah.
Where things get a little it's like 70s, 80s, both.
It's a little bit like disco, dance floor, walkman.
It's a bunch of stuff kind of all mashed together.
And up on the wall, there's two album covers, vinyl album covers.
One is Mouser Size, which I was also proposing that we do and we will do soon.
But I was realizing there's OK, there's the album of Mouser Size,
but there's also the television show.
So where that is going to take ample time to figure out.
But also next to that, Mickey Mouse Disco.
And this is part of this lineage of Walt Disney Records attempts at like pop crossover,
which eventually leads to this album Splash Dance from the early 80s,
which we did an episode about and which we're very fond of.
What I would consider the crown jewel of that stretch of time of Walt Disney Records,
and this, you know, Halyx is in there, too.
It's some of the same people involved in putting Halyx together,
but they never released an official album.
So if you're dealing with these albums, Splash Dance, my favorite, Mickey Mouse Disco.
I was aware that it happened, that they did this, never listened to it,
never actually gotten into the music.
No, I hadn't.
So that's what I figured we could kind of do here together.
I think it's an interesting reference point.
A great album cover.
I feel like that's a lot of the strength of it is just like it kind of paints a picture
and it is just a it is a fun picture, regard even if you haven't heard the music,
you know, kind of swirly, very ELO, kind of like squiggle font neon for Mickey Mouse,
big blocky chrome disco.
And then there's Mickey and Minnie, both Mickey's in a sparkly vest, big puffy sleeves.
They're in color coordinated like orange costume.
She's got a big flower in her hair and they're dancing and they're bumping seats.
They are bumping seats, yeah.
Doing a little seat bump and having a good old time.
These dresses flying up, you know.
Oh, to be on the other side of this camera angle, huh?
Ooh, hey, just us boys, we can talk show.
Oh, yeah, no, Jason's not here.
Because he would be hornier, I'm saying it would be out of control if he were here.
Yeah, yeah, well, he's so much more in touch with sexuality than we are.
Yeah.
I would just make a little comment like I just did and then that would be it.
But Jason, who knows?
It would just do boil over into a raging sexual trough.
Right, exactly.
Trough.
We'd have to jump into, I was trying to say froth.
We'd have to jump into his big sexual trough altogether if he was here.
But no, I will stop the dialogue here about what I've just said.
But it is a fun, they're having a fun time on the dance floor.
And they're really like, I don't know if this is the coolest.
No, Mickey, I guess Mickey's looks a little cooler, but they do look like cool.
They look cool to me.
Maybe.
I don't know if I grew that because I think they look like they're contestants on Dancing
with the Stars, which I wouldn't call cool.
I guess that's true.
It's fun, maybe.
It's fun.
All right, fine.
When do I find Mickey cooler?
I mean, it really depends.
I mean, if you're a more 70s oriented person, then sure.
I mean, obviously Mickey was cool as balls when he looked all hip hopped out.
That rap album that we talked about a while.
Well, and on the cover of A Whole New Sound, the recent Walt Disney pop punk album.
Which we really, we owe.
Which we do owe that at a certain point.
Club three loser, but I think we could circle back to it.
And that's an episode I could do.
We could hit stop on this.
I could do it right now.
I've listened to the whole thing three times.
You know it well enough.
I know it well enough to do it off the top of my head, what I like, what I don't like.
But yes.
How much do you like?
Well, I don't want to save it.
I like percentage of like is an interesting word when it comes to this.
I like 25 ish 30 ish percent.
It's pretty good.
I mean, that's really all we like.
I'd say on splash dance.
True.
Yeah.
I think that's a huge percentage for a Disney album to like
sincerely like that percentage of a quarter of it.
Yeah.
But yeah, I'll save my further thoughts for that episode.
I don't think they look especially cool.
He's just in a hoodie.
Yeah.
He just looks sleepy.
He's actually trying to play it cool.
He's trying to not be so.
Right.
Not effortful.
Yeah.
There's effort going on in disco.
Again, I'm familiar with this image so much more than I am with the music itself.
And I like the image when it appears.
I think I thought I had the vinyl of this.
I don't.
I do have mouser size, which we'll cover when we get there.
But yeah, I was just curious how on the money this is, how accurate of an entry
in the field of disco music it is.
Because we've talked a lot about, okay, whenever Disney and the big characters,
the big six or whatever entering into a musical field, whether in the parks
or on an album, there's always the question of like, how of the moment is this?
Yes.
And in this case, this did come out in the 70s.
So you're like, all right, yeah, disco in the 70s.
Sure.
They made it technically right under the wire.
It doesn't seem so crazy.
But what I didn't realize is that this album was released in July 1979.
July 1979 is also when that event was held, the Disco Demolition Derby or whatever it was
at Comiskey Park, is that correct?
This is a big Chicago event.
Steve Dahl is the notorious DJ who held this big event where he exploded
lots of disco records and wore a big helmet and was this kind of like military guy.
And disco sucks and this is the end of disco.
So this album did come out in the same month as this very aggressive event,
which is kind of viewed as having worked and been a big public sign
that culturally we are done with disco.
So that doesn't feel good.
And any write-up that you find of this album does call it a late period disco entry.
I saw that a couple times, late period.
So first of all, we've said this before, disco is awesome, I think.
Disco rules, in my opinion.
See, I'm in a weird, I'm all over the map on this.
No, there's bad disco, but just the best disco is great.
Well, I entered into this, I went through this thought exercise.
I went, do I like disco?
It's like, I think that I don't.
Then I'm going through a checklist.
Bee Gees, incredible.
Love the Bee Gees.
ABBA, like ABBA.
I like Donna Summer and especially like the Marauder stuff.
I'm like, well, aren't all those the primaries?
I guess I do like disco.
But all of that stuff feels like it all transcends the genre,
that it's just like really great dance music.
Not even in all cases is it really dance music.
I think what I don't like is kind of like cash in shit is like,
well, there's a lot of it.
I think that's where we're getting.
Yeah, but I saw Sheik listed as dance music,
and I know some of that stuff is overplayed,
but it is great.
There's really great stuff in there.
See, I don't know, because I do listen to a ton of like 70s funk soul R&B.
I might move that over to like is cool.
I don't think cool in the gang is disco.
I think that's closer to the funk area.
Love Hangover by Diana Ross, which is awesome.
What is that?
I don't know if I know that song.
I guess we're just going to be playing.
OK.
Let's see.
It's kind of like it's a longer song, but like it's I don't know.
There's so many different weird like genres and sub genres.
I think when it comes to disco and dance music from the 70s and early 80s.
I certainly like lots of dance music from then.
This is very disco.
Yeah.
Oh, this.
OK.
Yeah.
It starts slow and then it goes.
Silly Love Songs is kind of a disco song.
Sort of.
Not maybe the first part of it, but the baseline is pure disco.
Well, look, I have my own Silly Love Songs opinion, which is that I prefer the second
version, which is in the movie, Give My Regards to Broad Street, even though it is
paired with a very bizarre music video with like a break dancer and everybody's in bizarre
white paint like they look like they look like Starlight Express.
Yes, honestly.
But it's got the Toto dudes on it.
So I like that's my Silly Love Songs.
I hear you.
It's very cheesy in its own way.
The duck I was talking about might have a version of Silly Love Songs on one of the albums.
Get into the duck before this album.
Well, maybe we do it at we do.
Let's do it when we get to our duck.
Yeah, that's right.
That's the thing.
So there's tons of like stuff you I think you at least disco adjacent that it rules.
Yes.
But I think here's what I was thinking about.
Disco also made me think about the Bee Gees documentary, which I enjoyed very much directed
by Frank Marshall.
That's right.
I am a fan of Frank Marshall's Bee Gees.
How do you mend a broken heart?
I think the name, which I did like Beach Boys documentary horseshit garbage from the worst
things I've ever seen.
Bee Gees documentary.
Excellent.
And they weave this narrative in the documentary, which I thought was very compelling, that
involves that disco demolition thing.
And that when things get to a fever pitch of disco sucks, we hate disco, the movie's
theory is that the Bee Gees, which are great, timeless, obviously, like, you know, revisionist,
like we, you know, like everybody loves Bee Gees now.
Still, they didn't die with disco.
Uh, but commercially, then the Bee Gees paid the price for a bunch of cheap cash in bullshit.
And in the documentary, they flash through a bunch of things like that.
A disco Christmas, a disco duck, the Rick D.
That's there's there's one of the ducks.
They really pin it on disco duck, which I love because that is a that's a pile of shit.
I mean, it's a novelty song, I guess.
I guess it's supposed to be silly.
But I think there is like we aren't even dealing in the same like realm of music when you compare
like actual staying alive to disco duck.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
And well, and and the village people also, I think, fall in the category of it feels
a little gimmicky.
Yes.
Around the same time.
Are we allowed to say that on microphones right now in America?
That's a whole thing.
That's the official nationwide anthem.
It replaced the Star Spangled Banner and the national anthem.
That was right after it was an addendum to the Gulf of America.
Right.
Yes.
Initiative.
But that is a sillier.
YMC is a sillier song.
Now, I'll say this, I listened to Macho Man for the first time in 30 years or something
on the way over here because I hadn't I didn't remember how it went.
I'm like, Macho Man is kind of good.
Maybe not the chorus.
Probably is.
But it's kind of good.
I mean, any of these slaps is the kid to say.
Because I just all I remember is the chorus.
That's very nice.
But I would not go I would not start going around saying, hey, Macho Man slaps.
Depends who you're with.
Again, if you've got if you're trying to seem hip and youthful, just word to the wise.
Yes.
So I also think and they talk about that and I forget if it was the Bee Gees documentary
or not, but then it's also like there's a lot of like masculine guys in the 70s who
were like, what is this disco stuff?
Is it is it for wimps?
Like there's all that element to it for.
And then we say five words that we shouldn't say.
Right.
Exactly.
That I think was completely the feeling.
Yeah.
And that's also yeah, the documentary is definitely like, yeah, there was kind of a
homophobia racism to the yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I guess it was a fever pitch, probably just of the genre, which happens to everything.
I mean, there's always reactions to things that explode.
Yeah.
And then you have to like in time sift through the sand and revisit and go, no, this thing,
like the thing that took the fall like the Bee Gees did is so great and remains so great.
And think about like how deep is your love?
It's like that's not even.
No.
Disco.
So yeah, we're just in another like, oh, it's just so like lush and moving and incredible.
So even like lump that in forcibly with just like, you know, the worst of Casey and the
Sunshine Band.
Although even them, I was about to like hate on Casey and the Sunshine Band.
And then I'm like, oh, wait, boogie shoes.
Shoes is kind of good.
Yeah.
There's a good, I don't know.
Yeah, it's.
Well, and then like even like Rolling Stones Miss You, which I love.
I love the like eight minute version of that song.
Yeah.
That's disco baseline.
Like that's so influenced by disco.
Like even like bigger artists from decade earlier were like, well, maybe we try a disco.
This is another weird thing about me that I, when, you know, in this era, a lot of bands
reached what critics might call a disco nadir where like a bunch of groups tried to like
get in on the trend.
And at the time they might've said like, oh, this is the worst song they've ever done.
I like most bands disco nadir.
I like Miss You.
If you consider the Chicago song Street Player disco nadir, I really like Street Player.
The Beach Boys have a pretty indefensible disco song called Here Comes the Night.
And the main reason it's indefensible is because it's 11 minutes long.
Oh, God.
However, one time I put it on in front of Erin, who actively dislikes the Beach Boys.
And it's the only time I've ever put on a Beach Boys song.
And she was like, oh, what's this?
I like tricked them because it's such a different sound.
I like tricked them into.
There's another disco nadir I'm not coming up with.
There's an Elton John one, but I don't remember it.
I don't know that song very well.
There is.
I know exactly what you're talking about.
I found this like a year ago and I was like, what is this?
I did like it and I can't think of the name of it.
Yeah.
Unless there's a couple of them, but I found one.
I want to say it was on an EP or something, but maybe I'm misremembering.
I guess maybe we're finding as we talk, it's a better genre than not.
And I think, yeah, got like a, I don't know, an unfair tag is being like cheesy.
And you know what I really hate is just like Halloween costume.
I don't like seeing like a, you know, like a big puffy wig and a big open shirt.
Yeah, that's kind of annoying.
Yeah, no, always.
But if you can separate it and go into what it really was.
Now to tie it back to Mickey Mouse Disco, that is the thesis I wanted to bring to the table.
Is Mickey Mouse Disco worthy of inclusion in the Bee Gees documentary,
flip through the bad disco shit, or is it done kind of affectionately enough?
And is some of it catchy enough to actually be upgraded a little bit from,
you know, the disco quickie cutout bin territory?
And I'm not sure.
I think I don't even know my opinion exactly.
I think we're gonna have to listen to these tracks together to figure it out.
Okay, yeah.
I think I have an answer, but I'm not sure.
I guess I think I have an answer, but yeah.
I'm not totally sure.
Now, one thing that confuses it a little is like,
it's not like they put this out and everybody made fun of them and yelled at it.
This album peaked at number 35 on Billboard's Pop Albums chart.
It went double platinum.
So this was a success.
And in fact, emboldened Walt Disney Records to do more stuff of this nature,
things that we like like Splash Dance.
And they went into it with the goal of highlighting the characters in a new way,
in an unexpected way, in an updated way.
Because I think in this weird, listless, post-Walt, pre-Eisner Disney era,
not a lot was happening with the characters.
You could meet them in the parks, but I don't think a lot of shorts are happening.
It's not like they really had TV figured out yet because there's no cable yet.
There's no Disney channel yet.
So like new stuff with the characters, almost not at all.
I believe, if I have my history correct, that Mickey's Christmas Carol was like a real,
like a homecoming feeling, like a sigh of relief of like,
wow, this is like this magical piece that uses all the classic characters
in a really affectionate way.
I don't think there'd been like a new thing with Mickey Mouse really in years,
or a lot of those characters.
Like they were dusting them off for the first time in a long time.
And that was a bad time for animation too, because like Robin Hood was good,
and then almost nothing else worked for a long time.
So this is these Walt Disney Records people going like,
let's bring the characters back from the dead.
Make them boogie.
Well, you may as well.
They weren't doing anything else.
Let them boogie.
They got nothing but time to boogie.
Let them hit the dance floor.
The people who put this together, by the way, who come up in the Halyx story,
Jim Magan, who I think is later part of Disney afternoon shows as well.
He's like on every Disney afternoon show when I looked him up.
Yeah, like a writer also?
Like a music person, but then also, yeah, this is clearly a big, big figure.
That's a guy I was like, oh, maybe we should try to get him on the show.
That would be a great thing to try.
Yes, maybe not constantly getting hounded by requests.
Another person involved in this, there's a book about Walt Disney Records
that goes into some of this history.
But a guy named Gary Kreisel was putting all this together.
And I learned that he is the uncle of the great comedy director Jonathan Kreisel
behind Portlandia and Baskin's and Kroll Show and Tim and Eric and a lot of the best stuff
for the last 20 years.
So, yeah, his uncle was responsible for a lot of the best stuff of Disney's musical
history and part of the Halyx story as well.
So, yeah, so there was their goal to revitalize the characters in some way.
And being that that was the goal, I don't think they really knew a lot about disco.
And this guy, Jim Magan, Magan?
Yeah, I don't know.
I've never heard of that one.
But Jim, let's say, which is spelled J-Y-M-M.
It's like a Star Wars character.
Jim Magan, yes.
Especially you put like a second A or like five G's in that Magan and then we're good.
Anyway, Jim was kind of like really quickly trying to digest a lot of disco the night before
and bringing in things like, OK, so they do this like, boo, boo, boo.
So we should do that, boo, boo, boo.
So I think that's something to judge when we listen to these songs.
Is it clearly somebody trying to figure out what disco was the night before?
Cramming for a test, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Or does it feel mildly lived in, mildly authentic?
Yeah, I didn't realize.
I looked at it right before what the pew pew sound is.
It's an electronic like tom.
It's like a drum.
Oh, so is that played off like a little pad?
Yeah, played on a pad.
I didn't even realize that until 10 minutes ago, 20 minutes ago, or 40 minutes ago.
I didn't realize how long we've been recording.
Oh, 190 minutes ago.
I was like, oh, we didn't even play the album yet.
How long was that disco?
How long did I talk about Street Player?
Well, anyway, I mean, I guess why not just start talking about the album itself?
We talked about the cover.
There's other bits of history that we could talk about, but I think we can learn by listening.
So when Mickey Mouse set out to do disco,
what was it like?
Was it good?
Only we can answer that.
Well, I guess let's listen to the first track, which is the first track on Mickey Mouse Disco
is Disco Mickey Mouse.
Disco Mickey Mouse.
Move some words around.
Right away.
Which I love that.
I really do.
That weird disco noise.
Yeah, it's a good sound.
Oh, he's got the motion.
I don't know.
What do we think?
I'm kind of like, do I have any response at all?
It's kind of neutral about it.
Yeah.
Which is maybe not probably not what you want to happen.
It's not the laziest thing in the world, I'll say.
I feel the album is there's effort.
I've heard lazier cash-ins for Disney and other different, like, whatever,
like, cynical corporate attempts.
It really doesn't get worse than that rap one.
Right.
Yeah, well, that's true.
Yes.
So this is not my favorite song on the L, I will say that, but it is like-
It's just setting the page, I guess.
They don't want to get two.
They don't want to get up here, the height of the album.
There's a phrase they used in the Conan writers room, the Earl of Early.
That's like kind of one that's like a good starter, conveys the premise,
but it's not that good because the good, that good one you got to close with.
Right.
Earl of Early.
I think that's the one where they say he has Clark Gable ears.
Yeah, I almost was going to let you keep playing it just to get to Clark Gable ears.
Yeah.
Which I like.
And then they also call him Macho in this song.
They call him Macho.
We might say that these people listened to like four disco songs
and then just kind of rearranged all the words they heard.
But I don't know, I think it is a, I think it works as a,
it sounds like a disco song.
It does.
It sounds like it is effort.
I don't know that anything is so unique in the arrangement as far as a disco.
Again, it's not going to, I mean, spoiler alert,
it's not going to hit splash dance levels for me.
I don't believe so.
Well, another thing lacking is that no voice either.
And that's not the case with the whole album, but yes, there's no Mickey voice.
Some characters do appear, but you got to knock at points right away
that Mickey Mouse disco does not have Mickey Mouse on it.
Yes.
So I think this one is like, you give it if it's, to me it's like two stars,
two and a half stars out of five.
It works.
I don't know that it's in my rotation like some other songs from A Whole New Sound.
Let's say there's songs from all new sound in your rotation.
I think on my top songs, there might've been like one that had been like number 50 or something.
Here you are harassing Jason.
Well, maybe I was trying to invite it.
No one would go, well, what are your songs?
Let's talk to you.
No one's picking up the hint when I'm trying to get Jason's songs out there.
The idea where we supposed to turn it on you and go.
Well, not anymore.
Now we're into February.
So what's the time has passed?
I don't want to just do the whole new.
We can't, we'll do it on that episode.
Oh God, I'm dying to know something made it to the top 50.
I think it did.
I'd have to double check.
Minor, there would have been, mine would have been too confusing to get into because look,
my son really does like the Beach Boys much to my wife's chagrin.
So like 10 of the songs, just all it is.
I think my top song was Surfing USA and it wasn't because of me.
And I did, I have, I swear I have not forced the Beach Boys on him.
I did not tie him to his bed, play it definitely loud all night until he stopped screaming and
woke up and said, Brian Wilson was genius daddy.
I mean, I believe what you're saying, but that it was inevitable.
And in the same way that I would say, I did not force my daughter to like Ninja Turtles.
I didn't tell her to chase me around pretending she's crying, but it was inevitable.
Yeah.
I think so.
So, but she did, that's, she decided she liked Krang.
She gives Krang a little hug sometimes when she sees a figure or a little plush Krang.
It's just nice when the interests.
Yes, it is nice.
Yes.
I mean, there'll be a rejection at some point, a horrible rejection of everything,
but maybe there won't, maybe there won't be, I don't know.
But I'm just glad that you're aware of that possibility because that's been my fear with
you for a long time is that you, when the 12 year old, I don't like anything you like hits.
Yeah.
That you're going to be in a lot of trouble.
And then when you're, when your daughter doesn't like third eye blind anymore
and all the great music that you've convinced her is cool.
Well, I don't even want to think about that.
That actually isn't something I thought.
Third eye, that's going to turn you into a jumper.
Semi-jumper life is number three on my top 50 you listen to in 2024.
So blue, blue.
I don't know if that's a joke.
I don't think it is.
But my top 50 has a lot of children's songs.
Mickey's more on the way.
Railway song is in there.
Oh, that's nice.
Nothing can stop us now.
I was about to say like, maybe you don't have Mickey Mouse sing disco,
but then like Mickey's very nice in that they haven't figured out how to make Mickey sing yet.
Yeah.
They also, I think there was a lot that they were trying to figure out about Donald,
which we'll get to in the Donald song.
Yeah.
But I guess is welcome to Rio.
That's maybe the low point of the album to me.
Yeah.
It's the most uninteresting.
Well, that's not a good one to put in number two then.
Look, we don't have to do it.
I would say I almost want to just keep moving to the greatest band
because the greatest band has something to it.
I agree.
Yeah.
There's some melody here.
Here's the great, this song's called The Greatest Band.
Now, this is when you start almost like other genres are getting in here.
This sounds like Philadelphia Freedom or something.
This is, I was going to say it's like, what's the, Don't Go Breaking My Heart.
Or Don't Go Breaking My Heart.
Yeah.
It gets more disco-y after this part.
I think I'm going to change the lyrics a little here, but I like this.
Yeah.
I mean, I like these chord changes too.
Like that one.
Yeah.
That's very theme park too.
Like that's a very like 70s-80s.
This could have been in a great review on the Carnation stage.
Yeah.
This is, when I was listening to that, I was like, okay.
Those first two songs, okay.
And it's also unclear what the song's about until the very end.
Or like who's in the greatest fans.
Yes.
No Disney or characters are mentioned, which is to its benefit.
That's why I think you could put this on at a party and it wouldn't bother people for a while.
Yeah.
But I think if you were to, and I should have, I guess I could have done this,
but like if you break down the chord changes on this, I'd go, this is like auto.
It's interesting to my ear the way it changes.
And then I do enjoy like the reveal at the end.
It doesn't make, I guess it makes sense, but.
You want to go to the reveal?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh-uh.
Oh, listeners are racking their brains.
Who is in the greatest band?
Wait, did I go too far?
The greatest band.
So they reveal now.
Goofy.
Goofy?
What?
I thought Bootsy Collins would be in it.
Goofy's.
So they're all playing instruments.
Donald's playing the guitar.
And Minnie's playing the shaker or a tambourine.
Horace Horsecollar is playing the whoopee push.
Donald Trump.
Bear Bell's playing a horn instrument or a.
Wow, what a reveal.
That's the big reveal.
Glad we built it up.
Wow.
Get ready.
People are pulling their cars over to the side of the road.
Oh my God.
Well, this podcast has done a lot of big buildups and then wait till you see who it is.
And Mickey Mouse is dancing.
Yeah, Mickey Mouse is dancing at the end of a Star Wars show.
This is.
Unbelievable.
You don't see that coming.
We're gonna do a poll on that one.
We're gonna see who's.
I mean, I have a feeling people are never on my.
That one.
Well, sometimes.
People are never on my side except for the club three poll.
Well, that's true.
Even if they don't know it.
So yeah, so I wish there was more of that early on,
but I do think musically that's enough for me to be like, oh, I like this.
This is good.
Yeah.
So there that's.
That gave me hope for like music being acceptable.
Yes.
On the record.
But then it puts them in a tough spot because it now what that is set is that
less characters probably equals better song.
You know, but you want if the point of this was to keep the characters alive,
you're going to have to start hearing them at some point.
Right.
I guess we aren't quite there yet because they had they got to close that side one on a high note.
That's zippity doo dah.
Is there anything interesting about this?
I don't know.
It's just like it's it's like it's what you think it is.
I would I would argue that the other instrumental
of a popular Disney song is better than this.
Like like like there you go.
You got sorry.
If you like, okay.
This almost just feels like they could just play this in the park.
Yeah, it doesn't feel very remarkable.
You just wouldn't notice it.
Yes.
Now I hate to infect this episode with more a whole new sound,
but that is sometimes like the eye to eye cover on a whole new sound.
You go, well, this just sounds like the real version.
Okay.
So why do we do it?
It does it though.
Would I like it?
No, I'm not saying you would like it,
but I'm saying they didn't do enough to it to warrant it being on this album.
Does it?
I don't remember.
Okay.
No one I know.
None of my guys.
No offense to whoever does it.
And who would you call your guys?
I do not have that.
No one on that album.
Are you sure somebody made it to the top 50?
There's got to be some guys in there somewhere.
Well, it's a it might be the new found glory part of your world.
Not one of my band that I listen to a lot,
but a band that understood the assignment.
Okay.
Let's just say that.
All right.
Which I don't think you care for that genre at all in general.
No.
So, but I would say of all the stuff, they understood the assignment.
Yeah.
And you get all your like pop punk trappings.
All of the.
I will say, I think if you grew up with that kind of thing,
I got no hate for, you know, if they, if that,
if you're like nostalgic for it and that was your like coming of age music,
then by all means.
Like annoying, annoying voice, like.
If what, if what takes you back to the tender days of 17,
is somebody going, then sure.
Right.
And I don't want to step on it, but it is what it is.
Look at this stuff.
Isn't it neat?
Like that's what it sounds like to me.
Yes.
Yeah, that's what it sounds like.
What did you say?
But again, digressing left and right here.
I'm sorry.
I guess we're, what this is teaching is that we're really just dying to make it.
It's a whole new sound.
Something tells me I'm going to have a stronger emotional response.
I think that's right.
To the tracks on a whole new sound.
Let's go to macho duck.
I'm going to change that nice thing I said.
If you grew up with it, I'll end up like, if you grew up with it, you're wrong.
Don't get a different childhood.
Jump in a river if you like this crap.
That's where it's going to switch to.
Macho duck.
Let's go right.
Yeah.
All right.
Macho duck.
Top of side too.
Things have come to a head.
We've got to start hearing some characters.
No Mickey, but we might get a certain macho duck here.
Street noise.
Oh, geez.
It's very Saturday night.
It's gritty, this song.
Oh, good evening, Mr. Duck.
Can I get the door for you?
I mean, I love that Donald voice too.
He's got two left feet, but he doesn't care.
Justin blue, fit to the form.
Ladies love to touch his uniform.
He does wear a sailor suit.
That's what they mean?
That uniform?
I think, unless he's wearing a full dress sailor outfit.
And we haven't thought a lot about Donald Duck's military service.
Well, we should.
Donald's time in the Navy.
We should be talking about more.
Another disco song.
Yeah, right.
A song he would like.
Takes him back to his days in the Navy.
Right.
So ladies love to touch his uniform.
How many people or animals did Donald kill in the Navy?
He doesn't want to talk about it.
Why is he so angry?
Because he's seen some shit.
I'm just trying to stay busy.
That's why I make all these movies.
Psychoholic.
I can't.
I'm doing Jason Stitch.
I love this Donald voice though.
So this is a different Donald also.
This is a different, this guy's named Jim Tatevich.
He was on the Disney studio staff as location spotter.
Do you know what that means?
Does that mean like spotting of like sound effects?
Or does that mean like finding locations for live action movies?
That's a good question.
This I don't know.
But from 1964 on, he would fill in if Clarence Ducky Nash was unavailable to be Donald Duck.
And then they started, the Disney brass kind of started liking this guy
because he does the voice, but you understand it a little bit better.
And he apparently, what does this say?
He generated the voice in his throat rather than the back of his mouth,
which is what Nash and probably most Donalds have ever done.
The current with Tony Anselmo.
So they would send Tatevich, they'd pass Tatevich the ball if clarity was in the picture,
which I get, and I do understand what he's saying in this.
So they needed, yeah, they needed it here.
I mean that you get the gist of that.
Fine.
Not as, I would say it does, they sure did a good job being less sketchy than Macho Man.
Yes, it is less sketchy than Macho Man.
Oh, Macho Duck.
But not as good as The Greatest Band, but I do enjoy Donald's voice in there.
So I enjoy it from a comedy perspective perhaps.
He did just, he just ad-libbed it.
They finished the song and they said, just go in there and yell responses.
And he did four takes of that and then they combined the funniest stuff.
So it really, so it was, this is improv we're hearing from somebody who understood how to be Donald.
What do you think, okay, so you, I know you really want to crack this Donald voice,
but do you, what do you think awaits you in success?
Like if you, or do you feel like you're going to at some point get it?
And then like really make the audience laugh or applaud?
Like where does it, what happens?
What's at the other end of this rainbow?
No, it's all personal satisfaction, I think.
I'm not like, yeah, I don't, I think it's impossible.
I don't even know how, how I would go about it.
I still don't really know.
Well, does that help you that knowing about the throat and where do you,
where do you think it's coming from right now?
I don't know.
I guess I was, I guess I was doing it in my cheeks more than I was doing it in my throat.
So it's like, sounds like the xenomorph.
So back of the mouth is what the man himself, Nash, did.
Do you think you could throw it to the back?
I'm trying to throw it to the back.
Can you do anything from the back?
Can I do anything from the back?
Well that doesn't, you still have your effective voice.
I was somehow, I was like, if I just start,
will it just somehow perfectly magically be Donald?
All right, here we go.
I'm talking as me and now I'm, no, that just, nothing happened.
I don't know.
Like, I really don't know.
The worst thing would be if the two of us just did this
and then you just heard a thump and you're, and then another thump, we both,
and you realize that was us just asphyxiating, passing out on the ground.
Then, then it's just silent for 45 minutes.
Then a forever dog custodian comes in and says, oh no, and then stops the recording.
Well, then it's Jason coming in and saying,
what you've just heard is the way Mike and Scott passed away.
We wanted you to hear this audio document of how they died as fools,
trying to do a Donald Duck voice and getting nowhere close.
They would have wanted it this way.
And then he would have tried.
Their last words.
That's the way, when I'm doing it, I feel like I'm choking
within the throat.
When you throw it to the throat, I don't know what that is.
I don't know what that means.
It can't be good.
I can't, it's not sustainable.
No.
So I don't know.
I really, I guess in my private life, I need to keep trying
because I feel like, I feel like it's completely out of reach.
Do you feel like the best way that you could die would be
to at the same time, reach climax and reach a perfect Donald Duck voice?
Auto erotic ducks.
Duck fixation.
Duck suffixiation.
Yeah.
I mean, that sounds like.
The best orgasm of your life combined with finally cracking Donald.
Right.
Like you're like, I did it.
Like I yell, I did it in Donald's voice simultaneously while you orgasm.
Yeah.
That would be something.
I don't know.
That is achieving pure bliss.
I think mine is worse.
I think my Donald is the worst voice of any of our voices of any kind on the show.
It's possible.
I did it.
I'm coming.
Somebody's going to have to teach us.
I think I need to be taught.
I can't do this myself.
Obviously.
Well, it requires you got to like throw your, you know, this is like.
It's like a ventriloquist.
Maybe it is like a ventriloquist type thing or something like,
because they throw, they do their voice.
They have to throw it other places so it doesn't look like they're talking.
Yeah, sure.
So, I mean, I want to be more of a ventriloquist in my daily life.
So perhaps that's maybe a Terry fader.
Jeff Dunham could teach me.
Not them.
They're too busy, but somebody like that.
When you figure out your ventriloquist act where you make a,
you throw your voice so that a dummy can perform semi-charm life.
Your daughter will think you're cool forever.
Knucklehead Smith singing semi-charm life.
He's revolutionized the ventriloquism industry
while remaining hip and youthful to boot.
That sounds like a good act.
So what do you have planned next?
Oh, doing Donald's, Donald Duck's voice until I come and die.
All right.
A macho duck.
Are we out of that one?
Macho duck paints.
You know what I always, I do like, they like paint Donald.
They always give like Donald something fun.
Splash Dance does it too.
He's a digital duck.
Yeah.
So like they do give him like a little more character.
I mean, Goofy's got a song coming up here too.
Yeah.
But I feel like they always give Donald something fun.
He's the one who actually gets the most fun.
He's really, he's really winning in these for sure.
Now, is this where we need to talk about because
Disco Duck by long time DJ Rick Dees presented as maybe the worst disco song.
And then we got Macho Duck here.
Now you're telling me about another duck with albums worth the material.
There is another duck inspired by Disco Duck and Rick Dees, but not created by Rick Dees.
He must be fury.
He must be.
I don't try to sue this duck into the ground.
It's very possible he did, but we are talking about Irwin the Disco Duck.
I don't know if you've ever.
Nope.
Come across.
I haven't had the pleasure.
Irwin was put out by Peter Pan records.
It was a child's record label.
Where they tried to rip off visually.
This is, this is a rip off of Donald big.
Yes, his hair and his clothing apparently were a rip off of Rick Dees.
So he was visually designed to look like Rick Dees as well.
The human man is a rip off of tooth, a human man.
And there are, I think, six albums on Apple Music of Irwin the Disco Duck and
Irwin the Disco Duck Christmas and New Year's party.
Right.
And Santa's dancing with them.
In the Navy, Disco Fever for All Ages.
Oh, I guess there's only five.
Yeah.
Five on here.
Disco Duck Dance Party and
Irwin and Papino the Chipmunk fun songs for all.
The first song is called Shut Up You Face.
Oh my God.
And it has, yes, we have no bananas on it.
There is a wide range of songs that like he, one of the albums has Sesame Street on it.
The theme from Sesame Street, Candyman.
Rubber Duckie.
He's on Down the Road from the Wiz.
Like it is a bizarre collection of songs.
They're the one that in the Navy does have Macho Man and YMCA and La Freak by Chic.
Uh, I Love the Nightlife.
Sorry.
Also this cover that I'm looking at where it says it lists all the tracks on the top.
And the first one is Shut Up You Face.
And then there's an extra sticker on top that says with a little red note that says
Contains the Hit.
Shut up you face.
They want to make sure on two occasions to alert you to shut up you face.
Yeah.
So I like, I'll say this.
I like the drawings of Irwin.
And his lady too.
There's some decent logos on here.
It is also like this, like the Disco Duck Dance Party cover.
It's almost like the reverse of like whatever Lady Duck this is.
She's showing her on her butt to the, like there's a, there's a Fritz the Cat-ness to it.
Even though it's not explicit, it's for children.
Oh yeah.
No, I'm seeing crack.
I'm seeing duck crack.
This is predating the like very strong sexuality of Howard the Duck.
But a few years later.
But I do like these drawings.
I don't know how much more there is to investigate past these bad albums.
My recommendation would be investigating no further.
I don't know.
I don't think there's any.
I mean, I am kind of dying to hear Shut Up You Face.
Though I have my fears that Shut Up You Face is going to be offensive
on some level.
It's possible.
Perhaps all levels.
I haven't listened to that.
Let me just play Silly Love Songs for you to explain what kind of,
or what format these songs.
This is going to become my new favorite Silly Love Songs.
Well, just wait a second.
Number one, this.
Wow.
This is a magical hit for you.
Silly Love Song.
Disney should have ended this.
So, so what is, what most of the songs have is an intro by Erwin.
And then a poorly recorded cover of a song.
So let's keep going here.
And I want to get to the vocal.
It's like a tea kettle.
Yeah, it's a breaking pipe.
You're like.
Baseline a little off, a little, like a little wrong.
Wait.
Silly Love Songs.
It's not a duck singing.
It's just some idiot.
Some guy out of out of tune, out of key singing.
Let me hear.
Let's hear that one more time.
Here we go.
You think that people would have had Silly Love Songs.
It's like a little off though.
Hitting notes are coming at the wrong times.
They had like one take for this.
So that is like kind of how Erwin does things.
There's a love will keep us together too.
They just started, they just forced people into this.
They would like, they found people who they had like, they were blackmailing people.
Like we're going to, we're reporting you to the authorities to the crime for the crimes
we know you committed.
Right.
Unless you come in here and sing Silly Love Songs mildly on key.
Okay, please.
Please don't put me away.
We'll kill you right now.
There's a gun to your head.
Sing a semi passable Silly Love Songs or that's that.
You think that people.
That sucked, but it'll do.
A little awful, but okay.
This album hits the streets at midnight.
It's going to have to work.
We have a deal.
Okay, love will keep us together.
Love will keep us together.
Missing half the instruments.
True spit in the face to Neil Sadaka.
To Neil.
We didn't even get into the song.
Oh, I'd love to get into Neil Sadaka's Instagram.
Hello, I'm Neil Sadaka.
I'm Neil Sadaka.
The dorkiest hit singer.
The dorkiest pop star in history.
Yes, but a good Instagram follow.
Oh, a lovely tune.
That was a wonderful tune.
I'm playing with my grandson on Instagram.
I'm Neil Sadaka.
My Neil is better than my Donald for sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, to be as good at Donald as Neil.
So I guess we have to play.
What's the song you want to hear?
Let's do it at the end.
All right, yeah, fine.
Okay, so Irwin, I will still keep investigating Irwin.
I don't know if there's much more to do,
but I am delighted by the existence of Irwin the Disco Duck and his multiple albums.
My fear at this point is that no one bothered to save Shut Up You Face.
Oh, perhaps.
Which album is it on?
That's what, it has somebody named Papino the Chipmunk on it.
Oh, maybe I missed, I haven't seen this one.
Shut Up You Face, a song that exists outside of Irwin the Duck.
I don't know, it seems like there's a lot of covers.
Irwin Duck.
It is on YouTube.
Oh, thank God.
With 214 views, you all listeners will tie for 215.
Wow.
Lucky day for you.
But I guess for now we should actually listen to this album.
Mousetrap.
Oh, well, hey, I got good feelings towards Mousetrap.
All right, okay.
Let's check out Mousetrap.
Mousetrap.
It's got some energy.
That's good, I love to hear Mousetrap.
Yeah, yeah.
Mousetrap will slap you and grab you by the tail.
But he's slick, he moves quick, that fast will never fail.
You won't ever catch him resting.
His feet never touch the ground, no.
So this is a song about what would happen
if you angered Mickey enough for him to physically assault you.
You're right.
Ah, Mousetrap, hey, I'll kill ya.
These shirts look small, but I always keep a crowbar in them.
Mousetrap, Mousetrap.
Or a literal Mousetrap.
Mousetrap will slap you and grab you by the tail.
He just flicks it at your face.
But he's slick, he moves quick, that fast will never fail.
The horn's in it, I think, elevated, too.
I think the horn players are doing some heavy lifting on this record.
Yeah, I love those.
Yeah, that's passable, though.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah, I don't think there's anything stellar on this album,
but I think you put on Mousetrap, I think you put on The Greatest Band.
If that's just in a disco shuffle,
I don't think it skids the party to a halt
and everybody just stares over at the speakers.
No, but yeah, again, I hate to keep comparing it,
but it's not going to bring you to tears like Gyro Gear Loose
or Mickey's Got a Crush on You.
Those two songs, I just listen to those songs in earnest.
When I'm alone, not for fun.
I love the Sparks one, obviously.
Yes, and they're a great song, too.
From my little bit of poking around it,
I think we're going to find that Mouser Size is kind of a bridge.
I think we will end up liking the Mouser Size music more.
There's even a song on that album called Bugaboo
that I remember from the workout videos when I was a kid.
Oh, I didn't know that.
They would show on the Disney Channel,
and Bugaboo was a cut track from this,
because it is a little bit more disco than the rest of it,
which is more like early 80s.
Maybe we're more in the Earth, Wind, and Fire territory.
That's another band I really like.
I wouldn't call that disco, though.
Yeah, I don't know.
Who cares?
Like what you like.
If you like Earth, Wind, and Fire, great.
If you like Erwin and Papino the Chipmunks,
then that's especially great.
Watch Out for Goofy?
Let's play Watch Out for Goofy.
So Watch Out for Goofy, this song just existed,
and it wasn't even going to have Goofy on it
until they liked Tadevich's Donald improv so much.
They were like, we've got to get another character on here.
So they got Tony Pope, who I don't think was always Goofy,
but maybe sometimes.
Really takes a second here.
Four on the four bass drum.
And then the haba.
That's nice.
I like that.
Yeah.
He falls on his face and he's out for the night.
He concusses himself.
So watch out, watch out for Goofy, watch out for Goofy.
Gosh, what's my name?
Who's the president?
I can't draw a clock.
The other body just can't dance.
Yeah, this is another, this is a top three or four for me.
And it's just, yeah, like watch out when Goofy wants to dance,
but he will hurt himself.
You need to be careful around this giant dog.
Jesus Christ.
He will hurt himself and maybe you accidentally.
He does, he means well.
Now they also say Donald is two left feet in that as well,
but they don't, it's not a dire warning like this song is.
Yeah.
I like that that goes by and Donald just goes, what?
He's just insulted.
But this is like a sweet warning to any women
that get invited to go dancing or when.
Here's like, that guy Goofy, should I ask him?
I've been thinking about asking him out.
Well, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
No, great.
Really great honesty if he stays on his feet,
but you didn't hear that from me.
Right.
But you will end the night driving a bleeding Goofy to the hospital.
You have to understand that he will hurt himself.
He does it all the time.
You will be something we'll call it.
He will like hit a loose disco floorboard propelling,
which then launches him back up into the ceiling,
straight his face into the disco ball,
and doctors will be picking a disco ball mirror
out of his cheeks for the remainder of the night.
So if you're looking to hook up, not a good idea.
Yeah.
He's going to have to take it easy.
He will be in no shape to hook up after a night of dancing.
Have you ever seen someone break every bone in their body?
Because that is what will happen.
He will not be able to do anything.
I fell into the DJ booth that I got vinyl records in my penis.
Vinyl shards.
Oh, my teeth fell out when I crashed them on the floor.
We had to pick them up.
It took an hour to find them all lodged in people's boots.
Donald bought his ice cubes, put them in his drink,
took a sip, choked to death.
Yuck.
Sorry, Linda.
I wanted the night to go better than this.
I thought now it would be all right.
I thought I had gotten a handle of disco dancing,
but my eyes burst out of my head.
Hard to have sex with your butts in a cast.
So yeah, this is the sad song, I think, of the album.
Yeah, well, there's a melancholy to it melodically anyway.
But one of the better songs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that's some of that moodiness,
where if you pay attention to the lyrics of Stayin' Alive,
it's pretty heavy stuff.
Right.
If you pay attention to the lyrics of Watch Out for Goofy,
you'll realize how much you do have to watch out for Goofy.
Similar, yeah.
Now, if there's any musical legitimacy to this album,
a lot of it might come from what you're about to hear.
Do you know about this fact about It's a Small World?
Oh, is it in the Fat Boy Slim song?
It is.
Well, I was going to let the listener guess.
Well, I could cut it if you want.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yes, let's do it.
OK, do you know this fact about the Fat Boy Slim?
No.
I'm leaving this in now.
All right, it's in.
Now it's in.
Now that I've fucked up the reset.
I was going to cut it, but now we're not.
It's in.
God damn it.
All right, just play it.
I was trying to say a fun fact.
Let's say, y'all.
Praise you, right?
Wow.
Praise you.
No, I could have been the question.
But I have to praise you like I should.
Yeah, how about that?
Did you know the thing that was going around?
Hold on, it's a small world.
I guess I'll let it play out.
It's in a world of land, a world of people.
Or not.
I think it's successful, but it's not something I want to listen to.
I mean, that's clearly a great sound if it's
sampled for a big hit record later.
I mean, my God.
I like the music other than the lyrics are fine in there,
but I like the music.
I think the music sounds pretty cool.
Can you imagine if I'd done it smooth?
And if the big question.
If I'd done the reset right and then everybody was thinking,
wow, Scott really set up that trivia in such a clean, cool way.
He's like, God, him doing setups to neat trivia is as slick as Mickey Mouse on the dance floor.
Not good, but instead I was more like goofy on the dance floor.
Wow.
Yeah, boy.
Take me to the hospital.
Brain hospital.
You're really fucked up, too.
You're both in the hospital beds next to each other.
You break everything.
I fumbled a fun factoid.
Did you puncture your brain on the corner of a DJ table like me?
I just found this.
There's a, I get these Instagram clips from this guy, Luxury.
Do you ever get this gentleman?
No.
And I forget his co-host's name, but I think he has like a podcast and it's all about music.
The groove is in the heart sample.
You know the song?
Certainly.
Do you know where this sample comes from?
No.
Oh my God.
I kind of just play the clip.
Yeah, yeah, please.
Let me just play the clip.
This blew my mind.
Yeah, what is that?
I couldn't ask for another because it actually comes from this.
What?
This is the Green Acres theme.
Really?
From 1966.
Yep.
Little moment is Eva Gabor.
No way.
Right here.
Whoa.
And they've done a kind of classic early sampling thing where you just go.
Sampling Eva Gabor from Green Acres and doing.
And then more importantly.
Which is so like two of hearts.
Oh, totally.
That I trope came from.
I'm uncomfortable how much we're watching another podcaster and just playing him through.
Let's plug Luxury.
I mean, they're very successful.
They probably don't fumble their factoids.
L-U-X-X-U-R-Y.
Luxury always gets it right.
But every clip I've ever seen of this, and this is something I will be listening to,
but every clip I see I'm like fascinated by whether it's like old stuff or like
let's analyze the baseline to Mr. Brightside by The Killers and then say what like,
oh, this sounds like this song from 30 years ago.
So I'm into this channel, but that blew my, I was like, oh my God, Green Acres sample.
Green Acres and kind of a cousin to that Beastie Boys license to ill Mr. Ed sample.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Time to get ill.
So that's fun.
A good theme song representation.
Yeah.
Well, so there you go.
I mean, that speaks to the quality of this album, you know, a later very prominent
and catchy sample.
Um, but then the, you know, can you go to the last like 20 seconds of Small World?
Cause then, cause that starts and I'm like, well, damn, that's a fucking great sound.
And then, then it just kind of becomes like too many songs on top of each other.
They're like layering a lot.
So here we go.
This last 23 seconds was ambitious, but I don't know that it like hangs together.
It's kind of like at the end of the actual ride,
maybe that was like where they're like, everyone's singing their different sort of versions.
And it's I guess, I get what you're saying though.
I don't hate it, but it's sort of like a little bit like too much.
But hey, I don't know.
Notable.
Now they only got one more track to really make a big impression.
Right.
And that is Chim Chim Tree.
The big closer, another Sherman Brothers song.
It's a small world, of course.
Closing out with a disco Sherman block.
Disco Mary Poppins.
And of course, not like in a melancholy song in a lot of ways, Chim Chim Tree.
Not like Step in Time, which there's other versions.
I feel like there's a techno version of Step in Time somewhere that I've talked about before.
Maybe I'm wrong.
You can pretend all you want that's not in your top 50 for the year.
It might be in my top 50, but then-
Very good job playing it cool.
So track nine is Chim Chim Tree.
This sort of chimney sweeps lament from Mary Poppins.
Now I'll say this.
I like this.
I like this part.
It's very serviceable, waka waka waka kind of guitar.
It's kind of like a good music-y Herb Albert.
Little staccato trumpets there.
Like kind of good.
It switches.
I don't hate this, but then I'll always want to listen to music that's like this,
that isn't Chim Chim Tree.
Well, sure, I could agree with that.
This part is less fun to me.
But the sexier music version I like at the start.
I don't know how sexy I found it.
Sexier!
It was sexier than that, sure.
And it's sexier than regular Chim Chim Tree.
I completely agree.
Chim Chim Tree is a sad song.
It's not as sad as Feed the Birds, but it's sad.
But there's a lot of sadness in, you know?
Yeah.
Last Dance.
It's the last dance.
That's true, yeah.
Yeah, this part doesn't do much for me.
It also doesn't sound like the song.
Makes you think about the guy who's gonna have to sweep the chimney of the disco
when the party's over.
Right.
Get all the sun out.
So, I mean, that's the gist.
I don't know why they closed with this.
I'm not sure with the choice there, but...
I'm gonna go ahead and say Mixed Bag.
Mixed Bag, this record.
Yeah.
There's never anything so crazy, silly, insane.
The fine is fine.
It's just fine.
It's in this fine lane.
Maybe listeners feel the same way.
Maybe you knew that cover, never listened to it.
I think I imagined something much sillier.
Yeah.
Not so much.
It's kind of like sincere disco music that once in a while nods to the Disney characters
and to the Mary Poppins.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like it's somewhat successful.
It's somewhat successful.
And there's enough, you go, oh, you ever heard this funny little thing?
And then maybe you never listen to it again,
but you're never gonna maybe listen to Chim Chim Marie disco version again.
But it might be, oh, you know what's funny?
They did this disco thing.
That's sort of where it lands, I think.
I think we're giving people fodder for, you know,
hour, five and a half of a long car ride.
You're really running out of stuff.
Especially if you're in like, well, we're tight friends,
but we've still run out of stuff to say.
Well, that's the moment where you can say,
hey, did you know that there was once a disco version of Chim Chim Marie?
Right.
And then, oh, do you want to hear it?
No.
And then you kind of keep driving and just hope
there's a funny road sign to comment on.
Hopefully.
To break the next silence.
Oh, you ever heard of this Erwin, the disco duck?
Well, you mean Rick Deez's disco?
No, no, no, no.
No.
There was another disco duck.
Do you want to hear that?
No, even less.
Do you want to jump out of the car right now?
Yeah, I think so.
Tumble, tumble, tumble, tumble.
It walks the rest of the way home.
We delayed, at least you delayed that from happening
with some of this information on this episode.
So that's good.
That's what we try to give you is fodder to try to keep your friends
from physically jumping out of the car as long as possible.
Though it might eventually cause the physical jumping out of the car.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I don't want to say it will, but maybe.
We don't bear any responsibility for any of that.
Now, another thing to say about this record is that it also turned into a short film.
There was a theatrical release of Mickey Mouse Disco,
which you can watch kind of restored on YouTube.
They took the best seven minutes, which does cut down pretty good.
Actually, when you take the best of the best of what you just heard, that ain't bad.
Kind of give it a big optical title, kind of jazzy intro.
And, you know, they just like film some disco lights and they just keep cutting
to the words Mickey Mouse and Disco and then Mickey Mouse and Disco.
And, you know, when they did that thing, they always do where they took the old shorts,
you know, where Mickey's like dancing with the cards behind his back or, you know,
they found all the parts of the characters dance and they cut them together.
And that was enough to be the pre-show for a movie called The Last Flight of Noah's Ark,
starring Elliot Gould and Ricky Schroeder, a movie that Roger Ebert called a dreadful movie,
bankrupt of creative imagination.
Oh, wow.
This was in the, this was in the era that proved why Eisner needed to get in there,
because that's 1980, the kind of this dark, the Ron Miller time, you know,
they really don't know what to do with it.
The age of Candle Shoe and Condor Man, they don't know.
Disney has no idea how to make a hit film.
And then even Ron Miller himself called this movie a $6 million, a $6 million write-off.
So, but, you know, some disco, you might leave, you might like really sadly slump out of that
screening of The Last Flight of Noah's Ark, not know what to talk about and then go,
oh, you know what I like to say? Disco.
That disco made me smile before the movie crushed my spirits for, I'm going to guess 76 minutes.
As short as it could possibly be.
It didn't technically qualify as a film.
Merciful 76 minutes, I hope.
So there you go. Mickey Mouse disco.
I guess, I think we have to view this as a step in the path to Splash Dance.
It gets you Splash Dance.
Right.
And I'm going to say maybe have high hopes for Mouser Size as well.
I liked the Mouser Size songs from what I poked around.
And we still haven't done Totally Mini either, which I like.
Mini? We haven't done, we wanted you to do that Toontown album you brought up.
And my hopes are not necessarily for that.
Craig and Company for the album for babies.
I hope I'm wrong, but that one I feel like I'm lowering my expectations for.
And then all of which obviously culminating in the best thing that Disney or any company
has produced, a whole new sound.
A whole new sound. 25 years after pop punk.
Disney finally, finally.
That is true, I know.
When you really got it, it's like, okay, so what?
They're like a year, two years behind Saturday Night Fever as opposed to 25 years after the death of the genre.
Yeah.
I mean, not the death.
Right.
Because some of the bands are still around and able to participate.
But then there's like newer bands.
I'm like, okay, that's an interesting choice.
I mean, that's kind of like, hey, we finally did Disney D-Lite.
We got D-Lite to agree, at last.
It took 40 years, but I mean, that'd be better, probably.
Yeah.
It's D-Lite around, do we know?
I like the songs, those are good songs.
That's a good question.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, something we do know is that we teased a song for the end, which we'll have to experience together.
And you know how earlier we said we just didn't do the edit?
I think here, I'm going to say if the episode just goes blank after I do the plugs,
that means that there was an edit for offensive material in the song, Shut Up, You Face.
Somebody else has that song, I see now.
Okay.
That that is not an original.
And I'm going to guess that the quality of the original Shut Up, You Face was questionable.
So then to do a cover, they rushed out Gunpoint, much worse cover of Shut Up, You Face.
But you know, I don't know what Papino is going to bring to the table.
I feel like I know what Irwin the Duck offers,
but maybe Papino the Chipmunk is going to surprise me.
Well, fingers crossed.
So are we ready?
Maybe Papino is the Michael of this Jackson 5.
Well, I'll do the plugs here.
Oh yeah, go for it.
Yeah.
I'll say You Survive podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate.
Thanks for subscribing here.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month in our regular episodes ad free.
If there's albums we didn't mention in that album litany,
this seems like a good area for us.
We should make it through all of these odd Disney albums.
So always a good thing to get our attention by throwing them in the club three poll.
But now, let me do a big, as big as possible of a windup,
because it'll be funnier if then you hear nothing,
here with Shut Up, You Face, Irwin and Papino the Chipmunk.
And now here's another one of those great tunes that are guaranteed to set your feet a-tappin'.
Talking about feet, Irwin.
Yes?
Wait, stop, stop.
Why did Irwin stop talking like a duck?
That's a good question.
Papino, I was really confused.
Who's that?
And then a new voice, and that's a high-pitched chipmunk.
Cool, got it.
But at first I was like, is that Irwin?
Why did, there's no consistency.
No consistency here.
And who made a million in the footwear business?
No.
He started out on a shoestring.
So far, so not offensive.
I'm reading that this was actually a hit, this real song.
This is where Jason, shut up, shut up, you face.
Number seven, Irwin.
No, just say the phrase already.
No, I know, we gotta get to that.
Come on.
I still have it.
Say it.
Echoes from, what is happening?
They haven't set you up, you face.
Different voice.
Made for fun and frolic.
And so do I.
Can we not stop until they say shut up, you face?
I guess not.
I'll start cleaning up while we, well.
Oh yeah, this is the first gear tear down.
All right.
Yeah, I'll take the microphone stand out.
Apologies for all the rustling.
Yeah.
Well, good one.
So we're trying to clean up next Sunday, I guess?
I'm gonna, yep, that's good.
I'll unplug and light it.
Do you think you're free in the afternoon or the morning?
I think you're gonna hear the mic unplugged now.
I'm free in the morning, I think.
How's that, how's that McCafe you came in with?
Is that, mic unplugged his microphone.
So we can't, we're gonna have to go off mine.
Oh, well, I just have to go off the one recording the speaker.
Any plans for tonight?
Just kind of putting the kids down or?
I'm gonna give Gladiator 2 a go.
Really?
It's all right.
Verse three, for fuck's sake.
Save shit up, you face.
So do I, and so do I.
Something, it were to be our song.
Well, now the listeners know what the tripods holding up sound like.
To find a song.
With who?
But I, I love to spend my time in singing some joyous song.
Some joyous song.
Jesus.
What's possibly the appeal of a song called shut up, you face,
that doesn't even say the phrase, shut up, you face?
You're sure it's the right title?
Listen, listen, echoes from afar.
Echoes from afar, that's what the listeners are hearing now.
It's the only audio left.
Echoes from afar, funiculi, funicula.
Fa la la la, fa la la la, fa la la la, fa la la la la, fa la la la.
I think it's a lost cause.
Echoes from afar, funiculi, funicula.
What?
That sucks.
Fuck you.