FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcasts may contain
pleasant little welcome chimes,
shoe sole material investigation,
a long diversion about Vivian Vance's jewelry,
and clear door talk.
All that plus, we stroll through the new Disneyland turnstiles
on today's podcast, The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, where we know something
that never goes out of style is going in and out of turnstiles.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
I don't know why the man Jason Mraz popped into my mind,
but it felt like a rhyme, a Mraz rhyme or something.
You were reading some of his poetry.
I don't know why.
I don't even begin to know why that's the case.
I'm not familiar enough with the Mraz body of work.
I'm not really either.
I don't think to know that.
I don't know why I said that. I'm not either.
Listener, if you know, or if Jason Sheridan knows,
are you Mraz, him being a fellow Jason,
are you familiar enough with the body of work?
I'm not, but I will say Disneyland is a place
you can see fireworks from the freeway.
Is that something from Jason Mraz?
Isn't that a line?
Isn't that a Mraz line?
Again, I'm not the person to add.
I think you are the Mraz expert here.
He sings the remedy.
I know that it's about not worrying your life away.
Besides that, I don't know.
The remedy is the experience.
Is that what he says?
It's a dangerous liaison.
Look at this.
This is the most music knowledge he's had so far
on this whole podcast.
Well, that was in the college zone.
That was when your music aperture opened up,
the 10 months of new music.
That's right.
Mraz is right in the zone there.
But the one song, I think.
Yeah.
The remedy, yeah.
Well, that's the one.
Although he had a bigger one, obviously.
Well, he had the hats.
We were all like, oh, whoa, what are those hats?
He did have the hats.
Yes, well, but not to distract too much,
because I do want to get into today's topic,
which is the Disneyland.
If you know this, and maybe you don't know this
if you're not on the West Coast,
but the Disneyland has been redoing its entrance plaza.
It's been redoing.
Is that even the right term, entrance plaza?
That might be like what's between the sets.
The gate, the literal gates.
And we have the second gate,
but we don't do a lot of talking about the actual gates,
which are really the first part of your theme park experience.
Right.
And they're brand new at Disneyland.
They opened earlier this year.
They cost $4.8 million,
and it's 38 new entry gates,
so it's a whole new experience as you enter, though.
I feel like we haven't done enough gate talk on the show in general.
We've talked about Universal, which gives, like,
they do the, like, put your little finger on the dirty little circle
or dirty little oval,
and rub your dirty germs all over.
Everybody that's been there is, like, during the day's germs.
Step one, yeah, put your finger on.
But we haven't really talked enough about, you know,
all the different things.
Magic Bands, Entryway, and Disney World,
which, like, that is kind of supposedly in Disneyland yet,
but I haven't tried it. I haven't bought one.
You can use a newer one there.
You know, when we were down at Universal Orlando in 2023,
they had some of this facial recognition.
Oh, yes, and that's an aspect of this,
and I don't know if that's up and running yet,
but I think there will be a facial recognition component.
I think currently they're having cast members on their phones
scan you in, and then automatic gates open.
That's part of the new...
It's not the, like, metal poles,
whatever you want to call it, that spin around.
It's now these plastic gates.
And I think currently cast members are helping with this,
but I think the idea is that eventually it'll just be a self-serve thing
and that they'll monitor that via scanning your face.
And so Universal's been doing that for a little while then.
They were testing it, at least I think it was at Islands.
So we don't know if they've instituted the facial recognition.
Yeah, I don't know for sure.
They were testing it at Islands for sure.
It was live testing when we were there,
and I gotta say, I wasn't really a fan of the fingerprints.
I'm certainly not a fan of the facial recognition.
I was wondering where you were gonna go with it.
It kind of gives me the creeps, you know?
How long do they hold that data?
Forever.
We're just giving all our data away to all these companies.
They did have our face already,
because they would take the picture for many years.
That's true.
So you would see the picture in there.
And I think we discovered on some fine print recently
that they have the picture, I think, for like seven years,
and then they have to upload it.
There was a time limit on when you have to refresh that picture.
And it's more frequent with kids.
Yes.
Kids have to update their photos more often
because of the rate that kids would change and grow at, obviously.
What is everyone's favorite way to get into a theme park?
Mine is Magic Band.
That's my favorite way.
There's something class...
Hello?
Whoa.
What?
Hey, boys.
What's going on here?
Griffin?
Griffin Newman?
Griffin's here all of a sudden.
Griffin, what's up?
Wait, wait, what the hell?
We didn't even know you were in town.
What's going on?
Are we doing a main feed episode?
Yeah, this is a Disneyland turnstiles.
Yeah, we're just doing a...
New turnstiles is a main feed episode, huh?
How's that going?
How are you feeling about this?
How's this going?
I introduced a question I felt pretty good about,
but other than that, I think it's fine.
I was kind of excited to answer that
because I kind of like just the good old-fashioned...
What's your favorite way to enter a park?
Yeah, huh?
Yeah.
Right, yeah.
For a main feed episode!
Yes, yeah.
Why not?
What are we doing here?
What the fuck's the problem with that?
Why not?
It's our podcast.
This topic is feces!
It's feces?
Feces?
It's got mold on it!
What do you mean?
That means it's old, I guess,
but it's kind of a new topic because it just happened.
These are new games.
You're doing a five-minute sidebar conversation
and you're overpouring it!
You don't do a main feed episode!
I mean, you don't understand what this podcast is.
We mine a lot out of a little.
That's what we've always done.
How is this any different than what we always do?
This is our...
You come in here, you tell us how to run our podcast.
I'm shutting this down!
It's almost like you flew into a town.
You didn't know anything about the operations going on here.
You started demanding things.
Wait, yeah, wait a minute.
What did you just say?
What did you yell just now?
I'm shutting this down!
You're shutting it down?
Where do you get out?
You're shutting down our podcast?
You don't have the right to do that.
What gives you the right to do that?
Excuse me.
One year ago, 2024, year of our Lord,
Griffin Newman does whatever he wants,
wins a Club 3 poll.
That's right.
We have a very productive three-hour-plus pitching session
on Untitled Jason Sheridan animated project.
We've been pitching around.
We worked up a big deck.
It's been an exhaustive amount of pitching.
There's a bidding war going on for it, too.
The town is going crazy.
But at the end of the episode, before my title and my power seeded,
I slammed a bottle of Jon Taffer's brown butter bourbon onto the table
and decreed that Taffer 1 must happen, main feed, before the end of 2024.
Now, some things went awry.
Sure.
Life got in the way.
A lot of life got in the way.
We all had a crazy 2024.
It's got you at another child.
I left for a while.
My podcast co-host had two more children.
Two of those.
My God, my condolences to him.
Which basically amounts to me having one child.
I think law of averages.
There's enough spillage on that at scale.
One is kind of yours.
Engagements?
Mm-hmm.
Marriage?
What do you mean?
Time for marriage.
Are you upset about it?
Are you simply mad about this?
I'm thrilled for Jason.
I'm thrilled for my good friend.
But the point is, it got away from us.
Yeah.
Oh, shit, I forgot.
I forgot.
I'm telling you what gives you the right.
Of course you have the right.
Everything in the world gives you the right.
It's past the calendar year, but it's time to make it happen.
Tap for one.
Okay.
This is Podcast Rescue.
This year, 6,500 failing podcasts will close their doors for good.
If things don't change soon, Podcast the Ride of Burbank, California will become just another
statistic.
In 2017, Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, and Scott Gairdner invested their life savings
into their dream podcast.
It's time to make it happen.
we'll become just another statistic in 2017, Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, and Scott Gairdner
invested their life savings into their dream podcast.
Curious Theme Park fans flock to this trendy audio hotspot.
But today, Podcast the Ride has become a fractured mess of tangents, dry micro-topics, and barely
any theme park content at all.
You and your f***ing Madam need to get the f*** out of here.
People just don't know about Madam yet.
Counterpoint.
Oh, yeah, you f***ing up saying that.
Don't even say that.
Now, Podcast The Riot is over $300,000 in debt.
With nowhere else to turn, the Good Boys have agreed to bust open the books,
pull back the main feed, and do a topic the whole audience can agree on.
Bar Rescue.
Podcasts are a science, and no one understands podcast science like Griffin Newman.
I don't embrace excuses, I embrace solutions.
Griffin is renowned to all the Good Boys for having a more successful Patreon than theirs.
You've already served this story five times!
It's got bacteria on it!
This is Taffer One.
Wow. Oh my god. You seized your power. It's happening.
Disneyland's new turnstiles are out the door.
They are trash now, and we are now in the long disgust.
Bar Rescue, aka the Taffer Soad, aka Taffer One.
My god. The main branding that you, Griffin, brought to the table.
Wow. I mean, I'm freaked out. I'm pretty jostled.
I came with page after page of notes about the turnstiles.
We didn't even get to say that they're actually tap styles.
We didn't even get that term out there.
But I guess now we're talking about different styles of taps in bars that Jon Taffer rescues.
Tap styles is what we're talking about.
This episode's become all about tap styles.
Now some listeners, and perhaps these people overlap with the folks who think I should never be on this podcast.
I'm going to say they exactly do, yes. It seems like the type.
Have long seemed to stand in opposition to the very idea of Taffer warranting an episode, let alone one that I am forcing through.
People are coping with, some people, certain people, certain very vocal people are coping with a lot right now.
Not only is it you, they also maybe were like, I was kind of excited about turnstiles.
And now you've barged in.
They were hoping Taffer Club 3, no guest, 15 minute mini-soad.
Instead, you are getting main feed as you declare that to happen using the established Club 3 power.
And keep this in mind, if you are a Club 3 member and a Club 3 guest at the same time,
you, much like Daniel Day Lewis Lincoln, is clothed in immense power.
I don't know if that's the exact quote.
I always go for clothed in immense power.
Yes, he's very, no, no, no.
No.
We're on the world stage now, no, no, no, no.
I'm Abraham Lincoln.
Only he knows, only he figured out the real voice.
Now I want to settle something, because I understand this is sensitive time.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of talking about Taffer is talking about facing our own depression, right?
I think John Taffer, more than anything, is a depression warrior.
I think Bar Rescue is a show about depression.
And so I'm just going to give some hard truths right now to the audience.
People who are locked in and excited for turnstiles going, oh, finally, theme park content.
They're getting back into the theme park minutia.
And now it's being interrupted by Taffer on main feed with my least favorite recurring guest.
I got bad news for you.
You need to adjust to the marketplace.
This is no longer a theme park podcast.
It hasn't been a theme park podcast in a long time.
You have to rebrand, much like Corporate Bar needed to let go of its pirate dreams.
Look at their clientele.
Look at the clientele of the show.
They don't even want, they aren't even theme park people anymore.
You have to adapt to the times.
Look at the neighborhood.
Surrounding Forever Dog Studios, 20 bars.
Right there.
The Universal Studios is closed, sure, but only one measly theme park.
20 bars.
Universal Bar and Grill is right there.
This podcast needs to adapt to relate to bars.
Each bar a dirtier or flipping concepts than the last.
Do you think if you dropped John Taffer off the back of a plane with a parachute and landed him onto this block.
If we did it, actually physically?
If you hired someone to be like kidnap John Taffer, swat his home.
I don't want any part of this, wink wink.
I want enough deniability that I bought the plane.
Multiple Trank Darts, Elephant Grade.
Yes, sure.
It takes a lot to bring him down.
Get him in a cargo ship, drop him off with a parachute.
He lands on this block.
Do you think he ejaculates immediately seeing the amount of bar rescuing he could do with the 15 steps?
Here in the Lankersham area.
Right?
Yeah, there are some bars and the bars do seem in dire need of rescuing, yes.
I also think another observation he would make is they do the show, they all live in Burbank.
Burbank is a college town.
Look how many colleges.
You've got Accidental, you've got Glendale Community, LA City College or something is right there.
Woodbury University.
And they aren't servicing Woodbury University whatsoever.
Talking about theme parks kind of sometimes.
Boys, I know the theme park podcast dream has been nice.
But it's just that it's a dream and it's time to wake up.
This needs to be a podcast about underage drinking.
Look at your surroundings.
It's easy for you to come in here and say that.
But I promised my dead husband that I would start a theme park podcast and that I would keep it about.
And I'd keep his belongings around here in memory of him.
Let me ask you a question.
You think your dead husband would be happy to see you being a big success?
That is what he always said he wanted for me.
Let me ask you another question.
Did your husband ever go to college and have some beers when he shouldn't?
Yes, of course, that's how I met him.
We were both in a bar at 15.
I think he'd be smiling.
I think he'd be looking down on us and smiling if he saw what this podcast could become.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to work with you.
I want to believe you.
I'm going to work with you on this.
We're going to do an episode about Jon Taffer.
God damn it.
One week later, Scott reinstated podcast the ride has since been canceled.
Six weeks later, the podcast was canceled.
Jon saddled it with an unusable premise.
The full-length New Turnstiles episode becomes the only podcast to get negative listeners.
Kettle One pulled their sponsorship.
They realized it was doing nothing for them.
Kettle One's been keeping this pod afloat for years.
People don't know that.
Jon's major suggestion was to light the logo from underneath.
It draws the eye.
That's something they're doing now.
Get with the times.
It's the 2010s.
This podcast needs a butt funnel.
You need to encourage listeners to touch each other.
There are so many odd, weird little elements.
All those phrases.
All is like draw the eye and stuff.
Come and go over the years, I think.
I went back and watched the very first one.
There was so much talk about hidden cameras, I feel like, in 2000.
In the episode of Bar Rescue?
Was that the premise then?
That we're putting hidden cameras around so he can do the recon?
At some point, it clearly became they have the most produced reality show cameras in the world.
In the bar for five hours.
We are not hidden anymore.
I think that's all.
Believe it or not, I think some of this might be constructed.
I think some of this might be cake fabe.
I'll say this.
My favorite cave fabe moment is in a more recent episode for a bar called Sacktown in Sacramento.
Sacktown?
Yes.
Maybe we should call this podcast.
I hear that kind of thing is doing really well these days.
I'm open to it.
This isn't like Old Town Sacramento.
It's very touristy area.
How many colleges?
A lot of colleges surround us.
This is immediate income!
Women!
Well, okay, now here's the thing though.
It's a touristy area, but it's a guy who's an ex-cop and funneled all his money into making a massive sports bar
filled with signed jerseys and memorabilia.
And it is not doing well.
Because he keeps insisting, you don't know, this is a sports town.
Taffer's like, it's not.
But the funniest moment is...
Wait, does he mean all of Sacramento isn't a sports there?
In terms of like versus like a Chicago with a million sports bars.
That's strange though.
People like sports in sports towns.
He's going to judge the entire city that no one likes sports in all of Sacramento.
So this is a real touristy area and there's a lot, they say there's a lot of farm to table restaurants popping up.
Come on.
So this is all his thing, but I haven't even gotten to.
The recon is they go in with all the people and Taffer does it himself with his guest, T-Pain.
Oh, I have seen this episode.
Taffer and T-Pain put on plain black baseball caps, walk in and walk right by the owner who goes like,
Welcome to our very usually quiet bar.
And then later in the episode, they're confronting him.
He's like, I didn't even see him come in.
And Taffer and T-Pain are pretty recognizable.
Taffer is a giant.
He's a giant.
Even if you don't know who he is, you would notice when the giant walks in.
I'm going to go one step beyond this.
He is the single most physically distinctive man alive.
Part of this episode is going to be drilling down into why all four of us felt compelled to do this episode.
Yeah.
I think we're going to have to break down because this is a bar rescue episode.
This is a John Taffer episode.
Why are we fascinating with this man?
Part of it is no one in history has ever looked like him.
Yeah.
If Shredder created Toka Rezar and put John Taffer next to the two of them, he would look right.
They would be three scary guys that could beat up the Ninja Turtles.
Can you imagine a NECA ultimate Taffer?
Yes, I could.
Oh, geez.
Now that would get me.
I'd be in the NECA game all of a sudden.
All the different variations.
Casual Taffer.
Chef Boyardee.
Color Scheme Taffer.
Yeah.
On the Taffer's Tavern website, John Taffer and his furry friend with just a casual dress shirt and one of his dogs.
I'm a nice guy too.
I have furry friends.
I don't scream at him.
He'd run away.
With his rescue pup, Bentley.
That's nice.
I'm just imagining John Taffer singing the Sarah McLachlan part in the SPCA commercial.
In the arms of an angel.
They're dying.
They're dying every day.
You are right that it's one of the immediate things I think that locked me into the Taffer universe the first time I stumbled across Bar Rescue is like,
is this show actually pretending in the first five minutes of the episode that everyone is surprised when he walks through the door?
Despite there being like fucking sitcom lights, like 20 cameras.
Angles.
Coverage.
Movement.
Camera movements.
Not like zooms.
Going into the back rooms.
A camera went into the kitchen already.
Tracks.
A camera's in the accountants office.
Right.
And as you said that he can walk in with a hat and be like, oh, I'll have chicken fingers, please.
And you're just like, even if you don't know what John Taffer looks like, in a world where you're pretending these people haven't all signed NDAs.
And they contacted him too.
Of course.
They begged him to come.
Still, if that guy walks into a bar, every single person turns around and goes, how does someone look like that?
A giant man walked in.
A giant, unique man walked in.
He even says a word.
Yeah.
Can I say my Taffer resemblance?
I might have said this on the show before.
And by the way, I want to back up a little and talk about our history with Taffer.
I think that might be important to stay in case people are really like, what's going on?
Why is this episode started?
And now it's about the guy from Bar Rescue.
And that's for the best.
No one's making you listen.
If you want to hang out and enjoy it.
Those customers didn't pay.
You didn't get them upgraded.
You didn't get them behind the second gate.
They're freeloaders.
I've always thought that John Taffer looks like, if you look up, not the cartoon character, but look up Governor Ratcliff Disneyland.
Oh, yes.
The villains from Pocahontas.
Specifically the walk around.
And if you imagine him without pigtails and colonial garb, without his big purple hat, just put the walk around Ratcliff in modern clothes and big billowy clothes.
I think that and you got to get rid of his mustache proper.
But then you leave kind of the unshaven nature.
And he's got the big lips.
He's got the big angry pouty lips.
Can you see it?
Yeah.
He's a little bit like Taffer.
I'm going to throw another one out.
I think he kind of looks like the handsome ogre played, voiced by Jon Hamm and Shrek forever after.
If you guys want to Google Jon Hamm.
Now in the universe of Shrek, this is supposed to be the hunkiest ogre imaginable.
Hunky ogre.
There's a little bit of a...
Brogan?
The name is Brogan.
Brogan.
Right?
There's a little bit of a thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Just kind of the most face and head you've ever seen.
But also like skull, neck and shoulders all being one.
Yeah.
There's a, oh my God, there's a side character in the first Despicable Me that Aaron said that he looks like.
And this is going to drive me crazy.
Who is it?
I put in an accountant.
I don't think it's someone with a mundane job.
Is it a lawyer?
No.
Yes.
Wait.
I think so.
What is this character's name?
Oh, it's in the TV tropes.
Oh, God.
Here, this guy.
Does anyone know who this is?
Oh, no.
There's some Taffer resemblance.
Yeah.
I don't know Despicable Me well enough.
Anyway.
So first things first.
Which animated character does Jon Taffer resemble the most?
I'm glad we're getting past this.
I think I texted this to you guys recently.
But the realization that his birthplace is Great Neck, New York, when he is perhaps the owner of the world's greatest neck.
Yeah.
If we're talking greatest as in most, does anyone have more neck?
Great as in mass.
Yes.
That's the home of Andy Kaufman, is it not?
I think that's where Andy...
Oh, wow.
Two of our greatest performance artists.
Right.
The ability to walk into a room and make people question reality.
Yeah.
Kind of a real life Tony Clifton.
Who was stuck that way.
That's another resemblance.
Is he, is Jon Taffer an alter ego of another more like, but not like a, like a nice figure who we've never gotten to meet?
Business man, Tony Clifton.
He's playing the long haul.
There's a nice, meek little guy operating that suit.
Yeah.
Is Great Neck, that's New York City suburbs, like Long Island area?
Nassau County, Long Island.
Nassau, okay.
Yes, North Shore.
Yes.
All right.
That kind of unlocks a lot of the screaming.
What about the voice?
You get it better now.
So let's talk a little bit about how we got here.
I think it's a voice we've been doing a lot.
I want to say that Mike was the first, but I think it was one of those that we, it like spoke to, it like caused us all to like, oh, that is a shared interest we didn't know we have.
I think we've all watched the show and enjoyed the show and enjoyed the explosive presence of this man who comes in and screams at bars until they change their name and then possibly change the name back three weeks later.
So I think this bit was happening for a long time.
There was plenty of shut it down.
I know one that really lingered was the thing you're obsessed with, Mike, where he yells about the guy's wife.
Yes.
He tells Harold at the Scottsdale Comedy Club, this is why your first wife left you.
This is why your first wife.
He goes, I'm going to be, I watch it.
He goes, I'm going to be rough with you.
This is why your first wife left you.
I'm sure someone on the Reddit will be able to carbon date the first time it came up in conversation.
I feel like I heard you guys all in real time realize that you shared the interest in Taffer.
And I think pretty soon after that, I messaged and said, I too am obsessed with Taffer.
It wasn't a I need to do this episode with you as much as a I endorse the idea that this should be a full fledged episode.
Yes, you were supportive of that regardless of participating.
I do think there's something here and I think it falls into some of my favorite PTR bits.
The ability to like drill down into the couple of conversational verbal go tos of a character and apply that to different subjects.
Right.
Sure. Yeah.
Yeah.
The sort of Kathy Bates like.
Oh, boy.
Late shift thing.
Right.
Which as well helps me, I think, work out aggression in a way.
Maybe that's true.
Maybe like us all fairly meek men, maybe like getting to live.
Right.
In a kushnik or a taffer for a little bit like helps like get something, get some of the inner anger gunk out.
And, you know.
Is it Kathy Bates?
I don't know.
This is maybe two inside.
The Kathy Bates character from Late Shift.
Is that your favorite character to perform on podcast?
Oh, yeah.
I can.
I feel like I can get lost in that.
Yeah.
Sure.
Have you have you dug down in her recently Critics' Choice award winning role of Matlock?
Now, Jason, I heard you're exploring CBS's Matlock.
You've been negotiating to watch one episode.
Let me tell you, I didn't know that was her.
I only saw the billboard far away.
And the other night.
You said to yourself, you tap Jane.
You go, who is this fresh face discovery?
I only saw the ads.
And then Jane was like, oh, Kathy Bates just won a big award.
And I looked it up.
I was like, oh, my God, she's Matlock.
I was just saying, who is going to fill Andy?
I sincerely would say, who is going to fill Andy Griffith's shoes?
Did you say that out loud to Jane?
And then did you say, who's Andy Griffith?
She said, please go back to bed.
That's the thing you say in the morning.
Who's going to fill Andy Griffith's shoes?
Your sleeping cap flies across the room like, don't wake daddy.
You said that in like an alma mater speech at your high school.
Yeah.
I look at you at the student body.
Which one of you is going to fill Andy Griffith's shoes?
We've been waiting 20 long years.
There's a lot of fishing and a lot of cricks to do.
Which of you is going to do it?
You see a bouchement in theaters.
You go, call me crazy.
Call me crazy.
But someday.
I think she's got it.
Look, I've clocked a lot of Matlock and diagnosed murder hours
when I was a kid of my grandparents, OK?
Those were the shows they like.
And then later on, they short-lived martial law.
I don't know if that was short-lived.
I think that was maybe by those standards.
I think martial law was a law.
Martial law only lasted eight seasons.
By CBS standards, you're right.
A failure.
Diagnosis murders 30 years or whatever.
Jason, do you know the hook of this new Kathy Bates Matlock?
Well, I bet she doesn't take any guff.
Mike, do you know where I'm going with this?
I believe I know.
Is she a computer simulation?
Is she AI or something?
It's some clunky ass convoluted explanation of like she was...
I'm going to say this very quickly because I also haven't watched it.
But the day it premiered, and the show seems to be doing very well.
Yeah, it seems like it.
She won a Craig's Choice Award.
She got up.
She said, this isn't just big for me.
It's big for network broadcast television.
So she and Tim Allen are saving network TV.
Shifting gears is going wild.
That's what I read.
So Matlock old folksy lawyer, right?
Gentile folksy lawyer.
Yeah.
They announced Kathy Bates.
Everyone goes, oh, the hook is just gender swap Matlock.
We've been here before.
Then the first episode premieres, and I see on Deadline, the shocking twist at end of Matlock premiere broke down.
Oh, my God.
And listeners, skip ahead if you don't want to hear, if you know Matlock spoilers.
We're now halfway through the season.
Jason, cover your ears.
So if people have watched any amount of this show, they know what the twist is at the end of the first episode.
There is a conceit twist from the get-go that was not in the marketing.
Lindsay told me this, and I can't remember it.
I believe the conceit is, oh, Kathy Bates, I'm folksy.
I'm Matlock.
I'm just an old lady.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Then you find out that she had a close relative, maybe a son, who died due to an opioid addiction.
And the law firm that she's working for represented the Sackler analogs in this universe.
And she's like fucking trying to get in from the inside and tear this whole fucking place down.
Oh, my God.
It is Opioid Crisis Revenge Matlock with Kathy Bates using this cover being like, oh, I'm on a CBS procedural.
I'm taking all these fuckers down.
Was she not a lawyer before?
I don't know.
She's just an angry mom.
But I'm like, there's maybe a little bit of, like, mushnik in the Matlock.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Kush, Kushnik?
Kushnik, sorry.
Close enough.
Even I couldn't place it for a second.
Kushnik.
It's very funny you say that because in the first or second episode of the new hit show that I have watched all of, Dr. Odyssey.
Of course.
Spoiler alert listeners.
Dr. Odyssey.
Dr. Odyssey is the show about Joshua Jackson playing a doctor on a very high end cruise ship.
Playing?
He's the head of medicine.
Head of medicine.
But is he really or is he playing one on a cruise ship?
The character in January.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Joshua Jackson is a false doctor on a cruise ship.
He's saying the role of a real doctor.
Okay.
Don Johnson's the captain?
Don Johnson's the captain.
And there's love boat, like, guest star roles.
So, like, Rachel Dratch is on one.
Oh, God, the guy from A Serious Man.
Michael Starbark?
No, the other one.
Richard Kind?
I keep going.
All right.
How many serious men can you name?
Ed Malamud is on one.
But the twist at the end of an episode is Dr. Odyssey reveals he did all this amazing charity work all around the world.
But then he's working at a hospital in Massachusetts where he was patient zero for the novel coronavirus.
What?
They spent a lot of months in isolation, like, until they could get it to...
The number one first person to get it?
He was number one.
He was Dr. Odyssey.
And is Dr. Odyssey his real name?
No, the name of the ship is the Odyssey.
His real name is Dr. Wuhan?
I might say he invented the virus himself.
In America, he was patient zero.
So that's the big twist.
Are you still watching Dr. Odyssey?
Well, it's not come back from its midseason break yet.
But you've seen all of it?
I've seen all of it.
Jason has been down in the dumps recently for that reason.
For that reason alone.
Yeah.
I want to amend an earlier statement, Jason.
Sure.
Tim Allen, Kathy Bates, and Jason Sheridan are single-handedly keeping network broadcast television alive.
Very good.
Yeah.
How many people are going to start...
And I was recommended Dr. Odyssey by this podcast.
And it has been...
I finally understand COVID in a way I never did before.
This is now a podcast about recommending network broadcast television shows.
Recommending things with approximately 200 times our audience.
It has not been a podcast about theme parks and gear.
Let's get some audience on these shows.
If we became a Shifting Gears recap podcast, that's when the money would roll in.
Yes.
And that is when all of America's most important political figures would start appearing on our shows.
They would have to be on our show.
And they'd go like, that's supporting Kath Denning, Sean William Scott.
Like, these aren't like spring chickens, you know.
What?
These aren't fresh new fish.
They are not fresh new faces.
Spring chickens.
Faces, they're pros.
Was that also when you saw Kathy...
Now, who's that on that billboard?
Is that a spring chicken or more of an autumn chicken?
Yeah.
Taffer is, just for me, one of the great Podcast the Ride bit run structure guys.
And you'll never devote a full episode to him, but sometimes you'll go into a sidebar of like,
imagine Taffer commenting on this subject or this situation.
And it always makes me happy.
And part of what makes me happy with it is that, and I'm going to join you guys in this.
The pressure's on now.
The four of us at the table, none of us do an even reasonably good Taffer impression.
I think that's fair.
You have fun doing a take on Taffer.
There's a game to how to do a Taffer.
But like, you had James Adomian on here.
He does a great Taffer.
It's a great casual impression.
That very much illustrated what a real one is, yeah.
All four of us, I think, are hobbyists in the sport of just yelling in a hoarse voice
and making extreme statements.
What the fuck are you talking about?
It's very well observed.
I understand what great neck is as opposed to just general New York.
This is very regional accurate.
You want to have a perspective on the character.
That Dana Carvey, George Bush, he was not necessarily accurate.
Accuracy isn't as funny sometimes.
You pick one or two things and you use that as your touchstone.
You exaggerate.
You blow it out from there.
It's just term and you wind it up and go.
What do you know about impression science?
David gives you shit about every goddamn impression you do.
I'm shutting you down.
Let's compare track records.
For me, I have to give my knowledge, at least at the start,
I will give it to Mike in his tastemaker role.
Excuse me?
Elaborate, please.
I like what he's saying, whatever it is.
Griffin dropped the bottle at Mike, the tastemaker.
This place has fallen apart.
Secure my water bottle.
He's trying to compliment me.
I am.
Sometimes, at least in the past, Mike would get really into something
and talk about it and show it to you.
I remember being over at your apartment.
You're like, have you seen this show?
You found it either on demand or at the time,
it was like 80% of Spike TV's programming.
It is addicting.
You made tastemaker for you.
That's what you're saying.
I don't know.
I'm just saying, I've looked at a lot of numbers involving a lot of puppets
and polls lately, and I think Mike, the tastemaker,
might be a questionable term.
It's got a big old pin in that one.
Oh, no, that's the entire episode unravels, if that's where we go.
You've got madam sins to answer for yourself.
Pin for later.
All right, I will break it down.
I trust my friend's taste.
We usually often see eye to eye.
And so, I agree with him.
Don't let him bully you.
That's what I do on the fucking show.
You're going to tell me to not do the thing that I do?
What does that leave me with?
People love my suggestions.
I've got to say, Scott's going full physical with his performance.
Apologies, I've been banging on the table.
Face red, arms flailing.
I'm trying to surf the levels on that Zoom.
It's a nightmare.
They know what they're getting into.
It's a Tapper episode.
Everyone trying to lean back from the mic.
We needed an engineer.
It's hard not to never having an engineer.
We should have hired an engineer for this episode.
This guy's doing Sonic the Hedgehog recordings in here.
What did that?
What the fuck did that mean?
That reference was too obscure, even for a currently relevant piece of IP.
I'll explain it later.
We'll put a pin in that, too.
Okay, second pin.
He made a naughty joke he shouldn't have made.
Oh, no.
I will say, though, I showed Jane a couple bar rescues last night
because she had never seen the show.
So I showed her what she wanted to see.
I said, oh, there's some in the San Fernando Valley.
There's a couple in Burbank.
So we watched some of those, and she got it immediately.
She was immediately on board.
Yeah, she understood the hypnotic.
Did she say who was the tastemaker who showed you the show?
Somebody with incredible taste must have made his taste
the way they would go in front of you.
I guess I'll just be the server waiter,
goes like, I'm not taking this, and then storms out.
They're like, I don't need this.
No, I like it.
Yells back at Tapper.
I like the compliments.
Do you, Jason and Mike, or Scott and Mike, excuse me,
remember your first exposure to Tapper, how you locked in?
Because I'm genuinely struggling to think of when he hit my radio.
I was no big fan.
All right, I will give some shine to Mike the tastemaker, I guess.
Thank you.
Because I think it was the thing I just watched a bunch of on a plane once,
and that was kind of all.
I wasn't really watching it regularly.
And I guess it is only post Mike the tastemaker bringing it up
and it becoming a runner that now it became like, well,
defaults at lunchtime, maybe I throw on the All Bar Rescue channel on Pluto.
Which is just...
If you don't know about it, Pluto TV has the...
I love every Pluto TV channel.
It doesn't matter what it is, but they have such...
I love blocks.
It's like Nick at Night when I was a child.
Cheaters that I can flip between All Cheaters and All Bar Rescue, my God.
What a world we live in.
Two Star Trek channels.
I discovered a Pluto channel the other night that is Cheers plus Frasier.
Wow.
And I was scanning what was coming up.
I love Cheers.
And I was like, oh, it's kind of later season episodes.
I prefer the earlier ones.
Let's see what's coming up for the next couple hours.
Going totally chronological.
Oh, really?
Presumably just does all 11 seasons of Cheers in order in a row,
which begs the question, are they alternating with Frasier days
or is this channel 11 seasons of Cheers in a row
and then like 11 seasons of Frasier and then back to the start?
That's like a full shift of format, essentially.
Right.
Like every week.
Is it every other week between the two shows running in their entirety?
I also know...
I've enjoyed Cheers when I've seen it, but I'm no expert.
And that's why I'm just going to throw it out.
If anybody else has any thoughts on what Taffer would say to the gang from Cheers.
Does anything come to mind is what he might criticize.
I took some notes.
I was doing some digging in some different areas.
I didn't quite make a research fort, but I tried my best.
We decided this was not a spacey-esque structured episode
where we're each coming with one piece.
We all were just trying to dig around and see if we found some interesting stuff.
I listened to a couple Taffer podcasts.
I was trying to get some more backstory of his own podcast.
I listened to one episode of each of his...
Multiple podcasts.
He had two podcasts that both ended.
He just signed a deal last week for two new podcasts that will launch later this year.
But he's in between podcasts.
So I listened to episode of both.
I also listened to Taffer on Rob Lowe's Literally podcast.
And Taffer on the Idiot podcast.
The former Nerdist.
I listened to some of that as well.
And I think it was in the Rob Lowe episode I actually had the best meet in it,
but I just need to throw this out.
Rob Lowe was asking how he got started.
How he made the transition to TV, rather.
And he said, well, I was friends with a bunch of the people at Paramount
because I used to work with Paramount.
And Rob Lowe said, what do you mean?
And he said, you know, they had restaurants and stuff.
So I would consult on like Bubba Gump.
I was instrumental in Bubba Gump.
Which you guys knew, right?
But then him bringing it up as I worked with Paramount for many years.
I was like, Taffer must have fucking consulted on Cheers at some point.
He didn't say it.
And Lowe kind of cut him off.
Once he said Bubba Gump, he was like, Bubba Gump, does Tom Hicks get a piece of that?
Like then he just jumped on to that.
Sure, as we might.
But yeah, you're right.
You remember the corporate family.
Paramount restaurant chains?
50-50 shot Taffer consulted on Cheers at some point.
Did he have anything to do with the Cheers airport bars with the animatronics that got sued?
I'm just like, we need to follow the trail on this.
He couldn't immediately find any results.
But he didn't say, I worked on Bubba Gump.
He said, I worked with Paramount for years.
Because what other Paramount restaurants exist?
The Quarks bar in Las Vegas.
Oh my god.
But that seems like the kind of shit he would hate.
You're dressed up like space people.
You look ridiculous.
I know he's not a Star Trek fan because I listened to his audio book about conflict.
By the way, I don't want to cut you off.
We're all bringing so much to the table.
For the runtime, I think it's important to remember that this is Taffer 1.
Because I think we're all going to get through a tenth of what we're bringing to the table.
The power of conflict.
I had no idea the power of conflict was on the table.
Speak your mind and get the results you want.
Scott, this is why I texted last night.
I said, any guidelines for structure?
You said free for all.
Everything's on the table.
We're not attempting to get through all of it.
But everything was on the table.
He uses the famous Star Trek episode, City on the Edge of Forever, to prove that conflict is good.
And he says, even though I'm not a Trekkie, he explains that he's not a Trekkie.
He uses that episode, very popular, famous original series episode, to prove that a war doesn't happen and then things go bad.
So it proves that the conflict is good.
Military conflict is good.
We should be in every war. We're not in enough wars.
Wasn't Roddenberry's whole thing, like, kind of trying to make a sci-fi show with as little conflict as possible?
Yes, correct.
That was sort of his, like, life's mission?
A peaceful future, yes.
Yeah, the vibe is very polite.
Yes, there's no money, there's no conflict.
They found it hard to write Next Generation because he put rules on, like, the people cannot have conflict.
And then he dies and then the show gets a little better.
Yeah.
Like, the rules loosen a little bit for what the characters can do.
No one wants peace in the Space Federation!
He also explains that great music has come out of conflict.
Go on.
Including the Rolling Stones, Fleetwood Mac, and even the Beach Boys!
He addressed the Beach Boys in his book?
Yes, he talks about how the Beach Boys had conflict and they created wonderful music.
Although, I think the music gets worse the more...
Their commercial prospects go down as they're fighting more.
I don't know if that's exact.
Yeah, I don't know. That's a mixed bag.
But Fleetwood Mac, for sure. Can't argue that.
We all know that he started as a drummer, too, right?
I have. I do know that.
I do have a photo in front of me of him in his band days.
Here is a black and white photo of kind of a little bit of a retro throwback greaser guy, young John Taffer.
Like a bowman, a John Bowser bowman.
He is very Bowser from Sha-Na-Na-esque, I would say.
And he, in fact, described this band that he was the drummer of as being a little bit like the stray cats.
He is after my heart now.
Conflict! What gives the ride thrives on conflict?
That's why you have one who doesn't like the stray cats and the others...
I don't know how they feel, but it's fun to fight them at the stray cats.
You've got to get on board. You've got to rock this town tonight!
Not tomorrow! Not in five years!
I don't embrace excuses about rocking this town. I embrace solutions.
I embrace the rocking of the town.
That photo, he is looking pretty fit and thin.
It is alarming how much his neck is still twice as wide as his head.
It's an unbelievable...
It's very long in this. This shows you that the neck is quite long.
Right, yes, yes.
It is pro wrestler neck.
Yes. It's wild, yeah.
But I'm like, in that photo, it's like he looks kind of beanpole-ish.
Where you're like, the neck is not muscle, it is not fat.
That is just his basic construction.
He's sort of built like a popsicle stick man with arms and legs.
It's what made me good at observing what happens at bars,
because my neck allows me to get up above where other people can see.
I can see everything that's going wrong.
I can see all the roaches. I can see the bugs in the bottles.
Much wants the bottles lit from underneath.
But I can't install them. I'm too tall.
Somebody's balls got to go down and do it.
In the early credits, opening credits of Bar Rescue,
which you see the show change a lot over the years,
the narrator in the opening credits is so reserved
and doesn't really find the full this voice.
Yes, yeah.
But they say something.
There's a moment in the credits where it's like the bar science
from the height of the stools to where your eyes first go on the menu.
And I'm like, I do not remember menu eye lines.
I see it. I don't remember it.
It's when they have on a menu, they'll have like a little thing in a rectangle
and they want your eye to go to that to order that
because that's where they usually make the most money.
And I don't remember if I learned that from Jon Taffer
or from one of my other restaurant guys.
You're never happy with just one type of guy.
Yeah, Robert Earl. I don't know.
I mean, I shouldn't say my guys.
Yeah, they dropped that.
That was like a subtlety in the early opening
that just kind of gave way to like just showing people
having full meltdowns in the beginning for a while.
They use that.
Slamming windows.
Yeah, they use that voiceover guy for the Jon Taffer podcast.
Yes, which I love.
So he still has an intro that's very bar rescue-ish.
Is it called No Excuses?
That was the first one.
That's the first one.
And then I think the second one was just called the Jon Taffer podcast.
Yes, and he has like interviews with people like Guy Fieri
or Guy Fieri and Kristin Chenoweth.
The one I listened to was,
is live entertainment coming back with Caratop?
Yes, Caratop's on that.
It's a lot of COVID era stuff.
It's a real fucking time capsule in a way that's a little upsetting.
It is not a great listen.
I listened to, there's an episode of that show
that's the first episode of 2020.
2020 is going to be your year.
Do not embrace excuses.
He was talking to the virus.
He's talking to everybody.
And it's just Taffer going like,
I'm telling you, this year, anything you want to do, you can accomplish it.
On that show in particular, he does a little bit of NPR voice,
which is very unnerving.
Yes, he does.
Yeah, he's like another guy on the podcast.
He's trying to prove that I have another mode.
I'm actually smart.
Very together and very calm.
2020, I got great feelings about this.
The economy is in a great place.
I think divisiveness is down.
He's got a sidekick on the show.
Is it Jamie, who he goes like,
Chase, you know what I'm talking about here?
Is it Chase?
It's not.
Or is it Cory?
It might be Cory.
I think it's Cory.
And he goes, Cory, do you know what I'm talking about here?
It feels like people have calmed down.
The era of peak divisiveness is gone.
We're all starting to get a lot.
January 2020.
He goes, people just had Thanksgiving.
I think families aren't fighting as much.
I watched the Golden Globes.
Not too much politics.
But in this very quiet voice, he's like,
2020, I'm telling you, I think everyone's going to calm down in 2020.
My good pal, my good friend, the doctor,
got a great job on a cruise ship called the Odyssey.
It's going to work out fantastically.
He just caught a little bug, and then he's getting on that ship.
Once he works out this cough, it's a billion dollars for this guy.
I listened to something in the start of 2023, one of those,
and he is in the same way you're discussing,
where he's like, everything's going to be good in this year.
He starts talking about the great success of Taffer's Tavern,
and how many locations they have,
and how Las Vegas is coming.
January 2020, it's unbelievable.
Las Vegas is coming soon.
We're rejecting franchise applications.
We can't handle all these requests.
I looked at, there is an episode that is October 28th, I believe, of 2020
that is the state of businesses with President Donald J. Trump.
I was like, fuck, this feels like maybe the most fruitful thing to dig into,
and I actually don't think I can listen to 45 minutes of this
without having a nervous breakdown.
Trump one week before the 2020 election with Taffer
explaining how America's coming back.
And it's a lot of like, and I need you to promise, Mr. President,
because we need you.
We need minimum wage kept low so these lazy people don't get too comfortable.
Well, he addresses his political beliefs while he does it on the podcast,
but he addresses political beliefs in the power of conflict.
He explains that he is a fiscal conservative,
but he's very socially liberal.
He explains he supports all the different people.
I grew up in the rock and roll scene.
You can't be a conservative in rock and roll music.
Not only that, the big formation of the John Taffer legacy
is him becoming the manager of the Troubadour, running the Troubadour for years, right?
Yes.
And he always likes to underline that was the black flag, dead Kennedys, Adam Anthony.
We are past the, yeah, the Troubadour famous nightclub in LA,
been around since the 70s, or really like peaked culturally in the 70s
with like gentle singer-songwriters, like the birthplace of James Taylor.
He talked about doing an anniversary event where they convinced
Ronstadt and Jackson Brown to come back,
but Taffer, failed rock drummer, was overseeing all these early punk guys,
which just feels like the most incompatible vibe,
even more so than the singer-songwriters.
Yeah, he came in, not in the early days of Troubadour,
but in the punk era, dead Kennedys and Fear.
And was the guy to put the foot down and be like,
as he put it, you gotta pay for that steak!
And he said all the audiences would fight,
like the Fear fans wanted to crush the ants.
They wanted to crush the ants.
Oh, that referring to Adam Ant,
because New Wave people hate punk people,
so they'd be fighting night after night.
Taffer talking to Lee Ving, who was the lead singer of Fear, is insane to me.
But it doesn't make sense, I could hear Taffer definitely kicking off of Fear style.
Yeah, he could have been in a punk band too.
I wonder if he thought about it then.
Fuck you Reagan!
I'm only fiscally conservative, fuck Ronald Reagan!
The socially liberal thing feels like it starts there,
where it's like, look, as long as you're bringing them in, I don't care.
If it's good for business, I don't care.
You have to imagine he's seeing these bands every night and being like,
I don't fucking get this shit.
But if they respect me and they sell tickets, I don't care!
If they aren't being overboard too!
He's name-checking a lot of these.
He's done a couple interviews of his nature,
and like, wow, just incredible, groundbreaking punk bands,
and you were around, and he's like, yes, but you know who was really great?
You know who I really loved? The Knack.
When those guys, when they kicked into My Sharona,
the whole building shook.
That bass line, there was magic in that bass line.
So My Sharona was his favorite.
Yeah, The Knack's good, but that's just a funny...
Of all the ones to shout out, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's all well and good,
The Knack.
My Sharona.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
What were you going to say, Jason?
I was going to say, was the troubadour before or after another L.A. landmark, Barney's Beanery?
Well, he started it, I think, I don't know what opened when,
but his first job was bartender at Barney's Beanery,
which is also in West Hollywood.
It was a Burbank location with the originals in West Hollywood.
This is notable as this bar used to be like this was kind of the end of Route 66.
Yes.
Where this bar was.
And then eventually they either opened up other locations or franchised,
and now they're kind of everywhere.
But the first location was in Radiator Springs, is that right?
Barney's oil rig.
So, but I'm glad we're touching on this history because, yeah,
so bartender at Barney's Beanery, and he must have kicked them off,
he must have done something right because it's still there.
Then you saw the troubadour through a big wave of success,
then moved to a, you ever heard of this, Jason, Philadelphia nightclub, this is Delaware County,
a nightclub called Pulsations.
Anybody know about Pulsations?
I do.
Delaware County is where I grew up.
Oh, okay, gotcha.
Delco, they say.
Delco, yeah, mayor of Easttown, sat there.
Does Pulsations have a little friend in there, maybe?
It does.
Do you know about the little friend?
Pulsations?
Well, it's kind of a big friend.
Mike, do you know about the room?
I actually don't.
Oh, Mike.
This is pretty wild that his history, and I'm sure, you know,
not that we have to justify any connection to theme parks
or the things that we're theoretically supposed to be talking about,
but we do have a pretty good one here.
Taffer maybe ties back to Cheers Airport Bar and Taffer.
He might, he might.
Certainly ties back to a classic friend of PTO.
Yes, yeah, so this nightclub is called Pulsations.
It was a sci-fi nightclub.
There was a giant spaceship in it, 27 feet in diameter, 70 lighting systems in it.
It would fly over the crowd at an I-beam track.
People would cry.
I had listened to three different podcasts where he described it and said,
people, tears in their eyes.
They'd try to get on it like Close Encounters.
I want to live here forever, they'd say.
They want to abandon their families.
They didn't know it didn't actually leave.
It was so realistic.
They'd leave Terry Garner in the dust.
But the main thing is the door would open, dry ice fog, bright lights would blast,
and out would come a robot.
A robot would come out of the spaceship every night.
The name of the robot is Pulsar.
And I will let his quote say it.
It got so popular that they had a clone built for Rocky IV.
This robot that we've talked about, that one robot.
Seiko.
Seiko, he claims Seiko was made, I think he's wrong on that.
I don't know what's going on.
Taffer does seem to be a fabulous in listening to a bunch of different stories.
I've noticed every time the telling changes 25%.
I heard three podcasts where he said, and then they rented the robot from us,
and that's the robot in Rocky IV.
But then if you look it up, it says the story is that Sylvester Stallone's autistic son
encountered a Seiko, and it was helpful for communication,
and that's why it's in Rocky IV.
Seiko was a thing.
Here's my take on the story as he's presenting it.
They, too, found a Seiko and purchased one, or commissioned one.
Seiko was a thing that was being made for multiple applications.
International Robotics.
I'm sorry.
International Robotronics.
A shop in New York.
Much cooler name.
My guess is that he bought a Seiko.
He didn't create it at a nightclub.
No.
And then Stallone put Seiko in Rocky IV.
He's like, must have taken it from me.
But sometimes he's saying they cloned our robot.
Sometimes he's saying we rented them the robot.
Yeah.
Oh, so sometimes he claims that the robot in Rocky IV is.
I heard two separate podcasts where he said that.
That's weird.
This one says it was so popular.
That's a Philadelphia connection, right?
That does make sense.
That adds up.
Maybe I saw it.
Now, to refresh my memory, I know we talked about this on the show.
I think it was in the episode about Smart One.
But what was Seiko had an Epcot connection?
Am I making that up?
Or did we?
Why did we end up talking about Seiko in relationship to.
Is Seiko in the.
Yeah.
The special?
The special with Danny Thomas?
Or is it Thomas?
Danny.
Danny Kay or Danny Thomas?
Which Danny?
Don't know.
I don't remember how we got there.
We ended up with Monomy Seiko, the single that Seiko had.
That's right.
YouTube recommended it to me last night.
OK, OK.
I mean, but I.
Anyway, sometimes it's named Seiko.
Cut out of Rocky IV.
But Taffer claims.
Taffer claims.
Cut out of sex.
Rocky IV.
Out of some.
The final cut or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
But.
But says Taffer.
You have the toy?
I have the toy.
Oh, I have the Super 7 one.
Right, yeah.
Because you remember, Jax had a prototype, but it never got released.
Oh, right, right, right.
They were supposed to do a Seiko and a James Brown in their second series of Rocky IV specific
figures.
Oh yeah, because this robot also introduced James Brown in concert.
That's a video I watched last night.
There was an unproduced Rocky IV James Brown action figure that was solicited.
That's good.
And never, never actually hit the factory line, unfortunately.
Oh my God.
Anyway, so Seiko, according to Taffer, and there's a video of this.
You could watch this on YouTube.
Seiko's name in this version was Pulsar.
And he came out of a big spaceship.
And so says Jon Taffer.
Pulsations.
It was the greatest nightclub in the world.
And I am honored to be part of that history.
The greatest nightclub in the world ever is where you grew up.
I'm crying.
That's right.
Seiko, by the, yeah, just to confirm, it is Danny Kay and also Drew Barrymore.
That's why.
Met Seiko at the Epcot opening day special.
So they needed a little extra robot help, even though that's a robot that would not
stay at Epcot.
So really, if we want, again, we don't have to, but the justification for talking about
him on a Theme Park podcast is that he, you know, he's an older man at this point.
He is probably influenced chain, crap, robot type, touristy garbage stuff that we love.
Yeah, I think so.
Well, and there's another gigantic reason to talk about him.
And it is this.
I bet I bet you didn't even know that this guy is an Imagineer.
Let me prove it.
Here we go.
I want to thank Disney Imagineering for this incredible Christmas basket and also for making
me an honorary Imagineer.
Thank you, Disney.
Done.
Did you know that?
He is more, I think he's more on topic than a lot of things that we talk about.
He is an honorary Imagineer.
This is him at his office and he's got a big, he's got a big basket.
It looks like it has an Imagineering shirt in it and mouse ears in it.
And yeah, look, this guy, who, who is, who has the title at Disney to make that call
for an honorary Imagineer?
Just Walt.
Only Walt.
So the robot, maybe the Walt robot now has that power.
Look at this Frasier.
Feces.
Walt's head.
Disgusting.
You're not taking care of it.
It's not going to, it's not going to touch back to his body.
You got Walt next to meat.
Nothing.
You're storing old chicken in there.
The bacteria is getting into Walt's nostrils.
You let his soul escape to hell.
Feces.
Nothing about this restaurant says Tomorrowland.
It's barely a terrace.
It's horrible.
Let me, here's, let's, let's keep going with the massive Disney connection.
As if we had to prove any further than that this guy's an honorary Imagineer.
This guy, let's quote him, the man himself.
I'm a Walt Disney World nutcase.
The Neutron ride knocks it out of the bar.
Here's him riding the Tron light cycles.
He's a nutcase.
We haven't even called ourselves that.
No.
Here's him in the Millennium Falcon.
Look at that.
He goes there all the time.
He was at the opening.
He was, you know, the, the opening where, with Harrison and Hamill where they,
where they got the cue wrong.
He's, Harrison banged on the thing all weird that he was at that.
He has photos of that.
So I think there's a lot of credentials he has here.
He also credits, in general, Walt Disney and all of their operations as being one of his primary areas of inspiration.
Walt Disney, Walt Disney had an apartment above Disneyland where he would watch the entrance gates.
The turnstiles, you might, the old style turnstiles.
They weren't tap styles yet.
Anyway, he could see the facial expressions of people entering and exiting the park.
Disney was the pioneer of reaction management.
He created the human transaction experience.
What a way.
And then he made transactions twice the price.
I, I.
He invented transactions, Walt Disney.
That's what gets him really excited.
The mouse and the big whale and the roller coasters.
Who cares?
He invented transactions.
I had never heard.
I've heard a million times about the Disneyland apartment above the firehouse.
I had never heard it referred to as like rear window style.
He would watch them and wonder what they were doing.
And note the beautiful, beautiful ladies and hoped that their hubbies were treating them right.
Binoculars in one hand, a can of cold Denison's chili in the other.
And he's just scooping.
I hope that Taffer buys the apartment above every single bar he's ever rescued.
So I can watch their smiling faces.
He, the reaction management thing, he was getting into it in the Hardwick episode where he was saying,
I believe that he, he grew up with a very emotionally erratic to say the least mother.
And then he said, from a young age, I learned reaction management because I had to keep her happy.
It wasn't something I even knew I was doing.
And later I realized I have a skill for it.
And then he said to Rob Lowe, we're both in the reaction business.
And he goes, what do you mean?
He goes, the product we're making, we're not in the business of bars or making movies or TV shows.
We're in the business of making reactions.
The product isn't the thing we make.
It's the reaction that people have to the thing.
It's not about making a movie.
It's about making a reaction.
And then he asks Rob Lowe 20 questions about the scene in Tommy Boy where his shirt gets sucked up the pneumatic.
He goes, that's the funniest thing I've ever seen in a movie.
How do you do that?
And to sit there in the theater, oh, the reaction you must have gotten.
Now I heard you were on the Doughboys podcast recently.
What was the reaction to that like?
You made quite a reaction there.
Here's another thing I like about Taffer.
I was trying to, I always have struggled to find the language to describe what it is I find so fascinating about him.
We talk about physical appearance.
We've been trying to emulate his voice.
The body language, the movement of the man, right, is so unique.
He moves unlike anyone else.
The way he floats through a space just like chest way out as he's floating.
Especially for how large he is, right?
Like he's just like physically imposing man.
And then he has this sort of very odd, yes, kind of floatiness to him.
I think I finally cracked it last night.
He moves like a hand puppet.
And I will explain what I mean by this.
The way that like a puppet can't make micro expressions, right?
Because by design, unless you're putting like significant sort of like mechanics or animatronics or like rigs in there or whatever,
you're basically like a hand puppet where your hand operates the mouth and you can scrunch it a little and try to make it look angry or whatever.
You notice like the muppets, there's a lot of head and neck acting because they need to sell the emotions with the full body.
And also because like a puppeteer only has two hands.
The main one's the head and the mouth.
And then like they're usually puppeteering one of the arms.
If a character has to use two arms at the same time, you have another person just supplying that.
But very often you have a puppet who has like one of their arms kind of glued to their chest.
And the other arm is moving really wildly.
John Taffer's right arm never moves.
Very often.
Sometimes he'll do the full Kermit like arm flap, right?
Which requires the second puppeteer.
But very often one arm is like straight by his side or across his chest or pocket.
And he's like doing this where you're just like, man, they're overselling the arm in the head because they have to make this thing look like it's alive.
And the way he's talking to anyone, any reaction shot of him listening to someone's troubles is like, yeah, that's right, isn't it?
Like he tilts his head all the way down.
The camera can't see my feet.
I ain't got to do nothing with those.
Yes, it's incredible.
But unlike a puppet, he is flexing every single muscle in his face at all times.
Like he's always pulling the most extreme expression.
It looks like his body is exerting the most effort possible.
It's worrisome to some degree how much energy he must be expelling just when he's talking to somebody about the scale that weighs the bottles, the drink bottles.
Even his quiet moments where he's trying to show compassion for people.
Yeah.
And he's like, so you gave up.
You lost your way.
You know, and his whole body is just like a rocket about to take off and his eyebrows are all the way up here.
That's not how a successful marriage works.
You're a good man.
I respect you.
He's just I mean, there's a thing he does.
We pegged it early on is that when he's talking, he's explaining something.
He goes like this.
He takes his arm or he takes his hand and he goes like this and he almost like cups and invisible ball like a basketball.
He always does this.
And I don't know why, but he's been doing it since the start because it's a good place to pin the puppet arm.
It's what it's kind of natural.
Right.
It looks right.
And then you can put the arm somewhere else and move a different person.
He's just what I think what is so engaging about him is just you've never seen a more fully formed specific character like this.
Even like he Joe Pesci and all the Martin Scorsese movies wishes he was this like weird and scary when he's talking to somebody like you've just this.
He would you would be almost too much with him in a movie.
Well, here's another thing.
You're making me realize it.
All of us are dirty, dirty sketch comedy monsters.
Right.
We come from the sketch comedy filth.
Sure.
And this is just like an area.
Right.
This is an immediately fully realized sketch comedy character.
It's unreal.
You can drop him into any scenario.
He's got a look.
He's got a voice.
He's got five games.
It's not just one.
Right.
Yes.
And they all work and they have some games.
Right.
Where you're like it's that feeling of watching Matt Foley for the first time.
Yes.
You're like holy shit.
Wow.
He is Chris Farley.
Not Chris Farley like vibe whatsoever.
Right.
But amount of physicality and presence.
I think of Matt Foley as kind of being like the pinnacle of like sketch comedy characterization.
Right.
He lost in the online poll to Stefan on the NBSNL.
What are you talking about?
There was they did a whole brackets.
Yes.
They had all these different voting and he lost.
He was a final two with Stefan and Matt Foley.
Let's say that's recently pious.
The original Matt Foley sketch which is the one they did at Second City for years and
years and years that Odin Kirk wrote that was so honed at that point that it was just
like a perfect diamond cut thing.
Right.
Is for my money the best thing SNL ever put on there.
Might be number one best.
I think it's just like the tightest most perfectly executed especially with the live element
where you're like the one they got was by all accounts the best it was ever performed.
It's lightning in a bottle.
Yeah.
When I rewatch it I'm like huh were the other ones not as good and you watch them and they're
all good.
Right.
Like there's no like oh fuck they tried it again and it fell.
No they never did.
But I know what you mean.
That's true.
Because they all are kind of the same.
Right.
Like one is A plus plus and then the rest are all like B plus.
Totally.
Yeah.
And they'll do other moves and they're funny ones in there but I always think of like oh
Spade flipping it to him.
What do you want to do when you grow up.
I want to live in a van down by the river.
I don't remember if he says it or the apple.
You're like that's the kind of joke you think you get to the fifth time you do the character
and they got there in the first one.
Right.
Taffer enters at a first Matt Foley sketch level.
Oh true.
With catchphrases.
You watch the first episode anytime I've shown Taffer to someone they immediately go like
holy shit he's like this all the time.
And then you go but clearly you must be showing me the best episode he can't be this good
all the time.
Taffer is like what if every Matt Foley sketch was the first Matt Foley sketch.
Wow.
Yeah it is.
It is a pretty fully formed that first episode.
Yeah.
It's like all the pieces.
How is it different.
Is it less aggressive in general.
It's a little less of aggressive.
The narrator is less aggressive.
They are explaining the concept of the show.
A little.
And then new stuff comes along later on.
I feel like it gets much slicker and I feel like there's more sponsorship.
It's not as good anymore.
I hate to bring that in.
Newer ones are just there's something missing.
So I.
Bar Rescue is one of the things that I use as a very depressive person to sort of gauge
how my mental health is doing.
Where if I find I've been in a three day hole of watching Bar Rescue and Paramount Plus
I'm like oh I'm going through something.
But if you're doing a three hour podcast episode about it you're having the time of
your life.
And if I'm watching it's productive.
It's for research.
But I'm like there's something I find very comforted in watching Bar Rescue.
This goes back to my read on being a show about depression where basically the through
line of every episode is that like the people running the bar are really depressed and have
sort of like stopped giving a shit to some degree or another.
Or like can't find the will to like do the hard work anymore.
Although sometimes they're like I'm pulling my tits out and they love it.
They love to pull their tits out.
This is true.
They hate when that's robbed from them.
I would argue though there is perhaps a core sadness.
Maybe some depression in there somewhere.
I think there's usually some level of sadness.
Depression and also no education or no training.
Yes.
About how a restaurant works or how a how to tend bar.
That's a good delineation.
It's the sort of like be fun to own a restaurant or bar.
Like almost every Bar Rescue starts with that energy.
Yeah.
The next story for the place is I thought it'd be fun.
I thought it'd be easy.
I got in a business with two people.
You know I didn't know them that well.
We were friendly enough at the time.
Or I knew them too well.
There's always you always like not always maybe on every episode but like the one eye
the Scottsdale that's the that's in my mind the gold standard.
But it's every like so many episodes have these just sad tragedies just immediately.
And it's like Harold this guy is going to he's a stand up comic and he's just so sad.
And this guy sunk a hundred and other guys sunk one hundred and eighty thousand dollars
into this comedy club and was like Harold's the face of it.
And then this guy's just kind of a meek guy and John's yelling at him about like you're
emboldening him.
You're not helping.
And he's like yeah no I guess so.
And then like Harold's sister is there and she's crying.
Like there's immediately these like epic like family dramas unfold on these episodes.
By the way why of course Paramount was like we should have him do Marriage Rescue a show
that makes perfect sense on paper because you're like that is the core of the thing
of him yelling at depressed people and being like stop lying.
Right.
But it is not as fun to see him in Puerto Rico.
No no.
With like one couple.
And the other problem with that show which I'd never watched before is like he basically
does one check in every 10 minutes and then he's like I'm sending you out on a challenge.
And then they go like boogie boarding and he's not with them.
And he needs to be over the guy's shoulder.
Kiss your wife.
Give her compliments.
You don't stand up on boogie boards.
You're laid down on them.
And you don't stand up in conversation either.
Point out the sunset.
OK this is a thing I think that comes into the show kind of later still pretty early
but where it's like there's family dynamics or there's there's husband and wife dynamics
and they bring in a counselor or a therapist and for show purposes it gets wrapped up in
five minutes when that sort of counseling takes ages and ages.
Not when it's me.
Three days.
I know a marriage expert and if not I do it myself.
That's the thing about marriage expert that it seems to be the selling point seems to
be like I'm a bar expert but I'm also a marriage expert.
You know why?
Because I'm in a marriage.
Plenty.
Marriage rescue he does not outsource to anyone.
Any greater authority than him.
He is the guy.
He's not around a lot.
All the hard conversations funnel through him.
The one I watched was the last episode they ever did because it did one season in 2019.
A short season.
It was a short season.
Quickly this wasn't working.
Any chance of it coming back was probably killed immediately by the pandemic of like
yeah right.
This whole thing is like luxury getaway whatever.
But the one I watched was two couples.
One of them is two stand up comedians.
Always fertile territory for Taffer to take down a yuckster.
But the other one.
You're hiding in your bits.
Is a guy who's become addicted to DMs on social media.
And the whole thing is has he crossed the line into the physical though?
And they keep asking him have you and then he with like the biggest treasure cat grin
is like I have never since I met you stuck my dick in another woman.
And he's grinning ear to ear.
And Taffer's like you're a lion.
You're a lion in my face.
I got a test.
I have a challenge that's going to settle this once and for all.
And you're like holy shit.
What does Taffer have up his sleeve?
A lie detector test.
He just bends in a polygraph test right.
Three questions.
Are you in Puerto Rico right now?
Yes.
Do you DM women on social media?
He says no.
A thing he has previously already admitted to in the one episode.
And then question three is has it crossed into a physical realm with any of those women
or maybe have you cheated on your wife ever?
And he says no.
And the woman holds the printout and she goes you lied about the cheating question.
And he goes I didn't.
I didn't.
And he's smiling.
And Taffer goes you're a lion.
You're a lion.
He refuses to admit it.
The segment just ends.
Then they go to another challenge where they're like fucking like on RVs or whatever.
Like painting rocks or whatever.
It's entirely, it's marriage is being solved through amenities that are just at the resort.
Correct.
You're having a lot of trouble.
You aren't communicating.
You know what you got to do?
You got to make your own pizza.
Yes.
But then he's not there for the pizza.
No he doesn't do that.
He'll say that in voiceover and then you'll just see someone else be like hello I'm a pizza expert.
I got a nice lunch scheduled.
I'm going to the way better resort that didn't give us a deal up the coast.
Pizza is a popular food introduced in Italy and perfected in America.
Using a very hot oven.
I guess they have this segment that is like they have to renew their vows and decide whether or not the marriage is rescued or whether they're giving up on it.
And the woman like gives like reads this tearful written speech about like I am willing to accept you back and forgive you for the mistakes and for cheating on me.
And then he just goes like thank you for for your tolerance or something like that.
He the whole episode never admits that he has cheated on her even though he clearly has.
He denies it the entire time.
And then when she says I forgive you he goes I accept and I'm like and very good.
Well that was ends like marriage rescue.
Cool.
Look as long as it happens within the three days it goes enough for me.
But like yes.
So what I was going to say here is I'll go down these like three day rabbit holes of depression watching the show where I think I'm like I feel something in Taffer being like.
Snap out of it.
You gotta get to work.
You end up with an angel and devil on your shoulder.
Devil is loud Taffer.
Angel is slightly quieter podcast Taffer.
It eventually like gets me out of my funk.
There's something cathartic to it.
Right.
I continue to do these.
I fall into these Taffer holes a couple of times a year.
I have not.
I don't think I had watched a single episode post pandemic because a lot of TV shows.
Produced post pandemic you mean.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'll go on Paramount Plus.
I'll scale the mountain.
I'll watch any of my favorite episodes from the first like six seasons.
Stephen Colbert is up here too.
And the South Park kids.
Come on.
And Dorothy Explorer.
This I want to interject.
This is a little confusing.
On Paramount Plus.
First season is like 10 episodes.
Yes.
Ninth season is like 40 episodes.
Yeah they ran way up.
Way up.
Because I was like there's gotta be 13 seasons at this point.
I was like Paramount only has nine and I'm like oh the later ones are crazy.
I saw an announcement that like they just announced it was renewed for season 10 this week.
That is the official number.
The announcement was like after that.
They may already be out by this.
This month whenever we're putting this episode out.
Season 10 is about to launch.
So get ready for three days of depression.
The Taffer seasons do tend to average 40 episodes.
Which means there are favorites I can go back to over and over again.
But I also constantly like oh I don't think I've seen this one.
Like digging through the old ones.
Most reality shows or I'll just even say shows that reflect reality in any way during the pandemic.
I was like I don't want to watch pandemic episodes of anything.
I don't want to watch television with people wearing masks and talking about working through this.
And I was like I could see this being fertile for bar rescue and being like the bars need me more than ever.
But I didn't want to watch them.
And so I've just never wanted to venture into the post pandemic episodes.
Last night I was like I should watch a nine.
If we're going to talk Taffer one.
I should watch at least one nine just to sample the current batch.
This is one you got to do a nine.
Watch a nine.
For one. Watch one nine.
For Taffer nine.
I'll watch all of one.
I'm excited for Taffer nine.
Let me call it.
Taffer nine is going to be good.
By the way are you asserting that you are always on them?
Maybe.
Do you ever do episodes about theme parks ever again?
Am I going to be the Evan Susser of Taffer?
Oh yeah yeah.
It's the yearly Taffer check in.
Well so we've lost.
You no longer talk about theme park attractions.
Weiger does not seem interested in doing so.
We're losing a lot of the big ones.
I'll say this.
Eva doesn't really do theme park.
Look every time I come on here I say there is a pure theme park topic.
There were like three years of kicking this down the curb.
That's going to happen.
That means a lot to multiple members of this crew.
A childhood favorite of mine and a big one.
So I watched this episode of nine.
The thing I knew and I feel like we've been texting about this without seemingly any of us watching it seriously.
Is that nine is the season where he starts not being in every episode.
Oh shit.
It's like a Hot Ones thing too where they do Hot Ones now where it's not the guy.
Right.
Which I'm like if Taffer's gone from this.
What's the point?
The format's whatever.
Right.
Like the format is sturdy.
But like what I'm here for is Taffer and a lot of his regular rotation of experts are just now going in without him.
And you have to look on Paramount Plus.
Obviously if he's in the thumbnail he's in it.
But the description will either say John Sends or John Visits.
Right.
That's a trick.
That's like putting a pretty lady in the thumbnail and then I watch it because I want to see a pretty lady.
But then it was a lie and there was no.
At least they tend to be honest you're saying.
Yes.
I watched the last one of season nine.
The most recent episode at the time of our recording.
And he now seemingly is only in a third of the episode.
So his workload is lessened.
And I hadn't watched a couple of years and I don't think it's advanced stage.
But I was just like the anger seems a little forced.
He's still doing the thing.
Yeah.
And it doesn't feel like oh no he's slowed down.
In a way that makes me sad for like the passage of time.
Yeah.
It just felt like he's phoning it in a little bit.
That's pretty depressing.
Well I'm like if you're telling me that he doesn't want to do the full season anymore I want it to be because he's like look I only have so much anger left.
I want to give each episode all I can.
Well that's like in our season nine I'll be like you guys I don't want to talk about Frank Marshall.
And you can just tell I don't have it in me.
I just don't.
It just doesn't have the verve.
You're defeated.
You're dead inside.
I'm sick of I love Lucy guys.
Gary Morton.
Lucy's second husband.
You.
Why are you supposed to talk about theme parks were.
Why do you have so many thoughts about Lucy's feelings on her second marriage.
Mike the tastemaker.
That's ridiculous.
This actually sounds good.
Yeah.
Because I'll still have my juice.
Gary Morton talk coming up here.
You can steamroll all over me.
OK.
I can't let what happened to Taffer happen to me.
Yeah.
Season nine will only be twenty two at that point.
I don't want to talk about it.
Yeah.
It's he says I believe it's in his book.
I'm getting some of my Taffer information confused.
Maybe the podcast maybe the book I believe it's the conflict book.
But he explains that he had a screaming match with an executive.
Early on in the bar rescue process where they wanted to fake something and he said you can go fuck yourself.
And he said that that was a good thing.
He did that because he put down that he was only going to make these shows authentic.
Yes.
It couldn't be fake.
So it's I agree with you.
I even think around I don't even know if it's like five six whatever whatever episodes I watched.
I feel like he became too self aware perhaps.
Yes.
Those first few seasons he's just going on instinct.
He doesn't know what he's doing even.
And then he know all the press comes in and people tell him what they like about him.
It's a similar thing we've talked about Leslie Nielsen then people telling him he's funny.
Right.
And then he goes on with the fart machine.
I mean I did the fucking my annual rewatch of the naked gun trilogy.
I think I do without fail every year.
Sure.
That's a smart move.
It is stunning.
Sure.
And it always is this thing of like should I dig into the rest of Leslie Nielsen comedy catalog.
And none of it.
I know.
I'm like is one of them accidentally a little bit.
Is there just even one sequence.
I'll find pieces.
I'll find slivers.
But you're just like there was something there.
Spy Hard with villain Andy Griffith.
Yeah.
Is that good at all.
Is Andy Griffith as a villain in a movie any good.
I've seen that but many years ago.
I've never made it through that movie to the end.
And it always felt unpleasant.
Something about it was unpleasant.
Jason wants to see that Mr. Magoo.
Have you made it to that list.
I haven't no.
Jason do you know the craziest thing about that movie.
What.
I keep wanting to text you every time you bring up.
Mr. Magoo.
Yeah.
It's only been once right.
Has it come up more than once.
I don't know.
I feel like I remember it once.
Maybe 22 on Magoo.
I believe that film is directed by Stanley Tong who was one of Jackie Chan's go to directors.
OK.
It is a movie that on paper you're just like this actually is the right formulation.
Leslie Nielsen is now a surprising comedy star.
He's good at playing oblivious to what's going on around him.
Right.
What's a cartoon character.
Mr. Magoo.
That's all physical comedy.
Hire someone from the fucking Jackie Chan school.
Smart.
Whoa.
Yeah.
The movie is like a disaster.
It is like so immediately inert.
I remember seeing it as a child and like being raring to go and it's got that thing.
I feel like you guys might relate to this where a movie would have an animated opening credit sequence.
The old Pink Panther trick.
Right.
Yeah.
Really locked in and then the second it cuts to live action you're like immediately not as fun.
You know.
Oh so they do a little animated Magoo.
They do a Magoo voiced by Nielsen and he's walking on fucking eye beams and shit and it's funny.
And then it cuts to live action and it's immediately dead.
Geez.
So that's Stanley Tong's only English language film is what this is saying.
He did like Drunken Master.
Right.
I feel like he did several of the biggest Jackie Chan movies.
There's not even like one sequence that's impressive.
I have not rewatched.
OK.
Well now we need Jason to watch them.
Huh.
Put on the list Jason.
Now that Dr. Odyssey is on hiatus you really should be digging in all that.
Jumping into Magoo.
Right.
Magooing it.
Yes.
You should be.
You should be walking off the edge of a building without realizing it.
Getting accidentally rescued by like a construction beam that goes by.
A beautiful day outside.
Beautiful windy day.
His big breakthrough was he did Police Story 3 Supercop.
Wow.
I didn't realize this.
So he joins Jackie a little later.
Jackie's main 90s collaborator but he does Rumble in the Bronx.
He does Jackie Chan's First Strike which was Police Story 4.
Like he was.
He was the guy.
And.
Hold on.
Let me check this.
He did in fact work on the TV show Martial Law.
Whoa.
It's all tiny.
How many seasons we got on Martial Law.
That's something.
That's outstanding.
Thirty one.
I'm going to say three.
Martial.
You know what.
I think Jason was right in his original assessment.
Really.
He invested for two seasons a combined 44 episodes.
Wow.
Forty four episodes.
That's less than one season of Bar Rescue Net.
Wow.
Geez.
I think I just assumed.
I do too.
If it was CBS in that era.
Well let me take that back.
But Stanley Tong executive producer.
And I guess by that logic Mike is a tastemaker.
Yeah.
All right.
If we're reassessing things from an hour ago.
Or more.
Well Jason remembers when I first introduced the idea of Lucy's second husband gearing
Morton to him.
He remembers that.
Yeah.
Because I'm a tastemaker.
Don't push your luck on Morton.
I've still got it in eight season nine yet.
It was during commercials of Bar Rescue.
Oh good.
I got 30 seconds to talk about Gary Morton.
Talk about Gary Morton.
Can I throw out just a very quick tidbit that I'd be remiss if I don't get in here somewhere
and there's never going to be a clean transition to it.
OK.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
The John Taffer podcast or John Taffer show episode I listened to is the one with Caratop
about his and live entertainment coming back and then doing the rundown of his credits
that was clearly pre-recorded with Corey.
Right.
Yeah.
Caratop not in the room.
He's like this guy.
His credits are unbelievable.
And he's doing the NPR voice.
I mean his credits are unbelievable.
He's got 20 credits here.
He lists off the credits.
Here are three direct quotes and I'm going to verbatim try to even if I can't do the
impression say these credits the way he says them.
Real time with Bill Mahara.
The Jim Gallifan show, which I imagine has to be the Jim Gaffigan show.
Did he have a show called that?
Yep.
OK.
And then he referred to Tashow.
In one rundown of credits, real time with Bill Mahara, the Jim Gallifan show and Tashow.
There's a typo in Tashow.
They put a period in it.
It's not supposed to be.
All right.
I don't know what's.
He fucked up three of them.
What is?
OK.
Tashow.
Just picture it in your head.
But also imagine.
Is it Tash.0?
Yes.
OK.
Tashow.
But just imagine the him and Sirius MPR voice, right?
It's like him trying to do his best like Terry Gross and trying to imbue these credits with
the energy of and what big credits they are.
These are.
Of course I know what all these shows are.
He's been on Tashow.
Tashow.
He's selling it as if he's not cold reading these names incorrectly.
Being a Carrot Top show is like seeing a great motion picture like M3 Gann.
Now there's an M3 Gann 20.
Or M3 Gann 20.
M3 Gallifan.
Gallifan I had to stop and rewind and go, what is he trying to say here?
And then I went, it must be Gaff again.
Gallifan.
He's been on Jay Lanou.
This is huge.
Does he not watch T like that is such a Bill Maher, especially for him, like that feels
like he would know who that is.
He talked a lot about the Basler and Elvis movie and the Rob Lowe podcast where he was
talking about it has to be authentic, has to be real.
They told me not to scream.
They said, you're too old, you're too ugly.
I said, I gotta be me.
And he was saying, it's like in the Elvis movie, they want him to wear that snowman
sweater and sing the Christmas song.
He's Elvis.
I'm like, oh, yes, the famously authentic Basler and Elvis movie,
which he might have been drawn to because he he, I believe, lives in Vegas.
Yes, he's a big Vegas guy.
And he he talked a lot about in twenty twenty one and twenty twenty two.
Like the city's coming back, the city's opening up because Vegas was obviously hit hard in
twenty twenty.
But they the amount of advertising I feel like I saw from them online.
And then when I was there over the years, I'm just like live entertainment is back.
That was come breathe the others air.
I mean, he just kept in this podcast saying, and I'm calling it now, April 1st,
twenty twenty, that's the day everything's coming back.
I'm sorry. It was twenty twenty one because Trump in twenty twenty said by Easter,
everything's going to be real.
Oh, right.
This was a podcast from the end of twenty twenty or the very beginning of twenty
twenty one. And he's saying, I'm calling it April 1st.
Everything's going to look normal again.
Live entertainment, road trips, people are ready.
He needed to make it.
He he's let us all down by not doing a Vegas review.
Oh, a bar rescue live.
I mean, he was coming out like going to tell some jokes.
I'm going to sing some songs, going to talk to some bar owners about what they're
doing wrong. It's a chance.
I was one of these podcasts offhandedly referred.
It must have been the Carrot Top episode offhandedly reference.
I know I did stand up for a little while.
No, shit. Oh, man.
Which, of course, he did.
Like, I'm sure that means that he went to four open mics, right?
Maybe he did one bringer show.
Look at this couple here in the front. Look at these guys.
She doesn't love you anymore.
Why aren't you laughing?
That was funny.
What do you do for a living?
Nothing.
Your father would be very disappointed in you.
Don't you think?
You're a good guy.
I could see that in you. You're a good guy.
Why aren't you all saying, oh, and clapping for that?
You told us you should be reacting.
You're talking about it feeling a little less authentic at some point.
Sorry, what were you going to say?
I was going to say that in the Sacramento ex-cop opens a sports bar,
which is really kind of like just a place for him to display all this memorabilia.
He has. And it's also probably failing because it's massive.
But at one point in terms of like funny, it ain't real quick.
Because you used to be a police man. You're a hero.
But now this bar is failing.
Like he like so quickly got through like you're a hero, you know?
And we all have so much respect, the whole crew, everybody who's here.
We're all tearing up with respect for what you do.
But you're a failure and a crook.
But he's calling the guy a hero and the guy's just like,
I just want to do my so many jurors.
He's just so mopey and he's losing just so much money.
I mean, some of these, the Pirates one always stands really tall for me.
Oh, yeah. I believe it is nine hundred and fifty thousand dollars in debt.
Yeah. Jesus. Whoa. Wow.
Yeah. Let's do it.
I mean, I think we got to do just kind of a round robin of episodes and bar
esky classics and Pirates absolutely is what this is.
This, I think, is his magnum opus.
The name of the bar.
Pirates. What city is Pirates in?
Is it Baltimore?
I think so.
Let me check that.
It's something like that.
But it is. Yeah, it's like it's a pirate themed bar.
There's a bunch of dorks there who want to dress up like pirates.
Like I and it feels like Silver Spring, Maryland.
Silver Spring. It's a very corporate town.
But yes, this is his assessment.
You know, it's these it's these dorks and making them
dressing up like pirates makes them happy.
No one goes in there.
But like you could say they're they like what they have here.
They aren't running a good version of what that could be whatsoever.
But nine hundred and fifty thousand dollars in debt.
They have only 15 employees who are just people who want to live
like a pirate all day long.
She cites it like she's like, well, of course, Pirate Bar makes sense.
It's the ultimate fantasy.
We all wish we could be a pirate.
She's she's what she says is being a pirate is the ultimate Peter Pan syndrome.
Words that must have warmed your heart.
Well, yeah, I yeah.
First, once I wrote once I pick myself off the floor,
having flung myself off the couch, I thought, no, it's the opposite.
Peter Pan doesn't get along with the pirate.
Yeah, I think the opposite of the ultimate Peter Pan syndrome.
A lost boy. Yes.
The enemy of the pirate.
You've got it fully wrong.
So that might indicate what's wrong with your pirate bar.
But then he oh, by the way, and we should say this episode is the episode.
There's even even though like he
takes great pains to be like thoughtful and like
because you're dealing with a lot, aren't you?
And your kids and that's that's very hard.
And then it'll still name the episode something so insulting,
like in this case, that the episode is called Yo Ho Ho and a bottle of dumb.
The episode about champs bar in Burbank,
which seems to be very popular and doing very well.
Still, that episode is on Paramount Plus's chumps.
Geez, geez.
I mean, the thing about the Pirates episode is it's one of the strongest themes
in relation to the level of failure the business has been going through
for the amount of years it's been failing at that level.
And he's basically like, you got to take all the theming out.
And she's like, I want you to fix this and make this more normal.
But my dream is to own a pirate bar.
And he keeps on being like, you got to meet me halfway.
This woman is close to a million dollars in debt.
I forget what she says, but she used to have like
what seemingly was a fairly successful job in like a corporate sphere.
She has a much younger husband named Juciano,
who she installed as the chef with no cooking experience.
Oh, yeah, he's one of the worst chefs I've ever heard.
Juciano terrible and just curses whenever anyone says anything to him.
He goes, what the shit? Fuck you.
Why do you think it's dog shit?
I think you're dog shit.
She's got a 16 year old daughter.
She's now moved into her parents basement with the daughter
and Juciano and sold her home to keep the pirates bar afloat.
And the whole time, he's like, you got to trust me.
I can tell you're going through a lot.
All these things where he really wants to be Mr. Compassionate.
And then it's just the greatest bar rescue moment for me
is the redesign of the bar, which so often is like
he turns it into the blandest airport bar possible.
That's usually the idea was his taste is so, so lame.
And then he'll point to one thing and be like, and look,
I still kept your love of football in there.
There's a helmet on the wall.
Like a point to one thing where he's like, I know your dad was important.
So I scribbled your dad's initials under the table.
If you go in the second stall of the women's restroom. Right.
But the bar is always like renamed the drinking place or something.
The beer pub.
I'm trying to think of it of a more like the here's a more tepid example.
As one is called the poor house. Right.
And it's more like you are.
Yeah. Which makes plenty like, yeah, I got that makes all the sense
in the world for a bar to be called the poor house.
And it's a play on words.
He's so like, that sounds sad. That's miserable.
People put a gun in their mouth when they are poor out.
And then and then that would be people smiling when they see this.
I'm the like, did they learn?
And that when he changes to the study, right?
Whatever. But they're usually that like so it's like, whatever.
They aren't as offensive as Pirates Bar is the only one
that feels like it is actually spiteful.
Yeah. Yeah.
Saying you're in a in a corporate area.
There's so many corporate is corporate offices around.
He drills that corporate people don't want to have lunch at a pirate bar.
People famously love being trapped in offices.
Of course. Yeah.
They go do it as their job and then they want to leave and do it again immediately.
Yeah. It's having to go out for lunch and being outside of the safe,
comforting walls of a cubicle.
Want to walk out in their coat and tie and see a logo with a coat and tie in it.
His logic is very few people live in this town.
This is a town that people commute into for work after five o'clock.
People are gone.
You need to be a happy hour and lunch bar.
In that case, I'm like, OK, this this is a guy speaking like he's an expert
in bar science, that he understands the basic tense of what he's saying.
Makes sense to me.
And the pirate bar does seem like dog shit.
It seems like a terrible, terrible place to be.
It seems less committed than when like a cruise ship does pirate.
Yes. Yeah.
All right. Yeah. An elementary school.
Like I wear pirate costumes today.
It is worse than that.
We're trying to be that theme.
Like, it's not like a bar that has some pirate shit on the wall.
It is a bar where your servers are like, hey, you know, it is immersive.
They're trying to make it.
There are a bunch of creeps in there.
And it's basically get a bad vibe from who are like,
I can't exist in the real world.
Have these like emotional breakdowns to tap or where they're like,
I've tried to exist in the real world.
This is the only place I feel safe if I'm not a pirate.
And his rebranding is corporate.
The bar is called Corporate.
The logo is a man wearing a shirt and the theme of the bar is the office.
It's just like this is designed to corporate place.
You do corporate bar.
And if there's a town with a lot of construction in it,
the people want to end up going to the wrecking ball.
But she's just pacing around and she's like, I hate it.
I'm miserable.
And he's like, you're going to ride this out.
I hear her body is rejecting it.
There's never one that's ever gone.
No. So where you could tell they might not make it through the night
without her taking it. Yeah.
There's one where he doesn't he like, I forget which one that it was.
There's one where he just leaves.
That's maybe the worst one.
But this is, yeah, there's not one where there's the
there's the female staff member who they were physically abusive to.
And they won't take responsibility.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
It's like they have one staff member who gets really drunk
and is starting a fight with a nicer woman.
Yeah. And he keeps on saying, like, you have to fire the woman who hit.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
And the owners go, she was asking for it. Right.
And they have my bottles falling down.
I was asking for it last time.
And that's the clangiest bottle I've ever heard.
But he leaves where he's like, I cannot abide by this.
And then I think the owners went to jail.
Oh, I don't know that.
Oh, that's it. Maybe that's the same episode.
I'm trying to remember.
There's something people won't do something.
And then he leaves.
There's the Chicago Sports Bar one, the dugout.
Yeah. Where the guy has his special is the hot pussy shot.
And he has an all female staff and taffers like, this is revolting.
How dare you make them say this?
Well, that's in dimples in the dimples episode.
That's the other burbank.
The burbank is a former burbank karaoke bar.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Was known as the first karaoke bar in America.
Just a couple of blocks from Warner Brothers Studios.
Now it's a Whole Foods and apartments.
But when it was your birthday, you would go and they were like,
hey, it's Christian's birthday.
There is a million year old running man running it.
He has no charisma.
Yes, he's really really creepy.
And he's like, got to get the blow job shot.
You got to do the blow job shot.
And that's where he like puts his shot with whipped cream on it
between a woman's leg.
And he tells a man to get down on his knees and he goes,
hey, that's not the first time you're going to hear that tonight.
And everyone's like, I don't really do this.
I don't really want to do this.
And he goes like, I don't care.
Like, you know, like we got to do anyway.
And the bar seems very unsafe.
There's chachkis and mementos and movie memorabilia everywhere.
Yeah. The sound system is awful.
Yeah. And he moves everything into the parking lot.
All the memorabilia puts a little back, gets them a new sign.
And the guy's like, wow.
And eventually, like in the post show, Chris, they're like,
he did put a lot of it back.
Well, that's a case where it's like,
look, maybe it makes a good television.
You're not changing this guy.
Yeah. Right. Like this bar has existed this long this way.
And this what I have a connection.
I never went to this bar,
but this bar is in walking distance to the Oakwood Apartments,
which is now called something else.
Yeah, it is a long walk.
But when you have college students who just turned 21
and want to get hammered, wow, that's an old classic.
Yeah. Wow.
See, this episode does have to do with the podcast.
You have to know what theme parks are doing, other things, other things.
That was the Ithaca or Emerson
bar that people would go to.
No, I never part.
I never seen so nasty.
I would look up pictures and I was like, I don't want to go there.
That seems awful.
Hmm. But people would go there and get their video of karaoke.
The other regular of this bar, Mr.
Belding from. Oh, I remember that fact.
In that episode, is he not?
Am I misremembering? I didn't see him.
I rewatched it. OK.
I would think he would be.
I'm learning a false memory of just hearing for years.
People be like, there's this funny dive bar.
We go to where Mr. Belding is there every night.
If you want to. Yeah.
And he he was kind of a lush.
And but that is the one where the cook gets so overwhelmed
by the stress stress that they have to call an ambulance.
Yeah. And he's OK.
But you can tell it is like everyone's really weirded out after that.
Even more than the creepy owner.
It is another element.
It is cathartic to see people get yelled at if you feel personally
that they deserve it. Yeah.
Yeah, that's one thing about this is that, well, you know,
sometimes Taffer's tactics can be like upsetting and it's fun to make fun of him.
The other side of it is often pretty wrong, too.
It's like Jews, I disagree with everyone in this all at the same time.
Do you remember like the I think it's a Vegas episode where there's the bar
he re themes into a very immersive zombie bar.
Oh, yeah, that's I haven't seen that one.
And I feel like it used to be like a fucking heavy metal bar or something before that.
But the bartender is like incredibly gross with all women.
Yeah, yeah. And it's like the whole episode is him being like,
you're scaring women away.
You're disrespecting women. My wife.
He would scream that a lot, because that's that's that's Lindsay's go to.
And she's quoting Taffer.
She disrespecting women.
Well, that's that's a big that's it's my favorite thing is when he sends his wife
in to do the call. Yeah, you go do it.
Worst of all, that's my wife.
You said that to my wife.
There is an episode of Marriage Rescue where somebody
in the couple, there's one of them
is really obsessed with social media and her social media brand.
And her partner is doesn't really into it and doesn't want to be part of it.
And his solution is you should be in her videos, which, by the way,
it's a former Harlem Globetrotter.
So he does like basketball spinning like you should be in a basketball
Instagrams, because you know what?
You know, I've I've been married for a long time.
And when I got a TV show, you know what I did?
I put my wife in it.
I put her in it.
And that's what you have to do with each other.
You got to be you got to spin a basketball with her.
That's the solution. It's so good.
I feel like this this might have restarted a wave of the Taffer
conversation a year or two ago, but I went to my friend's wedding in Chicago
and I walked out of my hotel and I was waiting for an Uber
and I recognized the signage and I texted you guys.
And I said, do you know what this is?
And it's another one of my top, absolute top tier bar rescue episodes.
I realized I was staying outside the husk of it, which was the the Wonder Bar.
Do you remember this one?
Yeah. This woman, the underground Wonder Bar.
Oh, yeah, yeah. The woman's name had like performance arts.
Yes. She's like an old hippie woman.
And they're like crayons on the tables.
And she basically performs a four hour set of her music every night.
And the bar is clearly like she got it for a song.
She paid five dollars for an 80 year lease in like 1965.
And they can't kick her out, but it makes no money.
And she's just like, this place, it's it's about love and it's an attitude.
And he's like, but it's not a successful business.
And she's got an adult son who she's now like tasked with managing the bar.
But she he can't break his mom's habits of what she wants it to be.
And he's just like, she's out of touch with the times.
Our customer base is literally dying off.
We have this whole downstairs area we don't use.
And he rethemes it as the ice bar.
He's like, you're going to have the best ice in all of Chicago.
And he always has his weird product sponsorship, a POS system from one of these.
You know, he's always got companies.
His good friends at Blank tender.
Yeah, our tender is the one.
But he's got this ice company
that he's like, you're going to be on a bar in Chicago with square ice.
And the ice comes and Ziploc bags and the bar is made of ice.
The whole thing is ice.
He like watched Batman and Robin the night before, maybe.
And you're just like, this woman is just doesn't give a shit.
She just wants to get on her piano and like singing Age of Aquarius or whatever.
This is going to like disappear immediately.
And one of my favorite batch of ice, it's all done.
One of my favorite corners of like Taffa, Taffanalia, Taffa, Belia, Taffiana,
whatever we want to call it.
And do you guys watch any of the
what are they called back to the bar episodes?
Yes, I have.
Yeah, there's a Scottsdale episode.
Oh, they do go back to where he like narrates it, which is great to like
these knuckleheads didn't do what I said first time.
Let's see if that changes when we go check in on him again.
His teleprompter reading is there.
Also the ones where like he's hosting it from a giant set
surrounded by a live audience.
That's like a circular bar.
Oh, yeah.
And he's like, we're going to today, we're going to revisit some of our past bars.
And it's him trying to do like genial emcee shit.
It's like a Vegas show.
Yeah, and he does magic like live.
And his DJ, put him in that DJ on camera
in a booth with like headphones and turntables will be the announcer.
Yes, yes.
Which this is another thing that's great about him.
Taffer has lasted so long, like a cockroach,
that he is like the one vestige of the Spike network
that still has that energy.
And even though they've rebranded that channel like four times,
I crushed Mansers.
Right. Mansers is dead.
He's still got the Mansers vibes.
Yeah, yeah. That's the voice.
John Taffer coming live from Las Vegas.
You see him. He looks like one of us.
It's very disorienting.
Wow. Because you're just like, he just looks like a comedy, dude.
You know, but he'll have, you know, he'll play like a clip package
of the worst moments from that episode and be like,
and we're going to catch up with them now.
And he'll have them live in studio and he'll just kind of castigate them.
But he'll do it in a like, wow, we're old friends kind of way.
Yeah, it's a real like a jump to go like your friends are the pirates people.
You know, we've been so vicious to them.
Do you know what it reminds me of?
Like, we just lived through months and months and months
of the Democratic Party being like, fascism is knocking at the door.
This man's an immediate threat to our country.
And I'm like, I agree.
We should figure out some way to stop him from getting elected.
It seems like you don't want a new Hitler in there.
Probably. He gets elected.
And they're just like, well, of course, we have to find a way
to meet him in the middle.
And I'm like, no, stand by this.
And you pointed out that Biden's Biden goes, hey, welcome home.
Right. I'm like, you don't need to be fucking friendly to this guy.
Your assessment was correct.
Yeah. And I'm like, for as much as Taffer can be an asshole,
like he'll have the Wonderbar woman on and he's just like,
you never change your ways.
And we love her for it, don't we?
And I'm like, her business is like collapsing.
Yeah, I hate I don't like those.
It drives you crazy.
It's weird to watch audience responses.
Weird. It's weird how insincere he is where he's trying to play nice guy.
We're going to do a fashion show at a worst uniforms that we ever saw in a bar.
That shit.
We're going to make some women where some really embarrassing scanty stuff.
The insincerity, I think, is why there was only one season of Hungry Investors.
We got a whole other show.
His other show where him and two of his experts choose between two
restaurants to invest in a very boring shark tank.
Whoever put the shows together, whatever person, people that put the shows together,
I they made him look so impressive.
Even though we know we're smart guys, savvy to the biz,
we I still kind of came away from like the first so many episodes being like,
man, he really gets to the heart of the matter.
Literally from the business.
Well, yeah, nobody understands bar science like John Traver.
It makes sense that people like we he must be so talented.
He can work in any genre, right?
Any type of show, right?
And he can solve any kind of problem.
We're talking reality drums in every genre.
Stand up. Yeah, I know.
This is not just a perfectly constructed piece of reality television
that makes him look like a superhero.
This man is a superhero.
This isn't just a Svengali.
This isn't like, you know, some kind of wizard.
This is the Wizard of Oz, but he's a real wizard.
Oh, he's a real wizard. There's no man.
I'm the size of the wizard. I'm the size of the big head.
I got the magic. I'm the size of the balloon.
The magic is real.
Mike, I feel like you have many times over the years said to me in your way.
Yes. No, I hear from a lot of people.
Very smart.
You'll repeat this thing of like once in a while
who have worked on some of the shows or met him in situations.
Well, we have to talk about somebody because we have a connection to someone.
Oh, right, right.
Who has been a part of this franchise.
We should say that that comment has not been made by this person.
Oh, that's true. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I actually don't know the reaction.
Let me and this might require a little bit of tea, because coincidentally,
this is I knew that we we know somebody who's been on a bar rescue.
But then still, I was trying to find unusual episodes.
And I started watching this one, not even realizing, oh, that's the one.
Because the episode in and of itself is extremely notable
because it's the one where reality genres all clash.
And we have not just a failing bar, but a haunted bar,
a bar that has a ghost in it and where the owner
will not lock it up by himself because of the ghost.
And I don't have the exact quotes, but I know that it builds to things like
you have to choose.
Is it the is it the boy who wins?
Is it the bar and a ghost?
Hearing him yell about the ghost is so awesome.
And I am afraid of no ghost.
But that makes me feel good.
I never liked the girls.
An invisible man sleeping in your bed.
Oh, you're the bacteria.
Thank you, Brian.
Mike, I'm sorry.
He would be a good ghost in a Ghostbusters movie.
Like it would be translucent, whatever the effect on it.
He's just like a scary ghost.
Slimer is they imagine what a ghost of me would be like.
And that's what I thought a slime.
He should have been muncher.
Oh, oh, oh, my God.
Yes. The dream casting.
If muncher had the voice of John Tapper, even if it was much, much, much.
I'm muncher. I'm munching.
It wasn't words. It was just him going, ah.
And they don't even tell him he's doing it.
They just wake him up in the middle of the night.
See what sounds he naturally makes.
But then this boy, it has him yelling about the ghost,
but then it also has the tender side.
And it's like they fix the bar stuff and then like, OK,
now it's time we get rid of this ghost.
You are going to you're going to close this building alone.
And then and he's also working the angle of like haunted attractions
are big in this country. Imagine you're in a haunted bar.
It's going to be huge.
But here's what's funny is that there's a premise laid on top of it,
which is that, you know, he sends people in to do the recon.
And sometimes those people are connected to local industry or whatever.
Sometimes they're experts.
Sometimes they're past bar rescue. Oh, that's right.
Right. And if it is from Taffer's.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But in this case, I met two podcasters.
If they recommend this place on the show on the on their podcast,
it could change everything.
But one negative word would send them plummeting into the toilet.
I hired.
And then it's the other one is Matt Myra.
Because I'll talk about it in the idiot.
Is that why the Nerdist appearance happened? Correct.
Oh, OK. Wow.
It's like Myra was really into bar rescue.
This is Hardwick has saying like, Myra's been trying to get me
to watch Bar Rescue forever.
Then he was on the episode.
Then I finally watched it.
And I was like, Matt, we have to get Taffer on the show.
Well, that's because which and then because they have a relationship,
he keeps like zinging him like, right, because like, you know,
because you're in a nightclub now, you're feeling confident.
You want to be talking to the girls, everybody except for you, man.
And I love he's zinging him so hard. Yeah. Yeah.
But you know, normal guys.
So, Matt, you stay out of this.
But the other one, Jordan Morris from Jordan, Jesse Gold.
Yes. He which I and I saw this at some point
just on the Pluto feed without knowing.
And I just bugged out.
What do you mean you were on it?
And I know I've talked to him about this a bunch over the years.
But then remembering, oh, my God, and it's the ghost one.
And I thought a bar rescue episode would not be complete without some chip
in from somebody who was actually on an episode who had the opportunity
to make or break a bar. Yeah.
You know, like, did he say negative words about it
just because there's a ghost in there? Was Jordan so cruel?
I'm not sure. And he sent us a voice memo.
I don't know what's in it.
I haven't listened to it, but you know, experience this together.
We can maybe get some some actual feedback of the kayfabe and the character.
And is he smarter? Whatever it is. Yeah.
Hey, podcast, the ride occasional guest Jordan Morris here
with a remembrance of my time on Bar Rescue.
In 2015, I was working with writer and podcaster Matt Myra.
He knew I was a fan of Bar Rescue and he knew a few of the field producers.
He asked me if I wanted to be one of the recon guys in an episode with him.
It was shooting in El Cajon.
And I, of course, jumped at the chance.
The recon segment of the show, of course, happens early in the episode
before John Taffer rescues the bar.
He sends in his friends to order drinks and report back on what's wrong with the bar.
This particular bar was Myers Poor P.O.U.R.
House, a very down the middle SoCal strip mall bar.
They apparently had two problems.
Bartenders that overpoured and a ghost that scared away the owner.
We got told all of this ahead of time, and we were also asked
if we would be OK ordering kettle one spirits who were sponsoring the episode.
I was just kind of excited to be there.
So I gladly ordered kettle one, which I never had and never have since.
So we we were set up not as just John's friends,
but as podcasters whose recommendation or pan could make or break the bar.
If you've heard of my podcast, Jordan, Jesse Goh,
you know, of course, that we spend most of our time reviewing bars near San Diego.
We had a little like meet and greet with John before we went in.
He was very nice.
And I got to see his famous one sport coat that he owns.
We went in, ordered our kettle one cocktails
and tried to get the bartenders to talk about the ghost.
I remember it was really awkward for a bunch of reasons.
First is that it's really strange being in a bar with harsh TV lighting.
It was just so bright in there.
Second, the bar was filled with all these locals who were just really excited
to be on camera and were just shouting insane shit all night long.
It was next to this one woman who had clearly just learned the phrase
by Felicia, and she would just yell bye Felicia at anyone who walked by.
So we drank a little bit.
The bartender was doing strong pours.
And since we kind of knew this was an issue going into it,
Matt and I really played up how strong the drinks were because
we wanted Daddy to be proud.
Speaking of Daddy, it was a real thrill to see John come in
and do the shut it down speech.
He did it in one take.
And that's basically the take you see in the episode.
Also, I was really impressed that he was really watching a feed of the bar
outside in the SUV, something I had assumed was faked,
but is is totally actually happening.
So I walked away from the experience, really impressed with the authenticity
of the timeline they present in the show for that particular segment.
Anyway, I still have not been to the rescued bar.
It was changed to the vaguely academic themed the study.
And according to Google, it's still there.
I was paid nothing for my appearance and do not receive any residuals
when it is rerun seven times a month.
OK, I hope that was enlightening.
If you'll permit me a plug that might be of interest to the PTR audience.
I wrote a story for the upcoming comics anthology Godzilla versus L.A.
It is three comic stories about Godzilla visiting L.A.
and all the money goes to wildfire relief.
My story is from the POV of the Universal Studios Tram Driver.
There's a bunch of theme park in jokes that I think you all will enjoy.
And the art is by the amazing Nicole Goh.
It drops on April 30th.
And you could preorder it at your local comic book store.
That's Godzilla versus L.A. coming on April 30th.
Wow. Thank you, Jordan. Great.
No, that's very good. You're always selling.
Every everything you do is an opportunity to sell.
And that's why Jordan, I'm gifting you this POS system
so you can track how many people on podcasts are getting
the comic work that you do.
Daddy, I, I, Mike, I need you to correct me on this.
Are do we?
My memory is we have a connection to one of these bars.
Very briefly, you and I.
Which bar? Pat's Cocktails in Valley Village, California.
And my memory is we filmed something in there
that you wrote a web series you co-wrote that never came out.
And then I think after we did this,
Pat's Cocktail Bar sticks out in my mind as one of the fixes.
They make a cocktail with a smoke gun.
I don't know what to call it
other than just a gun that shoots smoke in your like whiskey cocktail.
So we're going to get you this gun and you're going to use this every night.
And that's how you're going to fix it.
What was happening in the scene?
I don't remember. We were just in this bar.
Who are we with and where have they been canceled?
No, it was there.
I don't see Owen Benjamin.
It was that scene. Yes, yes, yes.
No, this was something.
We made this for Justin Lin's YouTube channel.
When there were just there was just money.
YouTube handed like millions of dollars out to a ton of different people.
And Justin Lin, the famous director of many fast and few
many fast and furious had
dumped a bunch of money into a project that never showed up.
Second, emerging new Internet media.
Invested a bunch of money into people who are already proven
in the most legitimate sectors of the entertainment industry
to then underpay struggling creatives.
And then the thing was never released.
That doesn't sound like a worry.
I know a lot of people are not paid at all.
The ultimate underpayment, the ultimate under zero.
What I remember about the Pats Cocktails episode,
there was barbecue place next door and they cut a hole in the walls.
Like, now people can order the barbecue and then you can you just
everyone makes more money.
We're going to ruin their business, too.
But what I read about Pats Cocktail Bar after that,
or I think people I knew visited and are like, hey, do you sell that smoke gun?
And they're like, oh, that's up to working weeks after that was long gone.
I feel like whenever Taffer and Bar Rescue comes up,
this is always one of the main things you hone in on, Mike,
is that like every episode starts with they're overpouring.
They're sloppy.
They're taking too long to make drinks.
And it's like a gin and tonic. Right.
Like, yeah, they don't know how to do it.
Who doesn't know how to do a gin and tonic. Right.
And like, yeah, everything's going wrong.
And then they bring in the world's greatest mixologist, whoever it is.
They happen to be the world's greatest every time.
The winner of the most prestigious award.
She's very cool.
She has a big pompadour curl on her head.
That's something that we're doing now, like the band that was bad on SNL, Carmen.
We have a Carmen and she's going to fix your bar.
It's just the leap from they can't make two ingredient cocktails.
Right. The name is the two ingredients.
And it's taking too long.
They're doing it poorly and they're losing money.
And they come in and they're like, here's the concept.
The drink is inside a skull.
It's on fire.
You need to shake it with some flair.
You know, let's make it a show.
It's complicated to make.
It costs $40.
Proprietary equipment.
There's cinnamon hair strands at the top.
And you singe.
Don't burn them all the way.
You lightly singe the cinnamon hair.
This this season nine episode I watched was it's like the bar needs a gimmick.
You got to have a gimmick and a challenge to get people in through the door.
So they had a drink called the Bucking Bronco where there's a pepper
and you have to eat the pepper first.
And then the drink has like 10 different types of like chili and hot sauce in it.
But then like a tahini rim and then like a straw that's coated in some other spicy substance.
I'm like, there are 27 steps to this thing.
And the woman at the beginning of it was making martinis with orange juice.
There's like it's the same way with the kitchen.
Like there's a guy who cannot figure out how to make mozzarella sticks in a microwave.
And he's like, I want you to cook a full Thanksgiving dinner for every person on that bar.
You better plate the Caprese successfully because we eat with our eyes
before we eat with our mouths.
You need to slaughter the bison yourself.
Take the table from the table.
Let the littlest kid take the knife and do it.
In one of the recons, before everything's fixed,
one of the Burbank bars, the expert orders a scotch and soda,
gets it, takes a sip and goes, oh, like he just drank toilet water.
And just hearing Jordan talk about like playing up the reactions, I was like,
how badly could you fuck up a scotch and soda?
This is interesting what he's thrown into question.
He through he himself, perhaps, was not authentic,
thinking that this was what the show asked for.
But then found the man himself, John, to be a beacon of authenticity.
Right. That he nailed it in one take.
That the time I am very surprised that the recon in the van is happening.
I am, too. Yeah, the fakest.
Like, I'm going in there.
I assume that he just knocked out all the van scenes.
Like in a separate sound stage, months and months later, always my guess.
And then I was digging in and it seems to be that the timeline of the show
as represented is pretty honest and accurate.
But my head always watching the show was like, he must go to one bar,
do those couple of days, leave the renovation, takes a week or two.
Then he goes to another bar.
He circles back to the first bar when that renovation is done.
Then he circles back to the second bar when that renovation is done.
But it's like, no, it does sound like each episode happens
within one five day week, basically.
And he's actually in the van.
Right. I'm sure they time it.
So it's like 20, 15 minutes tops him in the van looking at the footage.
Yeah. But the fact that these things are actually happening, like, yeah.
Yeah. Makes you feel good. It does.
Do you think that one thing Jordan didn't say is whether or not
he made good on the promise?
Is there an episode of Jordan, Jesse go where real quick,
I don't want to sidebar too much, but I found myself in El Cajon
where I often am, and I was mortified at my experience
at a little place called the poor and then just like a 15 minute
just absolute tear down of. Yeah.
And and and and forgive me, Jesse, I will let you format.
Well, I was confused at first because I always knew the show
is Jordan get Jordan, Jesse go brought to by kettle one.
Yeah, there's a later season like the sponsorship to it.
Sorry, I'm all over the place.
I feel like there's more of that and there's more synergy later.
Don't worry. I got a whole leave on that.
I have a whole PDF take behind about his philosophy from
just for us to read.
Well, for us to apply to our lives.
Oh, sure. Wow.
Well, that's what I think it's about when we get together.
Griffin gifted us a television premise, which is now the subject
of a massive bidding war. Right.
And you're going to help us.
So I think we'll learn that making that show, that that conflict
will be crucial and you listen to the one audiobook.
But you didn't even listen to the older book, Raise the Bar
and Action Based Method for Maximum Customer Reaction.
No, I understand. I didn't have a double meaning in that title,
if I'm not mistaken.
I think I don't understand. I think there might be.
I just want to at least say the name of this.
It's called Taffer's Toolkit Takeaways.
So that's where you learn about conflict and how to use conflict
to help in your daily life. Wow.
But we don't have time to get done.
There's so I know we do have to start.
I think maybe one thing to talk about a little bit,
and we've referred to this a bit, but I this is also something to
you know, that's that's a promise and something we can make good on
a little better in Taffer, too, is is his own restaurant,
Taffer's Taver. Yeah.
So the ultimate bar scientist has applied this science
to a restaurant chain. Yes.
And wouldn't you know it, of the three locations that have opened,
two of them have quickly does not seem to be going very well.
Every time it opens in a new city, the food reviewer for that city's paper
tears it apart.
I mean, that's like what a great opportunity to do so.
You can't blame the one that remains open is in Alpharetta, Georgia.
It's 40 minutes north of Atlanta.
That one has maintained.
But D.C. closed Watertown, Massachusetts closed
in trying to assess what a problem might be.
Well, the very thing that we're referring to, the drinks in the skulls and such.
I was curious what is on the bar menu at Taffer's Tavern.
And one that jumped out at me is a drink called Lost at Sea,
a glistening deep sea experience with vodka, tropical orange and ginger flavors
garnished with a mermaid.
What do you mean by that?
Yeah, I have no further information on what the mermaid garnish is.
But this does seem in keeping with like he like I'm going to check in
on these knuckleheads and see what if they kept my system in place.
Excuse me. Where are the mermaids?
I don't see.
I don't see clamshell bras anywhere.
I hand shook those clams.
I took the clams out themselves.
We were importing the clams from Sicily.
Why aren't you keeping the mermaids in your drinks?
They could talk. I bred them in a lab.
They were real live mermaids.
I'm trying to find this article I found yesterday that was him breaking down.
I can't remember if it was right before the pandemic or sort of like right
at the beginning of vaccination when he was ramping up.
And he was just like, this is ready to overtake everything.
I got some Taffer vaccination things.
But yeah, I forgot.
But he was basically saying, like, I've just been studying the restaurant
industry, and it just angers me how broken it is.
And I'm ready to fix it all.
And I've recently gone down a similar rabbit hole.
Steve Ells, the creator of Chipotle, has been like,
I've seen my thing go through its whole like rise and fall or Chipotle
to wherever it's landed. Right.
And I'm ready to revolutionize the industry again.
And he's like robots.
People don't want to interact with people.
It's plant based robots.
No seeding takeout only.
And he started these restaurants called Colonel that opened in New York
that very quickly closed because people found them unappealing.
And now they keep rebranding and be like, we've heard you.
We're going to make it more warm.
Warm. You will see a person's face.
There will be a chair.
I don't understand the greatest nightclub in the world that a robot.
If it was Seiko, though, I bet it would have worked.
Yeah, Taffer's Tavern.
I was finding this article sent to you guys and their quotes.
I'm looking forward to pull up here.
But the model was based on labor costs have become too high.
Taffer is a real big fighter against minimum wage being raised.
Small business, Seiko.
Yeah, it's all business time, right?
Labor costs versus material costs.
It's like the health of the business is the only thing that matters.
And the numbers have been out of whack.
Places like Applebee's are doing like four entrees for five dollars or whatever.
And he's like, something has to change.
Higher quality food, but less people working.
So the Taffer Tavern model I didn't realize was at least at the beginning
very much conceived of this is a largely robotic kitchen.
Really? Yes.
Oh, I miss this.
And the food is sous vide.
Yeah, that is a big high quality food that is prepared
and seasoned by experts sous vide en masse.
And they were like, so do you need to have some offsite location
that's making food for all of the franchise locations?
If your thing expands, he's like, no, we use the company
that makes the sandwiches for Starbucks and now they make steaks for us.
What? And so they make steaks, they vacuum seal them in bags,
they ship them to Taffer's Tavern, and then a robot cooks it,
which is dumps it in water.
Sous vide, as I know it, it is vacuum sealed in a bag.
Yes. Placed in boiling water.
Yes. Then opened and put on the plate. Right.
And he was like, incredible.
It's easier. It's cheaper. It tastes better.
We don't have a 15 year old seasoning on a line.
Now it doesn't take like a day to teach someone to cook.
It takes them like a minute
because they don't actually have to do the cooking.
They just oversee the robot.
And he's saying like, and you won't believe how good this steak tastes.
You won't believe. Review from Washington Post.
Steak frites in which the flat iron cut had been waterboarded
to the consistency of guacamole.
There's almost evocative descriptions
I've ever read in a restaurant review.
How do you possibly end up doing this after?
You're the guy. 300 episodes of screaming at people.
You just put it in water.
Chicken and waffles in which the pre-cooked bird
was fried in-house to a nice crackle.
But the base was so gooey and underdone
that the pearl sugar concealed inside the waffle
cracked against my teeth like grit from a poorly cleaned oyster.
The waffle's the problem? Oh my God.
He'll give Taffer that the chicken was good, but the waffle.
The cost of making waffles is what's bringing this country down.
And Mr. Trump, I need you to assure me
that you'll get the waffle prices there.
Let my robot put a bagged waffle in a tub of water.
Is there a detail left in that review that you could read
as if it was Taffer yelling at the person who, like,
it's Taffer yelling at the cook?
Scott, let me see if I can scan this review for even one more negative statement.
That must be all of them, right?
I'll read that part of me is dazzled by technology
that holds Taffer's tavern together.
And what do I mean for the future of hospitality?
Kitchens that require fewer and less skilled workers.
Read between the lines there.
Now, this we can all agree on. Yes.
This is a very good thing. Yes.
Yes, we all agree on that. More POS systems than humans.
Well, basis owners are better.
The only way I agree is if it's like a kitchen of Seco's.
Yes, yeah. And they are wearing big old...
Wait, here's a point of discussion.
Giant chef's hats or regular human sized chef's hats
that are very small on Seco's big head? Regular, regular.
OK, got to talk to them.
They have a lot of these in Vegas now where, like, a robot will make your cocktail.
But it looks like a robot arm from an assembly line.
And it's just grabbing different bottles from the seat.
So it's not made to look friendly at all.
And then it's not a robot.
It looks like it could torture you if you get tangled up in its robot arms.
It's like, here is your Jack and Coke.
That's what I want. If it says that, I'm happy.
All I need, just talk to me.
Talk to me and it's not in a human AI voice.
I did like, I hope you are satisfied.
Enjoy getting hammered.
The only robot you want is the greeter.
Yeah. But going table to table, being like, how is your dinner?
Where you're like, that's fun novelty entertainment shit.
Have you been here before?
At a pulsation type restaurant. Right.
I mean, this Washington Post review goes in multiple paragraphs of being like,
I think I've identified the problem with robot restaurants.
Like, this person is like, in theory, I get it.
But here's what's terrifying about going to a restaurant without humans in it.
I will read this paragraph in my best worst
taffer here, the section about the drinks, which should be taffers special.
Of course, the cocktail list, which would seem to play the taffer strengths
borrows ideas from the wider world of mixology without apparently
understanding how to best apply them.
The tiny pile of wood chips that sits next to the trademark Campfire cocktail,
basically a fat washed old fashioned is ignited purely for show, not flavor.
I'm still not sure why my server served charred a jalapeno table side,
which I was then told to switch around the spiced rum based resurrection.
A drink that looks like it was mixed with water from Splash Mountain.
So if anyone thinks this podcast doesn't have to do with theme parks, it really does.
Yeah, you got a problem with the way I make my campfire drinks.
Do you have a better way to make campfire?
What have you gotten a little set next to your beverage?
This other article when they were about to open where he was just like,
and we're turning away applications, too many franchisees want to open one.
He's like, it's simple.
We've simplified the cook robots and sous vide.
And they're like, what about the drinks?
He's like the most obnoxious drinks of all time.
Every drink has five glow sticks.
There are backstories to every drink.
You have to have read a graphic novel prequel to understand the beverage you're drinking.
And the interviewer straight up asked him, like, doesn't that seem counter
to the philosophy that you just outlined for the food?
And he's like, no, it's going to work the same way.
And they're like, how is that possible?
And he's like, well, obviously there'll be a big component of premixing.
And I'm like, yeah, but you're also advertising that the drinks
have 10 novelty toys inside of them.
The drinks are like magic tricks when a magician has to escape from a straitjacket.
You only have one minute to find the key to rescue your drink from a straitjacket,
which is going to fall into a little mini tub of fire.
It's simple.
It creates excitement to the night.
And we're in the reaction industry, of course.
You're going to react to that in the industry.
Can I actually can I bring it to theme parks a little bit?
I have a little like I have a little challenge that I think
just to tie some things together.
There are, of course, some bars in the world of theme parks
that do kind of have stories, backstories.
Yes. And there where there is like a canon to it.
And I just thought I'd propose and anybody jump in there
how Taffer might go about rescuing certain theme park.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Let me start with an obvious one, perhaps Ogas Cantina.
You're over serving.
You're over pouring.
You're making people get two drinks at once.
This aliens lay eggs in this tank and the tank is dirty.
The eggs are poisonous.
There's a frog in there.
There is a frog in the jar and the pipes go straight to the consumers.
They're dripping mucus and pus into the drinks.
And where are the aliens serving?
These are dirty human beings working.
Not enough droids automate.
You've got one droid here, but his programming don't work.
He thinks he's a pilot.
He needs mental health counseling.
You have him playing music.
He should be doing sous vide.
He's got so many arms.
He could be making three meals.
Play the music on a tape.
You don't need a DJ.
It's the same shit every hour.
Have you heard this thing?
He says he did seemingly create the NFL season pass
or whatever that fucking business model is that sells
the NFL games to bars, which he's part of the permanent.
He's part of the NFL Hall of Fame, was part of the board of directors
at some point or something.
But basically, as a bar guy was like, we should have some unified program.
I don't know. Everyone gives him credit for that.
He also keeps saying in interviews, I found that he's the only man
in America with a patent on a music organizational system
for public spaces or something like that.
It's a weirdly convoluted thing.
And only in the Nerdist episode did he kind of get into it
where he's like, I spent seven years studying the science
of how emotions make people feel with music
and get them to do different things at bars.
And I have a system where you can't play the same song the same day,
but you need to know how to adjust to the crowd.
And he the one study throughout was I with music
can do anything I want to a crowd.
I can get gang members out of a bar in three weeks.
I heard this. He said, I've musically eradicated a bar
from the gang members in three weeks time.
And then it's like, what do you mean?
And he goes, two out of every three songs are a female artist.
That's his only follow up explanation.
But you have a lot to say to Rex.
Do the gang members have to go through the butt funnel?
Presumably.
That's a very small entry.
X, X awaited the dance floor.
So everyone has to lean in to get to know each other
a little more with their crawls and bands.
I've eradicated a bar of storm troopers.
It is a fascinating thing, though, where like Taffer is like,
the butt funnel is one of my big inventions.
You need a space that's too hard to walk through.
So people are forced to interact because people go to bars to meet people.
And you're like, oh, so you basically like have created
like a tunnel of sexual harassment.
It's fire hazard.
Yeah, that's why he calls it a butt funnel.
It's like a core.
It's like a fucking corridor that forces people to get uncomfortably
close to each other while very drunk.
This drink with the word pussy in it is disgusting.
This system I've implemented nationwide with butt in it is perfection.
He's only comfortable with his sexuality, he says.
Oh, I heard that's what you said, too.
Yeah, you want to control control it.
Yeah. Oh, go. Oh, go.
Come here. Come here.
I went to the stand at the entrance.
You see where we're at right now.
All right. Look over there.
That's the closest bathroom.
That's one block away.
Why are there no bathrooms in your establishment?
Why are there no bathrooms here?
And then people have to take dirty bathroom return cards.
That card's been in the bathroom.
The median income on Batu is over 25000 credits.
Why do you call it August Cantina?
It's an ego stroke.
Your name's not even that you won't even appear in this place.
Look around this area.
Seventy percent of the surrounding businesses are frontier themed.
You need to appeal to that clientele.
All right. Here we go. Rebranding.
Three, two, one. The spur.
There you go.
That is genuinely what Taffer would do is he'd go to Olga's ago.
You have to appeal to the frontier land crowd.
And then it's the one frontier land bar in a Star Wars area.
Take a look at this on the map right around the corner.
Big you have railroad workers coming in here.
They want to think about they don't want rails.
You could call it the sidecar, the caboose.
We're going to serve the caboose.
And this girl with the big hair is going to teach you how to make it.
It's got 25 ingredients.
This part of town's been through some rough times.
This used to be credit country.
That industry failed.
People don't know where to go.
Entire critter bands have been evicted and replaced by cheaper ones
with less characters in them.
I'm bringing in my expert chef, Dexter Jetster.
He's going to overhaul the whole menu.
Olga, what you used to have a fire in you.
I read about you.
You were going to put a dinner theater right behind this bar.
That never happened.
Instead, you're addicted to Dexter's death sticks.
If he should, if he had if he had gotten into the star cruiser,
it would never closed.
Yeah. Well, it's that whole thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. He would have identified right away.
Yeah. There's pillars in the way people can't see the show.
I've got an idea for a rebranding.
Here we go. Three, two, one.
The Imagineering Office.
I've sent Jenny Nicholson in.
She's one of the biggest influencers in this space.
Just one four hour video could make or break this establishment.
You know, it's a really depressing one.
There's like a season five episode where he sends
fucking David Portnoy, Dave Portnoy in Barstool Sports.
And that way, he's like, you're a bar sir's pizza.
This is Dave Portnoy.
He's the most important man in pizza.
One word from him could make or break your business.
I'm like, oh, this is like classic fucking taffer blow up.
And now you read these articles of like pizzerias
that are clinging on for dear life because like Portnoy
started a flame war with them and now people like jam their phone
number all day saying like, Baba booey.
And you're like, this guy actually is like a force who is able to like.
Oh, in a dark way. Oh, no.
But also now everyone has to curry favor with him because they're like,
if he likes us, then the business like goes through the roof.
Oh, Jesus. It didn't save Pizza Rizzo.
It didn't save. Did Portnoy ever do Pizza Rizzo?
Yeah, I've gotten the Portnoy Pizza Rizzo.
This year, over one rat themed pizza restaurant will close its doors forever.
If he's not careful, local pizza maker Rizzo.
I can't believe it took us this many years to get to Portnoy
One Bite Pizza Rizzo and Taffer Galactic Star Cruiser Rescue.
Take a look at these guys.
These these old men, these two old men,
they're they're influencers in the theater community.
They if they criticize a live production, it might close its doors forever.
They make a punny joke about you.
If they do a single heckle of your restaurant, you're done for.
If Stadler and Wolderf get on Yelp.
Oh, no, that then.
If it happened, and maybe then that could be a stand up bit
worthy of Carrot Top or John Taffer himself.
Well, are we sort of getting to that?
Has this been ample time?
One thing I think is funny is that a lot of people woke up
or whatever that people encountered this episode and went, sorry,
two and a half hours on the turnstiles.
Although I think they would.
I don't know. I don't think they would have been.
I think they would have gone, let's go.
I think that's the only note
I wrote down that I want to hit as a bullet point that I didn't get to to get today.
And forgive me if this has been covered in a past episode.
Do we know? Did we know previously
that he was involved for years with the Rainforest Cafe?
No, no.
He threw this out, I think, in the Rob Lowe, because Rob Lowe
was talking about like the rise and falls of these things where he's like,
I remember when Hard Rock was actually cool.
And then now they became this like mainstream thing.
And he's like, what about Planet Hollywood?
And Taffer was breaking down the differences in business models
where he was like Hard Rock when it started
advertised having the best burger in the world.
They actually did have a great burger.
And then Jimi Hendrix came and he left his guitar because he liked it.
And that was the first piece of memorabilia they had.
That's why it happened. That's what he said.
Wow. Also, Rocky 4 is based on John Taffer's personal life.
Not just the robot, but the toughness of a great Italian man.
Yeah, Rocky is me.
Yeah, I met this guy, this failing actor Stallone.
I said, you know what you should do?
You should do a story about boxing.
Yeah, but with a heart of gold.
I texted this to you guys last night that one website says that Taffer,
the origin of the name is Tavern. Oh, right, right.
That it's a last name based in the tradition of the Tavern Keeper.
And it's like, I'm going to plant something on on Google
that maybe people maybe.
Yeah. But he was saying that was the origin of hard rock.
And then he was like, and then Robert came in and Planet Hollywood
was done the opposite way, where it was memorabilia first.
And then he was like, and then like Rainforest Cafe.
And he was like, well, I worked with Rainforest Cafe for many years.
And, you know, it was a silly mob.
And then he explained it.
This is the other thing I'll say about these podcasts I listen to talking about.
Is Taffer dumb?
Does his suggest or his suggestions like stupid?
Do they not work or whatever?
I listen to four random podcast episodes and each one of them.
There was at least one five minute run he went on where I was like,
this is the first time you've actually sounded like you know what you're talking
about, where he is speaking calmly and getting into like hard data
and saying concepts I have never heard in over a decade of Bar Rescue.
Where I'm like, there is something here.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was breaking down like the analytics of like, here's what I've learned
over 40 years of doing this and this and that, and was talking about
like the margins on drinks in a way where I'm like, I've never heard
this monologue in an episode.
And this feels like basic stuff.
Huh? Well, and there may be something, there may be some disconnect to that,
like applying like the science that you get of how a Bubba Gumps
or Rainforest Cafe works to some bar where a guy just wanted to have
his five sad friends around. Yes.
That's what I think.
Where I think it all falls apart is like, we're going to do the stress test.
We have people at every table.
They don't want people at every table.
They don't want to be failing, but it's their worst nightmare
to have a full crowd of people come in.
We cramped 500 people into a clown car.
If they can't handle this, you should be at business.
But this is my big discovery from like this this bit of a dive,
is that like it sounds like a lot of his resume between the troubadour
and pulsations and like Bar Rescue was like him having success
launching bars or clubs and then becoming this high level consultant
for like these very corporate enterprises that were like,
how do we make this work? Yeah.
We know we should have Cheers in an airport or Bubba Gump in a strip mall,
you know, or like, how do we scale Rainforest Cafe up or whatever?
And he used like 10 terms I'd never heard before that were kind of interesting
where he was like, I don't know, he called like an atmosphere packet
or whatever it was where he was talking about like, well,
Rainforest had a different model.
It was about this and it was about that.
And that's how they scaled it up.
And I was like, all of this is kind of interesting,
but it also means he's particularly all suited to like a small dive bar
because the only thing he knows how to turn it into is like something
that could be franchised that is kind of like bland and automated enough
and kind of like refillable.
Mm hmm. I don't know.
I think the study has has legs.
I think we're going to be five hundred the studies across the country.
He's very numbers guy. Yeah.
So like I'm assuming he has like some sort of I don't even want to call an expert.
Maybe it is an expertise in numbers or something.
He's an aspect. But I would love to hear.
I've never like he doesn't seem like he overlaps with the Tillman
for titas of the world.
No, but yet when he's talking about like turnover at tables
and trying to like maximize profits and whatever and like this corner
of the bar should be worth one million dollars a year. Right.
I'm like, what he's saying makes sense for like Applebee's in Times Square.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like perfect sense where I'm like, if I run that,
I call him and go fix my business because it's Applebee's in Times Square.
You just want this thing to fucking run like a machine.
It's bad. It's also just the it's it's bad for the world
to think of everything like that. Yes.
Yeah, because things are supposed to have character and be odd.
And like pirates wasn't good.
But if you applied the logic that wipes pirates of its theme. Right.
If pirates worked, yes, there would be something actually special about it.
Pirates were 10 percent good.
It would be our favorite place in America. Right.
Like the four of us are the target audience.
Oh, yeah. Even not caring about pirate specific.
When are the boys going to go to pirates?
Why haven't they done it?
Why haven't they got boys?
If you ever make it to Silver Spring, you've got to do the pirates episode.
I think Jane said when we were watching, she's like with dimples.
She's like it had more character before they changed.
There's the whole thing with it.
They certainly had to gut it to repair some of the safety issues.
A sound system seemed like it was still from the 1980s, they said.
But it's like you could have put a little more bric-a-brac in for the charm.
It didn't all just have to be black vinyl booths.
He doesn't like it.
He doesn't. The whole thing with pirates, he just didn't like it.
If anything about him, if anything about that tickled him,
then he would have been like, because that's an easy theme to kind of do.
Long John Silver's has been a pirate theme.
Tell me one example of a successful pirate chain.
Pirate Disney, I'm sure he would love Pirate's Dinner Adventure.
He would.
Oh, and the way the food, the food that they serve and the efficiency
with which they, I just know it's the sous vide.
This is the thing, though.
It's like we're fascinated by Taffer, but a big part of it is that he is so repellent
and kind of stands as an enemy to the exact type of thing we like.
Well, he's a representative of everything in culture that, like, it scares us
that I feel like the four of us are always talking about.
He's a contradiction, though, in some ways, because obviously he appreciates
imaginary, appreciates Disney and themed shit.
But he is not able to apply, like to change his thinking
when it comes to different scenarios.
He has one single focus.
So what I'm saying is numbers brain, which is the danger
of everything fun in this world, is a number brained business moron
killing all the dumb shit that we love for all the fun in the world.
Algorithm based entertainment that shouldn't survive.
He seems to have actual knowledge
and the show is entertaining on like a trashy reality TV level.
And the core of it, I do think, is him like digging into the psychology
of these people. Yeah, yeah.
And then but then he also does those like
speaker conventions at a hotel by the airport where it's like
Condoleezza Rice, General Mathis, John Taffer for small business.
But I think that's one one of the things that I remember
of other podcast like I think Matt Christman and someone else
took mushrooms and then went to like a CPAC thing in Pasadena.
Yes. Until they were kicked out and they saw like we're sitting in a conference
like a convention center watching John Taffer talk.
Oh, you're high as balls.
Oh, yeah. Isn't that that sounds better than anything.
You can see a Coachella, right?
Oh, yeah. Festival audience.
And I was I was fifth row for Taffer.
Now I'm just imagining Taffer on the Coachella poster.
Oh, headliner Taffer playing drums.
Saturday afternoon.
Oh, does he mean he comes out and just yells at everyone on stage.
What are you wearing?
Feathers. That's weird.
I've got you a new hat.
It doesn't have any feathers in it.
And it's better for blocking the sun.
My talk today is called You Do You.
Everyone write that down.
Like that lady who just wanted to play her songs and own the building.
He should have all he should have been like, all right, here's the deal.
Let's figure out a way where this doesn't sink you financially
and you can play your dumb songs till you die.
Because the part of like the the thing we joke about of like every bar
gets reverted back to what it was within three weeks
and then is out of business within four months.
Is that he goes from one extreme to another where they're like,
this is why I started the bar.
This is my emotional story.
This is why I love it.
And he's like, throw all of that fucking garbage.
You need to be worried about making money
and appealing to the blandest, broadest, like group of people possible.
And then they revolt against that.
And you're like, right.
How do you like split the atom and find a way to make both people happy?
I feel like there are a couple of episodes I've seen amidst the like 800.
Right.
But there's like the one that's like a bar in a trailer.
And the guy is like they're like safety code violations.
He does like hillbilly.
What they call like a hillbilly plumber or some shit,
where they're like everything's held together with duct tape.
And they're like, this is the charm of the place.
I'll call violations mold.
And at the end, he like redoes it and is like, I'll make like the Disney
world version of the character you had before.
Now, I don't know if that works, because I think the people who go there
don't want to go see the like in-quote self-parody version of what the bar was
before. But that was a rare example of him at least trying to keep the thing
that he liked. Yeah.
You know, what they've like identified as this is the heart of the place.
This is why our 10 loyal customers come here.
And every other place, he's like, the dream has to die.
You have to shoot it in the head. Yeah.
Some of that wouldn't work in Philadelphia, because one of the things
about certain bars in certain neighborhoods, it'll just be a blocker,
a few blocks of row houses, townhouses.
Yeah. And the corner house, the bottom floor, the ground floor is a bar.
Yeah. But that is like basically a wreck through that.
But do you don't want to try to run that bar like the rain forest cafe?
I'm afraid you want the same 20 bar flight.
With Moe's, you basically like he should not try to fix Moe's.
They're not the most entertaining episodes, but the most effective
episodes are the ones where he just stumbles onto a poorly run bar.
Yes. You know, he hasn't tried to change the character.
Right. Where it's like this bar already has no identity.
Right. Yeah. And it's just not operating well.
Yeah. And he's just sort of like, how do I tighten this up?
It's like because you can't change the core character of things like this.
Like, let's say there was a podcast and maybe the branding of it was kind of
confusing because it bills itself as a podcast about theme parks.
But then the character, the heart of it is that all of this other bullshit is
talked about at extreme length.
And maybe some corporate person would come in and say, you need to like, you
should crank this out like an assembly line.
Right. And you know, to hear talk about a ride and keep the episode to an hour,
90 minutes or so.
The last time you were on, there was a gift that didn't come in during the
episode. I don't know if I said it on the show that the gifts did it ended up
coming. It became not what it was, not what I suspected, which was a bunch more
Kingo toys I would never do that for my first son.
For my second, you sent a bunch of sprites.
You said the exact variety, five of Funko's, five of action figures and five
key chains of Sprite Sprite is another character from The Eternals.
Yes. Now I thought Sprite would drive you particularly crazy because Sprite is
the Peter Pan of The Eternals, the ultimate Peter.
It's the being a pirate is the ultimate Sprite syndrome.
She's a little girl who can never grow up.
This is the creepiest shit.
And there's like somebody who wants to be with Sprite.
No, Sprite wants to be with Richard Madden.
OK, and she has a complex about the fact that Richard Madden will never be with
her because he doesn't want to look like a pedophile.
What a wonderful story for a great superhero epic.
And what if he's got this weird kink where he's sexually attracted to women who
look like adults and thus Sprite is always heartbroken.
This is how this narrative plays out.
She sees him kissing Gemma Chan and gets angry and almost becomes bad out of revolt.
Wow. Yeah.
So what if there was this this kind of creepy element to the story?
Yeah. And on top of it, it was the boringest movie ever made.
So anyway, I but I did want to thank you for that for that gift for my second son.
And I also it we've been recording a while.
It's getting a little hot in here.
Here we go. And I wanted to.
Oh, look at that. Oh, I happen to be wearing.
Yeah. Something from Griffin's second round of gifts.
The website Boxlaunch connected to Boxlaunch.com, connected to the chain of
mall, mostly mall based stores.
Oh, yes. It's having a sale on some other items I wanted.
And I was trying to hit like some some free shipping minimums.
Yeah, of course. I was like, what else do they have that I maybe want?
I was just doing, you know, I do that keyword searches for brands.
I like my favorite IP. Yeah.
And I was like, do they have any deep discount Eternals merch?
And what I found is specifically that they sell two different kinds
of Sprite and Kingo shirts. Sprite.
And yes, we should say that's the shirt.
It is Sprite and Kingo together.
I can't really say.
Yeah. Only the two characters that I have.
Oh, great. Great.
Scott's children with the character. Yes.
But you have decided that my oldest is a Kingo kid
and my youngest is a Sprite kid.
And that's how it will be. Yeah.
But you were also kind enough to make this a a a pair shirt.
You got a pretty matching child coordination shirts, coordination
so that I could have one and so that my son could have one.
So here a photo from earlier today.
But a different Sprite and Kingo.
Yes, a totally different shirt, but still with Sprite and with Kingo
on the same sides, there is one for my oldest son.
And I am wearing one as well.
And then there's an entire other one that's like the like
it's like the magical patterns of goo is a costume shirt.
They are shirts that represent really uniform.
Oh, wow. Famous Eternals
fucking space garbage that's on their uniforms.
So there's a you can be Sprite and Kingo. Wow.
I don't think that my oldest even knows that there is more that there
is there are more Kingo shirts available.
But yeah, we will get to go out and be the envy of all the dads and kids in town.
I forgot I did.
I forget if I ruined it.
But when you said I didn't know about it, but when you said
there's a new package coming, I pulled up all the eternal action figures.
And I was like, I in my head, I may have texted him.
I was like, I will bet a hundred dollars that he picked Sprite.
You got it right.
Yeah, which is the only way I was possibly previously familiar with Sprite.
But now I am. Thank you.
Mike and I did some back and forth because I was like,
is Fastos the second funniest?
But Fastos doesn't come in the the pocket pop keychain form factor.
That was a big, big role.
It has to be a character that fits into these pre-established patterns
with the Kingo.
And then I was like, I could do Crow, the evil deviant.
But Mike agreed that it might be too scary for your children.
You don't want that.
Yeah, no, no.
I want a story that everybody can get behind, like a eternal girl
who wants to have sex with a man.
Something great for my baby.
Yeah, to be a lot more appropriate.
Start the world thinking about.
And I also I believe to make this a mega episode,
I don't think that's the final reveal.
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, if here's the thing,
Griffin, I have your Galactic Star Cruiser toy right here.
Amazing. You mean yours?
Wait, not Galactic Star Cruiser. Yeah.
Yeah. Yes.
Yes. You got the names wrong.
Star Speeder is right here.
It's so much bigger than I thought it was.
It's giant.
About three feet tall.
How are you going to transport that?
I brought extra empty luggage from D23 to get this back home.
And I'm still going to have to do some adjusting.
You listener, you this is so huge.
And it's also what I think now what's happened is that it's like
you put it perfectly in a place where I can't see Jason.
Right. It's massive.
More than blocks Jason.
And there's a whole discussion
that's going to have to happen off the air because we I have pulled
the carded Rex out of the box
because it was we were going to try to just put it on eBay
and recoup some of the cost.
But then it's a carded and a loose.
There's a loose Rex in there, which is the same one.
But this is a carded Rex.
And we have to have a whole debate off the air of what we're going to do
about this. Maybe nothing.
But I also want to say that I have gotten everyone a gift.
What? Same gift.
And maybe Griffin has this already and it's sort of redundant.
But I just wanted to make sure that there was a character
you could put in to the Starspeeder immediately.
OK, where are we going?
Sitting on this for about a year, maybe a year.
This actually just lined up perfectly.
I have a guess what I am going to give everyone a Miles Quaradge
Oh, my God.
From Avatar. Wow.
Everyone got them.
They were on a nice discount on Best Buy dot com.
OK, I got to stand that.
You can hand one to Griffin.
And of course, you see, he comes with his trademark cup of coffee. Right.
And he fits. I already he's already in my this perfect scale.
He's already in my Starspeeder, because the problem is,
is that you need something in a specific scale because the seat
there are the exact amount of seats in this toy that there are
on the actual Star Tours ride.
But you need toys at this scale with knees that bend.
Yeah, it's very important because some of the different toys
I have that are this size don't have bendable knees.
You can't use reactions.
You've got to go can't unless it's power force to these knees.
Look at these. Look at these.
They can't even bend.
What kind of figure is that?
Well, I'll say it.
So Mike and I were very invested in trying to get the Starspeeder
when they went up very quickly on the Disney store site.
And I had a fancy one with the script where it plays the ride.
It was very limited and went like super fast.
We were waiting on line online for like a fucking hour.
Yeah. And then I found a hack that I thought would maybe help me get one.
And it didn't work for me, but it worked for Mike.
But Mike had also bid on one on eBay.
So and then this is the extra one he had,
which he'd been holding for me for a while now.
I similarly at New York Comic Con at your request.
Yes, of course.
Got you an action figure of Kevin Eastman, co-creator of Ninja Turtles.
So dressed as a garbage man from a deleted scene of the first live action movie,
but included in here also from New York Comic Con are a pack of blues.
The mascot of Thrilljoy.
Oh, wow.
Well, we haven't even talked about that.
I met Brian Marriotti, the former CEO of Funko.
We got Marriotti stuff.
Mike likes blue.
Mike thinks blue is cute.
I think this new mascot character, blue is cute.
But then here's an extra bonus.
I bought some other bullshit on eBay recently, and because I bought enough of his stuff,
the eBay seller threw in a mass amount of Batman Forever PVC.
So I think I have two Kilmers and two Chris O'Donnells in here.
Oh, wow.
This is a little a little gift bag for Mike.
Well, I mean, if they're the same as Batman, I mean, I can I can spread the joy,
the thrill joy around of.
Jason, I've been I've been hinting for a long time.
I have a thing I've been trying to get to you.
Logistically, it's been a little difficult to make sure.
And it's not from the dollhouse museum that you said you were stopping at.
It's not which I did stop at.
OK, I woke up this morning in Santa Barbara, made a quick stop at the dollhouse,
the Teddy Bear and Doll Museum.
That's pretty excellent.
Wow. A big discovery I found there, Mike, that I think I need to put on your radar
if I can take the pin out of puppets from. Oh, right.
Oh, my God.
You know, we are at almost three hours as you know, we're approaching three hours.
Sherry Lewis doll, the doll of the woman, Sherry.
Correct. Mass produced was on a shelf with Buffalo Bob from Howdy Doody,
who I know was not strictly the puppeteer of Howdy Doody.
But I am now like, is there a entire sub universe
of merchandise of the people behind the ventriloquist?
Because it was above ventriloquist shelf, which had it did not have a Knucklehead
Smith, sadly, but it did have a Charlie McCarthy.
OK, it had a he was more and more snared.
Why would they not make a Jerry Mahoney?
That's a reference people are making all the time.
I did have a German.
I was like, where's the Hector Bergdahl?
Where's the Hector Bergdahl?
But I just I now know there's a Buffalo Bob and a Sherry Lewis.
Interesting. What does it look like?
Doll that says Little Sherry.
Is she like a baby?
It's just a little Sherry, the same size as a really got to find little Sherry.
Little Sherry.
I actually have a topic next month.
I had to introduce a little Sherry.
Enjoy your five percent, little Sherry.
No, madam.
Fine. No, I actually have packed a peanut butter and jelly,
knowing this would happen today, and I am looking forward to eating it
because I am running it as the let's do it.
So, Jason, let's wrap it up.
Wait, Griffin's a guest.
What do you got? Final reveal.
OK, so I think it was a year or two ago.
It was after I'd done the first Kingo drop of the mass amounts of
where Mike bought you a creepy,
stylized Japanese toy of director rock and tour.
Kevin Smith, a posket, I believe it was called.
Yep. Yeah.
And on my key invoked me to say, now Griffin has a tendency,
our friend Griffin, to sometimes buy multiples of an item.
Oh, no. Perhaps this will encourage him to buy multiples.
And I originally that was my plan.
Going to buy several of these at discount.
OK, and just bombard you with Kevin Smith.
And then I was like, is there a more meaningful thing I can do here?
And it took a little while logistically to make happen.
But especially you've had a year or two of high highs and low lows.
Yeah. I owe you multiple.
I've been feeling like it's been building of like,
I need to give you something meaningful,
both in commiseration and celebration and everything.
So this is a cute posket signed by Kevin Smith.
Oh, my God. Now, here is the funny part of this.
We I kept trying to get in person interactions with him.
He was supposed to do the podcast in studio a couple of times.
Then one time I was out here and I saw him, but I forgot to pack it.
It kept not lining up at the last second.
And then we did George Lucas talk show at his theater in New Jersey.
And as I was changing out of the Watto costume
and I knew he was going to run off quickly, I was like,
I forgot to get him to sign this.
Patrick, can you go give this to him and get him to sign it?
And he went sure. And he brought it back.
And so it is signed.
I heart you, Kevin Smith.
I saw. I love it.
Which I didn't say it's for me.
I didn't say it's for you.
But I think the message translates.
We all heart you, Kevin Smith, most of all. Right.
Wow. That's really beautiful.
Yeah. Well, Jason, let Kevin Smith's love of you,
his heart of you, resonate
and power you through stuff.
That's beautiful. My God.
Now I just need to get him to sign 10 more of them.
Oh, where are those?
Wow. Geez, a massive.
There's never been more on the table.
I mean, this is a gigantic box.
Yeah. What are you going to do with this?
I don't know. I really want you guys to see it,
but we can't do that on the air.
Oh, the I want you to see what looks because you guys
have not come over and seen the.
No, no, no, we haven't.
We haven't been invited.
Well, that's our speeder party. That's true.
Yeah. No, the scale is massive.
We'll post photos of it.
But Griffin, the greatest gift that you gave us
was coming in here, veering us off topic
in an original Star Tours kind of way and sending us
on a much more entertaining adventure full of twists
and turns through the world of Taffer one.
An adventure that's just beginning.
I mean, we've already referred to nine,
which is the amount of the original Star Wars.
Yeah. So we'll at least get to nine, you know,
and then we'll end up with our Rogue Ones and our solos.
Taffer side stories. Yeah, yeah.
I'm looking forward to all of it.
But I guess for now, my God, Griffin Newman,
you survived podcast The Ride.
What a time. Exit to the gift shop.
Any energy left in which to plug anything?
Blank check.
Podcasts, Griffin and David were doing a miniseries
on Steven Spielberg right now.
Followed up by a miniseries on the work of Jon Taffer.
You're also doing it.
You're going through episode by episode.
Yes, I'm treating him as an auteur of bars.
We're shifting our format a little bit.
We have an episode in the planning stages.
In theory, that would be a PTR-BC crossover
that hopefully will happen soon.
We've got to figure out some of the logistics of it.
Also, years ago on this podcast,
I mentioned that there was a movie I got cast in,
largely because the director was a listener of this show.
Yeah, indeed.
The great Michael Taberski, who then I went to,
it premiered at a film festival in Europe last fall.
So then we went to Disneyland Paris together
and had this very nice full circle,
we're getting to go to a theme park together moment.
Anyway, this movie got released on VOD
very suddenly without much advanced warning.
Oh, sure.
That sounds like how things go, yes.
Very much the state of the industry,
but we're trying to do ketchup, promoting it now.
So it's called Turn Me On.
It's Bell Powley and Nick Robinson are the leads,
but a bunch of comedy people like Darcy Carden
and Patty Harrison are also up in it.
Julie Shiplett, who's a great standup.
And it's like a dystopian sci-fi relationship satire thing.
Oh, wow.
It's rentable in most places.
And half the length of this episode?
It's, yeah, just half.
Okay.
I think it's pretty close to 90.
It'll go down, it'll go down a smooth level,
less challenging work.
We don't like things if they're not three hours.
Three hours and a threatened part one of nine.
Okay.
Well, it's really, it's, I mean,
it's less our Star Wars and more our Avatar,
with the run times, with the,
now it's just on us to release them, you know,
with a better pace than, you know,
to not have the amount of time between
Fire and Ash. Fire and Ash.
Yeah, yeah. Fire and Ash.
Yeah, God, we really gotta put a pin in Pelak.
Pelak the Wind Traitor.
Oh, my God.
We don't have time. We gotta get out the door.
Because as for us, for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcasts that are at the second gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier Club Three,
where this entire taffer mess began.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast,
the right, I found the guy who suggested it,
Jordan Kegel.
There you go, Jordan.
Two years later.
Are you happy now?
You better be.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.