Right now, the Club 3 executives are upstairs,
and they're meeting, and this meeting is going to determine the fate of this entire episode.
So I'm a little bit nervous. We're hearing the entire topic may be changed,
it might be thrown out, we might have to start over.
We're hearing that the Jason character may be cut altogether.
I don't know. We're waiting. Wait a minute, wait a minute, he's here.
I guess he's not cut. Jason Sheridan is here.
I heard they added him back in. Like 10%.
After some of the test screenings. Sting fought for him to be back.
And I appreciate that. I always appreciate when Sting and Trudy...
Put their thumb on the scale.
Yeah, put their thumb on the scale.
Now, like, one month I'm out, another month they're like,
oh, your part has been increased like 100%, and poof, boy, it's a swing, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, it's the kind of stuff that happens in a sweat box situation,
and we just have to be happy that artists like Sting and Trudy have your back,
and so do we, but ultimately we just follow orders here.
We've got to wait for the Club 3 executives to work in.
They're very opinionated. They rarely do,
but the amount of power the three of us have on the show,
especially in Club 3, is limited.
That's right, yeah.
They come in every three months, they muck it all up, they change everything,
and it can be stressful.
And look, I don't want to get too personal between your relationship with you and Sting,
but is there a bond when it comes to the sexual arts, the tantric arts?
Oh, well, we've all seen that picture, and someone had to take it.
Now you have immediately thrown out a reference that you said we've all seen,
and I have not.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is it a Sting? Is it a picture of Sting?
Oh, you've got to find the picture of Sting and Trudy.
You've stumped us.
Sting, can you describe it? What would we, how would we find,
what's happening in the picture?
Well, one of them's like, I feel like...
Is it like a two lovers...
What are you going to type in to find it? That's the question.
Sting and Jason naked. Is that what you're typing in?
Is it you, it's him and Trudy, it's not you and Sting or you and Trudy.
Jason in Hour 10 of Tantric lovemaking session with Styler Klan.
Jason with notepad taking notes, watching Sting and Trudy in Hour 10 of Tantric.
Mentor-mentee relationship.
Among the notes, wow, all three of us are way past Mike and Scott.
Right. We are so much more comfortable than these two losers.
What are you, bring us in on your process.
I'm trying to find this.
Do you have it on your photo roll? Are you finding it in your saved photos?
Is it Sting? Is it of Sting? Is that what you're thinking?
We can get to it faster, I think, if you tell us.
It's Sting and Trudy.
Yeah, I have that typed in.
Maggie Sarota, a music writer who used to have a podcast with Tom Sharpling called The Low Times or that interview possession.
Got it, got it. If it's what she, that helps me, thank you.
Is it a weird Christmas card where he's holding a weird old guitar and she is in a leotard and she's very flexible.
That's exactly.
And they're in front of a bunch of candles and stuff.
I apologize. I apologize.
I may have, you know, Maggie may have posted it so many times.
It's just ingrained in my mind and I thought it was a little more.
You thought it was more like a John Lennon, Yoko Ono, two lovers photo.
I have never chanced upon this photo, but I'm glad that I have now.
They both look incredible.
I don't know what age they are.
It doesn't matter.
There's only mild signs in their other, in their immaculate bodies and faces that they're anywhere north of 50.
But they're both like true specimens.
They're so jealous.
And what a setup. My God, this like, it's like the basement of a winery and then like 25 candles in the frame.
Wait here, I'll turn it.
I'm not seeing it.
Yeah, yeah, there you go.
Oh, I have seen this, yes.
You have seen the photo.
I have seen the photo, yes.
No, it's interesting because I didn't know if the photo would be like overtly sexual.
And it is because they're gods amongst men, but they aren't having sex in it.
It's just kind of, this is like the ritual.
They do six hours of this before they do 10 hours of that.
Jealous.
I wonder if they are using that Steve Harvey red light that I'm kind of obsessed with.
I haven't done it yet, but I'm very obsessed with red light as a way to like make your skin look more youthful.
Infrared light?
I don't know what kind of red light it is.
I bet not. If you were red, it wouldn't be infrared.
Those are different things.
Yeah, I don't think it's infrared.
But it's some sort of red light.
And then a friend of mine who does some PR marketing type things was working for a company that has a new red light mask.
And I saw a photo of the mask and I go, can you get me one of these masks?
You've already pursued the red light mask?
I'm interested, yeah.
And it sounded like a maybe because it's a very expensive red light mask.
It's like $500.
What I'm gathering from all this is that unlike Roxanne, you do have to turn on the red light.
That's pretty good, right?
Very good, yeah.
I'm glad I found it.
Tied two together. Yeah, that was really good.
That was really good.
Great, great.
Well, you know, we're going to get maybe we can go all over the place a little bit, but maybe something to talk about is any of our relationships to Sting.
Because what we are talking about here is Sting is very much the star of this, and it's a documentary made by Sting's wife.
Obviously, we have these associations with the sexual nature of things.
And to be clear, the sweat box, the topic does not refer to Sting and Trudy's bedroom.
No, I mean, the stress of working on this movie likely led to some tantric encounters when it's just like, I just need to take my mind off.
This is just cut the llama song.
I just can you just give me 14 hours, please?
I just need a quick 14 hours.
I'll that's that's I'll rush it.
Yeah.
And then I should be good.
But yeah, how do you feel about Sting?
Yeah, yeah, it's interesting with Sting.
I like Sting the man.
I like he's he amuses me in this.
Like, I don't like seeing him like, oh, shit, this is such a pain in the ass.
Like, there's such a funny energy coming from him.
And I know he's like, that's kind of like, oh, God, like, I don't want him to suffer.
But it is he's amusing me in this.
Well, he's because he's there's like a stuffy it's like, oh, boy, he's a funny character to see having to roll his eyes and write angry letters.
I mean, it's truly a great person to see in a like, you know, works on all kind of situation.
So I like that.
I like that.
I like that he's on the Simpson episode where he's helping save the part.
Oh, yeah.
Which was supposed to be Springsteen.
I read somebody on some Simpson interview.
And they were like, oh, we've got Sting.
And then I do like the big hit police songs.
I do like them.
I feel like I hear them a lot.
I really do like the arrangements.
So I do think I'm a fan of all three of these guys because the songs themselves sound cool to me.
Yeah.
Like the way I was late to arrive in any of the but yeah, some of those.
Driven to tears and those kind of like even then like not the three main hit like you go.
Yeah.
Some great ones.
But yes, then you get to 90s thing and brutal desert rose.
And I'm just it's less interesting to me.
And again, I think we've maybe touched a little bit about upon it.
But it's like maybe there's some better Sting stuff, but it's all pretty like heavy.
And it's ponderous.
The wondrous is a word.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I was in my head.
I mean, I think when I was trying to dissect this, like what is your why do you struggle with Sting?
I ended up looking at his discography.
And if you just say the names of his solo studio albums, it answers the question for you.
The dream of the blue turtles, the soul cages, ten Summoner's Tales, songs from the labyrinth.
Wait, isn't the guitars from the police Andy Sumner?
Is it Sumner?
Isn't Sumner is the guy's name?
I think Andy Sumner from the police.
It's not Summoner, right?
But it sounds close.
And he's not.
He's not.
He's not related to Alf Gordon.
Gordon Shumway.
No, no.
You're right.
Gordon Shumway.
Who am I thinking that is the last name?
Sumner.
There is a Sumner out there.
There is.
Sumner Redheart is who you're thinking of.
And those things aren't related either.
There's also someone named Joe Sumner.
Who is that?
Maybe I'm just thinking of Sumner Redstone.
I mean, I'm always thinking of Sumner.
Listener, if you could see the two of them furiously trying to find the name of this
guitar on their laptops.
Yeah.
And then Stewart Copeland is the drummer from the police.
I know that.
They all seem cool.
They all seem cool, yeah.
Yeah.
So I was just wondering if he named it very similar to his old guitars.
I like the police, but here's how I very late coming to my music knowledge.
In high school, I guess it would have been about 15, I saw the movie Moulin Rouge and
I recognized some of the songs and I did not recognize some of the others.
So you thought they were Moulin Rouge originals?
There is one or two in there and I knew about that.
So when it got to the Roxanne sequence, which is very starkly filmed, it's very intense.
And I was like, wow, this is a really good song.
You did not know it was based on anything.
No, it was a police song, you know.
That is funny.
But when they're doing earlier in the movie and they do a chunk of Nirvana, I knew that
song.
Okay, great.
You did know.
Newer song, I guess.
And now in the scheme of things, what were they, less than 10 years apart?
Yeah, of course.
Even though in my mind, that's like 30 years.
I was doing some of this.
I don't like to do this like I am old math, but I couldn't help it.
I was telling you guys before we started recording.
78 was longer than 10 minutes.
Thank God.
I was telling you guys before we started recording for the kids yesterday, we ended up throwing
an impromptu birthday party for Aaron's car.
So we ended up singing Happy Birthday, Dear Kamri.
I'm not exactly sure how this transpired, but my oldest was dead set on it, and my youngest
was bouncing around some of the most he's come to life yet, still a little guy.
But I was doing math based on when my youngest was born.
Basically, we ended up putting on a bunch.
I put on what's like a birthday celebration mix we could put on, and we ended up on the
classic, the immortal I Got a Feeling by the Black Eyed Peas.
Oh yeah, of course.
And I was like, okay, that's 2009.
My son was born in 2024.
What is an equivalent song from when I was born?
And what was the one that really got me?
Bridge Over Troubled Water is as old to me as...
I've Got a Feeling.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Isn't that really upsetting, isn't it?
That is upsetting, yeah.
There's one more.
Oh, there's one that, oh, Raindrops Keep Falling on My Head.
Doesn't that feel, in my head, that song is...
100 years old.
Yeah, yeah, that's 40 years older than, which that's some of my feeling about some of these,
about like, staying to me as a kid felt like, how old was he then?
Oh, he must be 90 years old based on the kind of music he makes, which we can get into.
But you know what I should do is I should read the official submission.
And I wanted to say some other stuff.
I wanted to get into the topic a little bit first before I do the thing that we do every time,
or we're supposed to, which is we discuss what came in second place in the poll.
I can't remember what it was this month.
But given the current temperature of some of our online forums, I don't know how aware you are,
I don't know how much you've been checking this, Jason, but things are heated over in the Patreon comments.
And it's making me wonder if it's best to not say anything.
So that's the tack that I'm taking this time.
Even though it's a tradition, we've always done this.
We've always referred to what is the runner-up.
This is in the official constitution of Club 3.
Yep.
And the runner-up stays.
It was nominated by a person.
Whatever was in second place was nominated by a person.
What I think it's important to reiterate here is that no process has changed for this particular topic.
And in fact, the topic rolling over again and again has happened before.
It happened with the masked magician.
And things remain pretty calm, pretty civil when it was the masked magician.
But now that it's happening for the masked musician, the tenor of things has changed.
So that is why I'm not going to say the topic.
I'm not going to say the potential guest's name.
I'm not even going to say what kind of sauce he likes.
You know what it is.
It's on the table.
In fact, I think that this particular topic's rise from 26% to 34% in the last month says more than I would ever need to.
So you know what the topic is.
You can vote for it if you want to.
You cannot vote for it if you want to.
Nothing has changed.
And speaking of things not changing, as always, it is your right to not vote for whatever puppet Mike picks for next month in the poll.
It is your right to help it.
What did my puppet get this month?
8%, 7?
Less than 10.
Yeah, less than 10 for sure.
Or 10 or less.
I said this in a text message somewhere.
There's that quote about the definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over and expecting different results.
And that doesn't apply here because technically you are picking different puppets.
Right.
And who said I expected it to win?
Who even said?
That's true.
Your choice does not imply that you are imagining it going all the way.
8% is the number, by the way.
8%, okay.
For lamb chop, to be clear.
Because that last time we made a big thing out of the immediate plummet of madam again.
This time you went right.
You got right back up to the plate.
Lamb chop.
8%.
Not last place.
Did the weirdos get like 20% or 15% or something?
Weirdos did okay.
The weirdos did better than lamb chop.
The weirdos are the highest performing puppets thus far.
And a lot of these, by the way, will get another chance.
I think we are overdue to do one of those like we all get one of the old topics again and give it another go.
Sure.
So maybe they take it all the way there.
We've got so many of those things.
I wonder why the weirdos though versus lamb chop.
Maybe more people don't know who lamb chop is than I'm thinking.
Once again, you pin it on people.
If they knew lamb chop, they would want to hear us talk about her and the other puppets.
In his defense, I have more memories of lamb chop as a kid.
The song that never ends became a bit much at some point.
Certainly.
In the first era.
Yeah, it never ends.
But I mean, the weirdos might have gotten a little bump because of Coldplay.
People like Coldplay.
People of different age groups like Coldplay.
I suppose.
But I don't think there's a giant gap between people who like Coldplay and people who like the weirdos or have even tracked it enough.
I think that the bump may have been because I feel like that was a particularly aiming for my aggravation topic.
The weirdos was.
Because Coldplay mixed with puppets.
Weird puppets and weird voices.
I think possibly.
That might help explain that.
Did the Henson people have something to do with making the weirdos?
I believe so.
Yeah, yeah.
So there's some Henson shine.
There's some Coldplay shine.
And that may have given them a little bit of a bump.
There's also.
I guess there's something to.
I mean, maybe you're right that Coldplay's popularity is also the fact that it's like something from the last five years and not from.
That's possible, too.
I bet there's a.
For a half second, I thought you called Lambchop Glamchop, which I think is like a really good like drag name or something.
I bet somebody has it already at this point.
That's a potential rebranding that Mallory Lewis, Sherry Lewis's daughter.
Right.
Could and should look into.
Glamchop.
But yeah.
But for now, we have landed on this, which, by the way, was also my choice.
There are people.
Oh, yeah.
There are people in here saying, like, if Scott wants X topic to win so badly, why doesn't he?
But I don't.
Who says I want that?
I just want good topics to win the Club 3 poll and I want democracy to prevail, which is why I'm thrilled that the Sweatbox won.
Yeah.
That's giving me first and second place and a 75 percent share.
We all.
Of the votes this month.
I don't want anything so bad.
I'm doing great.
I'm on top of the world, gang.
Good topics.
Well, that's what I want, too.
It's just good old fashioned topics.
Uh huh.
With characters that are made out of felt or cloth or have a little stuffing in their cheeks.
Or the most creepily shaped wood that's ever been shaped.
That's right.
Or a wooden, a little wooden boy.
Well, what is the little wooden boy?
Anything you're you're hoping to do in the near future?
Oh, no, I was the one who was very enthusiastic about hunting this movie down.
And you hopefully said because I had only found a YouTube playlist that was doing the trick of putting the video in a real little in the corner.
Yes.
Because we talked about this a little bit ago and I was surprised you guys hadn't seen it.
And yeah, the only version on YouTube.
Yes, it's squeezed into the bottom and flipped backwards.
That's making it a pretty impossible watch.
Yes.
And and but thanks to listeners, you you passed along that you could find it on Archive.org.
Archive.org much like many great treasures.
So thank you.
Thank you.
Whoever figured that out.
Yeah.
Thank you to Bobby Libby, who pushed it over the edge and made it an actionable episode.
Bobby says, have the boys actually done an episode on The Sweatbox, the documentary by Sting's wife about the making of the movie that became The Emperor's New Groove?
It came up recently on an episode, but it's a great watch that merits a deep dive.
Thank you, Bobby.
Agreed.
And that sums it up pretty well.
This is technically a making of documentary about The Emperor's New Groove.
But when it began, it was about the making of a very different film called Kingdom of the Sun that had a lot of the elements that ended up in Emperor's New Groove.
Like as you join the creative process in progress, you have a lot of what we know from this film.
It's Eartha Kitt as Yzma.
It's David Spade as Kuzco.
It's about the Incans and Sting is doing music for it.
And all of that ended up in the movie, but all radically rearranged and changed around.
Some of the events of which you get to see in this film, which makes it a very fascinating watch.
Now, when it started, I was a little confused about like, wow, this is really polished in terms of the way everyone was composing themselves.
Was that kind of weird, restrained, Disney like, oh, we're keeping, we're being professional and complimentary to the company, but you can just see the rage in their eyes.
Because I feel like everyone, but I feel like people are being pretty, you know, respectful.
But occasionally what they were saying was pretty brutal.
So I was quotes. There's some quotes in this for sure.
There are some quotes. And so I was like, what is the, you know, ownership of this?
And the Walt Disney Company does own the rights to this.
It was shot by Sting's wife.
An edited version exists on the Emperor's New Groove DVD.
Yes, it was.
This footage was reappropriated for a very like, I haven't watched it, but I would imagine kind of a more sanitized, like typical DVD making.
Is it, did it become about like, here's what it took to make the song in the movie?
I haven't watched it either, but they, I think it was very similar to this.
And long enough that they aired it, they showed it at film festivals and did a week long run in LA for Oscars.
That was of that or it was of the sweat box?
Of the edited version is what I saw.
Are you sure about that? Because I feel like.
I'm not 100% sure.
I think the sweat box did, again, I don't know what that DVD special feature is, but I imagine it's kind of like standard fare.
Right.
I feel like I do think they gave like some amount of screening to the sweat.
I think that because I think the sweat box got out there enough where there was some like murmuring about it.
And I think people involved in the making of the movie went to see it because they were like dying for the truth to be told.
And I think they went and they booed certain figures.
Yes.
And then I think that that initial reaction caused Disney to go, OK, this is like too close to the bone.
I don't think we can like put out something this honest.
And they kind of sucked it back, which is why the version that you watch on Archive.org is like finished, cut, like a very clean watch.
But then at some point it goes to like ending placeholder shots of Sting singing mixed with shots of premiere.
Like it never fully got finished.
But like but mostly mostly.
Yes.
And this unedited version, what what I saw and again, just on Wikipedia, was that the only reason this exists is because in 2012, an animation student or animator in Europe released it on the Internet.
Yeah, just leaked it.
Wow.
I mean, that's great.
There's there's some like crazy populism to this thing.
And I think that's the thing that makes it the most fascinating to me is that it is a I mean, you'd call it like a warts and all kind of movie.
But it's still pretty like everyone's pretty polite in it.
Yes.
There are not parts where as you know, as we've discussed, the legend of Tony Baxter throwing a chair or whatever, it is not like that at all.
Everybody got thrown at him.
Oh, is the other way?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure thrown at him by the architect that he had to tell that we're not going with your design for Disneyland Paris, I think.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
That's the story he told.
I think so.
OK, Jesus.
I'm glad he got hit by a little wheel.
Eisner made him tell him too, I think.
This is his story.
Eisner goes, that's fine.
But you got to tell him.
Whoa.
Wow.
You got to tell him all this work he did.
We're not going with it.
Well, his look Eisner's face has to be on television.
He can't he can't afford to get nicked up.
No, he made the right call.
Absolutely.
He got to protect that.
You delineate that stuff.
But so anyway, it is like what I'm saying is it's it's a it's definitely a very truthful, honest look at the process.
But by Disney standards where things are so cleaned up and anything we've ever seen about the making of the movies or the rides or whatever it is, it's always like, well, it all starts with the story.
We begin with the story and we sprinkle a little bit of pixie dust on and you never get anything close to like what really happened.
The only like they've embraced a little bit that story of that Toy Story was fucked when it was first whatever the first like assembled version of Toy Story was a disaster and Woody was mean and terror.
They've I think embraced that story a little bit just because like an empire was built on the back of those.
Yeah.
They make it really seem like, oh my God, how do they do it?
It's to go from that point to it's one of the great films of our lifetimes and one of the biggest companies of our lifetimes is grown in the back of it.
But this is like maybe they don't have the reason to embrace it.
Maybe it's just like it's like a bunch of wonkiness and fighting that led to a pretty solid movie.
Right.
It's not like a masterpiece.
It's not one of the greatest ones ever made.
Yeah.
But it's fun.
It's definitely a fun.
Right.
I think I've said this on the show before where like Pixar, the Pixar spin when they were hot was always, well, the Pixar process is why these movies are so good.
We are willing to throw out a complete like third, it's two acts of the movie if we need to six months before and fix it.
Oh, that's oh, that's really great that they recognize a problem.
They can fix it.
But then you really think about making a movie and how things are usually dated and they need to make a deadline.
And you go, that sounds like a nightmare.
That sounds like truly like being able to do that so late in the process seems like it would be awful.
And I'm sure as I got older, I was like, oh, I bet there's really like harrowing tales from people who worked on all the good Pixar movies.
Sure.
But it does, you know, it worked in a lot of those pictures and we know it worked in every Star Wars.
Trust the process.
That's true.
The process.
But it feels like they almost took this.
This feels like a similar process where it was just like they were like, we have to make this movie now.
There's so many elements that are already here.
We can't just scrap the movie.
Well, and literally they sort of this is a little bit in the in the documentary, but it's maybe not underlined as much.
There's an excellent vulture oral history of Emperor's New Groove that obviously touches on the sweat box.
But there's kind of some extra stuff that's fun with with people who you see in this movie, the producer Fulmer, I forget his first name.
But the after all these big shake ups and changes that happened, here's here's what he says.
We had a year literally to put that whole thing together.
There's a deadline because we got a McDonald's Happy Meal that has to come on a certain date.
And there are big fines to pay if you don't do that.
Right.
So they were boxed in by the Happy Meal.
That is driving.
I mean, we know that these release dates are important and set in stone and they're declared years in advance in, you know, in these D23 and Comic Con type presentations.
Right.
But in this case, the Happy Meal drove it.
Well, it's incredible that it made.
I know what you're going to say.
Yeah, you're right.
I was going to say that must have changed because the Captain America Brave New World Happy Meal came out a while ago.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
Six months ago.
And when does the movie come out?
Valentine's Day 2025.
I looked this up because I was like, when did Captain America 4 start shooting?
And then when did the Fantastic Four movie, which comes out this summer, start shooting?
Fantastic Four started shooting last summer.
Captain America started shooting early 2023.
So they have really had to reshoot and move.
They moved the date on that twice, I think.
So that's like, they really, they paid the fine for the Happy Meals, I think it sounds like.
The Happy Meal forgot at this point.
Right.
They got enough money now.
This was a more precarious time for Disney.
Now they can pay Happy Meal fines left and right.
It doesn't like who care.
Ultimately, like that is definitely weird.
But like, you know, the world kept turning even though the Happy Meal toys were early.
They were saved by the fracturing of culture.
Yes, now no one cares.
The fracturing of monoculture.
No one gives a shit.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Do you think that Harrison Ford toy, Griffin and I have been talking about the likeness on these Harrison Ford Red Hulk toys.
The one that Hasbro made, we're not a fan of, the face isn't right.
But there's like a popcorn bucket with him.
It's a big Harrison Ford Red Hulk head and it is Harrison's face that we really like.
But I wonder what the Happy Meal toy, I should look and see if it looks like Harrison.
Because I really would like a nice, real good likeness of Harrison Ford as a Red Hulk.
That's the key for you.
If it's just a Red Hulk who cares, you need to see the Harrison in there.
Exactly.
Yeah, because otherwise you could just get another Green Hulk and paint it red.
Sure, and there's plenty of Red Hulk toys already, so.
Okay.
Oh, you're saying predating the casting.
From the comics.
Yeah, from the comics and stuff.
Gotcha.
But I'll look.
Let me say this about why, like I don't remember when I discovered this, but I devoured it as soon as I knew this existed.
I knew some of this backstory.
I knew that the fun, kooky, non-attempt at, I think Embers New Groove ended up being very refreshing because it's not trying to be pillar, serious, Pocahontas.
They got so ponderous there trying to make their next masterpiece, Chasing the Lion King.
Even though The Lion King was kind of the scrappy movie that was not intended to be among the finest they ever did.
But once, you can feel that once that happened, especially Katzenberg is now chasing, like, we need to win that Oscar this time.
This can't be like Beauty and the Beast.
We're coming for the.
So I think the sense I always got, my guess was always that whatever Kingdom of the Sun is, which they had announced and Eisner would refer to it and his stockholder letters and everything.
And with the music of Sting, I was always like, that sounds like the most serious thing you've ever heard of.
Even though maybe not.
You get glimpses of it.
They're still fun because it was Earth a Kid and there's you see a recording dialogue.
So like there was obviously jokes, but you're probably a comedy.
Yeah, but it feels yes.
I think it may have gotten.
It was going to be.
Yes, probably not pure comedy.
And that maybe it was confused because there's comedy, there's pure comedy people in it and then it gets more serious.
But anyway, I always knew that story.
And then, wow, it ended up being extremely different.
Wow. Once I heard there was the sweat box whenever it leaked and it was available to see, I ate it up so fast and I love it so much.
And I recommend it so much because it's like I think especially as a as a creative person, seeing kind of warts and all documentaries, I just like I mainline the inject them into my veins.
And especially of this era where like the lo fi of it and the digital of it was kind of like novel and that you see like kind of a grimier look like a not so polished look at like what's supposed to be a really polished movie.
I've devoured like all of Project Greenlight.
I've watched all of Project Greenlight three times.
Oh, yeah.
The filmmaking, you know, that it used to be Damon and Affleck and isn't anymore.
The Lost in La Mancha, the Terry Gillia, the making of Don Quixote.
That's excellent.
That's really good.
That's like this except where a movie falls apart, except they don't fix it then.
And like there's like floods.
It like you like see like true disasters.
This is all like Emperors New Groove is all meant like mental disasters.
That's like, oh, the set flooded.
We're fucked.
And that's that's the one that where they try to make the miracle Don Quixote.
Is that right?
That's what they try.
They eventually did with Adam Driver.
Yes.
A version of it.
But a story of Don Quixote, like, you know, a lot of antics and foolishness and it's full.
The story itself is a metaphor for it's a perfect metaphor for trying to make the story.
Yeah.
Have you seen Burden of Dreams, the Werner Herzog movie about the making of Fitzcarraldo?
I have not.
That's good.
Oh, yeah.
I've seen that a while, but that's good.
Klaus Kinski was crazy.
I'm going to write it in my notes.
Burden of Dreams is the movie.
I won't even.
Well, it's a crazy stunt they try to do that they do not like or crazy big thing they try
to do that gets like stuck.
OK.
Yeah.
Oh, great.
It's like the movie is about one thing and the making of they're like, well, it turns
out they tried to do the one thing from the movie.
I guess I won't even say.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Don't spoil it for me.
I'll come back and report if I like.
But it also like I'm just like trying to name check these because I love them all and they're
all kind of of a piece in their production.
That made me think I just rewatched the other night the making of Island of Dr. Moreau.
Oh, that's so insane where the director ends up fired and then sneaking around what used
to be his set dressed as a dog, man, and if he gets caught, he could get sued into the
ground.
So he has to all the extras are taking their masks off, but he won't because he there's
like giant legal trouble if he does.
So it's saying so much stuff that we like, I think, in a way like would be good documentary,
like stuff like bad stuff or weird stuff is always just like, boy, this choice was odd.
I would love a full length documentary about whatever the strange movie is.
Well, imagine, imagine if we had it in the world, if we could actually get here's what
it was like making Superstar limo.
Here's Tomorrowland 98 and Rocket Rods.
Here's light magic.
This is not a disaster at all, but that one there's this French made document or BBC
or something documentary about Tim Delaney making Space Mountain for Disneyland Paris.
And that's close enough to an honest, like not Disney polished.
Yeah.
That it's it's fantastic.
Oh, my God.
Right.
Even seeing any honesty in the Disney process anywhere.
So.
Yeah.
The way everyone is in this movie, I mean, there I understand and I've tried my best
to do it.
I don't know, successfully or not.
But there is a certain level of polish and professionalism.
But with the Disney company, they're everyone's laying it on so thick it seems like it would
drive a person to madness or at least burn out, you know?
Well, the guy Roger Allers, who's the guy who gets fucked the most by the original
director, who was one of the directors of Lion King and a major creative figure and
at least beating the beast.
And I forget Aladdin or a little I want to say Little Mermaid, maybe who and who after
this left the company, did not do anything with Disney again, kept working.
But like, I mean, you see him just like on the beach and like he's just like dried by
the hole.
And he describes in this vulture thing like, yeah, imagine you get you get like good and
you get like the worst screening of my life.
And now I have to go like pull it together and like talk on camera as if I'm not having
a meltdown.
Right.
I mean, it's like it was probably not in there at the maybe now people might kind of be themselves
a little more.
But at the time, can you imagine like actually just like just bursting into tears in a document?
I don't know.
It would be crazy.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It wouldn't have happened back then.
So it's incredible how he kept it together.
Right. Everybody keeps it together.
And I I forget who says this now that you bring that up, because I something caught
me. Somebody says, I think it's after Sting sends.
So, yeah, we'll guess we're jumping around.
Sting sends a letter at some point being like, I don't agree with the choices in this
essentially. Yeah, I need to leave.
But he was a polite letter.
But it is like I don't like this.
But then one of the guys on the crew, shit, I forget who it is.
He says something that I don't believe he believes.
He says, well, you know, Sting isn't used to getting all these different opinions in
these voices, but we are we love to get we love to hear like all these different
opinions about everything. And I'm like, you don't believe that.
Yeah. Like, this is just how it has to be.
You have to talk yourself into it.
Right. I obviously like collaborating is good.
But like, it sounds like there's so many voices, people wanting to get their two cents
in that, like, I don't believe that guy could pass a lie detector test saying that.
I also, I mean, as someone who's been in therapy for years, like watching this, then
I'm going like, this is an absolutely terrible way to communicate.
Like, you're not no one's getting their ideas across with this many members of a
committee like this many cooks in the kitchen.
No one's getting their ideas across.
No one is happy.
But like Sting, I you do at the end of the documentary, you begrudgingly
go like, yeah, it's a lot.
But I mean, I guess it works sometimes.
I know. And it kind of does because he's performing at the Oscars.
It all did kind of work. I think there's I think there's also I wonder if it's worse
with what you're saying about like, yeah, like being in touch with, you know, therapy
teachings or whatever that like I wonder if it was like in a way, would it be more
helpful? Because like this seems like a bad creative process.
Right. But then I'm like, well, you know, what would have been worse is like working
for like Scott Rudin or something who's screaming and throwing phones.
Probably worse. But also, there's something to be said about like like a despot.
And at least you're like, well, I hate the despot, but at least the despot is clear.
It's clear. It's not like 20 people being passive aggressive with each other,
because that's something I read in the vulture thing that, you know, a lot of people
in the vulture thing have very bad things to say about Jeffrey Katzenberg, you can
imagine. But they do say, look, at least it was like, here's what it is.
You're doing it's Pocahontas Shades of Romeo and Juliet mixed with such and such.
Right. And they always knew that's what it was, even if the movie wasn't working.
Right. They that had been handed down and they were making that.
This thing was like, OK, so it's Incans and David Spade's in there and it's Prince
and the Popper. But also somebody wants to rope the sun and Isma wants to be
eternally young. And in the vulture thing, somebody describes like, I was like,
somebody asked me on a plane. So what do you do?
I make Disney movies. Oh, really? What are you working on now?
And then they felt like it took the entire flight from New York to L.A.
to explain the movie. Yeah.
That's when they were like, maybe something's wrong here.
Maybe we have to.
So I think that's maybe the problem with this is that that's good.
We'll just no wonder. Yeah. Maybe you needed a despot.
You know what you get with what you've described about Pocahontas?
That's a North Star.
That's at least something can go back to. Yes.
And you can also like crack open Romeo and Juliet and start going.
There must be something in.
Something's not working out when we go back to the tools of.
Yeah, yeah. Right.
Or I feel we're bringing that up, though, because I hate Pocahontas.
The movie Pocahontas is so like pond embers.
New Groove is absolutely more fun to watch.
Well, it's more fun. Yeah.
My my social social studies teacher in middle school
despise. Well, sure.
That's a good reason.
Because then every she was teaching like early American history
and all these little asshole 10 year olds are coming in like, oh, I know.
I know. And I saw Pocahontas.
I have some affection for the songs, but it was a similar
and we've said this a hundred times on the show, probably at this point.
But it was a situation where I couldn't articulate
that it was different than the last four movies.
You know, I mean, like it wasn't like I ran out was like,
I'm going to play like as Miko, the raccoon.
Like I love like, yeah, I need those toys or like whatever.
Like it was different. Yeah.
Wasn't it weird after like being children going from whatever,
like five to 10 or whatever that whatever it was.
And like, oh, my God, the group that makes the cartoon movies
gets better every time there is how do they manage to top themselves?
And then so what's the next one? Here we go, baby.
Uh, OK. Well, there's
Flick. What's the name of the hummingbird?
I know Flicks from Flick is from from books.
Is Flick also the hummingbird, though?
Miko is the raccoon from Pocahontas, I believe.
Yes. OK. And there's another that I don't know is telling.
Yeah, it is. Oh, it's Flit.
Apologies. Flit, the hummingbird.
Yeah. All right. You be Miko. I'll be Flit. Right.
I want to be grandmother Willow.
Mother. Well, I do think my sister and I did grandmother Willow like bits.
Yeah, we tried. Oh, we tried to do it.
We have to love this, don't we?
It made it very convenient to hop over to Toy Story.
You're like, oh, good. All right.
There's a new one that's fun and for children. Yes.
And great. Yeah.
With lots of characters we want to embrace and play and have the toys of.
Pocahontas and Hunchback back to back is similar.
We're like, we have to see these movies.
We love these movies.
And here's with apologies to Jane.
I know she loved Hunchback. I hate this film.
I hate the Hunchback. I find it so unpleasant.
I haven't watched it in a little while.
So I would be interested because I honestly this might be controversial.
I don't think Lion King is nearly as good as the three is Aladdin,
Little Mermaid or Beauty and the Beast.
I like Lion King a lot.
I think a lot. Yeah.
But like we watched it a couple of years ago and I was like,
I think it's less good than those three.
I mean, I know it's a different song.
Obviously, Howard Ashman not involved in so.
But I was like, it's a little less.
I think I don't think I don't think there's any wrong opinion within the four.
I think the only wrong opinion is that the four are bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know. I think it's a step down from those those three.
But as a kid, I know I would love they they got me back with Hercules and Mulan.
You know, you really like those.
Yes, I like Mulan.
I mean, I think what makes I think clearly the answer started to become fun
because like when you when you assess all of those, like post the Golden Age,
you know, everybody might have a different answer of what their favorite is.
But probably people's answer most likely is going to be one of the fun ones,
because like what kind of worked and resonates and what do they still acknowledge
and use the characters from?
There's this and there's Lilo and Stitch.
I mean, like I think once the masterpiece thing got out of there,
well, it's like you have more user friendly movies.
You have to I don't know.
It just feels like you can't keep chasing the exact same thing.
Also, I mean, the big thing is they is Howard Ashman dies also.
Like, I don't know what would have happened.
I mean, that's that's in there, too.
Not nearly as hard.
Ashman's obviously like the the heart and the literally like the heart of the songs.
Right. Characters.
So I wonder what it would have looked like if he lived.
How many of these you would have you don't like, you know, like you're watching a lot of like
there's all these like SNL 50 documentaries right now that tell these off told stories.
But what you don't have is like and then Lorne died.
Like you like it is crazy that in the height of or whoever, you know,
I mean, gee, Smith, it is.
What if they had lost it and never gone on as far as the analogy?
The heart of the show.
I don't know nothing against you.
Great. But you know what I mean?
I get this tragedies.
Chris Farley dies, but people were off this.
But it's not like, well, there's no Hartman dies when he's on the show.
So that's I think it's particularly insane that like this empires ramping up
gets better and better every time.
And then like the writer of the like immaculate music dies.
It is crazy.
I guess I sometimes maybe things are over dramatized or like
importance is put on it just because it's better for whatever documentary.
But it kind of I think is true that like Howard and Al Menken,
of course, their songs saved the company.
Like, I don't think there's no high hyperbole there.
Like, I don't know what Disney looks like without the talent of those two guys.
And especially Howard, who is the driving force.
You need the songs.
The songs like the songs sell the characters which sell the toys,
which makes it all work and that you fall in love with them.
And then you want to go to the theme park.
So like it is the engine of and you have to go back to like,
yeah, the songs are how you know the characters and love the characters
and love the brand. Right.
And they hadn't had any in so long.
And you bring it up to like my mom and my mom just, you know,
she has kids at this point, whatever, 1989.
And like she was like, and we saw the little mermaid.
We were like, whoa, like, like even adults were like, oh, shit.
OK, it's a different situation now.
Yeah. And like literally that.
So so here's just the momentum of those three movies carry Disney farther, farther along.
But I guess I'm lost a little bit of my point.
But basically what I'm saying is just like keeping to like chasing like epic Oscar
at a certain point, you got to switch like people that like
they like because they forgot with Pocahontas.
Who do you love?
John Smith, of course. Right.
I love John Smith and Radcliffe. Right.
You got to make it.
You got you can't make you can't make the same album all the time.
You know, at a certain point, you two makes pop,
but they got to go back to make a different course.
You know, Sting can't make I mean, the pressure that you can't just
they already made American Idiots perfect.
They can't now. I agree with you.
Twenty first century breakdown.
I feel like it's a disappointment because they tried to chase the exact same thing.
It is as American Idiots.
And I think it's just less successful.
They need to go back.
You know, Sting can't just do another dream of the Blue Turtles.
He has to. He's got to shake it up with the last ship, right?
He has to make sorry.
He has to make an entire album with Shaggy.
Oh, I brought this up on the show before.
Yes. And they're on fucking motorcycles like the Casamigos guys.
I showed it at the one holiday show like the Disney
parade or Disney Christmas special.
They're like, please welcome Sting like to the stage with Shaggy.
Yeah, it's like, what?
There may have been a couple of episodes where we talked about Sting and Shaggy's
collaboration. This is a while I somehow managed to forget your club three suggestion.
I don't want to possible possible club three loser.
It sounds like one.
Was there ever a puppet in any of your music videos?
I don't know.
But here's the thing.
I'm convinced of without even reading that oral history.
Is that the movie that came after a lot of these movies before I first knew Groove is
Tarzan and so much of that is Phil Collins.
Right. So the feeling of the must have pitched to sing like, well, this would be your
Tarzan.
Well, absolutely.
And I assume. Yeah, I've always viewed this as as a trilogy.
Lion King, Tarzan, Kingdom of the Sun.
That was Disney attempting to complete the trilogy of music by stuffy old Brits
because the first one, I mean, they don't I don't think they ever achieve higher pop
heights like like like more awards and and album sales and everything than they do
with the Elton John Lion Kiss.
So that obviously they got to keep going in that mode.
So Phil Collins fits the bill.
Also, also pretty big and award winning, maybe less resonate resonating culturally.
But yes, Sting clearly wanted that.
And I think what he was tasked with was six songs, which was becoming the standard.
But so this is them trying to it is them trying to 21st century breakdown.
Like, that's right. We this works.
All right. So we get a guy who's doesn't make fun music anymore.
So we'll get them to come make very, very serious music for us.
And it is as I add up like and we talk about our relationship to Sting.
I mean, like, as I said, when I was growing up, these people all felt 90 years old.
Now, since then, I've I've I like a ton of Elton John Phil Collins completely my shit,
not less the Tarzan stuff, but the pop Phil Collins Sting.
Well, I like the police.
So listing pretty ponderous.
And it's like and then you wait.
The glimpses you get in this definitely are odd, right?
Of Sting. Yes.
The Sting when you because you kind of get some demos of what the kingdom of the sun
Sting music is going to be. Right.
Yes. Some of these are a tad hard to swallow.
Let me and again, maybe jump.
There's probably a cleaner way we can like tell the story of this.
Well, here I'll just do it.
Basically. Yeah. What you said.
I think it makes sense. Of course.
Like like like complete the pattern.
Elton John Phil Collins Sting.
They get him. There's immediate concern about like apparently they clocked even
before the documentary.
Well, you know, he might he might think he's just going to sail in,
write six masterpieces, collect his Grammys and Oscars.
And that is how this works.
I think they knew that it was going to be a bumpy ride and that they were at Disney
was a little bit more all over the map at this point.
So Tom Schumacher, executive who appears in this film, thought,
oh, well, if because they're proposing this documentary thing, we should do it
because that keeps Trudy Styler around.
And that makes it more likely that Sting will not bail when this process gets hard.
Because, spoiler, he kind of tries to leave in the movie.
Apparently he tried to quit the movie five times over the course of two and a half
years. But the documentary was part of like keeping him there.
And she's a filmmaker.
This was co-directed by Trudy Styler and John Paul Davidson,
director in their camp, who also directed a movie that Sting is the star of
with the very odd title Gentlemen Don't Eat Poets.
I don't know much about Gentlemen Don't Eat Poets, but neither a previous Sting
director. So that so that gets you here.
And it kind of cuts to like midway through the creative process.
It's not for the you don't watch them invent the movie from whole cloth.
It's like, here we go. We're at the Disney studio.
We're in Burbank.
You know, we're working up storyboards and Sting is all over the globe
making up these songs.
And then you'll start to.
And they do have the llama thing figured out.
They know that there's an element of somebody turning into a llama,
which results in getting to hear a little bit of this llama song.
Llama song is the highlight.
Yeah. Do you want to do do you want to do it?
I can sing a little bit of my memory of it.
You do a little bit. I you get it's like it's Sting and there's like his piano guy.
And I know this is demos, right?
So it's not going to sound like Rich and Liv, but it's like very like keyboardy.
A ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
And then and then like a bunch of like like six like kind of cheesy session
people singing and they're all singing this song about like a llama, llama,
a llama, llama, taking the panorama, a llama, llama,
put on a green pajamas, a llama, llama.
Like, oh, this is what we're like a children's song.
It is for like babies, a song for babies.
It's it's like Raffy, Raffy would go a little bit cheesy.
Yeah. I don't know.
Llama, llama, boba, banana, fan, a pho, banana.
What you said about Sting being all over the world leads to one of my favorite,
if not my favorite line in the movie.
Go ahead.
Good luck, gentlemen.
I'm going to the Himalayas.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that is great.
Doesn't he keep going, doesn't it?
Like, we'll see if I return.
Right. There's a lot of that.
There's a little bit of. Yeah.
The whole thing is, yeah, he's somebody's in the Himalayas.
And then he's in like he's in like the, you know, the deep British countryside.
The vulture thing said he lived out, you know, in the out in the countryside,
kind of near Stonehenge. Right.
And then you see him like he's even I mean, you see him like,
is he playing the literal Coliseum or did they just drive by the Coliseum?
But he's like globetrotting.
The first time the first time you ever see him in the movie, he's
playing chess, sipping tea while holding an acoustic guitar in his lap
and in the most like English garden, kind of.
It's it's so getting the slices of Sting's life.
He's sitting by the.
Yeah, he's sitting by the ocean.
Oh, well, yeah, because he's got a Malibu house as well.
Yeah, he's in the Himalayas.
In the Himalayas.
They keep cutting the people in hot springs.
What am I forgetting? Tuscany.
He goes to Tuscany. He goes to Tuscany. Yeah.
Thinking about the like anecdotes about Bono writing Spider-Man
Turn Off the Dark, Sting makes Bono look like he has no pretension at all.
Just a guy. You know, you catch him at Sabaro.
Like Bono seems like kind of more excited during that and reading that book.
Well, I ran into I ran into I ran into Bono just ordering from Kane's Chicken.
Yeah. Right.
Saw to the Earth guy.
Oh, yeah. Like George Lucas at the food court.
Oh, wait, when he called John Chu, is that what you're talking about?
Oh, no. That's a different.
That's a different food court.
But he did call Wicked's John Chu.
I'm at the food court. I just saw the movie.
Yeah. Yeah. He went to a movie theater by your animal.
There's no there's a photo of him, which is like
two items and noodles and a diet Coke.
He's alone.
And a newspaper just sitting in a food court.
There's a great one of the greatest George Lucas clips is that he accidentally
walks in the frame of a documentary or a news you've seen that before.
It's kind of goes like that's fascinating.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, sorry. Sorry.
But yes, thing is so it couldn't seem more comically pretentious.
Yeah. For again, versus Bono, who is comically pretentious already.
Yeah. Defined by comic pretension.
No adult. All the globetrotting just made me like,
you know, that next they're going to cut to him like, well, gentlemen,
I'm heading to the lost city of Atlantis for only Bono and I know where it is.
So I'll be I'll be breathing through the gills I had.
I took a number of pills in order to make me last for 16 hours in the bedroom.
And at the same time, I had a gill gill surgery.
Performed a ritual where the ancient king of the fish came to me
and granted me certain powers that will allow me to breathe.
What I'm saying is I don't have cell service down there.
You'll have to you'll have to send a ship in a bottle.
That's the only way to reach me.
And even that's probably going to take four months.
You'll have to prick a hole in it for it to fill up very slowly
and then drop all two miles down to the bottom,
where I'll be residing with the king of the fishermen.
And then he does a 15 minute version of message in a bottle with on a loop.
Oh, yeah, I'll I'll be unreachable.
I'm going to Santa's private villa at the North Pole.
Saint Nicholas is what he calls him.
I actually people don't know I bred Donner.
That's that's Donner is co-owned by Santa and I said, do you want
do you want to help raise a reindeer?
And I said, yes, well, I've always been concerned about deforestation
and the melting of the North Pole.
And so I helped breed.
I chose a sire to breed Donner.
Santa, no, Santa and I go way back.
What you were saying earlier, Scott, about the three like
the stuffy Brits, the stuffy Brits, like even those movies.
Again, they had no stars to go back to.
I always heard Lion King.
Well, it's pretty similar to Hamlet.
It's not an exact one to one.
But there's a lot of this thing, Kimba, that we're ripping off.
Right. It's Hamlet meets the thing we're stealing.
Yeah. So you got a hamlet to go back to.
Worst case, then Tarzan.
Well, there's tons of Tarzan.
So you got to have Tarzan.
You got to have Jane. You can blow it out.
It seems like that was missing if it's taking a full plane ride
to explain what kingdom of the sun. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's what it is.
It's interesting that they would like that they had all these elements
and they just weren't like cooking them correctly.
I related to it.
And it's funny that I like watching these things
because it's also like stress inducing in a weird way, too.
Oh, I felt it. I felt it. Yeah, yeah.
But it flashed me to there was there was this is such a small potatoes
in comparison to a big movie that millions are being spent on.
But I do remember
a movie city, my show I was making like the first round went pretty good.
We're like everybody.
We got our head around the first set of episodes.
And then there was one we're like, what if we did something with this?
And I had this and this and this. Yeah, that sounds good.
And then it was like it was just not jealous.
There was no it was just not gelling.
There was no core.
It was like it was like what's described in this movie, like why?
It seems like a story with this and this and aiming for this guest
and all this shit that it would all and it just doesn't turn into anything.
It's like and it gave me those panics.
And and and that I just related to it in that, like, well,
you can't be too heady about it because they they need a draft of this next week.
Like we can't take forever.
And then extrapolate that with like like, yeah, well, we're back
to a happy meal deal and we've spent 40 million dollars.
Another thing that's not in the documentary is Tom Schumacher,
one of the executives going to forget who one of the writers
or somebody on the creative team.
And and like he has to he's going to meet Eisner.
They're in the animation building.
It's the fun over here with the hat and it's kooky.
Oh, he's got to go across the street and go talk to Eisner.
And he's he's close to tears.
And he's saying, I have to talk to this man.
And we've spent 40 million dollars and we have nothing to show for it.
What can I tell this?
And this is after some of the events of the film. Right.
This is how close to the bone they were.
One one thing you got a fortunate thing about the movie.
Almost no Eisner. You see his back at one point.
I was going to say, yeah, I George Steinbrenner.
Yeah, yeah, it's too bad.
Getting some candid Eisner definitely would have been great.
You get some Roy Disney.
And what you get is I don't want to go too far without talking about Tom Schumacher.
And there's another guy.
Now I'm forgetting the other name.
But either way, there's these two guys who are like the same
and they're the same as all executives are.
And this was these guys.
Look, I'm sure they've all done some good things
and they've contributed to these movies.
But like, boy, these are some executive executives.
They come off pretty bad.
They are because they're they just seem so like silver spoon
elitist. And you're like we were watching like direct this.
Roger Alex just pours hard into it.
And it all stems from his like desire to like get the Incan culture correct.
And then forgive me, I might butcher the name, but Andreas Deha.
The and that's a cool facet of this is that before the conflict starts,
you get to see some of the people involved in the Golden Age just raw
and looking at their process and watching, seeing how excited they are
to talk about their art. And that's the guy.
He was doing Yzma in this and before that, he was like Mr.
Villain. He was Gaston. He was Scar.
He was Jafar. Yeah.
And he was really excited to do a female and a larger than life.
And then like he's just the rug is pulled out from under him.
And this look ultimately, I don't know, maybe somebody could tell me
what Tom Schumacher has done that I'm supposed to be excited about.
Yeah, I'm looking at the guy who fucking drew Gaston.
Yeah. Like who then this went in another direction.
And this is in there a little bit that he's like, I just don't think you want
what I'm selling here, even though Yzma stayed in the movie.
And there's a period where they're like, where all the characters might be cut.
Yzma stayed. But he's like, you don't want my Yzma.
I'm going to go find a movie better suited to my talents, something that I believe
is going to turn out better. Right.
He moved to Florida where they were making Lilo and Stitch.
And I believe he was the supervising animator of Lilo, I think.
So that all worked out.
But I'm like, I just look at this like things.
They all seem pretty happy, right?
It's a very it's a very different documentary for the first 45 minutes.
And then there's a screening and these two uppity guys show up and then everything's
toast. It's scorched earth after.
And I'm kind of like, where were you guys?
You get to come in and just say, you know, it didn't work for me.
It's not working. Cut. It doesn't work.
Well, the artists just bleed onto paper and earth.
The footage of Earth Earth Kit recording and then right after that,
it might be who you're talking about goes like, and she just adds like a life to
this character. She has her own take on it.
And it really magnet everything, everything with her, which all seems like stuff
that's not in the movie. Right.
I rewatched the movie the other night and it all seemed unfamiliar to me.
Entire song sting or a song for her.
And she seems like she seems like the coolest person.
She's still with us. She passed away.
No, she passed away a couple of years, a while ago, I think.
But yes, she's just like, I don't know if it's just her voice, but the energy like
she just always has her energy, like her Earth, a kid energy where she's like
completely magnetic in addition to just having an unusual voice.
But still, yeah, you're watching this.
You're like, why isn't Earth a kid?
Why wasn't she more stuff?
The other person were like, they should have.
People should have used her more.
I mean, this is a that's a very cool use of her.
It is great. Yeah.
Yeah. And they that said the walk around Yizma at the end is terrifying.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
And they send the well, that's a fun thing, too.
That's a funny thing, too, that they like they like there's bits of it that seem
fun, even in the even in the torturous periods.
Yeah. And they see at some point.
All right. The theme park characters are ready and they do a little walk around.
And yes, that's very scary.
There's a part where they install like a big stone gateway, which reminded me a lot
of what we got to see when we went to Mattel.
That's what Mattel is. A lot of Mattel is just like an office.
But then, like, oh, here you get to enter your cubicle, but it's through like
Barbie land or, you know, whatever.
Or the He-Man or whatever.
So that was cool to see.
But I like that people I like that people are having absolute panic attacks while
walking under a big ink and still like pillar door every day.
That that does bring up a couple that the thing seeing at the end
says something. This isn't the exact quote, but he refers to Daisy
taking the best parts, the best of different cultures and grinding up like
hamburger. And I did.
I was like, oh, it's pretty, pretty good line.
And then you look at this, this everyone interviewed.
And I'm like, I thought of that.
There's a stand up.
I forget who said it at the beginning of a set, said, like, wow,
a lot of guys here tonight that look like me.
And I got that kind of ice.
Felt like that.
Looking at this movie like, oh, a lot of guys who look like me there.
I did not see.
I mean, that's a lot of dopey white guys with beards and that's the enjoy.
Yeah. Once they open it up to the full creative brain trust.
Yeah, it's entirely that.
And there's no one of this lineage to like give the real deal in the history.
And then there's like there's maybe one woman interviewed on camera.
Maybe so. Yeah.
It's also funny that they're like when we need we want kind of like a Cuban beat
to it. Who should we get? Sting Sting.
Well, and they're like, they might move it to Jamaica.
And I'm like, Jesus, I'm like, yeah, this wouldn't fly today.
But now today they just take the best of different intellectual properties
and try to cobble something together.
They just bought Marvel and Star Wars and try to figure it out
because it's not appropriate to dissect cultures.
I feel like really nearly it's there's like hints in the early part of the documentary
that like they're like, yeah, you know, Sting's in use recording songs.
But like, we don't really know what this is.
Like there's a mention of there's a couple of mentions of like,
we're not it's not quite coming together.
But like we have a lot of elements and you're like, do you already have Sting?
Like I would be so nervous to bring Sting in until it was like set.
Right. Go. Yeah.
The confidence of maybe the studio at that point or the people involved.
Like I like I'm trying to think like I haven't worked with that many famous people.
Pauly Shore, Bing Crosby's widow.
But when you're dealing with a Pauly Shore, Bing Crosby's widow.
Yeah. I mean, how that ups everybody's game.
Yeah. But I will say I was stressed out like if I had to show them a thing I did.
Like, so like that, just the idea of like Sting's coming in here.
And there's a chance that like we're going to really have to rework this.
The stress, that's the biggest stress I felt early on, knowing that like
you're going to have to have these uncomfortable conversations with Sting.
Well, look, Sting is Sting and Sting's done what he's done.
But Tom Schumacher is Tom Schumacher and he studied theater in college.
That no, that is what Tom Schumacher was thinking, probably.
So it's a I hear I get it.
But that part of it, I'm like, oh, my God, Sting should come in six months
before this comes out once the movie's like done and just be like, Sting here, here, here, here.
Yeah. Write your songs, write your.
But they write them with the Howard Ashman model is the
yes, the composer writes the movie, too.
I guess that's the problem.
But there should be like a crash course.
There should be a fixer gets one hour.
It take it goes to lunch with Sting and goes, OK, listen,
here's how this stuff gets done.
We recognize that you're like a top selling recording artist.
And we're willing to work with you on making bingo, baka, baffo.
Let me talk turkey with you, pal.
Here's how this shit's going to go.
You're going to be on this for like years.
Yeah. That like, I don't know.
I think there is going to pop in and pop out.
Get your Oscar, pal. OK.
You're going to be in the shit.
You're sorry.
The brand new day tour.
It's going to be a brand new millennium by the time you cancel that shit.
Yeah, thing. All right. You're in here.
Move next door to this studio because we're going to need you here from nine to five,
nine to ten every day. All right.
Get a little duplex in Burbank.
I'm sure you and you and Trudy can make it work.
Get used to jerking off really fast.
You ain't having sex for a long time with your wife, OK?
You're going to have to speed tantric. Five minutes.
There's a room for it.
Drill a hole in the wall.
There's a room for the animators. Go in there.
Go at it like a woodpecker.
None of these guys have had sex with their wives in ten years.
They've been hitting out, putting out classics.
These work days are tantric.
These are 18 hour sessions, OK?
That's how it works here.
Pick what you like for lunch.
Paquito Moss or Ribs USA, because that's what's closest, Trudy.
There's a wiener schnitzel over by NBC.
Everyone gets sick there, but they keep getting it.
Let me go into the actual.
That's like weave the tale a little bit and say some things.
You know what's interesting?
This is not referred to out loud.
This is just you have to catch it and you have to hear the iconic voice,
the now iconic voice in order to get that it's happening,
because you see some clips of the old movie of Kingdom of the Sun
and you see that it's a Prince and the Popper situation.
And it's the names of the characters that ended up in there.
It's Kuzco and it's Pacha and Pacha
in what ends up being John Goodman,
a like a much taller, stockier sort of a father figure
to Kuzco in this.
It's the same name.
Yet the character, it's a Prince and the Popper situation
where they look similar enough that they could switch places.
And that Pacha is voiced by Owen Wilson.
Yes, that is an Owen Wilson performance cut from.
And I think when they hired him, he had not.
There had not been the full wave of Owen Wilson work yet.
I think this might have been some animators going, hey,
this movie bottle rocket is cool.
We should get this guy.
So it's kind of interesting.
It's a false start of Owen Wilson Disney before.
Kachow. Imagine that it's the year.
How many years before the I mean, six before it's released.
But I don't know when they start making it or whatever.
So you catch some Owen Wilson.
The you know, like you said, like things are like
you'll occasionally catch that things are fraying a little bit.
And I think they're all pretty honest about the fact that,
you know, you get what you think is working.
You think it's it's coming together.
But then we do these screenings and the screenings
might kind of like rock the boat a little bit.
And in the fateful meeting halfway through,
where they go into the sweat box proper,
which they define at the top of the movie,
it's a reference to a Walt era thing
where wherever they screened all the animation or the final products
was a very poorly ventilated room that made all of the animators.
No air conditioning, no air conditioning, which is kind of crazy.
It's like, oh, you know that one thing about the movies
that we try to get people to go to air conditioning.
You see, well, that's for the people enjoying the movie.
Yeah, for the people who have to be scared of
Walt putting a cigar out on their forehead.
Walt's not hot.
He's got an unlimited supply of scotch and ice.
So he's good to go.
Was his room where he got the massage from Hazel George,
was that air conditioned?
Was that a sweat box too?
I'm not sure. Was that kind of was it kind of an early
like sweat yoga? Maybe that would like help him.
Perhaps exfoliate by getting getting it super hot in there.
That helps. Yeah. Getting sweaty. Hazel.
You know he said it, Jason.
Don't act naive, Jason.
Your tea cakes from Martinos are starting to melt.
Finishing is chilly.
Yeah. Chilli cigars and no ventilation.
Give me one of those tea cakes.
I've got to sop it up. Hazel.
But anyway, they they everybody enters the screening
and they even kind of say like, so who knows?
We might go in here and it all comes apart.
And they have no idea that this might be one of the worst
in the history of the company. It's wild.
It is alluded to because somebody says somebody
who kind of runs the screenings says every week
people pull their pants down in front of me. Yes.
And also somebody that person quotes somebody else saying
that it's like these screenings are like having someone
chop your hands off and pull your pants down in front of a crowd.
So you just have stumps that are bleeding.
So you're incapable of pulling your pants back up.
That is what it's like to screen a fun cartoon for the fun executives.
This is this is one of the like is the term dramatic irony.
But it's one of the things when you hear about some of the behind the scenes stuff,
it's like that's an insane way to make stuff.
Well, they have made a lot of hair.
Like it's one of the things, the weird things that I think does make Disney interesting.
But then what it but what happens when but like but here we're getting into
this is our tried and true process.
And this is how you get Treasure Planet, Atlantis, Home on the Range,
Hunchback of Notre Dame.
Like what is the justification of this process when when those are the movies?
Yeah. And again, and again, look, this did result in Emperor's New Groove,
which I can confirm from the other night is is pretty delightful.
So I guess you can't. I don't know.
But there has to be another way, right?
Well, there's an opening shot and there is a sign of like
what the projects currently are, what the offices are.
And it says, does it say Emperor's New Groove in Atlanta?
I would whatever it said, I would.
Oh, well, that's the point where, yes, in production,
one is Atlantis and one is Kingdom in the Sun Kingdom in the Sun.
And you're kind of doing a double take, like I thought it was Kingdom of.
And then they explain it to you that.
All right. So one change we've made is it's now Kingdom in the Sun.
And what that is supposed to connotate, I don't know.
I mean, is that like because now we're basking in this.
Does that somehow from of to end, does that make it more fun in some way?
Maybe. But that's one of the big day.
All right. Disaster screening.
No more of now it's in. Yeah.
I good question.
I like with with big corporations, big companies doing animation like
it does feel like there's no other way to get around it.
But having a ton of people put eyes on things way too early.
Yeah, like it just that's the nature of it, like because it has to be storyboarded.
Like there's so many more opportunities for people to get involved
versus like just reading a script or like even looking at dailies
from an executive or a producer, you're like, well, I can say it looks OK.
When it's cut together, I'll see.
I feel like you can get farther along in the process
before you get more interference.
Yeah, maybe I'm wrong about that, but it feels like there's so many more steps
along the way of like.
Are you saying it's worse that there's more points of check in
so it can be noodle with it all time?
That's what I mean. Yeah.
And later check ins like I feel like if early on, everyone got together and went,
OK, we're going to be frank, but not cruel.
And I will not get my feelings hurt.
That is the agreement we're working off of.
OK, everyone good break, but that doesn't often happen
because it's hard to get everyone on the same page.
And also, it's not just like, what's your endgame here?
There's 12 different endgates because marketing has to worry about one thing.
Executives have to worry about one thing.
The McDonald's reps have to worry about one thing.
It seems like a common thing.
It's like, all right, if we assess what came out of this process, pretty strong.
Lion King, Toy Story.
I think Leland Stitchmack qualifies this like a common thing you hear
about a lot of movies that succeeded is that like it's there's this
is this aspect of nobody knew what we were doing.
We didn't have a lot of oversight because they were paying attention to the other thing.
So we're just these scrappy guys in the bungalows and maybe some of the early ones, too,
because like, you know, they think Disney animation is dead.
We're trying. All right.
Let's try a little mermaid before we burn the entire thing down
and then and then ended up working.
But it does seem like an important facet
that things get to operate in sort of a bubble where there's not a zillion
people weighing in at all times.
It does seem like a lot of great things come out of that.
Yes. Yes.
And then, like, if there is, yeah, I don't know.
Obviously, I'm sure there's great things have been made with a ton of input.
And in some ways, I feel like newer Pixar stuff that works,
maybe like a Toy Story 4 in some ways, I feel like I can feel a committee of like
everyone is like the jokes.
I don't know. It's packed full of stuff.
And I or Simpsons or early Simpsons works.
And it's from what I've heard, it's like everybody threw in
joke punch ups like there are 20 voices in that room.
But there's that committee.
There's not. But it's a literally no executive type of committee.
That's another thing, too, is that when you look at it, let's take TV.
What are some what are we?
What do we agree are some of the best shows ever?
Simpsons, Seinfeld, South Park, zero executive notes on any.
Right. Yes, true. Yes.
At least not past the very, very early.
Right. Point.
Which is why I am staring at this Tom Schumacher like, all right, buddy.
Right. Yes, of course.
Yeah, because like it's every every all those shows have different processes,
as far as I understand.
Like Larry and Jerry are the ones who just did the final pass
and made everything seemingly better or punched everything up.
You need your internal despotism. Right.
I think. But you.
But it has to come from people who know how to make the right to make a thing.
But it does sound like when Conan's talking about like writing
monorail episode of The Simpsons, he's like, yeah, I wrote it.
But you have to understand that all these great comedy writers.
Oh, that's very true. Yeah. So much stuff into.
And I almost feel like I took the reverse with Seinfeld.
We're like, you got a good writer who gave them a script.
And then Jerry and Larry finished finished it. Oh, sure.
So it feels almost like reverse.
By the way, eventually credited with screenplay by or written by,
I forget, is a guy, Dave Reynolds, who worked on a lot.
He was he ended up part of the brain trust.
I think ended up writing on writing.
Did he get the credit on finding Nemo?
He's one of the main writers on finding Nemo.
But original Conan writer late night in 93, he's in there with Smigel
and Louie and Dino Stamatopoulos and Odenkirk.
And there's a photo of Michael Gordon, who I crossed over with,
who was the masturbating bear.
It was always the same Conan trivia.
If you don't know, the masturbating bear was always the same guy.
That's great. All those years.
When another star struck, if I met him and knew that
Tress McNeil, I would just feel like the bear.
I think he was pretty, you know, because like we can all picture
the motion, right?
And I think sometimes other people would do it and he'd go, no, no, no, no.
As it was, there's like a particular way.
There's a cupping and then a pause,
like a kind of a pause for for dramatic impact.
And then, but, but, but, but, but, but, but.
And it's not even really a proper jerk off.
It's kind of this like wild.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a very odd motion.
And with circus music.
Hard to do in a bear suit.
So credit to the great Michael Gordon.
But anyways, but yeah, you know, like comedy,
royalty, original Conan guy writing it.
And he seems delightful.
He seems like one of the people who's like part of the rescue mechanism.
I will say that after the schism happens, big scary screen,
then you go to a meeting where people are just saying
that didn't work for me. It's not funny.
It's not everybody's against this thing.
Except it stings in there because he went and he's just like
kind of like staring at the wall and like, oh, I don't know.
I liked it. I quite liked it.
And then clearly, that's one of the junctures where you think he's going to bolt.
And while they're all meeting and they're all like
and what I was doing at the top of the episode, like everything might be gone.
What you say might be in Jamaica now.
Like like all the characters might be gone.
New movie and all the casting might be different.
Like nobody knows.
And I guess what really happened here was that the team was split in two.
They took the entire story department and they said, all right,
first half goes with Roger Allers, the original guy.
Everybody else goes under another guy named Chris Williams,
who ended up being one of the primary people on Bolts and Big Hero 6 and Moana.
Huge Disney career after that.
And Chris Williams cracked the new path
that's more about like buddy, buddy.
And Pacha is a very different guy.
And what about this guy, Kronk?
He might be in there.
I think no Kronk in the beginning, who ends up being very important to the movie.
But so like they pitted two sides against each other.
And from the vulture thing, everybody said this was harder than the movie made it.
This was like somebody who's lived with this for two and a half years has to like
he knows that in the room next door, his friends are competing against him.
And ultimately, before the die was even cast, he just said, like,
I see where it's going. I don't want to disrupt.
I don't want to be in anyone's way.
I'm just going to bow out.
And then he's just like sad and walking the beach as you see Sting as well.
This thing, this this documentary just watches all these people just get
hit by the Disney wrecking ball, one big ball and then two little balls on top.
Oh, that's your ball.
That has to have been a joke that you somewhere, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Somebody must have drawn that on the wall at some point.
People devastated and then the middle in the middle of this
David Spade trying to toss off off the cuff.
Joe, oh, the cop that he probably worked on.
Well, well, they they also say that he was like always stellar
and it would whatever version Spade brought it.
The only thing that he could just improvise and improvise
and the only thing that I have to say is like, well, no, wait, hang on.
You can't joke about Michael Jackson.
This is it.
And this is not technically a pop culture.
Although it got a little bit more that way.
Shrek coming.
Yes. You'll have your place when Shrek is here. Yes.
But anyway, new, new, more fun, silly deconstructionist movie
is is built up.
Suddenly, Warburton on the scene, the revelation of Warburton at this time.
He clearly just like that they just like
from not a character to like the main thing you remember
to the point where I forgot that there was a straight to video
called Kronk's New Groove.
They just gave they gave it fully to Kronk.
And it got everybody back to every everyone's.
That's one of those straight to videos that everybody's in.
It's Spade and I think Eartha.
And yeah, they're all still there.
There there is a point where someone says like and they there he is,
I guess, he's my boyfriend.
And I'm like, do you didn't remember that being the relationship?
I want it's in there.
There's a part where there's this kind of awkward small talk.
And I think Spade says like he's a how old is he?
A little younger than you.
Oh, OK. They talk about it in kind of like a meeting a new boyfriend.
It's never like explicitly said. OK.
But there's that flavor. It's a good watch.
I forget. Are you guys fond of this movie?
Or I am. I remember seeing it, Chris.
It would have been like probably went with all my family, Chris.
Yes, I think I saw this in Hercules and I was I liked them.
But I almost was like, where's the epic? Where's the epic nature?
Yeah. Well, and it is it is like a weird like I think critics felt that way, too,
that it's like a weird trifle of a movie. Yeah, it's like really fun.
But when you're in the mode of like the Disney movies,
I go to the Disney movies and they change my life. Yeah.
And it's not that.
But in a way, I was also watching like, well, you know, it's the old ones
weren't like that, you know, they do an aristocats or something.
It's just like a bunch of silly fun.
It's almost a throwback to like 60s animated.
You know, it's not important. It's just a bunch of fun.
Here's a fun comic of the day. Here's a fun singer of the day.
Yeah. You go to all these places and you have a little fun time.
I was wrong because I should have just been like, oh, it's a different tone.
Yeah. But I so it was funny because I think as a kid, I was like,
oh, these are a little less important.
I wouldn't have articulated that, but I think I almost felt
they were like more frivolous.
I love that John Bolton's song, Go the Distance, though.
John Bolton, John Bolton, John Bolton, your secretary of
MSNBC contributor.
What is the who am I Michael Ball?
Michael Ball, not not the former ambassador to the UN.
I the guy that the guy that we were taught was like a monster
during the Bush administration, but now MSNBC brings him out
as if he's like one of their best friends.
It was like because Trump said he didn't like him anyway.
I was strong of a voice.
I love the Michael Ball.
I will go the distance.
He's got the big funny mustache.
Look at a picture of him and imagine who John Bolton is.
We all know John Bolton.
We, of course, I know.
But Trump took us to security clearance away.
Oh, that's right. Yeah.
I have often dreamed of a far off place.
That is really good.
I know. I know.
I understand the humor.
I put a little something like this, don't you think?
If I I was proud of myself for getting Bolton.
So I got half of it.
Yeah, I got to have it.
That's half a name.
So we had to be with the VHS.
I think at least there was a version that came with a single of
sure. Yeah.
And maybe one of his other songs he did for it on the side.
And then just a speech he did to the UN.
Right.
You know who I you know, I'd never heard.
This is another fine friend, the Vulture thing.
Credits of Vulture for this great piece.
Not shown in the movie.
Cut from the second.
This is post revamp.
Yeah, West.
Adam West did a whole character for this that was fully cut.
He was a he was a strange conspiracy theorist in the town
that the John Goodman is so could we extrapolate that maybe
and say there were 60s bat fans because the kit was Catwoman.
Yeah, yeah.
West was in there.
That feels like too much of a coincidence, but maybe not.
I would admit. Well, and if I don't know who is a fan of the guy
from Conan's original writer's room, I would guarantee is that
that's a good point is a bat fan.
And then Seth MacFarlane plucks him to be the mayor of Coahog.
The family guy.
Yeah, his animated rewards are waiting for him.
Yeah, I watched this in chunks.
And I for like a couple of days, I kept having the feeling like
what does this whole like process remind me of something that starts
kind of straightforward, maybe more straightforward,
and then ends up kind of being a light, silly take on the material?
Like you take the bones of it or whatever and you make something out of it.
And I realized what I kept trying to think of was Conker's Bad Fur Day
for the Nintendo 64.
Scott, I don't know if you know what this is.
So Rare was the company that made GoldenEye, Perfect Dark,
Donkey Kong Country.
Yeah, you collect you collect R.A.R.E.
Right. Which was not.
I was so excited about Donkey Kong Country 64, not as fun to me
as Donkey Kong Country was originally the Super Nintendo version.
But still, I liked it and I played it.
And I remember, you know, you get Nintendo Power.
They would say these are the games that are coming.
And Rare was making Banjo Kazooie, which is was a fun platformer.
I know they've done one in a while.
And then they were also making something called Conker.
I don't know if it was Conker 64, but it was a cute little squirrel
game that looked like Banjo Kazooie.
And I remember people being like,
oh, they're making like kind of the same game with a different,
like cute little character.
So all of a sudden, like I guess no one had heard about Conker
and update for a while.
And all of a sudden, Rare was like, we are changing what Conker is.
Now it's called Conker's Bad Fur Day.
And he's now a dirty squirrel.
And there will be like a flower with a big boobs now.
And it's rated and now it's rated S.
And that Conker is spelled, not like they're like Conker and C-O-N-K-U.
Yeah. And then they released like dirty
Nintendo 64 game with Conker.
So they take took what was there.
They determined, OK, we are not going to do this like straightforward version of it.
We're going to turn this into a mature game
that I don't know that I like love so much or anything.
This is sorry.
There's a there's a sexy sunflower.
Yes. And Doja Cat dressed up as the sexiest sunflower for Halloween.
Oh, wow. Yes, that is a really obscure reference.
But they had had they were already like all in on Conker
so much so that I had a straightforward Conker game for Gameboy, I believe.
Like they were already doing like they made up like the non nice con.
Yeah, they did make it like that was already like far enough in production.
And then they just ended up releasing.
Well, you must have been you must have felt very betrayed
when your innocent Conker shows up all body.
I was on some level, yes.
But then also like like uncomfortable with a human female,
but more comfortable with a sexy flower female.
So on some level, there's a layer of protection.
Is the title also bad for Day itself is kind of suggestive?
Oh, perhaps. I assume I assume so, but maybe not.
I don't know. There's a there's a sexy squirrel on the I don't know.
Yeah. So I mean, yeah.
That is what was nagging me in my brain.
I was like, what does this feel like?
And the answer was Conker's bad for Day.
I had heard about the, you know, nice conquer.
But then a few years later, I bought a Nintendo power
and I had mostly Nintendo systems.
We had Genesis and then we went to N64.
So I'd buy Nintendo power pretty regularly
and would read cover to cover,
like would read playthroughs through for games.
I'm like, you didn't have I don't really have this.
And I don't think me or my brother are going to have this.
But I remember getting one and reading the playthrough
for Conker's bad for Day and going like, oh, my God,
no way my mom would ever let me get
her day to hide this.
Well, as you're as you're telling that story,
I found the summary of the story.
This this is the wiki.
And I know what you're talking about.
Here's just a random part.
The dung beetle near the entrance offers Conker
poo balls if he can make the farm cows excrement
in the pasture.
Doing so involves Conker on the poo cabin's pasture,
turning on a big spigot to activate the prune juice,
which gives the cows diarrhea and using a bowl to open gates
for the cows to get out as well as as well as to kill the cows
once each one finishes defecating.
You make a bunch of cows diarrhea and then kill them.
It seems. Yeah, I will say potential club three
Conker. Yeah, I'd say so.
Yeah, you seem excited by suggesting new topics.
I don't want anyone to vote for anything that their heart doesn't desire.
If you want Conker's bad for a day, Conker's bad for a day.
Right. I got to find it.
Well, can I play I guess an emulator? I could find it.
I don't have the actual cartridge.
I have my N sixty four. Don't do all your mom's over.
You know, a good point.
I was afraid to try. Probably goes for a lot.
I think that one might be a little more expensive than
yeah, than some of the other ones.
But you could probably you could find it at like a vintage video game store,
but you got to go behind the beaded curtain.
Oh, yeah. Good point.
And there's these poo balls are too sexy to put in the front.
It's like 10 installments of Leisure Suit Larry and then Conker.
And that's and ones that aren't even allowed in America.
Yeah. Was there maybe there's a full like catch all of like
horny video game characters that aren't that popular.
Leisure Suit Larry and Conker and trying to think there was one other.
Was one other one we had talked about that's like a Leisure Suit Larry rip off.
Oh, Spoogey the Dick. Oh, yeah.
From Neo Geo.
Jackie, the balls Neo Geo system.
I guess the Duke Nukem is popular, but he he was horny,
but he was also just regular to I bought a Duke Nukem rip off
when I was a senior at high school.
Ten dollars called Serious Sam.
Was serious, Sam. I never heard of this.
It was just also a violent first person.
Was there was there light nudity like there was in Duke Nukem?
I feel like more of a maybe a bikini.
Scott, you ever play Duke Nukem?
No, I never had whatever Duke Nukem is because I whatever I download
a version of Duke Nukem and you would go to like a lady in a bikini.
And I think she would flash you.
But it was like the graphics were not sophisticated.
You felt comfortable because they were realistic enough nipples.
It was pixels.
It was not anything that was so does its own pixelation.
As far as that was the big.
Yeah, it was there at Duke Nukem, like Chinese democracy
had a game that took forever to come out.
Oh, yeah. Later. And when we talked about that in the show,
I think, yeah, for some reason, it just it took forever.
And it sunk a company like an entire company.
And then it just came out to like silence on the on the flip side.
Last night, a friend of the show, Kevin Tully, exposed me
to a video game I'd never heard of called Pebble Beach Golf Links.
That's a very dry title.
It's about golfing at Pebble Beach up in northern California.
But what's notable about it is that there's a video contributions
from the golfer, Craig, the walrus, Stadler,
who is like a big stocky guy with a mustache.
And he hears a here's a here's a photo of him.
And he appears in CD-ROM form and like,
like you're going to have to try harder with that pudding.
You think you think it's a weird phrase that sounds kind of dirty,
like you're never going to beat me on the inside.
Yeah, I forget what it is.
But it's the it's the dullest.
It's just the opposite of the Duke Nukem you're describing, where like it's
it's it's just playing golf and like you're not working on your pudding, are you?
And then at some point in the game, there's what's called a coffee break.
And it's just go it's just like smooth jazz playing.
And it just shows you the outside of the real clubhouse at Pebble Beach.
This might be the tamest video game.
This is literally Lou Carvello's putting putting challenge.
But yeah, it's a real life.
There's this maybe there's also a CD-ROM catch all because we do.
But how do you catch all?
I think that's because the catch all becomes a nine hour episode.
No, I think we got to break it up.
So much CD-ROM stuff out there.
I knew I couldn't wait many episodes to talk about Craig the Walrus.
It's great. Yeah.
Anyway, let's let's wrap this up.
So so they do start like turning the ship around on this thing.
And then those those persnickety executives come in
and they say, no, now this group may have come in with reduced expectations.
And everybody's like, oh, boo, boo.
And then they proceed to offer a lot of praise for the new comedic direction.
But it's still like, God, you like looking.
Why don't you draw the movie like the way the movie?
Why don't you write the jokes, dude?
It's just regardless of where they got it.
I just are these guys.
There's early on in the movie where I thought this was their direction.
They were going, someone says, like, yes, maybe it's Sting.
Yes. Well, fucking say that in the first place.
Like, oh, yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Well, I'd say I'll say that to begin with. Yeah.
He's just not built for this process, seemingly.
Another weird thing.
I started texting Kevin because a very in our aesthetic wheelhouse thing.
Sting had done a soundtrack before.
You can find this on Spotify. Never heard of this in my life.
He did a full soundtrack to an IMAX movie in 1994 called The Living Sea.
Confusingly, much like The Pavilion, but unrelated.
It's just like a movie with a lot of nice footage of like the tide rising
and falling in the Bay of Fundy and and then Meryl Streep narrates it.
And it's very pleasant.
But it's a full album of like kind of new agey,
maybe sometimes veering on Donkey Kong aquatic ambience.
I mean, it's lame as hell.
No one don't it.
I let me not as good as the Donkey Kong.
No, no, no, not even close.
I'm just saying it's like a it's very it's Sting doing mostly instrumental music.
That's very much like DCA 1.0, like noodle mixed with like
it's the kind of like like weird,
cheesy sense that you might hear on a video game.
You know what that that reminds me I'm cutting off.
Do you know? No, no, no, no.
No, check out The Living Sea.
Sting keeps making these like little remarks about water slides,
like insulting theme parks.
He does, because yes.
Well, because the context is that
Cusco is David Spade's trying to build.
Yes, it's in the movie guest house.
Yeah, that all stay.
He's trying to build like a like a summer home
and kick John Goodman's family out to build a nice house
with water slides and stuff.
And he is digging at them about.
Yeah, that the message because the original ending was
he just built his house with a big, crazy water slide
next door to John Goodman.
And then he wrote a strongly worded letter saying, yes.
Why is the ending still about water slides?
All right. He should learn to live without water slides.
And I don't know how to this is Sting's letter and everything
he says about culture and grinding it up like hamburgers.
I don't know where this leaves us because everything he says
I agree with, but I'm like, we do a podcast about theme parks,
water slides and hamburgers.
Well, that's what I was getting at.
And we don't like Sting's music very much.
So I don't know what to think.
Because he keeps he has more to life than water slides.
And I'm like, water slides are cool, man.
Yeah, I know.
There's a way to have you have your cake in it, too.
There could be water slides in places that respect the sea.
They also show Sting a portion of the completed
Emperor's New Groove.
And he's laughing and laughing.
He is.
And I'm like, OK, it was fun movie.
But I don't know if you might have just not seen a cartoon
in a while if you're not watching a lot of cartoons.
Yeah, from the Himalayas to Tuscany, you know, he's reading
ancient scrolls.
That's exactly what I was about to say.
I was about to say he's reading scrolls.
That is mostly how he gets his stories these days.
Yes, yeah, you know, he's like he's translating
copies of the Latin Bible that that are like like only only
three only three czars have read this before.
I took it out of their tombs.
I went and exhumed these these Bibles that haven't been unearthed
in fifteen hundred years.
Has he ever seen an episode of The Simpsons?
That's a good question.
That's how they got him.
Right.
And what is this now?
It's a culturally enriching piece.
But hey, he hosts.
Look, he was in the first Richmeister sketch.
So that's true.
And he's funny in that.
Stingling a ding dong.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like him.
Bono does that Mr. Burns impression in the and when he's
making Spider-Man turn off the dark.
He does.
Yeah.
There's a part where he goes like excellent or something.
He does like Mr. Burns voice.
Wow.
I was like, he does Simpsons impressions just like Ted Cruz.
Yeah, that's a very good point.
Bono seems so chill, you know?
He seems like such a cool guy now.
Yeah.
Sting's cool, but he's like in his own little world.
Bono is one of us.
Literally, he's in his own.
I'm going to my little world that was built for me.
The scientists built me a planet.
I've asked for it to stay off of the solar system map
so that it's not taught in schools and people can't find me.
But it's just past Neptune.
If I wish hard enough, I can teleport there.
I just want it badly enough.
And I do.
Days are much longer.
That Tantra session seemed never ending.
The gateway is I can only get there if I have sex for 18 hours without ejaculating.
I have to edge for that long in order to transport across the Milky Way.
There's another song.
We can't end it without talking about the other song.
This is like, OK, so now it's a comic.
So throw out all the songs.
Start again.
And then he's kind of going on.
It really reminded me, actually, of what happens before Bono and the Edge,
before the Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark Letterman performance,
where they're going on about Tin Pan Valley.
Oh, right, right, right.
Just a long set up to get to where, and it's a lot like that, where Sting's like,
and I started thinking about the great movie musicals.
And I thought about Rex Harrison and My Fair Lady.
And that's how I thought about the song, Why Can't a Man Be More Like a Rock?
And then you and then you pause and you get a big, like, bad Yamaha intro, like,
Why can't a man be more like a rock?
He just sits.
He just doesn't move around.
He doesn't talk.
This song seems I don't I don't think maybe he just wasn't a fit.
These songs are brutal.
When he mentions that movie, I think Jane and I were both like,
where is this going?
Where is he going?
What song could he possibly?
He's going for the actual song, but he makes about a rock instead.
Yeah, I went at the very end of the movie when he plays the song of his dad.
It's over the credits.
Yeah, right.
That's where it ended up.
That was their single, and it was nominated for an Academy Award.
When like I think Jane went like, that's what they got.
Like she was like, this is not great.
No, because even that.
Yeah, it's I mean, look, yes, he does end up he's performing on the Oscars.
He's nominated for what that was.
That song was nominated for everything.
It could have been nominated for and lost everything as well.
Lost the Oscar to Bob Dylan song.
Things have changed from Wonder Boys.
So he did get his song, but that song is not a hit by any means,
despite that they tried to do like kind of an adult contemporary.
They were like aiming for the pop charts because I saw on the credits.
Oh, it's by it's produced by Jimmy Jam and Terry Lewis.
Oh, yeah.
It's by like the maestros of all of Janet Jackson's best music
and they're members of the time.
They're fucking awesome.
They weren't on this.
They do that kind of they do that production where it's just like all it is is like
that's how you make it for R&B radio is a little bit of shaker.
It's so boring.
And it doesn't really feel like the movie.
Now, he did do the song Perfect Day.
That's a that's a part I like to where they love.
They go in level with them and they're like there are we are sorry, Sting.
There is there are two spots for your songs now.
Maybe the credits, maybe.
And then we've had they've had an idea if it's kind of two songs.
It's the song you hear at the beginning and so you're at the end.
It's just working title Perfect Day cut to the song.
Well, it's a perfect day.
And like Sting would probably at that point, just like that's that's to quote Simpsons,
like, you know, something like poochy, but more proactive.
The guy is so poochy.
Then I like it.
I think Sting Sting by then is like Perfect Day, whatever you want.
They ask him to sing it, too.
They're like, well, you want to sing the song?
And he says, I don't think I'm right.
I think you want somebody younger and hipper than me.
Then they go with Tom Jones, significantly older.
And that's good.
That is good.
He's good.
That's a very in a movie that's been full of like misery and depressed people staring
at waterfalls, pondering the rest of their creative life.
Then you go to Vegas, like the perfect world and creation.
You see Vegas at that time.
Yeah, because Tom Jones is playing at the MGM Grand,
which is currently hosting FX, possibly with Tommy Tune.
All right.
I think I don't know who is in FX by then, but it could have been Tune,
could have been Cassidy.
Some great mini DV tape footage of Vegas.
Yeah.
Yeah, you see it all.
You see the Luxor before it looked like absolute shit is a prime 90s Vegas.
That's an exciting part.
Kuzka, what's his name?
That's all great.
That's a blast.
And what you do get fun in this, you get like, because what I gather from the Vulture
thing and for Dave Reynolds, like they were having fun and what this all ended up at.
Sure, there was the pressing timeline of this has to come out in a year because of Happy Meals,
but also it created a fuck it kind of atmosphere where they're like, I don't know.
What if cronks into spinach puffs?
Great, in.
What if he does jump rope with kids?
Everything suddenly was like, yeah, we have no time to question that.
It got reduced to a not over thought movie due to the crazy timeline.
And you get some of that fun in the movie a little bit.
I think there hits a point where it's working.
Everybody likes it.
Executives having fun.
We're looking at the Happy Meal toys.
Everybody's happy except for Sting.
Except for Sting.
Sting is just, and there's more great where he's just like, the amount of time I'd allotted
for this is gone.
I'm not a quitter, but it's not an ideal situation for me to be in.
And you do get the context when it loops back around to the fliers and like, oh,
because he's working on a brand new day.
He knows he has desert rose up his sleeve.
He's got Chib Mommy in the tank ready to change the world.
Didn't those all like win tons of Grammys?
I'm sure those are made to demolish at the Grammys.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So he was right on some level, but also it's.
Yeah, that stuff was those were.
Yeah.
How many maybe I'll go back and listen to.
I'll try to be a brand new day guy.
I have to admit I came around on if I ever lose my faith in you.
It took me a lot of Kevin New Age type CD
rom type music for me to realize, oh, it's kind of like all that.
I admit it's not.
It's lame.
It's very, very lame in its production, which is why I.
He won best pop vocal album and best male performed.
Presumably.
Here, I'll try to look it up.
Talk amongst yourselves, but I bet this beat.
This must have beat like in sync.
No strings attached, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I guess.
What did it?
Oh, yeah.
It beat it beat Backstreet Boys, Millennium and Ricky Martin.
Brand new day beat Livin' La Vida Loca.
And the next the next year, no strings attached.
And oops, I did it again in the same category.
Beaten by Steely Dan.
Oh, I remember that.
I remember that.
That's insane.
I love I live and breathe Steely Dan, but I'm still like bye bye.
Bye was beaten by.
What is the song nature?
Oh, you know, Cousin Dupree and Jack of Speed.
Look, I'd rather listen to Jack of Speed than bye bye.
Sure.
But I'm insane.
Right.
I feel like, you know, Chaperone or Shaboosie.
There it is.
When you were gone, we commented on how you bring up Chaperone in every episode.
Now, OK, I'm glad you're back.
I you know, I like that.
Sure.
What I'm getting at is the Grammys this year as we're recording are tonight.
And I don't think that anyone's going to be covering brand new day or desert.
You never know.
Don't count the Grammys out of being the lamest thing you've ever seen.
Cynthia Revo might not do a wicked song.
She might do Desert Rose.
Yeah, yeah, it's possible.
OK.
Well, there was another 25th anniversary.
You got to acknowledge it.
There was this big fire benefit and now all the biggest stars came out to do their hits.
Red at Chili Peppers, blah, blah, blah.
But then Gracie Abrams.
You just see what she did in Long December by Counting Crows.
Don't know.
You must have been patting yourself on your 90s back.
I was in heaven.
Yeah, Gracie, Gracie Abrams, a young lady, new music artist, daughter of J.J. Abrams.
Yeah.
Doing Counting Crows December.
Yeah, very cool.
It's also Billy Eilish with Billy Armstrong.
Yes.
But with doing a 21st century breakdown song, I believe.
Wow.
I didn't see it, but if I had to venture to guess, perfect.
Perfect.
I would agree with you.
A perfect day.
It was when this song was performed.
I clicked on a couple Red Hot Chili Peppers links and all of a sudden my algorithm thought
that I was I mean, I guess I am the biggest Red Hot Chili Peppers fan, but I was going to say
all of a sudden it's but it said to me.
Stupid algorithm thought I like the chili.
I started I started getting like John Frusciante like like love posts like,
oh my God, look what John's wearing.
Like I got so many different posts than people comparing like his striped shirt to like Chris
Kurt Cobain's striped shirt from whatever the smells like teen spirit.
So I got in a weird like Stan culture like Red Hot Chili Peppers algorithm.
And I've just been getting pummeled with it for like a day or two.
This sounds this sounds like such a chore for you, Mike.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't happening.
Just like what is Anthony Kiedis' skincare routine?
And they're showing like his right up right up in his face.
I mean, look, those guys got good buds.
Flea was in his underwear.
Everybody they show it off there.
Everybody's in fantastic.
Flea was in his underwear with like a little belt, but everybody else had clothes on.
So there was a benefit.
You got to be.
Yeah.
And then fleas got a flea.
And he played with Stevie Wonder and Sting.
Sting, I think, sang higher ground.
Flea played bass.
That's so lame.
Stevie Wonder didn't sing.
Stevie, you would have preferred Anthony Kiedis singing with the
red hot chili peppers.
Maybe.
Yes, I would like.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
Brand new day.
The song is kind of a Sting.
Sorry, a Stevie ripoff in a way.
Harmonica.
Yeah, yes, yes.
Yeah.
Anyways, so look, it all works out.
Tom Jones, it works out for everybody.
The brief Eisner, not enough.
It's like getting it's like a new Star Wars giving you one Darth Vader scene.
You're like, oh, but come on.
Don't just give me an Easter egg.
Give me the whole.
But you get a lot of Roy Disney.
Sting writes a letter about how it shouldn't be waterslides.
And it has a impact on the movie.
They do give it a better ending.
So Roy Disney and Sting join arms and do a great collaboration.
Then you see him doing that song wearing a sleeveless black shirt and a pork pie hat.
Sting.
Oh, my God.
Oh, but on the way out here, just a couple of things on the way out the door.
They do a test screening.
The test screening I recognized as a man theater in Westlake Village.
That is but a parking lot away from it's the same
Rick Caruso shopping center that once was home to Club Disney, one of the only club Disney locations.
Episode coming soon as a guest who was interested in doing that.
So that was just like that.
That's a good little Disney block over there.
Then there's you do it all again.
It cuts to composer Mark Shimon.
Mark Shimon.
Shimon.
And he's doing the music.
And I was like, wait, I just watched the movie.
I didn't see his name in the credits because he gets fired.
They do it again.
Mark Shimon, a genius.
He's Billy Crystal's guy and Martin Short's guy and a zillion things.
And he gets fired by Tom Schumacher.
They bring in a new guy, John Debney, who I didn't know.
John Debney is who did the Disney Studios logo.
Like the one with the one that started all of these great films.
So credit to him because I love that little guy.
But yeah, it's thing heartbroken.
Mark Shimon.
Mark Shimon is such a pro at this now.
He just cackles at it seemingly.
Whatever.
He's just on the next job immediately.
You see the Happy Meal toys.
You get a taste of the video game.
I Googled the video game.
Immediately found the Reddit thread calling it the worst game I'll ever have.
The displeasure of finishing.
Then you see the marketing people going through what might a funny tagline be.
And you get this great funny guy who's like, so we're thinking, you know,
looks like royalty smells like llama.
Thank God.
This is why posters are terrible.
Yeah.
And that's such a 90s.
Like night's 90s, too.
Smelly stuff was 90s.
And they, yeah, well, like stinky cheese man kind of thing.
Like kids like stink and smell.
Yeah.
90s Nickelodeon.
All that was gross.
Hey, real quick.
Mark Shimon, another Disney connection, did that short-lived Steve Rogers musical
that was at California Adventure.
Also started in the Hawkeye show.
Smash.
My beloved TV show currently going to Broadway.
They're finally doing it 14 years later.
Is it?
When does it open?
I might already be.
Smash is beloved.
I don't think I knew you were a big smashhead.
I would leave Harold Knight most Mondays and go watch Smash.
Wow.
I don't want to say I particularly liked it, but I liked parts of it.
I see.
Well, this will give us plenty to talk about down the road because Smash with Cat McPhee,
eventual bride of David Foster.
Of course.
My hero.
We'll have to address all of that somehow.
But we're sort of getting, I don't know, any other observations about this,
about Sting, about Craig Stadler, or what's the name of the squirrel again?
Conker.
Yeah, I have none.
I have Red Hulk pictures.
How does it look?
Well, it's just like, it's a plush.
It's really not.
It's like, it's a very generic face.
No, there's no, oh, you got no, no Harrison in there.
So far, the best Red Hulk is the popcorn bucket.
It's not as good as it could be, but you get like a real actual Harrison.
Maybe his facial scar is on there.
But yeah, somebody send me a picture of what they think the best Harrison likeness is on
one of these Red Hulks because I do want it.
I want to own it.
I won't be available.
I'll be hulking out.
It's an actual drug you can take.
You can physically hulk out, which allows you to last even longer in tantric lovemaking sessions,
which become very demanding for your wife because you are now giant and red.
They don't make it available to the public.
It's only to me and Elvis Costello.
It's a natural growing drug.
It's in the mountains.
It's like ayahuasca.
From the poppies of Colombia.
He was on that Elvis Costello short-lived show.
I was trying to find it because he actually was.
Yeah, because he performed with the police, which I thought was really good.
Oh, yeah, because that was around the same time with the reunion.
Also performed with Bono on the Edge on that, which was.
I love that show.
Springsteen episode of that Elvis Costello show.
Costello is obviously of a piece with all of these stuffy British Brits, but he's fun.
His music is very fun.
And he was never dumb enough to do a fucking Disney movie.
That would have been a catastrophe.
I wonder if he was even ever approached.
It does feel like something he would have tried.
Yeah, maybe.
I think he would have tried.
He's done a bunch of different stuff.
I feel like, am I crazy?
But was there a certain strain of music writing when he was first starting out,
where he was kind of like, and this guy, he's a little out there.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
So that was in my mind.
You know, rebellious, anti-authority.
He was kind of the green day of his time.
Elvis Costello did a musical last year.
Oh.
Face in the Crowd.
Based on the short story and 1957 film of the same name.
Really?
Oh, the...
Who is the star of that movie?
That's the Andy Griffith.
That's the...
Yeah, it's the Andy Griffith.
Trump kind of.
Only it's a version of it where the guy gets his comeuppance in any way, shape or form.
That's a good question.
I don't know.
Is this still happening?
Maybe.
It's the story of what would have happened to Trump if anything had happened after the first.
Wow, good news.
Larry Rhodes is back.
He learned nothing.
He's worse than ever.
Face in the Crowd 2.
Well, anyways, I think that does it.
I think you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
A lot of good morsels there and things we can throw out next time.
But especially, I thank Bobby Libby for the great suggestion.
Wait a minute.
I found another comment that Bobby made elsewhere on our Patreon.
I think on the poll post.
Whoa, Bobby Libby.
Let the record show that I, the person who nominated the Sweatbox, ultimately voted for
Bug Buzz Buzz Pudding Sauce.
Oh, no.
Discourse.
No, no.
Turn the recording off.