FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning, the following podcasts may contain
pie-based social media,
the dream of flying with the Pteranodon,
lightsaber patio accessories,
and lots of talk about Mickey Mouse's special little outfits.
All that, plus some nautical chat about the new cruise ship, the Disney Treasure,
with Kitra Remick and Peter Serretta from the YouTube channel Ordinary Adventures.
Let's set sail on today's podcast, The Ride!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast hosted by three men
who take all their pills with water from a souvenir sipper.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
It's funny, I do have a souvenir sipper that I bought online
that I didn't actually buy in the theme park.
I bought a universal souvenir sipper because it had a big pharaoh's lighthouse on it.
And how often do you see lighthouse merchandise now?
You just bought this is what you're saying?
No, like a year ago.
Okay, how often do you sip from it?
Pretty regularly, it holds a lot of water.
So you will oftentimes just have a water glass, because I'll be honest with you,
that was mostly a joke.
Yeah, no, I know.
But you do sip, how often do you think you sip from the lighthouse?
Maybe like once or twice a month.
I have a lot of these water bottles.
I think it's cool.
It sounds like I'm being insincere, but I do think that's cool.
I should drink from my pirate's dinner adventure glass more,
and the different souvenir glasses I have.
But I don't have anything as fun as that as the souvenir sipper.
I don't know if the chip on it would work if I went back to,
if I went to Universal Orlando and I said, please reactivate this.
Do you think they could do that?
It's one of the ones where it's like drinks all day and you can reactivate them.
Oh, that chip.
Yeah.
I don't think that's still going.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
But it's worth a shot.
It's worth, well, we'll see.
It's been through the dishwasher a lot.
Okay, do you think you could go to like, where's the like city hall at Islands of Adventure?
Oh, it would be on Port of Entry.
Our guests are the real pros at this sort of thing.
Right.
So they would know where to complain when you throw like an absolute fit that your sipper won't get you free refills.
And then I'll be out of the sipper because you know I'm going to throw it in anger.
You would throw it at the employer at the wall.
At the wall.
Oh, please.
I'm not totally uncouth.
I do have manners.
All right.
Well, let's bring the guests and see where they would throw a sipper if they were having a fit at the theme park.
From the great YouTube channel Ordinary Adventures, it's Kitra Remick and Peter Soretta.
Welcome.
Did I say your last name right, I'm realizing now?
You did.
I did.
Okay, good.
I just had a freak out in my mind.
I should have checked that.
No, I get it.
I have a very unique name.
Okay, yes.
You did great.
Okay, because I would have edited this part out and it would have made me look, I would have done it later and then imitated your voice saying, great pronunciation.
So, guests, thank you for coming.
Long time coming, I feel like.
Finally, you guys have been.
We have been Podcast the Ride listeners for so long.
I remember, how long have you guys been doing this?
Since 2017.
Okay, yeah.
So we definitely, we started in 2019 and we were definitely listening.
I remember how it happened too.
Paul Shearer DMed me and was like, Peter, they have made a podcast for you.
Wow, really?
Yeah.
So I'm not sure when that was, probably like 2018 or 2019.
Yeah, because he did the show pretty quickly, I feel like.
Yeah.
I'm forgetting which episode, but yeah, he did it pretty quick.
He was, yeah, Shearer has been really good.
He's told a lot of people, I feel like, but I didn't realize he was the reason you got into it.
Oh, yeah.
We're obsessed with you guys.
We subscribe to all the Patreon levels.
Wow, thank you.
Yeah, you guys are amazing and I feel so grateful and honored to be here.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you so much.
That's very nice.
Thanks for doing this.
Yeah.
Thank you for talking, Scott.
We're on the Scott Free episode.
We are, yes.
Thank you for joining us.
We can talk about the points.
I like talking about points.
I love the points episode.
So yeah, so on one hand, I apologize because it's not the three hosts, but on the other
hand, we're Scott Free.
So if you want to talk points, we can do anything today.
The sky is the limit.
By the way, quick aside about the points.
Please, yes.
We recently, we're doing a lot of traveling now.
We recently got into, we love Delta.
So we got a Delta MX card.
Yes.
And we travel a lot, but not a lot in comparison to like people that actually travel.
But that card, putting all our expenses on that card gets us upgraded to first class
every time like we fly.
Really?
Yeah.
That's nice.
Is there a big annual fee on it?
Yes.
Okay.
It's like 600 or something.
Does it have a credit, a travel reimbursement credit as well?
Yes.
We'll also get you into the Delta Lounge too.
So.
Yeah.
And how is the lounge?
I know we're supposed, ostensibly we're talking about a cruise today, but how is the lounge
review wise?
The one in LA is great.
Yeah.
The one in LAX is good.
The one in Orlando is still nice, but LAX is better.
The one in Orlando has these creepy Mickey and Minnie art paintings on the wall.
But the one in LA, if you get there early enough for breakfast, they'll make you breakfast
tacos.
Like they actually have someone there cooking them and yeah.
Wow.
Lounge, Jason, lounge wise, have we, we have not talked about lounges a lot on the show
and that maybe is because Scott is a third host of the show.
I don't know.
I don't know where he feels.
I don't know about the lounge, if he gets there, but once in a while I've done an airport
lounge.
I've never been in one.
I know.
Right.
I thought we were going to talk about points, like all the castaway, is that what it's called?
The cruise ship loyalty.
Like, and you just keep getting more and more free totes and stuff.
And I was excited for that.
I didn't even think about the, uh, go ahead.
The way Disney does these castaway points, it's infuriating because you basically get
one point for every cruise you go on.
Okay.
So if you go on like a three night cruise, you get one point.
If you get, go on a 14 night cruise, you get one point.
Well, that's foolish.
And then there's different levels.
So if you get to five points, you're at a different level.
You're 10 points.
You're a different level.
If you're a 50, you're at a different level.
On Royal Caribbean, the other cruise, big cruise line, you get a point for every day
or every night you stay.
So I feel like that's better.
That makes a lot.
Yeah.
It makes more sense.
I don't know.
I have a background.
No, I've never been in an airport lounge.
You've never been, this is shocking to me.
Scott has already tuned out of this.
He's furious right now.
He's thrown, he's thrown his phone against the wall of whatever building he's in right
now.
His phone is broken and now he has to go get a new one.
I, I don't know.
I should, I should think about trying it.
Cause I had, I should try it.
I should try it next time.
I don't know that we get there or I get there pretty early.
Yeah.
I, yeah.
You got there earlier than I do recently.
I really like show up very late.
In fact, the last time we went to Orlando, I was late and missed the flight.
So it was like 15 minutes too late.
Yeah.
So yeah, you just, yeah, I don't know why I never even realized this about you.
The splurge I did last time.
Cause you know me, I don't think of myself as splurging much.
I did the Uber X that can pick you up right curbside.
And it's nice because when I flew in, I flew in October and November, December.
And when I flew in October, taking the bus to they, they call it the LA exit.
Horrible.
It's awful.
And if you have mobility issues, super awful.
It's like a death trap.
So I'm like, Oh, I'm just going to pay the extra $30 or whatever.
And they could pick us up at the curb.
I could just sit for a little while longer.
Because I'm like, this airport is not ready for the Olympics.
No, it's just going to a dirty parking lot to get a taxi or a lift.
It's just a little much.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So, but you don't get like a warm buttered roll in an Uber X.
Like you do at an airport lounge.
I know.
You sometimes get candy though.
I feel like it's grandma candy though.
It's like those little strawberry hard candies.
Yeah.
It's like whatever the cheapest candy.
I mean, you don't, I don't need candy in a lift or an Uber or something.
I don't.
I mean, I like candy.
I don't need it.
But yeah, it's interesting.
So I guess, yeah, we've got to get you in a lounge, Jason.
This is a whole, this is a shot to the list of my priorities in my life is to get you in an airport lounge.
Yeah.
So we'll figure that out.
And, and yeah, any points talk in the, we can do it.
Feel free.
I'm so sorry to the people out there listening.
I know some people are probably very angry that I brought up points, but.
I know.
It was the only one who was upset with Scott.
Everyone seems to like it.
Well, maybe one or two.
But let's talk, let's talk a little bit about your YouTube channel because I am fascinated by the rise of the vloggers.
And you've been doing this YouTube channel now for what?
Five years?
Roughly?
Four?
I think this year will be our sixth year.
Six?
We're coming up on six.
Wow.
Like in when?
Like April or May?
Yeah.
May maybe?
So pretty soon.
Yeah.
Congrats.
And the channel does great.
It's real fun to watch.
It's in the rotation.
Yeah.
With Mr. Morrow when we're watching.
Oh, what an honor.
We love Nate.
He's the best.
By the way, he is the greatest guy ever.
I know you guys have met him and hung out with him, but like he literally is the person you
see on his videos and he's just like the nicest dude.
I was in awe.
I mean, I'm not even, no, no hyperbole.
I was in like awe of him.
I was like, wow, he's like, this is the guy.
He's this guy.
Yeah.
I don't know how he exists.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like it's, it's hard to explain, like, because he's just so nice.
Yeah.
And then I was like, oh, you're doing a panel.
We did a panel at Comic-Con for the, to celebrate the street sharks last year.
And he's like, I'm coming to that.
He showed up there and then like we saw him later.
Yes.
Very, very nice.
And just like, he seems like he runs Disney World.
He just seems like well connected there too.
He knows everybody.
He knows what's going on.
I'm like, I was fascinated by that aspect as well, which makes sense.
Cause obviously like that's what he does.
He's just there all the time.
But yeah, so you're, you're traveling, you're doing cruises.
You're doing Disney World.
Like I am, I am a little jealous.
I'm a little jealous, honestly, cause I'm like, oh, they're there now.
Like, oh, look at there over there.
Like it is a little bit, a little bit of jealousy on my part, but like, could you
just talk about starting it and do like, did you have grand plans for it?
Like what was, did you, it was, it just sort of, it happened and like unfolded as
you went.
Yep.
Okay.
All right.
I got it.
Nevermind.
All right.
You can tell the story, but like honestly, it just kind of snowballed into what it is
now and we never, not that we didn't talk about it, but it was kind of like, we started
it and it's just like, okay, now I guess we're like full-time YouTubers.
So I used to operate, I started this website slash film.com, which is a movie news blog,
which I no longer own, but we got invited to galaxy's edge, the opening of galaxy's
edge.
And I was like, no one's going to, and I used to, as the theme park nerd, we used to get
invited out to Orlando for openings of rides and stuff like that.
And I used to, you know, write up a blog post and she would take the photos, but I was like,
no one's going to want to really bad photos.
No one's going to want to read about this land.
They want to see it.
Right.
Like, so I was like, maybe we should, because we were watching vloggers, we were watching
like, 10 tracker, Adam, you know, the OGs.
Sure.
Yeah.
And she was always like, oh, it'd be fun to start a blog.
And I'm like, no, it'd be so much more work than you think it would be, which is, I mean,
it's both true.
Both of it's true.
Um, but like we use that as an excuse to start the channel and it was supposed to be like,
we're going to do one video a month and if we ever do anything cool, like, oh, we're
going to Galaxy's Edge.
I'll show that.
And then it kind of, yeah.
Like I said, snowball that first two weeks of Galaxy's Edge.
I'm not sure if you guys, well, you guys remember you needed reservations to get into that land.
And since we were so such Star Wars nerds, all our friends put us as one of their plus
ones on their reservation.
So for the first two weeks we were in Galaxy's Edge, like every other day, every other day,
a lot.
And every time we brought a camera and at that point everybody couldn't get in there.
So they were like, wanted to see what it was like.
So our Galaxy's Edge videos kind of blew up right away, um, in a way that we didn't expect.
Right.
Yeah.
Don't go back and watch them.
They're not.
Oh, they're bad.
They're really bad.
Okay.
But, um, yeah, we started doing three videos a week.
Um, and it's become like our full time thing now.
Yeah.
Right.
How does the planning go?
Like you probably saw as we were setting up this podcast, it's like, these guys don't
plan very well for anything.
Their setup looks haphazard.
They've been doing this forever, but it seems like this is their first podcast.
But do you have like, do you feel like you're, do you have like six months worth of vlogs
planned?
Like how does it even work like that?
I wish.
Well, Peter's the planner.
Okay.
So he'll, I just kind of show up and I also edit the videos, but yeah.
Yeah.
So I'm doing the, I do the filming.
She does the editing.
I do the planning.
Right.
So like, uh, you know, recently we went to Japan, doing that is like months of like us
watching vlogs and reading, I'll read those like lonely planet books and, uh, going on
TikTok and seeing what's, and then building a Google map and then I'll be like, you know,
what can we accomplish this day?
Right.
Yeah.
So it is a lot of like planning, but I mean the regular stuff, I was going to Disneyland
is, you know, the week before us like seeing what's the new food items, what's the new
things, what should we, you know, right.
What can we accomplish?
Are there things like where, you know, the algorithm like certain type, like, you know,
let's say for instance, like we know that YouTube, if I say the word pie or something,
like it'll boost my video.
Like, are there like secrets like that to YouTube and maybe you shouldn't even tell
me this.
Maybe this is like a trade secret.
I wish there was.
Yeah.
I don't think they're in the title.
Oh, you don't want the bakers coming after you.
So that Jason really should become like a pie influencer.
I'd watch that.
Yeah.
Just going around tasting the taste.
Tasting different pies.
Yeah.
Just keep going to house of pies.
Just trying to make money.
It's mostly just one place.
Yeah.
One place.
And ordering the same pie every time.
Yeah.
You make the same comments every video.
Hey guys.
Ending the channel.
Parking's gotten really bad at house of pies.
Yeah.
So there isn't like it can't be like that
Pacific yeah, or I guess yet. Maybe the AI and I mean for a while
Like there were stuff that our channel would hit for like if we did a Star Wars video, right?
Right, right. The the people that were watching and subscribing were
Star Wars fans, so like it would just perform better, right? But now I don't know. I mean cruises does really well for us. Mm-hmm
We recently been doing a lot of international travel
So we went to China recently did the theme parks over there people seem to be really interested in traveling
Yeah, now that is I guess I do like that. I like just watching videos of like walking around
Japan or something a 4k video and you put on the TV you just like kind of zone out a little bit
Yeah, there's something I don't know. I don't know if that's just like
Vicarious. Yeah vicariously living vicariously probably on some level
so yeah, so so
Yeah, I guess Star Wars. Yeah, that makes sense
As far as I like when you go now to these places
I'm just so blown away by how much this is blown up by how often you will see somebody taking video
Do you run into like oh someone else is taking video for their vlog in the section where we're
Trying to do our review of the new like food item or something like does that happen often a lot? Yeah
Opening day or something when you know, everyone's gonna be there, right?
Yeah, like we were there this past week for the the video that we published today
Which I'm not sure when this is going up, but it was a video in Avengers campus. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I watch and yes
we run into our friends magic journeys and
They were there doing the exact same clearly had the Captain America sipper and they like they were doing the exact same thing as us
And I was like, oh no, we got we were both doing the same video
So is there like as their etiquette is like, okay
They're reviewing the sipper and we have to move like they were here first
Is that just general the general rule or you or you wait for them to stop or you do it at the same time?
Well, we I mean we featured them in our video they were they featured us in the world
I mean not all of us friends, but I would say most of the people are friends, right?
so it's also you're like the other thing is I've realized is
People don't just watch ordinary adventures, you know, they also watch paging mr.
Maura, they also watch magic journeys or they also you know
I mean and they like seeing that in the same way that people liked seeing Avengers and see everybody come together
They love those true. That's one look. There's a crossover. Oh, right. Yeah. No, you're right
I was about to make that same comparison because it does feel like us to the vendor
You're not. No, you're saying you're like the Avengers. You're saying would you say you're more like you're like?
Captain America of the group of like the group and some other people are Thor
Yes, and then I mean
Oftentimes when we will be watching like sometimes they'll be like, oh this person's in a video a lot
And then all of a sudden they disappear and then we're like, where did that person go?
Oh now like there's and I'm I'm trying to think if I have a specific I won't say a per specific person
but like there is there is like a
Fascination about that as far as personalities are concerned too where you're like
Oh, it seems like this person's hanging with this person a lot and then they go away
I don't know what that's about whatever but then you can if you're watching with somebody who is like-minded you can speculate you can
Talk about as if you know, these are people we know this is a reality show of some kind sparks were maybe flying
But now they fizzled out more ten
You could do a very tabloid style
Report it to your partner my favorite version is this I think it was
Jane and I were watching like the opening night of horror nights like
2021 I think like would have been the first one that was back
And it was just a torrential downpour in Orlando
So that always scare actors were out and then the streets are empty besides guests
So we just kept strict switching between live streams and it would be like, oh
This live streamers meeting up with this live streamer under an umbrella and they're like, how about this rain?
It's like yeah, I might go to a house but it the way it's kind of long and you're in the rain outside
So it's just getting all the angles of like the soggy theme park
And I'd like this is must-see TV for me
It's too bad. There's not like a Google map where you can see where the live streamers and I click on to them
I don't want that's a great idea. Everybody was like a little Apple tracker
If you if the right patreon tier
We should do that Jason we should do that for you for how we'll add a patreon tier we're gonna add a tracker to you
Oh
It's gonna be a very high tier though people really have to pay for that
So I say to just see where you are at any moment of the day. Yeah, we want that. We don't know
Oh, oh, so it's my whole life. It's not just theme parks. It's your whole life. Oh great
Sort of show like as if it was my neighbor Truman some sort of it's like Truman show but with no budget
Or my other neighbor ed TV
Yes, I remember we remember ed TV. Yeah, the other
Yeah, do you remember the the real-life version that they had before?
Twitch was twitch. I think it was called Justin TV
Oh, really? I don't know this and they used to have people like I think I Justine was one of the first people that did
This where she like would broadcast her life 20 like you could see her sleeping
You did the only time she would turn it off
I think was like when she left her house she would turn it off for like five minutes
Watch so you couldn't see
Where her house was? Oh, yeah. Yeah, I knew about like on twitch. I knew there are people who live stream
sleeping
Like if you donate enough they'll like wake up. Oh, really? Yeah, I think it like triggers like alarms or something
Wow, those maybe it's on tik-tok Jason. We gotta get
Disco ball will come down and they'll like wake up
No, the disco ball actually come down in their house, I mean there's different scenarios, okay a hundred bucks to watch you
So just torture me. No, no, no. Well, we don't I guess the disc we don't even have the disco ball
Maybe it's just something else. It's like but it's just a watch you sleep for $100 a month
Club one club Z's
Yeah, well we'll talk about that off the ear so
We were talking a little bit about this and this is this is very embarrassing maybe and I'll just share my part of it
What I was saying is, you know the whole the the politics of being invited to things is very interesting
It also makes me feel
Loser ish sometimes because look we have a well-documented ghosting happen hook ghosting happening with Knott's Berry farm
With Knott's Berry farm, it's been well documented that Knott's Berry farm stopped inviting
It goes some ghosts that are ghosting. It might be we don't know
That's the thing when ghosts happen, you don't know which ghost is ghosting you the ghost that works in the PR office
But I am also fascinated by that because sometimes you're like, oh look who got invited to this on YouTube
And then sometimes you see a vlogger didn't get an invite and this is always I'm so fascinated by this and I do
Now having experienced it from doing this podcast a little bit
I am always like I wonder what this person thinks about if they got invited and this person didn't like does this does this weigh on?
Your does this bother you like it bothers me. I guess hopefully it doesn't
There's a little bit of FOMO there. I'm not gonna lie
Like especially for the most recent thing like the Disney treasure. We already bought, you know our voyage
We're already planning to go but deep down you do hope like oh
Maybe we'll get invited to like a preview thing and then seeing it like because all of our friends there
Yeah, there's an advantage of being first
Right right videos early. I should say being early
There's an advantage of being on the ship before the public is because then you can get out and like more people
Or you can like watch a show and there's not like a million people in the way and you get like a good shot
Or whatever. Yeah, that's it. Yeah, so there was a little bit of FOMO there for sure
Yeah, makes you like I try not to dwell on it too much
But you know, I'm only human only human. Yeah, I'm like, why don't they like us?
It's weird because you know, I came from the world of journalism with slash film and in that world
If you don't like a movie, you know
Just on to the next one and you get invited to the next premiere or the next test
You know screening or whatever or set visit like it's not like they
You don't get punished for having any critical thoughts
But I feel like now that we're in the world of
YouTube and even you guys with podcasting. I think it's all lumped into like influencer. Yeah world, which I think is more it's weird
It's a weird world. Yeah
where people are incentivized to just like everything and we always want to be I
think one reason we have a big audience is as much as we
We do love to spotlight the things that we love
We are honest about the things that we don't like and I
Don't know why we weren't invited on the treasure but
There was a bunch of people. It was amazing. Yeah
Yeah, we there was a private island that Disney opened up last year called Lookout Key at lighthouse point
Was that the one with the bugs? Yes
And it just so happens that anybody that showed the flies wasn't
Okay
Yeah, we think we don't know interesting that isn't yeah, I could see something like that happening
I like to think that Disney has never extended any invite to us because you know
What maybe will be like very critical something but I think actually what the case is if anyone ever tried to listen they were too
Bored by what we were talking about
That's probably more likely as they were like these guys are just talking about Lucille Ball too much
When are they gonna actually talk about the ride like it doesn't make any sense
So they realize how much little scene specials are on hoopla to watch
But it isn't it is interesting cuz yeah, well you gotta think too like how much is just someone
Making a split second like yeah, I gotta finish this email with the invites for lunch sure like
What are their number I know it's just like a meaningless metric like I read so
Often about like people it's like yeah
We really wanted to cast this person in something and then the studio was like they don't have enough Instagram followers
And it's like how does that?
Translate like what are the metrics?
What does that mean?
well
that's also a thing I think Disney's focusing on is they want tick tockers and Instagrammers and
You know you posted a tick-tock from the Disney treasure of you dancing on the deck and it gets millions of views
That's millions more people than would have watched our video on the right treasure
But I don't know it
My argument is I think there's more of a connection there if you watch a 40 minute or 50 minute vlog
You're not just like going through your your for you page, so I think
people that watch that kind of content could
That you have the potential to convince them to go on to Disney Cruise where I don't think like a tick-tock
Is gonna convince anybody, but that's just my right yeah that makes sense
I mean look I'm would I argue that a two-hour episode of a podcast might help in yes
You to do something I would say it would even if how many people do you think went and saw David Copperfield because of you?
Guys I we've heard a lot of them
We've heard a lot of people that have gone to see yeah the tale of blue 32
Yeah, and they are all delighted and and so yes, it would make a lot of sense
But I think I did really not enough to save I left my M in Vegas the M&M store that is true
Movie which I think has been retired like it was dying when I saw it at the start
Yeah, well, okay, we can't save everything we can't do we can't work mad
We're not David Copperfield
But yeah, so it is
Yes, I try not to be like try to make up stories about what what like PR people think of us in my head
It's hard though. You know the other thing is
My experience meeting PR people just like from
College or at these various companies every time I would go to something it would be a new part
It'd be like oh no Jenny went to go work at like
Speared off for something it was like oh they went they moved that this was their first second job
And they just kind of they were here for six months, and then they moved on every time
It's like a totally new person
Mm-hmm, but it's not you're saying that they're not thinking too much about like like Carlson and what they think of him
And he's funny or not in the right way
No
Yeah, they're not analyzing your life from a far right, but sometimes it feels like they are
Do you encounter PR reps when you go to like?
Some of these theme park events that have actually listened to the podcast or never never
I've heard store of like
Was talking to someone who worked for the company and they really enjoyed your hotel like there's such and such
Yeah, definitely people who work in the the parks and work behind the scenes, but never the actual people making the decisions
I don't there's never been a hint that anyone has listened to a second of an episode
Before which I guess is probably good. Let's be honest. Let's it's probably good because it's you know
We're just a bunch of silly gooses
What are we gonna do? We don't know what we're saying
Three silly gooses just you guys
So, yeah, you can look at the analytics and see how many listens are coming from a campus in Glendale
Oh, that's interesting. We definitely down pretty far, but I don't know about that
I don't know. Yeah, we know the longitude and latitude of where people are listening. I don't know but we know like city wise
Do you have any sort of grand plans for the channel or is it just kind of going and cool stuff comes up?
Is there like are you gonna do like we're gonna make a pilot?
Like is there anything I guess I shouldn't you shouldn't reveal that really if I'm asking like a big ambitious plan
No, I don't we just like doing what we're doing
I mean epic universe this year is probably gonna be a big thing for us, right the Disney adventure
Which is their ship going out of Singapore, right? The ones are two big plans this year big plans
we recently kind of in the last couple years got bit by the
international travel bug and
And
So we want to do a lot more of that
Sure, but is there let's real quick or not real quick
Is there stuff you saw in China anywhere that you were like particularly we're excited about
That like you want to tell everybody to go do oh my god, I universal Beijing. Okay, I was gonna
One really surprised us because we did we went to Hong Kong
Shanghai and Beijing and I think like I wasn't expecting much from Beijing and it was so awesome
Yeah, yeah, and we were over there in their city walk when you guys were doing your last city walk
So I got you know, it was like us. Oh, yeah, we're like listening to on the plane ride and stuff
Like they need to get out here
Bubba gumps over here, too
And we need to review the shrimp there you need to know how it tastes
Way different I bet but it like that park is so crazy because it debuted during the middle of the pandemic in
Almost no one's been there. Like at least from the states. I people are afraid. Yeah, people are afraid I think to go to China and
We found I mean politics aside
We found as tourists going to China. It was very easy. Yeah, it wasn't scary
It was very intimidating. But then once we got there it was
Very chill. Sure. Yeah, I mean there was like police on every corner, but they just
They reminded me of like security guards like they're just like clocking in and clocking out and I don't know
Yeah, but that park is insane. They're Jurassic right that old ride right is like
Amazing I hope they bring that to like epic universe or somewhere over here at some point
Yeah, I watched the video the video on that you sometimes you're like
I'm not sure if this translates and I feel like it there's just no way it's not ten times even better every time
We wrote it like literally ten times and every time I was like, are they real like they seemed so real, right?
Yeah, that's like a scoop vehicle the spider-man transformers vehicle. Yeah, but it's like basically the same thing
It's just there's a lot more practical stuff. Yeah on the ride
And yeah, the crazy thing is I guess spoiler alert is the the was it in Domus or t-rex?
That's coming at you. I'm that like circular part
I
Dominus right or I don't remember. Yeah in Dominus. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, cuz that's the the transitions in that one
It's just so good. There's a part where you're in the middle of that mean mean street of Jurassic world
I don't know what it's called
but like the t-rex and the
Indominus are fighting each other and then the t-rex throws Indominus through the window and you're moving into another right minute
His head just comes in as you're going through the other room
It's something like a part where you go by and you see like the margaritaville like cups
Yes, like from Jurassic world. That's good stuff. There's no you not Jimmy, but just the cups
Yeah, cuz the Jimmy Buffett robot would be a great tribute to the man and
People would finally would flock to the
Universal Beijing if they knew that was there even the red the dress world restaurant looked
Awesome. Yeah, just the scale how big it was and unique and I always your guys's a
Lot of your videos from Asia. I'm like that theme park food looks so good and so affordable
Yeah, it's so much cheaper to get food, right?
Especially in Tokyo that restaurant is so cool. Like it's a fine dining restaurant. It's called Hammond's and it has like a
John Hammond outside like they really look their water world has like this
What are you 30 foot tall? Yes, their water world the statue of of Kevin Costner. It's amazing
Ever seen water world, I don't know, but they love it there
So there is a big it into it like likeness full Costner face. Yeah
Scrap metal
So that's interesting to me. Why don't we have that here cuz that's a whole land
Yeah, right a restaurant like has a restaurant in the show and I think like a churro stand
Yeah, it's become its own just like theme park specific IP even though there was a movie
And that land is cool for a theme park fanatic because the costumes in that land are just
Stitch together pieces of cloth that they have found but some pieces of it have like theme park references
so I'll have like the Institute of
Future technology. Yeah future technology will be on someone's shoulder and like oh my god. Yeah, that's cool
Man, I yes, I am jealous of that stuff, too
I'm just I am one like water world just survive. He'll never go away. It's seemingly like
It's just like it's been they've built new ones in the last few years
Yeah, I was gonna say that's a new park and they decided to build over IP. They have yeah, that's movies
Yeah, so they determine that water world is more important to do there than like a new movie, man
That's interesting and it's fun watching like those crowds like the Chinese crowds
Fill up that arena and every one of them buys like a poncho
They like to buy the poncho and sit in the wet area like they are they love it
And is it the same show
I mean the same kind of like the plane everything and just in a different language, but yes same exact show. Yeah, wow
Okay, it's funny. Like I wonder yeah, is there do they have translations going like is there any way to know what it's in English?
No, I mean, it doesn't matter obviously for that one. No. Yeah
I'm just like wondering if they had like updated the shown anyway, or anything. Do they have horror nights in Beijing?
I think yeah, I have it in Singapore and Beijing right and Tokyo or is it one of they have it in Tokyo
I know that because we remember seeing a video of like one of them were like somebody was in a bathtub
Oh, they popped out. Did you ever see that? Yeah, and I don't know where that was, but it wasn't in America
Yeah, cuz I was like, wow, maybe that was Beijing. Maybe it was
Somebody was literally submerging water and would pop out. It seems dangerous
It's like they're paying him seems like there's not there's like a law against that one of the Universal parks
in Asia eight horror nights was
All day long and included but it was only a few houses and then I think when the Sun went down
Maybe there was a little more stuff, but it wasn't a separate ticketed event
Right interesting. Yeah
Let me ask this you've been to a lot of places you've done a lot of rides now if like you could if there could be
One ride that you've ever been on that just existed next to your like home that you could just pop out the door and go on
Shanghai Pirates of the Caribbean for me. Okay, or the Jurassic World ride was pretty good, too. Okay
The Shanghai Pirates so good because that's another one right like the video makes me think it's amazing
Yeah, it's so it's crazy how big and scale it is. Like yeah, I really feel like you're underwater
You don't see the ends of the screens anywhere, right and that one
Yeah, I guess we've talked a little bit about it
But it's like there's a lot of like practical effects and robots and animatronics and then there's these big crazy
Dome screen type things that make it feel like you're being submerged and in water and then popping out of the water
Yeah, and the boat goes like all over it like goes backwards. It goes sideways. You're like how how's this?
You kind of don't know where it's gonna go at one point
It goes like inside a ship and you you're kind of surprised that it goes into the ship and it's really like I
experienced of course on Guardians and Scott always
Makes fun of the way I describe things but Guardians of the Galaxies the Epcot ride. I
Never had been handled like that. That's what way I described it
I was handled on a ride like it felt like so precise and it seems like that boat is similar where like
You've never been on a boat where you feel like you're like there's pinpoint accuracy of where it's pointing you and what it's doing
Yeah, like it's an unusual feeling especially for a boat. What would you pick?
I don't know why that I have to pick something came to my head. I have to pick something from Asia
It could be anywhere. It could be anywhere
Resistance would be no bullet. Oh, okay
If you have a big Star Wars person boy
In my mind all your favorite after all the rides that you've been on
I think so, but the thing is I could just drive to Anaheim like
Yeah, I guess probably the smart thing to do is would be going to a far away
Yes, you're think you're putting actual thought into the yeah
You're stressed you need to come down a little
Would you be mad if rise the resistance jostled you more like this is the constant refrain that I'm saying about the ride
I wish it would would fuck you up a little more. I
Mean I wouldn't be mad. Okay, like it's not a good. It's not a great you have with it. Yeah. Yeah
Like it can't do it. Why would that be if you
Wish you were getting pummeled with lasers from stormtrooper. I want to feel the heat. I want the yeah
I want like that would be kind of cool. I would like that if they are interesting because I'm that I remember we went to
D23 a couple years before
Galaxy's Edge opened and I remember clearly talked to Imagineer in front of like the rise of the resistance area
And he was like you're gonna feel the heat of Kylo Ren's lightsaber
Okay, and I was like, oh, that's cool. Like and I yeah, you don't feel the heat
So I'm like wondering like did they get rid of that or probably but maybe it was when it comes through the ceiling
It could either have been the car comes to the ceiling or when you like walks out
Yeah, one of those two points, but that would have been cool. Right or you like yeah great. Yeah, I wonder
Yeah, I guess cuz like how would they have even done that from the ceiling like just make the ceiling hot like
Just funneling a space heater. Yeah
Yeah, like one of those things you get like when you're eating outdoors at a restaurant
No, yeah, they just dress it up to look like a light saber
Or that's a pretty good like if you have a patio and you're a Star Wars guy
You could just have like a lightsaber
Space heater maybe or whatever patio heater. That would be a good
I'm sure you can sell a lot of those if you could design probably
And it would have to be like the Sith lightsaber because of red makes it have to sure it just makes the most sense
If it's red, yeah, because you could have a blue flame flames are blue
It can be they could be purple. Sure the the things that amaze me about the
Best rides in Asia are like the magic tricks that they pull off. Mm-hmm like on pirates. There's this part where
Jack is a skeleton. He's like skeleton in the animatronic and then you're going towards him and all of a sudden like he just turns
Into a full-on Johnny Depp animatronic and it's similar to that. What I've the Beauty and the Beast
Japan effect where you're just like I don't know
Now I've said this before any every time like we dig into like hey, what was that? It's like that's like a pepper's ghost
It's all the same thing. Oh, it's mirrors. Yeah, but I don't know
I still don't really know exactly how it is because it does just look like things are disappearing
But yeah, those those are pretty amazing. I assume we'll get
Some version of that in the next round of rides out here. I'm assuming something will use of them disappearing thing
I don't know which one I would hope so. I I'm hoping that that Pandora boat ride is the Shanghai Pirates
Where do you think that's going? Oh, he's got a theory Hollywood back lot
That's
What I think and I took me a while to come around to the idea of it the monorail goes right there
So I'm like how it seems you'd go under it
Well, the thing is they're gonna take over that those bus lanes
So it's gonna like they're gonna have to transfer those bus lanes to where they're gonna have to build
They want to build a parking lot across the street and they want to so this is gonna take forever
We're not gonna get this until you that well they claimed five years
But five years ago they were talking about the garage the gateway
Well, but that was when I had an unfavorable City Council. Oh, right now the City Council will do whatever they want. So we're good
We're back to good
Rubber stamp everything but yeah, yeah, I that's I assume it is going Hollywood and then the cocoa was going behind
The coaster or yeah, I'm assuming in that like facade area back there
Yeah, I think that's the best place to put it like there's not much going on in that area
It's kind of sad because it's our on our first date. We our first ride was Monsters Inc
So we're gonna lose that Disneyland history because it was the limo ride before that
Was your first date at Disneyland
Yes, we actually met at Star Wars celebration
We hung out at Star Wars celebration and then once that was which is like a Star Wars
Convention and then once I was over we walked to Disneyland and we went to DCA and we got margaritas at Rita's margaritas
And then we went on whatever had the shortest line, which was Monsters Inc at the time
Yeah, and yeah, that's very sweet. I was like, hold on. Did you own a first date?
Were you like guaranteed three hours in a car 90 minutes each way?
Yeah, it's just like so what is what what do you like on your pizza?
So no, that's very sweet, yeah, I that's always nice story of a first date
We're like go to a second location, you know, what is what year was that celebrate Star Wars celebration 2015 2015? Yeah
Okay, we walked over to the Captain EO theater and we saw a preview for the movie Tomorrowland. Yeah
After
And it had like the song from carousel of progress in it so that's like our song
Did you guys did you guys follow the optimist at all? No, or you did. Yeah. Yeah, I have like a
PDF that's like a 30 or 40 page
Explainer of the storyline of the optimist
Because I was kind of following it as it was happening and then just online I'd see it like
Oh, if you've gone to Chili John's today, Bob Gurr was hanging
It's like I was right down the road. Mm-hmm. You didn't make it though. I didn't make it. No, I didn't really
Play along I was just kind of following you guys should do an episode on the optimist
Like I know on that like that's the whole thing. Yeah. Yeah, that was a cool
I mean I didn't get to I kind of followed it from afar like you did
Yeah, but I heard some of the stuff they did and it was crazy because they were and there was a literal
JJ style mystery box. Mm-hmm that they're likely found this box in the archives
And this was all like hype months hyping up Tomorrowland
yes, and then I feel like
All of the mystery that was like laid out was not in the movie
There was it was almost unrelated to all of this like because it really felt like oh wow
Tomorrowland is gonna be for the nerds or at least it's gonna have the treats in there for the nerds
Well, I had also submitted what happened
Like through one of the casting websites. They were looking for extras to just ride
Space mountain and or no ride the Matterhorn like for hours and I was like, yeah, I want to do that
Oh, that's and then there is probably
In her second shot in the movie. Yeah, my back would be destroyed
That is anyone has any vlogger done a Matterhorn challenge how many times you can ride the Matterhorn in one day
I'll stop see if before your neck goes
That's a good look that's a maybe if we start a vlog that'll be my first video is like
How many times can I ride the Matterhorn before I tap out twice? Yeah
Steel spine Carlson doing the challenge. I feel like a lot of people I know have declared
They'll never do the Matterhorn again. And now I'm out there. I'll do it. There's a trick. We have a trick
First of all, you need to go on the fantasyland side
Yes, the right side that one isn't as violent
Okay, okay
And then when you sit in the bobsled and you can easily remember that because it's the right side not the wrong side
Okay. Sure. No, it's a good way to remember
yeah, when you get into the bobsled you want to
Grab the seat in front of you and kind of like prop your back off of your own seat
And you just ride the entire ride like that and you will not it doesn't really yeah, it makes it so enjoyable
Wait, okay. So if you're holding on the seat in front of you, does that mean you should hopefully know the person in front of you?
Unless you're in the very front so you like kind of just have to prop your back off of the yeah
But it is a game changer
What if you like grab the skull of the person in front of you?
Just hold their cheeks, but I feel like once once we learn that secret now anyone like even if they don't want my advice
I'm like you gotta do that when you do the Matterhorn
We learned it from a VIP tour guide and ever since I've learned that like it makes the Matterhorn so much about how this is
This is game-changing news. Yeah, I'm glad this is this is not a horn fun
Dude, did you during that date whether any other tips that the VIP guide gave?
About like riding rides or anything right now or that was the only
Mickey's and so the guy yeah, did you have you how I don't know how often you do a VP
Did one VIP guide VIP guide once and I tried to get in the Matterhorn with the basketball court
But they said there's no way you can do that. That's not I actually got walked off the Matterhorn once and I got to see the
Told me this I mean, it's literally just it's not what you think
It's like
Peter still threw a souvenir sipper at the wall
I ended it out the noise of it hitting the wall like the one cool ride that I've gotten walked off of well
That is that is a big deal though, but yeah, but at that they also explained to me like look
It's not yeah a court like it's usually picturing like an NBA court up there a little hoop in them, right?
Yeah, but it's like danger. I was described like it's dangerous
trap, but
They didn't have phones to occupy themselves
Did you do that? Have you been go if you go into the bathroom in the secret star tours bathroom for employees?
Cuz I got to do that, but I did do is the secret
Runaway railway bathroom, which is very boring. Oh
The queue for runaway well at railway and then it's not public
But we were on the VIP tour and I had to go the bathroom and then you just go into this very boring hallway
And it's like just I was expecting more
Interesting wow, they probably don't want people like I want to get I want to see if I can get in this secret
Bathrooms, I bet they all have one they I'm sure they do. Yeah, but I and the bathrooms are at least those star tours one
Unremarkable. Yeah, nothing special about it
But the idea of going to it is so interesting and fun to me
No, I want to go to the bathroom and all the secret bathrooms. I always I mean, it's not super challenge
Secret anymore, but if I go to Tiki room, I always go to the single occupancy
That's a good one because there's still like I feel like vintage fixtures
Well, they change those bad
But they're both family bathrooms now
I believe there used to be like there used to be like urinal men's bathroom and now I believe they're two
Family bathrooms because I went in there to try to change a toddler
They did not have the proper table and I had to go to the much more crowded bathroom across the way and that was a
Crazy
Yeah, I should have gone over to that
We need to do an episode about the baby changing area on Main Street because that is it's it's fairly efficient
But it's interesting. I don't know if you've been in this now
This is you know, this is the perk of having a child is that you can now go in certain places that you couldn't before
So my wife has gone into the place where you can nurse now at Disneyland
So she needs to come out and talk about that
So we got to talk about all the different places
But it is like a weird assembly line where you're waiting in line with probably a bunch of children that have a big shit in
their diaper
And there's a line of parents holding their kid or their kids like whatever and you're just waiting for these little
Stations to open up and they're big. There's a couple people in there almost like you're you know
Collecting your meal at a McDonald's like a wave over in here and then you go and you go and then you go into these little
Stations and then you're right by
Yeah, it's right on it's it's by I'm trying to think it's it's what's that the last
Store on Main Street on the right if you're looking at the castle
Yeah, it's like right next to there and that is where you go to change your child and there's so many people in there
But it is themed and there's like little TVs and there's like a little area for kids to run around
But I'm like in the middle of like, oh god, we gotta change this ever. She's having a fit
I'm still like the theming in here is nice
It's really good to be like things for some enrichment activities to tire myself out there. Yes
So I love the idea that there's this list of things that
Getting having a child on walks like the yeah petrodon flyers at the island's adventure
Yes, except what he's really fun what he really wants to do and he said this before is there's these events right which
Events and now
You guys ever been to one? No, no and that you were talking about what a great guy neat
Page of his tomorrow is he almost
Obviously, I would have had to change plane tickets and get a longer hotel stay and deal with you know a pet hotel
But he's like, oh shoot. Just stay a few more days come to the Orlando and former event. I'm like, oh
You almost got me
We're gonna get you on tarot on flyers. That is where you can do tear down flyers without a child, right?
Yeah, I will say we've only done one Orlando and former event it was amazing totally recommend
But for some reason that ride wasn't open like maybe it was down for
Here like there was yeah
I was like, this is my chance. It wasn't working. Right? Yeah, cuz I tried in like
1999 or
2000 and it was the longest wait in the park I think and
My parents were just like do you really wouldn't do this like man, wouldn't you rather do spider-man like yeah
Yeah
Well, we're good. We'll get you on it
I don't know could we maybe like maybe you have an inside person that can like sneak you on or something
Well, if you get me a big lolly
Well, we can dress you like a child. Yeah
What do you mean get you one you have one hanging in your closet at home? Yeah, I know and it's getting everywhere
You guys need to go to the Orlando and former event
Like it is literally walk up to any ride except for a great grids
Maybe it's like five-minute wait there. It's amazing and every food place just has free food
It's crazy. You go up to the food places and they they bring you out
But you don't pay anything and you see the total on the cash register
Oh, it's a hundred thousand dollars that it's gone through of like
That always fascinates me that like yeah and unlimited bread pudding
So yeah, it's a miracle. I've been there already. I was gonna say you could get like so you could have unlimited food at the Fantastic Four cafe
Yeah, basically. Oh, how are you not been there?
I know and just like you were just ordering a thousand dollars worth of bread
Seems you get to have access to this secret walkway between the parks because they connect the parks
Yeah, really? I didn't realize this. Yeah, so is that where the train goes the Hogwarts Express?
No, it's closer to Nickelodeon. Yeah
Up in the front
I mean, it's kind of like the same area that if you're an age of ten like those mazes are kind of right
I don't know. Yeah, maybe okay, you can see the impact zone
The old sound stages where they get rest where professional wrestling took place. Yeah. Wow. All right
Well, did they do these?
Our friend Ryan for the love of theme parks just recently did this episode of his he does these documentaries on YouTube and he did it
About wrestling
I
Yeah, I should watch that. It's very very comprehensive, but also frustrating because WWE
doesn't allow a
Even a second of footage to be all right. It's like all like still photos. I had to be very creative. Yeah
You did a good job. Yeah, like you have a WCW tapings at the entrance of MGM studio. What a time
It was just chaos. I didn't remember it. There was like people on top of like where the sign
Yes
Jim studios and jumping off there and stuff
People were freaked out cuz they had an ambulance like oh, he's getting stretchered out an ambulance, but it's like I
Think what was it? They used an actual Reedy Creek ambulance. So everyone's just freaked out
Yeah, we have we have a couple we owe a couple of wrestling
I've been like Jay Leno's wrestling career episode has to happen in the next year or so what Jay Leno had a match in
WCW and they ran an angle on the tonight show. Oh my god, and Jay wrestled and Kevin Eubanks his bandleader got involved
Kevin looked jacked too and Kevin looked like he was like the wrestling fan like Kevin knew what he was doing
And I was begging our friend Matt Cardona because he makes wrestling figures
I go people want Jay and Kevin and he said okay, I would make it J and I go no no no no
Jay and Kevin and he goes all right fine
And I go if you can figure out he goes if you can get the likeness if you can get Jay to sign off and Kevin
To sign off I will do it because it's not like you just got to show up at Bob's big boys every
Well, this is why the way we went there with my dad when he was in town like not thinking that he would be there
And he shows up every there
He is ever I haven't seen him a little bit, but Scott has seen Jay a couple times in the last few months
I feel like in Burbank
Yeah, so I if we can get to the big dog garage
I feel like part of it is just us doing an interview with Jay and then getting him to sign a contract to allow
Matt to make a wrestling figure of him and Kevin
And I guess we had to find Kevin too then but that is I do I want that's like my most wanted
Figures one of my most wanted figures is Jay. Do they have a figure of David Arquette?
No, I don't know. I think they do. I think he I think he may have matted may be made one, but I think yes that happened
But he yeah, he has made some more obscure things and then sometimes also I'll be like, you know Regis Philbin did a lot of
WrestleMania's and he's like no, but nobody wants like a no. No, they do. Yes. I want it. My friends want it
We need a Regis figure, please and then usually he just blows me off
But he's wrong. He's wrong about what people want
Let's talk about the Disney treasure you just how long ago you just got back from this pretty recently
Yeah, we went in January January. Yeah, okay. That is recent. Yeah
How long would you guys say the you know doing this thing to make a video about it is
On average, you mean where it comes out? Yeah when it comes out
Oh filming and then how quickly we get out? Yeah uploaded does it depend on the I think it's a it depends on
What we're filming like so for Halloween hard nights, I'll stay up all night and try to get out as quick as possible
Yeah
With the Disney treasure, we weren't like on the maiden voyage or anything. So we didn't feel that
pressure of like trying to get it out super quick, right so
Usually I think it depends but like it usually takes me a few days to edit and
We're kind of scaling back this year and only posting one video a week
Unless it's like very topical or something. Yeah, but
That those I got out I think like a week after so we also usually don't edit while we're there
So like if we're on a cruise or we're in Japan, we're not yeah gonna waste the time
They're editing right till we get home. Yeah, it just depends on the situation, but I'll never stress myself out like trying to
Except for Halloween horror nights. That's the one that all that I'll stay up all night for that one's interesting too
It's like Orlando you get one day one media day to film in the houses the rest of the time you can
Yeah, but out here
And like at a horror night see is that I would just as I was getting ready for bed turn on the live stream
And every night someone was in houses. Yeah
Yeah, I would hear you'll be in line with someone like a live streamer with like their their flash on
Yeah, there's somebody in front of us who was like a live stream or something
They literally had their flash on the entire time and nobody said anything. They didn't get in trouble
I was dangerous for the actor and I'm like, that's so rude. Like I don't know because it's blasting light in their eye. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I'm trying to think I guess I don't know if that's happened
But it does feel like there's just a steady stream of people that something like that would be like
It would be more annoying if you were like in a little small group to like I'm sure it's annoying
but it's also just like like there's just sometimes you're in those houses and I'm like there's a
Hard line of 25 people that are going through each like show scene to where I'm like
Which by the way is good for me who's still a little scared. Yeah, but I understand
It's like making the experience less good
So I'm conflicted about that because any time I've ever been there and like and just because of the way the line is
The flow is controlled. I end up being like the first part of the line
It's a little scary still we went to in
Orlando there was what was it called? It was like the night before opening night
It was like a premium of ticketed event. Oh, right, right, right and it was empty. No one bought take nobody was there
It was amazing because like I would definitely do it again, but I don't think they're gonna do it again
I think it's because they announced this way after so everybody already bought their opening night tickets and so again
They're like we're not gonna spend twice as much, right?
But like every house was like you were in it alone. So I don't know that would be scary for you or it was like
It's one of those were like I know that's like I would do it and I know it's good
But I would still be a little bit like yeah, I will say the cool thing about that
I'm usually in your boat Mike where I like having
The Congo line because they kind of write and see stuff coming and it's not as scary
But the cool thing with this is you got to see every single scare and scene and like a fact
Yeah, right, right
Yeah walking in that alone that preview night to food was included
Yeah food was included so it's a really good value and I don't think I think they lost money because nobody bought tickets
So I don't I don't anticipate them ever doing that again, which is such a shame. I thought it was totally worth it
Yeah, we'll see. I mean though. I was gonna say the rumor
Hopefully Scott has at least said he's gonna do some Halloween stuff for the first time this year
The only one that hasn't right? Well Jason also has not
Jason Scott are both scaredy-cats and I am a little less of a scaredy-cat. Let's just put it that way. That's my big brag
A little less of a scary kid. I said I would do it, but you have oh, yes
Push my ass in a wheel. I'll push your ass in a wheelchair
You can't nail a scare act you can't freak out and push me into a scare after
I'll push you but there's no guarantee of what I'm gonna do when I get scared. Okay
Well, just pushes you in the front and runs other way
I think that would be less scary for you because they're looking for like the normal height of people
They're not I can't cover my eyes. Yeah, like put a blanket over your head
Yeah, like I may accidentally will you into that giant pile of fake shit at the Six Flags Fear Fest
souls
Accidentally because I get scared by a scare actor. So we'll see I'll do my best to not be scared. That's
Solely BPA plastic all the BPA that they removed from plastic they put in the sewer of soul shit
Yeah, yeah, have you done sewer of souls at Six Flags Fear Fest? No, we've never done Fright Fest. Oh, wow, really?
Okay. We were thinking about doing it last year, but we just
Never got around to it. I think it's worth it. They're doing a lot more IP whether that's a good thing or bad thing
I don't know. Yeah, but it seems interesting. It was very intriguing
Maybe this will be the year that we'll finally do it. We could all go in the sewer of souls together if you want if we
Want to go on opening nights?
Hopefully this year we do it everybody does it so everybody will get
to walk the like
50 miles that you end up walking when you go to Six Flags
Because of how it spread out the park is and how confusing the layout is still to this day to me
But let's go back to Disney treasure. So how many how many different crew that Disney cruises have you been on?
Good question. I know that I am a gold level. So how many is that? That sounds impressive. That's at least five. Wow, okay
It's under 10. I don't know what the
Number is but like we've been on every Disney ship except for the dream. Yeah, okay right now currently there's how many six?
Yeah, we've been on at least five of them. Okay, and they're all in the Disney like those 15 Disney approved words
So the treasure the dream
The is there a wish there's the wish there's the way
fantasy
Magic and the wonder magic. Okay, we don't have believe yet. So maybe believe might be like
This year they're coming out with the destiny and the adventure destiny feels like a new one
Yeah, as far as Disney approved words. Yeah, so that's interesting
Okay, the weird thing with destiny is there's no Star Wars on the ship and you think like I know you're recently down on Star Wars
But I feel like out of all their properties destiny when I think destiny I think like
You know the hero's journey
Skywalker saga sure. Yeah, that makes sense and there's Star Wars like do they have most of the
IP on all the ships like there's always like a little Marvel something a little Star Wars something like the newer ships
Yes, the older ships are more like nautical themed. So not as themed the four legacy ships
the older ships were kind of made during like
the Michael Eisner times the glory days
According to
Yeah, do you remember the big red boat I've seen YouTube documentaries of a vibe don't remember I it was just I think they
subcontracted with a
Cruise company
I only know
Remember it because of the commercials on vacation planning VHS is or parades and stuff
But it's interesting because you go on the older Disney ships and it feels very Michael Eisner in that
He was kind of almost like
Embarrassed to have like Mickey and friend like, you know, I mean like yeah. Yeah, like when he opened DCA
There's no Mickey and friends right Kingdom. No Mickey and friend like so like the lobbies this it feels like the Golden Age of
Cruising but it doesn't feel Disney in any way. There's like some carvings of Mickey like, you know, look subtle
Yeah, right. So I mean that's what he was into and I I think those earlier boats were less
Themed than the new boats and that's why I like the new boats. They're like, they're really themed out
There's tons of IP all over the place and the adventure like so the new boats are the wish and the adventure
The wish came out like right at the end of the pen measure. You mean or sorry wish in the treasure
Why keep on say it's weird because the theme of the treasurer's adventure is very adventure
And there's all these adventure shows adventure land theming and they should have called that the adventure
I think and the theme of the wish is kind of like fairy tale
Magic. Okay. Yeah princess. That's it. That's confusing
but also
Aladdin is on the treasure. Not the one that is called wish which is but
The theme of treasure wishing
But the cool thing about the treasure I think that you guys I know
Nobody in the podcast the ride group has been on dizzying. No, I know this is one of the areas where we have not
Indulged or experienced in which I just there's a we were both we met like strangers the other day not strangers
I guess they weren't my neighbors of yours
But they were like, hey, we just wanted a Disney Cruise
You got to do it a giant Disney Cruise bag. Yeah, yeah, and we were like, oh do you like and they're like, oh, we love it
Right. It's awesome. And this was change your life. Yeah. Yeah, and this was just they didn't know like they didn't know who we were
They just were giving us advice like as a human to another human, but the reason why I think you'd like the treasure
Most is it's the it is a cruise ship made for theme park fans, right?
Because it has spaces based on Haunted Mansion based on
Jungle Cruise based on 20,000 Leagues Under Sea. Yeah
Yeah, so it's like that that is yeah enticing to me more so now it's hard because I want to hand the old boats
Are touched by Michael Eisner who's never never made a mistake in his life
So I have to like his decisions there, but what you're describing is more what I want from my Disney experience
Yeah, and some purists like those boats more because they're more
Luxury more less like in-your-face Disney, but I kind of want the in-your-face Disney
I don't want to go stay at a Disney hotel and not see
Yeah, right, like I want Mickey to tuck me in. Yeah, I want like that
Knott's Berry farm thing were like the elves elves tuck you in or what?
Did you say?
No, not Elvis. That's a Vegas is our Vegas service where Elvis tucks you. I'm sure
On the Disney Cruise doesn't Mickey call you before you're bored. You're sailing. Yeah, I think so
We did that like my very first Disney Cruise
I don't know why we've never done it since but you could have like an automated call will happen to you like a
week or something before your cruise and it's like maybe like
Get excited to come on the crew like which is very magical. Don't forget to check maritime law
Does Mickey have a wake-up call though with the resorts to like is Mickey the one who makes a wake-up call to you with?
Or he does that's right for a while. You could request right you would like your birthday or something
I'll call well now you could just go like do you want to wake a call from Mickey Goofy or Woody?
Oh, so you choose the character you could choose the character. Yeah, okay, but goofy would forget to call you sometimes probably
Like five days later, I totally forgot I set my alarm for 9 p.m. Not 9 a.m. I'm sorry
I have time blindness. I can't tell time anymore
Yeah, that's fun. I mean I want I want a lot of that. I really the number one thing
I want is Mickey in a full
Captain stooping loveboat outfit and an impeccable white
Sailor type suit captain suit and that's what they the newer ones for sure have that
He has a nice little sailor suit on does he have
Wait whatever you would call it does are there multiple outfits that Mickey has on the boats
Do you do you see him in multiple outfits over the course of the weekend? Okay, so there's a pirate's night
He'll dress up as a poet. Okay, there's like a formal night if you do one of the longer cruises
He'll dress up in a tuxedo. Whoo. I love tuxedo
He's got his he's got his classic like sailor outfit or outfit. Is there another if you go on an Alaskan cruise?
Yes, he wears like a little
Parka I guess yeah, right Eskimo outfit. I don't know right, right
Okay, cuz that's that's good to know because I do want costume changes for Mickey
Oh, yeah
And then on the island the private islands that you go to which is like why we love Disney cruising so much
He'll wear like his little board shorts and his
special outfits
Yeah, I we we have we done. I mean we talk about Mickey's special outfits a lot on the show
But I do we should try to do a conference
Yeah, what's your favorite?
Decades of special outfits if you ever do an episode on special outfits, you need to get Disney Dan
I'm not sure if you've ever seen his YouTube channel
Yeah, literally just does the costumes of Disney and he's right so great out
He may maybe he already has like a Google document of all the special outfits is a wiki
Yeah, yeah, cuz it would be I there's so much stuff like that that I wish there was a comprehensive list of like
Here's every outfit Mickey wore in 1985
Like and I just a picture of all of it. I know one took that good a record
So I'm sure there's clothes that he wore that just like there's no picture of it. We don't know
like what did he yeah, like what did he wear at
the what is the
State Fair like do we know all the outfits Mickey wore at State Fair the limited time event 30 years ago
I don't think we do but somebody I wish there's like Polaroids in a box
Yeah, East Berlin Mickey the wall just fell and he finally got Levi's
In East Berlin Mickey, yeah, that would be good
So all the characters are like the main five or six also are both are all on the boat
Yeah, and do they all have the wardrobe changes like they all kind of dress similarly. Okay, that's that's good
That's again. This is a good check in the right
Characters, I would say a Disney Cruise is the best place to meet them because they're very easy to meet
They're always around and the lines are usually pretty short
Okay, and do they have like
You can't meet Star Wars characters or do is a chewy on the boat aren't some of these boats
They used to have a Star Wars day at sea
We're like the characters would be around on the new ships like on the treasure
They have a Star Wars area in the kids club. Okay, which you could go as an adult without children
You could go into special times. They'll allow everyone to go in right and they had stormtroopers
They're chewy in Ray. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, so they're not just wandering which is a shame
I wish chewy was just but I think that's why our outfit on and was walking around
Yeah
But I think that's one thing a lot of people that wonder that have never been on Disney Cruise like why would I want to?
Go on a cruise with all the you know, there's tons of children right whatever a lot of the children
Just go to the kids club. Okay, and I think that's the pro tip for a parent
Right is literally you can drop the kids off in the kids club and then go have your own fun
You can park them there basically and they they love it. So yeah, like there's an area of that
That's an imagineering and they can like design rides. Oh, that's cool looks really cool
Yeah, can an adult also design a ride if they wanted to or is that only kids?
But they do have open houses. Yeah, but yes, I'm the right you could just look at the little station
That is a mistake though, because I would like to design a ride
Am I the only one who has been on a cruise period? Okay, so has my family
went on a cruise in like
New York to like Bermuda
Which is of course a fun vacation island in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean
There's a triangle there, huh? Well, I was you don't have to tell me twice about the triangle I was
So scared going I was a nervous child. I was an anxious child was terrified the Bermuda Triangle and
And
1997 there's Titanic stuff everywhere. There's documentaries on TV
there's kids books about like what happened at the Titanic and of course the
You know hit movie and I was so scared and for whatever reason no adult took me aside to go like
Listen to me. There's no icebergs
Don't have to worry about this the ship is not going to sink
Because of that
but yeah, it was a
Lot of yeah, we were put at the kids club a lot
We certainly had days at the pool and like we all got packed together for like breakfast and
Dinner and I was like the age where you got the the stamp on your badge
Like is everyone wore names tags or whatever I could wander the ship myself
My brother was just a little too young to do that and he was very mad that I could do that
But there I mean there there is
There's a lot more stuff on cruise ship nowadays for sure. I mean we ate dinner
I think at the same place every night. We always had the same
Waiter I know this has
Rotational dining do they call it where yeah, you do different restaurants with the waitstaff comes with you
So you see the same people?
But I my big memory of
That cruise were midnight buffets
Yeah, that's not a thing anymore
Yeah
There's also no casinos on
Yeah, okay, there's some sort of gambling I could read the table on that
You mean you would win you could do good. Yeah hustle people at bingo
We had a friend that won she won like the big jackpot
The big jackpot yeah
Yeah, that's the soft like preparing everyone for the gambling
Peter you want a bunch at a slot machine on the cruise ship
Oh, yeah
Royal Caribbean, yeah, they have a fun casino on their ships. Yeah, I won. How much did I end up winning like 6,000? No
Like 4,000 maybe still a lot
Like you rock up points in the casino
points, yeah, thank God
Though so they'll offer you like free cruises and you get like free drink depending on what level you are
They want their money back. Yeah
Yeah, I don't I think works I think Disney will have slot machines in
Say 10 within 10 years
I was really hoping the one in Singapore was gonna have a casino because it was
They've bought a ship off of somebody and I think they're originally was supposed to be a casino in it, right?
But they wiped it and now
Mm-hmm. Yeah, will there be let's let's all do we think within 10 years?
There'll be like a slot machine on Disney property. Well, they're getting into sports batting
SPN and there'll be like laws especially the laws in this country will be a little looser and going forward in the next few years
so I feel like I feel like everyone's gonna have a gambling addiction in the country and there will be like you will be able to like
Play a slot machine while you're on Pirates of the Caribbean
Play virtual blackjack on parts three fun
I mean, I want to I don't smoke cigarettes
But I'd love to smoke a cigarette on Pirates of the Caribbean and I would love to play blackjack while I'm on Pirates of the Caribbean
So I see that happening once if at least if there's just like a blackjack night at Disneyland where every ride has a blackjack dealer
It'd be something, you know Tiki room you're watching the show and you're playing blackjack or something
You could see that you can move out a couple benches doesn't seem like too hard
Yeah, right right now
I know Disney doesn't allow like the IP of their properties to be on some machines
But like when star before Star Wars was bought by Disney they had Star Wars. Oh, right. Yeah
I remember once they bought it like they were like no, right? Yeah, right. They all disappeared
Yeah, well, it's something like I'm not saying that's a bad thing that disappeared with that
but the other thing like I feel like I feel like alien and predator like I could see a slot machine being alien and
Disney owns them but like the slot machine the slot machines are wild though. Now, it's like there's a Whitney Houston slot
Oh, yeah, I'm like, okay
So like it's interesting like what just gets because those screens are now digital so you can like sub out
properties or pop stars, I guess so it's very like
You can see the Whitney and then you can see a hot stuff a little devil slot machine
Like they're next to each other and you're like, well, this seems very random
But ultimately, I don't know I don't know if it's a good thing that like Mickey isn't on a slot machine
I guess it's probably a good
Someone make a steamboat welly slot machine now, that's true technically. Yes
Yeah, no, I think for sure but it would have yeah, you just have to be wearing the right outfit
Yeah, I want a bunch of money on the riverboat mouse machine
Or yeah, I guess you could like Popeye's I mean
I'm sure there was a Popeye slot machine, but that's public domain
Now have you started production on your Popeye movie now that it's public domain
Hi, you know, we're still trying to beat out the script, you know, there's still where you play all the role cooks in the kitchen
It's mostly a story about wimpy
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, but it's yeah Steve's Allianz. Like yeah, you got to get Popeye in there. I'm like Steve. Let it go. Let it go
So there there is you said, okay, there's jungle cruise stuff. There's
What would I'm completely blinded mention?
Which is the best thing ever crazy that seems like the thing
Yeah, and that seems people keep on saying that's like why don't they build that in the parks?
And I'll tell you why they don't build it because no one would ever leave. It's like right
Yes, it's too
It's too enticing like they would have to do the I mean
They're still pretty aggressive about getting you out of the Cantina and Star Wars land
Yeah
But I do feel like people would really settle in a little more and if they built it exactly the way it seems to look
Like on them or from what I've seen
But I guess yeah, you could
It wouldn't be like are there I feel like part of the Cantina stuff is like standing makes you
Like want to get out of there faster
I know there's booths obviously too but like the last time I was in there
It's like here stand by these 12 people and you only can have 30 to 45 minutes in here
You got to get out of here to even the booths are awkward too. Yeah random people
Yeah, as long if you're not with a big party you get put with other families and it's like right
But I still don't understand why they why there aren't like seven of those rooms
They're all slightly themed differently and then get people to sort of settle in and then you can still put a time limit on it
Yeah, but it does seem like you would sell a lot more drinks and food. I know you don't want people getting hammered
At Disney, but it'd be hard to get hammered on those they're very light
yeah, but you would at least your lips would get very tingling if you did the
Fuzzy tauntaun, which I do which I did
I say this on the show that I took a big bite of the fuzzy tauntaun like six my did say this right right took
A big bite of the foam that has all the copper nose. It went up my nose and I started coughing
It was so embarrassed. I like lost I was like lost it
Like it went in my nose
I did not realize that it would have that effect and it took me like five minutes to recover
And again, you're it's close quarters in there and there is just I couldn't like go and hide anywhere
I just had to like kind of bury my head and like get down toward the ground
So I could recover from having whatever that is that's in that foam. They're the most sanitary thing
I know it's gonna sound awkward if you could go cough on Rex
This cough toward Rex people yeah, and if and they're like you can go outside and cough, but you can't get back in
The rules here
But yeah, I know that like it feels like every ride that people like should have its own version of this
yes, like and I've we've talked about this many times I think on the show where it's like I want like a
Saloon that overlooks Big Thunder
I know there's no room especially at Disneyland for that
If for some reason you could maybe I guess maybe you could get rid of the quick service right there and build something that's kind
of elevated
but it does feel like
The next logical step of being a theme park weirdo is I just want to sit and watch the rides
Like I don't believe yeah, I like the ride fine
But what I'd like even more is to sit and watch the ride
Comfortable position for whatever reason that's that's part of it
So yeah, so when you see stuff on the crew, you're like, why isn't this thing?
Why can't I just sit in the Haunted Mansion when I go to Disneyland's?
Why is this like and they're building what the Pirates there's building a Pirates bar in Florida?
Yeah, so it's cool. They're doing that type of thing. But then there was a rumor there
We're gonna build the tip-top club like permanent in
Florida for the Tower of Terror, but they'd be awesome to that
But yeah, I don't know I I wonder if it's what you're saying and it's like people will not leave
You will have to kick them out of here
Yeah
They will be like there'll be claw marks on the carpet from people being dragged by security because they will not leave
I mean, I think that's right, but in your videos you guys were saying like yeah
You just walked into the Haunted Mansion park. Yeah, we got lucky
It was we always managed to go in there when it was a good time and get a seat
Well, I do is it like a reservation serve like system or you have to wait in a regular line if it's
Yeah, you just go in but when the wish there's a Star Wars bar, which is not as cool as a Haunted Mansion bar
Yeah
But I think for the first few months of that like you had to like get a reservation and do all didn't you?
Yeah, yeah, I know it's like very hard to get in this one
We were kind of worried about that, but you just were able to walk in
Mm-hmm. And is this the best of all like the themed bar restaurant areas on any of the ships? Okay
It's so cool in the middle of the bar. There's this
Aquarium that has designs from Holy Crump and it looks amazing. I saw a picture of this. Yes has ghost fish in it
Yeah ghost fish. They'll sing during like the song one while the songs are playing and stuff
So there's some of like didn't they just it's like some of his like sketches
They didn't use like the Museum of the Weird Stuff that they didn't use and they've put it in here
Which is nice because sometimes you're like I'm worried like that. They've like fired everyone who knows history
Do do you think one of the cruise ships should have a big doll garage themed?
With Jay and everything I think so maybe not Disney one. Well, Jay was in Superstar Luma, right?
Yes, oh yeah, well with it will there be a Tron bar on one of these if this next Tron is a hits
How many more times will they try with Tron? Ah the first drawn that's a hit
2060 Tron bar would be cool. But a Tron bar would be cool. Yeah, cuz the aesthetic I
Again, we're fans of the aesthetic of Tron
We like the aesthetic of Tron a lot and like that it's around but it is interesting that we have this year
It's another Tron try they're doing it right. I think so the Leto Tron. Oh, yeah
legacy legacy areas
Okay, okay, uh-huh. Yeah
What so the honey mansion bar I
Did think it was very funny when you you guys were spotlighting the like different soda
they have like cream soda lemonade soda and
Some of them they're like mixed with a cocktail and it's like I poured the wrong. So yeah, that was
One of the drinks depends on you pouring the the sodas into it and the bartender told me he put
You know one in front of one one in front of the other so it was his fault
But so I did it that way. I'm not blaming him
But it was usually awesome
So we had to actually buy that drink twice and I thought like oh maybe they'll comp us for the first one
So we didn't drink it
No, we had to pay for it twice even though it was his fault that I poured the wrong soda in the wrong cocktail
But yeah now there is that was interesting. I mean
Most your food is included on the cruise
but there are upcharges of like if you want to go to the
Fancy steakhouse or the bar. Can you buy a drink pass on the Disney not on Disney? No on the Royal?
Yeah, I've recently done some surveys suggesting that maybe Disney's considering a drink package
Okay, so what would that entail like that would just be like on an open bar essentially for you
Once you pay one rail you pay the price changes depending on how much does it run like?
We did the math one time to figure out how many drinks we should be drinking to get our money's worth
Five or six a day to make your money's worth, uh-huh, and if we drink four
I'm like, I have to have one more I gotta do it our money is worth. Yeah, but so
That I don't know if they did it they would make so much more money. I think right probably
Yeah, did you see I mean, I guess there's a lot of families on these cruises
But like did anyone get they have to be like cut off. Is there a they go to Disney jail on the boat
There has to I mean every boat is a jail. Yeah, I assume. Yeah. Yeah, they have to have a break
Yeah, break the break right the break. I've never seen it on a Disney cruise that I have noticed
Royal people get a little you could tell people are like party. I'm royal sometimes right
I assume that Star Trek cruise that we talked about that that's that which is maybe the number one cruise
I want to go on and the Star Trek cruise
Yeah, I have to imagine that a couple people end up in the brig and they get excited because brig is
So they hope it's like a themed experience, which it's probably not
Are you guys excited for this for the Universal Fan Fest nights so excited for this for going on the Enterprise D
Which is from the Picard season 3 I am so and I I've sent an annoying email to
Universal Hollywood, but like I'm a Star Trek guy
Let me in let me see
And they're like, well, we're just figuring it out. I'm like, okay, but you don't know
I met Jonathan Franks and Burbank last year and I flipped out in a way that was maybe not smooth
I might say
So yes, I had that that specific like the back-to-future stuff. I know you went to a preview of yeah
Yes, which which looked cool and like the back-to-future like they're doing a whole recreation of the clocktower scene
Which looks very cool and I'm excited about that and just to remind it's it's all the stuff is on one night
Yeah, so it's it's a little confusing
Nights, I think they were just trying to do Halloween horror nights
Yeah, I know like yeah, it's all in one but you get Star Trek and back to the future and one piece
all that's right the casting I
Jane forwarded me the casting notices because she
And these were going around and it's very funny
Them trying to cast like
anime characters, all right, I
feel like there's gonna be a lot of a long line to meet Luffy from one piece as opposed to the the
ogre from
D&T
Or me in line to meet the like 30 year old playing Riker or something. Yeah
I'm a big fan of you're gonna have Yoshi. I'm excited for that. All right, Yoshi
Yes, all the creatures in the Wizarding World to which are not all of them
But a lot of them we got to see when we were in Japan because they just have them. Oh, okay
So it's cool that they're bringing it here
Yeah, one of my biggest regrets of not doing something in my life is that Star Trek experience that they had
I know me too, and I feel like this is gonna be the closest thing
Yes, and there is some cuz it you didn't the it's not built yet, right?
You didn't get to go in the enterprise or anything cuz like something had raised like a walkthrough and like somebody attacks
I assume Borg maybe they didn't say who okay
It seems like the Borg has to be the one and they also said you're gonna get to experience the being at the end of it
You're gonna get beamed out
Which is what they did in the Vegas one
Yeah, I may I may like weep a little bit going on the bridge of the enterprise and that's not a joke
That's just like that's that's what I guess other than like going the X-Men's mansion
It was like I wanted to live on the enterprise when I was a kid and this we'll see it
We'll see if it if it happens. I'm I I'll hide it in the moment if anyone's with me
But I will bring it up on the show if it happens the one thing that they showed us that they didn't release
Pictures of is for the Dungeons and Dragons thing. It's like oh, it's a walkthrough kind of like a Halloween Horror Nights house
Oh, that's cool. Yeah
The bad guy I don't know anything about D&D but the bad guy is like this
ball
creature thing
They had Jim Henson
Studio build this like puppets like oh really teen feet tall. It looks insane. That's great
Yeah, I mean this is a I hope this works because this feels like a great way to do just other non-scary stuff
Yeah, and to get at least like temporary walkthroughs because there's so much stuff
We like that's not quite like it doesn't make sense for a corporation to approve a budget for a 500 million dollar ride
It's unfair
But that's the reality
So at the very least if you can get little immersive things in these parks that have a good budget
You'll at least get some of it. Like I want to Ninja Turtles
I know there's Ninja Turtle rides
But maybe this is how you get a Ninja Turtle thing in a theme park at a pretty high level
Because it still seems like none of the movies nude or shows or whatever are popular enough for them to put again
$500 million into a turtles ride that it deserves
You keep walking through the Frankenstein parking garage at Universal Hollywood and going lays there any turtles Steph
Right left over from 1990 when they did that you did the walk through here, right?
But like going yet you can build a sewer and put some turtles and suits and I'll weep about that
I'll weep meeting Michelangelo. Like I weep when I met you just need to have a good cry Michael. Sure
Some stuff out. Oh, that's true. But it's help. It helps if it was a character
I liked when I was a kid, okay
It helps me to cry as I said on the episode with Matt Mazzani
It's interesting and this is my personal feeling maybe I think other people feel similarly
It's interesting being an adult because sometimes you need to have things like movies TV music or theme park experiences
Force you to cry like it needs to be extracted from you in some ways and I'm being serious like yeah
It's weird cuz you like all the time. Why am I tearing up at this?
There's so much misery in the world
that like it's just like I see it and I don't process it and then I like start crying because I see like data's console a
Recreation of it and you're like, what is this about? Oh, it's I needed to do this
It needed like yeah
It was just a functional thing my brain needed to do and it's looking for an opportunity to do it
What's very weird catcher? I feel like some scare actors got you pretty good less crying more screaming at some of those house
Expression too. They like to get me. It's so much fun though. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, my daughter loves to be scared already
She loves to like oh, it's interesting
We'll see if it lasts cuz like this stuff switches fast with kids
But like she likes like hiding and then you come in and like ah
Or she likes when I take the my leatherhead turtle figure and like oh, ah, she got like she jumps but like starts cackling
So like that's interesting too
Cuz like that's just like an early thing that people seem to like obviously she knows that it's her parents
And it's not actually a big alligator that's attacking her. But still it's interesting to see that
I always see people at HHM, especially in Hollywood with like their six-year-old or like
Yeah, there's strollers that they change at always make me laugh. You'll see that at Six Flags for sure
A lot of kids at Six Flags and yes
Some of them seem to enjoy it and then some of them are being punished by their parents
Some of them couldn't get a sitter for their kids and now they are going to suffer
Because of it or I guess maybe one parent waits with them outside
But we've all seen kids being forced onto a ride. They don't want to go on too. Oh, yeah, and that is
Weird that is something
It's right of passage just like you know, some of it is though. It depends
I've seen kids going please don't make me do this
Like it'll be fine and and then it's not fine like
Yeah, you have to know your kid since sometimes I feel like parents are just like I have whatever and then sometimes
It's like yeah, I know my kid will like this once they do it, which is
What happened to me at a certain point?
No, I was my mom held us off like doing anything for a while like I was too old by the time I did certain things
But yeah, yeah, it's interesting
School dance on Jeopard
Well, that's true. There's a lot of there's a long list of that of that type of thing
So crew like is there like I guess yeah, there's no midnight buffet on these cruises, but like is there
Like is it a wake up at 7 a.m. Go to bed at 10
Is that the sort of vibe of the ship basically or is it like everybody can do whatever they like?
Will you find people like roaming around at 3 a.m. I will say Disney cruise specifically. We've only ever done royal in Disney
Disney shuts down pretty
Pretty early, right? I feel like they shut down the food
They there are some like adult game shows and stuff you could go to or silent disco or whatever, right?
But uh, they have this thing on all the Disney cruise is called match your mate, which is kind of like
What is the the show that it's based on newly was like the newlywed game but like so like singles will go or no
sorry, like a new like newlyweds somebody who's been married forever and then somebody in between and
It's always like the highlight of the cruise
Out and then like they'll ask them questions like, you know
Describe your love life
It's funny because they do did its risque, but it's Disney. So they'll bring you like
Let's describe your love life and a Disney song. Is it?
Whole new world
Almost there under the sea. What was the other one?
Remember but it's so good first time in forever be prepared. Yeah
Fire yeah, yeah, that's it. Okay, that's interesting
I don't I have not seen a video of that cuz we we talked
What was this? What was the villain show called the weird Hollywood squares show? Yeah, that is weird
Yeah, and it's all pre-recorded like but people playing the villains. It's not like cartoon versions of the villains
There's like this is like a human being hostess. It's not one of the Disney characters, right? Yeah, it's a human being
Okay, almost like on the Disney treasure. They introduced this new show. There was an Indiana Jones
Themed choose wisely choose wisely like choose your own adventure and it was the highlight
By far. Yeah, so they have these new characters called coriander and stage and they're like improv actors
They've brought on to kind of be almost like your your host for the cruise and they do things every night
Yeah, but they're they're kind of like dressed up like they're from Agrabah or something
But they do a show one night in the adult area called Indiana Jones choose wisely in it
They reenact moments from Indiana Jones and the audience gets to choose what direction
Oh, they go in and like so it'll be like
The moment from last crusade and there's the the Holy Grail. There's a goofy cup and there's a
Sipper from 7-eleven and like the audience gets to choose what which one should he choose and like what happens and it's funny
because like sometimes they'll choose the right way and see what happens sometimes they'll choose the goofy cup and
Everything goes wrong and like they so like by applause. They'll choose. Yeah. Okay
It's so much fun and they have like references to you know, the ride from Disneyland or you know, it's
It's a lot of fun. So it's yeah, it's interactive, but then it's also for the Disney everything
Everything still has a little Disney in it
Yeah
That is interesting cuz I wonder if like that newlywed game is like did anybody ever say anything like crazy. Yes
Oh, that's that happened. Yes every single time we watch that show people will say the craziest things
And I'm just like and then you see them for the rest of the cruise
Could you give a like remember them do you remember one specifically? I mean you have to be you could you could clean it up
I suppose if you don't want to I don't have a good memory
I can't think of like a good one
but like one time they're like asking like
The most risky place you've ever like gotten it on and someone was like on the treasure or like like
Risky but like yeah
Earlier in our bedroom on the treasure and it's like why are you tell like right people go a little wild in front of the crowd
Probably yeah, and then that I'm sure that gets a good reaction though
I mean, that's not a risky one, but like risque one
Just say things near like what is they like feed them free drinks throughout the thing so they're feeling a little
Yeah loose, I guess that still feels like risky for anything related to Disney. So I give them credit for that
What do they win? Don't they you just win like a bottle of champagne or something at the end nothing like yeah
So you're not doing it for $10,000. You're doing it for a bottle of champagne
Yeah, trivia events throughout the day that will usually do and lose but like if you win that you just win like a medal
right, do you is there like
Like I'm guess I'm trying to say like are there things where now they've really expanded the the the theming
Is there like a plus-up that you're like now that you've you know, you're going to theme park so often
You're like I wish they could do this or like I know they can't build like a crazy big ride on it
They can do little things or like is there something you would be like if they only did this it would be the greatest
Cruise of all time. Do you have these feelings or I want a lazy river on a cruise? Oh, that's a great idea
Does any ship have it? I know there's these giant crazy new boats that look like they could do anything
But I know on the the new ship that's coming out of Singapore the new Disney ship the adventure
They're gonna have like a roller coaster on it. They're they actually have some like wrong. Yeah. Yeah, I've seen this
I don't remember what the other two rides are. I think they're like
Spinner rides or something, which I just think right so cool
I'm like why have they never done this before it's the the treasure has an attraction, right? It has the aqua mouse
Oh, which is a water coaster
Which is some screens in it and audio cues and yeah, and the aqua mouse is not the aqua duck
Similar but different. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, the aqua mouse that has like the little videos as you go up the conveyor belt and the aqua duck is just like a classic
Water coaster. Yeah. Yeah, very fun. I want a lazy river
I was gonna say like lazy river
I guess you would the way you would probably have to do it just on the top deck or
I guess not that's too heavy or something. Yeah
Yeah
Could I but like is there a way you could like have it be on the bottom of the boat and have it be like
translucent or something
It's like a glass bottom boat, right? So you could kind of see the ocean or a little bit. That's a great idea
I'm trying
Yeah, we're big lazy river fans on this show I feel Jason I want to speak for you, but I'm well
Yeah
So understated so I
Was winding up as if I was gonna go like I hate them
But you couldn't turn against your beloved lazy rivers favorite lazy river
I'm gonna say volcano Bay the fast moving reason. Oh
I'm the one who's done that and I who I guess so. That's a great question. I'm trying to think the
So Blizzard Beach lazy river is pretty good is my memory served as I'm correct aiming right?
There's some good theming. There's some pretty good to never done that
You guys need to go to a Lonnie is that yeah
I know we have you ever been to Atlantis in the Bahamas the Bahamas. No, they have this fast-moving lazy river that like
Many people get hurt every day
Like like was bleeding I don't think I ever would do it again it was that scary
They also a day the water slide that goes through the shark tank is that right? Okay, that was fun
And the the the bridge the walk that connects the two giant bit the bridges on top. I feel like yes
pedestrian yeah, yeah, yeah, I
Yeah, that I feel like in the early 2000s
Television channels were just bombarded with atlantis. Oh my gosh. Yeah when we finally got to go there
I was like it was the greatest moment of my life just because I'd seen it so much on TV
It lives up to the hype I'd say. Oh good. That's cool
You go. Oh, I was gonna say let me ask about the cruising because it does seem like
There's a there's a lot of stuff to do every how modular like how adjustable is
Or the Disney Cruises because I think when I go to the theme parks
I am like the operations person's worst night like I like to plan a little
But I like some wiggle room and I like to change my mind at the drop of a hat if I'm not up for it
You know how much in the cruising can you just bail and just go get room service?
The only thing that you I mean you could we do do that sometimes
But the only thing that you have like a quote-unquote appointment for is your dinner time is the same time every night
And then if you want to go see the the big show, okay
But besides that you could do whatever the heck you want and then the beauty of a cruise
Did I think it makes it better than like what the parks are now because now you got to do like the the lightning lane
And like yeah ever and like here you can choose. I'm gonna do this trivia
I'll go meet goofy or I'll like you know you just I'll go to the pool deck like you can you really don't have to make
Reservations for almost anything and the dinners because there are like at all you can go to the
Signature or the fancy dining yeah, and like can you change that like hey?
We don't really want to go to this right could we just make a reservation or could we just
Have a snack instead
Set to where you're going
They do have some food you could get room service, or you could go up on the pool deck
But a lot of those actually close early
Yeah, so room services 24 room services. Okay room services 24 hours, and it's
Included yeah on a lot of cruise ships you have to pay like an extra fee
So that is the beauty of it as many as many get like Mickey bars whatever you want is anywhere
That could be a video for me
Bars, I try to push it and see how many
Right yeah like when in hours are like within two hours before they go look sir
We have to there's a big article that just came out about
Netflix and all the different weirds like how Netflix destroyed everything
basically and how when they were do still doing the DVDs they would
Like choose the people that were you actually using the service a lot, and they would like throttle their delivery speeds
They were yeah, so like you would get if you were actually really sending DVDs
And you were watching a lot of movies a month. They would slow it down
Because that was not helping them you know make money or whatever so I wonder if like they they caught wind that like room 302
Is like ordering hundreds of chicken wings that they'd be like look we got a disconnect the phone or something
Like they would figure out a way to slow me down
They would have to I think because I would there's only a finite amount of chicken fingers you have on a boat
And they were not prepared for an experiment to happen for content. We're
Pulling into Nassau. It's an unplanned port. We need more chicken fingers because of Mike Carlson in room
300 he's making content
Making content he's eating about a few dozen DiGiorno pizzas that we keep on board
Or if it or it could be if you're on the boat
They've made a note that you brought several cool bags to keep the chicken fingers to take off the boat
Well, yeah, when you go home, then you can eat chicken fingers for a full like month or two sure filling up buckets with soft serve
I'll carry this off the boat. You don't need to check this
Well, you do have unlimited soft serve on the yeah, yeah like that is what I love about cruising
Especially on Disney. They have like unique flavors like banana, which is so good. I was gonna ask what the flavors
That's good mango. And do you do to self serve the soft serve on the older?
Yeah, the older ships you do but the newer ships they do it for you. Okay. Okay. Now that's another thing
Well, I like I've said this before I like it when somebody makes me a cone
Like I don't like this new like pink berry trend of I have to do it. I don't want to do it
I know people disagree with me about this
I like an expert to make a little thing for me or do the cone because I will mess the cone up
Oh that some of the dining halls in college you would make your own code right and it was I was a mess
When you go to like old country buffet with your grandparents like I would
You'd have to do it self-serve sure and I would ruin it or I would blow it mine just looks so bad
Yeah, you want it to be aesthetically pleasing before
So look, that's I guess that's another rare Michael Eisner lose losing
Choice, I feel like I'm on the other side of things because like like the buffet on the ship is called Marceline's market
You know reference a wall
At that buffet they
Put the stuff on the the plate for you and then hand you the plate
Okay, because it's trying to it's more sanitary than I guess
When you're like, yeah
It's a good point that is true if you're like, I'd like to really
Full of french fries, please the older ships. I think you're you could still do it yourself. So what that's an interesting change
I wonder why pandemic pandemic? Yeah, that's probably yeah
I am sure they're trained to make chaos plates like to
They're trained to like chow chow me next to chicken fingers
Yeah, I also I'm one of those picky people that I don't want the things to like to touch yeah
Yeah, I guess I'm like that more than not but yeah
Really have to think about my plate preference. But no, I guess I get pretty chaotic at a buffet
Now do the buffets live up because I do find buffets often even though it's fun in concept they often are underwhelming
but sometimes you get a rare like really good buffet, I feel like
Comparing Royal and Disney Royal is way better just because I have a bigger selection
But one thing that you could only get on a Disney Cruise buffet
One day out of the entire trip. They they serve you churro Mickey waffles. Oh, and they are the best
Breakfast item of all time. Oh, okay. They taste so good. They're so good
Yeah, and I don't know why they don't have them in the parks or why and it's only one day
I don't know why you can't have them every day
I guess it makes it special and you never know what day it is
You just have to go up there and hope that they're there really so it's kind of like a fun little challenge to try to find
Put something special in them, but we don't know what like it's a secret recipe that they don't use
I mean, they just encrust it in like sugar and cinnamon and it's
Fried yeah, they're like deep-fried like oh, okay
You don't even need like maple syrup on them, but I still put the you guys were on a seven-day. Yeah treasure
What
I guess
So I'm assuming do you repeat dinners when you're out that many days?
Do you repeat restaurants? Can you go like oh, I love Marvel. I want to go to the Marvel restaurant three times
No, you have to go to whatever you do repeat the restaurants, but there's different menus
And then at the certain ones like the Marvel one, there's two different shows
The play so like a second night. It's different same with the cocoa one. There's like a different show
I will say one of my complaints about this is the seating in the
in that
venue is kind of
That like we were behind a pole. We couldn't really
The old Jenny Nicholson
Yeah, yeah
But the the shows look good. It was just hard to see him
Yeah, but um one tip that you can learn if you're a seasoned Disney cruiser is if there's a food item
You like at a different dining venue you you can just order request it and you can get it like every night
That's like oh, that's a good tip. I like that cuz they're someone's in that venue
Ordering that food do I mean like it's like it's the same kitchen for all three, right?
So it's not sure someone's not like running that multiple decks
Yeah, like I one churro in their hands to get to you. It's all in the same area
Do you do the can you do the two entrees trick? Oh, yeah
Multiple entrees
Sure, you could order like you could order everything on the menu if you wanted they'll bring it to you
Okay, cuz it gets covered under the normal plan or whatever you want like you can't decide between chicken or salmon
So the two entrees trick could also be the nine entrees trick. Yeah, it doesn't have to just be two entrees
you know, I always ask like the server like what's better this or that and like
It's dangerous on a Disney cruise because you ask them that and they're like, I'll just bring you but yeah
They're like, no, I'll just bring you both
Interesting, so they have enough food if everyone ordered nine entrees
Hopefully, yeah
What um
So for like like there's a Zootopia ice cream parlor and sweet shop when you
order all cart stuff there
Is it do you just tap a room key or do you just pay with a credit card?
So you pay everything with your room key. Okay. Yeah, but yeah, the Zootopia one isn't up charge. Unfortunately, it's not the free soft serve
I
Was watching with beta breath watching that and then I saw the price as I'm like, okay, it's fun to try
Yeah, but yeah, the freeze officer essential. Yeah. Okay. Jason. Do you have any more questions about the amount of meals?
Sweets well, I now I'm moving like uh, I like all the freebies
You get on the free Jane made fun of me when I said freebies cuz she's like you paid for the cruise like
Yeah, you're getting a dry wet bag of like or a tote bag or something. I enjoy that as well
Yeah, we usually say free on the channel, but then people yell at us and be like, no, it's included, right?
It's like a brand new ship and it says like inaugural
Sailing or whatever on it feel special. Mm-hmm
Like first edition like we bought a bunch of tiki mugs on this on the treasure
Because for some reason they had so many like awesome tiki mugs we bought them all and they all said first edition and their ship exclusive
Yeah, and they're what they were all really cool. This is good. This is what I like to hear a ship exclusive stuff
Yeah, that's
Haunted mansion. They have one of the bride who's like this
Mermaid mermaid and then one of the captain. Oh, that's cool. And then at the Jungle Cruise bar
They have one of that boat with the chimpanzees on it that have taken over. Oh, that's cool
Oh man, but like now I'm extra incentivize shrimp is wearing like a Disney Cruise line hat instead of like so it's like special
Yeah, no, that's
People are serious about the all the merch that's sold on the Disney Cruise stores
I'm crazy just like that first day when they open right they don't open those stores until they get out to the water at the right
Like there's a lot like people are just it's like Black Friday people are hearing
I was gonna say like wow as if like that surprises me, but it doesn't surprise me because I would be in line
Yeah punching someone
First do you think that's people who want the keepsake or trying to flip some of them probably both I assume
5050 yeah. Yeah, I was surprised when you guys got on the ship. You couldn't go out on your patio or balcony
Fueling I'd never heard of that
Yeah, depending on what side of the ship you're on like I guess they were obviously have to refuel when they're back in port
So we weren't allowed to go out there until I I think with the ship left. Yeah, we've never seen that before
I don't know why maybe they think people are gonna smoke or something in a spark. Oh, I don't know
Does Mickey patrol the deck and be like?
I
Wish
Guess I want some of that fuel
Can you smoke on those balcony or there there's
Two but that they do have dedicated smoking areas. Oh, they do. Okay. Are they themed to any characters?
Is it lamp wick? No, unfortunately, no, that would be smart though
Oh
Here lighting up with you
Cruella Cruella de Vil. Oh, there we go. The friend from the goofy movie. It's like hey, man
Like play it cool
That's probably not a great idea you're going to multiple countries you might watch that
Well, look, we probably could talk about this all day Jason's already asked all his main questions about the meals
Which Disney character loves
But we'll have to you'll have to come back tell us about the other
Disney approved name boats. Yes, hopefully we will have gone on one
Soon, I hope I hope to go on one soon the Triton class, which I had to double-check like oh is that cruise line wide?
It's like no. No, that's a Disney thing
But Peter and Kittra, you've survived podcast, right? Oh my god. Thank you for doing the show
Let's exit through the gift shop. I mean we've talked about your channel
But if anything else you have any other things to plug social media names
I mean if you want to see footage from the Disney treasure, we have three videos
Well somebody Irishman's runtime length of video. Yeah
Sure. Yeah, we combined multiple days into a single video. So they're pretty long
But if you want to watch them go check them out, we'd love that. Yeah, check them out for sure and it's fun
It's like it's the next best thing to being in the park
It's like seeing what's going on there and seeing you walk around and I did I watch there's new
Drinks now in Avengers campus, which I am excited. We're gonna going soon
So I want to try is there is there a drink specifically the new of the new ones you would recommend that you tried
I think just you need to get the Captain America sipper, which is pretty cool. Oh wait, it's the shield
Yeah, the shield. I mean that's just you pour a soda into right, right. I think you like the litmus lemonade
Yeah, I don't remember what the names are. There was some kind of strawberry lemonade drink. That was pretty good. Okay
Yeah, that sounds like I would like that. Yeah, so I like the patriotic punch
Yeah, sure old patriotic punch. I did see that that stuck to I just like the alliteration of that
But that's all I need sometimes to enjoy a drink
And it's red white and blue until you mix it. You got to mix it, but it looks good until you mix it. Yes
As for us you can get bonus episodes the aforementioned points episode at patreon.com slash podcast the ride a lot of
What do we do lately disco Mickey Mouse the disco Mickey record? Yeah, sweat box sweat box the documentary about
Emperor's new groove we do it on Club 3 if you're not a club 3 member you're missing out because there's a lot of the funniest content
On this podcast. Thank you for saying thank you for helping us plug there. We love it
Thank you for being supportive of the show
And yeah, we'll we'll talk more
When I've drawn plans for this new lazy river that I just concocted that I am really like proud of myself
I'll be honest. I'm very proud of myself for thinking of it
But but I will have a diagram and I will fully present it next time you're on so thanks
Forever
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm
Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts, please visit forever dog
podcasts calm and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and
Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook