Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate where today I want to say first, much like
section of a YouTube video or a message board thread or something. I feel like that was an
early internet thing, but today I'm saying Mike Carlson first when it comes to the topic we're
talking about today. Jason Sheridan is here. He also should say first. You'll not understand
what I'm talking about in a second. I'm saying first. I mean, you were first. You clocked this.
Yes, I clocked this. So you're seeing this topic right now come up in your second gate feed and
you probably don't know what it is, but I just want to say Podcast The Ride, specifically me,
Mike Carlson discovered it first. So let's just get that out of the way. We should say that we're
Scott free today. Some stuff has happened, good stuff as far as Scott is concerned, and we will
be Scott free for a few episodes or so. It's not going to be as long as last time, but he is not
here today to enjoy the firstness of it all. That's right. And I'm sure he's kicking himself
for missing out on this one. Yeah, I can't tell if this is good that he's not here or he is going
to be jealous that he wasn't involved in the firstness of it all. I don't know. I mean,
look, I would love if he uncovered something that we missed because I don't know that I could have
searched any other thing. No, I don't know how much there is sort of to dig into this, but we should
just say now that I keep being vague that today we're going to be talking about a new Disney
character. How often, I should say this, park specific Disney character, how often does this
happen? It's so often these days. Kind of rare. Kind of rare, especially because all the rides
are generally IP based on movies and shows. So it's rare that you get a full original theme park
character. And that is what Disney has done literally two months ago. Yes. Two months ago,
like around December 13th. I'm not sure we were trying to find the exact date. So maybe this is
where Scott would have come in handy. He would know the exact date of this character's creation,
but they posted a video of the new character that is supposed to be the mascot of the Disneyland
annual passes, AKA the magic key passes. This character is a duck and his name is,
let's say it together. Ducky. Now I don't know if it's supposed to be pronounced duck key,
but that seems to be the pun, the joke of the name. He has key in his name. He has key in his
name. So this is the new character. No one is talking about it. I feel that Disney hasn't done
enough to push this character on the public. Yeah. Uh, I would agree because shortly before
you got here, uh, I was searching Reddit and the Disney store app and I found, uh, nothing.
I literally got this no results found for ducky on the Disney store app with this kind of condescending
upside down goofy. Yeah. So when you search for something on the Disney store and you can't find
it, goofy is like doing a headstand and he's really like flashing his groin at you. Yeah.
It's a little, uh, mocking. Yeah. He's not, obviously he has his pants on. He's not flashing
his junk at you, but he does like have his like, he's like man spreading in the air
and he's kind of thrusting it at you in that image. Yeah. I, I guess it's meant to be whimsical or
foolish as his qualities are. Right. He's not aggressive in general as a character. He's not
like a predator or something, but it does feel like put that, put that away, pal. Yeah. Um,
ducky has real, uh, if you remember the Mr. Show sketch of pit pat, the non-denominational
genderless spokes thing. Right. Yes. Uh, ducky is kind of, he's definitely in the zone of like
kind of generic character as far as like, who is this character? What's he supposed to be?
I will make the argument though that duffy, the Disney bear ends up being a little more like pit
pat to me than this character and ducky. Yeah. Because like duffy and they've given duffy some
stuff over the years. He has outfits, he has friends. The friends though seem to have a lot
more personality still to this day than duffy. I would say so, uh, duffy is kind of like,
do you remember action man? The dolls that you could, he was just kind of a generic
GI Joe kind of soldier. Right. But then he would have a scuba suit. He would have space suit.
These are characters where you're supposed to like kind of infuse them, I think with your own
personality. Yeah. They're kind of ciphers. They're ciphers. So like when you, Jason Sheridan is
playing with a duffy doll, duffy is you. Yeah. Right. Well, you sent me earlier, you sent me
a limited edition, uh, Donald duck D mu. Is that how it's pronounced? Yes. That's yes. It's a very
cute, like cutie doll sort of thing. This is something I wanted to maybe, I was trying to
figure out if we were going to bring this up, but this is a whole thing. So there's this company,
I believe it's a Chinese company, uh, called pop Mart. Yes. And they have a store in the Glendale
Galleria. I like this store a lot. They got a lot of little figurines. They have very cool store.
They have a character named Molly. Okay. And I really want to get into buying Molly toys
because Molly has a bunch of different series of toy, series of toys. So there's baby Molly.
There's like, it says like Molly carb lover, and she's just eating different foods that she likes.
Then there's space Molly. Oh, and they have different sizes of the Molly space, Molly toys.
And some of the Molly toys have IP characters on the spacesuit. So you can get a space Molly
with a Ted spacesuit or a Care Bear spacesuit or a Garfield spacesuit. So when she pulls down the
helmet on the spacesuit, it's Garfield's face and ears. That's great. And then you can buy what's
called a mega space Molly that is about this big, let's say like a foot, foot and a half of the
Garfield of space Molly. Uh, I need to learn more about Molly. Yes, do I. I'm not an expert on Molly
yet, but anyway, so I sent you, um, a Pop Mart toy cause they do, they do IP, they do Disney stuff.
And they have put out what I can only describe as a nightmarish child that is dressed to look like
Donald who was also holding a Donald like plush. Yeah. Sometimes he just kind of looks like one of
the love is characters. Uh, if you're listening to the show, you probably know what love is.
I would hope so. Yeah. And you might also get the shivers every time you think about it, like I do,
but this can be plain like doll wearing Donald duck outfit or you can give him a beak.
Yeah. So imagine, um, on the Island of Dr. Moreau, they kidnapped like a child
and a Donald duck plush doll and they mutated them together somehow. Yeah. A mutant it's like
half boy, half Donald duck doll. And that's what we're talking about here as far as a toy.
So I don't think I'm going to buy this. I'm not as into this toy as I am into the, the Molly toys.
Okay. But I mean, maybe I could buy it for you for your birthday or something.
Yeah. Especially if they have a big version of it. Oh no. Something that you could put in your bed
or something. Something you could sleep next to. Yeah. There's a little space between the pillows.
Right. You might hit your head on its beak. Sometimes if you toss and turn,
there's usually a Snoopy, uh, Squish Malo floating around the bedroom, uh, from Nod's Berry floating
around. Oh, you mean like sometimes like I'll fall asleep clutching it. And then sometimes it'll just
be at the foot of the bed. Yeah. Do you, do you mean to be like, did you wake up and you go,
how did this get here? Or did you start? Well, it's less, you know, when you try to hold a pillow,
it's kind of sizable and then try to get on the, like I was, I kept falling asleep like that. It
kept taking up so much room. So like it's a body, it's, it's not as big as a body pillow though.
No, no. It's like an oval shaped, like very cartoony, very simplified version of Snoopy.
This is there, there was a prize booth right at the entrance of Camp Snoopy. Right. And they said
every, um, how did they phrase it? Every player wins. Right. And we're like, okay,
well, and they're like, well, do you want to play $10 or $15? And we're like, what? And they're like
pointing at the prizes. So if you paid, so did you, so $10 would give you a less good prize?
Yes. But this is the one I wanted. The, the $15 one was not as good. And I was like, well,
want to win that. Well, and they're like, okay, pick up the duck. All right. Picked out the duck
and here's your Snoopy. I basically bought a Snoopy for $10. Is it a decent quality?
Cause sometimes those carnival games have like really shitty quality plush. It's a,
it is an officially branded squish mallow, you know? Okay. I guess those are of a certain quality.
Right. And they're like, can you show me on your hands how big it is? Oh, it's very small.
Like paper size. Yeah. Okay. Cause I was picturing like a five foot tall Snoopy body pillow.
Oh no. I did have like, uh, two or three feet high Snoopy when I was really young and it started,
uh, leaking, uh, beanbag beans. Yeah. It started leaking pretty quickly into elementary school
and my parents were like, we have to get rid of it. I was like, no,
no, we can't throw out Snoopy. Did you end, you had to end up, you did, right? They got rid of it.
Yes. We, I finally caved at some point because there was just so many little
beanbag beans in my bedroom. Did they make you do it or anything? Was there like a teaching moment?
No, it wasn't. It wasn't an old yellow row. Jason, you have to get, you have to become
a man one of these days. Please throw out your broken Snoopy plush. Please cut Snoopy's head off.
Please set him on fire. Yeah. Woodstock will watch. Uh, well that's good. Uh, uh, yeah. So
this is this nightmare toy that I sent you. Um, that's not the thing. There was a lot of other
things I was going to maybe bring up at the top of the episode, but I decided to get right into
Ducky. Uh, and we'll see what else we talk about in the midst of this. Um, so Ducky the duck,
they posted, uh, there's, there's some pictures. There's like, he's in some magic key videos kind
of bopping around and it's a very like, like retro-y style video and it's cute. It's a cute
duck. I'll say that. You know, we don't talk, we, you really don't get a good look at his seat.
If that's what people's head are at when it comes to podcasts to write in duck, like cute ducks,
because we talk about, you know, Donald duck seat, but that's not what this is. He's a very
much a realistic ish looking duck. He's the right size. He's not walking around talking to Mickey
and friends or anything. Right. Yes. He is, uh, seems to be, well, I got a couple of things.
First off, Ducky, I don't believe Ducky is not the bird at the end of runaway railway,
which I've been meaning. That's an episode I want to do similar, but that was a character that was
introduced as a joke of like, this is a character made to sell a plush of it at the store.
And I feel like that's a pretty decent, that's a solid joke. Uh, and they abandoned that very
quickly. You mean as far as trying to sell the merch? No, I think they still sell it, but in
terms of like, he doesn't get a lot of stage time in the ride. You're saying that he should
have been more prominent in the ride. Like, like you feel like that was something they initially
were pushing with marketing or what do you mean with like marketing and like the, the whatever
store plushy booth when you left, but it's like kind of, you only really notice it when you're
waiting to like pull up to unloading. He's about to born and like he occasionally tweak tweets, but
he isn't as memorable as like Shondu, the tiger and the Sinbad ride in Tokyo Disney Sea. That's
true. Yeah. And it's kind of funny because he would fit throughout runaway railway. There's a
lot of stuff that goes wrong. I feel like there's a lot of antics. I bet you can track him. I bet
he just doesn't sort of register as a character. It could be, he could be in the background and
I just have never caught it. Maybe I'll have to, the next time I go on it, all I'm going to be
doing is focusing on that bird. On this little yellow bird. I'm not going to look at anything
else and I'm going to just keep my eyes on it. Cause I bet he's like doing stuff. He's got to
be doing stuff. I would hope he's doing stuff. He's up, he's in the background. Like maybe it's
unrelated, but like he's up to, I would say he's up to no good. Maybe he's just enjoying the
amenities. He's just enjoying the carnival and the underwater kingdom and the dance class. Oh,
he's underwater and he can't breathe, but he's enjoying it. Maybe he has a snorkel on or a
breathing tank or something. He's just sort of doing a, um, sort of a deep sea diving expedition.
Yeah. Or he's in a sub. He's in like a submersible. Oh, that would be good. Yeah. If he had a
personal submersible. Um, the, uh, the other thing, uh, I wanted to bring up with Ducky.
Ducky's story has a lot of beats as the little man of Disneyland. Well, okay. Yes. Yeah. Let's
get into it. That is, that is if, if they were like, okay, well what else are they going to say?
It's a cute little duck, you know, not a lot to it. Mostly what I want to talk about is this
video that they posted that explains the lore of Ducky. Yeah. And I'll give them credit because
there's a lot of lore packed into a minute. Yeah. So, cause they could have easily just said,
oh, it's Ducky. He's the magic key duck, blah, blah, blah. Here's a picture of him. And then
every time they post a video like magic keys are on sale or whatever here, you can, you can buy a
button or something or whatever. Like here's Ducky. They could have done it. They didn't.
No. So kudos to them for developing an origin story for Ducky. Now I think today we're going
to dissect, do we like the story? What does the story mean? Yeah. What are the implications
of this story for the rest of the Disneyland resort? Right. So I have it here and yes,
I agree with you. This is what we need to talk about. Once upon a time, there was a sweet,
friendly, curious little duckling who loved the Disneyland resort with all his heart.
It all started when as a tiny hatchling, he migrated to a beautiful river that would become
the rivers of America. Let's just start right there. Yeah. So Ducky was a little baby
before Disneyland was created. Yes. He existed in Anaheim before that. So automatically,
Ducky is 70 years old, easily 70 years old. So right there, there's something magical about him.
You drew the parallel to The Little Man of Disneyland, which is a little golden book
that is like 60 or 70 years old or whatever. It's a similar story where The Little Man of
Disneyland supposedly lived in Anaheim before Disneyland existed. Mickey and friends wined and
dined him and were like, we're going to build this thing here. You're going to have a house
in Disneyland. Bro, don't worry about it. You're going to love it. And he did. He loved it. You
can still see the little house over in Adventureland still to this day. In the tree,
yeah, by Indiana Jones. So very similar to his origin, Ducky's. So already Ducky is magical
because like Little Man of Disneyland, he's already kind of a magical character. Ducky is
being presented as just a regular duck, but they've already introduced the wrinkle that Ducky is at
least 70 years old. Yeah. Just looking real quick, the average age of a mallard duck,
five to 10 years. Yes. So this creature has likely watched his friends and loved ones die around
him as he does not age. I think that's true. Now, could there be an implication here
that living inside Disneyland keeps you young forever? Well, now we're getting into kingdom
keepers, like magic territory, like powers. Ducky likely has powers. Well, he does have
powers and then he gains more powers as you learn, but he clearly has some sort of powers.
And I'm just wondering, like, if I were to, like, do I age the days I go to Disneyland?
Oh, that's good question. You know what I mean? Because like I've been to Disneyland a lot in my
life. I'm very lucky. Have I been a hundred times to Disneyland? I don't know. Maybe approaching
that. Does that mean, though, that almost like a third, one of the, I'm almost getting back like
a third of a year. So I'm not actually the age that I am. I'm a little younger. The touring plans
crew must be like ageless. Right. Guy Selga. Guy Selga is 12 years old. No. He's in Disneyland
almost every day and he's only 12. Yeah. Yeah. That's interesting. So again, that's what I'm
saying. The implications for what it must mean if this Ducky is still young and vibrant seeming
and living in Disneyland for 70 years. Yeah. When he gets more powers, it's with the behavior that
I don't know that they usually like to encourage in children. What do you mean by that?
That's a very good point. Yes. Okay. Hold on. Hold on. We're not racing yet, partner. I think
there's like seven things I want to talk about before that happens. We'll see. Okay. Here we go.
Growing, he knew it would blossom into a place filled with wonder.
Bit by bit, he watched it all being built. He napped underneath the shade of the greenery,
dreaming about exploring the entirety of this special place. He played make believe in the
minute. So, okay. He's sitting there in this cute little video they have. He's sitting there with,
I presume is his mother and they're watching as Disneyland is built. So they're sitting there
watching it and there's a clip, a part of it where it's winter time. Yeah. They have winter clothes
on and they're watching the castle being constructed. Yes. First of all, what happened
to his mother? Well, she might be an ageless one too. I know, but she doesn't show up later
in the video. Yeah. Good question. But, you know, who knows? Maybe she left Disneyland because she
was ready to go. You're right. She's like, I don't need to be in this park every day. I've got a life
to live. I, yeah. I got to go to Universal. The one thing I haven't done is death.
So he's so, so then they immediately like, they're watching Disneyland being built. And then they
also, Ducky knew this was going to be the greatest place. You're like, how did he know that? Because
like the little man of Disneyland, Mickey Mouse told this little guy, hey, this place is going to
fucking rule. Well, I, if I remember correctly, they just started building and knocking stuff
down. Then he gave them a piece of his mind and they're like, shit, we have to deal with this guy.
That is true. Now that is a very interesting change to this type of story because I do feel
like that's a difference in modern Disney thinking where you have to make sure that there was never
a problem that our product presented. Correct. Yeah. Right. So Ducky just was like, hey,
they're building this big thing where I live. Great. No problems versus like decades ago where
they were like, oh, wouldn't it be interesting if we started building Disneyland and there was just
a little like leprechaun guy that lived there. He would be upset at first and then he would grow
to like it. But modern Disney would be like, no, the Disney company has never displaced someone
from their home. We've never taken, our parks are not responsible for doing that ever. All they do
is good stuff. Once they, do you remember well before we ever went there, there was an RV park
by Disneyland and I forget whether it was Disney Run, but people- Disney ran an RV park?
Lived there. Like people would park their RVs there and eventually in the late nineties,
they're like, we're ending your, we're ending the lease. We're closing the park. Wait,
did you say Florida or here? No, here, Anaheim. Really? Yeah. Where was that?
I, it was close to Disneyland. And you, you saw it? I've seen, I've seen pictures of it.
It came up on Sunday. I think it came up when we were talking about Anaheim. I can't remember
the city government or maybe the monorail. Like, but it, you know, it was,
I think meant for vacations, but then some people would stay there long-term.
Right. But I think there was a pool and an arcade and a general store, like a normal
campground, you know? Right, right. Hmm. Yeah. It's worth looking, if Disney owned it, that's
worth looking into. Yeah. I mean, it's worth looking into now, even if they don't, because
there could be a harbor hoedown eventually. Sure. That might be part of it. Sure. We just
started getting to the point where Ducky is now experiencing Disneyland. Yes. Here we go.
So Ducky is shitting and pissing in the Sleeping Beauty Castle mode.
Yes. Just because he's a duck, that's how it goes.
He's being a good boy. He's not sneaky on rides.
Right. That's true. He's going on bodies of water
that are kind of open for the wildlife. Right. And he's going in the storyboat
canals and pretending he's part of the story. Yes.
So this is all pretty cute, pretty standard stuff, I feel like at this point.
Yeah. He's just, he's just enjoying, he's kind of like,
oh, you might see Ducky one of these days, right? It's kind of inevitable that they monetize the
wildlife, the ducks, the cats. I haven't seen a lot about the Disneyland cats. I feel like
they're still plausible deniability, even though they feed them and spay and neuter them.
I'm realizing now, and I should know this before I say it, but I saw some tweets maybe today,
even showing that like on Donald's 50th birthday, he was surrounded by a bunch of actual ducks.
I think that's right. There's certainly been, it was a Disney World commercials where little
duckling stumbles upon a walk around Donald. Yeah. Well, this was like 50 ducks or something
surrounding him. So they'd obviously like done something, put seeds around Donald's seat
to get a bunch of ducks to take that photo. Sure. So they have used, yeah, you've never seen a
picture from Disneyland where there are 50 feral cats surrounding one of the characters.
No. I'm trying to think what character. Some of them are very friendly. I have
petting some of the cats I feel like. But there's not like honest John from Pinocchio
and there's 50 real cats surrounding him. No. Or like Cruella de Vil is surrounded by 50 cats.
A little wilder creature is the ducks. Right. I got attacked by a duck like lightly over a jolly
holiday. Have I said this on the show? Did you have food on you? Well, I was eating food. Yeah.
But the ducks, I just like a beak hit me right in the thigh. Not the thigh. That sounded like the
duck was higher up, but like more of the calf, I guess. A duck pecked me in the calf. And I was
like, this is crazy. Cause like you could easily nail a duck in the head just by scooting your
chair out. Cause it's so close, like such close quarters at jolly holiday. Yeah. And the ducks
are just that comfortable. I mean, it kind of, I was like kind of worried. Then I was like really
stressed eating cause I was like, I'm going to run over a duck. Yeah. By just standing up or
moving a chair. Well, that's what at Sleepy Hollow the last time my family went to Florida
and it was just the outdoor seating area just covered in bees. Like all they sell there is
waffles, berry waffles, waffles with syrup and butter and sweet and spicy chicken breast
waffle sandwiches. So the bees are just having a field day. So they were like, you mean just,
they were swarming. There wasn't like a layer of bees on the floor. There wasn't a layer of bees.
It just, anywhere you looked, every table was like swarming bees. Yeah. Did you stop and eat there?
Yeah. Really? Even though with the bees? Well, we had already ordered. Oh, so you saw the bees
after I see. And then our food came up. I thought you were like, yeah, but I really want a waffle.
Sure. We all wanted the waffle. We love that waffle sandwich. A thousand bees swarming,
but I got to eat in a waffle. So did you just eat farther away from the bees? Yeah. I think we
eventually moved or just tried to keep an eye on the bees. Just keep them. One of you were the
designated lookout to look out for the bees while you were eating. And it was busy. Like there was
a lot of family seating around there. I've never seen that many bees at Disney World or Disneyland
in one place. Is that like, is there a conspiracy theory that Disney knows how to control the bees?
Well, clearly something was going wrong this day. Well, right. I was going to say. Or they're just
trying to turn people over faster. Like don't savor that waffle. Woof it down. So they can get
out of here. They can unleash bees on parts of the park when they want people to disperse.
So they have a machine to keep the bees away, but they also have a bee machine that shoots bees
at part of the park when they want people to leave. Yes. And they were shooting bees
at this waffle. They were shooting bees. The demand for waffles was so great that day.
Get the hell out. Get to a table service restaurant now.
None of this quick service bullshit. They were shooting, yeah. They really that,
they should have never done the virtual queues or the like, whatever, the lightning lane stuff to
to make the lines smaller. They should have just shot bees at the rides that had long lines.
Yeah. People would have gotten out of there. No problem. Okay. So again,
this is pretty standard stuff. Yeah. Or, you know, a little mascot.
While he was taking a dip, someone dropped a mysterious key into the water.
The duckling, ever curious, dove down to follow it. He prodded it, inspected it, and swallowed it
whole. Okay. What the fuck? What the fuck? Why? That's Pika. You're not supposed to be eating keys.
Why would he eat the key? Why would he eat the key? It's a key to a door. Also, wouldn't a key sink?
Yeah, it did sink, I think. It showed in the video. Oh, okay. It did sink. So he was just bobbing
down. So he bobbed down and they said he really, this is also what it is that confuses me. If they
said, oh, you know, he was sunbathing, someone dropped a key and it fell into his beak and he
ate it, like fine. But they really present it as he went down there, prodded it, saw what was going
on and then consciously thought, I'm going to eat this key. Right. He didn't. It's hard. It doesn't
taste like anything. He probably licked it. He smelled it. It didn't taste or smell like food
and this fucking idiot duck ate the key. Why would he eat the key? I'm assuming a certain level of
hubris comes with the magic gained of living in Disneyland. Like you're powerful, you know,
you're invincible. So you're saying like when we're at the end of a five day vacation and we're just
like fucking feel so good. Yeah. I want to eat a key right now. I'm on such a high. I want to eat
a key. If somebody were to drop a key right now, I want to smell it. I want to lick it and then I'm
swallowing that thing. This is, I was trying to think of this name a while ago when we were
recording, but one of the guest stars on Dr. Odyssey is Fred Melamed. Have you talked about
this before? Did we get there? I couldn't remember, but his whole thing, his medical condition is he
just keeps going around the ship eating objects. Oh, so he is like a key eater. Like Dr. Odyssey
has got like, and his wife is in denial. So what does he eat on the show? Like a ring.
I think he eats a key or two, cufflinks. So he eats a key. Yeah. And they have to like pump his
stomach. Is that something you would develop later or is that something you would have since you were
a kid? I don't know much about it. I think it is a thing where it's like, oh, he's had this for a
while. He has been sick and they didn't like suss it out in time. Can I ask this? And maybe this is
just, this is ignorance. Yeah. Is it a sex thing? No, it's not a sex thing. I think it's like a
bullshit thing. Oh, okay. Is it similar to that feeling people get when they're on like a high
cliff or they're on the third floor of a mall and you kind of look down and there's this weird thing
in the back of your mind that's like, I could just throw myself over this. No, I believe that sensation
is normal. Yes, I think that is normal. I think that's healthy to have that thought. Right. But like,
I would have a feeling like when I would be in the audience watching a band concert in high school,
like, you know, there'd be multiple kinds of bands, symphonic band, concert band. So you'd watch the
other bands and then you'd go up and play. Yeah. I would have a weird feeling in a similar way.
Like I could just blow my trumpet and ruin this whole song right now from the audience. Yes. Like
there's like your brain oftentimes is like kind of like floating ideas that you shouldn't do that
you know are bad. Yeah. So it's a, that's what I'm saying. It's like a similar thing to that,
but it's so strong that you're like, I know I shouldn't eat this key, but I have to eat.
Can't help myself. Right. Right. Interesting. So what, how did that resolve on Dr. Odyssey?
Well, I think what happened is they had him for a day and a half because he is not in that many
seeds. Do you think his schedule is so demanding? No offense to it. He's great. I'm just saying like
if he signs up for a Dr. Odyssey, he should be there for a week. I don't know that it was his
problem is what I'm saying. It sounds like the writers didn't give him enough stuff.
Well, I'm trying to figure out who the actor who plays his wife, but she, she isn't a much more,
she gets more of a starring. But she's not eating everything in sight.
No, but she's in denial about like, no, we're basically like we're normal. We organize these
crews and like clearly he's doing it out of like stress or something in the thing. I don't know
why Ducky is doing it. They don't, they don't flesh that out. Yeah. Does he just not maybe know
the concept of keys? I guess, but at this point, okay, so let's start extrapolating here because
the magic key program is new in the scheme of things for Disneyland. They've had annual passes
for decades, but magic key is a name that just came about a few years ago. So I have to presume
that Ducky ate this key a couple years ago, which means that Ducky was in Disneyland for
over 60 years, not eating keys, not eating things he found. When it was closed for like a year plus,
was he confused? Probably, but I don't know that they did not address that in this minute long
video of like what he did. They did not address what he thought about State Fair or Thumper's
Easter or the various reigns of CEOs. They did not say what he thought about Michael Eisner or
Card Walker, E. Card Walker, whatever. So he ate that key a couple of years ago
and it's confusing to me because it just, it's presented in the video as like a positive thing,
like, oh great, he ate the key, which I don't understand. It's not like, no, Ducky, what are
you doing? No, everyone's like shouting at him. Ducky, no, spit it out. And it's like, and there's
not, the next part is not they take Ducky to the vet and give him the like dog throw-up drugs.
That's not part of that either. No. It's just presented as a good thing. Now I also ask the
question, who dropped that key? Because they're going to reveal that that key is magical,
but someone dropped that key. It's also an old fashioned key. It's not like, right. It's not a
house key. It's not a house key. It's not like a modern hotel key. It's not a card,
like a credit card size. But here, okay, let me just play this a little more and then we'll
talk about who dropped this key. It wasn't just any key. It was a magical key that could open
doors across the Disneyland resort and it gave the duckling powers that made his dreams come true.
Basically, it's a magical key that opens doors and Ducky has swallowed it. Now, first of all,
why couldn't he just pocket the key and use it on a practical way to open a door if he needed to?
Right. Why did he eat it and become, because also the key is going to kill him or it's just
going to sit in there and fuck up his digestion. How is a key that's a practical, real,
old school key going to open a door when it's in the duck's stomach?
Yeah, or it's just going to shoot out his cloaca. It's going to rock out of there.
It could rock it out either side. He could puke it out. He could poop it out.
Right. It's very confusing to me. Just say he got a key and he has a little key ring
and he puts it in his little duck pocket. That'd be cute.
It'd be adorable. If he had a little carabiner.
Right. Who dropped the key is also my question. Walt Disney has been dead for a long time. Now,
remember, it has to be a couple years ago because that's when Magic Key was introduced.
Yes. So it has to be somebody. Is it Bob
Chapek? Is it Bob Iger? Is it John Lasseter? Back in the parks for some reason.
Is it abandoning his Magic Key? Right. John Lasseter has a Magic Key to Disneyland
and he drops it in the water because I'm not going to need this anymore. I don't know. I'm
just saying who would drop a key in there and why would it be anonymous? Do they know that
Ducky was going to find it? What if a different duck ate it?
Yeah, because they also seem to apply that it opens a lot of doors.
Yes. That's another thing I'm confused by. I'm just saying my Magic Key is just a tab
on an app. It's the simulation of a button on a touch screen and it can't open shit.
It gets you in and out of Disneyland and California Adventure, assuming you have a reservation.
So that shit's still going on. Right.
But I wanted to open locked doors. I wanted Jimmy open doors with it.
Right. This doesn't make sense as far as being one to one with your annual pass.
It isn't like Ducky dreamed of going to the Disneyland Resort and for 70 years,
he was too poor to do it. He was just sitting outside the resort wondering and then one day
from the sky up a key dropped. But then Ducky used the key to enter Disney's California Adventure.
Don't worry. He reserved a date multiple weeks ago and he made sure that his starting park was
Disney's California Adventure and he won't be able to switch until 11 a.m. That would at least make
sense for what the actual Magic Key product does. No strikes against Ducky. No strikes on
his Magic Key if he lives there. Ducky forgot to go for the third time and now Ducky is blocked
for 90 days. You must be punished when everyone's favorite part of purchasing goods and services
being punished for being a naughty boy. Ducky is locked into Disney jail for 90 days.
Will not be able to enjoy his fun. But he's delighted by the 10% off food and merchandise
he receives. Well that's what they're sort of implying that like all these doors that open
for you when you're a Magic Key holder is that you get 10% off your food or your plush purchases.
That's what the doors opening are. But the way they make it seem is that oh my gosh,
you can go in places that other people can't. The regular guests only dream of going through
these doors. Yeah. But not you. Yeah. You do the special stuff like Ducky does.
So it just it's here. Okay, let's keep going. Let's keep going.
Now with a magical click click, he could open the door to the happiest day ever.
What is the click click? What is click click? What are you talking about? Even if he had the
key out of his digestive system, that's not that is that a noise that turn like an old-fashioned
key might make that noise? Sure. Well, click click, I guess you put it is one of the in
is that going in once a click and then turning to the left a click. Look, I'm going to be honest.
I've mostly seen that kind of key in movies and TV. So I think the click click is put in a post.
So I can't say what the actual sound would be. I mean, I guess I've been to Colonial Williamsburg
and the presumably it's some name, something different now. The Plymouth Plantation in Plymouth,
Massachusetts. Yeah. Learn how candles are made. He doesn't have the key outside his body. Right.
Why is it click clicking? It would the door would be like the door opens. Let's just say that
the door would open magically. Like let's I'm just trying to logic this out. The door would open for
him if it was magic. Oh, the door is magic. It recognizes that the magic is in his belly.
Let's just open the door for him. Creek like a magical creek opens the door like smart locks
or like electric cars where they play car sound audio to you that it's a car. Yes, that's yes.
But I just, again, logic policing this and I wasn't so like hung up. There were too many
things in a row in this video for me to let go. That's really what happened. They're just thing
one after another keeps making me go. I don't understand what's happening, but this click click
thing. My I am wondering if whatever marketing person came up with this, did they get to like
day before launch day and go like, Oh fuck, we forgot it. We have a duck. Donald shit.
Well, the posts are already scheduled. Let's no one's going to know. Just post it.
So somebody is like, I got the perfect character. It's the perfect animal. We don't. Oh shit. Oh,
shit. Donald duck is very famous. He's like one of the most famous characters we have. Oh shit.
All right. Well, I've done so much work on ducky. There's just no way we can
pivot to a different animal. This has been six months of my life. I am not switching it up.
I've been working on this video for six months. No, don't tell me goofy start in a series of
shorts where he learns how to do things. Yeah, that would have been helpful to know six months ago.
Goofy learns how to use his magic key. All right. What if he's ducky the squirrel?
Okay. I understand it's confusing, but follow the logic here. He's just, they call him ducky.
Okay. Because his nose is sort of shaped like a beak. That's kind of scary.
Yeah. It looks kind of like a hybrid there. Okay. All right. God damn it. All right. Well,
it's got to be a duck. Just leave it. Just leave it in. Just go home. Leave it in. It's ducky and
he's a duck. Okay. People have to fucking deal with it. All right. You would think we're done
with this video. We're not done with the video yet. This video, by the way, is like 80 seconds long.
It's so short. Yeah. But there's a lot of lore.
Okay. Okay. From then on, he was known as ducky. This duck has been nameless for 70 years.
This duck didn't have a name. Or he had a name like the other gods in like a Lovecraft story where,
oh, if you knew his true name, it would drive you insane. We can't say. Because he is magical
already. He's 70 years old before he gets the key. He's 65 years old before he gets the key.
Yeah. But like, I guess if it was like, they called him Brian for 70 years and now they called him
ducky. Why would they just start calling him a name? Yeah. Just because of the, he's got a key
in his belly. So everybody's like kind of making fun of the key that's in his belly.
Is he getting rezzed? He's getting rezzed. Like, hey, ducky. Hey, we're calling you ducky now.
We're adding an E to the ducky nickname. You idiot. You're not supposed to eat a duck.
You're not supposed to eat a key, man. That's for opening doors. Why would you eat that? This wild
man, you're ducky from now on. So, and then they have these like, they have cute like pictures of
ducky and he's got kind of like, you know, that long, what is it? A grand marshal in a parade.
Oh, a baton. Baton. Yeah. He's got Disney ears on and then there are two smaller ducks behind him
with Disney ears on as well. And again, I do like the graphics. They're not dissimilar to like the
newer Mickey cartoons. Yeah. But okay, so he is now sort of showing his duck friends around the park,
but I don't understand what the new way he's, he's experiencing Disney now. He lived in the park.
Yeah. He was doing everything for free. Yeah. There's nothing different other than he's getting
a discount on Jolly Holiday Bakery items. He can get a muffin for 10% off. But not at the cart.
It doesn't work at the carts. It doesn't. The 10% does not work at the carts. It doesn't work at
the cart. Maybe it's, is that a little dictator as he sees control of the ducks?
Is he a little dictator? Is he too powerful? Is Ducky a little, well, I would say, okay,
it depends what the key, what doors the key opens. Like they're showing literal doors in the video.
Can Ducky get into the weapons cache? The Disneyland weapons cache? The security,
yeah, the security, like. Do you, how many weapons are on the premises of Disneyland?
I, that's, I'm legitimately asking. I, well, if there's Anaheim police there, you gotta factor on
that. Sure. I feel like the security area backstage, I feel like they have to have something. Do you
think it's like a Kingsman closet where it's full of weaponry? I don't know. I don't,
I would not think so, but. These theme parks, especially the Disney theme parks, are like
national security, like points of interest, you know? So. Right. And there's a lot of
plain clothes guys roaming around. We know that. Right, but are those people armed? I don't know
they're necessarily armed, but might be backstage. So you think maybe down like in the like corridors
or in the Disneyland tunnels or Disney world tunnels, it's like there's a room where you're
getting dressed to be goofy in a parade. And then next to it, there's about 500 guns on the wall,
just in case. That's a good question. I don't know. I suspect there's not that many. I don't think
there's that many weapons there, but according to this video, Ducky can get into those rooms.
So Ducky can like watch you change. Well, okay. Without that brings up a question. Is management
scared of him? Scared of Ducky? Yeah. Yeah. Well, they should be scared of him because he's got a
key that can open any door in the resort. He can open up the bathroom door. He can open up a door
if you're having like a meeting with a coworker, like if you're one of the like supervisors or
something and you're like, I need to pull you in here and we got to talk about something. Ducky can
just walk in. Ducky is essentially the child from the Twilight Zone episode who has powers.
Right. Ducky can literally open, like there's the doors that don't go to anywhere on rides
can be opened by Ducky. Yeah. He can open up the doors in Indiana Jones that don't work.
He can mess the rides up because he can literally open any door with his belly.
We are starting to get into the territory of does Ducky ever reality warping powers?
You mean like, can he will something into existence? Like if he goes through that door
in Indiana Jones, is it just hallway? Is just machinery back there or is it a temple door?
What were you picturing? I was picturing just a flat wall. Okay. I was just picturing he's like
messing up the ride because he just wanted to see what was back there.
Yeah. What do you think? I mean, Ducky lives, they do make it pretty clear because Magic Key
is the branding for the Disneyland annual passes. They make it clear that he lives in Disneyland,
not Disney World. Right. But what would Ducky do if he found out that they were paving over the
rivers of America? Oh, we'd go ballistic. He would probably, because yeah, that's where he like lived
most of his whole life. Yeah. Which I assume they didn't want to introduce Ducky living in
the place they were paving over in Florida. Yeah. But they don't call the Magic Keys there.
Right. That's what I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah. But I'm saying that like they have one cute new character
living in basically their version of a waterway. I feel like if the character were to catch on,
then it would be like, Oh, well, we destroyed the little man of Disneyland's house. It's the same
thing. So they wouldn't want to introduce like that the rivers is the home of one of the characters
because then if they decide ever to destroy our rivers of America, like they are doing to Florida,
then you're like, well, Ducky doesn't have a place to sleep anymore.
Yeah. So I don't know if he could stop it. I mean, when you ask reality warping powers, like he would
he would be able to stop something like that, I assume. Yeah. He would be able to open up like
a door under one of the construction cranes and it falls through into limbo or something.
Yeah. Like, yeah. Does he have chaos magic? Yeah. Why I'm even saying he if he has reality
warping, if he's like Dr. Manhattan and Watchmen. Yeah. Or yeah, he's yeah, he can just he can do
whatever he wants. But oh, Ducky is for sure tired of these people and their problems and
knives. Yeah, that's true. Now, if that's true, then I think Ducky is comfortable with all the
different changes that have happened to the Disneyland Resort over the last few years because
he would have stopped them if he wasn't. So he's he's on on the team. He's on the corporate team
is what I'm saying. Is he a driver of some of the changes? Perhaps he is. So they just wake up one
day and the burden, the bride with the axe is gone. Ducky has replaced the bride in the Haunted
Mansion and then they have to get Kim Irvine out there to pretend that they did something.
In reality, it's just Ducky and he's drawing his wing across his throat and he's like, that's
everyone's like, what happened? How does this happen? They just turn and Ducky's just there.
Right. And they're like, well, say no more. Ducky has made his decision.
Yeah, it's like the Coliseum or something and Ducky kind of gives his thumbs up or thumbs down.
Yeah, but there is no Ducky merch, right? No, I've searched all over. There are two or three posts
with Ducky on the Instagram. There are one or two articles written by other theme park bloggers
that mention Ducky, but there's not been a big push yet for Ducky.
And I don't know. It would make a good plush. Yeah. It would make a cute thing, key chain,
whatever, pin. It will be interesting to see because I've also heard rumors
that they could abandon Magic Key as a title. Okay. And abandon it entirely or just go back
to annual pass. Go back to annual passes or passports, whatever they call them at the time,
because I think the majority of people call them annual passes. Yeah. I don't think Magic Key is
stuck in the minds of parkgoers and the youth of today. I think they call them annual passes
still generally, not Magic Key, but we'll see. So will Ducky go away if that terminology goes away?
Because they've already changed from the same era, Genie and Genie Plus. They've gotten rid of
that Chapec era branding. Yeah. And it will be interesting to see. Yes. Is Ducky already going
away, which is almost the feeling I get because most people don't know about this. And is that
because they had just finished up all the Ducky stuff and then they're like, yeah, we're going
to get rid of the Magic Key thing. So for me, we're going to kind of send Ducky out.
I mean, I still, I still say fast pass instead of lightning late. A lot of
of course, all these, all these things that were burned in our brains, there's just no reason to
change them. Yeah. It's just weird. I fast pass is like, everybody loves saying fast pass.
Everybody has such affection. Now on some level, I don't know if it's protecting something beloved
to test out if the new version that costs more doesn't work. And then we could go back to the
original. You know what I'm saying? Like if max, whenever they change fast pass to max pass,
okay, well, if max pass people really won't pay, then we can just say fast passes back.
And we haven't soiled the good name of fast pass. I don't know if that's the thinking. Yeah.
Like that's why we were saying with Jeannie and Jeannie plus, like, why would you want to risk
using one of your most beloved characters for a service that's going to just drive everyone
insane? And they did and it did. And now they've rebranded already. There is a little more of this
video. A little more, believe it or not. Just play the rest and then we'll chime in.
Follow his adventures around the parks. You have the key to the best Disneyland day ever.
So that's basically it. They close like it's a storybook and Ducky is walking with his friends
or his children. Maybe those are his kids. It's possible too. Sure. Underlings. Underlings. Yeah,
it's possible. And yes, that's basically a little short story to tell you, the consumer,
that you should get a magic key because so many options open to you at that point.
But they don't, they don't describe any of the actual benefits.
No, I know. There's no, I don't. It's barely a metaphor. It's barely holding on for an 80 second
minute. That's what we were talking about earlier. Yes, I know. It doesn't, it doesn't make sense.
You're like, oh, so I get to like go in the back way on Star Tours? Is there a back door on
Star Tours? From watching the video, it looks like I can like walk on the Incredicoaster from
a secret door. Is that what this is? Yeah. No. There's like, I know someone showed me once
the like backstage door by the Grand Californian where the security, the metal detectors are to
get to downtown Disney. Right. There's a door, if you didn't turn to go to the metal detectors,
there's a door right around there that goes backstage. I think that's where like time clocks
and bulletin boards and stuff are. Well, Ducky can get in there. Yeah, he can. He can go in there.
He can run havoc and everyone runs scared when they see him coming.
So yeah, that's Ducky, like that's Ducky. And I could, do we like Ducky? I think we do.
I think so. I like him okay. I like him okay, but he's first of all, look, I hate to be so insulting.
He's dumb. He's a dumb duck. Yeah. He ate a key. He shouldn't have eaten that key. Was there moss on
it or something or like delicious moss? Like delicious underwater dirt? Does moss smell good?
Is moss a good smell? I feel like it smells bad. I feel like if it's mossy, it's like smells bad.
Can he only, well, birds don't have teeth. Is that what? Or no, they do have teeth, but they don't.
I forget. Yeah. Something about the beak. I guess I like him. I guess I hope for him
that he has more mythology that's more confusing even than that. Now that if they like triple down
on Ducky being confusing, I would love that more than just sort of pretending he's normal
because he's not normal. No, he's not. Ducky is not normal. Duffy is normal. Duffy is a normal
bear guy. He's kind of a boring bear. We have to steer him in the right direction though
to protect the world that hates and fears him. Sure. Yeah. I mean, I think this episode is going
to start doing that. We're going to start that conversation with America as far as what is good.
Have we gone too far? No, I think we're right on. I think this is the right amount.
Okay. But yeah, go ahead. Yeah. Oh, I was going to say I had something else outside of Ducky,
unless you were to say about Ducky. Well, I was just going to say if they can,
we could pitch real quick on what extra stuff we want Ducky to do that confuses the hell out
of a possible Magic Key buyer. Oh, I would like a full court press of Ducky. I would like shirts
and spirit jerseys and pins and keychains. Okay. I think they should go all in on Ducky because then
if they pull back really quick, then that stuff becomes rare. So you just want merch of Ducky
because then there'll be like a, there's a small window here where we know Magic Key exists
and that's when we could get all the Ducky stuff. Like you want, what would you,
of all the merch possible in a realistic sense, would you buy a hooded Ducky sweatshirt that had
like a duck bill on the hood that you could kind of pull down and it would look like your Ducky?
And then over like sort of by the pocket, by the belly, there's a key has been sewn into the
sweatshirt. Oh, see, I thought maybe an image of a key on the backside. Yeah, there could be an image
of a key on the backside too, but I think they should sew an actual metal key in the lining of
the sweatshirt. So when you touch your belly or sit down, you can feel it because you know,
like you really like feeling what Ducky feels. I would love to like, there's a little surveillance
steady, but if they sewed in like an RFID chip, so then you don't have to get your phone out if
you have a Magic Key. So you could wear your Ducky hoodie at the turnstile and that would read.
So instead of a Magic band, you're advocating for a Magic sweatshirt. I mean, those bands get
more and more expensive. So you may as well have like some practicality to the function.
That's okay. Yeah. Magic, it's like a Magic sweat, Magic sweatshirt,
and that gets you into the parks, but it's Ducky branded. Okay. Would you, let me think.
So it's like every now and then there's limited run vacation club. They can only buy if you're
in the vacation club. Supposedly. I bet if you like, we think not that cashier and they're cool
about it, you can probably buy it. You think you could do that? I think it can probably be like,
where, where, where do they sell it at the vacation club? I mean, like, like on the cruise ship,
on the cruise ships, they have some- Right. Oh, you're saying on the cruise ship,
you'd have to be a vacation club member to buy it? Or the emporium, like there might be
an exclusive vacation club shirt. Okay. And you think if you kind of give them the like the
little eye. Hey, you know. Sweet talk them. You know. I don't know. I feel like the opposite.
I feel like they are really like restrictive as far as what they do. Now they do have Magic Key,
like pins that they're selling. I saw they have an Indiana Jones one today.
Okay. I'm not sure there's a pizza Rizzo one that just came out. I'm not sure if that was a,
what is it called? What are the passes called in Florida? I don't remember. There's like an
Accredited pass. There's like an Accredited pass or something in Florida. There's like a different
amount of branding. And there's no platinum pass. There's no both coast pass. There is,
but it's not advertised. Oh, okay. I believe. Now you do get one if you're club 33. Yeah.
On either coasts, you get a whatever the premier pass. Okay. Whatever they call it. I'm not sure.
But, and I think you maybe still can get it. It's just not listed on the website. Oh, I see.
That's a wink, wink. You go up to one of the booths and go, give me the special pass.
You go up, you find the one ticket booth that still has a person in it. Yeah. That's like
dusty and you got to get the cobwebs out of the way so you can see them. They put the premier
pass on the table and I pick it up and I eat it. No. I eat it in front of them. No. I sniff it.
It's not there yet. I sniff it. I assess what it is and I eat it and it's in my belly forever.
You're like, smells like delicious moss.
If it smells like moss, I got to eat it because moss smells so good. So yeah,
ducky. I would a little ducky plush makes sense. But yeah, I don't know. I would think like, what's
the like a ducky corset you could wear? A corset? Is that what you would want to waste? Like a
waist trainer? What? You know, like you're trying to cram yourself into a dress or something.
Yeah, no, I'm familiar. Or a corset or like a cummerbund. It could be whatever you want. It
doesn't have to be. It could be gender. Obviously any gender can wear either of those. A girdle?
You want a ducky girdle. It could be a ducky girdle. And again, there's a key sewn into the
lining of it. But that would be, I think the ultimate ducky merch is something that really
made you feel like you were ducky. And then as the idea you had to use that as your way into the
park and on rides and using lightning lane, et cetera. Her universe clothing line is going to
make a fortune on the ducky past. The ducky, how much you think a ducky girdle would cost?
100? 150? How much is a girdle these days? I don't know that they're that popular nowadays.
How are girdle prices doing under Trump? Where is William Frawley's? Like the Smithsonian
have his girdle? Yeah, it's the first room with the Smithsonian is William Frawley's girdle.
It's by the big pendulum and the ruby slippers. Right. Yeah, they've kept good care of it. They've
taken good care of it. So you should do like a national treasure and try to find William
Frawley's girdle. Well, Michael, since we are scot-free today, I figured it'd be a good time
to give you your Christmas present. Christmas is coming, I was going to say early, but it's
coming very late. Very late. Very late. Whoa. It's flat. I see something that's flat. It's flat.
Okay. Oh my gosh. Just Christmas present here. Let me open this. It's stuck together. I'm guessing
this is a photo of some kind. Is it? Let's see. Is it a photo of the two of us perhaps?
An eight by 10 photo of the two of us? You know, you've seen like a headshot before.
I am very sentimental. It's a headshot, but it's our two heads. Yeah. So we can go out for
rolls together. Oh, there's so many rolls. Oh my gosh. It is a picture of Chuck-O the Clown.
Whoa. Is it signed by him or is it just a... No, it's a news file. Oh, wow. It's got notes on the
back. So it's old. It says April 20th, 1988. So this says Chuck-O the Clown on the back
and it says Randy Runyon. That's right. It's the son. It's Chuck-O's son. It's not the original
Chuck-O. Now here's a frame for it, but I want to make sure you could read the back. This is a
pretty good... You could use that for like a photo of your daughter or your family. I could use it
or I could put this photo of Chuck-O next to where my daughter sleeps. That's right. Now,
she could wake up. I originally got you this self-published book, but there's a catch.
Are you sure this isn't for Scott? Oh my gosh. This is a used book. It's kind of a dirty book,
but it's also... It's like printed. You can tell it's not like a professional printing place
because it's a little off center. Correct. Yeah. Oh, so the twist, you want to tell me what it is?
It's... I got too excited when I found it and I didn't read the fine print that it's a different
Chuck-O. There's a second Chuck-O. Holy shit. So this is a book about Chuck-O the Clown,
but it's not the Runyon family bloodline of Chuck-O. Yeah. Chuck-Chuck-O Sidlow has been
clowning around. Is this a... This is not a real clown, is it? No, it is. Oh, it is. It's a Barnum
Bailey clown. I thought that was fiction. Oh, it is. I thought it was a book. Chuck Sidlow's
amazing story as told to Judy Pichelle Van Tegen. So this is Chuck-Chuck-O Sidlow. Yeah.
And he's from New Jersey. He became the youngest boss clown of the greatest show on earth.
This is about his life after the circus. Yeah. Okay. So he was the boss of the circus. Yes.
This Chuck-O. That Chuck-O. But not Randy... So I had to correct myself and I went and I found
that file. So you get all of it. I do get the book though, even though it's not about this Chuck-O.
Is this... What is this in the... Are you reading it? Why is there a... That was just the packing
slip. Oh, I thought it was like a receipt for laundromat or something. You can use it as a
bookmark. Okay. I know you love self-published clown literature.
It says on the front, it says destiny or a gift from God. And then it's a drawing of a clown with
a picture frame and you can see his head through the picture frame. That's what all the clown
teachers in Los Angeles say in their first class. Is this destiny or a gift from God?
Yeah. And he's really like, he's kind of like hunched over. And it's like, it's like a child
drew the front of it. No offense to if this is like, if Judy Pochelle Van Tiegen drew this,
I apologize. It does look like an art class painting. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Well, I guess
I got a lot of work to do. I mean, we've been... Okay. I don't know if Scott will listen to this
at this point. I think this has been a pretty good episode, but... I think so too.
I... Well, Chucko will show up this year. I'll declare that. Chucko will be on
the podcast again. Not him necessarily. Maybe. I don't think there's been a younger Runyon
that's taken up the mantle. Well, they're both long dead. The father and son. I don't think the
grandson took it over. Yes. Yes. But okay. So thank you for that. There's one thing and I'm
stumbling all over myself because there is one thing else I wanted to bring up and I guess I
will. You know, we love our influencers. This is another zone. This is another Scott-free zone,
I feel like. Sure. It's sort of internet people making little videos that are not necessarily
comedic. They just decide they have a thing and they go for it. There's a lot of food reviewers.
Right. We like Costco guys. We like Luke's foods. You know him? Yes, I know him. And dang, it's Wayne.
There's the Maryland boys. Yes. What is their thing? They're like doing podcasts now. Okay.
But they were talking about different buffalo wing sauces they do or don't like. Okay. I don't know
if I follow them. There's of course Shirley Temple King who's been around for a while. He's a little
boy that tries the Shirley Temples. But then he does other stuff too. But Shirley Temple is not
the child who looks at stores lights turning on and off. No, that's a different one. That's Anthony
Geo was the one who told me about him. Okay. And I can't think of what his name is off the top,
but he'll wait outside like say a Ross or like a TJ Maxx at a mall and he waits for the lights to
turn off. And that's sort of a big moment. But I found a new one and plenty of people have found
this. I'm not saying I'm first like I am when it comes to Ducky, but I think you should know
specifically about this because I think you should either steal his bit or should go back in time
and try it. Okay. I am talking about my new follow on Instagram, Retro Samuel. Retro Samuel
looks to be a guy in his maybe early 20s. He could even be late teens. He looks young,
but his whole thing is buying old clothing like from the 20s and 30s and wearing it and then
posting like him in sort of an old like fedora and long coat looking wistfully into the snow
as an old song plays. Wow. And he's even got a picture that he's made black and white with him
and a little Mickey Mouse. And I don't know what country he's from. He seems to be European.
Somewhere in Europe is what I'm saying is where he's from. But this really should have been what you
did maybe with your life in general. And this is different than the like men's wear guy on Twitter,
the die work guy who it's a little more straight forward. It's a little more actual historical
stuff and modern stuff. Right. This guy will just, Retro Samuel will just put on like high
waisted pants and an old dress shirt that you would see like a president in 1920 where.
I gotta tell you, I hate high waisted pants. Do you really? My parents both were so like,
you wear your, excuse me, you wear your pants around your belly button and I'm like,
this is so uncomfortable. Like your natural waist is low. Like that's where I wear my pants,
where they sit naturally. Do you have like picture day where you were wearing like your pants up to
your belly button? I, well, I don't know. I don't think I have full, um, full body shots in the
first grade. No, I, I think it's like a chest up basically. Okay. But I'm, I'm interested because
I don't think, I don't remember like having a fight with my parents about how high my pants need
to go to my belly button. That didn't, I don't think they were like that. Yeah. So I don't,
I think it's just a matter of taste and tailoring and stuff. And I think it's just
my mother buying the same dockers at Sears or Boscov's for everyone at the mall. But let me ask
you this, would you, would you wear the Retro Samuel like this short tie? Cause that was the
style a hundred years ago. So were those short ties? Yeah, I don't mind the tie. I mean, I,
pretty slim ties caught on in the 2010s. And yeah, I had a few of them, but like,
I feel like there's a common ground now between a fat tie and a skinny. There's a medium tie.
There's a medium, you know, and I, I was never really a tie guy. I much would rather wear a
jacket and no tie as opposed to a tie and no jacket. I'm trying, I am trying to find,
I may have sent you, there is a channel on YouTube where a guy dresses like an old detective sitting
at a desk. It introduces like public domain film, the war, even I were sending those back and forth.
But it's very much like a old detective version of Svenguli. Right. That's good. I like that gimmick.
Yeah. So what I'm hearing from you is that you don't really want to be like Retro Jason on
Instagram. Well, no, it seems like he's, you know, got a good thing going. Yeah. But are we funny if
all of a sudden, like an older man stole his gimmick. Wren just said, it's a Retro Jason
and you start wearing high-waisted pants and then like, well, in the mood played in the background.
Like that would be funny. I mean, I guess I don't want to start a fight. He seems like a nice,
a nice young man. So I guess I don't want to weird him out. But I appreciate you letting me know.
But you should follow Retro Samuel. Yeah, I will. Like he'll come back. Yeah. Follow him right now.
And then just, I like, I like his idea because I, what I like about the influencer types and
he's got like 180,000 followers. He really doesn't need our help at this point probably.
But I like about the followers is they can really just like find a very simple thing and do it.
You know, it doesn't, it doesn't need too much to be somebody that I'm going to be obsessive about
on Instagram. Yeah. And he looks like he's doing it for fun, you know, for the love of the game.
Yeah. He has a Patreon too. Does he? Yes, he does. Does he post exclusive photos?
I haven't investigated what, you know, what would be really good for him to do on Patreon is he
would post photos in modern clothes. So it's like, yeah, you know, that would be funny. What's free
is me in the old clothes, but if you want to see me wearing a Looney Tunes t-shirt, you got to pay.
I Looney Tunes with Bugs Bunny wearing a chain and baggy jeans and stuff. Right. Yeah. A supreme
shirt is behind the paywall. That's behind the Patreon. Yeah. Oh, it looks like you just get
early access to the posts. Like I can see he's wearing like some old sweat, old style sweaters
like he's dressed like maybe Jimmy Stewart or something. And it's a wonderful life.
That's clever. I mean, it's a miracle that he's found this much in this good of shape.
Yeah. Oh, there's some, but he has bloopers too. He's got some bloopers on the Patreon as well.
We should do that on our Patreon, have some bloopers, all the mistakes we make that we edit out.
Oh yeah. Just tripping over things and hitting our heads on microphones. Yeah.
I don't drink seltzer or soda when I record anymore because I feel like it gives me gas.
I feel like it makes me burp. I hear that. And I do enough of that to be in with. You're burping
enough to be off mic. Yeah. I'm like moving away from the mic. Yeah. Well, look, I've tried to get,
yeah, if you have too much soda, I feel like sometimes my stomach these days, I can't have
two sodas in a day anymore. That's over. Now I can if I had to. If the fate of the world depended on
me having two sodas, I could have two. Yeah. Well, hey, we've got a Cherry Coke Zero and Sprite Zero
in the fridge. Help yourself if you want any. Well, we've got another episode to record. So
maybe on that second episode we will do it. But as for today's episode, I think you, the listener,
have survived podcast the ride at this point. Yes. But follow Retro Samuel. Follow Disneyland Magic
Key so you can keep up on what's going on with Ducky. And just keep this in the back of your mind.
Chucko is coming. I'm not going to say when. I'm not going to say where. I mean, probably October.
But I'm not going to say exactly when or exactly where. But just keep your eyes peeled for
Chucko from Los Angeles TV, not Chucko from the Barnum and Bailey Circus. Yeah.