Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday.
Michael Carlson.
Did I say you could wish me a happy birthday yet?
So sorry birthday boy.
I tell you when you can come in and say happy birthday to me.
Now you may say happy birthday to me.
Thank you.
No, I'm just joshing.
I'm just joking around here.
It's podcast, the ride, the second gate.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yes.
Uh, we are Scott free today.
This is probably Scott will be back very soon.
Very, very, very soon at this point.
Um, and today's episode and he hates to miss the idea of this, but he's going
to miss my birthday shot, which is a tradition now on podcast, the ride,
where we choose a topic that is a little, I guess, indulgent, not that
the show is an indulgent in general, but these are a little extra indulgent.
I feel, yeah, the birthday boy takes a lead and in most cases, the other
hosts are surprised by what they're.
Yes.
That is a, that is a thing we've been doing lately where it's
a little bit of a surprise.
Now last year, I didn't know what I wanted to do until the night before.
Okay.
And I'll say this today.
I didn't know what I wanted to do until an hour and a half ago.
Oh my God.
I had an idea in my head that I was going to maybe do a Charlie Rose.
I shouldn't use Charlie Rose because he's canceled a Charlie Rose interview
of you today for my birthday.
Oh my God.
That is the definitive Jason Sheridan interview that is somehow
indulgent for you, even though that would have been a lot about me.
Exactly.
And it would have been theme park, you know, there would have been
theme park stuff in there, but I said, ah, it's not, I don't, I have too much.
I was like, I need more prep.
I need more prep time.
I need to write.
I prepare.
Like, uh, one of the great interviewers would, uh, Joe Rogan, um, Larry King,
you know, the greats, all the greats.
Uh, so I did not have enough time to do it, but one day, maybe when we sit down,
I'll give the, I'll, this will be the definitive Jason Sheridan, be the
frost Nixon interview of Jason Sheridan.
So I was like, ah, what else am I going to do?
There's all these ideas floating around.
This is what happened last year.
I was like, are we going to do Indiana Jones too, for my birthday?
Uh, we have obviously ended up doing that later in the year.
Yeah.
Um, what else, what else there could be?
I I've been trying to concoct a game show for a long time.
Okay.
Something probably to do live, but I kind of figured something out
that I think is fun, but then I was like, well, I want to do that with like
guests and with maybe a panel of, of deciders of experts.
And you want a whole audience to go like, whoopie.
It's basically the newlywed game.
Yeah.
Okay.
No.
Um, yes.
So I was like, I can't do that today.
So I dug, I dug back into the archives of club three of things I like.
And I thought also what would be something that Scott wouldn't want to do.
And I came to one conclusion and one conclusion only Dan Ackroyd unplugged
on UFOs, this, uh, somewhat off discussed, uh, very cheaply made documentary
where one guy goes in interviews, Dan Ackroyd about UFOs on the set
of Christmas with the cranks.
The Christmas movie that Dan Ackroyd made, I guess almost 15 years ago or
something at this point, and Dan Ackroyd sits behind his desk, chain smokes
while wearing a brightly colored vest.
They love it when you chain smoke in those, uh, production trailers
in those dressing rooms.
Yeah.
So today you and I will go through the hour in 20 minutes.
It's like, uh, will we get to all of it?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Uh, if Scott were here, he'd say, uh, I hope you don't get to any of it.
Um, but he's not, it's my birthday.
So let's talk a little UFO is my history.
I guess I've always liked UFOs in general, but in the last so many years, I am a
little more invested in the idea that something strange is going on.
Yeah.
I always thought it was fun, but with all the different, there's like been many
different people that work for the government that have now basically on record said
like, yeah, we saw a bunch of weird shit.
Some of them are very casual about it.
Like, Oh, I was in a fighter jet and there's a, I saw something in the
distance that moved in a way that I cannot explain.
We don't have engines that can, you know, shoot a craft up and down that fast.
Can't change direction that fast.
And it also goes, uh, swings all the way to, uh, yeah, we've made contact with
aliens, there have been people killed by aliens.
We've recovered alien craft, uh, Boeing and other companies have this somewhere
in a warehouse and they've tried to like reverse engineer it to steal the technology.
Right.
So there's a lot of different, interesting stuff.
And I feel like it's becoming more and more mainstream.
It's definitely becoming less of a fringe theory and more of a, like, there's
plenty of people just saying this that seem credible, perhaps they're not,
but they seem credible, whatever.
The speculation is fun.
So I guess what I'm saying is, uh, I bought this DVD a long time ago.
I remember when you got it.
Yeah.
I remembered you, uh, on that TV, we're, we're skipping around on the DVD.
Like you were like, I just got this DVD and you were like showing it to a bunch of us.
And I got it cause it's funny.
Like it is funny.
And it wasn't like, Oh my God, you guys got to see this.
I believe everything in it, but it's funny.
And with Dan Aykroyd, I think Evan Susser and I were talking about this.
And I think he has a good point, uh, about Dan and other people that have made
stuff we like is that the, uh, the deep dive interest that Dan has in ghosts
and in aliens is the reason is like the secret sauce to why Ghostbusters is good.
Sure.
Dan Aykroyd like knew how the PKE made her work in his head.
I, yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, so what I also like about this Dan Aykroyd thing is you're seeing the mind,
this guy who, look, he, he gave us the blues brothers.
He gave us the cone heads, uh, and he gave us Ghostbusters.
So crystal head vodka, crystal head vodka, which also, if you're not following
him on X or wherever he posts, he has this very interesting way of posting
that also was a promotion for his vodka, where he says that he's going to crack
a head in celebration and that is his phrase.
I assume you're looking it up now.
Well, I was looking up the name of his history channel show because I can
never remember the unbelievable with Dan Aykroyd, right?
So like this is, you know, Gene Hackman recently passed away and this is how
he's eulogized by Dan Aykroyd, uh, pouring two headshots, one in sorrow,
one in celebration for the loss and for the life and career of that great
Gene Hackman.
So he's cracking a head.
Cracking a head.
Or pouring, well, he's pouring two headshots, um, but he was cracking
a head for the, uh, SNL 50th anniversary, which he was not a part of.
He was not there.
No.
Um, and then he wrote, he wrote cracking all heads, original Aurora and Onyx,
which are the different types of crystal head vodka with friends in heightened
anticipation of the Eve of SNL's 50th celebration.
So he cracked all heads.
What's he there?
Did you see him in like, uh, oh, he wasn't.
He wasn't.
And I'll tell you why after when we're off the air.
Cranks too.
Yeah.
Electric Boogaloo.
So, you know, before we get started, I forgot, actually, I told Scott what we
were doing, um, and he sent a message, uh, and I want to read it here.
He wrote, I know this is Mike's birthday shot, but not having to do this UFO
episode is better than any birthday present I've ever received.
Thank you, Michael.
Happy birthday to me, says Scott.
So he is thrilled to not be talking UFOs.
The UFOs is interesting.
I am, it is, I understand why he doesn't want to talk about like Brian
Setzer or Billy Joe Armstrong, but I am confused why he doesn't want to talk
UFOs and I am being sincere.
I think, yeah, it's interesting.
He seems like a particularly like, um, um, that the topic is repellent.
And it's interesting because it's, I don't know.
It's fun to me because it also can provide, it's not only fun on a level of
like, well, what's really going on, but it is also fun because there's so
many fun aliens in pop culture.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
So like, it feels like it's attached to a lot of different avenues of discussion.
And he's always making those little mashed potato mountains.
So I thought he would love it.
That is true.
I mean, he's real.
He's a real like Dana Scully when it comes to UFOs.
Well, I want to believe though.
Well, we want to believe.
Uh, I just, uh, funny note, the official history channel page for the
unbelievable with Dan Aykroyd show has a very funny image of his literal mind
being like an explosion on top of his forehead and he looks like Ray Liotta
in, uh, the Hannibal movie where he gets his head cut off and you can see his
brains and then his brains get eaten.
Uh, it looks like Dan Aykroyd is like blowing his stack or it's like
he saw like a, like a sexy lady walk into the beach and his head exploded.
Anyway, I don't know why Scott doesn't want to enjoy the UFOs,
the Dan Aykroyd UFO stuff.
Um, but here we go and we're going to jump around and so right away we have
the most like Apple, like video editing software from 2006 ass graphics you've
ever seen, uh, uh, and the first thing says Gravitron Productions.
I like that.
Oh, it's Gravi- excuse me.
It's Graviton Productions, which I don't know what else they've produced,
but Dan Aykroyd unplugged on UFOs.
Basically this does look like, like the Fox show in the late 90s, early 2000s,
where they would bombard you with different close-up video of just
like blurry lights in the distance.
Um, and with, with scary music, you know, you're like, oh God, yeah,
something's going on out there, but if you really slow it down, are all of
these videos actual UFOs?
I don't know.
You also get David B.
Sarita is the name of the guy and the guy you'll, you'll hear interviewing Mr.
Aykroyd.
Um, I'm just hoping early on when we see Danny, he's lightened up a cigarette,
potentially in silhouette.
Well, it is very, you'll see.
So it says millions of people worldwide claim to have seen UFOs.
Dan Aykroyd is one of them, which is, I'll give them that.
That is a very good intro for this.
Yeah.
That is exciting because you're like, okay, yeah, millions of people have seen
them, but have any of the original not ready for primetime players seen them?
And the answer is yes, that one of them has, and it's Dan Aykroyd.
2001 was a real space Odyssey for me.
Instead of flying on a spaceship to the moon, he doesn't need light
a cigarette for the first time to talk about UFOs.
That's when I knew I had to sit him down in front of a camera and just
when I'm talk about the truth, because if I didn't, no one would believe
we had this amazing conversation.
It's funny.
He brings up 2001 because he does sound like hell the robot from that movie.
Now what's great about Aykroyd is that he always like, seems like he's in character,
but yeah, they get them, they get them lighten up a cigarette with a match too.
Yes.
Which is really good.
He's not doing a lighter.
He's got a match and he's behind a desk.
So it is like he's playing a character, but I do want to reiterate that he is
wearing a red vest and a red and green checkered shirt because it's Christmas
time in the movie, Christmas with the cranks.
So they fade out.
One time I had this long conversation with Dan Aykroyd about UFOs and I thought
it was like Einstein was hiding inside of a comic genius, just so that if he told
us the real truth, he wouldn't have to believe it.
If Einstein had told us UFOs were real, would we have believed him?
He never spoke about it.
So David Sarita is doing his commentary already and he's saying that Dan Aykroyd
is a genius and you know, we don't maybe take him seriously because he's such a
funny guy and he's been in so many comedies or whatever, but then he also
says that he's like Einstein.
I'm trying to follow the logic here, but would we have believed Einstein if
Einstein told us about UFOs?
Well, he never talked about it.
Never?
I don't know.
Did Einstein ever talk about it?
I guess I should have done some research and figure out if Einstein was ever
weighing in on the topic of UFOs or UAP.
I'm not sure, but David says, David's a guy who's interested in UFOs, I assume,
but one of my favorite things about this video, and I guess I encourage anyone to
put this on and watch at your own pace as well, but David's voiceover and
commentary, I really, I enjoy that.
I like it too.
Hey, did you know Christmas with the Cranks is a screenplay by Chris Columbus?
I did not know that.
I didn't know that either.
I mean, I guess that makes some sense.
Based on Skipping Christmas by John Grisham.
Really?
Yeah.
But are you a Grisham guy?
I was never a Grisham guy.
No.
It seems like a mistake for you.
Yeah, maybe.
It seems like you were a white Grisham.
All right, let's go.
But Dan Aykroyd speaks about UFOs as if he were a full professor on the subject.
So now we get a video with another title.
You think the movie has started already, but it is not.
Then you go to a title card here that says, Aykroyd's Mind Probe.
And why it's got not what it was.
Well, I don't know.
I think he would have been happy to do this.
I don't think he wants to hear about me talk about how it could, like
interdimensional beings are visiting us.
Or it could be us from the future or think, like, I don't think he wants
to hear that type of thing.
I do think he would have liked Aykroyd's Mind Probe, which is just, again, we're
only two minutes into this thing, so we may not get through all of it, but I,
so I guess he's just saying, I'm going to ask Dan Aykroyd questions, but he
has set it up very alien-esque.
He's going to probe, which generally when you think of aliens and probing,
it's a rectal probe.
Oh, sure.
Generally speaking, as far as I know with aliens, it's, they put like a alien
piece of technology in your butt.
Does Aykroyd at some point, like take a moment and just like hits the harmonica
just to like recollect, like re-center himself.
I'm probably swinging, I'm taking a big swing on that.
Yeah, I don't think he does.
And I don't think he ever like sings the blues or something.
I don't think he goes, like he takes a call from, from Jim Belushi or
something and goes, yeah, we got it.
Like they go over dates for future blues brothers performance.
I don't think that happens, but I don't know.
I, you know, I don't remember all of it.
So perhaps I'm wrong.
Uh, so here we go into Aykroyd's Mind Probe and this graph, yeah, this
graphic is amazing.
We should do, when we interview anybody, we should do like a graphic like this.
If we ever do video again, and we should be like, if Griffin's on the episode,
it should be Griffin's Mind Probe.
And then we start asking him questions.
Griffin, real quick, could you just, it's a, just take this American spirit
and this match and just, you don't have to inhale just, but like light it real
cool, you know, Griffin, would you crack ahead, light this cigarette because
we're going to give you a mind probe.
I want to try to figure out how many times you said crack ahead and add up.
Like that would be 50 bottles of vodka.
Like has he drank 50 or is it just a phrase?
He should have cracked ahead for this episode.
See?
Yeah.
Damn it.
You got to drive home though.
That's a good point.
I'm at my home.
We are in, yes, we are at your home.
So you could have cracked ahead.
No problem.
Yeah.
And all three of the different ones, the other two original.
Uh, okay.
Aykroyd's Mind Probe.
You know, how did you get started in UFOs?
What sparked your interest?
What was the first thing that you can remember that happened to you that made
you, uh, you know, ponder the question?
Well, I was born in July, 1952 and, uh, I guess about, uh, maybe when I was eight
years old, I found a magazine, a life magazine with a picture of the UFOs from
that sighting on the cover, uh, with a big inquiry, uh, you know, what, what are
these UFOs?
Then I saw the day the earth stood still as a, as a kid.
And, uh, I mean, that was a film that was directly related to maybe some of the
motives for visitations from other planets.
This is a common thing with, with UFOs and UAPs is where, you know, the reason
aliens or the other creatures might be interested in us is because of now we're,
you know, pumping so much carbon into the atmosphere and we're threatening each
other with nuclear weapons.
We've detonated nuclear weapons.
So he is, he's definitely on the same page as that.
Um, I, that always felt like kind of a weird explanation to me where it's like,
oh, uh, uh, aliens wouldn't be interested in us unless we were on the brink of
destruction.
Cause like we were making, like, people were doing cool stuff on the earth before
this, they weren't interested in like Shakespeare's plays.
Yeah.
Alien would be interested in a play.
I mean, I guess they don't understand the language, but if they were
sophisticated to be like, you know what?
Some, some people are writing cool books and they're making some cool plays.
Have you seen this painter?
It's like Michelangelo, Michelangelo.
He's painting some cool stuff on earth.
We should go visit it.
Like, I don't quite believe the idea that they're only aliens or whoever.
Let's interdimensional travels only interested in us because in the last
hundred years, our energy consumption went up.
I just saw a post the other day, I forgot whether it was Twitter and blue sky,
but there is a Wikipedia entry on this.
Do you know about the Zimbabwe, the aerial school UFO incident?
It's called the kids, the kids claim they were, they saw UFOs and some of
them communicated telepathically.
I had never heard of this.
Yes.
This is like, this is one of these events when this is real.
This is not a joke.
This in the not 1994.
This is one of those events where multiple people had the same story after
it happened, because like mostly with this UAP UFO stuff, it's like somebody
gets visited or they see one and it's one person's story generally, if they
were abducted or whatever, but this is an incident where a bunch of people had
the same story and they all matched.
Their stories basically match.
Well, and they stuck to it.
Right.
All their lives, you know?
Yes.
I, I, I am wondering, and maybe later in the documentary, they get to this
acroid names, all those big world events.
Yeah.
Well, do they address that?
Like, is it, there's also the theories that, oh, UFOs are a distraction.
This is distracting you from wars, from arms sales, from poverty.
Well, there's, I mean, this, we're not getting through this whole thing.
Uh, uh, what's interesting is there's people then that have the theory that,
yes, the, the talk of UAPs, especially the recently are like Psy Ops to throw
you off what's really going on.
Right.
Tom DeLong from Blink-182 is a big UFO guy.
He has a song called Aliens Exist.
It was on Enema, the state 20 years ago.
And he has had like contact with government officials.
This is how much like actors and musicians like get access to things.
Cause as soon as, you know, he's writing about aliens, he's talking about aliens.
He's contacted by, this is from his own words.
He's contacted by people in the government and like he, he has interactions
with Hillary Clinton's, what campaign manager, John Podesta, where they're
talking UFOs, I think it was in the leaks and the email leaks.
Um, so he now presents himself as an actual expert on this topic.
There's many different podcasts you can listen to some things where he goes, I
can't talk about that because it's classified.
He's like, well, it's a gauge on Podesta.
What are all those pizzas come at?
Big Kong, you know, that's satanic performance artists on take off your
pants and jackets and all the great Blink-182 songs.
Um, he is also has to say many times now on podcasts, I can't talk about
that because it's classified, but okay.
So just to be clear, Tom DeLong's history channel show is called Unidentified
inside America's UFO investigation.
Yes.
There's so much Tom DeLong alien stuff out there.
And then I've also read though, from other people that go Tom DeLong is
being used by the government, they're feeding him misinformation.
So to throw other people off of what's really going on, which I don't know
what's really going on, what their theory is about what the actual reality is.
But some people then yes, believe that Tom DeLong is a tool now being used
by the government for 20 years to, I don't know, spread fake news
about aliens, I guess.
Right.
Um, so yes, anytime you go down these weird rabbit holes, you get to the
point where everybody has a theory about how one level deeper is actually the
reality.
That's what's always like every, every, you know, QAnon people, whatever
they think Trump or whatever is doing God's work or whatever.
But then there's other people that go, no, no, no, no, Trump is actually a
Psyop.
It's a one, like he doesn't even know he's being played too.
So you really can always go one level, one level deeper with what's actually
going on.
The human brain is very bad at remembering things, being able to all agree on
something, which is why some of those alien stories are particularly
interesting if everyone has a very similar accounting of events.
Because generally if you, if something happens in a crowd of people, there's
going to be like 10 different stories.
Right.
The Rashomon.
People really don't, the brain is bad at memory.
Like remember when I remembered that you wanted a warm Walnut.
Uh, yes.
That was not, that didn't happen.
Wet Walnuts or pop ups Walnut barrel.
Pop ups Walnut barrel is what I wanted, but I, I just, I went back to listen to
the episode because I accused you of wanting a warm Walnut and it never
wasn't in the episode.
Like my brain totally shorted out there.
Did not even remember what was going on.
You might've been confused.
Just the phrase chestnuts roasting on an open fire is in your subconscious.
Right.
But weeks later, after doing that episode, I then put it in my mind that you would
get a Walnut out of a big barrel and then you would want to heat it up.
You would want to put a warm Walnut in your mouth on Christmas Eve.
So, but that was wrong.
That was wrong.
So, so yeah, I would have probably been bad at recalling exactly what happened
if an UFO landed and approached me and my fellow students.
Yeah.
I'm guessing.
Um, all right.
We're about minute three here.
I think that in terms of the extra terrestrial machines that are coming
and going, that may be maybe a part of their motivation.
I cannot emphasize enough how the graphics are amazing and shitty.
There's been so many varieties of them.
Yes.
We got some sound public domains, sound effects in there as well.
Yeah, I know.
It's like, and like Dan is trying to talk and he's like, like fighting
for volume, uh, with the sound effects.
Uh, it's like, it's like you are on space mountain or you're like in
tomorrow land and you're hearing those noises.
It also kills the credibility of the documentary.
Like if he's really just like talking to a guy who seems to know a lot
of stuff, which is Dan Aykroyd, like just let him talk.
Like we don't need these like beeping boops to remind people of Star Trek.
Sure.
The sighting that took place over Mexico recently where, uh, drug
surveillance, uh, twin engine, turboprop plane was at altitude, uh, taking
pictures of possible smuggling routes.
And, um, they photograph with their infrared cameras, 11, uh, unidentified
object, so I, this is interesting to me.
And I said this already.
It feels like Dan is in character.
Like ashes, his cigarette with such purpose.
Yeah.
Is that like just a long time smoker doing it and a long time actor
knowing he's on camera?
I guess maybe that's what it is.
He's just too dynamic.
A performer is that he cannot help, but ashes cigarette in a way that is cool.
Now you're more of a cigarette guy than I am.
I maybe had two cigarettes in my life, three cigarettes in my life.
I not quite a while.
Right.
But you've asked more cigarettes than I have.
Now, does that mean you've asked 40 cigarettes and I've asked two?
Right.
Perhaps that is what it means.
Have I also asked poorly?
Have I, do I think you can ask as cool as Dan Kroyd?
No, I don't think so.
Did I ask a cigarette at San Diego Comic-Con in the smoking section of the
hotel and I accidentally got some of it on the shorts I was wearing that were
very clearly polyester cause they melted a hole and then like, you wait, they
melted a hole in your shorts and then there was like hard plastic and I was
like, well, I'm just going to throw these away.
This was a three pack.
You haven't brought this up on the show before that you
melted your shorts at Comic-Con.
Right.
So it was just, it was loose shorts.
It was excess fabric on the inside of the leg.
I spill stuff all the time.
I put on my Ninja Turtle slice, slice baby shirt with Raphael and
there was a big like stain.
I don't even remember where it came from, but it had just been washed.
So I was like, well, I've ruined a shirt and I don't even know what happened.
So I'm just saying, I'm not trying to put you on a spot, but there is
something extra funny about it burning through in a cartoon style way.
And leaving a hole that wasn't just singed.
It was like, oh, that's hard plastic now.
Cause this is like, this is, this is plastic.
Was it a whole thing?
Did you go, ah, like, was it a like scared thing?
Oh, no, I didn't notice it was night time.
I wasn't paying attention.
So maybe you were like nonchalant in a cool way, like Aykroyd, like no
problem with Dan Aykroyd, like drop some ash on his pants and it burned
through and he didn't even like react to it.
As nonchalant as you can be ashing a cigarette poorly, sitting in a
wheelchair, uh, in between canned cocktails at Comic-Con.
Hey, I don't think you could, I think you could look cool if you were sort of
leaning over and you were in a relaxed manner.
Sure.
I think you look as cool as, as detective Aykroyd here, but I do, I
give David Sirita, I've already forgotten his name again.
I give him credit when he was putting this together, cause he knew the
smoking was cool.
Yeah.
And I don't advocate anyone's smoke, but unfortunately smoking does look cool.
On film, in real life, even if you're a Comic-Con and you, and you burn your pants,
burn a big hole in your pants, it's still cool.
The connection on this cigarette smoking man in the X-Files is in the shadow.
So he's kind of cool.
Right.
This guy must've been an X-Files fan and he probably put two and two together.
Yeah.
So anyway, so yeah, they're talking about this incident with 11 different
UFOs in the sky from 2004.
Um, and it is like, I understand skepticism about this because you do
look at this video and you go, it's 11 lights in the sky.
What am I looking at here?
Like if you don't want to believe, I understand how you would be
disinterested in this topic to some degree.
But also why are there lights in the sky?
Well, of course that's what I say.
Yeah.
That's what you say.
That's what I say.
I say, why are these 11 lights there?
They're moving in a one, but to a, to a Scully, to a Dana Gairdner, we could
call him Dana Scully, of course, Gillian Anderson's character on X-Files.
Um, yes.
He says, well, he's 11 lights.
It could be anything.
What are you talking about?
11 lights.
It's a sub-reflection, 11 reflections.
People are, 11 people sunbathing with that big reflective thing and that's
bouncing off the, the something in the sky and it's hitting the plane.
It's 11 different reflections.
That's what he would say.
You know, these were objects that couldn't be seen by the naked eye, but
were visible on the infrared cameras.
Well, the United States Air Force, after the, uh, the news appeared in, in
America and it was covered on CNN and Fox, the footage was shown on Fox.
It was shown on CNN and in the Valley Daily News on the front page had a big
headline UFOs with a question mark and it had pictures from that sighting.
And of course the United States Air Force had to respond and
they said it was a swamp gas.
So Dan is saying that the government's official position was swamp gas.
Got into the sky and obviously he's being a little glib.
He's, he doesn't believe that explanation.
Swamp gas, weather balloons.
Those are often.
Yeah.
Now, swamp gas, what do you know about swamp gas?
Only, only in the instances of like, oh, it was actually swamp gas.
Don't worry about it.
So that's all you, so you were not, because swamp gas
does feel like a thing you would have said.
Well, you know, when I was a kid, we'd always run into some swamp.
Well, you capture the swamp gas in a plastic shopping bag, you know,
and you try to save it like, you know, and then when the swamp gas coming,
you knew the fireflies were far behind.
We would keep, we would keep a jar of swamp gas in the house.
It would ward off evil spirits.
Got a mirror badge and the boy scouts for catching the swamp gas.
We would catch a swamp gas in our mouth sometimes and swallow it.
You know, I think the nineties, I did actually borrow an
audiobook from the library about the rise of conspiracy theories in the
nineties that I haven't, I haven't started yet.
Um, I think it's called when the clock broke, but, um, wasn't until much later
in life that I learned like, okay, I, I knew like, I was really into the X files.
I was really in this conspiracy theory stuff and alien stuff,
alien autopsy, all that.
Uh, wasn't much older that some of that stuff, what the crank version,
like cranks, not Christmas with the cranks, not Chris with the cranks,
regular, like Mooney, John Birch society types, kooky people, kooky people
were using, they live a type like lizard people and stuff that was actually
coded anti-Semitism.
Oh, sure.
So, and, uh, yeah, I didn't know about that until I was much older and I was
like, oh, this is taking some of the fun away, but then Hollywood came roaring
back because they just kept the conspiracy, you know, stuff going.
Or so with shows and movies and stuff.
I the Mel Gibson movie conspiracy theory.
Uh, well, yeah, I remember watching that on like the network TV premiere.
And that one, he, his character is right about everything, but also like
enemy of the state, the late great Gina Hackman, uh, Will Smith, Jean
Hackman kind of unofficially playing his character from the conversation
and that, I believe, I don't know if they can officially call him that.
Was that the idea?
But I didn't know that.
I think that is, that's what I always heard.
Oh, interesting.
I have not seen either of those in a very long time.
It's weird with conspiracy theories because conspiracy theories, like you
can make stuff up about anything.
And I think a lot of conspiracy theories are the human brain trying to organize
things in a neat way, trying to make things make sense because in life, stuff
just doesn't make sense.
Shit happens all the time.
It's really, it's too much, too much information, especially now for our
brains to handle.
So conspiracy theories, oftentimes trying to put things in a neat little box
and it explains a way and it explains that, you know, all the bad stuff that
happens, like the government is so, the secret government is so, um, um, planned
out about things and there's only a couple of people, but they're the ones
that actually control everything and they control it to a T and with the
reality, I think with a lot of things, it's just, uh, people are lazy and kind
of dumb and it's chaos and you know how hard it is for like you to finish your
paper in college, you finish it the night before you're not like so engaged in
it, but you're like, I should, I got to do stuff.
That's how everybody is with almost every job.
Oh yeah.
That's how everything works in the world and a lot of things, it's just chaos.
A lot of stuff doesn't make sense and that's unfortunately the way we have to
live and it's easier to think that everything is connected, that there's a
couple of people really controlling everything in a hardcore way and there's a
trail of bread crumbs that you just have to unlock everything.
It's like a treasure hunt.
It's like going in an escape room.
It's like, oh, oh, if we, uh, if we answer this riddle and we follow it to this
place, we can uncover what's actually going on and then my life will be good.
Then I will be happy.
I won't be chaos.
You know, we, we were talking at, I, I'm not sure the episode's out yet, but we're
talking about cruise ships and a thing I meant to say, but I forgot to on that
episode.
Sometimes like scale, the scale of stuff freaks me out.
Like if I think about like, okay, there's a grocery store down the street and
that's a chain and there's dozens of that chain and they all have the same stuff.
And where does all that stuff come from?
Comes from factories.
Where is the food grown?
Where are the animals, uh, slaughter, you know, and like, uh, similarly like,
okay, cruise ships, how many cruise ships are in the ocean at any given time?
Well, there's like 50,000 boats in the ocean period at any given time.
And it's like, just trying to think about making that scale.
Make sense is like, okay.
I don't, I think I'm done thinking about this sun tapped, you know,
I think maybe, and correct me if I'm wrong, but I think on some level you're
thinking about how mysterious it is to be alive because you keep going out.
That's what I, because I don't, I just, you know, whatever little world you have
is nice and it's fun to just exist and like, well, are my friends and my
family and the things I do.
And then once in a while you kind of remember that, oh, the world exists.
And it's very overwhelming.
Like it can, it, depending on what information you're receiving, but like
there were fires weeks ago and I'm looking at fire maps and people I know
are, are having to evacuate and I'm leaving and I start to feel very small
in that moment when you quickly, when you see how quickly like a whole town
can get like washed away or fired away, whatever you call it.
You go, oh shit, we are fragile.
This sucks.
I don't want to think about this.
Like, like you start to look and you go, God, it was tiny.
And then you start to, I, me personally, I started to think about my own existence
and it's too much, it's too much to actually have that information, to think
about how small you are, where you are, you existing at this very short window
on this planet.
And we don't know what's going on.
I have to reiterate that.
What is going on?
Why are we here?
It doesn't make sense.
No one can explain it.
Uh, so the one thing for, for our, uh, tiny little world, I always, I always
laugh when I see people complaining.
The complaints about theme parks, like, well, this track, people
tried to escape the world is a fantasy world.
People trying to escape their everyday lives.
And we're talking about all this, all this shit.
And you're like, yeah, of course people want to escape their daily lives.
Like, this is just too much.
It's a balance because like, sometimes you're like, Oh, this person's too
worried or they're too invested.
Or, you know, there's definitely the song of the South splash mountain people
online that won't let it go.
We're like, let it like, just get, get on with your lives.
Like it's okay that you like that ride and now it's a different ride.
Like that's fine.
But then of course, on the other hand, it's like, uh, obsessing about stuff
you like is part of being a fan of things and is hopefully for you fun.
Fun.
And it's certainly human.
Yes.
You know, and it's certainly a thing that people bond over and
connect people in the best cases.
Right.
Cause there's plenty of stuff you'd be like, you are wasting your time
thinking about this or speculating on this or explaining to somebody for the
hundredth time while you don't like this certain movie, but it's fun.
That's what I would say, depending on what it is.
And you know, somebody could correct me if I'm wrong, but like, you know,
caring about dumb stuff is like fun and a distraction.
And as long as it's not ruining you and as long as you're not posting about it
24 seven online and people would be like, like, Oh, we better check in on him.
Well, sometimes people get so down a rabbit hole and they just keep posting.
It's like, Hey man, did you finish processing this?
Like, did you try looking at it from another angle or take other
stuff into consideration?
Yeah.
Or, yeah, I don't know.
Everyone, everyone's different, but yeah, I don't the best days is when I just
like look at like toy news and can watch like a video about the theme park.
Like theme park Patton that's been made by a park and you can speculate
what that ride is going to be.
I don't really want to deal with your reality of being alive, but you know,
that's what, uh, that's unfortunately the reality of our world.
You gotta go back and forth and I don't want to, as my daughter says, I don't
want to, which she's imitating a muffin from Bluey.
Have we talked about this for years?
I thought Bluey was the dad.
But Bluey is one of the kids.
That is correct.
And the dad is named a, a, a bandit.
Bandit.
Yeah.
Yes.
Which is also a great name for a dog.
It is.
And Blue, look, Bluey, uh, my daughter wants to watch Bluey 24 seven.
It just has a hold on kids.
And it is good.
Like it is better than a lot of stuff for that age.
So I give my daughter credit for liking something that is quality.
Somebody we know said that their similar age kid is into Paw Patrol and that's
all they want to watch.
And this person said, thank you.
You should be very thankful that your daughter is into Bluey and Paw Patrol.
It's just history, right?
Cause I'm sure you and I just wanted to watch Ninja Turtles.
Yeah.
But I would say Bluey is probably a more consistent show than Ninja Turtles.
Yeah, I would, yeah, I would, I would think so.
We did try, I have tried a few times on different screens, trying to get
Garfield to watch Bluey cause there are videos online of dogs loving Bluey.
I think because the, the colors, the gradient, I think they pop for them.
Yeah.
But our dog, Edwin does not care about television, but my parents' dog loves
television to some degree, but hates when an animal is on the screen.
Their dog, if they, if, if my parents' dog sees a cartoon dog on TV, he
will lose his mind barking.
I've never seen anything like it.
You cannot watch Lady and the Tramp on Disney Plus, the animated version, or
else my parents' dog will go insane barking.
Just seeing it.
Seeing it.
Wow.
Thinks that's a real dog.
And I was like, does this dog have the best vision of any dog in America?
Like that's so wild.
I get it.
Maybe if it's a live action dog on a big HD screen.
Sure.
Maybe he thinks a dog is in like a little box.
You know, a nice thing when, before Jane and I lived together, she said that
Garfield would occasionally perk up if she put the podcast on and hear my voice.
Oh, well that's nice.
And that was very sweet.
I thought.
Was she being serious though?
She was being serious.
Okay.
Come on.
She didn't make that up.
No.
I believe it.
I, you know, I just never have had a dog that likes podcasts.
I'll be honest.
A dog's not responding to podcasts.
I think it's purely my, because it was me.
Okay.
So it would be, it would be interesting to see.
Can we, I don't want, it's too, too, we're in too deep to test it out, but I
would love to test it.
Oh yeah, that's right.
You're already in the room.
He saw me.
I would love to do a test to see if Garfield could tell your voice and what
it means would Garfield like perk up and the tail start going or would it be just
like, what would be the sign that Garfield noticed at your voice?
Would he be panting?
I think he would just sit up or like, yeah, I think maybe some of that.
He pees on the phone to mark the territory.
Oh, don't get started on him being inside.
Like then they got older.
They just have accidents all the time.
Where, when was the last time he peed in here?
Uh, hours ago.
Oh, where I'm sitting.
No, you're not sitting there.
There is a puppy pad over in the kitchen.
Uh, our old dog has liver problem.
This is man, Scott really missed out today.
Uh, our old dog has liver problems, but we're not sure what they are.
And I don't think there's so serious, but,
Oh, you know, I forgot to tell you, uh, I, um, I was, cause you and Scott did a
post office when I was, we did.
Yes.
And I was like, Oh, I said to Jane, would it be funny if I just
respond to all the questions?
And I had forgotten.
She's like, Oh, that episode was a lot about kids.
And I was like, would it be funny if I just subbed in every question?
I just crossed out kid and wrote Jason.
Where do you take your Jason when he's having a fit?
When he's really crying, not for us, it's a hot dog stand or the ice cream
stand, you know, are you revealing that Jane still listens to all the episodes?
She didn't listen to all of them, but she did listen to that.
I think she was checking in, you know, while you were gone.
Yeah.
Okay.
So she just wanted to monitor it to make sure we were only saying good things.
Cause we were just trashing you while you were gone.
Oh, good bereave and getting roasted while on bereavement leave.
It wouldn't have been too insensitive.
Yeah.
Uh, no, I think we were nice.
I don't know.
Mostly nice.
I would think, yeah.
Maybe we talked about that warm Walnut, but other than that,
that's fine.
Look, look what happened in the last hundred years.
We have the Wright brothers in at the turn of the century, taking off and
basically a fabric and wood aircraft.
In 1969, we have, uh, lunar expeditions in the year 2004.
We have massive airplanes being built out of alloys and, uh, and graphite
and these, this big ship that air Airbus is building the new Boeing plane.
So in a hundred years from fabric and wood, we've come to, you know,
advanced metallurgy, uh, fuel use and propulsion in just a hundred years.
Imagine what a culture could accomplish in a thousand years or 10,000 years.
They just keep making the seats smaller and smaller.
This was a good documentary.
It could have used you in there to add like a little aside once in a while.
Yeah.
Just, just chiming in about like, and where do all the coupons go?
Now I got to get apps and you don't get dinner on these flights either.
Are you kidding me?
There's no breakfast.
There needs to be a meal service.
You have to pay extra for it.
Come on, Dan.
I'm not paying for an airplane sandwich.
Are you kidding me?
And then you take a drag off your cigarette and the ash falls and
burns your pants right off.
Well, I was going to say, and they hate that on airplanes.
Yeah.
Did you, I did learn, I think I started following a pilot on YouTube or TikTok.
The reason airplane bathrooms still have, uh, ashtrays is they're like, well,
we don't want you to smoke, but if you're going to, if someone's fucking around,
we'd least want them to put it out somewhere safely and not start a fire.
Really?
That's what I are.
And now certainly some of these planes are older.
What pilot are you file a following on YouTube?
I'll have to find, let me find it.
What kind of content does this pilot do?
There is a pilot who talks about like, Oh, what is, why do you have to be there
this early?
Like why, why is the plane sitting there?
But it still takes an hour to get on.
Well, we have to do this and this.
Is the pilot like kind of an influencer pilot?
Like is on TikTok as well?
Kind of an influencer pilot.
Is he on, he's on Instagram, TikTok.
Probably Twitter or X or whatever.
I'm guessing is the pilot on only fans as well.
It's not a naked pilot.
It's not a standup.
That's a, have you encountered that?
Is that a standup?
You only fans has been sponsoring like standup tapings and trying to get people
on there because it essentially acts as Patreon.
So, right.
We may have to switch to only fans at a certain point if Patreon goes away.
If, if they ever, Oh my God.
There's porno anymore.
What's the name of this pilot?
I'm trying to find him.
There's multiple pilot that you follow.
No, just on if you search pilot YouTuber, we got, I forget the person's name, but
we, a few months ago, I suggested that no pilot would listen to podcast the ride.
I don't know why I just felt like too professional of a job to listen to our
nonsense, but we, a pilot did reach out and say that they listen to podcast the
ride.
So we do have a pilot in our audience.
Okay.
So I'm going to shout out to that pilot and all the pilots out there that
listened to podcast the ride.
Yeah.
Um, and let us know if you have some sort of a social media presence, um, um,
Instagram, only fans, whatever it is.
Uh, and then Jason will follow you.
I will make that pledge right now.
You tell me if that's wrong, that if we have a pilot in our audience and they are
on social media, you Jason Sheridan will follow them.
Uh, pro yeah, I probably will.
I mean, my subscriptions on YouTube are just out of control.
Like obviously a lot of theme park content, ordinary adventures, expedition,
theme park, right?
So Cal, Hoennson parks.
And then like pilot Pete or something.
I, a lot of, uh, old wrestling stuff.
Jeremy the pilot.
Yeah.
But I can't even like scroll any Silvio, the pilot to the pilot.
Oh, thank you.
Captain Steve.
That's S-T-E-E-V-E.
S-T-E-E-E-V?
No, S-T-E-E-V-E.
Captain Steve.
Can I take a look at him?
Sure.
Well, how old do you think he is?
Oh, he's older.
I would say in his forties or fifties.
No, that's, that's not that old.
I guess I don't know how old everyone.
I still think I'm like 25.
Uh, you know,
you are not, I'm just a little guy.
Oh, captain Steve.
Yeah.
Maybe captain Steve is in his fifties.
I'm not sure.
Um, okay.
So you, this is great.
I did not know you follow this.
I, this guy is very successful.
He's got like 360,000 subscribers and he's got like classic YouTube
thumbnail where he's like putting his hand on his chin thinking, and then
it'll say smoke in the cabin with an exclamation point.
And he's kind of making a thinking face.
Wow.
This is good.
I got to follow this guy.
I kudos to you for final following, finding this guy.
This is like an account.
Like I don't even watch a lot of the videos.
He just does so many shorts.
Is there anything where like, it's a little bit like, um, a trashier
thumbnail where it's like doodoo on the plane and captain Steve is
like holding his nose?
Uh, yeah, potentially.
PP, like PP on the floor.
And he's like looking at the floor.
Like he's kind of got his hands in the air.
Like I made PP on the floor.
There's one thumbnail where it says don't open the exit door.
Three exclamation points that he's holding his head to keep it from
not exploding like Dan Aykroyd puked on grandma and he's like holding
his tummy, like he's sick to his stomach.
I, uh, I want you to do stuff like this.
I'll tell you my, my goofiest plane moment.
I feel like I was, I was getting on a plane.
I was flying, I was traveling alone.
Um, someone had like a coffee bean or Starbucks, like frappuccino sort of thing.
Yeah.
They put it in the pocket of the chair and I like nailed it.
With my like quad or my, you know, uh,
Oh, as you were walking down the road.
Yeah.
Cause it's so narrow.
Even back then.
That is wild.
I just think I nailed it with a messenger bag and I'm like, why would you?
And I'm like, I'm really sorry.
I, if you want to drink or snack, I'll, I'll pay for it.
That was too nice of you to do that.
That was a while.
Well, people were loading in a person, put their coffee in the, did they
forget about it in the little, I think they just, they must've forgot about
have they ever been on a plane before?
Yeah.
I just, some people recline on a plane before we take off, which is not allowed,
but I've seen it happen a couple of times.
Well, my favorite is leaning forward, trying to get my bag under the seat in
front of me and someone reclines and just nails me in the head, like you
gotta and everything, like I said, those plants are so thin and shitty
plastic nowadays, you can really get nailed.
Have I said on the show, I'm anti recline?
I never, yeah.
Never do it recline.
I never recline.
Yeah.
I feel it.
I feel there's two, there's not enough room to do it.
I, it doesn't help me in any way.
I have some of those travel pillows, you know, with bean bags or I think we had
memory foam ones floating around.
I don't, I don't like them.
I, you know what, a DM us, uh, if you have a good pillow that actually
can make someone sleep, because I agree with you.
I've tried all the different pillows to sleep on a plane.
It doesn't work.
I just put it behind my bed, but it's the same as like balling up the
sweatshirt and putting it behind my bed.
I just pop-
Behind your head, you're saying?
Yeah.
I just put it-
Behind your bed.
Oh, behind my head.
You're pulling the seat, your bed, your sky bed.
Yeah.
My, no, I'm saying I just put some sort of fabric behind my head and like,
leave, you know, put my head back or something like that.
Um, but then those travel pillows are hard.
If you have noise canceling over your head, it just gets so much shit on you.
You know, I just popped two Xanax and go to like, uh, sleep.
Yeah.
Wow.
I've only ever done one.
Oh boy.
Usually I'm doing half.
Those 0.25s are really-
A lot.
Um, I don't want to blow on a breathalyzer.
I don't want to get in trouble with the authorities.
We have gotten through 10 minutes of this dumb special.
Did you think where we're going to get through?
No, no, no.
I'm just, I think it's, I think we've been good.
I mean, Mr.
Ackroyd is very knowledgeable and I would love to talk to him.
Uh, let's keep going for a little bit.
This just, I mean, really all this means is that we've gotten through
like one eighth of the special and we're going to have to go through more of it later.
As well.
And the planes of St.
Augustine and we have reverse engineered that technology today.
That's the theory.
Why aren't we using it in our military?
Why isn't it evident?
Well, I think, uh, I, I, again, I, as far as military applications, uh, maybe
they're, maybe they are being used already.
I'm not sure that, uh, the U S military would want to play that card right now.
So Dan is saying here.
It's a big tangent about the big hopping the air force.
Yeah.
You've probably heard this and I shortened whatever clip we just watched
because he goes on and on and on.
Uh, the question that's posed to him is why haven't we seen this technology?
If it's been, you know, harvested by the U S government or weapons manufacturers,
we would have seen evidence that our vehicles have, you know, similar
propulsion or something where they can go very fast, very slow or, or wherever
underwater, that's another thing with a lot of these UAPs and Ackroyd is,
uh, uh, suggesting that we have it.
We just haven't needed to show it yet, which I don't know.
It's interesting.
Cause I guess I understand what he's saying.
It would be pretty wild if, you know, like all of a sudden the blue
angels show was a little bit upgraded.
Uh, yeah, I mean, obviously stealth technology has been upgraded a lot.
Um, it's been 20 years and there are sound weapons that they've used in
battles and turned on protesters, uh, drones obviously, but, um, and the
machine that keeps mosquitoes out of Disney world.
Yeah, usually they got to use it for those bees, which we recently
talked about the bees that chased your family out of, out of Disney world.
Uh, um, but it's an interesting thing.
Cause I, I don't, basically Dan is saying that he thinks like, we're
not going to show it until we get attacked by aliens well, but then you
see the folly of like, uh, the air force bought a new jet, uh, and it's full.
It costs millions of dollars for one jet and the pilot can see, he has to rely
on the camera feed and it's full of problems that it's so you, you, you see
plenty of folly, but is that again, it's not a distraction that here's also
though profit, the profit motive is very strong with our country and a lot of
countries, so I feel like, okay.
They're like, all right, we're sitting on alien tech.
This is wild.
You basically can go like a hundred times the speed of a commercial aircraft.
This is amazing.
We could sell super fast flights to anywhere in the world.
Now this excites me even to talk about this because I don't like to fly.
If it could go in, like, if we could go in a super alien tech commercial
aircraft from here to Orlando in five minutes, in 10 minutes, I would be
in Orlando every weekend.
Yeah, I would be, I would be by co maybe by coastal.
We can go that fast.
So what I'm saying is I kind of think if they really had the technology, they
would have tried to apply it to something where they could have made a ton of money.
They're potentially bringing back the Concorde.
Oh, is that right?
London to New York in three and a half hours.
What does it take in a commercial flight?
What's that?
What?
How long does it take a regular commercial flight?
Doesn't it take eight hours?
Probably something like that.
Um, but I think this is just the Concorde from LA or Burbank
specifically to Orlando.
Oh, in probably industry interference.
Cause you're saying the reason, cause the Concorde is a very fast plane, right?
Is that correct?
It was very fast plane.
Yeah.
I think at that, you know, early nineties, it cost tens of thousands of dollars for a
ticket.
Okay.
So I can imagine now, but it would be like very noisy over if it flew over like land
by where people live.
I don't really know, but I know it as a reference for a very fast airplane in like
a movie or TV show, you know?
Okay.
Maybe that's your like thing.
You're like the Concorde influence.
I'm Mr. Concorde.
Mr. Concorde.
And you tell facts about the Concorde and you wear clothes like that.
The flight attendants would wear on the Concorde or the pilots.
Ooh, maybe.
Yeah.
Are you allowed to just wear a pilot's outfit on to an airplane?
Like, oh, I just rolled down the bed.
It was five AM.
I wasn't, I wasn't looking at what I put on.
I don't know.
I just pulled stuff out of the closet.
I think you have to be allowed to wear a pilot's outfit because other pilots sometimes
fly.
I've never flown on Halloween.
Can you be like a ghost?
Can you be a ghoulie or a zombie or something?
What would be?
Yeah.
What would be the problem?
I don't know.
A nerving other.
You mean like a Charlie Brown, some psycho, some psycho passenger got, grabbed the
like in plane, like communication thing was singing God bless America.
Yeah.
But I think that was a plane of mostly people coming back from like CPAC or
something.
Do people get thrown off planes if like they're showing too much skin?
Cause like, what if you're a sexy pilot and you're like, I don't know if I can
pull that off, but like if you're a sexy, if you say it's Halloween and you're
dressed up and you're going, you're flying to a Halloween party, you're going to
flying to Miami and you're going right from the airport to the Halloween party
at some club in Miami and you are a hot pilot.
That's your costume.
So you're going to be wearing like a little like crop top pilot shirt and like
a thong.
Is that a thing where they're like, Hey, could you put that blanket on and maybe
just change it in the bathroom when we're about the right.
Would you get through security?
That's a good question.
I bet you wouldn't.
I bet they would.
Yeah.
They would try to give you some pants or make you put pants on.
I think that'd be a little suspicious.
What if, okay.
Well, how short do the shorts have to be before they would tell you, you got it.
Get some longer shorts.
Can you go through security cheeks out or does it have to be at minimum
Lieutenant Dangle shorts?
From Reno 9-1-1.
Yeah.
Tom Lennon.
I bet Dangle could go through no problem with the length because he has
short shorts on, but he's okay.
His butt isn't hanging out.
Sure.
But they are very short shorts, but I think that would be okay.
Yeah.
But I think, I think if you're, I think it's probably at the discretion of a
few people at the checkpoints, if they determine there's too much cheek showing
for you to be on the airline.
It might read as suspicious.
Um, it would be suspicious or it would be distracting for passengers.
Distracting and weird.
And so they just chalk it up to like, sir, please come with us.
You know?
I bet, I bet, I bet, I bet if you wore a pilot's outfit, you could be fine.
I bet no one would bat an eye even on non holidays.
You know, it's funny.
And we've talked about this before is I was with my daughter at city
walk, as I often do, it's just a couple hour trip, uh, total.
And I always like seeing somebody clocking in at Walter's gate for work
on transformers because they're wearing full military outfit, but it looks
like a Halloween costume outfit.
Yeah, yeah.
But they dress, they dress up before coming into universal.
Are you hoping to catch Yoshi clocking in for one of those?
Yeah, that would be good.
I I'm more just sort of like, I like the idea that they're out in the world
before in full military outfit, but they're not necessarily service members.
Can you expand that out?
And it's like Marilyn Monroe clocking in Dracula and Frankenstein.
I would like having a cigarette break.
I did see Dracula.
Oh, oh, I've talked, I talked about this on the show before.
I saw Dracula on his break at city walk.
Oh, really?
Yes, because I clocked a guy I don't remember was a little while ago.
I, I'm sure I said this on the show.
I clocked an interesting looking guy and I was just like, that's kind of
interesting, like, is he wearing makeup?
I didn't put two and two together.
I just like clocked that he looked odd and he was walking and I think he had
a jacket on or whatever him and he was eating something.
And then I was in the park 30 minutes later, an hour later,
and he was in full Dracula outfit.
And I was like, Oh, I saw Dracula having lunch at Johnny Rockets.
Did he just have a polo and slacks?
He had a jacket covering.
Okay.
So it wasn't for whatever reason, it didn't read to me like Dracula.
I just, he looked unusual.
Jane has tall, I think as well.
Jane has talked about like when they would get a lunch break or just a
break break in between shows, they would often go from backs.
Their break room was kind of close to Walters gate and a water world.
So like the frog choir from Harry Potter would like partially lose their
outfits and go to the mini monster bubble tea.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Cause you just want to like, you're not going to, you don't want to be hounded.
You know, you're not on the clock.
Yeah.
So yes, that's, yes, that's what absolutely happened with Dracula.
I think I was texting you guys.
I was texting somebody to go, Oh my God.
Oh my God.
I saw Dracula eating lunch.
Holy shit.
Dracula was eating at Johnny Rockets.
Johnny Rockets also maybe on the chopping block and Jamba as well.
Supposedly I got some insight Intel that city walk Hollywood that those two are
going to close perhaps next because of the moving the security out from just
outside the universal entrance to the entrance to city wall.
I had yet there before.
I don't want to go to the fuck, go through security before I go to a
fucking mall, you know, I guess I, I like it having up before.
I mean, I'm surprised it's taken this long, but I was like, I've been saying
we're, we've been saying where we're going to dinner and anahitos for ages.
Dinner and lunch.
And I'm like, I don't, did you say dinner and lunch dinner or lunch?
Okay.
Uh, but I'm like, I don't want to go through a security corridor to
go like get a fucking enchilada.
You know, but when you're at the Disneyland resort all day and you're
going at back and forth, it is easier.
It is easier unless you go out grand California and you want to go somewhere.
That's true.
Go back in.
But if you're just popping in and out California eventually, like you don't
have to keep going back through security.
It is nice in that way.
Yeah.
Um, but I got, I was up there and we're not, we're going to do an episode and I
still don't know what shape the episode will take, but I was up there on the
last day of billabong and I will tease to the listeners, the good listeners
of club, not club three, the second gate, but you also, some of you are on
club three, uh, I will tease to the Patreon that I did get something, get
more than one thing because you were tweeting at a, was the universal high
universal high.
And I may have DMed with universal high a little bit.
Cause they got some good stuff.
They did get good stuff.
I thought they got good stuff.
Yeah.
It's nothing compared to what I got.
Let me ask, did you buy the wave pool?
Oh, I wish.
Did you buy the little wave pool?
I tried to get the vacation mode neon sign and it was already sold.
And we asked, we asked about the sign itself, the billabong sign itself,
but they're going to destroy it.
Oh, but I got something that is so good and exciting.
And you were, you went up there late.
Well, right.
And which was kind of my plan, not because I thought that would, this
thing would be there just because I was like, Oh, maybe they'll slash prices
even more.
Yeah.
So I do have things.
I got some gifts for everybody from the billabong and I bought a
piece of city walk history.
You bought the neon sign that says the most beautiful pieces in the world.
I would have bought that if they was available to me.
A lot of things were sold, but there was this thing.
And I will say this, a big thing, a big, this tall thing I bought for very
cheap that I'm so excited about.
I don't know what I'm going to do with it.
I sent a DM to this universal account and they said, what?
That wasn't there when I was there.
I hope you got a cardboard Rob Dyrdek like Stanley.
I think this is better than that.
And I don't even want to all I'll say.
Well, I'll say one more thing about it is that multiple people, as I was
carrying this out, that didn't know where it was from went, Oh, that's cool.
Wow.
So people that did not understand, they did not know the city walk history.
They did not know who I was.
They thought this big thing that I got was cool.
Usually that only happens when you're buying a Michael Ferrari.
Well, that's often what happens when you're buying a $10,000 pointillism
Harley Quinn, but I, I did, I had some fun with this thing too, around city walk.
That's what I'll say.
Oh boy.
I know nothing dirty, nothing untoward.
Um, but soon ish, I think we will figure out what this sort of city walk update
episode is and I will reveal and you're going to wheel in something covering in
a black sheet.
I don't know how did that move?
I'm going to have to feel like it moved.
Well, it is a character.
It could like, it looks, it looks like it could move.
I'll say that.
That's I said too much.
I've already said too much, but yes, we will be doing, I know people.
People want it.
People want us to weigh in on what's happening at city walk, but they do.
I, well, look, you mentioned gifts for everyone and this is your birthday shot.
It wouldn't be a birthday without a birthday gift.
Oh my God.
Really?
Already?
So, wow.
We have another two hours before.
Oh my God.
It's a photo.
You got me, of course, a Chuck-O photo for Christmas.
And I believe, is this another photo of Chuck-O?
It is, it's even better.
Uh, uh, it is a photo.
It's a replica.
Okay.
That's okay.
Uh, a replica photo of Paul Winchell and his two ventriloquist dummies, uh,
Jerry Mahoney that everyone, the name that everyone knows and knucklehead Smith.
Uh, and they are both, or all three of them are looking up toward the sky,
singing, uh, possibly, and it's got a Paul Winchell signature on it.
Wow.
This is fantastic.
Thank you very much.
Can I ask where you might purchase, uh, an item like this?
Oh, eBay.
Oh, it's on eBay.
Okay.
Yeah.
There's a lot of photo stuff on eBay.
Now I, I did, I do have to still send you.
I was watching 2 AM last night.
I was watching some Paul Winchell clips with Jerry Mahoney and
knucklehead Smith.
And there was an element, excuse me.
What'd you say?
Knucklehead Smith.
Thank you.
I thought you said Smith.
I did not.
I just want to make sure.
Okay.
Uh, and there is an element that I didn't know about.
Uh, it mostly there was like seen like one late night appearance, but they
went to a kid show at some point and there's an element of these dummies.
I don't quite know that I've seen the execution of this element before.
Well, he was an innovator.
I'll share, share some of these.
So I was watching just to make sure like they called him the most
racist ventriloquist alive.
That was not the case because we're very wholesome segments.
Yeah.
Very goofy segments.
So, yeah, so far.
Yeah.
No, I haven't found anything awful about Paul Winchell yet.
So fingers crossed fingers crossed.
So, okay.
Let's look, let's do a little bit more here and then we'll call it
on the UFO UAP Dan Aykroyd.
I mean, obviously it's going to be more accurate.
There's there's certainly a blues brothers episode in our
future at a certain point.
Um, so.
Oh, cause we never did the in park show.
There's still the in park show to talk about.
Yep.
And it's just a lot.
Um, and there's hopefully more ghostbusters.
When we look at alien abduction, I mean, the idea of a human being being taken
and having an implant inserted into their body, um, I often think of how
biologists, um, how we tag whales.
You know, we put a chip on a whale and we can track them via satellite.
And also how, you know, we go into a frog's pond and we pull out the frog
and we spread it out on the table.
Remember biology class?
We used to do this.
And editing is really, they found a frog autopsy video and are now showing
us, um, and another life form in another world.
I think it's really a sign of violence.
We can go get a frog.
There's gotta be a frog place in Burbank.
I mean, I think it's a sign that civilization is coming to earth and doing
the same to us, putting computer chip implants on us to track us, know what we
are, study our species, do a little bit of biological experimentation.
I mean, I know for us, but from their perspective, do you really think that
they're being violent?
Well, again, I have to go back to some of them might be here for good purposes,
interested in perhaps helping mankind.
When he says some of what I like about Akroyd too, is that he, I think he
envisions a world of many different types of beings visiting us because some of
them are, are, are happy to be here and they're trying to help.
And some of them are here for evil.
So he's, he, you can see his creative brain imagining this, like very, uh,
detailed world of all these different types of travelers here, which I, I mean,
I like, again, it's more fun that way versus it's just like the aliens from
independence day that are scouting this place to gut it and destroy us.
Well, that would be, I wonder if you attract that throughout movies.
Cause obviously I feel like there was more sinister stuff and like the B
movie, sci-fis of the fifties and sixties and then, uh, close encounters are
benevolent.
The ETS good in Mack and me is good of VT.
Yes.
Botanical is the nineties.
There was a lot of like bad aliens and that might that they touched on
independence day of like, well, the cold war is over so we can finally come
together for one common threat.
You know, the first thing that, uh, that happens is the army is assembled and
you know, guns are shot at the, at these, at these beings and at the ship.
What's really funny about the music in general in this thing is that it's, this
music is either like spooky UFO documentary music or it's like day spa
music, like basically the same thing.
Like you'd have a massage, like quote unquote world music.
Yeah.
But it's, and it's funny that he just plays it the whole time to give it like
an eerie feeling because I also think that's like, you don't need to, it
doesn't all need to be eerie.
Some of this is sort of like, it could just be sort of mundane or matter of
fact, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
It's just cause I guess the unknown, but you don't have to, I guess it's just
two on the nose when you're putting this together.
Why don't we have some fun music?
Sure.
Maybe some of these aliens are fun.
Yeah.
They're just coming here.
They're taking a joy ride.
There's some alien teens joy riding around the globe.
I think I said that the, the graphic at that live show ages ago, take me to your
dealer.
Have you made a shirt of that?
No, that's not, no, that's not a me thing.
That's a long time.
Like you should make a poster.
Sure.
You should just, so many people have made shirts of it.
I bet you could do it.
You could probably make a killing.
Yeah.
I don't know who has the trademark on take me to your dealer.
There have been so many celebrities.
And, you know, people like David Bowie and John Denver, many people who have been
interested in UFOs, but also in the idea of going into space, would you train and
go on the space shuttle yourself and conduct investigations into UFOs?
And if you did that, and you took an oath that stated that if you did discover
something out there, that you would not share it with the American public.
And if you knew you had captured on videotape, actual UFOs from the space shuttle,
would you break that oath and share the truth with the American public?
That is the opposite of what they teach you to do in journalism school, which is as
short, clear questions, don't ask a question that's longer than the answer would be.
Would you, Dan Aykroyd, train for several months to become an astronaut and go into
space and investigate aliens?
And then if you saw the aliens, would you tell us, would you keep it a little secret
from us? Would you not tell us?
Would you not tell your friend David Serreira?
That was like one of the questions where if you go to a movie screening where a
director and actor is there and they open it up for a Q&A and people ask just
insanely long questions that are mostly statements.
Well, mostly statements and mostly about themselves.
Like, that's what happens at the Q&A.
Well, I, you know, first of all, I'm claustrophobic, so I doubt I'll go up into
space. But if I were to go up into space, I wouldn't have to say, look, you know,
what we see up there and what we find, you know, we're just going to, we're just
going to have to throw out that law.
There's a law.
I also like this. I also like this question because this interviewer, David, is
asking a question.
He's imagining a world where Dan Aykroyd goes into space and becomes a space
detective.
Well, he says investigates.
But he doesn't even know about the future that awaits with Blue Angels space
flight.
Blue Origin, you're saying?
Uh, is that, oh, Blue Angels fly over the football stadiums.
Yeah.
Blue Origin, Jeff Bezos.
Uh, Blue Or, oh my gosh.
You want to take a Blue Angels jet into space.
I just, you know, I like seeing them at the stock car races.
Um, Blue Origin, SpaceX, you know, space tourism, the emerging field of space
tourism.
Right.
I mean, there was talk of it back then, but I'm, I'm just liking that this guy
is having a fantasy where Dan goes into space and spends a lot of time up there
investigating aliens, which I just don't see how, what that would look like.
I don't like the technologies.
Dan was not going to live long enough to go to like a enterprise D scenario where
he's like piloting a starship is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
So I just don't know.
Will Katy Perry reveal the truth when she goes in that Blue Origin flight?
Oh, who's going, there's a couple of people going.
It's a, it's Bezos, his new wife, Lauren Sanchez.
Is that her name?
Laura Sanchez, uh, Katy Perry, and then somebody else.
And I can't remember who it is.
It was an interesting group of people though.
Um, are they dishing out the money or are they like comped?
They're famous enough to get comped.
You've got to comp Katy Perry on Blue Origin is my feeling.
Shatner, I don't think had to pay when he did Blue Origin.
Shatner just went to Antarctica too.
Lauren Wendy Sanchez.
Lauren.
Did I say Lauren first?
I think so.
And, and, um, Lana Del Rey's husband is Jeremy Dufresne.
I don't know if we even determined what it was on the kids, uh, we are back
kids from the future episode.
Um, so.
Jeremy Dufresne.
Uh, primary credit Lana Del Rey's husband and he's feeding a
gator in the first picture.
Let me, um, let me just play this last chunk here.
And again, there's so much more to get through.
If this is an interesting topic to you, please, I implore you watch
Dan Aykroyd unplugged on UFOs.
It's all on YouTube.
We'll post a link.
It's on the neighborhood UFO watch YouTube channel, not often updated.
So how do people respond to Dan Aykroyd when he talks to them on
a personal level about UFOs?
They come to me and ask me about it.
And I basically lay out, you know, my thoughts on it.
I'd say half the people that I speak to about this have either seen themselves,
heard about it from a critical credible witness or are willing to, to accept.
The other half totally not Harold Ramis, my good friend and collaborator
does not believe, will not accept until, you know, proof, hard proof is presented.
It's the Harold Ramis of Podcast the Rock.
Something tangible.
And so, uh, what I'm able to do is just open people's minds a little bit and,
and let them think about it.
And of course, the greatest proof are the kinds of tapes that now exist,
the kind of videos that exist.
Jason, you're a podcast.
I'm the new podcast.
I'm the new movie boy of some different.
Things that have been exposed to me, there are, you know, tremendous,
there's tremendous divisiveness in the planet.
And, you know, perhaps this study and this, this understanding of things
that are greater than we have accomplished technologically
will lead us to a spiritual awakening, one that helps us
respect other beings out there in the universe and other dimensions
and also in our own four dimensions and here in the physical world that we live in.
The sacredness of human life,
the willingness to get along a little better, to relinquish materialism
and territoriality in favor of a more
comprehensive worldview, which in which we unite
and we all feel the energy within us
as as part of a part of a universal light.
Honestly, pretty well said.
Pretty well said.
But by the way, Mike, to answer your question, the other passenger
going up in Blue Origin, Gail King.
Oh, OK. Gail King, Oprah's friend Gail.
Katy Perry and Gail King will join Jeff Bezos,
fiance Lauren Sanchez, a Blue Origin state
space flight that's from the Associated Press.
I like the idea. Now I realize I looked at you while Dan was talking
and I'm like, you know, Dan is really making a lot of sense
because if I'm analyzing about what is interesting to this,
interesting about this to me, it's like it is like,
oh, I want to like learn more secrets of the universe and why we're here
and interdimensional stuff and multiverse.
Like that's all confusing.
But on some level, it kind of I don't know.
It feels reassuring to me that like, you know, there's a lot more out there
than this life we're living, which is a nice thing.
I mean, it could be maybe not a comforting thing,
but at some level, it could end up being a comforting thing
to know that maybe we exist forever in some way.
And Dan is kind of articulating some of that same sentiment.
And I look over you and I'm like, what's Jason thinking about right now?
What's he doing? And then after it was over,
I realized you were just waiting to say Gail King's name.
I think I was trying not to slip of the tongue and say Gail Gordon,
because you I know you love him so much.
I was sitting like kind of being moved by what Dan was saying
and feeling like I was having my own thoughts about it.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, I think he's on to something here.
And I'm like, oh, it seems like Jason may be upset about this.
But you were just running over in your head.
Gail King, Gail King, say Gail King.
Don't say Gail Gordon.
I often when I have to listen to something,
I need to have something visual to sure like so I can focus on the listening.
Yeah, I hear you. It was just funny.
I didn't realize. And then I was like, oh, I get it.
Gail King, Gail King.
Gail King is the third name.
So, yeah, Dan sums it up pretty well there, I think, on some level.
That I think it plays into stuff.
I like like Star Trek.
It is fun to think about aliens.
Different shot, different angle.
Not he was you could not tell if he was wearing his plaid shirt and vest.
Well, it's just his head. Yeah, real close to his head.
So that might have been filmed separately.
It might. Yes, that's well, I don't know.
Separately, maybe they did have two cameras on him.
And then this guy just filmed himself in front of a green screen.
The interviewer. I just met like later in the day, maybe.
Well, yeah, maybe it's all cut together.
So, yeah, I don't know.
I don't you know, there's a lot of things I'm going to get out of my system,
I guess, this month in regards to puppets.
That's the Club 3 poll in case you're not on the Club 3 tier on the Patreon.
The topic that's been voted on this month, I guess maybe it's come out already.
I'm not sure how we're going to schedule these releases.
But Mike gets all this puppet stuff out of his system.
But to some degree, I've gotten UFO stuff out of my system talking about it here.
I forgive me.
And there's people that are much more knowledgeable about this
and remember names and remember all the events.
I'm a very novice.
Yeah. UFO guy.
But I like talking about aliens and puppets.
Ironically, I feel like share
something similar with you're trying to get to the human condition.
You're trying to get to the human experience.
Well, that's true.
I mean, we'll talk or you've either heard my thoughts about puppets.
I think puppets, puppets in some way are a mask
that allows me to be more myself.
I'll say that.
Comedy, drama.
But also human beings respond better, I think, to puppets than they do to humans.
I'm getting giving up too much of the puppet philosophy on this episode.
But my daughter doesn't like to listen to me, but boy, she likes to listen to Alf.
Let me just say that.
Alf had command so much more respect with her than I do.
A child going into preschool and speaking,
fawning over her best friend, Alf, in 2025 is just going to be very excited.
She gets so excited when Alf shows up.
Yeah, she just because we have an elf puppet, a new puppet,
and she gets so excited with Alf.
But yeah, dad can't tell her what to do, but Alf can.
And you know what?
If any of those other kids give her lip,
she's kind of tall like her dad.
She is tall, so she can put them in the ground.
That's true.
And you should also draw the parallel or draw the draw
the mixing of UFOs and puppets with Alf, who's an alien.
That's right. Right.
So anyway, you've survived podcast the ride.
My birthday shot, Dan Aykroyd unplugged on UFOs.
So let us know if you've had any sort of interaction with,
I guess, I mean, I would like to know with ghosts and like cryptids
and like Bigfoot or something, but mostly UAPs, UFOs, aliens.
I am interested if you have a picture, too, of like,
I guess, a sighting, that would be cool.
But generally, these videos are hard to see.
Yeah. And hey, I, you know, where my mind went to,
are you familiar with the Nevada long time?
Business, Alien Jerky.
Yes. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I stopped there. Yeah.
They, the hotel you talking about?
Yeah, they're still working on the hotel.
Well, I don't buy it not too long ago.
It's still under construction.
But this there is obviously there's a lot of alien
based souvenirs and stuff in Nevada due to Area 51.
Right. And Alien Jerky, it's good jerky.
You've had the jerky. I've had it.
I didn't actually get the jerky. I've given it for Christmas.
Really? You can buy it.
They have an Amazon store front. Oh.
I sent it back east.
And they're doing an immersive hotel.
They are building the UFO hotel.
The UFO hotel is coming to Baker, California.
It's in Baker, California.
And I yes, I was like, that's an episode.
Gio and I were talking about doing that as an episode
when that is built, this UFO hotel on the way to Vegas. Sure.
Yeah, there's going to be a lot of Vegas.
They crossed out the UFO hotel attraction as being planned in Baker
and replaced it with the UFO hotel.
Attraction is under construction in Baker.
Well, it was not done when I drove by it a couple of weeks ago. Yeah.
So I signed up for email updates.
So we'll keep everyone posted.
There's that whole the universal thing is opening in August now.
August 15th is the universal like their permanent horror
night's maze out in Vegas.
The Backstreet Boys are playing Sphere.
Oh, my God. I forgot about that.
I don't know if the dates stretch all the way out to that 15th in August,
but I wouldn't mind going through those mazes
and then seeing the Backstreet Boys at Sphere. Sure.
And then the way home, you don't have to drive all four or five hours.
You stay in a UFO, stay in a UFO, pick up some jerky to share with everyone.
Yeah. And maybe then there's a little bit more UFO talk on Podcast the Ride.
Yeah. We'll see.