Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, today focused on Back to Neverland, a phrase
I hear in my absolute darkest stress dreams.
I'm Scott Garrener, joined by Mike Carlson.
Uh, yes, I'm here.
Uh, I, when you, I'll be honest, you suggest, I mean, I'll be honest with the
listener, you suggested this.
And then when even just the phrase, I said, how is he even typing this in a text
chain, I thought like, oh my gosh, what's going on here?
I think I can explain why I'll go get Jason Sheridan in.
Yeah, I, I'd seen a couple of people suggest this when we asked and that's
why I'm doing it for them, for the people.
It's not for me.
It's podcasters for the people.
But this was one where I was like, what is, and then as soon as I started
watching, I was like, oh yeah, this is in my bones.
So yeah, absolutely.
That's why I like that phrase.
That's completely how I feel about this.
There's so many aspects of Disney MGM studios where you can't exactly conjure
where it was or when you saw it or what was the flow from this into that, or
sometimes even the name, but you just, you go as like, as soon as you experience
any of it or see a still from it, you're like, this is in me.
This is my DNA.
I like like primary core memory.
I am coming to life.
I'm alive on this earth.
I am in Florida watching Robin Williams goof around with Walter Cronkite.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, I'm probably in Hollywood because of it.
This is probably one of the reasons.
Totally.
Yes.
Great movie ride.
Exactly what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Well, no, and I know that was a big one for you and it was a disappointment for
you to get here and realize that it's all like improv comedy and that you don't
get to like stand on a big cake with 70 people in unitards.
There's no Esther Williams numbers to participate in in today's Hollywood.
I didn't have the cardio.
I just couldn't keep up.
Yeah.
Well, but even if you could, I mean, there's just not like, you know, like I
know I recall you saying in your talking to agents initially being like, you know,
I think I could see myself as swimmer number 56 in a group of 120 agents.
Love it.
When you're like, I just want to be a number.
Thank you so much.
Well, it takes pressure off as you're getting into the business, having to come
up with a name and like flesh out a character like that, as opposed to just
like, you know, like just being there to learn learning from swimmers one through
55.
Now I'm just holding on for like the return of like being lowered from a
ceiling, like a swinging Teddy Barra.
Yeah.
You know, I, I seats lowered from the ceiling on a swing.
Specifically on a swing.
Yeah.
We're like that, um, uh, uh, that show that was at the fantasy land stage.
We talked about, uh, was that just a TV special?
We talked about the TV special.
Someone on a swing nutcracker.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's why I wasn't coming to me.
I wasn't here.
You weren't here.
Uh, I didn't realize it had a swing.
Didn't realize it had a swinger.
There was a swinger.
Jason's into swingers and swinging this.
We know I sign all my internet posts with an upside down pineapple.
Just so everyone knows that cruise ship symbol sign of swinging.
Well, that I think it's a universal sign.
Okay.
Not universal parks.
Universal is in all work.
If you left an upside down pineapple around at a, at a, you know, at Mel's
diner, it might read as something.
Maybe.
Yeah, we should try it.
Worth a shot.
Yeah.
See if you can do the siren song of the swinger there.
You kind of pocket it when you get the stomach ache that immediately hits
two bites into a Mel's diner meal.
Is that true?
Now I would assume I'm not surprised by this at all, but, uh, as, as Mel's a
particularly disappointing, and are we talking West Coast Mel's or East Coast Mel's?
Oh, I think West Coast Mel's look in my older age, I understand the phrase
theme park, chili dog is a no-go.
In my older, the wisdom that comes with the passage of time.
I, I, you know, I, I put away childhood things, you know, you put away childhood
chili, basically your childhood desire for theme park, chili now outside of
theme park, chili dog in a mall.
Now that's, that's fair game.
That's obviously fine and should be pursued at all times.
Yeah.
Well, at least it's not hurting your wallet.
If you're getting a tummy ache, the mall, the mall, I'm just saying the
mall food court, chili dog is usually more cost effective.
But at CityWalk, we, we always talk about the massive markup at CityWalk.
There's no way you're getting a chili dog for cheap.
Not a theme park.
Well, I mean like Burbank town center, Glendale Galleria.
No, that's no, I'm saying city.
I'm saying theme park, adjacent chili.
These are all different varieties of chili dog.
And just to be clear to the listener, you aren't swearing off all chili
dogs, not by a long shot.
No, I love, I do love a chili dog.
And this is probably a moment where I should bring up before we get into
this very fruitful topic, I, it's just for you, Patreon listeners, following
up on Mike's adventure with the Taco Bell Caliente Cantina menu.
Oh, I, Jane and I were ordering Taco Bell in the Taco Bell app.
And I saw you could get a side of the Caliente sauce for only 60 cents.
And just to refresh, this is that Mike took a swing at an item that he'd never
tried at the CityWalk Taco Bell, where once it came out, it seemed like some
kind of cleaning fluid.
It was covered in neon yellow and it was just so gross.
Now we believe that the neon yellow was meant to be the Caliente sauce.
That's the theory.
It's a working theory.
This one was more neon orange, you know, of the thing that assures us.
And I took two bites.
Wait, yes, a yellow alarmed you, but orange would have been no problem.
Orange means go, yellow means stop in Taco Bell language.
Yeah.
And red means go extra hard.
You need to eat there to know that.
But in the favor of being a theme park journalist, I was like, I am going to get
a side of this and dip like a chip in it and see if it was just the CityWalk
location that was a problem or a problem across the board.
And, um, I, after two bites, um, I, uh, gave up and I said, I don't want any more
of this and I'm not hungry anymore.
So, Whoa.
I were hungry.
Huh?
And then it zapped.
You're just zapped.
Yeah.
I, my mouth was numb and then my lips were numb for the rest.
Like I finished the last couple of bites of a burrito.
It's just like liquid ozempic.
What do you mean?
I, it was, it was awful.
It, it tasted like lemon heads rolled in cayenne pepper.
Okay.
So that is the same taste.
Yeah.
What is this fucking sauce?
What's going on?
I don't know.
I thought it was just going to be like, uh, uh, the fire sauce packets or like a
sriracha thing.
I'm going to, I'm just going to read, keep going.
I'm going to click on this, but the, like, there's a Reddit, Taco Bell Reddit, which
I assume that you're on, uh, fairly frequently.
He's more on the Wendy's.
More on the Wendy's.
But now what the, this thread is titled, what's the Caliente Cantina sauce made of?
But after hearing both of your trauma, I can't help but read it in more of a
Soylent Green kind of, what's the Caliente Cantina sauce made of?
What's it made of?
So like for the next couple of hours, my like lips and mouth were kind of like
numb hours of numbness.
Yeah, I had a bad time.
Like I had a really bad time.
It's a bad trip, man.
Just like, just lay down, let it wash over you.
You were numb for hours?
For like a couple of hours.
And Scott, I was reaching for my, Scott, you're going to hate this phrase.
Do you know what a dirty soda is?
Um, no, no, I don't.
Okay.
Well, apparently I always saw it like, oh, this thing in Utah, it's very popular.
And it's like Dr.
Pepper Coke with a million syrups and cream in it.
And now Sonic is doing it.
And I would hate this phrase, but I hate the idea.
Yeah.
So this was just a, a dirty Baja Blast Zero.
So it was just Baja Blast Zero, which is already an unnatural color, which is
like a pump of half and a half, I guess.
Heavy cream, heavy cream in your Baja Blast.
Yeah.
So think about it that way.
All right.
I'm just going to close my eyes and imagine heavy cream in your soda, your Mountain Dew.
So I was like, that sauce was so nasty.
I was like, it's going to be so heavy in cream.
I'm chugging my cream.
It does taste it like Baja Blast with cream soda.
Jason's lips went numb, so he chugged his cream to bring the feeling back.
Actually, it's funny because they do say dairy if you eat something too spicy.
You're not supposed to drink water, you drink like milk, like hot ones.
They've got the milk there and that's better.
They say, they say dairy or blast.
They say you're one of those food groups.
Yeah.
You're having your five daily blasts.
But yeah, Mike, I will back you up.
That collie and that sauce was nasty.
Well, you sound, your sounds way worse than mine.
I did not have a good time.
Like you were numb.
Something that is being distributed at a very common restaurant should not be
numbing people.
It's like the fuzzy tauntaun at Rex at the Cantina in Star Wars land.
Yeah, but that's supposed to do it.
That's like, that's a certain type of peppercorn.
Right. That's fun.
That's fun numbing.
What you're describing is not fun.
Could you talk? Was it like you had Novocaine?
Yeah, I could talk fine.
I was just like.
Here's what it is. It says it's part lemon, part Novocaine.
That's what Taco Bell puts into the sauce.
They struck a deal with a dental products distributor
who needed to move a lot of Novocaine.
Right.
Get it off the ship.
Expired. Maybe that's why it's not.
It's not strong enough to use during operations.
Right. So they have to get rid of it.
But it is strong enough to make you require dirty soda.
Right. Maybe this was all some weird backchannel deal with the dirty soda people, too.
This is to raise sales of dirty soda.
Yeah. Trump signed an executive order to to make Novocaine legal and fast food.
So that's also probably part of it.
Yeah, beef tallow and Novocaine.
Beef tallow and Novocaine.
We all grew up with this.
This is when food was great in 1988.
That's right.
OK. To go back to the Reddit,
somebody has written the ingredients, which are mostly obscure.
You know, the ingredients, if anything, sound bad.
But somebody has said the lemon oil is the culprit.
They believe that the lemon oil is either what makes it gross or what makes it
is that extra too much sting.
It might not be the right what does the numbing.
A quote, one Dr.
Doinkers, honestly, Dr.
Doinkers, Dr. Doinkers, a doctor is weighed in.
Dr. Doinkers.
And he has said, honestly, it's the worst colored sauce of all time.
It's like it was mad. It was made.
Taco Bell Reddit seems really upset.
OK, so they do. They agree with us.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, everybody. And when the question is posed, what is in it?
All of the answers are, you know, people say like sour green skittles
or like, I can't, you know, Windex, whatever.
Like, yeah. All right.
So this is not uncommon with your guys experience.
And it's not a city walk problem.
I think now we can. Yeah.
So now we can. It's a rare lot.
Yeah. Thank God.
So because I was getting worried there that this would cause Mike
to stop going to the Taco Bell at City Walk.
Crisis averted. Thank God.
There's nothing now to get in your way of going there.
The crunch was good.
I had one other item that was good.
So it's obvious.
It's obviously a quality establishment.
Yeah. Yeah. And not even any nubs.
You didn't even get just a little nub in there.
No nubs to see. I didn't see any nubs.
Yeah. So plastic nubs.
No microplastics in all our normal microplastics.
Yeah. And my pickle didn't blow away
while I was up there or the chalupa didn't blow away
or whatever it was called.
You guys really do.
You did have a you went up there and you had a bunch of little rascal problems.
Yeah, that is true.
It was a real and then that was it was at the same day
that Jamie Loftus met us up there accidentally after recording with us.
Yeah. After we all talked about hot dogs and then we encountered her.
You know, we went to banks afterward.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
We're not the only ones.
That was the the yeah.
Mills Hollywood Mills in the park
got a chili dog that made me feel bad.
And then a few years later, if you recall, briefly,
there was a pinks in the park.
And I'm like, well, surely this is a different kind of chili dog.
No, absolutely not.
It's like the Simpsons when they go to the pier
and they just get great slop and they they put it to every restaurant.
It's like you've all had to learn a hundred different variations of the lesson.
Fire is hot.
Fire will burn you.
It's probably a different kind of fire, though.
Like not all fire burns you, right? Yeah.
Not not all stoves get hot enough.
This scorpion going across the river is going to be cool on my back.
Yeah. Well, call fire is Caliente.
I think that's what I remember.
It's a lesson.
So when they introduce a new item, that's just a cup of fire.
And then you won't. So I and I had a free deal on the app.
I got this. So the fire was free.
So that I was excited about.
But then I tried to put the fire in my mouth. Right.
And now, if you notice, I don't have a tongue anymore.
Yeah. No, Mike, I understand.
Everything you just said didn't sound like anything.
It was really hard to understand.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
If it was an app, it was an app deal.
I'll be interested.
These are some previews of podcasts that write hijinks in 2035.
But for now, let's go backwards.
Let's go back to our childhoods and to this nice thing.
I think that is nice enough to completely override any Neverland connotations in my head.
And the quick Cliff notes on this.
Jason essentially said it.
But what we're talking about here is a short called Back to Neverland.
It premiered in 1989, along with the Disney MGM Studios.
Brand new theme park at that time.
This was a short film that kicked off the animation tour,
which was called The Magic of Disney Animation.
It was a peek into the animation process that showed you
all of the steps of the process in a fun, enlightening,
funny way that probably made it stick with all of us forever.
Like it's, you know, you're showing this before you're cut loose
in the actual studio so that now you can go, oh, I see.
There's ink and paint.
There's people illustrating at desks.
And it's like it does a really great job of just like teaching you
that animation shorthand really quick and in a fun way.
And it, of course, brings together the classic comedy team of Robin Williams
and Walter Cronkite.
It's so fun.
I mean, like, could this be folded into a general animation tour episode,
something that we haven't done possibly?
But it's also I think there's enough to meditate on here.
And also, I've come to realize, like, if we need to flesh out a little bit
of time in an episode just to make sure we get it to time,
just say the word chili dog and then 15 minutes transpires.
Very, very good point.
It's always a way to flesh things out.
But I am very excited to to talk about this.
As we dive into this, it also makes me flesh too,
because this kind of came out of we're saying is there something like classic
Disney MGM Studios?
That'd be a nice vibe to tap into for a second gate.
And I was thinking about a couple things.
And these might all be things worth pursuing.
But when you obviously, you know, you go into classic films
like the, you know, like Hollywood magic is evident all across that
that initial park.
And there was like star wattage throughout.
But I think something that was especially special about when that park open
was like custom little short films and videos
made with very big stars of the time.
Like, it did not feel like some weird favor of a favor.
We owe this guy. This is somebody we could get.
Like, they really got the biggest and best, as did Universal, honestly, too.
Like in that little arms race of which is going to be the best movie,
movie studio park, everybody brought out the big guns.
And a couple that I think we need to get to at some point
just to like paint the picture of everything you could see at this time.
Remember the lottery with Bette Midler?
This is something we have not referred to ever on the show.
I am positive of it.
I I've I think I watched it.
This is another short, right? Yes.
Showing movie making techniques. Yes.
This was one of these like made to made to show you the process.
You know what I mean?
Like it existed so that here we'll make this thing,
but then we will show you the sets and we'll show you how we did the special effects
and we'll show you the costume.
It was like a like a thing meant to be a compelling little short film,
but then also that they could break into elements and like day one have like,
we'll take you behind the scenes. We have made something here.
We swear it's not a fake movie studio. We have made things.
We made the lottery with Bette Midler, a short film directed by Gary Marshall.
This thing is so charming.
Did you remember this? I don't really remember.
I don't think I remember it at all.
It was real. I mean, I think they might have changed it out.
And it wasn't always what you would see on the behind the scenes tour.
And it's I also never remember which is which I remember.
I feel like you would watch this in a theater and then go through some catwalks
to see like stages and props and stuff.
I think that was part of this.
The whatever step of the tour where you would ride the bee,
where you would end up riding the bee for money.
I shrunk the kids. Right. Yeah.
So the lottery is a fun one, I think, to explore at some point.
Speaking of funny, I shrunk the kids.
There was a Rick Moranis, Goldie Hawn, two hander
that I don't even remember what this was about.
And I think you can only watch it in real shit quality.
Unlike back to Neverland.
There's a pretty nice YouTube rip of it.
But like, you know, hey, those are great stars to see together.
There was a little thing that George Lucas did this.
This I have only the faintest flickering memory of.
I think that was called the editing story.
And George Lucas talked to you in it.
Custom Luke, custom Lucas acting.
Yeah, we know the like red hot charisma machine that is George Lucas.
Yeah, I really want to recall whatever the hell it was.
Yeah, learnings were really, really worth a phone call.
Yeah, we got to do that.
There's a lot. There's a lot to get through.
But just the star wattage just in these like behind the scenes things.
This is this is Eisner, like feeling himself using his powers,
making sure that Disney feels like a real big movie studio with a listeners
and not like, well, you know, Jodie Foster used to do movies with us
till she grew up.
Jodie Foster would return our calls till she was 16.
And now he can't get her anymore.
See, I say with Kurt Russell, he's just too he got old.
He got handsome. He doesn't call us back anymore.
That's basically where Disney was at in the early 80s.
This was late 80s.
It's Eisner, baby.
He's got everybody in the Rolodex.
This kind of lines up with in the Disney war book,
the section about touchstone pictures is really interesting
because they're like, we're going to make movies for adults
and they're going to be mid budget.
And they kept plucking people who were maybe in a career downturn
or in the case of Robin Williams, had just gotten out of rehab.
So they're striking the people were low.
Yeah, basically.
But then they looked at what a listeners are looking sad
while they walk to their cars.
But it's like recognizable people.
It's like Robin Williams, Bette Midler,
Richard Dreyfuss, I feel like.
And it pre-Disney animation, like second golden age,
like they hit on something of like, we'll make these solid movies.
They won't cost a ton of money.
They'll have a recognizable person.
And then they just
a batho box office, as they say out here in Hollywood.
As they definitely say, you hear a lot of batho every day.
Yeah.
There was definitely a clear at least one class in college
where they were trying to explain variety magazines,
annoying terminology like they felt like they had to teach you.
But before you go to Hollywood, here's something you need to learn.
Well, watch this Animaniacs song.
This book, there was multiple books
they encouraged us to buy in the early 2000s.
One was The Thomas Guy, the spiral bound book of maps of L.A.
And then another one was like, oh, God, I forget what it was called,
but it had all production companies and agencies, phone numbers and e-mails.
And it was like a phone book.
And then you took it upon yourself to get a third book, Pipe and Hot,
all the best chili dogs in the Hollywood.
Well, I didn't read that one.
I don't know what happened, you know.
They would have guided you away from, you know, go to the theme parks now.
Yeah, that's that's interesting.
I yeah, well, no, I think I think you're seeing the like
fruits of the labor and of the recent success.
They like plugged everybody in.
It just felt like you were like you were part of it.
It didn't feel like a fake movie studio, you know.
And Robin Williams, a huge get.
Is this the first Robin Williams?
It's not the first Robin Williams Disney, because he must.
I don't remember which was Touchstone, but was like
Dead Poets Society or Good Morning Vietnam.
Yeah, they use that clip all the time.
So much good.
I think every scene in the great movie ride
squeezes in a Good Morning Vietnam sting,
whether it's a Western or the Wizard of Oz.
Yeah, well, yeah, with anybody, anyone out there
who went to a little event called BugCon, Buzz Buzz, where we did a brief
pop up event called The Magic of Editing with Craig Healy, the star,
the auteur behind Complicated and Craigfix America and so many great shows.
That was but that was a choice we Craig and I made was that
making a montage like that, where every third clip was Good Morning Vietnam.
As a kid, almost no one, but it was effective.
The big movies, you know,
singing in the rain, Wizard of Oz, going with the wind.
Good morning, Vietnam. Yeah, absolutely. Yeah.
And well, I also this wasn't right when the park opened,
but I think that you've definitely felt a sister act presence
as soon as they come, but absolutely, because it's not like they could make
they couldn't get a live show together that fast or like a certainly not a ride.
There was no spoiler. No, no sister act ride
where everybody where you everybody puts on like you get in the ride vehicle
and there's like there's habits in that you put you put the hat on.
Like it's Mario Kart. Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, you get to have none vision. Right.
Shows you who's who's good and who's a sinner.
Yeah, well, you're not launching shells.
You're clapping like whatever you see a sinner, you start clapping.
And when you feel the gospel rhythm or when you need to teach that
there's a symmetry between the music of the Supremes and gospel music.
Right. Well, that was a very like
barred it from the neighbor, got the VHS from the library.
Like, oh, I I'm watching a big boy movie.
I'm watching Sister Act, a big boy movie.
I'm watching an adult movie, but it's pretty fun.
Yeah, there's crime in it.
There's people who are implied criminals, right?
I don't know if there's guns, but they like say
that guy does crimes and she's got to stay away from him.
Stuff like that.
But I haven't seen it in years, but I have such warm memories of Sister Act.
I didn't really I don't know if that's come up on the show before.
I don't think so.
I think this was just unlocked.
Both both Sister Act or just the first one?
I think both. OK, because with the second one,
you're happy to see all your friends and Galveston sisters again.
Aren't we talking Sister Act three is in their talk of that?
I would imagine there is because that's the kind of thing
that there's always talk about. Yeah, right.
Uh-huh. No, probably.
But this show, animated show, anthology, passing the torch to new generation.
Fifteen people watch it.
Dolores is in it for eight minutes. Yeah.
This special, it is very I got confused.
I watched it and then I wanted to pull it up again.
I kept typing and returned to Neverland.
This is back to Neverland.
Return to Neverland is the direct to video Peter Pan's sequel.
Yes, yeah.
And I also got extremely concerned after we pulled the trigger on this
that Back to Neverland is also the name of the upcoming sequel
to Leaving Neverland, the very disturbing Michael Jackson.
I was like, what if we like we'll have to pull this
if that's the name of the movie? And it's not.
It's called Leaving Neverland to the phrase Back to Neverland is fine.
Other than it's not something I want to hear.
And other than this fact that it's going to be very easy to confuse all of these names.
No, I think people can keep it together.
Yeah. Back to Return to Leaving.
Yeah. It's all fine.
Some of them are different directions.
I mean, I guess that's technically true. You're right.
Oh, yeah. All set. No, no confusion whatsoever.
No. But this.
Yeah, this this thing is really delightful.
Little backstory of how it came together.
So this a big centerpiece of new
Disney and Dream Studios was an animation tour.
They made the effort to start a new facility down there in Florida.
Forgive me if I'm mixing things up, but I think where the initial things
animated in Florida, like those Roger Rabbit shorts, did they like?
That's what I make that like, let's let's have this Florida studio
fill the need and we'll start getting that.
And then features ended up starting to get made there as well.
That's what I recall. That's my one with the where you freeze frame.
And there's inappropriate stuff, big boy stuff. Yeah.
Rigid tools.
Well, I mentioned this to Jane and she's like, oh, is that the one
that would play before the Mulan tour?
And I was like, further, further back.
It probably was still playing then.
Well, but maybe. Yeah.
I don't know when they stopped showing this or if they did.
I'm not totally sure.
There might have been something where you went from this into Mulan.
I don't know.
But so it was kind of being set up and actually prepared.
But I think that the entire
experience of the animation tour was set up by a guy named Bob Rogers,
who made, you know, like themed entertainment,
but also things with a little bit more of an educational angle.
I'd run across this name before because he did the
it was for an expo or something, the show Spirit Lodge,
which later became not the not show Mystery Lodge,
which we all know for the Raven, the Raven.
Oh, what a prankster, the Raven.
But that's that's a show.
I think a lot, I think like you ever you guys get to see Mystery Lodge.
I think we saw the first time.
Yeah. First time I have never said, is it still on hiatus
because of very specific technology?
I don't know about specific technology.
What have you heard there?
I heard there was some sort of projection or were bold.
It was one of those theme park things where it's like,
well, the manufacturer of this went out of business
and it's hard to get a replacement.
I could definitely see that.
It could also be I maybe over time
you didn't want an employee wearing a weird rubber
Native American mask.
Or it's both.
Well, yes, that or the or the technology was that the weird
the weird old wig with the bald spot,
there was like a hole broke in it
and they couldn't find anybody to fix old weird toxic plastic.
It is very much like the Tracy bad guy kind of face, right?
Yeah.
It still says closed for refurbishment, but that's been since 2020.
It's a bit of a long refurbishment.
Yeah.
I'm beginning to have my doubts.
I would be thrilled to see Mystery Lodge again, though.
But I think like, well, everybody was happy with generally
what was being put together for the tour.
It was sort of being done in a little bit too dry of an educational way.
And the director, Jerry Rees, who we'll get into
was kind of assessing it in whatever movie they were starting to make.
And he was like, they're focusing too much on stuff like, you know,
how many drawings you do per second and not enough on the like emotional pull
and what we could like gives emotional weight to Disney's animation
and and to the storytelling.
It's got as classic Disney stuff.
It's got to be about story.
So this guy, Jerry Rees, kind of revamped it and felt like
was there a more palatable way to quickly teach this process
to kids coming on this tour?
Jerry Rees is one of these names we've said a zillion times
because this guy was the director of everything, everything that like
had an effect in a cool like a like a particularly filmic style
in Disney attractions in 80s, 90s and even beyond was this guy.
Disney MGM Studios alone and early stuff.
The editing story I mentioned with George Lucas.
Tourist from Hell is apparently the name of the Rick Moranis one.
I think that is familiar, though.
Yeah, I can't tell you any specifics about Tourist from Hell.
Yeah, again, I'd like to dig into these rock and roller coaster.
He was the director of the the Steven Tyler Lude gesture.
He was the one who didn't catch it.
First movie where I felt like an adult that I saw.
Big boy, big boy, big boy stuff, big boy, big boy, rock and rollers.
Yeah, this guy, also the director of something that you that was shown
at the end of the animation tour, I think
something that it's it's so improbable that we've never done an episode
about this, the short film where
Michael Eisner and Mickey meet and gather the troops to go watch a screening
on the Disney lot, a masterful work.
We've certainly talked about when Michael Eisner is wearing a Mickey watch
and Mickey is wearing a Michael Eisner watch.
But we haven't done 35 minutes about it.
So maybe the watch will have to be its own.
Just the watch joke will be its own thing. Yeah. Yeah.
But Jerry Reese, this big feature was Brave Little Toaster.
He is credited as director and then he's just,
let's say, as character animation for a million things.
Oh, yes. Kind of like earlier 80s Fox and the Hound.
Yeah. Ereth type stuff.
Pete's Dragon. Oh, OK. OK.
Yeah. I mean, he just did such a great job with all of these things.
And his website is full of great behind the scenes treasures, especially for this.
There's a number of wonderful photos of of putting this short together.
Another cool behind the scenes person person
credit is animation producer, a guy named Mark Kirkland.
Mark Kirkland is the most tenured director of Simpsons episodes.
He did 82. All told,
including, I think, a really primary one is he did.
He directed the one where the Germans take over the power plant
and thus directed the Land of Chocolate, right, which is very impressive,
because that to me is like, oh, it all cracks.
So there were probably weird Homer fantasies before the Land of Chocolate.
But I think without Land of Chocolate, you don't get like the rest of the Simpsons.
You don't get family guy.
You don't get like crazy side tracks to that degree. Right.
That is a wonderful, wonderful sequence.
Yeah. Good point. I never thought about that. I think so.
That opens it up.
Fundamental in like the prime time, adult animation in general.
Second season, third season, third, third season.
Then my Conan Monorail is when when for four,
because the nemoid beaming out also breaks something.
Oh, that's true. Yes, that is like starting to get into you.
Yeah, yeah. They were still nice and selective about it.
Yeah. Yeah. No, cartoon stuff.
All right. Didn't I, didn't I, didn't I?
Um, uh, yes.
Mark Hogan, also supervising director of a show called Housebroken that I wrote on.
I was on one zoom with him and I was like, wait, that's a Simpsons guy.
That's a big land of chocolate guy. That's a big deal.
But he did a great job with this.
So anyway, but the big talent to talk about in this, obviously,
Robin Williams, Walter Cronkite.
This is apparently Jerry Reeves idea specifically.
I think he pitched it almost more as a type.
Like, what if there was somebody with the childlike wonder of Robin Williams
blended with somebody more stern and official like Walter Cronkite?
And then it ended up being the real deal.
And this is this is Robin Williams pre genie.
Pre genie and pre hook.
Yeah. Pre genie and pre hook.
But he is seemingly it's at the height of his power.
Like he is giving you the 110 percent. Extremely.
And then Walter Cronkite is like a really solid straight man
and has some like Uncle Walt characteristics about it.
Yes, I always felt that way, too.
And are we just tricked because his name is Walt?
Possibly. Possibly.
Somebody says the word Walt.
But it does make you think like, yes, he has that gravity.
And it is. Yeah.
As much as I don't even want to say what I'm about to say.
Sometimes somebody might throw out the opinion
that Michael Eisner was a little bit stiff on camera,
a little bit stiffer than Walt Disney himself.
Sure. Right. That could be a fringe opinion right there.
But the warmth of Walter Cronkite is extremely like 50s
Walt Disneyland show vibe.
You know, what with Tinkerbell flying out of his pocket
and him kind of like weaving people now we're over here and now we do this
and here's and like letting in like, I don't know, being a very like
kindly guide through a kind of technical process.
And I think it's a good pair because like kids are like,
oh, that's a silly guy, Ron Williams.
And then whether they knew Walter Cronkite or not, he's kind of like
news like they have him doing man on the street at the beginning of it.
And then for the parents, it's like, oh, it's more from work.
And the man who told us President Kennedy was dead.
So something for the whole family.
You were excited about Cronkite more than Robin Williams.
Oh, yeah. I was pushing my little brother out of the way.
And I was like, it's America's news man. Yeah.
I'm going to do my alt opening joke now from Dallas, Texas.
The Flash, apparently official
Robin Williams cartoonified at 1 p.m.
Central Standard Time, 2 p.m.
Eastern Standard Time, some 38 minutes ago.
It was a little weird in the later in the short film
where he takes his glasses off and he's like crying as Captain Hook shows up.
And he's like, I can't do this again.
Captain Hook, not dead, apparently.
I assumed he was eaten by the eaten by the crocodile.
But we have learned that.
Jack Ruby has a wind fire on Mr. Smee.
All right, Smee, he did it with a sword.
Just imagine all of the Kennedy stuff happening, but with swords instead. Yeah.
It's a fun steampunk redo of the JFK tale.
That is that's fine. Yeah, that is fine.
I looked into this. I was like, why?
When did he retire?
And Walter Cronkite retired in like 1980 because there was a rule.
There's a rule that anchors had to retire at 65.
So he retired in 1980.
So that's why I've been like, why was he doing this?
Oh, I guess he was retired by then.
Me just doing Rolodex of every horrible politician and Supreme Court justice.
Like, oh, right, right. Who would be gone?
So you're saying there was a time when people were supposed to leave their job
because they weren't at the peak mental condition.
Yeah. Yeah. Interesting.
And that time was before we were born.
Right. When life expectancy was not as good.
So well, Reagan changed it all is what he did.
He proved that being a strange,
doddering shadow of your former self. Yeah.
No problem. A bunch of a bunch of weirdos push agenda through is what we want.
Yeah. Desired.
I love seeing the opposition party, the Democratic Party, every now and then.
We allowed a different dying man who's like, oh,
he's one of the most senior Congress party somebody just died on the job.
Who was it a couple of weeks ago?
I forget. You know what I'm talking about?
There was a was it a state rep or there was somebody who they were like,
he was like, you know, just maybe newly elected and then passed away.
Maybe I have this wrong, but I'm pretty sure when Pelosi and all of them
did that thing where they took a knee, it's incredible.
They all made it back up.
Very true. Yeah.
It's improbable that like 65 percent of them didn't just stay on the ground
forever. That's a very good point.
Anyway, hey, let's not go there. This is fun. This is 1989.
Oh, well, now that's when all the bad stuff started, started happening.
Flashes me back to Reagan, you see. But we didn't know that.
We were wide eyed kids taking an animation tour.
And absolutely, everybody's everybody's so charming.
The Robin Williams aspect that you bring up.
This is a very strange thing because I did this for the first time,
I think, in 1992.
And this was post Aladdin was very soon after Aladdin.
And I think I just thought, oh, of course, Robin Williams,
Disney cartoon voice makes all the sense in the world.
But apparently for Jerry Rees, it was a little bit of a sell.
And some of this info, by the way, I'm going to say coming from a great article
on Cartoon Research Dotcom written by the late Jim Corkus,
a great Disney and theme park historian.
So if I ever start quoting something word for word,
credit to that site and to Jim Corkus.
This is from Jerry Rees.
Casting Robin was considered a huge risk because he was considered
an adult comedian who grabbed his crotch when he performed.
Well, like Michael Jackson.
Yes. Neverland connection here.
But that's well, and they already done Captain EO by that point.
So they proved that they were open to crotch grabbers.
Yeah. Associated with the word Neverland.
So why why wouldn't this be a problem?
But Rees couldn't point didn't point to that precedent.
He instead pointed out Cliff Edwards, who had done the voice of Jiminy
Cricket, was an adult nightclub entertainer.
But Walt still picked him to get that edge.
I don't think I realized that, that the voice of Jiminy Cricket was edgy.
He was a real edgelord of the 19.
He was a ukulele edgelord. Wow.
Yeah, I did not know that.
Yeah, we're going to have to analyze that act, I think.
Yeah, we'll go find the forbidden Red Fox style tapes of Cliff Edwards.
Buddy Buddy Hackett style bodyness.
I yeah, Shabupi was banned in some states when the music band movie was released.
Yeah. Yeah, I'd be curious what that means.
Two House Democrats have died in office in the last month.
I was going to say, since we started recording, we started recording.
My God. And you mean literally in, were they like in the middle of a speech?
Yeah, I don't know where.
Yeah, I don't know what part of the process it was, but they were in.
I don't know what office they were in, but they were serving.
They were holding office.
That's all I know.
They're not holding space. They were holding office.
Holding space is what young people do.
Holding office is what ancient people do.
Nancy Pelosi holding Richie Torres' finger, single finger.
The person I was thinking about was there.
There was a very old man who caught a seat on like the oversight board
that did not go to AOC.
And he was very old, tenured man who is fighting cancer.
And he's in his late seventies.
Yes, yes. And they did not pick the person.
Pick the younger person.
Yeah, yeah. Yes.
Yes, there you go.
Good stuff. Good plan.
Who needs a bench in any field?
Well, and everyone else is out on a book tour.
They're all doing book tours, right?
The only older gentleman I would endorse for the next
Democratic president presidential ticket, Michael Eisner.
I was hoping I was going to say that if it wasn't what you said.
I knew it wasn't going to be a serious thing.
You were saying, although it wasn't very three.
Yeah, he's all compared to these and like me or me having not seen
any footage of him in the last three years or so easily
better shape than any of these people.
I check footage of Michael Eisner every couple of weeks,
maybe every six weeks via a drone camera that you send by his beach house.
I do a little Malibu complex.
I do a little YouTube search and I think there's an interview
from like two years ago and he's at a football match.
Yeah. And I think that's the most recent one.
But I there isn't a newer one.
I'm I want a newer one.
Yeah. But we haven't seen it.
So I'll keep checking.
Yes. Yes.
Need to know, because we have a lot of Eisner plans as we just brought up
a new one today for so many Eisner plans.
And we don't want this to be we don't want to be in PTR curse territory.
Did he sell his house? Do we know that?
That I'm not sure. Yeah, we don't know if he was on the market,
but it was very expensive.
I did not buy it.
I didn't buy the house premium trading card vending machine in Burbank.
And Steve, he goes like, hello, thank you for buying some baseball cards.
You know, there are there is a Michael Eisner rising in the world of politics.
That's incumbent commissioner Michael Eisner,
who just won a seat on the Tarpen Springs City Commission
just one week ago as we recorded.
I don't know what city that's in.
What's what where what am I looking at?
Pasco, Hernando, North Pinellas.
I don't know what what state what I want to know about this
because we got to talk about this Michael Eisner, too.
Doesn't he look nice? Hey, I like this Michael Eisner. Nice.
Yeah, I got it.
OK, I got an Eisner interview here from June 9th, 2023.
Like at CNBC.
It's it's some football thing.
He's here. He is.
This is a year and almost two years ago at this point.
Mm hmm. He looks all right. He looks pretty good football.
They mean soccer. I am.
I said football match, which I feel like conveyed it.
But maybe I mismatch.
OK, does they own partial ownership of one of the L.A.
football clubs?
All I know about it is that you're supposed to call it football.
That's the only thing I know about it.
You're supposed to make a really big deal.
I made a meal, a little meal out of it.
So that's all I know.
Other than that, I don't know who owns what.
I know he's involved. Yeah.
And now I know Tarpen Springs is in Florida.
So we could go to Florida next time we're in Florida.
We could meet this guy. Sure.
I would I it would it'd be fun, but would also really disappoint
people if we go the Michael Eisner interview and then it's
Tarpen Springs City Commissioner Michael Eisner.
Terrifying, terrifying to look up.
Michael Eisner, Florida politician positions.
Where does he stand on?
Oh, no, I have no desire to know that's that's none of our business.
Anyways, back on track.
Robin Williams doing this, I think, like is the first step
in sort of bringing him into the world of Disney animation.
It makes all the sense in the world.
He's always done cartoon voices, and it does, in fact, predate Aladdin.
I don't know if this is too much of like the end of the story thing, but why not?
In the first scene of this movie, he is
he's basically met as a tourist,
not even really identified as the movie star Robin Williams.
It's right.
Walter Crockett just says, we're going to take a tour
of animation, animation works you there.
And Robin Williams turns around and he is wearing a yellow Hawaiian shirt,
a goofy hat, big clunky camera, shorts and sandals.
This is his uniform.
This all goes so great.
And everybody gets so excited about Robin Williams being a Disney voice
that Jerry Reese's friends, Musker and Clements say
he might be great for Aladdin.
And I don't know if you know, and a little known fact,
he became the voice of the genie in.
OK, yeah.
I don't know if you know who that was.
I thought all the impressions were the people.
I didn't realize how did they do this?
They had to get Schwarzenegger, they had to get Nicholson's.
These are expensive people.
I turn it off after the first time and then the Ralph is eaten
because I am a scaredy cat.
It was very curious.
We put it on for my son the other day and he requested it to come off
when the genie came on.
So what are you doing now?
Yeah, you want to do you want to watch just a guy getting swallowed
by a cave and not the fun guy who does voices?
We'll see how round two of Aladdin viewing goes.
But anyway, the end of that story to nod to what gave them the idea
to cast Robin Williams at the end of Aladdin.
The genie is wearing a yellow Hawaiian shirt, a goofy hat,
a big, clunky camera, that is this.
And that is a nod to back to Neverland that inspired this whole thing.
There is some like self-deprecating stuff
that I feel like universal does it a lot more.
It kind of became a trademark.
But like he, in addition to being dressed like a stereotypical
tourist, at some point he is Mickey Mouse.
And he says, oh, I'm a corporate mascot.
Like, yes, that I feel like, yeah, that's fun.
People like it when the companies like tease themselves a little thousand percent.
That would destroy every viewing of this.
I remember this from being a child that that would kill.
I would kill with the parents.
I think it would kill with the kids, too.
And it's the kind of thing they would never do today.
How that came about.
There were storyboards made for that sequence specifically,
because that's the section where like now we learned about how voices work.
And now we're going to see sketches, like precolored sketches of animation.
And he's turning into this character and turning into that character.
And he turns into seven dwarves.
And then he turns into Mickey and he says, I'm a corporate symbol.
That was on that was written on storyboards done by a guy named Steve Moore.
That was just like that wasn't even the intended line.
It was just to be fun to make a Mickey.
And that was a little joke just for himself that the storyboard artists made.
But this is being shown to Robin.
And he said, that's great. We got to do that. I'm doing it.
And I think everybody went, oh, you can't actually do that.
And he's Robin Williams. He's going to do what he wants to do.
He's right, because that's like the hardest, funniest joke involved
out of a lot of theme park attractions, I would say.
And it is like a perfect proof of concept
for like Genie transforming into anything and everything.
It is. I mean, it's so obvious, the one to there that like, oh, I see.
Like utilizing his capacity to switch between a zillion voices.
Yeah, it's it's it's a kind of a rare little
example of, you know, these little theme park videos
that not everybody regards as important, but we do.
But this is like literally it becomes the setup to Aladdin.
It's like a promotion from theme park pre-show video to feature film.
And what a brilliant one.
It's very important, really.
Yes, like it was that leads to the genie, like the primary
character of our childhoods, one of the best animated characters of all time.
Certainly, yeah, the biggest non princess character
of those big four movies, I think, right?
Has to be, has to be.
And I think a big piece in like getting the boys in, you know?
I mean, they weren't really struggling with that because there was like, oh, yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like I think there was still a thing of Little Mermaid and Beauty and the Beast
or four girls in broad strokes.
Yeah, yeah. But Aladdin was definitely the boy one
because it's got chasing and action and swords.
Big boy stuff. A lot of swords.
And there are more swords in Aladdin
video games and promotional material than in the actual movie, I feel like.
Yeah, the video games. Yeah, for sure.
Yes, it was a primary facet of that video game.
Like swinging it around, like just in a house,
my house growing up, so many plastic swords.
Like any time we went to like Disney on ice or a theme park,
like, well, I don't have that kind of light up sword.
My parents are like, yeah, it's cheaper than a t-shirt.
You know, like you didn't have swords.
And then immediately my brother and I just wacky each other with plastic swords.
It's like, OK, well, just avoid the head and face.
My daughter, my daughter has a foam sword from her Halloween costume
that she still will run around and play pirate.
She was a pirate.
So she will run around and be like, I'm going to steal your treasure.
And then she'll wave her sword around.
And I'm like, I don't know where she got.
I don't know what pirate stuff she's been watching.
I'm not sure where she got it.
And sneaking pirate material, like she got the treasure
came into play at a certain point.
So she steals our treasure now.
You know what I'm really proud of?
Here's my kid sort of thing is that we've been playing.
So his sword lately has been just a bunch of markers stuck together,
like at the top, like you can extend that into five.
We've been bashing markers all stuck together until they break,
which is immediately.
But the one because I've been trying to show him just like really silly
physical things that's been making him laugh a lot.
And let me I'll just cut cut to the chase, which is him saying,
putting a sword together and then saying, I want to play body moving,
body moving, referring to the Beastie Boys music video
in which there's a decapitation,
which is, I guess, a little too bloody for me to show my four year old.
But it's a it's such a silly, funny MCA.
And then he gets his head back on almost immediately.
But it like it made it killed with it.
It made him laugh so hard.
They like this, this like funny, hokey sword fighting scene
where MCA's head comes clean off.
And then later they're in a plane and they leave a hatch of the plane open
and a bird comes in and electrocutes the plane and the plane blows up.
It's like, I think these are primary pieces of my sense of humor.
And I think they're going to kill with my son.
And they did. And now he says, now we'll play swords and he'll say,
body moving, body move.
All right.
That's good, which I'm very excited about.
But it also I feel like I should not be a hypocrite
because this is also 25 year old music.
And I should say, Mike, if you want to play your daughter, Third Eye Blinds,
I do play your OK.
All right. Well, don't feel don't have any weird feelings about it.
I'll I'll do one more one more quick one.
She she really laughs when the chorus the boys are back in town plays.
My daughter laughs at the boys.
She just and then she starts going, the boys are back in town.
And then she'll start putting the boys are back in.
And then she'll say like something like mommy diapers.
She'll like put bananas and cackle and cackle.
And then she really that's she just for whatever reason,
the boys are back in town.
She really thinks that's funny.
Wow. Wow. Yeah, it's nice.
Yeah. You don't appreciate the little thing.
We've we've we've liked the song, but we forget that it's funny.
We forget how funny boys are back in town.
Boys are back in town is like in Lizzie.
There's that great vice article by Tim's writer, Tim Faust,
about how he played like in one of those digital jukeboxes.
He set it up to play the boys are back in town.
I think it was like 15 times. Oh, yeah.
And then he went back up to feed it again.
And a guy was like, you're not putting on the boys are back in town, are you?
And he went, no, of course not.
And of course, you put the boys are back in town.
They go on again.
Yeah. Any song.
I would like that bunch of times in a row.
But anyway, yeah, this sequence.
Yeah, very important.
He also did what he ended up doing on Aladdin,
which is like doing way too much material and more than they could use.
And, you know, Jerry Rees said that could have been a 10 minute
sequence in and of itself, and they had to be brutal and only
do the best of the best.
He's wearing a Google.
Robin Williams wearing that goofy hat, which I own still.
I found it a couple of weeks ago.
Big old teeth in the front.
Yeah, with the teeth in the front.
And there's a lot of pictures of me wearing that at Disney World around this time.
I was a Donald heck.
I like a big plastic Donald Bill.
Oh, you had. So you had that one?
Yeah. Yeah.
Did you have a character that other than the Mickey ears?
I don't know that I did.
Or even like years.
No, I didn't get Mickey ears until I was like 26.
Oh, OK.
I think I went on my birthday and someone bought me.
Sure. Yeah.
The ones with your name stitched.
You can get your name. Yes.
Yes. Yes. That's nice.
But yeah, goofy Mickey Mickey Mickey Mickey ears.
While fun are not really practical to wear, there's really nothing
keeping that on your head.
It is in a place with a lot of rides that easily blow hats.
That's a difficult thing.
I got to get a chin strap to go with it.
Definitely. Yes.
Yeah, that's really the only way I believe.
You know what I had?
I think I had a big bad wolf hat, the Busch Gardens Williamsburg
roller coaster, and it was a cap.
And then it had this safari flap on the back
because I think my my mother was terrified of me getting a sunburn on my neck.
So you had a you had a neck.
I had a neck safari flap style.
The safari like the I think you should leave like the hat.
The I'm calling it safari flap because that's what they call it.
You didn't just put on sunscreen.
Oh, we slathered on sunscreen.
Oh, OK. So really just a double double protection.
Yeah, exactly.
I burned occasionally.
My brother was getting sunburns all the time.
Like, I don't know what it was.
He was just wasn't enough.
Very fair skin. Yeah.
Should have done a full beekeeper uniform. Yeah.
Yeah. But I would go to the beach and put sunscreen on.
We first got there and I would never reapply it.
And I really burned.
Oh, but my brother burned left and right.
So it seemed like you didn't need that extra layer.
Yeah. Just in case.
But it was pretty cool graphics.
There was a wolf of the roller coaster cars.
And it was a cool fashion thing.
It was in a protection thing. Yeah, it wasn't.
I'm not. You just walk up to people and say,
I'm not wearing this flap because my mommy made me.
I'm wearing it because it's cool.
Oh, please, Scott. I was be the child to go like, my mom bought me this hat,
like unprovoked to shop keeps, like to shop keeps shop,
which you would call them say their shop keep. Hello, shop keep.
Do you have change for a penny for a thing?
What is this kid talking about?
That hasn't been the currency in this country, well, ever, frankly.
Anyways, another part of putting this together is that they
before they reached out to actual Robin and Cronkite,
they brought in Cory Burton, voice of the Disneyland tram and a zillion things.
One of the voices who does like, all right, this this actor
who did all the voices in the 50s, he's the guy who does it today,
including Captain Hook.
Well, I think it's Hans Conrad.
I think I'm not making that up.
But yeah, he did a scratch track and imitated both Robin and Cronkite.
Eisner thought it really was both of them
so much so that, all right, well, it proved the effectiveness
of these dynamics together.
Let's get the real people and let's get Cory Burton to be Captain Hook.
Would love to hear that.
Would love to hear of how he got fooled.
Maybe it was perfect.
Now, why didn't you film them?
If you were going to bring them in, you should have shot them with cameras, too.
That was a waste of time.
He was approving like seven other different of soon to be failed
ventures in the middle of it.
So maybe he was just distracted.
I'm right. I got to rubber stamp the ESPN ride.
Disney trampoline park.
I'm working on that right now.
Proving designs for the Craig Kilborn walk around character.
Disney Cement Company.
We're going to own all the cement America.
Different colored cement.
Think about it. Everywhere you walk, what's below you? Cement.
Why isn't it Disney Cement?
Could be.
Anyway, I don't know how to like go.
I mean, that's a lot of like how the thing came together.
We're sort of starting to get into it in the beginning.
And like, you know, we're like we're outside the studio.
Right. And we're a Cronkite wants to bring in somebody to show them
the process finds Robin Williams.
One thing that I always wondered about this was how did they film this thing?
If the park wasn't open yet, were there enough facilities
that they could dress a small part of it?
Did they have to film this really close to the opening?
But they also had to animate it.
So that doesn't make sense.
Like, there's no way this thing could have been shot or they did just animation
and then film the rest like four days before the park open.
That doesn't make sense.
And I realize this is a fake Disney MGM studios you're looking at.
They film this at Raleigh Studios, which is across from Paramount.
And there is an earful tower in the background.
But that was like a large scale, maybe like a forest perspective thing.
Or they only built one side of it or something.
Or they put it on top of a roof so they don't have to build the entire water tower.
But anyway, that's just one of those little things that because I feel like
I clocked that when I was a kid.
Like, now, how did they film this?
Yeah, I was I already was going into like the technical things
because I took you right out of it.
Yeah, complete. Yeah.
Well, that's a sign I needed to like make videos and stuff,
because I was never in it.
I was never I was always picking apart the behind the scenes,
especially from this tour on.
I mean, this had a huge.
Oh, my God, this animation tour.
Like, like I would the two the tour groups would pass and lap me
and I would like stay back with.
I recall that happening to us.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Because I wanted to be an animator.
I think I thought that too before I realized that's an insanely hard thing to do.
Yep. I want to be a comic book artist or an animator.
And then I was like, holy shit, this is hard.
Yeah. Yeah.
The hand drawn animation.
One of the hardest things like a certain point, it's just like, I'll never.
Now, maybe if I was I didn't think I could get better.
Also, that was a problem.
I was like, well, that's as good as I'm getting.
I know as a child.
This is not going anywhere.
Yeah. And no, no one.
I guess I never expressed that.
No one ever was like, you know, you're little still.
You know, you're not.
You can dream.
Yeah. You can go to advanced education to learn how to really do.
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't know.
You desire to be the least paying occupation and the second least paying.
Yeah. No, I I feel like every few months now,
there is like a news story about like a big Marvel comics artist.
Will shit on the company on like paying low rates or being behind on royalties.
And then like five or six other artists will be like, yeah, I'm right there with you.
And it's just like these great, wonderful artists just getting screwed left and right.
Yeah. Well, luckily, Mike figured out some solid careers.
Actor, pitcher of projects in Hollywood and podcast.
Yeah. Three extremely dependable.
It was easy. All of them are easy.
You are not lucrative.
You're not going to believe which is most dependable.
The answer may surprise you. Yeah, yeah, really.
OK, so, yeah, we get into it.
Fake Disney. I also just liked it because I thought the same thing about
Muppet Vision 3D.
I was always like when the wall gets broken at the end
and Kermit comes up on the fire ladder, I was like, what's back there?
Did they go right there?
But it also doesn't make sense that they would have done the entire product.
So what you're seeing there, they they filmed
Muppet Vision 3D at the Disney lot.
And then I think that is some like old like town square kind of sets
elsewhere on the lot that they dressed to look like a little bit theme parky.
It's a little hazy.
I feel like there's a lot in the background to kind of like.
So you don't focus on anything.
And then there's just a million of the Mickey Balloons.
Mickey Balloons is what that's a perfect.
Yeah, yeah, some some like no nonsense guy on set for sure.
It's like just put Mickey Balloon, Mickey Balloons up.
That'll do it. That'll sell it.
This is the real magic of the movies is trickery.
That's what we all learned at Disney MGM, it's all tricks.
You see, we learned everything.
It really sobered us up at, you know, seven to nine years old.
Yeah, it's all fake.
You mean sadly eating your meatloaf at 50s primetime diner?
And like, I don't.
Is there any like that's impressive?
That's insane.
There's no way Jason was ever sad eating meatloaf at 50s
primetime cafe.
Not one of my go tos was until a Boston chicken.
Later, Boston Market opened up down the road from my house.
The only reason I'm not going to ask you further about that is that this is
that's going to take us to another 20 minutes.
Yeah, you know, I got I got takes on it.
It was next to the little league field where we play baseball.
That's another 20 right there.
Next to the little league field.
These days at Hollywood studios, can you learn how shifting gears is made?
Is there anything about shifting gears?
Tim Allen's ABC sitcom?
I don't think so.
And that's a crime.
That's what I believe is missing from Hollywood studios.
There should be some new stuff.
Is Doctor Odyssey ABC?
It is on ABC.
So there should be Doctor Odyssey learning how to make Doctor Odyssey
and learning about the magic of TV.
If any movie studio learn about attractions remain, it is learning about
how to make things that stopped being made 37 years ago.
Right.
That is what that is.
What these are now.
But that's the thing. It was so current.
It was so vibrant watching this as they are cresting the hill.
Like this comes out in 89 Little Mermaid is like we're about to get
into second golden age.
So then you're seeing it in the subsequent years and we're in second golden age.
And everybody wants to know how these things are made.
Yeah, like like truly was magic.
And the fact that they got him in before Aladdin.
So by the time Aladdin comes out, like, oh, my God, it's like a little extra Aladdin.
It's more Robin Williams transforming.
It's it's incredible.
This thing was so fun.
Do you want to just like call out moments?
I don't think we have to like step by step it.
But basically Tinkerbell.
Well, one thing you get is a real like here's a joke for the parents is the
like, you know, Cronkite asks, what's your favorite animated film?
Or what animated film would you want to be in?
And he does this joke about, well, I've always found Fantasia to be a bit
Fellini ask, I don't know.
I didn't get that then.
It's a really good proof that like you just put in some word
that like reads as a grown up thing.
And it doesn't matter that a you should respect intelligence.
Like you pull the room.
No, no kids would know who Fellini is.
Maybe little Jason.
But besides that, I barely get the reference now.
And I've watched a good amount of Fellini movies.
I don't. Yeah, I don't necessarily understand why Fantasia in particular is
Fellini ask.
But I like the I like the snooty voice.
Yeah, the joke works with the snooty voice and the reference.
That's really great.
But he sneaks that in and then it becomes about
Peter Pan and the magic of Peter Pan and like, oh, getting to be in that world.
And then I'm glad he said
Peter Pan, because Tinkerbell happened to be in Walter Cronkite's pocket.
So if he'd said another movie would have been screwed.
Uh huh. Walter Cronkite.
Sorry. No, no, no.
Walter Cronkite picking up a cartoon, particularly I like.
And that feels very Walt Disney.
Yeah, sure. Yes.
Having to like mind the space of the little that they made him
like figure out cartoon space.
They made him do a little bit of mocap avatar acting.
He looks like Captain Kangaroo, too, to me.
He does. Like very like kid show host.
He's part Captain Kangaroo, part Walt.
Of course, we like him.
Yeah, like this is this in particular, like this image here.
That's great. Well, you're showing that he's holding up
not Tinkerbell, but holding up little lost boy Robin.
Yeah, which is, I guess, a good way to transition into, you know,
we go into this room.
This is how Jerry reason wants to hammer home
that animation is about stories.
How better to do that than a room with giant books?
And that should that which really just illustrates
like how all animation starts with
stealing the story of a book that's existed for a long time.
That's the beginning of Disney innovation.
That is now I felt like little Scott at that moment
because I kept pausing and going like that green screen
or just plywood they painted to look like big books.
That's all. You know, I think the VHS quality
that you're going to watch it in on YouTube masks that.
But yeah, those are big old books.
And that's your show.
You the behind the scenes photos show that some of which are on
Jerry Rees dot com and some of which are on the IMDb of the
of this particular movie.
So that's how a story is made.
And then we go to the sound studio.
Oh, wait is I think I skipped the storyboard step
where the story is laid out and Robin doesn't really have any say in it.
The story already exists.
It's a story about a new lost boy
who is planted on Captain Hook's ship alone
without the help of anyone else in the Peter Pan of hers.
This poor boy doesn't seem to know the other lost boys
is just like plopped in his PJs
onto the most terrifying location in in Neverland,
which is saying something because it's all terrifying to me.
Of course. Yeah.
But you got to admit, Robin Williams lost boy is pretty cute.
Yes, absolutely.
Yeah. Well, that's the whole thing about this.
Like, Mike, right off the bat, you mentioned my version to this world.
I don't have any of that with this. I like his lost boy.
I this is like it's a very palatable take on Neverland.
I think mainly because you only go on the ship
and you see Peter Pan for one shot only.
Yeah. And none of that other crap.
You like Neverland.
None of the creepy crap.
None of the racist crap.
There's a ton that you don't have to go do.
You see some pretty mermaids waving at that.
Yes. Robin Williams.
That's that's plenty.
Tinkerbell. It's nice to see Tinkerbell.
Absolutely.
It is a little implication of an adventure to come,
but I don't have to go on it.
I get to go look at animators desks
and not be stuck in this stupid world for 80 minutes.
I was so excited to see it on the other side of plate glass
and stare at animators desks.
Even more.
Huh?
Sorry, I get distracted at looking at your iPad.
That looks appears to be a screenshot of Walter Cronkite's giant face.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, what's what are you illustrating with that?
That I we hadn't gotten to there.
Sorry, sorry.
I I force you to bring this up.
He's like hyping up the tension.
He's talking about editing and sound effects,
and he gets a little scary and they light Walter Cronkite from underneath.
I see what you're saying.
He looks a little sinister.
And I was like, that's such a good trick.
And I think I don't know if we're giving Walter.
I think Walter Cronkite is having fun with this.
Oh, I think he's having a great time, like everything he has to do.
And yeah, I think he's having fun.
He's a nice counterbalance to Robin Williams talking a mile a minute.
Will you make that the background of your iPad or the home screen?
I would like that as well.
I would also vote for that as well.
Oh, that's a boy. You got nothing going on there.
Oh, make Walter Cronkite.
Both of them. Great, great, great. Yeah.
Are you sure you want him to do this?
We're going to lose him for a while.
OK, OK. I mean, for the listener could take our word for it
that he made it the backdrop.
I want you want to know that it's true.
I'll hear the joy in my voice for the rest of the show when he does it.
It's a very I think you probably respond to that over on Jason's lap,
because it was I think it was very Vincent pricey.
Oh, I guess you light him from down low like that.
And suddenly Cronkite is price.
Yeah. Do you think I've said this before?
I don't necessarily like it when news people, serious people
in the media do like shows and movies.
I don't anymore. I used to like it.
I used to love when, you know, because growing up here,
it was often like my local and the anchors are in things.
I'd see Kent Brockman inspiration, Jerry Dunphy
in like volcano or independence day or something.
Local guys, I like. Yes.
Yeah, I always like that.
But I don't, you know, like, yeah.
Who on this earth at this point is like, you're telling me that
Jake Taffer is is a Taffer Taffer.
I'm sorry. You got Taffer.
I always have Taffer on the brain.
That was guaranteed to happen.
You're telling me that Jake Taffer is like a funny guy with a sense of.
Yeah. Telling me Anderson Cooper goofs around a bit.
Yeah, they all they all do so many cameos that there's no I know.
That's what I feel. I don't like.
I don't think I like it.
The only one I like is the Wolf Blitzer Mission Impossible one.
I was going to say it doesn't get better.
That one is good.
But the other ones, I don't love it.
But like, I guess it was so like he was retired for a long time here.
And what else is he going to do? He's going to host specials.
He's got a good voice.
Yeah. Present.
I'm trying to remember any other was I feel like I can't conjure it exactly,
but I feel like there was a serious news guy who showed up on Sesame Street
for some reason, that era, because they didn't used to goof around.
Peter Jennings or something.
Could have been Jennings, could have been Sam Donaldson, somebody.
And it was on like a more like more of a special.
Sesame Street did great specials.
There's probably one that's rare right for us to talk about.
Don't remember who that news person was.
Yeah, I don't know.
But Cronkite could have been Cronkite.
I don't know. Cronkite, Sesame Street.
I could see it. Don't know.
It could be any of them. How's that iPad coming?
I'm working on it. I'm working on it.
You've got it. It's on there.
He did it. His face is on there.
I'm not sure what he's.
He's not giving himself that he just wanted to be.
That's really weird, because all your apps are covering his face.
But he's got the home screen, too.
It's the last.
Oh, it's six o'clock, you see.
That's good. Comforting present.
Yeah, he did that on the mic.
Oh, good. He rotates, too, whenever it's.
Oh, yeah. Hey, look at that.
Looks good. Horizontal and vertical.
Hello, Jason. It's so complicated to do it nowadays.
I feel like I haven't changed it a lot.
I never changed it all to default.
I'm sure glad you did.
Soon, AI will have him talking to you every morning.
Any alert, he'll be able to say,
Wow, Jason, Mike just texted you about a new sandwich at Burger King.
Like that. Oh, that's the future.
You're on about target toys without Scott is blowing up.
I and Apple started playing a slideshow with music.
Of songs or of, excuse me, of photos of yours.
Photos of this nice photo.
Didn't start revealing your top five Apple songs, did it?
In front of our.
Oh, he's playing it again.
Is it all your different Walter Cronkite photos on your iPad?
No, is there a nice trip to Orlando in 2023?
As you can see me in front of the incredible.
Boy, if he just if you if we just said, here, one should play it for us.
And then like a few photos in there were,
let's just say, Jason being a sexual being.
Whoops. Oh, boy.
From the Orlando trip.
Well, yeah, look, we all know how port of entry makes this guy feel.
Port of it. Yeah.
You get a Crescent Moon Bakery Club sandwich in me.
My my. You get a cigarette and a crescent.
You get a cigarette, a sleeve of mini cinnabons.
Oh, the sleep. We forgot about the sleeve.
Got about the sleeve.
Get this guy's sleeved up and all of a sudden Ferro's Lighthouse is rising.
Jane's spraying me with like the water bottle.
You get to spray your cat at the lover's suite at Ferro's Lighthouse.
All right. Let's get let's let's find our way.
Let's weave our way out of this.
You know, it's another thing that you love to see also is like those
something that is obviously not part of the process today,
but the big jars of paint, the bright.
Oh, yeah.
Paint are so pleasant.
I did something like a like a class down there where I got to do what they do.
I got to paint this a cell, but backwards.
You paint it on the other side so that the lines still remain.
Right. I still have that.
You guys may have seen it in the garage where we haven't been recording in a while.
But the yeah, I've held on to that forever as a Mickey that I painted.
That's cool. From the back.
Oh, man. I cherish it.
My old neighbor in Studio City,
she owned this house and she grew up in the house.
And she's like, oh, yeah, my mom used to work in the ink and paint department at Disney.
She'd walk a blocker to North, catch the red cart trolley.
Wow. To the Disney lot.
And I was like, man, what a time.
Oh, boy.
Now the red cart trolley.
Don't even move them.
Buena Vista Street.
That's right. Yeah. Yeah.
Stationary and to propose that as an app for I did a long time ago.
And now in the subsequent, that's a PTR curse.
Then it's it's gone away.
Hey, Robert Downey Jr.
said it's not going to run anymore because he was in Imagineering.
They're working on Avengers. He did it.
He did it. Sorry.
86 at X.
It's my acro it actually.
No, I don't. Yeah.
That's a that's a fine line.
We only have we only have so many.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's going to fall into accurate.
No, that's that's yeah.
It's it's so nice. Those jars.
You wish they still did it that way.
Also, I forgot that that gender division.
The girls do the ink and paint.
Oh, right.
I'd rather have them breathing in the fumes.
Yeah, we're not allowed to animate for many years.
That's right. Yeah.
Yes. Very important.
Divine state to keep up.
But you go through all the steps.
You see cells, you see like you see how color transforms a space.
You see how we're on the happy pirate ship during the day.
But then that's a world of difference from dark and foreboding at night.
And then Robin Williams, new Lost Boy character is abandoned,
left to deal with scary sound effects and Captain Hook.
I think I think there is something to this where, like, I like that it's
like this just hook.
I just like I because none of my issues,
none of my not wanting to go to Neverland or Captain Hook related. Right.
Not that I want to hang out with Captain Hook, but I heard the same thing proposed.
I was just at a thing like a mystery screening that some friends put together
and somebody ended up putting it to the audience.
And they said, here's three movies. What do you want?
One of them was Hook.
I watched not one hand go up.
No one really voted for Hook.
And I was like, is that something to this specific group of people?
Or has there been some sort of anti hook turn?
And in the same room, there was discussion of would we like hook more?
If it was just supercut, Dustin Hoffman, Bob Hoskins together
and nothing else.
I know you're doing it, Peter.
I think I'd like it more.
I that's an early going movie.
Memory is hook when it came out.
Specifically, I remember an intermission.
But the last official intermission, I looked this up.
Um, the last movie with a built in intermission was Gandhi.
But I think they stopped hook
so kids could use the bathroom, probably when they were changing reels.
OK, I think they made on hateful eight.
I think hateful eight may have had an intermission.
What's that?
Didn't hateful eight have an intermission on like the longer?
Oh, yeah, I think I think you're saying like the full all.
I am, of course, the brutalist.
Oh, right. Yeah, very necessary.
I haven't seen it yet.
But I looked it up and Hook's runtime is only two hours and 19 minutes.
Wasn't even that long.
Like all the Marvel movies I feel like are longer than that.
Yeah, yeah.
But I think they they built it in.
And as we're talking about hook, I'm remembering how like I
I loved Hoskins and Hoffman.
I liked Robin Williams when he got in the silly outfit.
I had a bunch of hook toys that Christmas,
but I really did not care for Julia Roberts Tinkerbell.
She really bummed me out.
I don't know where this was going.
She's a literal manic pixie dream girl.
Well, yeah, she's like,
does she go like you abandoned us or something?
She becomes human sized at one point.
So you better believe I don't like that part.
Creepy.
When she gets, yeah, it's Hulk.
I love Julia Roberts, but I like and that unnerved me as a kid.
Didn't we talk about like Spielberg didn't get along with her?
Yes, we definitely had this conversation.
We talked about that in the show.
So maybe you're feeling that.
Right.
You're feeling hatred.
Yes, it's true.
Hey, I brought this up on the show before.
I've never seen a minute of that live action.
Peter Pan.
I think they just dumped on Disney Plus during the pandemic.
Did you know Smee is Jim Gaffigan?
Oh, I didn't know that.
I've never seen like a picture even from Tim Walls himself.
It's strange also that this predates Hulk.
Is it weird?
It is weird.
It feels like I've been on the horizon for him.
Yeah, I don't think this also inspired Hulk.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Yeah, because it's just it doesn't.
I mean, he's in the family, though.
So I'm sure I could have helped.
He's the ultimate boy.
You never do it.
And what a run Williams had in the night.
The Hulk.
Goodwill hunting.
Aladdin, like, yes, I think that's all over the place.
And there are also some bombs in there, too.
But yes.
Oh, yeah.
There was all. Yes.
Well, I liked Pysontaniel Man when I was 10.
Did you?
Yeah, I did.
What if you were 10?
You were older than that.
I don't think so.
I swear.
I swear it came out like 95.
Pysontaniel Man was released in nineteen ninety nine ninety nine.
You were 14.
You were just dreaming of it.
I swore it was there.
I swore I went into you had a psychic vision of it.
We saw Pysontaniel Man.
I think you age yourself down in your memory
because of how that's not thought of as a good movie anymore.
So you're like, well, I was 10.
That's why I was just I wasn't a sophisticated 14 year old.
Maybe a silly 10 year old.
Maybe I was just mashing up A.I.
and Pysontaniel Man because of the unnerving elements in both those movies.
A.I. is 99.
Yeah, that is 90.
That's what I'm saying.
Like, well, they traumatized me, so they scrambled my brain.
Oh, OK. All right.
I guess in a general sense, I get what you're saying.
I was annoying 14 year old going like, you know, Stanley Kubrick was he was.
That's like I was just talking about how phenomenon Michael
and powder are all a trilogy in my mind.
Yes. Yeah.
I don't know.
Two of those aren't thematically or two of them are thematically similar.
And then Michael is different.
But because it felt that era of Travolta, the creepy trilogy. Yeah.
Michael doesn't belong in those three, but it feels right to me.
Yeah. Yeah.
And they're all like they're for grownups and continued.
Those are for grownups.
I assume that grownups are big boy movies, big boys, big boys.
Anyway, Cronkite, they look down.
How long do you make it with that scary Cronkite?
You seem forever.
Anyways.
Oh, by the way, that that movie screen,
this might help explain why hook got zero votes is that one of the options
for what movie we're going to watch here was Clifford.
Clifford ended up being that.
So it was kind of a boys who don't grow up.
And I guess given the choice, at least this group went with Clifford,
not with hook.
And I I went with the third choice, the tingler would be Vincent Price.
Oh, I've never seen that.
I've never seen that either.
I don't know about that.
That's one of those like there was like the gimmick in the theater.
With the seats. Yeah. Right.
So I was curious anyway.
Here's what I learned about Clifford on big screen.
I continue to think there are some zones
that movie that are some dead zones.
There are some there are some stretches that are like, OK.
However, I think I've always been a little too hard on the priest wraparounds.
There was a lot of laughs. Fine.
At this priest, I guess.
Him like trying to relate to the kids and then like stuff at them
and kind of stiffly catching footballs.
And I'm like, this is how you can tell the movie's a rewrite is all this priest stuff.
And then I'm like, ah, pretty funny, pretty funny.
Yeah. That's so updated.
I'm working my way up to a Mount of Clifford that I will sign off on.
I'm working my way up to Jason's one hundred.
That's like the perfect film.
You love Clifford. Oh, yeah, I do.
That's what he's saying. Yeah.
Do you think I'm crazy, though?
There's some because there's zones.
Yeah, there's some very dry set up.
There's some long set up or like stuff about the office or sure.
Sure. The girlfriend fiance.
It's all it's all in.
Yeah, there's some there's some Uncle Martin world stuff.
That's a little a little brutal.
But not as fantastic transportation plan.
Those would have been a great, you know, been a public transit.
Hey, Richard Kahn, you know, he's a sidekick on the Blaney show.
He's very funny on that.
It's very fun.
He's in Clifford for so little time, but he's so funny.
And it was a big day. Yeah, yeah.
Fantastic. Yeah, yeah.
OK, so you get your you get your Peter Pan adventure.
Captain Hook is foiled.
I was like the crocodile rising up behind him.
A flying like flying crocodile always fun.
I think the making of this was really exciting for the animators
because I think it was a rarity to like go back in the movies at this time.
This is before all the weird knockoff sequels
and things like Draining the IP.
And they didn't really do this in like kind of TV style.
Bang it out like this is like very quality animation.
And I think if you were a Disney animator in 1989,
you were really nerding out getting to like Captain
draw these characters and draw film style.
So I think everybody found this really cool.
This is some it's like secret golden.
I've seen it presented this way online
that it's like a little secret morsel of Disney Golden Age.
Oh, yeah, that's a good way to think of it. Yeah.
Yeah, it's got that spirit.
It's got the quality. It's got bonus Robin Williams.
It's like extra Peter Pan that doesn't disrupt the original IP.
Yeah. Like fun bonus.
Great bonus.
It is funny that the directed VHS stuff did differentiate it in my mind
as a kid to some degree, even though I watch Return of Jafar
and then the third one, which I can't remember what it's called.
Well, they got away with Return of Jafar and then the rest are right.
Horrible. But but I still I like the it was like, well, that's different.
That's different than this.
This is a different thing, even though they're same characters. Yeah.
But this does feel like right.
Yeah. It feels much more right.
And what an intro like it gets you so hyped to go into the next room
and see how the stuff's made and see the people who make it.
Right. It's great that they I don't know, just that they put so much
effort into that, like what a kickoff that they didn't just bang out somebody
like animation is the art of bringing moving images to life.
They just they said they didn't sit Roy Disney down in front of a teleprompter.
Have him talk stiffly.
It'd be funny to and interesting in some level.
Yeah, I realized earlier I said how much I want to see George Lucas talking.
Right. Right. Right. Editing.
But there's a time and a place.
But it's always a time and a place for a boring behind the scenes person
to read off a teleprompter to me in a theme park.
But a magical, really elevated piece like this, a magical time in the company.
Yeah, it's really the perfect storm of a situation.
The animation is catches fire again as Michael Eisner is just this body
is so confident it's got just his body is so confident.
You heard me.
But I've always thought and said, yes, all of him, all of his pieces,
all of his parts are confident at this moment.
And it's reflecting that in the Disney company and the choice.
Yeah, yeah.
No matter how many serious sentences, the robbing with confidence.
Michael Eisner was throbbing with too aware.
Yeah, he's pushing it too far.
No, before it was just one of those weird things.
Mike says that he doesn't realize how weird it was.
Are you talking about Eisner or Williams?
Eisner. OK.
Yeah. Well, Rob Williams.
Fine. Great. But this is Eisner's doing OK.
Yes. Eisner once in a lifetime talent. Right.
Yes. Man of a thousand decisions.
Yes. Today. Right.
Yeah. A whirlwind of signoffs.
Whatever. Yeah. I want to update.
There is a newer Michael Eisner interview than the one from 2023.
There is a February 16th, 2024 interview with Michael Eisner.
Oh, good. So that's a year should go over a little over a year ago.
What's it about? It's about football.
It's about football again. OK. Yes. All right.
And it's called it.
The video is called It's Great to Be Back.
Michael Eisner exclusive interview.
Oh, boy. So is the interviewer.
Is it like a channel or it's Portsmouth Football Club.
Here's what we got to do.
We got to learn everything about football real fast.
Turn this into a fake sports podcast.
And that's how that might be the way to do it on the show.
That would be going to be a tough road.
Imagine us fumbling through
complete like the absolute basics of football. Right.
The town just north of where I grew up.
Town of Chester, Pennsylvania.
It was always hard hit economically when it like
department stores and local businesses started moving out of the area,
moving, moving deeper in the suburbs.
But in the last few years, Chester has a Harrah's
the of Philadelphia's Football Club Stadium and a prison.
So it's a lot going on there on the river.
We should town. We should start our own Disney prisons.
We should have different characters
drawn on the different cells.
The villains, the scariest villains.
One look at the face of Hades will remind you to never to commit crimes ever again.
You will pay for what you did,
just as Ursula will pay by suffering in the sea for her crime of voice stealing.
Judge Doom has sentenced you to a life here.
Who wouldn't sober up seeing the icy visage of scar
mostly consumed by recent but mostly consumed by the hyenas?
He once called friends.
Judge Doom is taking a hiatus says no matter the crime,
he just kept sentencing everyone to the dip.
The prison menu will be very similar to Mickey's kitchen.
The menu at the Disney store restaurant, basically the same.
We're just going to reuse the recipes.
We're making two dips, one to eat, one to burn people alive in.
Don't mix them up.
One will be bright yellow.
One will be orange.
And it will be Muy Caliente.
Um, I think I think we're heading to the door here.
One just one other thing to say is that this thing was great.
Really like sign of the times.
Cool, relevant, great.
Nineteen eighty nine new theme park piece of material.
Then the animation tour opens in DCA and they just throw this in there, too.
Yeah, it's one of the I didn't realize till today that that was in there.
And good like repurpose it.
I always I would go to Florida as a kid.
I'm like, bring all this stuff to me in California, please.
And then they did.
But so late and to the point where like now Muppet Vision's a little older.
And now this is a little older.
And it's like just feels like it's just repurposed and sitting on a shelf.
Our magic is old.
No, I got put that in the worst of all.
Yes. Yeah. So that's just what happens there.
Like, I don't know.
And for and the other one was a setup to like seeing real animators animate this.
But like now it's like going to the beast.
The beast's den or whatever.
Well, that was good.
Was the Beast Den Library closed?
That was actually cool.
That wasn't. Yeah.
I meant to go do it and then do an episode about it.
But we didn't. I forgot.
Yeah. But that was cool.
Actually, the flowers or the roses in there.
Well, I don't mean to slander the beast's den.
Don't slander the beast's den early.
The is kind of like 2000s, 2010s touchscreens
where you're kind of like smacking it to register that.
The Warner Brothers store, especially change into polka dot.
Yeah. Hey, why isn't this Taz turning into zebra stripes?
How's the future now with only some struggle and effort?
Quickly touch screen changing the screen of your iPad.
I got a very old man on my iPad now.
Lock screen and home screen.
I will sound like an old man going like, God, this took so many steps.
IOS has gotten so complicated.
But no, when we were kids, it was very fun to see this.
The Nickelodeon tour up the highway, where it's like you look out windows
and see sets of game shows or sitcoms.
And then you could see that orange schnick couch.
That may have been the most starstruck I ever was as a kid.
I think we've talked about this couch.
I feel like it maybe got under talked about in whenever we talked about
Nickelodeon studios.
But there was a runner on the show once about a famous couch
that you wanted to sleep on.
And was it a different famous couch?
It seems very possible this runner could have existed and been.
It could have been a different famous couch that you like.
I mean, all TV sitcom family room couches looked very
could have been married with children couch.
Could have been a roundhouse recliner that the guy drove around.
OK, right. There's no end of couches and recliners from famous media.
I wouldn't like to see Jason Sheridan step by step.
Full house, like great couch, friends couch.
Yeah, I wasn't a big friends guy.
Yeah, I like friends as I get older.
But while do this mental exercise, take friends away, a picture of Jason there.
Oh, I'm I'm on board. Great. No problem. Yeah.
The problem is not with the couch.
Problem is not the couch.
You pop Jason in any couch, he makes the couch shine.
I'm not going to be able to see those bowls of coffee they'd all be drinking.
Oh, because they had a big mug.
Yeah. How about just a regular diner mug?
Eight to 10 ounces.
That's more than enough for me.
Really? Sixty.
Just a good old cup of joe.
How big was your dirty soda, though? Huh?
What size was your dirty soda?
I reasonably sized medium.
We all medium, which would be like an extra large in much of the rest of the world.
OK, Jason's getting on the road there.
Just going to update a new new show.
People don't hang out at coffee shops anymore.
It's about a group of friends and they all gather at dirty soda shops.
If you want to appeal to the current kids, extra syrupy, please.
Yeah, this is you joke.
But in Utah, dirty soda shops and cookie shops are very popular
because of Mormon rules of like you can't drink hot beverages or something.
I think they've eased up on caffeine.
Can Mormons not drink hot beverages?
There's some sort of. Is that true?
I think it was caffeine.
That's different than hot.
It was both.
That'll inspire you.
Like your head will start spinning.
Once you realize that beverages can be warmed up,
then you'll start to want the warm fluids that come out of a human body.
I didn't read the book, you know.
But I see you have a train ticket book to Utah.
Dirty soda Stanley cups.
This is a thing.
I feel like that caught on.
Well, there's that soda influencer that's a soda addict or addicted to soda
that you send me sometimes.
Yeah, yeah. He just drinks an insane amount of it.
Yeah, it's like 12, 15 sodas a day.
Different kinds, different soda fridges.
But then he works out a lot, too.
He is in good shape.
And he got the turkey hair.
He flew to Turkey to get the hair transplant.
It I think here, OK, I think it is a mixed answer here.
What I'm seeing is Mormons are taught not to drink hot drinks,
meaning coffee or any tea other than herbal tea.
So herbal is fine.
I'm seeing some results telling me that hot chocolate is fine.
I think it's not.
I think it is a caffeine thing, not the heat of the because by that nature,
like can Mormons not eat stew?
Where does it end?
Miso. I don't know how much Miso.
I don't know if you're getting the best Miso in the world.
And maybe you are, though.
I shouldn't say that.
Maybe there's some Mormons out there who make the best Miso you ever had.
There's a OK.
I remember you remember the movie Swat based on the TV show?
It's Samuel L.
Jackson, Colin Farrell.
I remember seeing that when it came out in theaters.
And there was a weird throwaway line where like the the front desk
guy is like chugging a Dr. Pepper and he's like, and my wife's Mormon.
I'm not supposed to have this.
So I drink it at work.
Like, there's some weird moment in that that has stuck with me
for like over 20 years. Huh, huh.
They did that. That's your Book of Mormon.
That's where you learned everything about the religion was from Swat.
From Swat. Yeah.
Not the squad remake on CBS.
That's different. Yeah, yeah. It's different.
It's important to differentiate.
And not Queen Latifah equalizer, Denzel equalizer.
Right. There's going to be.
I feel I feel like no end coming to like the network
television shows Jason has been watching is reminiscing about.
That's right. This is there's there's an onslaught coming.
But I guess that's why we I guess have to end episodes.
Yeah, right. Save them, save them for those times when it's.
Well, after the two part shark attack episode of Dr.
Odyssey, there's a 9-1-1 Dr. Odyssey crossover.
Oh, my gosh. It's just too much.
ABC is in the Ryan Murphy business.
And they're doing boffo business.
They're doing boffo ABC doing boffo business with this big boy.
All right. You survived.
They're right.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate where it's becoming
extremely evident to me that a Dr.
Odyssey episode is unavoidable and that somehow we will like work
this audience into a lather like Mormons drinking hot drinks going.
It's happening. Dr.
Odyssey episode.
So, you know, get ready. That's coming.
So stay here for that.
And if you want to dig even deeper, join us in our VIP
patron to your club three, where you get one more bonus episode
every month and our regular episodes ad free.
Boy, lots coming up.
Which swat will we do next?