forever
dog
warning the following podcasts
may contain the neon
colors of taco bell
city walk google map detectives
exciting new
literal dirt
and a behind the scenes peek at scott's
recent directing gig on the oscars
wow scott goes to the
oscars city walk goes to hell
on today's podcast
the ride
music
a place for rock
a place for roll hardly
a place where oakland raiders
merch is sold well not anymore
a sublime hot topic
and billabong
some of that maybe
a smattering of that
a place where you can purchase a candy thong
well thank god thank god for now
for now but who knows
what can we trust
what can we grip onto
what can we move into the future knowing
i guess nothing at all
there's the grim tone
in which we enter this episode of podcast
the ride hello i'm scott garner joined by
mike carlson and jason sheridan
uncertainty abound
the markets stock market
and city walk both
everything is unstable the stock market
and the sock market all is unstable
very good point
oh no not
the sock market well not yet but
we don't know
major pieces
in the city walk hollywood line up
have been shattered
have been tossed aside as if it was
nothing
stuff happens all of a sudden too
there's no warning
this is what really is upsetting
to us is the store can close without
warning half the stores can close
while we record
you'd get heads up
possibly
presumably if there was an earthquake
you might get an alert
there's a little bit of a lead
new fires have been spotted
but instead
like the biggest disasters
in the city
the closure of all of these stores
in which we've never purchased anything
the oakland raiders
the oakland raiders store was just closed one day
people hundreds
thousands of people drove up to city walk
to get their raiders merch
on a thursday afternoon
as they always do
thousands of people
well after the super bowl
that they were not in
well well after the raiders
have played in los angeles
they were met with a closed door
a closed helmet
a shut helmet
sealed up forever
I don't want to say
did we cause this
I said we caused this
I've proclaimed that already
the butterfly effect
like the ripples in a pond
when you drop a pebble
you may not
see them for a while
you record a podcast
and then suddenly
the raider image is gone
suddenly years later
years later the ripples take a while to get to the edge
I would like to think though
that we were more directly responsible
not just the butterfly effect is like
oh I take a drink of water now
and then in ten years there's like
bulgaria goes to war or something
that to me was with the butterfly effect
I want to be directly responsible for something
I want it to be like three steps removed
we did a podcast about city walk
it should have been pretty one to one
but what's the theory
of us causing it
what's your more like closely
tied together theory about us causing all
of the city walk stuff
I feel like we directly put it into the air
that
the chapter of city walk
that we all know is closed
we literally closed the book on city walk
that's what I think
so you think they looked around
people are responsible for city walk
I think it's a feeling
I think we put something in that you can't even describe necessarily with words
where they just like felt kind of a
gust and they went
it's done isn't it
if you listen to all of our city walk
multiverse of madness saga
we closed the book on that version
of city walk and now we are entering an unprecedented
new version of city walk
and I believe we are directly responsible
even though I just
asked for it to be a little more direct
I was like no it was a gust
you still say direct
you're very particular
but Jason's was not direct enough mine is a little too
direct
you're dialing the knobs of direct
as precisely as you can
because I think what we did with the city walk saga
what happened there
what we did
and we did a lot
it's going to take decades to parse
everything that we did
artistically
that we can discuss at length
but in this case
I just think it felt obsolete
the current version of city walk felt obsolete
at that point
and never until
the year 2024
did any part of city walk feel remotely
obsolete
vibrant, current, now
very now
everywhere you look every sign that you see
every music track that you hear
could not scream more 2024
it's shocking development
putting in businesses
and restaurants that people
actually enjoy and would like
to patronize
it's quite disturbing isn't it
hello kitty
cookies
you say that and I'm like hasn't everything
that's called the NBA thing
like been an instant failure
it's pretty much a more
narrow lits though
if you want jerseys people want hats
lids is
a big success I feel like but I think NBA
in general seems like every time they open
and locker room by lids
I think it was strange that Jason as proof of why people want to go to the NBA store
pointed at his Philly sweater
at my baseball sweater
people wear baseball stuff
people buy stuff
with the NBA store I think it's really
generally with like the Disney Springs
thing it's tied to a bigger
idea that doesn't seem to work
probably just Jersey store
would work okay I mean I just hope
that's what it is because if it's
anything other than that it's over thought
because what's it called is it called the
NBA store maybe
it better just be a store
as soon as they add any sort of like experience
to customize
your NBA fantasy that's where
everyone checks
out then there's
it will failure
failure will come to it immediately
well there's a lot to
to parse here and it's been a
tough time for sure
you know all of us dealing with a
a crucial place
having been torn asunder
and who knows what else will happen to it
and it's in tough times like this that
all we can do is try to
do is to you know take solace in the
little things the little things like
directing Conan O'Brien's sketches for
the Oscars I'm just
trying to see this as kind of
a consolation prize
in my life in a life that has not
gone the way that I have imagined
that it would yeah you would
trade this experience though if
you could just get Sparky's back
of course yeah of course are you
kidding it was just like
a job fine I
need to stay distracted I as much
you know sure you can just you know
you can mourn or you can try to be
busy and you could try to try to
move past it right now that's
over all I have is free time to
to think about Sparky's yeah
yeah and to you know and and
you know to worry about
luck and stone
or whatever the hell that is
something and luck
I think so I went in there the other day too
virtue and luck
I don't think that's right
either I think I pulled that out of my ass
can I ask what you are talking
about there's a store at
City Walk now called like
virtue and luck but I don't I guess
it's a store what does it have in it what do you think it is
it's like stones karma and luck
there you go you bought virtue
and luck no problem I did and I was
right I was there literally a week ago it's a
store for stones I think they got like
not sector stones like crystals
and like worry stones
lucky stones that's my guess again
I will never go in I
they have like big the candles
too and then they have
like things like ceramics
that you can hang on the wall and I think everything costs
$200 I think everything is
very expensive these aren't
why are they there I don't know and it's still
so many of these places don't seem like they're
designed to actually be
to conduct business yeah
there's like jewelry I guess
that's still there for right now
so you can buy
onyx you
can buy jade these are the different
gemstones you can purchase at the
karma and luck that's great pretty reliable
the city for onyx precious
I can't find anything stones and gems yeah
not enough onyx talk on our various sagas
but maybe
that's I don't know
I guess a problem
well you know
the whole thing was about stones so when we
like whatever tortured expansion we
do with all of this stuff we'll have to we'll devote
a whole episode to every stone right
maybe you get your birthstones
up there I don't think so
like your own ring or brace no I don't think so
it sounds too much like something people might need
yeah it does seem like a thing
you might buy as like a fun
souvenir on a vacation that's like a wisconsin dells
thing that's not a karma and luck thing
okay I can't tell
the only vibe I get from karma and luck
is that it is of use
to no one I could
be wrong I guess I guess we'll have to poke our heads
in there and see
but no of course like
like you know here I am standing next to
actual oscar statuettes
and all I can do is worry
that something's going to happen to one of the stores
that sells fake oscar
statuettes that say best aunt
every little thing reminded
me my heart was always being pulled
elsewhere you know it's what
made this a tough situation
but a situation worth
talking about for a minute if
y'all don't mind
what's that yes yes
of course yeah
no it's a little bit of old news
as you're hearing this and we'll touch
on this for a minute before we get to the real shit
but we
yeah you know
y'all went scott free
for a couple of episodes and I thank
you for doing that because things
got really crazy for me because I
got this gig of a lifetime
which was directing Conan's sketches
for the 97th academy
awards this was
so bonkers to get to do
just the thrill of a lifetime
you all would see
because of all this this has been going
on also on top of me I'm like I've been
finishing the movie yeah the movie
that I've been working on since September
this also landed perfectly as we're like
wrapping picture on it and these things
that I've committed to on the movie like all
of course all of this at the same time
so the podcast we've basically
been just doing like one a
week like on a weekend
and I come in just with a flurry of like
I don't know I might be doing the Oscars I'm not sure
we'll see I don't know
and I feel like I
don't know I like would always dump a lot
of crazy stuff at you every
time I saw you guys I was
like sometimes you're like it's on it's maybe not on
it's different it's on but it's not the same
it's different it was radically different
reports yeah every time
and so I'm thrilled at this juncture
to be able to say it came
together it worked out beautifully
just a little bit of like
backstory here and how
this came to be and thanks listeners by the way
for saying nice things via
via social media
but basically
so I used to work at the
at the TBS Conan show
and my main bread
and butter there was directing
videos and you know
all the way from like little sketchier things
which is how you and I met Mike
as you're jumping onto a bed a
futon made of ramen
and all the way up to big
crazy things like like you know
big stylized cold opens
that were kind of
cinematic when he would have like entire
casts of a show
on the show like I got to do these cool
things that were putting Conan into the
world of Breaking Bad and Walking Dead
and then I left the show
and they would still bring me back
to do these things like it was this market
that I sort of cornered
and was so honored to get to do
you know like I Conan was
driving around in the real Batmobile
from Batman versus Superman
and we put him in Sons of
Anarchy and he was on a motorcycle
and it was just this
awesome stretch of stuff
that I got to do.
If I can pay you a compliment you directed
the Wes Anderson
Star Wars? Oh yes yeah
that always made me laugh so much
because he's such a distinctive
director with such like clear
tics in visual
styles and I always thought you really nailed
that. Oh man oh thank you you know
that also that was one of the first things I
got to do with the show I was
pretty new I didn't write it but I
was thrown in with I think that was a Dan Cronin
and Todd Levin two great
guys who wrote for the show
and yeah I
that felt like a oh geez
if I'm coming in with the hype of like this guy
directs I got to really nail that one
and I love Wes Anderson and I got to make
that look right feel right I also
got to act in that
I was very excited in that piece to get to do
I was like I'm going to try to do not
an Owen Wilson which everybody does
but a Luke Wilson can I
pull off a Han Solo via Luke
Wilson and I don't I've never
seen that impression anywhere else I feel
like I did a decently subtle
the
more thin slice of impression
to get to do and then there was a there was
a part of that scenario because I got to be
in it I was on a
a motorcycle side
car like an old timey motorcycle side car
and the the driver
of the motorcycle proper
was Chewbacca and
when we're riding along the LA River
and that's a moment I think about a lot
in any like situation seems a little stressful
or scary or outside the comfort zone I'm
like when I was there I was like if
you don't sit back relax and
enjoy that Chewbacca is taking you
for a motorcycle ride right now
then then you have no perspective
you have to
enjoy this moment and I tried to
get there when this
came up this is like a wonderful return
to Conan world so basically
like you know that's something that I got to do
for a while but then the TBS show
ended and I was doing other things
and Conan has become this
you know is leading this wonderful podcast
empire and you
know it all felt a little bit in the rear view for
me and
because like a podcast empire does not necessarily
need big
stylized cinematic cold opens
but then he gets announced as the
host of the Oscars and I thought wait a
minute I know something they might need
big stylized cinematic cold
opens so
I figured let me let me send an email
what's the worst that can happen the worst that could happen is that
they ignore me the best that could happen is
I direct the open of the Oscars
and hey that proved to me
take your shot you know if you're
feeling like putting yourself out there it's
worth doing because they
I sent an email they reciprocated right away
they said we were Scott we were already
thinking of you and that meant
a great deal to me and then it was
just kind of a holding pattern for a little bit I
was just kind of like hanging tight and waiting to
see what what they would come up
with or if they would come up with something and just
like weeks proceeding normally
and then all of a sudden oh shit go go
go they're calling you the Academy
his colleague it was so why
like once it took off
it was a launch to put things in
in our terms and
and then I was just like you know
thrown a bunch of possibilities of what could be
the sketches and there were things that didn't end up getting
made and things that got scaled back a little
bit but eventually we landed
on like what what the things were
and if you were watching the broadcast
and you sort of clock some of
these things it ended up
being three little bits one was this little
thing in the monologue where Jeff Bezos
was delivered to the
red carpet via an Amazon
box
delivery guy like throwing it
kind of brusquely onto the red carpet
and that was cool because I got to go to the red carpet
like shooting on the red carpet was
super neat one was called
Cinema Streams which is
a thing we shot in a movie theater that was basically
like imagine a building
where you can stream movies
just like it was like about you know
tricking young people into thinking a movie theater
is a streaming service
that was cool because we got to shoot at the Grove
closed down a theater at the Grove
yes yeah yeah no good like high
end theater to get to do something
in the site of Erin and I's first
date in fact she picked
up tour guide me
at the little city walk
cul-de-sac turnaround
she picked me up and we
went to go see Little Miss Sunshine
if that dates it and I think it does
and that was the first date and then
that is a great date
like that is a perfect
first date movie I went on
a first date once to see
into the wild
remember the
what is into the wild again that's the guy
Sean Penn
did he direct
that it's the guy
who goes off the grid and tries
to like he's sick of the
modern world Kirsten's yeah
yeah
he like dies
in the woods it was a
best-selling book but it was like an
intense movie the main thing
I remember from it is the Eddie Vedder
theme song oh so I'm seeing
yes guaranteed
Golden Globe winning song guaranteed
a depressing film though
ultimately an awkward thing for first date
pretty depressing yeah
didn't get everybody horned up
no
if you and me ended up in a bus going
across the country then we were
kept the temperature more comfortable
yeah you got to be careful
with those things yeah Little Miss Sunshine
a pleasant one I would say
so anyway that was super
fun to get to do but
the kind of the big one
ended up being this
sketch that put Conan into the substance
where
he basically ended up entering
the show
by rising up out of
Demi Moore's back and
this was basically like
like bigger backstory
to this there was another piece being talked about that was
more of a like Billy Crystal
style opening where
he you know where Conan was in a bunch
of movies albeit
with more of a kind of like clever
meta Conan twist
and it
ended up being like it
didn't make sense for them to do because the opening
ended up being Cynthia
Rivo and Ariana Grande singing songs from
Wicked so they didn't want to do like big
musical number and then you sit through a big video
but as
part of doing that I was
watching all of the movies and
like getting excited about like figuring
out strategy for putting
Conan into the movies and by the way
you guys know me we did
a whole episode about this stuff like
I love the Billy Crystal Oscars
I think we're all fond of the Billy Crystal Oscars
so as this is coming together
and I'm like holy shit this is one of these
things where the host is popping up in
the movies and he's like magically
in a tuxedo, Hollywood
this felt just like so
like clean and classic of
a thing to get to do
and I also
and it gave me license to alright
for work what I need to do
is research and study
the Billy Crystal openings
which is like
these things had such a tremendous
influence on me when I was a middle
schooler whenever the hell he started doing
them and
it got me thinking about how you know
you think of those and you maybe think about like oh yeah
it's where he would get green screened into the movies
and I think they did that somewhat
but when I started watching them I was like
the really good
shit is where they just they're doing
stuff practically where they've just recreated
the world of it and he's actually interacting
you know he's running from the
English patient plane that Letterman is
piloting and stuff like the most
effective always are the ones where they just
kind of matched it and did it for real
so the substance was part
of the first one that was being talked about
and that's the one I was salivating
over because like we can
do it for real this bathroom
set have you guys seen the movie by the way
I haven't seen it yet
I really enjoyed this ended up being
my favorite movie of the like
of the season
it's on Mubi
right now I was going to sign up for Mubi
an official Mubi film this is a Mubi
I don't know I paid for it but I like
I think it's represented at least
as a Mubi film I want to try Mubi
for a little bit because they also have
on there the People's Joker
oh really that's where that ended up
a documentary I like
I only learned about recently called Grand
Theft Hamlet which is
a production of Hamlet
done in Grand Theft Auto
whoa really
because I think Grand
Theft Auto
is called RP or Grand
Theft Auto Online I think there's
a lot more flexibility so you can
kind of do are they with like
custom dialogue
yeah like people are
into a gaming mic characters
and car and so they are
trying to line up all the events of the game
to perfectly mirror no
no I think maybe this was
a pandemic thing where someone's
like I think we can do like
people were collaborating
so all these movies I'm like
oh I kind of want to watch all of these
I feel like every once
every four weeks or so you do
just a voluntary ad for a streaming
service this keeps happening
you get so excited about like
and their library is immense
well this one is like independent
and international film
I feel like Mubi is a little
more
it seems cool like
you like streaming services he gets
excited doesn't he especially if it's one that isn't
like one of the primaries he likes good ones he likes
bad ones he likes to talk about
Quibi he likes to talk about Mubi
I just got an email today and Tubi has
equalizer one and two I gotta
go down I gotta learn about the equalizer
okay so you get an email
that says when you get a new Tubi movie in your
they send like a newsletter
every now and then that's why my email is
unusable I just sign up for every
clicker emailing streaming services
streaming services department store
many work emails coupons
as long as it's
a B as long as it as long as it ends in a B
you know it's a good streaming service that's
the rule Tubi emails I'm
looking the last email
I got from Tubi was in 2022
Michael
your movie I haven't opened to any of these
Tubi well it sounds like you're not as
committed to the Tubi relationship
as Jason is I'm not yeah you're
you get what you put in you get it
back that's what love is yeah the love you
make is equal to the love you take
you need to dedicate more
time to just endlessly streaming
and then giving up and turning on the Bar Rescue
Pluto channel sure
I'm excited about
Beetleby I don't know if you've heard about it but Beetleby
it's the new streaming service where you can get all the
Beatles albums they pulled it from all the other
services oh wow so you know for
the low low price of $14.99
a month you get all of the Beatles music
I don't know that's so far fetched from what will be
happening in 10 years yeah I think I just announced the
plan I think that's what it is going to be
and it will somehow present this like
it's a major bargain
better actually those are pretty hard to
track down right yeah yeah no
extremely rare you don't really hear yeah
imagine the convenience of all of the Beatles in one
place you only have to pay every
month for the rest of your life my mother and
I weren't going through her garage at
the old house once and just found
half of all Beatles albums on vinyl
like all the later
Beatles albums well that's vinyl
but you know can you get it sounding
shitty on your phone yeah that's a whole other
thing pay for it
pay up it's just not that same if
the vinyl's not mildewed for me
yes yeah it needs to have accrued years of gunk
that the gunk makes it sound good
but anyways
I like basically this ended
up being so exciting because I
like as opposed to something
that is entirely reliant on post effects
where you maybe
you're like okay well we'll see if we can color
correct it right and insert it right and if his size
isn't weird and you know maybe we can make it look like
as opposed to that it was like oh something
like this we can like we'll leave set
knowing that it was fucking great
we're like physical toys to play
with so when I realized it was
things were lining up for it to become just the
substance like yes I am
so ready for this loved
the movie started analyzing
like pulling all the shots I cut together
a demo of clips
from the real movie and then just like badly
inserting just a still of Conan
rising up out of the body
which you know like was quick
and janky and I just cut it on my computer
but I sent it to everybody and that
gave everyone enough confidence that like oh
this could be really funny this might be the opener
so things start lining up that way
like oh this could be the entrance to
the show so we really got to nail this thing
I felt motivated in the best way
we had to figure out how to do it
and thanks to the fine people at Mubi
who on their YouTube channel
posted an excellent making of
the substance we were able to just go right
to the source and go how did they do it
and we ended up building two
little sets one was just regular and on
the ground for Conan to stand in and do his stuff to
the mirror the other one we built
up like just a two wall set
up on a platform
four feet off the ground because that's how they
did it in the real movie where like
in the actual transformation
sequence where
it ends up being like an elbow comes out
it's a lot more disturbing in the real
film a lot gooey or a lot grosser
we did like the PG-13 version of it
but
they just had a bunch of people down there
like pumping their fists and do
like making weird things
puff up under this
this complicated back
prosthetic basically it was like a muppet
set that's when I got really excited I was like oh
this is how they do it they got to build all
of these high up sets
so puppeteers can be relatively
comfortable underneath so now
I'm like oh my god it's toys we get to build
a set we got to cut a hole in the
ground and then place a
demi prosthetic which was done
you know at some little shop in Burbank
that does prosthetics
for Star Trek and all these great
things like you know so suddenly
there's a woman of demi's
proportions getting into a
plaster cast and I went to go visit
and like oh god this looks incredible
this is going to be so fun
great production designer Dylan Hutchins
figured out how all this would work he really knocked it
out of the park so anyway a lot
of confidence going into the day
because we got like you know it's
going to look so great out of the gate
like very achievable and not a ton
to shoot so we can just like take our time
and play but then here's what happens
what we show
up to set with here was the here
was the plan Conan will be
birthed out of demi he will climb
up out of her then he will have left
something in demi's body he
will have you know is maybe
going to be a soda or a flask
or a watch or something nobody
could really land on the right item
so it's like well we'll just have a bunch of things
and we'll film a bunch of things and that's how
it'll go then Conan
shows up on set I
show him around I show him here's everything that we have
to work with and we're thinking it'll be
like this and then we'll pop over there and should be fun
and I see his gears start
to turn he's like he gets a little
serious and he starts thinking and then
he goes away and then I'm summoned up
to his dressing room five minutes later
where he has come up with entire
new plan new plan is
I left my shoe in there
I have to go all the way back into demi
to get my lost shoe
and I'm like okay oh that's great so then you're
reaching way down it's like you know it's like a magical
thing how far you're able to get and he's like
yeah yeah but like I mean
I'm going all the way in
I want to dive head first
and for my entire body
to disappear into demi
more and
I think for a second
my initial thought to that is not it's not
no it's like of course we're going to figure that out
but I just get a little look of concern on my
face mainly because I know that we
built the whole setup for maybe
his shoulders to get through
like possibly you know we literally
just cut a hole
with really precise measurements
and if we didn't do it exactly right like the whole thing
might cave in so I just kind of
furrow my brow and Conan takes
that as me saying no or something and he's
like Gardner relax you got
to cool down I'll be fine I'm a
rubber band man you'll see it's going
to be great like
and I go no no no I am not saying no
I just have to go talk to three people to make
sure and like come on cool and he's like
slapping me on the arm I'm like I can't let
the boss down I gotta
it was also very nice
after all this time I haven't I have not like
worked with Conan since
I did the calculation it was 2017
the week that we first
recorded podcast the run
when we went down to comic con
and did those bits
so it's been the entire
length of the show since I actually
got to collaborate with this man
and it was like no time had passed
he's slapping me on the arm
he's calling me Gardner the desert rat
which is a world war two reference that I
you know still have not taken the time to understand
but that's what he called I'm the desert rat over there
so anyways
we get this cooking
we get to that moment
alright here we go I'm going to do the dive
we're only doing one take and he
starts and I'm like I don't know where this is
going to go I don't know if he's going to get
stuck he's got like stage
hands helping him down there I don't
like we did not build it wide enough
for this gag and I'm like
as long as we get some piece it should be good
instead we watch and we watch
and he goes all the way
down he slides all the way
perfectly into that thing
this is a slender man this is a guy
in very good shape
61 he's like I should never
have doubted it he was he just like
perfectly burrowed in there
it was astounding to watch
and you know
A is a physical feat I feel
like I watched a little like Olympic act
occur but then B
watching this guy
a hero to all of us I think
come into the room
see through the matrix like something
that nobody else saw that is actually
the funny thing about
the piece you know
just like charge past any doubts
anybody could have had it's going to be great we're going to do
it I'm doing it stop asking
questions and like
the spirit of it watching the genius
at work it was so inspiring
he's been my hero forever
he's been my hero since high school he's even more
my hero now this was the
coolest shit unbelievable
to watch I loved this man
especially because the show
was great too you guys watched the show
right I loved all of it I
loved the monologue I loved the song
I loved Sandler I loved
every bit of it I hope they
I hope they ask him back and
yeah it was just I'm so blown away
one of the best things about
Conan is man of a million ideas
and if the funniest idea
involves him putting his body
on the line you will do it
yes absolutely well and it also
I went like oh and this
is the guy who's been like he stayed
in prime shape with this travel
show with Conan O'Brien must go
like you know where he's performing
physical feats every episode he
has yeah he does like it is comedy
first safety second for sure
I also got to watch him act out like
what would happen if he
got down there slipped weird
broke his neck and then I watched him act out
an entire here's what the Oscars would
be like if I had to do it with a broken neck
which is just perfectly
spun out of his brain with no
effort whatsoever
he's insane it was wonderful
it was just you know great great to get
to be part of it a surreal memory
came to me as we're talking about all this is
I remember being out
here for college going to universal
Hollywood for the very
first time where we are minutes
away from for the first time
and then coming
leaving and then
immediately getting back to
our apartment and turning on
the Conan O'Brien hosted
Emmys oh really
those were like killer
yes yeah 2006
oh another great I mean I watched that piece
too that had a fantastic cold open where
again it's like host in tux and
he's stuck in lost and he's stuck in the
office yeah also all done
practically like he just went and did
it came to he like smashed down from
the ceiling onto
Dwight's desk or whatever it was
yeah yeah of course I mean like the pedigree
has always been so high for
all of these things and I just I just wanted to
to follow in the footsteps and make it make
it cool and it was it was really fun to get
to do
the other crazy thing about it
you guys know
listeners may know if anybody
has ever clocked that I am a
huge unabashed fan of the Billy
Crystal Oscars you might know this
from an episode that we did a few years ago
that was like collecting all of this
kitschy Oscar nonsense
and talking about all
this insanity the Rob Lowe Snow White thing
and that was that was
an episode with guest Ryan
Perez our good friend
a guy who we're all very
fond of and when
you know so the substance part
was that was like a pre tape that was done with like a week
to go before the show a few days
before the show there was one little piece that we
had to add to it which is just like it was
supposed to feel like it was on the live broadcast
with the stage manager
going back and knocking on the door and saying Conan
we're ready for you when I realized
okay wait this is a thing
we have to film it at the Oscars
it's got to be a guy
who seems like a plausible
real guy who's not going to be like
you know doing some goofy side
bit we need like a great character
actor who sells this
part I was like
there's only one man for this job
must be Ryan Perez and you know
if you heard that episode I mean like
we've watched the Oscars together forever
you know like the epitome
of a cinephile to me. Yeah Mr. Movies
Yes. Yes. And this
year the Oscars were kicked off
by Mr. Movies. I know. Him so
and as I was feeling this all come together
and it did successfully land as
the opening of the show I was like oh my god
are the Oscars going to go
from Ariana Grande and Cynthia
Areva is it going to go from the wicked
note from the
defiant gravity note to
our friend Ryan Perez and indeed
that is how it played out I am so
proud I've never been prouder of anything in my
life it was like
amazing to get to put together
and to be like running around the Dolby
with him with like our holding
room to wait for that bit was
the theater they were like here you guys wait
here open door we're both
in the Dolby theater for the first time
ever like we've been watching this show
our whole lives and now we're in the room
we're watching a fake Emma Stone
hand a fake award to
what's her name from Amelia Perez
like a rehearsal only
award. That's another cool thing about
being around there is that you get to see this like
it almost feels like a weird like fake wrong
AI Oscars
where like all the details
are like okay all the right
things are happening but it's all the wrong people
like their faces aren't right
and it feels like they all have seven fingers
just watching the demo
Oscars was cool as hell
there was a musical
number on it that was kind of
derided a little bit there was like a James Bond
song
medley and I caught in reviews
later and you know just people analyzing
it like why was there that that was kind of
a weird you got Doja Cat doing
diamonds or forever what is that that's
what all the reviewers thought I got to watch that being
rehearsed and I'm watching it from the fifth
row in the theater and I'm almost
in tears I'm like the majesty
the magic of
oh my god skyfall
somebody came down from the ceiling and then somebody
else went back up like I was like
this is I almost wanted to tell people there's this James
Bond thing you are not going to believe so
I guess I was like I thought that was cool
oh great well
so did I
you would have lost your mind in person
sometimes it is just I've heard people say this
about musicals that you just get wrapped up
at like the power of people singing
no matter what it is
and that's kind of how I felt
so like yeah
I did want to ask because one
of the big viral
things of Domine's this year
of like oh my god
look at this goofy French bullshit
was that clip from Amelia Perez
where they're singing from penis
to vagina
did anyone pitch from
nominee to winner
oh geez
that would have been a good way to do it
there was definitely
discussion of like
can you do an Amelia Perez beat
of a thing like this
you don't want the most annoying people
to like latch on
Conan's Amelia Perez joke
was killer
about to like
a few less f-words than
uh
Casone's PR
about the publicist
yes yeah yeah no no agreed
all the jokes were killer
it was cool to see the videos
have like joke run off
and knowing like oh my god Demi Moore watched
this she was in the front row
and she watched this occur
I think she lost best actress
sorry Demi
I loved it I have a big fan
I loved substance and I also
very cool that I cut this little video
from cutting the little video on my phone
to less than a month later
director of the substance
Cora Lee Farja
is posting about I had a little back and forth
with her on Instagram
she really liked it and was posting about it
cool as hell
this is I just I'm coming to you
with Hollywood Magic
Hollywood Magic is real
I'm feeling it it's coursing through my veins
here I'll sing
I'll sing the Defying Gravity now
that wasn't bad
that actually wasn't bad see
Hollywood Magic is real yeah
well congrats on doing it
I mean Conan we all love
Conan and I love the podcast and stuff
but it was good Conan should be on TV
doing stuff and I'm glad you were
part of that too
there was a lot of comfort in it
I feel like if it had been like
you were doing stuff for the Oscars but it's all people
you've never met before there would have been a little
scariness to that
but being like it almost
what over rode
that was oh my god
the Conan TBS show is back and in this
bigger better way because that show it ended
really quietly in this weird pandemic way
and everybody felt that way even the people who were on
staff back then were like it
felt like it never had like a
big finale and then they
all got to do the Oscars together and I
got invited to the party too it's a
really special group of people all those
writers are fantastic and everybody
wrote that Jesse Gaskell
and Laurie Kilmartin and Mike Sweeney
the greatest the greatest ever
the head writer who brought me on years ago
it was
yeah yeah I know and that
was and with the substance thing just like
you know less than it being like
it's about this year's movies
or that less than trying to do something
edgy or whatever it was like oh
it's like big physical silliness
for Conan O'Brien to start the show with
I just I felt like
I felt the
baton getting passed to me of an important
thing and something that matters to me
just setting up a cool stage for
Conan O'Brien to be goofy on
yeah doesn't it feel good
it just feels good as a fan
or whatever it is
I mean TV isn't real anymore I guess
in general so I really shouldn't like say oh he used to be on TV
because what does TV mean really
for his YouTube but
him in front of a bunch of people
being goofy is really what I'm talking about I think
yes I mean a big musical number
and like yeah yeah yeah
the sand worm
the Scott Kronick
the Scott Kronick his incredible
wardrobe person one of the best one of the
coolest bits I ever got to do that show there was
a thing they used to do called NCAA
mascots who shouldn't dunk
oh yeah they would build these really complicated
horrendous costumes
that would be like an Olive Garden never ending
pasta bowl or something send people
up to dunk they said the costumes
go flying spectacularly make
a huge mess so seeing the
dune sand worm clearly made
by those same skilled hands
who were also who's also the same guy
making Conan look sharp
like picking great tuxes for him
yeah yeah yeah
it's all ends with that job
just a great
really good detailed sand worm costume
and then he's just doing this stupid stuff
imaginable on stage
yeah yeah yeah oh it's I mean
that's what you want out of him
the guy who had a guy who had to
I didn't realize at the time how much I was
torturing doing things
like please make a Princess Jasmine
costume for Nick Mundy to wear
I threw incredible
curve balls that guy's way
and I don't know boy
I missed I missed this crew just incredible
to get to do something with them again
so thanks for letting me nerd out about all that
I also I'm very happy with how it all
turned out I'm feeling great
about everything and all the support I've gotten
about it it does scare me a little bit though
because there
was another guy who achieved his
Oscar dreams and
shortly thereafter
some stuff went down and the equalizer
himself Denzel Washington
was telling him at your highest moment be careful
because that's when the devil comes for you
that's when the devil comes for you
you know what I didn't even need to finish the sentence
and we isn't that fun
you and Mike
and me and Brian Perez and others
watched that moment live
oh yes all together
in my backyard
and
and I was it just
2024 we did the Billy
Crystal segments
that was 2023
that episode yeah I think it was 2023
okay yeah so then from
2023 to 2025 then
you guys are you and Ryan
Perez opening the Oscars
oh jeez yeah I mean isn't that crazy
yeah yeah I say as part of a little
backyard Oscar gay who who would
have known from the Burbank backyard
Oscar gang to the real deal
and now I'm just nervous about
what does that mean for me what I
do I now I am worried the devil is going to come
for me well I well it's just
this closures at CityWalk is that kind of part
of it well yes I'm worried
that it could be that I'm also I
I'm worried that you know also
in the near future that the devil coming for me
is that episode that we got to do about
puppets oh yeah well
the club three at patreon.com
that might be it yeah I'm
worried that the devil is goes by
a different name which is knucklehead Smith
no he's a silly guy
can I trust him am I worried
no you can trust him he's fine
you can trust him just don't count on it
well that's a good piece of advice
well there's a lot to learn there
but yes indeed from Hollywood's
biggest night to
Hollywood's biggest plight
which is of course the ongoing
destruction of the place that we
hold so dear
so I think you know
we kind of talked at the
beginning with some
assumption that people know what's going on
but in case you don't
there have been
sorry it just made me laugh
like all of that build up and then really what I'm
about to say is some stores closed at a
mall a mall
which has been a long running subject
on the show and the kind
of cruddiness of it has been a long
running subject on the show okay wait but
like kayfabe right kayfabe
we are beloved
lands have been slaughtered and
taken for their natural resources
it draws us there
yes I never craved
sparky's donuts before but now that I
cannot have them
yes you craved a myriad of better
donuts but now that you know that it's not
an option now I need to go to the second
donut location it's anyone
which
I don't know if you want to do that look
voodoo's a tough one voodoo we have never spoken
too highly of voodoo
yeah look if you've
been with the show forever or if
you haven't you've gone backwards
and caught up on on the city walk
saga we have placed
an odd amount of emphasis on these weird
stores these weird names
with on popcornopolis
on the crepe cafe
on sparky's and
due to us doing this and kind of
putting a spotlight on these places and
underlining them I have
a kind of unreasonable amount of
you know just
just affection yeah for
these places and
over the course of I would
let's keep it a really rough time period I would
say like the last nine months
there have been a ton of
sudden closures of a lot of these places
yeah sometimes for them to be replaced
by a newer and better
sounding retail
location sometimes
just for nothing and in
fact if you go up to
city walk right now as you're listening
to this you will find a lot
of dead space I would say that right now
for maybe the first time
ever we've had our complaints about
city walk there's things that we've laughed at
city walk for but one thing
it has never felt like is a dead
mall right now there are finally
stretches of it I went
and walked it the other day there really are
places that feel fully
dead yeah it's a bit disturbing
and this is the episode to
parse that yeah there's a lot
going on there's a lot of feelings
you know there when you talk about
dead space at city walk
previously the only dead space
you would say was
vertical perhaps when we talk
about where wizards was the
three story wizard themed
restaurant and bar well the
entire that yes there was the
the multi-room magic
oriented
bar and restaurant and then I think
some of that space became various
other weird bars
John Lovitz comedy club and
BB King and weird other nightclubs
that all has been nothing
either somewhere between nothing
and sheriff substation
for many years so that
all has been the idea of like
and then up in the loft you can dance the night away
that's been gone for a long time
it's also
I guess it's not new that it's
kind of dead in an area that you can just
walk anyone up there can walk
which is the
unused top level of both
margaritaville and
buka D
Jason
Peppo
is that
for real are you giving the fans what they want
I'm not I'm not I fucking
broke on it I got confused
I started doing the same
battle you know what I you know
Conan I would be
upset if you didn't say Peppo
as good as he ever have decades later
as good as he ever has decades later
some things never change
and that's how I feel about this I hope you never
I hope you never get it
I won't and
once they sat down
and ordered the full
like appetizer salad
entree dessert I'm like well
now I'm really not committing this
cause this sucks
like this food
oh wait so you're saying when you finally ate it
so he's saying that because the food was bad he doesn't feel
he owes it to you learning the name
he's gonna stick it to buka da beppo
by saying peppo I had eaten a lunch special
in the bar before but
doing the full yeah
it was fine wait a second Jason
Jason not to reopen this whole thing
but your defense for a long time
has been I've never been
in there that's why I don't know the name
now you're telling us about this lunch special
yeah when did this come out
hold on I'm talking 2018
city walk one
I went up there
I ate in the bar
I did I had just it was a sandwich
and fries and an iced tea
the polar opposite of like
the family style
buka experience
has always been that you've never
you haven't done it right am I crazy
or
I'm trying to remember
I'm trying to remember cause Abercrombie
Fitch I believe you said
you called it Finch cause you've never been in there
but was there a buka da beppo
also that you said you hadn't been
yeah the defense for a long time
has been I never go over there
now I'm hearing about this 2018
meal and is your defense that because
you only had a small reasonable lunch
which sounds like all the components of a lunch
that because of that
that you it makes sense that you wouldn't know
the name well now I'm
saying that lunch was okay I
was just a bumbling fool and then after
I had the full like experience
which was recently
which yeah
which of course
involves sitting in a booth with a couple
people and ordering different menu items
while a
pretty sizable
prayer group is celebrating
the self publishing
of some Christian book next
to you and they are praying
a lot
were they in the room were they in the pope room
yeah they were in the tiny room I don't think we were in the
pope room well you would have known if they
were in the pope room if you're a religious group
going to celebrate a religious book at
city walk buka da beppo why don't
you go to the you wouldn't ask for the pope room
maybe they didn't know
or they got confused
about B's and P's and they called it the boap room
depends
plenty of flavors
of evangelicals are like
Catholics aren't questioned
that's not real
necessarily could have been people that didn't want to believe in the pope
so they would have been
that would have been a disgrace
do you think anybody just speaking of Oscar movies
did any groups go to see conclave
at the city walk KMC
and then follow it up
like at the pope table
perhaps yeah I think that's a very strong
possibility imagined all of the different popes
that it could have been hey no spoilers
but you know like
you know your Lithgows
that'd be a fun exercise I think to go to the
pope table and imagine John Lithgow's head in there
oh they should change that that's what Disney
would do if it was on property at Disney
because they want everything to be like IP
yeah they're arguing over where they were going to eat
afterwards mirrored the tense
cardinals retreats
no I want to go to two some chocolate
bread no I want to go to the pope room
we will take another
vote alright send out the
smoke signal we have
we have landed on just going to the food
courts and going to different places
some of these places would have been improved
by vaping cardinal
the smell would have been improved by the
presence of vaping
cardinal well we're going to have
to look into this I this meal is
surprising to hear that you had a meal
before this but I don't know maybe I'm
misremembering I just feel like the argument
has always been I've never really
been there and I
I've never really been there doing the
family style last year I did the
family style but the family style is
what's crucial to you knowing whether it's Beppo
or Peppo well I just never thought
about it I like though I like
the argument though that you've never
really been there been
the way you've ordered a big enough meal
that's
even though you've eaten in the restaurant
I always thought well I
hadn't done the song and dance and
I don't really think about this place
that much maybe
then when I did the full book experience
I was like this is not deserving
the respect of me remembering
this
well some listener is going to go through
it feels like there might be a bit
of retconning happening but if a listener
tells me again it's I'm remembering
Abercrombie and Fitch situation was
that you said you'd never been to the store so
maybe that's what I'm thinking of I could be wrong
the smells make my eyes water
make me feel nauseous
from the shirtless hunk that
would stand in the doorway sure
gets flashed by that
universal city
wind blowing the dancing
fountains that's something you and I agree on is
that wind up there so hang on wait a minute
the wind is not at the fountains
it's more at city food there's no
way for it to get but it did it now did
I go up to that top level the other
day and like try
to put myself in your shoes and imagine
this brisk this hurricane
that occurs only on the city food
level did you try getting lately
thing oh I've been up there a couple
times lately everyone's timelines are all
not matched when we were doing city
walk saga last year it was windy
up there it was very windy up there
look I go I go often now
when when my wife says
you want to take our daughter
to the park I say can I take her to city walk
instead park stresses me out too
much park stresses you
out park is great
city of bourbon I love park there's so many
parks there's so many parks
in bourbon I love the idea of park
but every time I go to a park a
bossy seven year old takes
over parenting
from me just body
slams you yeah it's often
rude to me takes my
toddler and just
tries to get her to do everything a seven
year old should do but not a two and a half
year old this this has happened
to us for sure you're not describing an unfamiliar
and I always want to like
just cut and run when a bossy kid
shows up almost every time
to me uh-huh it's so like
when we get there and there's no one on the park I go
oh thank god we
we do that too my son would certainly prefer
no one at the park but you just move to a different
area of the park maybe you gotta stand
your ground you can't only
I don't know like
your daughter deserves a chance she
you have to take her places that aren't city walk or
she's gonna end up like I hate to say it
well look like us like
all of us let's make it us
there's so much fun to be had though
at city walk you know oh yeah nothing
to play on or with no that
not true what is there to
come on what is there wait
wait wait answer the question
what is there to play with at city
walk play with okay there's not
really toys or
like a big wheel no there's not a
slide or swings
no but there's not
a novelty SNL character
cereal box that she can pick up and then
quickly put down yeah she likes to
learn who Gilly is she likes
to go up and down stairs she likes to see
the dinosaur the Jurassic Park dinosaur
on the wall
she likes seeing the dragon
she likes seeing there's a lot of fun stuff
look I take my son up there too I'm
just saying this is not a replacement for park
well the second replacement for park
is there's some play areas
in the Burbank mall that
are not always so populated if you go at the right time
there's that little section of like
hill kind of like this weird like
it almost looks like an art installation
it's weird little plastic
rainbow hills
at the entrance near the
cost plus right and she loves that
yes we've spent a good hour there
that's fun and there's not a ton of kids there
and there's more and more arcades
every six months
round one is
expanding there's a weird
AI advertised
candy land
yes and I don't think that's the only location of this
candy land new kid play
area
soon I mean soon we should do an episode on the
Chuck E Cheese style like Billy
B's that's around here
there's various chains with various
B characters that we could discuss
yes yeah B family characters
well unless look is that a harbor hoedown thing
oh perhaps it is
perhaps Billy B's
people are willing to wait for Billy B's
perhaps it is harbor hoedown also an interesting
thing to say in this in this state
because I look this
is a weird if you if you put on this
episode with a title presumably related
to city walk
you might be wondering well does that
mean we're gonna get an appearance from
an old pal yeah but
we said goodbye to our old pal
no yes I mean there's no way
even how would we contact
our old pal we don't our old pal
and by which we mean the sector keeper
and you know just like I
don't want to spoil the end of conclave
I also don't want to spoil the end of the city walk
Orlando saga
but let's just say it's you know it's
not as easy to contact our old friend
and that leaves us also as here
as his land decays
as the land that forged our
friendship decays we also
you know we're we're without
a guide we don't know the
sectors are all falling apart
and we don't have a keeper to
help us get through the sectors
I mean this is just
I feel
a mess right I don't even feel
are we even capable of putting on a show
or any of the words I'm saying making any sense
by saving the keeper we
may have destroyed
unpleasant city walk
well that's kind of I guess that's what
that's a bad version of what you're saying
I'm saying more like
a positive spin but I guess it could be that
as well we don't know that's some of what we're here to
figure out right what what are
these changes why are they happening are
they happening for the better are they happening
to slowly start piecing
off city walk to no longer
exist what is it this is so
okay let's let's start with
just rumors
and kind of what we know because there's
stuff we know permits have been filed
well can I also have
I don't want to you know
if you've got an order in your head but
it also feels like we should maybe say
some of what has happened yeah sure like
where where we stand today because
I have
I went and looked I found
the list that we made of what's
going to be right you know what's
in each sector and I did a
count of what all of
the I just left it at like
you know because we talked about things that are a little more
abstract like the
King Kong or Walters
Gate the entrance to theme park
employees I didn't count things like that what I
counted were restaurants
and stores places that you could
walk into and have an experience
I and I of that
I counted 57
I didn't
count things that we talked about that were already gone
I didn't count wizards I didn't count the hotels
I didn't count parking garages 57
retail locations are what
we covered in the original 19 part
series since we
did the original series
in what year 2018 yeah
27 of
those places have closed
and within that 9 of
them have closed in the last 9
months that
I expanded it to the 9 months because
I think that's when we lost oh which
one I mean
they really started flying I mean it's
been a ton you know kind of
since November or so
is it worth
saying what we've lost
meditating a little on what we've lost
yes I think it's worth it
the saddest one to me
is sector one sector one almost
doesn't exist and I don't think anything
in the original list is still
oh wait actually I missed one whatever
angle or
angl that's gone
I didn't count that so it's 28
angel yeah is it angel
or angle I think it was angel
there was a few other locations
of that story I think in Malta
I was still going to be angel okay okay
I guess that's more appealing than angle
like startup app
you just remove the vowels
most of the vowels
or put bi on it
and that's how you get your app
sector one this is the craziest one sector
one here I'll just you know what
just for old time's sake sector one
billabong popcorn
opolis fossil
zenzone angel
good luck boys
was that offensive that I did that
or was it kind of nice
I tried to make it
I tried to make it like you know
Jamie Foxx doing Rey but
you know I can't stack up to the original
fossil zenzone angel
long gone billabong popcorn
opolis gone recently
so sector one as we knew it
doesn't exist
yes it's and this is
okay let me say this
we'll save this for the end
I do want to say and tease right now
in case you weren't going to listen to the end of this episode
I was there the final day of billabong
oh oh Mike
Mike I went
up to city walk on the final day
of operation now I was very thankful
that they announced
when they were closing because we don't get that
kind of heads up with other stores
and other restaurants here because Mike you
go through surf wax like no one
is I'm a big surfer
we know that
I love the beach but I
will tease that
I will tease something I got
something happened whoa
at billabong the final
night of billabong
and we'll end with that
something happened tears were shed
scars were forms
that will last forever and it's interesting
it was funny I'll say this it was funny because
for a couple weeks I think you know
how you see a store going out of business they have
those big yellow signs and they have some
company that comes in there and like figures out a way
to trick people into thinking they're getting a deal on the
clothes or whatever and
this is what was happening at city walk
for like a couple weeks you'd have big yellow signs
going out of business sale at city
walk which just didn't feel quite right
I don't know why I thought it was
funny just like just like some
common stores some dirt place
yeah this is this is the finest
shopping institution on earth just shouldn't
be the case it just feels too low rent
how did it ever come to this but
yes this whole chunk is gone
it's all gone and empty
and now we were talking about this
they're building a hotel
right here in this area
and this is a key piece that people may not know
this has been rumored for a long
time and I think this is pretty official
that they are building a pretty
big hotel that's going to wrap around I don't
think we know the exact lay of the land
but it certainly it is
more akin to Grand
Californian being right there
mixed in with the retail
bordering the park
and I think it's going to wrap all
the way around to another
Fallen Brother
Saddle Ranch
and it'll take over a lot of parking
lot that's that's sort of the
a lot of stuff that is like non garage
just one level
parking is going to become a hotel
and the current security
corridor oh yes right
will be knocked down
and it seems like we'll get replaced
by some sort of more permanent facility
where like Disneyland
the security happens before you're even
in the mall so the way you have to go
through security to be in downtown Disney
seems like it's going to be the same
for CityWalk
get them up to CityWalk
that's going to get them up there
doing a quick metal detector
pad down it's going to bring
the people in
it's about time because
if I see some some godforsaken teen
with a switchblade
starting to you know climbing up and starting to
carve up with a cow that's upside down
on top of the Ben and Jerry's
protect CityWalk yeah I will
kick that switchblade
out of their hand put it in my
hand and slice them up a little bit
turn their face into a slice
house if CityWalk was its own
country and we could enlist in
its army we would
it's the only one
yeah yeah no if there was a
CityWalk flag CityWalk was its own
country we would always stand
and salute it we would I would I will
draft a bill
to let CityWalk secede from the
union so we
can have it to be its own country
does sound like a good deal hey the three
of us and the listeners
let's go find some places to you
know right I guess whole
you know well all right here's the plan you can't really
live there yet so we'll just
go sleep in the bathroom every night
hide on top of the toilets until
the security guards stop checking legs
yeah and then we get to live at CityWalk
as a sovereign nation forever beautiful
yeah and you know like in the way
that medieval castles and
stuff are fortified with moats
soon CityWalk will have a whole
building full of rooms that are difficult
to escape from oh well that's
we haven't even gotten over there that's the other side of the
place the whole other side of CityWalk let's
keep progressing via sectors
in sector two we have lost the crepe cafe
this is I knew it was serious
when we lost crepe cafe
because crepe cafe has sustained
for many many years in
which I imagine you know
a total of six people bought a
crepe per day so
you know if they're able to
live to survive in those
conditions yeah and then suddenly
you're gone I knew this was
a transformation yeah this was
nothing we could turn back from right and
and you know I should say
and I don't know if it's completely true we've said
I've said this at least a hundred times on the show
at this point it feels like
universal we've heard universal
is going to replace everything with universal owned businesses
yeah well this is something that's said
a lot about what the plan is or why this is happening
seems like that's not the case
as far as things we've heard now or
at least it's not so the folk at least
in the moment right now it's not the case
yeah it is still all these outside things
hot topic and Ben and Jerry's
still standing well yes they are still there
but yeah it's not everything not by
any means you're right you're right by the way
if I say any of these and you know what
the replacement is feel free to shout it out
I don't think I do in all these cases I'm trying
to remember now I look I've been
I hope he doesn't mind I've been
communicating with universal high
the Twitter account or
Peck's account a little bit okay one of these
accounts that's been tracking all okay I was
I was correct now apparently
there was a permit filed
for halal guys to
replace crepe cafe
which he
says is now it's been pulled
the permit doesn't exist anymore oh my
god what happened so what
happened would immediately
be the best food at City Wall
like number one
anything that goes in goes straight to number one
number one with a bullet
like I love halal guys
I haven't had in a little while some people said the Glendale
location has gone
downhill a little bit but I always liked it when I had it
and that's a chain
and yes that would be very exciting I didn't
know anything about this until today
but apparently it's not happening or it doesn't seem like
it's happening so we
don't know what's going in the crepe cafe
we certainly don't know what's happening with billabong
and all that stuff no idea no idea
mini monster
has recently departed yes
now mini monster is that one
that's being replaced by this new dessert
location insomnia cookies
insomnia cookies
Jason in a previous episode
you before time
pulled whatever story you have about
insomnia cookies now is the time
what do you know about insomnia cookies
okay well we're flashing back to 2005
or 2006
and at that time in
Ithaca there was warring late night
cookie delivery services
the late night wars the late night
wars yeah and
one time
one of my older roommates and I
he had his own dorm room that year
and we were just hanging out late on
a Saturday watching
mystery science theater 3000
on DVD sets
as you would it wasn't
a thing that you could before the streamers
this is before a Tubi this is before
a Pluto before you could just
pull it up on any
streaming free channel
and
we were like hey
you want to get
you want to get cookies
do you want
because there was one
the one I liked would sell cookie
like slight slices of cookie cake
or they'd bring you a Ben
and Jerry's pint for five
dollars and the economics of this
was all insane at the time too because
it's like why did the place
like that sold five
dollar calzones deliver one
five dollar calzones how did
that make sense
these are the mysteries that Jason has been grappling
with for 20 years I've been still thinking
about it so anyway insomnia
cookies had just opened
so at about one or two in the morning
we ordered a set of
cookies and brownies now when you say
set yeah what
does that mean like a
a box okay
meant to be shared
twelve
twelve cookies
it was probably like six cookies four
brownies okay
and I you know was
going nuts on those
I was eating a lot
and by
the time I left his door
of course when I left it was like 2am
3am in the middle of the winter
in Ithaca it's freezing out
and my stomach hurts
not made any better
by the cold and I
woke up with the worst stomach
pains the next I just like
horrible
so for years I like side eye
and insomnia cookies
anytime I see it now
was it the cookies or was it my own
foolish actions who's to say
what do you mean foolish actions oh eating
like half a dozen cookies
and brownies at like two in the morning
did you okay yeah
did you I hate to be
crass have a bad shit
or throw up a lot
I didn't throw up
I don't know that
my shit was I think I was just pounding
Pepto-Bismol this doesn't even sound that bad honestly
it was really pain it was really unpleasant
this is don't start teaching
this behavior this is not good this is how
it spreads about bad behavior how nobody
ever learns you're saying that a big stomach
ache is like that's not so bad you can get through
that you should keep doing that keep having those
let's go to insomnia day one let's be an opening
of insomnia I had insomnia
in San Diego a month or two
ago I will give them another
chance since they're reviving
at all it's been 20
years it has been 20
years what we need to do though is you need to eat
the exact same amount
at two in the morning
at two in the morning for a science it's for work
it's for science experiments six cookies
and four brownies and you have to go fucking
wild on them just getting a room
at the universal Hilton
yes like depriving myself
of sleep to eat you have to recreate
the situation properly
you could be sloppy telly
right have you
just you and me babies
by which I mean cookies and brownies
had you had then did you ever
order from them again no college
I haven't had them in 20 years
did you ever order from a different cookie
oh yeah I order from the other cookie place
all the time and did you order the same amount
no because it was
different it was different form factor it was
like slices would you eat a similar amount of
treats no
no because I would usually
get one or two
cookies and then split a pint of ice cream
with my girlfriend at the top
okay so you never recreated
you didn't have a
control or you guess you did
have a control but you never tested the experiment
well if I just throw
in Mano's hands of fate I don't
know if I'd be I wonder if it would just my
body would just react it could have
been that that might have thrown you too
it says is a nauseating film to watch yeah
this is going to be a big episode for us
back to insomnia is you returning
to insomnia cookies after 20 years yeah
to see if you can handle it
it is like
a place usually that
when it first caught on I think sprung
up around the college campuses
for like yeah stoners and
drunks these dumbasses will eat anything
that is
a lot of the food services
around the college campus
just use a bunch of newspaper cook
a bunch of newspaper and feed it to these losers
these hogs aren't going
to poke down tick tock long enough to know
what they're eating oink oink you pigs
eat up pay up
and eat up you know a lot of people
people experiment in college people like
you know try on different personalities
interests predilections
and to me this is like
this is a more experimental kind of
Jason a Jason who would get
stomach pains and then not immediately
go back to the place that gave him the stomach pain
I don't even know this Jason
you didn't really test them out
like you should have that's
it comes with maturity I'm saying
you and I go to city walk and if something kind of tastes
weird or bad or something we'll try it out a couple more times
alright you're on blast for six
days right Scott
did you test the wind did you get like
a three bite tuna sandwich and test
the wind factor no I didn't
I did no wind experiments
no I was not a little Ben Franklin
up there I'll leave that for you guys
yeah we'll do that
two bites of a pickle to get blew away
oh yeah your pickle blew away
no in fact because we recorded
after I went up there
just to like just to kind of walk around
take stock of things and I saw
you guys for a quarter after and as
I told you I made a point
of getting food not there
I left early
so that I could eat lunch somewhere that was
not city walk hey shout out
roadside tacos real good spot
down at the bottom of the hill
on Lankersham if you're going to Universal Studios
and you want food that doesn't destroy
you and that actually tastes good
and has real flavor roadside tacos
is the place for you
that sounds good
as good a time as ever
I'll tell a second part of I'll tell
what happened after the billabong
story right now because I was trying
to figure out where to eat at city walk I had gone up there with
my friend Tim and I was like
trying to figure out I really was having a difficult time
what time are we this is a dinner late
it's late eight or nine
oh that's for city walk hours
yes that's basically the two in the
morning yeah so I said ah
I got a free I got a free
menu item on the Taco Bell app
and I was extra excited
about this because
Taco Bell prices at city walk are
three times more expensive than in a
regular Taco Bell so I wondered
is it going to still is the conversion rate can be
the same here when it comes to the free item
because you get a free item it's you get one
cheesy goatee to crunch one chalupa
whatever and those are four bucks
at city walk they're eight or nine dollars
it's wild it's very expensive
but I realized yes I could get
the extra expensive cheesy
goatee to crunch for it's
$8.99
for a cheesy goatee to crunch at city walk
which is insane
that's for a full meal this is generally how much you
would spend so I could get that for free and I said okay
I need one other thing to eat
and I love Taco Bell generally
speaking I never have a
bad Taco Bell meal very rarely
so I go oh there's this like
there's a quesadilla for $10
okay I'm getting a free item so the whole
meal will be $10 that's pretty good
the caliente cantina chicken
quesadilla uh oh and
it's a new menu
item and I we're scared
just at the name I eat
and I eat the
cheesy goatee to crunch it's delicious it's as good
as a cheesy goatee to crunch ever is
I open the caliente
cantina and it's
covered in neon yellow
sauce just
even like crazy
fake looking for Taco Bell nacho
cheese no or it's the caliente
sauce like lemon like lemon
sauce what the fuck did
someone uh open a glow
stick that's what it looked like on top
of it accidentally and I this
this goes so south I forget to even take
a picture before it's thrown away
okay I I
take a bite of this it is like
tasting like
rancid lemon
candy that's
soaked in a chicken quesadilla
and it's it is so
it is like a pool of it
my quesadilla is sitting in a pool
of like neon yellow
candy it's leaking
out and again I've seen
all sorts of Taco Bell shit in my day
I'm a veteran of this place
I've never seen anything like this it's like
wet it's like been soaking
in piss basically
what do you think it is in their world
a cantina
first of all the only thing trustworthy on that menu
is the crispy cantina
chicken taco
is pretty good there's some great new cantina
items too this is a thing in the last couple of months
the burritos and quesadillas are too
gross they brought the
shredded chicken back which is what I was I've been
that I like yes it's much
better than their shitty chunk chicken
the shredded chicken is a better quality I don't know why
but it is this
imagine the candy piss from
its sugar and they just
dribble it all over your chicken
quesadilla and I made it through
maybe that's what it is it might be
it could be surplus piss candy
you gotta get rid of this piss
is that caliente sauce spicy
it was maybe supposed to be but it just tasted
like this weird artificial lemon
sauce that was a really
it was like it felt like it was giving me a headache
and I just I couldn't take it
it's actually it was
it's radioactive was it
barbicide it felt like
in some ways it was worse than
it was barbasol
it was yellow barbasol it was it felt
in a way like worse than the
flounder almondine
I would have rather had the flounder
from city walk Orlando
Toothsome than this chicken
quesadilla from Taco Bell
you just had your worst city walk food now?
just had it never had a worse city walk meal
than this oh my god and from Taco
my beloved Taco Bell of all places I don't know if
they I suspect that since it was a new
menu item they put like
fifty times the amount
on the quesadilla that they should like they didn't
know what they were doing they had not been trained
so there was a new right somebody
didn't come like the regional manager didn't come
around and explain the proportions
they're making what no
they're not ready
at least at johnny rock you get
a flat top grilled dog you know
I should have gone to johnny rock I thought about
it and then I was like I don't know why didn't
you go to a Taco Bell
down the street I
made a mistake I got excited at the
prospect of getting the nine
dollar cheesy gordita crunch for free
but then you still paid for this
other thing that was bad
yes so because the quesadilla
was still the prospect of the free
but then he just gives him ten dollars
of the worst thing he's ever eaten in his life
because it's still a case I'm sure that quesadilla was
four dollars more than it should have been
retail regular retail
but it still felt closer to
how much it should cost than the nine dollar
cheesy gordita crunch which is absurd
he only spent ten dollars
on the worst food
item that's ever been in front of him
Scott you know what else set the foot of
Universal Hollywood a Ralph's
grocery store oh yes where they have
the food that you can make for yourself
I love spitz spitz is on Ventura
down there
you're not a spitz guy I like it okay
there's a paquito maz I like paquito maz
do you like Mediterranean
style food in general I love Mediterranean
food did you just have one bad meal at
spitz once I just thought it was
kind of just fine
yeah just fine a little over
price well again you take that and you
move it right you just plop it right on
citywalk and you're raving about it
number one if you're craving
citywalk eats it's spitz for you
yeah cause citywalk
are the most beautiful people in the world
my favorite thing
about spitz there's never yellow
battery acid all over the
food it is reliable
for sure I mean
unless you want battery acid it was so
gross wow
so how soon you going back
yeah I would go back as long as I order
something dependable
I'll go back to taco bell I mean especially
if I have a free item you get a free cheese
goodie crunch and it does make me feel
good that I get that nine dollar for free
that nine dollar item you paid them ten dollars
you got screwed in this
scenario you're right in this scenario I got screwed
but I'm saying in the future I'm screwing them
in the future I'm taking it to them
I'm trying to just figure out how
much taco bell you eat cause the only
free items I get are like value
men you like rice and beans like
a basic taco and he's getting
like the giant free base
he's racking up points
I don't really know I don't have a log of Mike's
day to day but it does feel like there is
a lot of taco bell
we order pretty regularly my
James vegetarian very reliable
you can get a bowl too I get a power
bowl often as well
you know we get beans you get a little chicken
in there you get
cause he's a health nut this health nut over here with his
power bowls I don't know man
350 calories to get one of these bowls
if you make it right you put taco bell
pieces in a bowl or
Subway ingredients in a bowl
I'm like I shouldn't be saying this I shouldn't
be seeing this like this Subway bowl is the most
foul thought I've ever
I got one of my orders Wednesday
Wednesday 2-12-25 Cantina
chicken bowl modified reduced
fat sour cream easy on it
guacamole easy on it
health nut added a little Mexican
pizza sauce though
but I removed the avocado ranch
sauce and I removed all the rice
so it only ended up
being like 350 calories you're playing
with fire with this many modifications
I think no I'm not
I know exactly what I'm doing I'm just saying
you're playing with fire challenging
him you're coming at the king
my friend so real the
response you're coming at the king Sarah
I'm just saying I stick to the standard
goo that's on it
oh you never modify the goo at taco bell
I modify I might add one more
goo but like I don't
go too crazy
with it I my taco
bell thing is just of like
of as little meat as possible
if it's just potatoes or
beans or stuff like that I
don't get sick if I just eat vegetarian
the taco bell but you'll get sick
if you do the meat I'm saying that
beef is questionable
that goo beef
I can't I can't am I
experiencing this on the show
that someone who isn't me is
talking about the poor quality of beef
at chain restaurants what's happening
Jason and I are aligned
we're both making fun of how Mike
is eating the sands are
shitting on this show
all you're eating is what the lettuce at taco bell
then why do you even go
beans cheese nacho cheese
chipotle sauce
you're throwing shame on him you're Mr. Taco Bell
Taco Bell power bowl
power bowling your way to fitness
the shell is more unhealthy the shell is more unhealthy
than the meat I don't care about all that
I'm not it's Taco Bell I'm not trying to eat
healthy I'm just trying
I'll live on the edge I'll order Cinnabon
bites if I got a sweet tooth
you know
and there's empanadas there's sweet empanadas
of plenty coming back
I was just we were texting about the
Liv Moss presentation
event where they talk about the new
Taco Bell stuff coming
there's a Taco Bell keynote
that you both follow
Liv Moss yeah
that's how we live
Jason and I all the snacking counts
I follow on Instagram we're all over
so you text about Taco Bell enough to
cover the Liv Moss keynote but you
haven't run into this specific issue of
that you don't eat the meat and Mike's mad
that you don't eat the meat it just seems silly
to me unless you were a vegetarian
or a vegan to not ever have meat
I've always I've for the last few years
been trying to eat less meat
but unsuccessfully
no I'm doing a good job
of it what are you talking about
and you're also saying to never eat meat he's not
saying he'll never eat meat he's saying he doesn't want to eat the
shitty meat at Taco Bell makes sense
to me I'm not a perv I mean
look I like a little shitty meat so I'll have
Big Mac sometimes but I'd rather
have like it's either
I'd rather have Big Mac or I'd have a decent
steak and otherwise
that prefer not that prefer
chicken or fish Mike goes to a steakhouse
he's like how many modifications
do you have an app do you have an app for this
alright nevermind I'll go somewhere else
oh I mobile ordered
for the first time at
crypto.com arena yesterday
the modern world
we live in my god we are in the future
now our friend at knees was telling
us how dog shit the food is at
crypto.com arena how do you respond
you don't say he's right
yeah it was awful
but that's besides the point
Mike has a lot of skin slices
in his food discussion this is all about
skipping the line which was very exciting
you got to get you got to in a
faster way get dog shit food
I ate a shitty hot dog faster than the
line I ordered from the
chair I walked up it was ready to
go then you were to the
toilet before they were even done ordering
that's right that's right I threw it up
let me ask cause you were at AEW
Revolution were you eating a hot
dog during any of the very
bloody matches
no I ate the hot dog pretty
early yeah
no there was no blood cause I
was eating a salad as one match
was ending and then the next match was
in a steel cage so I
really finished that salad quickly
cause I was starting to get grossed out when you see
a human being bleeding it makes your appetite
less
I know I might be going out on them here
but yes Michael
to me the craziest
bloodiest match of all time was Mike Carlson
versus Flounder Almondine
yeah I bladed
I bit my mouth yeah
I bled as a bucket of blood for
that Flounder during City Walk 2
I'm gonna keep going through the list here
Sparky's we
have just lost Sparky's I think in
all that time I never actually walked into
Sparky's I don't think I ever bought anything from
Sparky's Sparky's very confusing
it seems to be it was a store that sold 100
things it had a cat that looked like Lady Gaga
well it doesn't have that
anymore yeah
Sparky's is being replaced by
Slice House
by Tony
Gamignani
Tony Gamignani you guys
spoke pretty highly
of this institution oh no I didn't
I've never eaten there you have not eaten there
Mike spoke highly of it
it is it has a Burbank location
where it replaced the
Doughboy's perennial steak
and shake by Big Laurie
which if you follow Steak and Shake on Twitter
has turned into an
Elon Trump simp account
oh no specifically
RFK all three of them
beef tallow they're like we're frying
our fries and beef tallow
yes they're frying their fries and beef tallow
make America healthy again
there's like AI art
of Steak and Shake being also like half
Steak and Shake half Tesla dealership
or Tesla restaurant oh my god
they're like going hard like they have a red hat
they're just kissing the brand down the drain
it's really interesting what's happened to Steak and Shake
wow wow I was not aware of the
Big Laurie turn Big Laurie is
like kissing Trump in everyone's ass yeah
this is very interesting oh my god
well anyway this is I mean this is a
this is a legit chain that's been going for a long
time just showed up in Burbank
I
as a theme park journalist was
got a little bit interested
in trying it seeing
if the hype lined up with reality
it was I'm gonna be honest
nerve wracking to do so
like going to a
going to a food establishment
where the only recommendation had been
Mike made me very
nervous and knowing that City Walk
has said yes you can set up shop
here I was wondering am I about to give
my entire family food poisoning
some bonus feed is I believe he's won
some pizza making awards
yes and he's called like I forget
that his Wikipedia says he's like
I don't know he's the
Elvis Presley of
pizza throwing
I don't know who the company I don't know
Michael Jordan I guess Elvis makes no sense
he's the saviour
Glover of he's
he's the river dance of
pizza throwing would you direct the cold open for
the pizza awards
I'd love to
that's really just what I've been
yeah me and Murr from the impractical joggers
are having a ball well that's what
for Oscars it's Ryan Perez for pizza
awards Jason Sheridan is my man
try to make people's dreams come true
anyway he's also
bone of feed is wise
he was a bar rescue pizza
expert I don't think
recurring I think maybe just one
or a few but he was the guy who
showed a place how to make better pizzas
that they probably did not implement
as a four days later and that
one stretch of shopping and dining
in the movie theater in Burbank
often used as b-roll
in early bar rescue
how is it oh to show like
some of their southern California
is a formulation
lots of college students
so the Burbank one makes sense because it's
literally at the foot of a 16 screen
movie theater yes yeah yeah
oh a quick slice that's kind of decayed
they've lost a lot of places why there's been a
Hooters that is set empty
for many years when will
this Hooters ever become something else
who wouldn't want to open a
restaurant in a parking garage
yes it is literally interesting
but that said there is a
very solid Indian
restaurant in the ground floor
of a different Burbank parking garage
yes that place is great we at this point
are going to have to like distribute a map of all
of the Burbank malls to the listeners so that they
understand what we talk about every
single episode it's almost impenetrable
alright please consult
A6 on your map that is to what
we are referring now Mike and I were
also messaging about some souped
up trading card vending machines
that are on the ground floor of the Burbank
alright where's that in the mess C2
consult your map that's in C2
anyway
with some trepidation
got slice house for the whole
family to try brought it
back big hit
this was a hit this was great
correctly hyped Mike
I believe you brought up the grandma
pie what is grandma pie
what is that defined as it's square
in this case Sicilian I don't know if
they're always Sicilian which is more
grandma pie is
a popular east coast preparation
of pizza involving
sauce and parmesan cheese
it's heavy like sauce
kind of like more like Chicago it's closer
Chicago style which I like
like kind of square slices
it wasn't so heavy with the sauce
it was
actually more of a light dusting it was
sweet Gino with sweet
tomato sauce and
mozzarella and basil and sea salt
I thought this was excellent I mean I liked
everything but that was the one like the one
that's a little more you know I didn't have
any just regular New York
but that's what's great you can mix New York
and Detroit and Sicilian
get kind of a grand bag of all of them instead of just
one pizza although I think next time I probably
put my eggs into the sweet Gino
basket I thought this
is great my son liked it Aaron
liked it I like this we
we were pretty knocked out
we're happy to have a pizza location we
like in the area and there's already a few
we got we got salad pizza in Burbank but we got
that now too and you get to you know
doff of the cap to Batman
to the Batman statue as you get it
so good so
this is eerily
good news for CityWalk I would say
replacing a store that was utterly confusing
with a pizza place that is
actually solid I don't want to get ahead of myself but there's
news that broke today
about another place that's coming to
CityWalk which is farther down the line that also
is shockingly good news wow
and it is scary because it's like what are they going to
do to these places
should I get to it in the list or do you jump to it
because we're not so far
we've gotten through a lot of the recent ones we've never addressed
by the way that nectar bath treats is now
nectar life that fixes
everything
Abercrombie and Fitch
is becoming
the NBA store which we
discussed a little bit I still
I feel like NBA might be a weird cursed
brand but
see what it's like yeah if they try to like
put you in VR goggles
and make you become a player
no it's over yes yeah
who was the commissioner who there
was a statue or a wax
Adam Silver
if it's your opportunity to meet Wax
Adam Silver then I don't know if it's going to work
out Dong Po Kitchen
the site of the worst meal
experience of my life oh well
right well what's coming to Dong Po Kitchen
Jason I'll let you do the honors sir
the rumor is
Raising Cane's
Raising Cane's Chicken
that's everywhere I love
it took a while
but it's grown on me quite a bit I like
Raising Cane's it's not like it's so special but I
think I do think Raising Cane's is pretty consistently
good and I have grown to really like
it what did Dave's Hot Chicken excite me
a little more even though Dave's has fallen off
because it's franchised so fast yeah the hot chicken
sure some of those hot chicken places are
falling apart for sure um but
yes I was but still Raising Cane's is
a solid if it was to maintain
the quality of the Burbank location
it would still be like oh I can at least have
a reliable chicken sandwich
up here you know I still have never
been because when they open
and the one close to us open and it had like the huge
line thing for a while and it's not the
kind of thing I eat all the time anyway
compare contrast
Chick-fil-A and Raising Cane's
God I haven't had Chick-fil-A in a long time
um does that imply Raising Cane's is better
because Cane's like only
has a certain number
of things on the menu similar to
In-N-Out Burger okay everything is
the chicken is cooked
really fresh in fact that's my worry
about the City Walk one because I find the
best way to eat Raising Cane's
is take out or try through
because then it goes from scalding
hot to reasonably hot by
the time you get home I promise you
the City Walk location and City Walk tradition
will find a way to be lukewarm
whenever it gets to you I would prefer that
because I ate at Cane's once and I
bit into it and like scalded
my mouth
it's well yeah it does feel I'm a car eater
I love to eat fast food alone
in my car yeah that is one of my
favorite things to do in life
and it is hot there was a moment
that went like the prepping of
the movie that I've been doing was exceedingly
stressful yeah and the
shoot way more fun and the post has been
a blast we locked picture we had picture
locked baby but
the prep was really insane and that I
like actually had five minutes to myself
before I had to go to some other
meeting and I sat and ate jersey
mics in the car
in five minutes
glorious this was yes
this was this was like having a like a
full weekend day off all
of a sudden in the middle of the schedule
it was really I will really cherish
that jersey mics in the car tossing some Miss Vickie's
chips you may as well be getting a massage
sure as hell did jalapeno my friend
oh the best they're really good that's a solid
chip barbecue one's really good too
yeah yes those are my two wow
alright hey
Vickie brothers
the placement
we're getting matching tattoos
we're all getting Miss Vickie's
the placement of
here's what's interesting city food
which is the upper level where the
Taco Bell is and where pink the awful
pinks hot dogs is and where you cannot
stand where you can where any
pickle is to the wind and where last year
was very windy this year less
windy so far but last year was very
windy the placement of
of an establishment at city food does
indicate that it's going to be worse
than the restaurants with more
space more room true
so that's what gives me
city food feels cursed yes
that's what I mean so if the rumors
are true and Raising Cane's is going to be
in the Dong Po spot
I have a little more hope for it
than I do and same with Slice House I have a little
more hope for those places than I do for
something moving up to city food city
food just seems like it's going to be
worse it has to be there's just some rot
and even when they change out locations
maybe they keep the they keep they keep all
the appliances like it's the
same crud that was accruing at the walk
in Dodger dog location
that is making the pinks taste
nightmarish today
yes so
yeah both of those things are
like oh man if those are if that's
open like at 9 p.m.
and you need to eat something you're coming out of the park
like that seems like that would be a
godsend honestly
sure if they're 75 percent
of other consistent quality
yeah but they got to change some
of these policies this everything
closes at nine and that's the
hotel so the rumor is two
hotels I think we know they're moving
faster on the first hotel that's outside
and we're going to get to where the other hotel is
potentially yeah because you might have some info that
we don't know well I don't know that much
more the second hotel I don't think has been
I don't know that I would bet a million
I think I would bet a million dollars that they're building the hotel
outside the entrance I'm less
certain for sure that they're
building a hotel over where iFly is
but that's still a rumor
and we've seen kind of weird plans
that indicate they're doing that
but we don't know because
will all guys permit yes no we don't
know yeah yeah if you want
to jump around from I was going to go to
sector 11 but I'll go to sector
13 instead because there's no keeper
to tell us not to do that such a crazy
jump crazy jumps
also what you could do in
IFly which is no longer
you can no longer indoor skydive
at Universal Studios
they have knocked that out to be replaced with
open air
I think that zone will be an
entrance to something that is what we
seem pretty confident of
did that also take out the outdoor
some of the outdoor seating at
Margaritaville I don't know
that's alright don't worry really
I thought the construction was and don't worry
no one is ever out there well you know what
I don't know if it's closed because they're working
perhaps perhaps you can't go
on the patio right now but it's not it
hasn't as far as I can tell from
looking it hasn't encroached on
it but maybe you're right oh okay because
I took a peek in there and maybe those
doors were closed because they wouldn't want you
near the construction not the fire
pit but they were like
fiddling with equipment once yeah
so maybe they had trouble
bad trouble night
bad troubles
so this is
interesting because this area yeah there's
an idea at least I
think they had to put a hotel here
which is a small piece of
land if you're just going by the
iFly but there's room behind it
I think it's more I consider that the iFly
is gone to be an exit
that takes you over to maybe and then
years ago I read a rumor that they would do a
second gate and there would be an entrance over
here in this zone wow
and I don't think
that's happening but all of this
and we should as I guess said this even earlier
all of this I think is happening right
now because as soon as epic
universe wraps up the word I've heard
from many people is we are go go
go in Hollywood for
what all every we're
going we're doing like
team shifts over really
yes so we get all the universal
stars that is the oh
that is a vibe I really feel very strongly
from a lot of different people
the construction too
when you're going up the hill by the existing
hotels yes is for a building
that people are calling a creative campus
oh wait
sorry where where do I point me in
the sort of by the
Sheraton and the Hilton okay
there is when you're going
up that hill to the left
really there is a large building going
up and they're like oh that's for universal
Frankenstein parking where the
unused Chinese restaurant
used to be well that
there was a rumored hotel
there I feel like for a long
time there's been a couple feel like
and there's also I
I don't know Scott you might have gotten
these mailings we both used to live a lot
closer to universal they're
always sending surveys
and sketches
and stuff of like
we're going to open
combined shopping and living
spaces on the back of the
back lot and that
tanked I haven't heard that
maybe nobody's living over there
so you think
not there's I sent
I sent a Google map
a couple days ago or last week
of like behind that
I fly zone okay yeah and I think
I don't remember I probably stole it from somebody
and I can't remember who it was
but there's a bunch of land back there
there's a bunch of space that people
are speculating that's expansion
I think which is current which is
where to again talk about early dating
Erin the place where I brought her back
to see the decaying
it was like
not a parking lot but just kind of like
storage I think it's where they yeah
that's what it's always seemed like over there
it's just like I don't know big like
just a vacant lot to put shit
and that perhaps they will put
some permanent shit they're going to yes
I think they're going to put permanent shit there like if
we have to identify now I hate to get actually
into the theme park of it all but
no I please don't we may
as well a little bit because it's
we could say right now
like things we want speculation
like there's rumors of Transformers
and mummy going away
more Nintendo down in that zone and mummy
yeah I mean mummy's been rumored
to go away for years never seems
to happen they're moving the tram entrance
today is the last day to see
fast and furious supercharge
oh and you know what
okay and that always felt like because also
if you're not up on what's going on at Universal
Hollywood they're getting real close on this fast and
furious coaster
maybe not that close
next year they said maybe it's going to
open with the new movie oh maybe
that's why they're holding it but jeez does it seem
like they're going fast I know and the track
is oh you got a track that is
looping above the starway nuts
it looks so crazy especially
if those pictures are right and
you're in little cars that rotate
spin around that was going to
roll so hard yes
it's like Velocicoaster level but also flips
you in little tiny cars Velocicoaster
level built into a giant
hill like a tiny mountain
and goes over the starway
holy shit is that exciting
it impacts like the skyline of the
city right and you'll see that from everywhere
from all around it's huge
so it seems
like the fast and furious
finale to the tour is going
away for that reason
I hadn't even clocked it like okay
so they're getting rid of that because there's going to be a better fast and furious
thing but
that land is pretty close to
that's tour exit so that
is land they could turn into something else
if you know the lay
of the tour land at all then it
seems like I feel like I've heard that
fast and furious stage is up for grabs
that falls lake
is up for grabs the big like lake
with the backdrop where they filmed the
TLC waterfalls video my favorite
thing to say oh right I'll go
a step further
the residential neighborhood that overlooks
were the world
I saw an account speculating that at
this point a lot of those houses
I had heard it
over the years oh universal owns
some of those houses for directors
or actors or producers
they're putting up there I've heard they
own a lot of it now I think they own a lot
yes I believe that's true I don't think
they're going to do anything with
that for theme park development
in the near term it's just a buffer
to where there aren't neighbors who can
complain about loud rides
right in their backyard right but
but overall I think right now
if you want to have fun speculating
speculate on what
will happen to transformers mummy
what will happen to Simpsons
and then the area downward tram
loading is now which will be moved
they're doing work right now on
the hill they're doing
something to it they're clearing things
they're moving it like I don't know if an
e-ticket that could go next to Harry
Potter that replaces Simpson
could kind of hang off the hill in a way
like there's not enough room
there's not enough room to put anything
other than a simulator ride right now where
Simpsons is yeah but I don't know
if there's something they could figure out
to build sort of on the side of it I don't
know interesting I don't like
because there's back like there's
I think and I've this is
was my guess but then I've seen a bunch of other
people say it wicked will be the
finale of the of the tram
tour oh that's my guess
that there'll be some sort of wicked thing and they want
to do it fast because why close fast and
furious now unless you've got
something that will be the finale
soon and the guy from the one
universal guys was talking about how
wicked is going to make a great theme park
yeah yeah yeah
no that's been overdue not overdue
because the movie was only out recently but like
that's a pretty big thing they're sitting on
even Ariana Grande was like
I got some ideas for wicked rides
yes I know she's a
Parks fan she's a big and there was
a recent video from universal
creative where they were teasing
epic universe stuff and they're also like
just so you know this isn't the end
this is the beginning we have
plans for every park
yes they're the they're putting
the pedal to the metal and they're like
really now a lot of people
have modern Disney brain and they're like yes
put wicked a Marvel superhero
island and I said
10 years ago said 10 years ago
but I'm like they're not going to retrofit
uh 25
year old rides oh
for this brand new movie
I don't know when they have
uh when they have all this space
and stuff it just feels like
I don't
I don't think they're going to do it because I think it's still valuable
enough to keep Disney from having it
I think so yeah I think that's probably right
but I don't know Toon Lagoon
I don't know sorry
I'm worried about
breaking hearts over here I'm worried about Toon Lagoon
I'll compromise and give them lost continent
because that's all vibes
that's no compromise
but I think we're getting
just because it's fun to talk about I think
Nintendo's going to sweep out Transformers
and Mummy I think we'll get
probably Donkey Kong and then whatever the next land
they build or we could put Pokemon
down there does all of lower lot
just what does is there some world
is the holdout yes but
what if otherwise well
yeah that's weird
Mummy is awkward I don't know what you do with Mummy
yeah I just I just think that whole
chunk then will become Nintendo
yeah just because it makes
the most sense if you want to have like a portal
if they want to keep this thing where the portals take you
that's what's weird I don't know what happens
because they don't have to do it but it still makes sense
or Mummy becomes that you enter
not there but like you go
through a portal and then enter the other way
they flip it around like Toy Story Mania
in Florida different entrance yeah
oh boy that'd be great to skip
early at Epicure
to speak great at forgetting
Donkey Kong out here
that's a whole portal to just
skip
there's no way I'm not going to Donkey Kong
see the big Donkey Kong guy
that's fun it wasn't as big for me as you
you know that's true I like it
I want to see the big guys
yeah you just got a Nintendo like a year ago
huh
I just started playing Mario Kart like a year ago
yeah you're not as you're not as fond of
Donkey Kong as I am no okay
well that's fair I like it don't get me wrong
but that ride the video friend Japan
it's like 82nd 90s
I'm worried about the ride
I'm excited to go on the ride
I have a feeling the ride is going to be fun but it's not the e-ticket
we want the blow away Nintendo e-ticket
we want and deserve that's that's the
reality I'm worried I have to meet
Vincent Various in his various shops
and establishments
I would play guys
we do have to explain what Vincent
Various is
it's shorthand for us but what is Vincent
they put out a casting notice
in Orlando for a character named
Vincent Various for the new epic
universe and apparently I've heard
on the inside some rumors and not rumors
that there are deep lore
about new characters at
Celestial Park
I'm so excited for Celestial Park cause two things
14 hours of original
music I saw that too
that's really fun a lot of
people who worked on
port of entry working on
Celestial Park
yes I saw that as well
no that's going to be awesome Vincent Various
is very exciting I don't know anything about him
but I love him
he's an astronomer a scientist who converted
a lot of his workshop spaces to
restaurants and shops
is that what Celestial Park is
it was some magical gathering place
for great minds
yes the greatest philosopher I think
that's the vibe of it
so I think that's you got Nintendo
I do think we'll get a version of
Monsters somewhere I think there'll be a version
of their Monsters somewhere out here
I'd like that and then I do
think Wicked is number one I think Wicked
goes in Orlando we're out here
faster than we expect
does it knock out fast and furious
in Universal Studios Florida
potentially
I could see it being a bigger
they wanted to have a bigger footprint for it cause
that's pretty small so you think it's built fast
but it's also huge
yeah I think it's I think like Wicked replaces
Toon Lagoon I don't know that as a rumor
but I think it's that size of a project
don't you dare tell me that Wicked replaces
Race Through New York starring Jimmy Fallon
I think it's too small
I think there's a new coaster
that will replace Rip Ride Rocket
possibly the Fast and Furious coaster
a different version of it
but I think
that I think that a lot of this
city walk stuff and hotels is in
preparation for what
our park looks like in five years
that's the vibe I'm getting
that's what people have said
so just to recap
parking lot behind
current city walk becomes a
hotel this we know we think a hotel
over by
over the area that they've cleared
out where iFly used to be
do you still believe any more
park over there or is that kind of an
impossible by iFly
yes I believe that I think there's lands
I think there'll be enough to can you can they
somehow turn it into a second gate
or is that insane I think you
I think they could do it I just don't think
they will do it I
think if they're opening one
hotel they're going to need a bunch
new attractions let alone two
hotels yes that's for sure
I just think I just think the second
gate I don't think they want
I don't think I don't
think they want to build it all at once
now I hope I'm wrong because that would be really
cool if they did because then you could
you could fix the problems of
universal Hollywood with a second
gate in a sense that like
universal Hollywood still is like I
don't know if it's completely fixable to
put in the magic
that it needs to make it on par
with Disney just because it's
still very piecemeal the
flow of it is a little awkward yes
there's plenty of magic yeah it was built in this
weird janky way unlike universal Florida
which at least did start as a new theme park
designed from the ground up it's always been
around weird this movie theater
staying and these bungalows are staying
but I think they've done a tremendous
job oh absolutely but it does still have
to remain a working studio
and offices need to not move it's
weird it's some of the same awkwardness
as Disneyland expanding as opposed to
Disney World yeah and that's the
I like it I've heard people be negative
about it that's the charm of like
you see Fast and the Furious from Hogs
or Hogwarts or something like you see
I love it all just slapped together
I love that yeah new coaster
will be whipping by big minion
it's like the it's like you know
hey it's magic of the movies
it is kind of true in spirit
not chosen of universal
Hollywood but the original
universal Florida where it was like
a movie studio there's
lots of stuff going on I'm a big
defender of it but I do think
it would be really cool to have
like an Islands of Adventure
Port of Entry second gate
where you did get Jason's
noise
like if we could get like a
Toon Lagoon out here
new Toon Lagoon
guess what everybody new for
2028 Dudley Do-Right
well I would pick that over a lot
of things I'd pick that over Wicked
Wicked's fine I like
Wicked but
I was saying this you could
do like a themed hotel that looked into
a land you could do Wicked
Hotel right there and it looks into a wicked
land these all do feel like more of
like Disneyland Paris style
or what they've done recently
in Tokyo like hotel that's like
backdrop to theme park
or entrance to theme park right
because the one that's in front of the
entrance you'd still see in from
it's a fairly tall
hotel from the paperwork
so like you're looking into the park
but if they do build a hotel right where
iFly was and they put
stuff behind it there's no
way you're not looking right into the park
like that has to be an element of it
so I don't know if that hotel has to be it doesn't
necessarily have to be themed like the land
whatever they decide to put there but it could
be it could be a monsters
area with a monsters hotel
this is a complete speculation
on my part the movies and stage
plays and going back to the original
Frank Baum books
Wizard of Oz
has entertained people for generations
so hey listen
I don't believe you
I don't think he's right on that
Hold on
fucking Emerald City hotel
is like that's like a home run
well we already had it it was called the MGM
grant well but that was unlucky
you don't want to enter through for a half second
I thought you said Emerald City the chef
I mean sure yeah
start your day with a bam
so I think all of that's
on the table I do think
maybe there'll be another Harry Potter I think
Monsters and Wicked and then more Nintendo
is probably in our near future
now I'm just like how can
I get that Wicked simulator
experience to transition
straight into something with Ryan Perez
I'm on a streak now I don't know
how I'm getting greedy
I could see the Wicked I could also see the Wicked
finale
just being there for three years until the land is
built or something it's a little stop
I could see it be just like we need to get into the park now
that's why we got to get rid of Fast
because they're going to like I don't
I also think it's Wicked
because why close
it now if you're not going to
put something new in there
that might be Fast because that second
movie comes out in the fall
of 2025 right it could be Fast but you know what I'm saying
like what's the why wouldn't you just keep
it open as the finale
sure because if it was a new finale
because we still don't get Fast and Furious for another
year right right there's got to be something
they want in Fast to be the finale
I assume yeah
so it was very abrupt too
that they announced that closure
no one was sad
no one gives a shit
my prediction for Wicked part two
is that it's kind of like an awards season
sweep in the way that
Lord of the Rings Return of the
King of like alright
there's been thrill let's get the last one
the awards yeah yeah
I don't know about that
well part two
is I think act two of Wicked
is the more supposedly the more
upsetting
part of Wicked
the dramatic south
that's another thing when I watched this weird demo
Oscars I got to watch
a rehearsal of the opening performance
with two people who were not Cynthia
and Ariana and they didn't sing
either but they did mouth
the words so I basically
sat there let's go down clips
play we love Los Angeles and then two
people come out and just like
silently pantomime the song
that's weird I didn't know they did
stuff like that but even that
was very stirring because it was
still the orchestra playing still
all the chorus like popped in from the
from all the balconies like that
made me emotional and it
wasn't even the real
that really is the magic
of the movies just people going
through the like a rehearsal
live rehearsal yeah we'll put
it in later or we'll tape we'll
do a take later it really got to me
and then and also the woman who
did the big final note who was
the stand in Cynthia Revo like
dung and then there's just the space
left and she just mouthed it she just
went and she got a
huge applause I think everybody really
enjoyed applauding somebody who
was on mute doing the final
note that's great
that of course that musical number at the Oscars
yes
started with Ariana Grande
singing somewhere with a rainbow
oh yes they kind of made it yeah they got
they went all in and then the whiz
later in the show
they got to all of them
but anyways
now so you know
what started we started all
grim because our beloved land
is being picked apart
but now what we're finding is that maybe it's
for very good reasons and exciting reasons
but where does that leave us with are we
worried about like
what if big chunks do
disappear what if we lose entire sectors
this is my theory that you guys seem to disagree
with what I said about sector one
that they're all gone like currently there's almost
nothing there I think it's possible
and Bill Bong's out I think it's possible they
yank that entire structure that's
what I was trying to figure out because that one's
kind of an island I think any
any sector right
any like CityWalk technically is broken up into
like seven different buildings you see
and I think that if any that are
attached to a parking garage are safe
they're not rebuilding any parking garages
that'd be a waste of money I think
cause you're gonna need people
I think are there multiple
security stations
there's gonna be cause if you park in the
ET one you'll go through one set
they're gonna have to fix this
problem of that there's eight ways to get into
CityWalk and you don't know where any of them
take you or where they take you out
I think any flat parking is
gonna go away
a lot of it absolutely yeah
but any parking garage is staying
then I was analyzing other buildings and I was like
okay some of these do have offices
up top where people work
sector one with Bill of Bong and the
wave pool they don't use anymore there's nothing
going on there I could see that becoming
like a little bit of extra
hotel maybe not maybe they don't have to
but something's moving in one of the stores
isn't it yes there's some like
cutesy character store but I still think
I still think you could evict
that 10 months later I it's
possible to do that I just don't know why
they wouldn't immediately move it
to some other empty store which they
have plenty seemingly plenty of
so that's the only reason I'm skeptical
of that and because one of the pictures of
of a permit or a plan
didn't show that
area gone you could retrofit
that building in to incorporate
it into a larger building
and knock down some walls and stuff
and I think the
what is your daughter like
the line friends yeah I think
if those were temporary
I think they'd try to
full court press like
marketing pop up
like only here for a little
while you know sure I mean it's
possible I if
if something moves into Bill of Bong we'll know
I think if they move
something into the billable if you find out
it's happening you tell us you don't keep that secret
from us right don't these accounts
out there you come to us right
this matters to us we got
skin in the game yes it's very important
but I feel like things actually
are pointing to a perhaps a changed
city walk but a thriving
city walk because it might be the
you know the conduit to even more
traffic than it's than it's ever been before
city walk might be more important
than it's ever been and I even say
I would dare say if these two hotels are
built maybe you can
find something to do after nine p.m.
maybe things will have to stay open
a little later and I'm
not always wanting to party late at
night at city walk anymore but it would be nice
to have the option so if there's a bunch of
other people that are going to be walking around
maybe later at night
you're going to have to have a little more fun available
I don't know that Howl at the Moon
will reopen there's no talk of that but I just hope
there'll be some saying that if you
bring hundreds if not
thousands of people plant
them directly in city
walk yes they're likely going to
want to enjoy food beverages
and various amenities I am making
this point yeah I never considered yeah
how about it think about it
when you go home tonight I will but are they
going to keep me up at night are they willing
to make a city walk that has things
for people to do that they like
to do I don't know that's
probably the big push and pull right now universal
is do we want to make this okay now
this isn't us don't you see
well they are putting in a
weird third party escape room
company oh right we missed that
Samba Brazilian Steakhouse
is now an escape room and that's okay
so this is why I okay real quick before
we do the big finale oh real
quick
I do think that at one
point they were thinking they would put mostly
universal owned businesses places
because they have an escape
room in Orlando with their
IP with their classic
things and for some reason they're
not just cloning it and moving
it over here it's probably
because it's bad and I have
to assume that
because this is like a company that
has a place in Woodland Hills I think at the mall
escapology this is they have
other locations and they have like there's
going to be a Batman escape room
at City Walk which is funny
which probably won't be good
but it's funny that like Batman's showing up
Scooby Doo but to me
that's the waving the white flag already
of like we just don't have the resources to
own every business at City
Walk yeah okay but
I'm sure at some point the thought
was like yeah we're going to do these escape rooms and then we're moving
them over why not
we did all the work anyway
why wouldn't they have done why wouldn't they just
put them over they got too much to do I guess
that's what I that's my theory is that
maybe at a certain point they were like trying
like our ultimate goal is to own
everything because why not but then at a certain
point they went we can't do this and there
is we can barely open up toothsome
and keep it edible
there there's something in the
because downtown Disney in Orlando
in the former Disney Quest space
that was the NBA experience
mostly the NBA experience
is getting what is
essentially an off-brand Disney
Quest like it's another like
laser tag escape like
no name yeah it is
really interesting yeah
so it's gone full circle
right but can we just decide that
we like these things we need things to
do for god's sake we can't
just wear helmets at home
I got kids I got to take them somewhere
can we keep these places around
well I if you're going
to outsource it just outsource it to
Dave and Buster's or round one
I
listen to the the recent Dough Boys
episode with Griffin Newman where they
went to Chuck E. Cheese
and had a horrifying experience
and it is a very
funny podcast episode
I went I went to a kid's birthday party
there this very weekend
and like oh my god that is an
unpleasant Chuck E. Cheese and I'm a fan of
the brand and I'm still yeah and I got to
watch my son be confused like
he was trying to say hi to
Chuck who is of course a robot who
doesn't respond or move
and I had to explain to him
dad why isn't Chuck
saying hi to me and
why does he look different than the other Chuck
and I said son this is the
there's a lot about parenting
I don't understand but this is the moment I've been
waiting for my whole life
this I can do can you just
clarify when you go to Chuck E.
Cheese now with kids you have to buy
socks there and kids have to
put them on yes yeah you buy
like I don't know anything
about this this is not insane it's not just
for there no I know I know I get
it but I'm like that is
no wonder they were saying
it stinks in there if every
child is changing socks
that's so nasty
that is gross
I have stood up
everyone's looking at me yeah what's happening
so now I'll do the rest of the show standing
whoa this is weird it is
weird so I went to Billabong
unless you have something else I want to
close out the I have nowhere
to go now that you've stood I'm so
I was like I had been keeping
my eye on the prices at Billabong
I had been and they were bad I went in
there was a big dirty like plastic
tub they were selling for ten dollars
that they kept in the stock room to
like store t-shirts or something and I was
like what ten dollars for a dirty tub
like what do they want
two dollars maybe if you need a
tub you can buy a new one for
this price so I went in there last day
well maybe there will be like some deals or whatever
maybe it would be something funny
now I saw universal high posted that
day this is of course parallel thinking
that they went in and bought
some hangers some coat
hangers from Billabong and
plants and like
and I was thinking the same thing
I go are they selling like parts
of the of the like retail
space or stuff on the wall or whatever
and I go wouldn't it be fun to go in there
and do this so I went in
and I immediately there were hats
that were pretty reasonably
prite oh you've been hiding
things in plain sight so I've
these are shorts I actually just bought for myself
but I bought you guys hats from the
final Billabong wow
they were discounted the last
items to touch the rear
side air Scott
do you have you picked them out for who to
I bought this one for Jason cause it's more like
a Sherlock Holmes pattern oh absolutely
oh my god it says new shit in
my pants they were seven they were
seventy five percent off wow
are eighty percent there maybe more
that money stayed in your pocket and then went
right to lemon
lemon battery chicken yes
that's very true so
I'm looking around and I was like
I need to buy something from
Billabong I need
to buy something from
off the wall or something obviously in the same way
that you bought something from Fry's
electronic oh yeah on the way out the door I
just want to I want to own a piece of our
beloved brand own a piece of city
walk so I walk and I'm looking around and I see
like there's there's like pictures of like surfers
in like frames
for five dollars and I'm picking I'm like this is
kind of funny you know it's just like a guy
and it was on the wall for a second there's
like stuff where there's like a like a metal
portal porthole or whatever
like a picture and I'm like oh that's kind of
funny in there everything's like dirt cheap
five dollars or whatever and
I'm looking around and I turn
around and I see
the greatest thing
I don't I don't recognize
it but I go oh my
god I need to own
this and I look five dollars
oh boy and now I will reveal
to you what I have purchased from
the Billabong oh I thought this was a
set of some weird thing at forever dog
I purchased
a
flat
of Santa Claus
but he's a wave he's like an actual
water Santa Claus is water
oh my god let me take a
picture of my view right now
he's got a candy cane and he's got sunglasses
on and he's
like giving I don't know it's a thumbs up or whatever
he's got a Santa hat on and I would
like I almost I was so excited
it was five dollars I like grabbed it because I was like
someone else is gonna want this like and I like
took picked it up and walked around
and somebody an employee looks over he goes
yeah that's a great piece and I go it is
a great piece really is
so I was like I put
down I think I was holding like one of the
framed pictures of a shirtless surfer
and I put that down like fuck this
this isn't worth it this is worth it
five dollars five dollars
for Santa a wave I
kind of holding a candy cane wearing
a Santa wearing sunglasses
I can't wait for listeners and I see
I broke his foot a little bit just now
when I was bringing him inside his little
his feet are tiny they're music
notes he's got little feet
there was a there was a neon pink
sign that said vacation mode that
I also inquired about but that had been taken
already I would have paid like fifty
dollars for that though that was cool
but that taxidermied pheasant or
wild turkey whatever that bird is you
did not buy that's no that's part of the difference
there's a lot of weird shit in the
room we record in yeah basically
so I so I bought this I bought the hats
and then
I took the
Santa wave on a
last ride through
city walk so
I will post this I
have I have me and Santa
outside the sock markets wow
I have a photo
of there's too many of these
but I have Santa
wave and Tony Geminati
from slice house
passing the baton I have old generations
and new and I'll set this
to some music I'll post this of course when the
show comes out me and the
King Kong and the wave Santa
and I have
us by the Raider
store was open at the time
wow the last possible
visit I have Santa wave Santa
over by the bouquet of Beppo
wow and then I
have wave Santa
which I think is the best one
by the mural
with the angels wings
that is
a great picture
that's great
there was a 13 year old
that was just laughing his ass
off he was like that's so
funny man still got it
wow that
takes me back to we haven't heard a 13 year
old laugh like that since that guy said what's
that a new slap shot right
and then I got him I got
wave Santa with a Michael Ferrari
pointillism painting
nice wow
wave Santa is so
chill and easygoing I feel like he would get along
with the Venice boardwalk keeper I agree
and
the little addendum to the
Taco Bell story is that he was
sitting up against the table
and just the compliments
from people
people fucking loved wave
Santa like oh wow that's
so cool where did you get that
well you know Billabong's closing I purchased
it wow wow
wow you had the respect and
admiration of your peers at
citywalk and the place that I want it the most
so I
I've been asking around to
I am addicted to owning pieces of
citywalk and I just none of these
other stores have given me a heads up
or an ability to buy
pieces of the
actual place so this is my first
first chunk of that and
I don't know if I'll have an opportunity to do it again
wow well if anyone has a way
to help you do it again if there's anybody
who deserves to own some citywalk
thank you thank you you have a spectacular
piece when the Christmas season rolls around you
got to put that in the front yard
I got to fix it first
there's a lot of grinch's out
there's a lot of peanuts gang out there
you will be the only house that has
wave Santa original
citywalk IP wave
Santa or Billabong I guess
well yeah technically my friend Tim
asked about the sign outside
and they said oh no we're taking that back to corporate headquarters
to destroy it
whoa wow
wave Santa would have been put into
a wood chipper
what Santa would be dead if not for you
he saved a life
I'm really disclosing a lot
of my correspondence but I sent this to universal high
and they were like what the fuck where was that
so I think wave
Santa was hanging out in the back
for a while and all of a sudden just popped
up and I just
it was it was fate that I
would get wave Santa oh my
god wow
this is really you know
in an episode where I tried to share
some of my my Hollywood magic
I got to experience and then where I
when I thought it would get Hollywood tragic
instead you have
brought a wonderful new
character into our lives
your pictures are great and I don't
want to create work for you sure but
it does occur to me that putting
them all into a video would be
a moving experience if there's a
way to all right all right if you have
a minute no pressure maybe
with that fast and furious when
I see you again
I was probably gonna do the city walk theme but maybe
I'll do that oh yeah you can do that too
or despacito maybe oh despacito
is also good fast furious
was just in my mind cause we talked about it so much
yeah yeah I mean
just I don't know this guy making it
him like propelling himself out of the
ocean into our world
yeah not being held down
despite being an unusual color
all I can think of is this
guy is wave santa singing defying
gravity oh yeah
I'm defying
gravity
I'm surfing
high defying
gravity
ho ho ho
anytime I try to do that
I just end up doing the Tarzan
yell cause I
kept seeing that Brian Blessed
talking about doing the Tarzan yell
and getting two contracts
for Tarzan the movie
close enough I'm realizing now
is wave santa like is it
is this an original character to the
store or is this something in other billabongs
well listeners
if you have billabongs near you and
if you've done Christmas shopping at billabong
then you're gonna have
to let us know that yeah cause if
not I think we just I just bought the
IP wow you've bought an
entire IP for five bucks
wave santa yeah
but you didn't sign any contracts
that like give you the exclusive
rights as far as you can tell I don't think so
but I think it's best to assume yeah
I love him it definitely
looks like at first I
was wondering like oh is this gonna be like in
10 minutes I'll be like man I bought it no
no I'm so excited I have it
it does look like it could be
shipped from Corpip but it also
looks like they could have printed it
at a Staples copy and print center
oh it's not yeah
it's really charmingly
hand drawn I don't know it's like a comic character
yeah I really love it he is
cute yeah he is cute
no argument from me yeah very
cute and very cool
and very pointing towards the
future he makes me feel optimistic about the
future I'm not scared of what's happening to City
Walk anymore I'm excited about
it and yeah hey
hang ten my
man keep it loose
geez congrats to you congrats
on the new addition to your family thank you but
if anyone knows where I can get more let
me know yeah yeah please information about
about wave santa
wow geez well what a
thrilling finale my god
and
I mean I guess that'll do it I guess you survived podcast
the ride we will
track whatever's going on
if whatever is going on gets so
confusing that we need to find a way
to talk to a
friend beyond this mortal realm
and I don't know if it comes to that
then it might have to but
for now we just figured we'd parse it ourselves
but you know what this one's for you SK
and I guess
for three bonus episodes every month check out
this stuff check out podcast the ride the second gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier
club three hey go to hulu
and watch the academy awards
where you'll see my work and besides
that our stuff at patreon.com slash
podcast the ride
definitely go to the socials so you can
hang ten with wave santa
ho ho ho
forever
dog this has been
a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott
Mark Gardner Brett
Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex
Ramsey for more original
podcasts please visit forever dog
podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on apple
podcasts spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts
keep up with the latest forever dog news
by following us on twitter and
instagram at forever dog
team and liking our page
on facebook