FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcasts
may contain drippy
rainbow art, reaching
cape maturity,
hypothetical spitting scenarios,
and the beginning of the
steak and bourbon wars.
All this plus we lower the draw
bridge on Sleeping Beauty's castle.
Hey! It's Podcast The Ride!
MUSIC
Welcome to Podcast The Ride with three
hosts who cleverly deploy forced
perspective. For example,
Mike appears quite tall,
but in reality he's actually
a good deal shorter than Jason.
Funny how that works. You wouldn't
know when you see us on stage it's really
it's a very clever forced perspective
thing. Yeah you know this is Mike and
yes Bob Gurr designed Jason and I
almost 40 years
ago to this day. So we're coming
out about that. That's interesting. I've
heard that rumor. Yeah no it's true.
I've seen it online but you're affirming this
only the clever
engineering mind could have created
Jason Sheridan. You know I
put enough turrets on my head
and paint on my body. That's
the thing people don't know after hours
a lot of paint needs to be updated
on me to keep the illusion
consistent.
There's a lot of maintenance going on. Your touch up team
your perpetual round the clock glam squad.
And also got a great deal
on of that lead boy paint
or whatever it was. Lead
boy? What was it called?
Dutch boy? Huh?
Dutch boy lead paint. Yeah.
Yeah I don't think they were so
out with the lead
paint nature that it was in. Lead
boy. Lead boy.
It might have been in the subhead.
Like I feel like it was like
Dutch boy lead paint or
something. Yeah forget the name of it.
Okay wait. Dutch boy tomorrow
land. What was the actual thing? We're talking about
a weird original Disneyland.
Let's see.
It was something called our future. Oh
Dutch boy paint gallery. So
yeah not lead boy
or
it's a fun idea though. If they really
had I mean it definitely was an exhibit
that involved how lead
paint will be part of our future. Right.
But if it had been much more so
like they say 70
years in the future this
paint will be 10 times
as leady as it is today.
I mean artists do your work. Jason
Sheridan is lead boy. Lead boy?
Sure I'll take it.
Rejected 50's mascot
lead boy. Lead paint
marketing I feel like was like the
four out of five doctors recommend
Chesterfields for your T-zone.
Good for your T-zone.
What's up with T-zone? T-zone like
your mouth, your nose
mouth. That was called the
T-zone? T-zone was a thing
in marketing. What does it mean
though? I think it's just like
your general lower
face area. That's confusing
because when you say T-zone I go to a different
part of the body. What do you
mean below the belt?
Well that's the P-zone.
Yeah
that's the P-zone. That's why I was confused.
Oh I see. When I think
T I think testosterone. Yeah which is
down in your P-zone. Or your T-zone
isn't it? I think testosterone is everywhere.
I mean look. It's all
around us. I think of the engine
of the T-zone as being
your two T's.
Is it the testosterone engine down there?
Is that what it is? Am I just completely ignorant?
Maybe.
You think testosterone is coming out of your
knees? I mean I don't think it's coming
out of my knees. My T-zone is
my knee zone. Circulating.
I don't know exactly where hormones are generated.
You guys talk amongst yourselves.
I'm going to find out where testosterone
comes from. Maybe it's the balls. Maybe it makes
sense I guess when you're saying it.
I think there's glands.
If you were exposed to a lot
of lead paint in the 1950s
then that may have caused
your balls to expand to such
a rapid degree that people
would think it was a massive
throbbing T-zone. But really
that was just lead paint. T-zone could be
lower below the belt if you're talking
tinkle time.
Excuse me? Tinkle time? Tinkle time, yeah.
When you go pee? Yeah, tinkle.
You gotta tinkle. We're throwing a lot of
I have the answer. Scott is correct.
The majority of it is produced in the
testes. Where else
in your mind? But the adrenal glands is also
part, they make a smaller amount
of testosterone. Now here's
a dumb question. Where are the adrenal glands?
Your adrenal glands are like right here. Okay, okay.
So you are mostly correct.
Okay, I see. But the adrenals make some
I don't think my eyeballs
are producing all of my testosterone.
Well I know you have like other different
glands. That's the only reason. So obviously
you were right. I'm just saying. Got tea shooting out
of my teeth. Yeah. I mean
the only one so far who's measured their tea
is me. But we still need to get definitive
tea rankings for the three of us I think.
The audience really wants it.
Do I just have to ask
Next time you're doing a physical ask I think.
I don't think
it's any extra. There's nothing
about me
that makes me believe mine
would be especially high or
higher than yours. I'll
just set the bar there.
So if I'm incorrect. Right.
But maybe that's
kind of a mental tea block.
I don't know. Maybe it's very high.
You're making your tea lower.
Yeah. Or just assuming as such.
I bet your tea is pretty good.
I could be wrong. But I bet your tea is pretty good.
Two kids.
Well it might
have something to do with it. It's not ten kids.
But it's something. No it's not ten.
It'll
never be two. If I had twice
made quintuplets.
You're a pronatalist guy.
You're one of those. What do you think
your tea would be? If you had to stack it
against.
If I'm thinking mine's lower than
Mike's. And Mike's.
Mine isn't.
Well as we talked about before I was kind of disappointed
with mine. But then I saw what other
people had and it made me look like a
king or something. Like made me look like a warrior
of some kind. So I
was totally off on what I even expected.
I think it's a big assumption also that kings have
high tea. That's why it's changed to warrior.
That's good. Because kings
might set out to become
kings in order to make up
for the lack of tea.
I've been taking a lot of vitamin D lately.
And I feel like, I feel like pretty good.
So you're in your D zone.
I think I'm in my D zone but it's helping my tea.
And I wasn't taking the vitamin D as much back when I
had my tea tested. That was last year.
So I'm taking the D to help the tea.
I take D and
a B complex.
So okay I take the D
in my T zone and it helps
my tea. You have to fill in, you just
point it to your mouth. The listener can't see
your mouth. My T zone.
I said my T zone. I said my T zone like Jason
said. Yeah.
But you have to, the listener can't understand the point.
When you're just pointing at yourself you're in your P
zone. But they could hear, they could hear
the brushing of the, I assume they could,
the wind off of my. But that might be your finger
on your way down to below the belt. Yeah I guess
you're right. Below the B zone. Well I meant in my mouth.
I take the D in my mouth
and it helps my tea. You take a big
tea in, yeah well you're going to end up with more tea
if you take a big D in your mouth. Very good point.
Jason if you had to guess
where do you think you're falling? You know
I don't really know. My immune system
is just constantly pulverized
these days by various
things. It's not fair. Your reading won't be fair.
I've done some looking
and actually I did see
a video
from
another MS patient
who takes the same
okra, he takes the okra
in conjunction
with a testosterone
supplement. And he says he thinks
that is helping.
Now, but I did some research
there hasn't been many definitive
studies, there's only been like one or two
studies back in 2007.
Let's run a study. I will be in charge of it.
We'll do it just you and I
and we'll do a study on it. Just Mike
injecting me with
he comes over. Mike injecting you with
this big tea.
Neugenics infusions every day
does not tell me about
like oh by the way unless you cancel
this at auto renews.
It's $80 a month.
Don't believe the television commercials.
Well we'll figure it out
and then we'll. I'll mention
to my doctor when I
need to go in for a physical at some
point soon. You say
ok so I've been you know I've been wondering
if maybe like an injection of extra tea
would help. So should my friend Mike come
over and put his D in my mouth.
Just say it like that
too and if he needs to talk to me give him
my number because he can call me
and run it by me too. Hey Doc
I'm up for it. I'll do it right now. Should I go over
there right now? Write me a prescription and go over
there. This is the Sleeping Beauty Castle
episode.
Probably the
tamest possible
topic and here we've defouled
it instantly.
It started with just the T whatever the T zone
he said he was talking about.
I'll find old cigarette ads.
Chesterfield. There was no way the phrase
T zone was going to be said and have it
not send us into a direction like
that. But let me corral things
a little bit. Not quite
to get to the topic yet but to talk about
some other show plans.
Some podcast business
that I've been wanting to talk about because we're all
here together after
some host departures and returns.
We seem to be here at least for the time
being. We'll see what happens.
But while we're here I think this is
a good chance to go over some
stuff that we might want to do
this year and some shots to call and
maybe this will hold us to doing some
things if we start kind of dangling some plans
that we think could be some fun plans
as I think these are. So
here's one. I'll address
this now. There was a shot
that I called before leaving
to make the movie and that shot was
Celebruary 2.
Now Celebruary
has passed and there was no Celebruary.
Could April
become Celebruapril?
I guess possibly. But
without going into it for various
mundane reasons it seems
like waiting on Celebruary 2
is going to be the thing to do. I think we will have a
stronger,
better, more coursing
with T version of
Celebruary.
So I think we are going to
put that in the T zone by which
I mean table it until
2026. I think that is the plan.
I think so. That sounds right.
Flag on the field.
Life finds way at some point
but for now we're pulling the Chinese
democracy on that one.
I guess so.
We're going to get sooner
than that I think.
Less weight than that.
But what happened
and it is very much still in the cards.
We are thinking about that. We are going to do it.
But even thinking about Celebruary
got us
a little bit hungry.
It got us hungry for a few things. It got us hungry for a
theme month which is something we haven't really done in a
while. It got us hungry for
theming and IP
as it relates to the world of
restaurants specifically.
And there's you know
for whatever reason this theme park podcast
when we start to veer restaurant
suddenly is where things are really cooking.
And with
that in mind there is a
giant area that we have
not covered where theming
and restaurant meet and
merge and make beautiful love.
And I think that's why I
want to announce this for this
year to try to lock it in and
commit without saying
when it will be exactly. I
would like to announce for
hopefully the near future
podcast The Ride 2025
McMonth.
McMonth. A month
long celebration of
all things McDonald's except the
food.
We kind of floated this as a test
balloon online.
I thought it was responded to very well.
It seems like kind of a cousin
of Celebruary.
And one that I'm very excited about where
it's one of those where if it seems a little
ridiculous on its face
you start adding it up and then you start to go
can it even all fit within a month?
There is so much there because this
becomes our opportunity.
And please tell me what you guys flash to.
But I'd say the big things
you know, McDonald
Land, I mean the Play Lands
are its own thing, right?
These slides and these things that
you wander around, the mouths that you
go in, the heads that you get to sit
in, the McDonald Land characters
are on the table, Grimace is
on the table, Uncle O Grimacey
is on the table.
Mac motherfucking tonight
is on the table. There is a
lot here I think.
I think we will find that McMonth is
teeming, bursting at the
seams. But as I say
this, do you guys flash to anything?
And I throw it to the listeners too,
like what do you think deserves
its own carved out territory in
McMonth?
Fry guys,
birdie bringing you breakfast.
The symbol of breakfast.
She is the symbol of breakfast? I believe she was
introduced when McDonald's started pushing
breakfast. She's like an early
bird. Oh right, that's right, you're right.
And
Officer Big Mac may
make cheese.
Now I don't know
if every one of these gets their own
star episode. No, no, I'm just
talking about. But we will meet and discuss
all of these people and get to know them very well.
Well, and when you
didn't mention, the
founder.
The film.
Ray Kroc, oh I'd love to do the founder.
Ray Kroc, the McDonald's brothers.
Oh my god, this is
I'm very fond of this film. That is
one of those just like perfectly
not average, it's better than average.
You'd never call it an A plus
movie. It's in that
late shift zone. It's just like
the B plus-iest of B plus
movies.
You let a wolf into
the hen house.
Dick, Ray Kroc
took everything. He took our names.
I'm going to take it. I saw your name, I'm going to take it.
I took it, I did, I'm going to take it.
I'm a big fan.
I've done a
lot of little founders plays in my
head. The milkshake, the
powdered milkshake at the steak house.
Oh yes, that Linda Cardellini makes
so suggestively.
It's really good. I like it.
Got it in the lips there.
Well we have to do that I guess now.
I guess so. Thank you
for, this is good, I'm glad I asked.
A more recent one that
I, you know,
we were busy being
teenagers or adolescents so I wasn't
tracking the McDonald's lore as
closely, but a few years ago
learning about, and I haven't watched
them all, but the Klaski, Suspo,
McDonald,
Land, Chupo.
Those kind of,
it's like really jagged
Klaski, Chupo,
late 90's.
Very much in that grotesque,
real monsters vein.
That made it a little bit far, you know some
of these, like Uncle Ogrimacy
was in a Club 3 poll, the Klaski
Chupo cartoons were in Club 3, and then Club 3 is part
of this. I think if there's suggestions for
what does Club 3 want in
McDonald's world specifically,
we can figure that out. Yeah,
I have a thing that pops into my head that you're not
going to like. Uh oh,
am I going to have to cancel the whole month now?
McDonald's points.
Come on. It's its own
whole episode.
If the listener wants it, that's what
popped into my head. If they
want it, we'll see. And you think McDonald's
points are so specific in such a big
area that it could not possibly be
contained within. I didn't say it couldn't.
I didn't say it couldn't. I just said it could.
Grimace is kind of like
de facto Mets
mascot. He is?
Is he? He kind of like
the Mets
fan base, I feel like kind of adopted
him. He might have
thrown out a picture or something in
the 2024 season.
Is Mr. Mets still there? Mr. Mets
and Mrs. Mets are still there.
But they've adopted Grimace. But Grimace
is also kind of. He's their third?
Skull King. He threw out the first
pitch somewhere in the run of
a seven game winning streak.
So he's beloved.
Also merchandise.
McDonald's merchandise, including
the Happy Meal Toys. Happy Meal Toys.
That's three hours. That's great.
We can go. Narrowing it down.
Yeah.
Yeah. No, there's
so much to end and not even getting into
world's largest McDonald's, the
non-standard McDonald's, the weird McDonald's,
the Roswell UFO McDonald's.
There's so much here.
Narrowing it down will be the hardest test of all.
This might be McMonth 1.
Possibly. Yeah, yeah.
But let's do what we can.
McDonald's video games.
McDonald's video games. Jesus.
Alright, so we better
do McMonth 1 so that
we can clear the path for McMonth 2.
Give us your suggestions. I'm curious
anything anybody wants out of this.
I think it'll be good.
I think that's going to be a good old time.
Now, to weave
us into today's topic. Today's topic
is also part of a broader
plan that we have cooking for
2025 because 2025
is the 70th
anniversary of
Disneyland Park. And that seems
like as good a time as any
to cover things that
have been there from the beginning.
Disneyland primaries,
classics, basics,
perennials. We have a lot on
the list of things that have been there
since day one. And it seems
like it would be a good idea to
tie them all together and to cover it
in this 70th
anniversary year. The platinum celebration
as everyone is saying.
Double diamond.
Oh man, they didn't use that.
Like
podcast the ride's platinum celebration is one
way of branding it. I had another way
of branding it, which is calling this the class of 55.
I have one more
way of branding it, which is getting a little
fancier and not just saying
class of 55, but saying class of
55.
My man.
That jazz
is it up? Yeah, that's great.
I'll leave that on the desktop.
That'll be ready to go anytime. They need to do
that for the commercials, the official commercial.
Yeah, they got to license that.
Most numbers
and years aren't shouted
by one of the great restaurateurs
in that way. It's the Red Rocker himself,
Sammy Hagar. Yeah, yeah. There should be a
Cabo Wabo with Downtown Disney.
But for some reason.
Well, there should have been and it should have gone
out of business to clear a path for all the new
stuff they're doing. Yeah, I just saw
Tortilla Joe's officially being gutted
right now.
It's like a steak and bourbon place coming.
Steak and bourbon.
I'm kind of interested by it. I don't know what
the restaurant is called, but I was
real because I was so
annoyed at the like steak
and bourbon. Why are you annoyed?
It's just a little exalt.
We're still doing this.
What do you mean? I'm not sure what he means either.
I guess people are
still eating steak and bourbon. The faux
masculinity branding.
It's
on the giant walls.
It's called Arthur and Sons Steak
and Bourbon. That's too much faux masculinity
for you. Nothing.
It's just nothing.
First you already got Arthur.
There's one man.
Patriarchy much.
And then Sons? We've just added at least two more.
It just seems like nothing.
It doesn't even say
steak and bourbon on it. It says Arthur and
Sons and it's like a mid-century modern thing
that fits into the rest of downtown Disney.
I don't know. I don't agree with you one bit.
I'm confused by you. It just seems like
a little gibberish.
It's a little Sip and Sonder
for me.
Sip and Sonder doesn't tell you anything because what do you sip on
and what even is Sonder?
It's acknowledging the inner
lives of the people around you.
We know what Sonder means.
But I know what steak is and I know
what bourbon is and I know what sons are
and I know that Arthur is a popular name in this
world. I don't know. What is one thing
that's obtuse about that?
Did you think it was like Andrew
Tate's Steak and Bourbon restaurant
or something?
Tony Hinchcliffe presents Arthur and Sons.
It seems like a nasty combo to me.
Steak and bourbon?
What are you talking about? It's a great combo.
It's a wonderful combo.
It is delicious. What's happening?
Honestly, I don't know. I don't even
I feel like if we dig in it's going to destroy the rest of the
episode, quite frankly. I don't want
to talk about the castle. I'm confused though.
Scotch and steak I
can say. It's smokier.
Kind of makes more sense. But it's harsher though.
Why wouldn't bourbon's mellower?
I don't think
bourbon is mellower at all.
What? I completely think
it's a little mellower.
I don't know. It sounds delicious
to me. I know. I'd love to go have some steak
and bourbon. This is the most contentious the show has ever been
or at least in the last two years.
This is like country bears level
I think we're at right here when we had
the disagreement. So if we said we're going
for work for the podcast
we're taking you to Arthur and Sons.
Wow. What if we made you have steak
and bourbon together?
Maybe steak and water?
Maybe
a little sloppy steak.
If you don't want to drink that's fine.
To me that is the most natural
combo in the world.
I'm not sure. Look I don't know.
I don't know what's happening.
I don't like to drink too much
in my early 20s. I don't understand.
I'm just showing you this picture of
a chef on the outside.
I hate to keep digging in
but you called like the like because this doesn't seem
so like aggressively masculine
to me. It doesn't seem like he's not
like smoking a big stogie and he's shirtless
making a steak and bourbon or anything.
No that picture looks
like stock image.
They both look like stock
image. It just seems
I don't know it just seems a little hollow
to me. Hollow?
As opposed to Tortilla
Joe's a restaurant that I
only went to once and it made me sick.
Tortilla Joe's at least I mean he's a guy
I guess you can think of him as like a little guy.
I'm not saying I'm mad at Tortilla Joe's.
Joe good. Arthur toxic.
We haven't seen what Arthur and his son look like
though. We don't know. We're
looking at the sons.
They're bare naked at all times
waving their big
flappy hogs around. These guys
are disgusting.
They're what's wrong with society.
They're like UFC fighters
or something.
And they're jacked.
Fascinating. Well this is going to be
a big I didn't think about this.
I didn't even know the name of the restaurant.
I didn't know the name of the restaurant.
Immediately it's now one of the great podcasts
The Ride Debates. This is going to be
open what in the next year I hope.
And we're all going to have to do it.
Unless Jason burns the construction
site down. I hope he doesn't
because I'm interested in trying it.
But maybe you know if it happens it happens.
Okay. So
with that
alright nevermind Class of 55
cancelled. It's going to be shit like this
from now on. No no no but I think like
as a you know maybe not as a series that
runs together but something like Tomorrowland
which ended up taking us a little bit
but a kind of when in doubt
when we got no other ideas like what's
something that we can default to
it seems like covering some Class of 55
stuff could be good the rides that are still around
maybe some original weird old
school stuff that has disappeared or things that never
got built. I flashed to some other things.
One thing that I flashed to is The Bench.
I think that's an episode for sure we
discussed this a little bit. By which I mean
Walt's Bench. The place where
he sat and stewed
while his daughters went on a
merry-go-round without him. And one question
I've always had is why weren't you on the
merry-go-round? I've been to that specific
merry-go-round and it's quite easy to be on it
with your children. So I don't understand
why he felt like and then he just
ended up building a carousel that also a dad
could not be on. I've always
been confused by the story
but that's one of the things that we can delve into
the Griffith Park Carousel
Origins of Disneyland.
There's potentially an episode out there
called Disneyland
where we just like talk
about the origins, whatever.
I mean I kind of like
that deep into the podcast
with all these micro topics
that at some point we would just do Disneyland
and figure out what that means.
The orange groves.
Absolutely.
Oh and who owned these lands before and how
they pieced it all together. There's a lot of
primaries in just
Disneyland here at 70. And it seems like
a good thing for us to do.
I think
we carry a little bit
of a mantle like we need
to celebrate Disneyland 70th
because my suspicion is Disneyland
is not really going to celebrate Disneyland 70th.
Well there'll be some
banners.
Banners on Carthay and maybe they'll repaint
the theater.
It's under scrims and scaffolding
right now. So there's going to be some paint
and there's going to be some signs
and it'll say 70th.
Projection mapping. Maybe a little
projection mapping. There's some drips and
drabs. Obviously we're getting the Walt robot
but I don't know.
The Walt robot's a big one. That's a summer blockbuster
for us. We're going to have to get there soon.
But we're going to have to get there in August because we're not going to be able to
go with our shit passes.
It just occurred to me
for making near future plans
that like oh I don't get Fridays.
How dare I want a Friday.
We're both on the same worst one
and you don't get Fridays.
We'll get to it but it's going to have to be
August by the time we
see it. But it got delayed until July.
Maybe it gets delayed longer.
Are they trying to have Walt robot up and running
for the actual day?
For the actual day probably. I would hope.
Gotcha.
Get in line Fantastic Foreign Jurassic World
Rebirth.
The blockbuster this summer is the Walt robot.
People flocking
saying no we're not going to the movies. We're going to Anaheim.
I don't have time to see a movie.
Fantastic Four coming to Tomorrowland.
In Disneyland.
You say this like as if it's for sure.
It is.
Walk around.
I know I thought you were referring to
things that we've texted about because you have the theory
that Fantastic Four is the best hope
that we have for Tomorrowland to get a little bit of juice
in it because it's kind of this throwbacky
mod thing and we always feel like
Tomorrowland just needs to go back to 60s
vibe. And Feige on stage said
modeled after Epcot and
Tomorrowland. The aesthetic of the movie.
Alright. So
maybe they'll be meeting a little
lead boy.
Scott's not the only one
who's been off on Secret
Project.
It's clobbering time.
I'm doing what Mike did
earlier. I'm doing physical
movements.
As lead boy are you fighting the Fantastic Four
or are you their friend?
I'm just one of Mole Man's disgusting
creatures that like skitter
around behind him. You're a lackey for
Mole Man. Yeah.
He's already kind of a lackeyish villain let's be
honest. Yeah he's a lackey
Alda of Horde. He's got mole people
but still yeah. Yeah. Well alright.
We're excited about that. I think if Fantastic Four doesn't
work it's not only
it's so much trouble for Tomorrowland
ever getting a redo but also like
is Marvel just are we
done with the MCU if Fantastic Four
bombs? It seems like the last
hope. I think we got two big ones
coming and if those don't do well
then we'll see. Yeah.
They're putting a lot of money into those. I liked
hearing that Robert Downey Jr. is apparently
writing a lot of backstory for
Doctor Doom. If only there
was already
sixty years of
backstory available for
Doctor Doom. I also think
by a bunch of losers by people who
don't have the brains. They don't have the
brains of RDJ. I wouldn't worry
too hard about him working on
the backstory. I wouldn't worry
about him. He's gonna work too hard.
He's gonna think of too much. I wouldn't worry.
And he's going there. He's taking pictures of Stark
flight tests or whatever.
I know. I saw the photos. Yeah. Yeah.
And he has glasses on. I know. He's thinking
really hard about it. I like the ride better.
Yeah. Yeah. He said he's gonna stay
on after he's done with Marvel.
He's gonna stay on helping Imagineering.
That's what he said.
Really? Yeah.
Okay. Yeah.
Got my work cut out for me.
Everybody's slacking around here.
What's he gonna
do? He looks good question. I don't know.
Like, wow, it's incredible.
Robert Downey Jr. personally figured out
how to make the Matterhorn smooth again.
Yeah. He saw what
none of us could.
All right. Well, we look forward to his work. Maybe he'll
come be on the show. Maybe we can interview him purely
as an Imagineer.
And then it'll be the Billy Bob effect of like
now people know you for your other career as an actor
and then he warms out of the room.
Yeah, sure. It could happen.
But it's worth a shot. RDJ's at
Imagineering. Ariana Grande
says she has ideas for
wicked projects in the parks.
These actors
are chair Imagineers now, you know?
Yeah. Everybody thinks they can do it.
Only we can.
Only the three of us can. Our genius ride ideas
we throw out sometimes. That's right.
We're the pros.
So, anyways,
that brings us to this point, and this
I guess would be considered the first
of the class of 55.
Oh no, I don't have it teed up.
55!
And that is a real
fundamental, the most fundamental
Sleeping Beauty
castle. I think it makes
sense as a place to start.
It is the centerpiece
of everything. It was
the symbol of the park before there even
was a park. They
wedded America's Appetites
in 1954
with concept art of this castle.
So by the time anybody got to the park
in 55, they knew it
from their TVs already.
They knew it. They loved it.
Sleeping Beauty Castle is pretty damn
important. And yet it took us eight years.
What happened? I don't know. Too many
restaurants. Life got in the way.
Life finds a way.
Life finds a way to get in the way.
That's
like a mug or a towel or a
pillow. You gotta get that.
Oh, that should be on what's the store at Downtown
Well, it's gone, I think. Yeah, I know. But what was it?
I don't know. Sleeping Saunders.
It's all 28.
The one that just had a wooden plank that
said imagine all the people.
It's a hundred dollars.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Everyone likes the castle, I think.
The only time I ever hear anything negative is
when people are comparing it
to bigger castles. That's the only time I ever hear
anybody trash it. Sure.
Mike, I wanted to ask you that because
you grew up in the Midwest. I grew up on the East
Coast and
we went to
Disney World fairly
regularly, so any times we
would see clips of Disneyland,
we'd be like, that castle's so
small. I want to go to Florida. It's massive.
I understand there's an adjustment.
Yes. Because it does
feel kind of like a toy castle. The first
couple times you go and
you're used to the Cinderella Castle from Orlando.
So I understand it,
but if you go to Disneyland enough,
I think you really grow to
love it and appreciate it.
This is interesting. Is this a perspective thing?
Do I prefer
the humble charms
of Sleeping Beauty Castle, being
that that was my home park?
Yeah. Do you have a...
Gosh, I don't know.
Well, it's a good fundamental
debate to get into at the top here.
It seems like one of those
Mitch
he probably did this in our third episode
or whenever we had Mitch on. He was
probably like, it's bigger. Cinderella's
bigger. It's better.
I would imagine. I think that the
coziness of Disneyland itself
and by the statue and everything,
all of that
together makes me actually now like
Sleeping Beauty's castle better.
But if it was just
I would say if it was just the castles
completely separate from the
actual theme parks themselves,
I can see the
Cinderella you liking it better.
It's a bit hard to argue.
I mean, one is more of like a
architectural
marvel. Yeah. But I do like
being in Disneyland in that
area on Main Street better than I like
being in the Magic Kingdom, even though I still like
being there in Magic Kingdom.
Are you like more at ease?
I think it just feels comforting. It feels comforting
to me more so.
Again, I don't dislike being on
Main Street in Florida, but
often there's some big stage.
It does feel like there's always a lot of nonsense
in Florida, too. I was thinking how
I have very few memories of just
walking in the castle gate.
Like walking
over the bridge
in Florida, because usually there's something going on.
Something going on. There's so much more space
there. So again, you're in the
coziness of Disneyland and
you see the castle there. Now I do
prefer that experience as a
whole. But I
can, I could, I don't know
if I have necessarily a preference
separating the castles from their location.
This, a
lot of websites mentioned, of course
this is the only castle Walt
ever worked on
when he was alive, like had
a hand in the direct
development. Sure, yes.
And it was
specifically from him
originally, like
the origins of there being a
castle go back to the sketch
that Herb Ryman did, I think
in 53, which was
like, it's one of those, if you look up
Herb Ryman Disneyland
map or Disneyland plans,
it's one of those images you know for sure.
Like, oh yes, they've put this up in like
Disney Gallery or, you know,
like the Lincoln lobby or whatever.
It's one of those, like, it's not the
Disneyland we know, but it sure has
a lot in common with it.
And a lot of the, like, original base ideas.
So that, I think
he left Herb Ryman
to do this sketch.
And he said, biggest thing,
it's all got to build to a huge
castle. That's going to be the symbol of
the whole park, we need a castle in there.
And what he drew,
it was all the way in the back.
It was like the entire park built
to it as opposed to it being the centerpiece.
And it was also
a lot bigger.
It was like,
yeah, just like a more
imposing
European rising up
over everything kind of castle.
And I think it was his decision
later to like, maybe I'd like it
a little more gentle, more humble.
And then I also heard that
there was an idea to flip it
as well. Yes, right.
Which is what he did. And if you look at
his map,
or like, here I'll flip this around.
Here's an old sketch
that I'll show you, where
the,
it went away, but you saw what I was...
I saw what you were getting at.
Here is like the front entrance of the castle,
but the back, like the window pattern
definitely feels like what we know
is the back today.
And the story of
that is that once this was turned
from a sketch, which I just showed you, into
a 3D model,
Walt was away
on a trip or something,
and was coming back, the first order of
business when he gets back is to look at this
model. There was an engineer
Fred Yorger, who
made a model based on the sketches.
And once it was physicalized, he brought in
Ryman and asked what he thought, and he said, well,
I don't like it. And it was built
to split in half, like exactly
at that point. And he said, I don't know if you flip it
around. And he flips it around, and everybody went,
whoa, whoa, whoa, that's not what, like,
Walt's coming in in 10 minutes, you can't just do
that. And he's like, why not? I don't know.
I like it better. It seems like, I don't
know, back seems like the front and vice versa.
And Walt came in, and the first thing he said was,
love that.
He loved it out of the gate. So,
yeah, a little last minute twist around
was a smart thing to do.
This is one where I think, I feel
like I saw multiple
urban, like, apocryphal
stories of, like, well, they were just
cleaning up, and they accidentally assembled
it backwards. And that's
what, well, Walt's like, oh, I like
that. So, I
feel like there's different stories
and justifications out there about
it. Sure, sure. As
kind of fits in with the
Walt Disney as kind of a tall
tale, American tall
tale figure. Walt sneezed, and
the sneeze blew the castle around on the
model. And he said, ah, wait a minute,
that looks better.
We made a little sound spun around.
Right. Yeah, yeah. Now,
I'm glad this happened because
here's a take. I don't know
if this is going to be a controversial take. Oh,
interesting. I don't really like the back.
There's something that I've never
liked about the back. The view that you have
essentially from the carousel and
from the Fantasyland rides. And I've never
been able to put my finger on why
I don't like it. But when I heard that
the back was going to be the front,
I was like, that's a disaster. I think
that's a really great last minute
decision. There's something really warm
and welcoming about what ended
up being the front. But I
was like, oh, this is an audio medium.
I need to be able to put into words why I
don't like that back. And I couldn't figure
it out. Do you have any idea why?
And I thought this when I was a kid.
I don't. I like the back.
I like seeing the little... Let's see if I can
figure it out. Do you think it's a mental
thing of like,
I am being presented
with this as the back
of the cat. Like, if
if you had first
encountered the castle with the back,
it's the front.
You see what I mean? Are you like, oh,
it's the back. It doesn't matter. You know?
No. I don't know if it's
that. Or maybe the back
just can't compare to the front.
I'm not
sure. I like...
There's a lack of like,
you could maybe consider part
like, it doesn't look as finished
even though it is. Yes. Because it doesn't
have the... I think I've always felt that. Because the blue, like the blue
on top, whatever you would call those like
things that cover the
whatever, the towers? I don't know.
Like, there's... It feels
a little like less finished just because there's not as
much blue sticking out
as there is on the front.
You know what? Maybe also the back.
There's something about it where I feel
the 50s nature
of it. It feels more dated to me. I see
I can see that. I see what you're saying there with the pinks.
It's a more 50s style of molding
or something. Yeah, I know what you're saying.
I don't... Look, I'm not going to turn my
back to the back. You're allowed to.
I'm not going to spit on it. I don't feel
that strongly. You could, but it would be maybe not a good idea.
I don't think I would make it that far. I'm not that
good of a spitter. I don't know. If you spit
on the castle, how fast
is anybody saying... Is anybody saying anything?
Do one spit?
One spit and two
employees see you and one's maybe working like
Toad and one's working...
That's what I don't know. I don't know. I don't know if the answer is nobody
sees it or if they have
a dedicated 14 person
behind-the-scenes staff trying to prevent
exactly what you're describing.
Spit squad. I think if you
are real slick about it
and you're dribbling on the castle,
no one would notice. But if you walk
up and do a hawk... Wait a minute.
So if you lean over
and you start drooling all over
the castle... Oh, I guess drooling is
different than spitting.
But if you walked up and did a hawk too,
I think people would
be upset.
You might get stopped. If you hawked too
on the Sleeping Beauty castle,
I think no one would say anything
unless there was a higher-up
manager that happened to see you.
That's my prediction. By the way, no one try this.
I don't want you to do it. Yeah, don't do this.
And I'm not winking when I say that. I truly don't want you to do it.
But hypothetically,
I bet most average employees would just be like,
God, I hope they don't do that again.
Because then I have to say something.
I hope they don't stay here for the next few hours
summoning all the saliva
they can find so they can spit on that castle.
Spit on that thing.
I bet you'd get away with one.
That's my guess.
But we'll never know because you should not do it.
I don't know. I think we're going to start getting videos.
I heard you, Mike. We should edit this out.
I wink-wink. You don't want me to do it.
I don't want you to do it. This one's for you, Mike Carlson!
No, stop!
Then they're
detained, but it was like, wait, but who gave you the idea?
Because really, that's where the crime rests.
Alright, Magic Key cancelled.
He already couldn't go on Fridays or during July.
It's basically no change.
It was Scott who did the idea, though.
I was the first who said spit.
And Jason's the one who added the
hoctua, which really gave it the oomph.
And the friend Sam Spittle.
I don't know in the
spring of 2025
that hoctua has quite any
oomph left. She'll be back.
She'll be back.
When we see the fruits of the
many, many television development deals
that she got,
she'll be back bigger than ever.
How does Secretary of State hoctua sound to you?
Because I think
in the next year or two,
little Marco's going to drop the vault.
That's what I'm saying.
Maybe she's up for it.
She'll be back.
Well, I don't know.
Again, I don't want to spit on the back.
I guess if that ever struck anybody.
It's not a hate. It's just like, that's the back?
Yeah, I think probably what you
respond to, I think, is what you were saying.
It feels a little bit older for whatever reason.
And I think if there was almost
more blue in the
front section here, I think
you would like it better. Maybe so.
Now, you have some inherent
pink and peach.
There's different color
schemes. It's always stayed basically
what it is. But subtle
adjusts and subtle. Again, this is the
sort of thing we can look forward to in anniversary years
is it's a more royal blue
on the turrets.
And they see if they...
Is that enough of a thing we did for the
70th? They should
honor early Tomorrowland
and put decorations made
of aluminum like that creaking
rocket that used to be in Tomorrowland.
That would be nice.
Which was going to be on the
castle more and then because it expanded
too much. I don't know that
it was. I just remember the rocket
was sponsored by
an aluminum company.
The tips of
the castle are made
of gold. And there is
another one of these apocryphal stories
as you described, Jason,
where
Walt wanted the spires to be covered in
22 karat gold leaf. He knew
his brother Roy would never approve the
extra expense. So rumor has it he
sent Roy on a business trip and
authorized the detail while he was gone.
I know. That's really good.
It waltzed up to
shenanigans, which is really funny.
That like his business partner,
his brother, you just have to trick him.
Like that's really good.
It can't
have been a great relationship on some level.
It involves trickery and
being put on a plane
under false pretenses.
I don't
understand. I have to go out of town
for, I have to go out of town
for 12 days to meet Disneyland's
official vendor of beef Wellington.
That doesn't even seem
practical. Day to day we're going to
have beef Wellington for 40
cents. That seems like we're getting
ripped. No, you go up there.
Walt insisted. He wanted me gone.
Some of the stories when you add
them up about Walt and Roy,
and even more so about Walt's
father, you're like, oh, maybe
some of this, maybe some of this
was a nightmare.
Maybe there was a lot of very
complicated family dynamics
going on. I think that's very true.
And that he's expressing a lot of like
strange, like stunted growth
things via the, I mean,
I think, look, as we've covered in a lot
with all the guys we've run into, I think
if you're, you know, if you're carving
up the planet and putting weird stuff
on it, like it comes from
some strange psychology. It has to.
It's the only way it can. Yeah.
It's a lunatic.
It's the only way to explain it.
But a nice lunatic. He presented well on television
and was friendly
and friendly. Yeah, folksy.
Right. Yeah. So we'll talk
about his bench later. We'll talk about
that aspect of it. Yeah.
Yeah. And why, like, just be on it.
What do you mean? Like, go be
at, like, there's, adults can be on
carousels. Maybe there was a, but what if we find
that there was a weight limit at the time?
I don't believe there was any rules
for rides back then, though. Oh, that's
a good, yeah, what am I saying? Yeah.
In 1951? Yeah. And it's all
aluminum and lead paint. That's where you see
all those, like, I,
something I think we need to get into at some point
is, like, the kinds of
rides that you see only in old
jittery films from 1892.
Yeah. Like, I always love those things
where it's people in, like,
four layers of thick
burlap, like, women in, like,
you know, like, skirts that add
up to, like, five inches
of thickness between all the
layers, and that they're just, like, sliding
down a conveyor belt, and then, like,
being, like, shaken around like it's a
raisin factory or something.
Like, those kind of things are so crazy
to me. It's like you get in a wash tub
and you get pushed off a hill, and that was
at a theme park. Yeah. And that was
a ride. Oh, man. Early Coney
Island was so crazy.
Even crazier in that
some stuff is not documentary
because often stuff would just burst
into flames. Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm. Uh,
yeah. It's sometimes on purpose. That was the
idea. That was it, yeah. Yeah.
Uh, so. The
exploder. It's not
going to actually explode, is it? No, that's exactly what it's
going to do. Uh, alright, fine, I'll
do it. Dynamite crate.
So it's an illusion?
It's an illusion of a dynamite crate,
you say. Yeah. Uh,
sure. No, it's, yes. Well, it's less of a
crate and more of an enclosed box. So, yes,
it is an illusion. Mm-hmm.
Uh-uh. Uh, lots of old-timiness
to get into. Uh, another
bit of old-timiness is that, you know, there's a
few people. I mentioned that Imagineer and I mentioned
her Ryman. But then there was another guy who I
think, like, was, like, the actual architect.
Or maybe not. Wait a minute.
Okay. Forgive me. I don't know exactly this
guy's role. I ran into a name. Roland
E. Mill. Uh,
Roland E. Mill was part of, became
Disney's castle guy at a point. And here's
the history here. Roland was a pilot
in World War I. He crashed his
plane and spent the remainder of the war
driving officers around France
and doing American government reparations.
While on the road, he sketched many of the castles
that he saw in both France
and Germany, including Nusch von
Stein Castle in Bavaria,
which became the basis of this castle.
In October 1919, he met
Walt Disney, also
a driver in France, showed him his castle
drawings, and they became great friends.
So when Walt starts his movie studio,
he remembered his old
ambulance driving
castle drawing friend.
I mean, that's, that's an odd
the, well, and hey, this
ties to Ray Kroc, too, because they also met
while driving in war. Right. Cause you've all been
in, we've all been in, like, a cab or a lift
and there's a chatty driver
who maybe has some conspiracy theories
or they want to show you something. Yes.
And we always end up being great
dear old friends with those drivers.
It's possible. I mean, I've had plenty of nice
people who, like, are very chatty and then some
people who are lunatics
tap both ways. So some... But if they
hand you drawings, you know you're in good shape.
You know those are going to be normal. If they're
normal, yeah, if they're normal drawings.
Here, I sketched you while I was
driving or something like that. That's probably a problem.
That's not good.
How did you, maybe I should have been washing
your hands. Yeah.
But Walt was a folksy guy,
I guess. I guess he was open to it if...
Just like meeting people. Open to things.
What, and he's 18 at that point?
Yeah, I guess that's right. It's just weird how 18 years old
he's in the war
driving around and he meets the guy
who ends up making the castle
for his theme park. Words that would have been
nonsense back then. Right.
Hemingway was a driver in World War I
as well. He drove an ambulance. Really?
Farewell to Arms. The book
is based on that. But did he meet
any friends that he worked
with later? I don't know. We've got to look
into drivers because it seems like
World War I drivers may have
shaped the 20th, much of the
20th century. Notable drivers, perhaps.
Maybe that's an episode.
Notable drivers.
Hey, fun fact about New
Schwannstein Castle, it
served as a depot for Nazi
plunder that was taken from France
during the Second World War.
Wow. Nazi plunder depot.
Your one stop shop.
Storage.
Does that mean, so like
they took it but then they got it back
and then that's a place where like
a crazy Larry type guy was trying
to move it all at low, low prices.
I think from just
reading on Wikipedia
that castle is not strategic.
It's not in a
strategic location.
So I think stuff
stolen from France was put there
because it was secure. It was a pain to get to like a Costco.
It was a pain to get to like a Costco.
Oh yeah, yeah, well
it was parking lots.
And if you need gas,
God forbid. How much stolen French
art is in Sleeping Beauty's castle?
Or was when Walt was around?
Oh yeah, how much
Nazi
plunder did Walt personally
have? Some of the projects,
the Operation Paperclip guys working
on Tomorrowland would just drop stuff
to store in Sleeping Beauty Castle.
I'm jumping around but did you see what
before they opened the walkthrough, because the walkthrough
didn't open right away. No, Castle
is 55, Walkthrough is 57.
Sleeping Beauty does not
come out till 59.
Something I never even thought about.
Yeah, it was a pre-promotion.
Yeah.
Getting the word out about Sleeping Beauty well
before it came out. I think it was delayed.
I don't think they meant it to be that but it ended up
being that. Sleeping Beauty was delayed
I mean. Oh, gotcha.
But you're saying, yes, because the
I swear to God also, I mean this like
this is probably a basic fact
to people listening to this theme park podcast
but I also think it's distinctly possible
that there are people who don't know that
there is this exhibit that you can
walk around in the castle. Oh yeah.
Because it is pretty easy to miss.
That is like an awning that says
Sleeping Beauty Castle and you might look at that
and say, yeah I know, but what you might
not know is that you can walk around
in there and see wonderful dioramas.
Yeah, I like that it's not publicized
that much because it does feel like
and I don't think I went on it for a little
while because I don't think I knew it was
there. I do think I happened
upon it one trip early on.
Right. Oh, so you were, it's not like
you came to Disneyland
with a big list of all the stuff that you knew
there is to do. Right. Yeah, it is a real
bump into situation. Because that's the best
stuff is when you happen upon things.
Yeah. In a lot of ways. Obviously not the big
rides but I'm saying when you feel like you've discovered
something that still feels exciting.
Whether it's this
or whether it's the first time I discovered
Abracadabra on the boardwalk.
Like whatever it is, you go, oh look at this
I didn't know this was here. They don't publicize this.
So you gotta have little things like
you know, walk through.
Yeah, well and yeah you know what you're right
that is like, it's part of the texture
that you know, like
maybe budgets don't always allow
these little things that
because like, now forgive me
I don't remember what this is but
DisneySea has great stuff in that capacity.
There's something that's like kind of
the headquarters of SEA or like
one of the primary places.
Are you talking about Magellan's the restaurant?
No, there's more of
a walk through kind of situation
with interactive stuff for kids
to play with. Yeah, what's the name
of that place? It's over by the volcano.
I think that's what you're talking about.
What's the bar in the steamer?
Is it Roosevelt's?
Yeah, is it Roosevelt's in the ship?
Yes. But that's not SEA
as much SEA stuff in there I don't think.
Literal SEA but not SEA the society
of explorers and adventurers I don't think.
No. But it's all SEA I guess maybe.
Maybe I'm wrong. Now when you talked about just
bumping into things, I flashed
to something, forgive me, I'm
delving into my eye photo
and this might not be interesting
it's not even called eye photo anymore. Look at me.
Oh geez, 2006 so much.
Looking at my photos.
When you talk about just bumping into weird little
exhibits that you don't know exist
I wanted to talk about this
on the show forever ago. We did
a little like baby moon
before our second baby showed up
in Westlake Village
and we stayed at kind of a moderate
hotel in Westlake Village but we wandered
around the nearby Four Seasons
which has a really nice bar and
after we got a drink, not
Erin, pregnant, she did not
but we were like
let's just wander the grounds here because we always like doing that
at hotels and we saw that there was this great
gallery of a very
like
I don't even want to say Banksy
more of a Mr. Brainwash
who did things
like here's, oh my god I forgot
it's Mickey. It's like Mickey Mouse
heads that are dripping with weird rainbow paint.
Okay. And you look at the like
oh very good and then like
how much would you pay for that? Oh maybe
$150. $6,000
for like
here's like a melting Darth
Vader that you can buy called
Galactic Blast that you can buy
for a mere $15,000.
I was taking a lot of pictures in here
because I was thinking about Michael Ferrari
the wonderful artist we've gotten to know
via City Walk and the
Venice Boardwalk keeper. But a lot
of, I just, this gallery was
so funny and douchey. There was a lot of stuff
by a guy named Josh Mayhem.
So
I'm like, I was instantly like oh man
Michael Ferrari would get along with
the thieves with Josh Mayhem, or their enemies
I don't know. Of the
Westlake Mayhems.
That's right they own
everything around there.
Oh the tire magnets.
I looked at Josh Mayhem's website just now and it
has like that, what is that from
is it Panasonic? Oh that's exactly the kind
of thing, yes. It's the, isn't that
or is that RCA records? Oh RCA yes you're right.
The thing where the guy is in the chair
and he's getting blown back by the sound of the speakers
and his tie's flying back
of, he's like reclining like
whoa man. Rainbow paint version
of it. It's that with just paint splattered all over
and it's dripping all the way on the back. I kind of like this
honestly. I mean I, look
I will admit I was taking pictures thinking
there are some things in here that I think
Mike would like. Yeah that's one of them.
Including, I can't believe
this was back in August, I can't believe I haven't brought this up on
the show. A lot was
Josh Mayhem and then there was another artist
whose name is just Risk.
All caps.
And here is a photo
check this out, as you look at the photo
Risk is to
art what Aerosmith
is to rock and roll.
Wow, well now you. This is the most Mike
sentence. That says all you need
to say. And that is a quote from Aerosmith.
It's attributed to all of them
together despite the photo being
of Risk, Steven Tyler
Joe Perry and Slash.
Slash? Yeah I know.
Gets along with Slash, Andy
Deep and Aerosmith. What does Chris
Angel fit into this picture? Oh man.
They're right off the camera.
They cropped him, he just wasn't
applicable. The quote's about music
so we just don't want Chris in there. Seems right.
He was at this, no question
he was at the event I'm showing you this picture.
He must have been. Can I show something to
get Jason's T levels revving
up? Yeah yeah rev that T. Jason
Josh Mayhem has
a blown away Popeye.
It's colorful
rainbow Popeye. Whoa a totally
fucked up pop art Andy
Warhol
steroids Popeye. Drippy paint
Popeye. Drippy paint Popeye.
I like that.
Scott you don't know this but I
did make a one dollar
reservation for a deck of
Popeye tarot cards.
Wait hang on.
A reservation? Like
they hadn't launched the Kickstarter
yet. But you got a big
discount. You got like a 20
dollar discount. I saw it on Instagram, I sent it to
him last night. And he sent it to me. I'm like
I truly don't know where
any of my tarot cards
we have a few decks of tarot
cards in the house but I think they're still
in like drawers or boxes or
something. He's going to be a
full tarot card guy now that
these Popeye cards are being made.
When Jane and I first started dating we
used to do three card readings for each
other pretty regularly. Could you do
a three card reading for us? I probably
could. With the Popeye deck?
Yeah.
That's great content. I don't know what every card
means but it comes with a booklet.
I've never cared about this
I've never cared about this kind of thing
until Popeye entered the party.
I was of course
as a man about to turn 40
I got really into it from
Ricky J and his history
of playing cards
and trick dice and tarot
cards. He was a tarot card guy? I like saying that like
say it with me folks. Ricky J
it was funny that you said it as if we knew
what you were doing. Ricky J don't make me finish
it. Ricky J Museum of
Jurassic Technology in Los Angeles.
Can I borrow
that tone to say a further fact about
Risk? Like 10 things to know about Risk.
Okay say it with me. Risk
was knighted by the Medici family
in Italy. He's Sir
Risk. Sir Risk. Why do they get
to knight people? Who the hell is the Medici
family? That's a good point.
Not a family you want to cross.
How could you be rock and roll
and a knight? Josh Mayhem
has a Scrooge too
there's a Scrooge here. Do we get prices
on these? No you have to call
I think it's probably like 10 grand.
Look I'm glad I saved it and just did it on the air
instead of texting you. I'm glad you're discovering
Josh Mayhem. Your new favorite
I don't like every Josh Mayhem piece
but there are some I wouldn't mind
having but I'm not going to
save up for some of them. There's one that
if you look at this another
drippy one
this is like
kind of like Mickey Mouse but it's also like one
of those bear bricks. It's a bear brick yeah.
The dumbest thing you like.
So if you want an expensive
bear brick for
$10,500
That one doesn't get me going.
That doesn't get my tea going
as much. I looked
risk the artist
has kind of an Alan Moore Rick Rubin
look
the long white hair. That is accurate
and so I was like
immediately endeared me to
him that look.
This just shows you
be open to anything
try anything. Bump into
expensive art galleries
whenever you can.
This doesn't really apply to Sleeping Beauty
because you can't buy that stuff.
You know what though I was going to say like
I was ready to do like oh yeah they redid it
in the 70s and now they've done it in kind of this classic
way and I'm like no fuck that
I want Josh Mayhem and Risk
Takeover of the Sleeping Beauty
dioramas. Make it rock and roll
guys. Well what if
Arthur and Sons now is owned by
Josh Mayhem and Risk
and fuse it with like some extra
little more. Oh now you like it.
Okay good because of that Popeye
statue. Yeah
yeah. Be a Popeye statue when you walk in. If you
could get steak au poivre
but it's all different colors and it's
drippy. Steak what?
Steak au poivre. And what's steak
au poivre? That steak with like black
black peppercorn sauce.
I Tom
plays the clip on the best show
a lot of
Orson Welles
I think it's from F for Fake and he goes
I love the steak au poivre please.
Like to a waiter
like to like
and it just seems
it's a very funny clip. It's
just big cape Orson Welles
just ordering something.
Would you wear a big cape
when we go to Arthur and Sons?
Oh you know
it's getting to that age
you know. You're almost a cape
age. Say it with me.
As a man who's almost 40 I'm now at
cape age.
Look at this. It's a big year for you two you know.
You're both at cape age.
So 40's cape age
I don't think I realized. It is.
You haven't been taking enough advantage of that.
That's right. I haven't. I'm insecure
about my cape wearing. The three of us
entering the next live show we do with a
big unfurl of a cape. Hello.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride.
And then I come out. You're hiding
Or Cape Fabe I unveil mine
and he comes out because he's actually tiny.
Cape Fabe.
Or a Sleeping Beauty
Escalusion where
because that's one of the things that happens in the dioramas
where the prince is
played by an owl and a bunch of birds
all carrying a cape.
So that'd be a nice thing if people
think it's Mike but wait that face looks like
Jason and then the whole thing's unfurled
and you're being lifted up by
several owls.
I've talked about it.
You know I'm realizing
there was like I feel
you know a lot of guys
RH I feel like oh
Roxanne from Goof Troop was so cute
and then girls
I've known multiple women
I feel like oh Fox
Robin Hood was like a big
cartoon crush. Did anyone
crush on fake prince
that's birds in cape?
I was really into
the birds in cape.
My biggest crush was 10 birds
all under one cloak.
I was
now I can't call it a crush but when I remembered
that there was that scene I was like
oh that's cool I like this guy.
I like Mr.
Mr. Birds
Mr. Multiple Birds
That's Prince Birds do you?
Oh yes knighted
just like risk.
Prince made
of birds. Prince made of birds.
Is there any
what's the term I'm thinking of slash
something? The porno
online fiction?
R34. No no no you're talking
about slash. Why can't I think of
the name of slash fiction?
What's the
dirty version though of fan
fiction? Rule 34 is the
slash something. Am I wrong?
Slash is like we're like hooking characters
up. I think it can be dirty.
There's got to be something about birds
in cape.
Has anyone ever been well I can explore that
a little bit. Let us know if you had a crush
on birds in cape.
On Prince Birds in cape.
To give full credit
here now that I'm looking at it because
Prince made of birds did
result in the Google image that I needed
and it was it's an
owl is the base. Two
smaller birds are the hands.
There's a squirrel on top of the
owl and then the boots are bunnies.
So it's not
though Prince made of birds
worked for me. Technically
that is erasure of the bunnies.
Right okay good to know.
And now to look for the porn of this.
That'll take me away from talking
for too long.
Let's talk about these dioramas a little
bit longer because there were two versions
of it. It opened in 57 because
Walt started complaining about
something up there. There's nothing. What do you mean
empty space? Put something in the castle.
All right I guess we'll figure something out.
And they started doing it
when that's tight. This is very tight
space. I don't know what we're going to put in there.
And they realized that well
if we do this art style they
worked with the production designer of the film and they did
this space maximizing
style of diorama
which you know
as the forest perspective you know
like makes you feel like there's more depth
than there is. Because the actual little windows
like the spaces they had to make the little
exhibits were extremely narrow.
So the depth is all kind of
your eye telling in the gaps.
So
it was this one in the 50s
that was kind of like
clever and made of flats
and almost like in the world of the multi plane camera
like the way the movies are done.
Just things stacked on different levels.
Then they redid it in the 70s.
And that looked kind of more like a
display at the Disney store.
That was done with like dolls. It was kind of
and then
at some point I think early 2000s
they evicted that and said let's go back
to the original. It's like a little bit more
classic and feels more like the film.
And in fact I went and looked at
that 70s version. It is kind of
there's something like kind of sort of a creepy
70s Barbie air
to it for sure. I don't know what it
is. It actually is a lot more dated
than the original one was.
Makes sense because the way that it is now
it feels so timeless to me.
It really is like
I still think it looks really cool.
It's really the depth
is deceiving.
Like how deep and big the little scenes are.
But yeah like dolls
I guess dolls give it too much
of a physical presence.
It grounds it in reality
too much I think.
Having them be more
I don't know what you would call it.
Not using the same effects I suppose
and just having them be represented
by dolls just makes it too much.
You know what. Here's the aesthetic.
Here's what the 70s version looks like.
It looks like is the show Thunderbirds?
The show that
Team America was based on.
Like the prince looks extremely Thunderbirds.
There's a charm to
the pictures I saw.
But it doesn't feel
quite the same. Like I think I would still like
going through it but it would be a little bit
more that it like creeps me out.
Yes. Yeah.
It also reminds me of the
Todd Haynes did the movie about
Karen Carpenter with Barbie dolls.
Oh maybe.
I mean as with all things
Karen Carpenter is really like heart
searing because she's so tragic
and it's a very upsetting unauthorized movie
about her spiral
done with Barbie dolls.
I'm looking at Sleeping Beauty I'm like
oh no.
Sleeping Beauty the band's going to die.
You're going to get unhealthy. Be careful Sleeping Beauty.
It very much
looks like a diorama.
The definition
of like school project diorama
where it's like I put a Barbie
and a GI Joe
and they're signing the Declaration of
Independence.
Yes. Extremely.
They seem like their bodies
aren't made to have like big hats
and wigs on them. There's something a little
disproportionate. Does anyone have a shoebox?
It is
just for school. Just because they're small I
do like think oh like there's little tiny
versions of them living in the castle and I don't
think that when I see the current
version. Like it feels more to you like
little doll souls are trapped.
Right. It's like oh yeah here's like tiny
Maleficent and here's tiny
Aurora and they're going about
their day or whatever but the way that
they have it now I do
my brain just sort of doesn't
think about the scale.
If they're 3D and physicalized
they're like half alive to you.
If they're flat they have no souls.
So you're not worried about them being trapped
in the castle forever.
This feels like these little dolls are trapped in this
castle forever.
That's upsetting.
Well you'll be happy to hear that now
they're all gone and we're incinerated.
Burn them.
This was
a switch out in 2008
that they went back to this original style
and boy this feels like unfamiliar to
me because I would go see
the dolls version because I was like
I liked being a kid and knowing oh there's this
kind of secret thing. Like I think I did
always make a point of going to the Sleeping Beauty
Walkthrough when I went to Disneyland.
As an adult rarely I think I've only
seen this like once since they did
it in 2008 which is a long time ago
now. Yeah I
because I went in 2007 for the first
time to Disneyland and I don't remember
the dolls. I don't think I ever saw
the dolls. I'm not sure. I don't think you could
go in there. I think that was during
a stretch of time. Oh when it was closed. Okay so then
it was never possible that I would have seen the dolls.
You would not have seen the dolls. Okay that makes sense then.
I don't think I saw the dolls. I don't think I really discovered
this until the 2010s.
The rare dolls Mike has
never seen. Oh and it makes me upset
because I could have been in the presence of these weird dolls
which is all I want in my life
is to be near weird dolls.
You're going to get a perfect recreation of all
of Susan's dolls from Seinfeld.
Everyone exactly where they were
on the shelf. Oh I would buy
what are the ones
which one did you have the doll look like?
George's mom. George's mom. Yeah.
I would buy an official Seinfeld
branded George's mom doll.
God. That would be good. I wouldn't
buy it but I'd happily come
over to see yours. I would like to go
see it. That would be good. That is an extremely funny
prop. Uh huh. Yeah. Hey talking
about school projects. The thing I was
thinking about recently.
I feel like we did a lot of projects
where they would say like go
home next week bring in a
coffee can.
Like a tin coffee can.
And like one teacher
like poked holes in either side
and had rubber bands in a weight
it put rubber bands
in a weight in it and you'd wind it up
and it would move like a remote
controlled car. Okay. Like
to demonstrate motion and
inertia and that sort of thing.
I was thinking the other day like
looking at a bag
of coffee grounds. I'm like
wait nothing I think I have like
a can of Maxwell House
in the house and that's like a
cardboard can. Like
do kids they
they just don't do those projects.
Kids don't play with cans anymore?
Well cause everything's like plastic
tubs of coffee
or bags of coffee.
Or curing pods.
Certainly can't do anything with those. No.
So you're concerned about the lack of kids
coffee projects in today's
elementary schools. Even
paper mache. Oh go home bring in
a bunch of newspaper.
It's a pain in the ass to get a whole newspaper nowadays.
I guess that's true.
That's true. Well
if you ever run for elected office
would you put this on your platform?
Just to get kids to be able to work
with paper mache and empty coffee cans again?
I would prefer coffee manufacturers
not use so much plastic.
So yes. Cause it was tin?
The old cans were tin or metal? Like what were they?
Some kind of metal. Lead.
Lead boy. Lead boy.
Lead boy. Lead boy coffee.
Careful
mom and dad your son might end up being
a podcaster if he drinks enough of that
lead boy coffee. Too much lead boy.
He's going into the arts and entertainment.
Too many school projects it ruined your brain.
I remember once in school
I was like okay I gotta make Stonehenge
I'm gonna get Styrofoam
I know that's easy to cut up and we'll just
buy a can of spray paint and we went to the
craft store and they're like you can't
if you spray paint Styrofoam
it shrinks. You can't do that.
Oh I remember learning that. Yeah I had
no idea. Did you make
Stonehenge? Yeah just
out of Styrofoam and like paint that
you just dab with a sponge. How did it look?
Um
We did our best.
We did our damnedest. Got it. Understood.
We did it the Sunday before
the Monday it was due.
PTR challenge. All of us make Stonehenge.
Who would make a better Stonehenge?
I'll make Stonehenge.
Maxed in pyramids much easier
to make with Styrofoam.
Did I make? I feel like I
did make some pyramids once and I can't
remember for what project but I
definitely made pyramids.
I think I made planets too. I don't know who of us
would be the best. I don't know that any
of us are particularly handy
good with our hands. The only challenge
really where we all made something
was the Ronto wrap
and I in that
I blew y'all out of the water. Yeah yeah mine was the worst.
The saddest thing I've ever. Sometimes
my phone
my phone that is now full of
photos of my children
sometimes my phone will still decide
memories and it's
a photo of your
weird sad Ronto wrap.
Kids a lot of kids probably
bored of that huh? Memories
weird hot dog today.
There's some stuff that you can't believe
technologically were there and then there's some
stuff where you go this is the dumbest computer
I've ever seen. Like
why is it showing me a hot dog?
Remember hot dog day?
That seemed important to you. I was
listening to you. You were all excited
about it. I saw it like the AI
AI confidently answers questions
wrong so often.
It's so fucking dumb this AI already.
It's so so dumb.
You seem upset Trump back in office
want happy memory from better
Biden days? Look at hot
dog.
I recently
searched Citywalk
Billabong to try to find pictures
and I had been trying out DuckDuckGo
it's my search engine
and the first
cause it's more secure it's more secure
than like Google.
The first result was our
fandom wiki
about the Citywalk Saga
Billabong Sector.
Wow and that was even before
Wave Santa got out there.
Wave Santa has made it
absolute and like
very tight bond between
us and Citywalk Billabong.
He's sweeping the nation
in a lot of ways. Oh that's nice to think about
I'm just imagining him surfing everywhere
surfing on the Pacific Ocean
but then surfing on the Mississippi River.
Right.
Have a fun journey Wave Santa.
One of his legs broke clean off
as I was leaving here.
Makes a lot of sense.
I gotta super glue it back on.
Those were really really skinny legs
those are puny legs to hold up
a whole wave. I pulled it out of the car and it fell
Thanks for aesthetic there's a reason the back was
covered in Velcro squares.
But don't worry he's in the garage he's alright.
He's still partying.
I think we can't move on from the
story of the diorama without
saying that it was closed
for a number of years you could not
access that you could not go in the castle.
That changed
in 2008 but it started in 2001
because of
Oh
see I saw this
I saw this mentioned
but maybe the line
September 11, 2001
in the terrorist attacks
on the United States.
I was reminded
of the correct pronunciation from
Mike's lovely Wave Santa
montage video.
Oh yeah because he took a picture outside.
So next time you need to know
just take a picture look at that video
with Wave Santa.
What is it Jason? Hold on.
It's my version of Memento
I just have Polaroids
mostly Wave Santa.
What do you remember about
your life? There was a cool
wave I think he delivered presents.
That's all I got.
Okay now you
were hesitant to say that the castle
was closed because of 9-11 because
they deny that.
Again like
Tall Tales urban legend like
a former head of Disneyland
was like no
because of 9-11.
They just actually didn't feel like running that anymore.
It wasn't worth the
staffing. It wasn't worth one person
to open the door in the morning.
Yeah so maybe not
because like I don't know once you got
they got security measures.
I don't know what you're going to do in the castle.
Well I guess I don't want to
I don't know the ins and outs of bombs.
I don't know what you could do.
But I don't know you could also blow one up just next
to the castle. I don't think they're stopping
all the threats by not letting you
go inside. Well if they're not going to stop a loogie
what else?
Yeah well that'd be the fear I guess
maybe like what if you're spitting
something explosive. What if
you're like that's gasoline and
then the next person comes along with
like a fire eater. Yeah.
You should drink gasoline and
you hock two with some gasoline
out of your mouth. Chris Angel
would do that I think. She said you got
to hock two of that thing but if
you're a flame thrower or if you're a flame
eater. Yeah. Maybe you don't
got to do that. That's dangerous for everyone.
Did Ricky J ever hock two of some lighter
fluid and turn it on?
There's no way he did it not.
You're saying he did of course. Yeah of course.
Alright they all do it. We call
this hock twoing.
I invented the phrase.
What have we missed
just general
I was going to say I think the
dioramas if I'd seen it as a little kid
I would have been really into it
because it's pretty dark in there. It has
these similar aesthetics
to a haunted house.
But it's Sleeping Beauty. I know I'm not going to get
scared. Yeah that's true
yes. Like you're nervous because it's
narrow corridors and like
you know and it's like there is
like evil laughing in there with
maleficent and stuff but like probably nothing
is going to. Yeah you know what it's a good
It's like a little test out I'd say of
of a maze or something.
Yeah. Yeah. There's an
old I was seeing I don't
there was a creepy picture from the original
version and it says
meet maleficent's demons
and you would see did you see this photo?
No. It's a really like it's a black
and white photo of these two really scary
like kind of the pig guard
guys and
there was an illusion where you would like look through
a keyhole and then your eye would be reflected
back as if they had a real eye
and it looks like this would just scare the shit
out of children. That's scary as hell.
Oh I take it back then I guess.
So I was like oh that was
kind of cool. Damn. You know as we
as we fight against the removal of everything
scary at the park I'm like oh yeah
give me back these pig goons.
Let me see the pig goons with the real eye human eye.
Yeah that's scar you might have dreams about
pig goons for the rest of your
childhood. At least give us a little corner
of scare like be like if you want to take
your kids over to get them scared by the pig goons
it's over here. Yeah. You don't have
to they don't have to if you don't want it
to. Yeah. Yeah. But for like
for like my daughter who seems to like
my daughter want to take a picture with Beetlejuice
at Universal on Wednesday.
Cool. And she turned down all the Simpsons.
She turned down any Simpson
any like Chief Wiggum statue or
Marge or whatever and then we saw Beetlejuice
and she doesn't know what Beetlejuice is but
I go it's Beetlejuice and she's intrigued.
I go you want to take a picture with Beetlejuice? She goes yes.
I go is he scary or funny? She goes funny.
I go okay so we go and we have
a picture and she's like staring right at him smiling.
She like seems to
like scary stuff. That's great. Weird
looking. That's nice. Just remember
to take her to parks too. Well
there's a park at Universal. I've been concerned about. Park at
Universal. I guess yes. There is
she loves it. They're okay well good. All right
if that's what it takes to get her to
I'm concerned about getting this kid into an actual park.
She goes to parks. I'm just explaining that
it's very stressful because of how often
Bossy's seven year old just takes
my child grabs her
around the waist takes her down the slide.
Not the same kids different
kids every time. Different
kids I would say eighty percent of the
time this happens.
Your daughter is very tall though you gotta
teach her some wrestling moves so she
can put those older kids in their place. She's two and a half
I don't know that she's
no self defense yet.
But I assume she'll
hopefully know it soon. But
we ran we kind of ran into a same situation
at the park at Universal
inside the playground equipment at Universal.
Oh my god.
Where she's an older
kid is doing something like climbing
on top of the playground.
She's trying to do it.
Okay. Okay. And then if I go no you
just go in the slider go over here she starts screaming
at me. And she's like
no let me. I'm like that
kid is climbing on top of the tube
not through it. Just go through it it's
fine. And she starts screaming at me cause she's trying
to struggle her way up.
She's very aggressive.
She's very spirited.
So no she still goes
to some real parks. But she also meets
Beetlejuice on a Wednesday afternoon.
That's what you get when you're
my daughter. I can't say that
a regular park gives you that.
You cannot meet Beetlejuice at a park.
And if there's a guy who looks like Beetlejuice
it might be just a guy who spent the night
there. Yeah. Get out of there.
Sleeping Beauty
Castle
is of course the original Disneyland
Castle. But it also got a sequel
when Hong Kong Disneyland
opened. And the idea was
that here for this new
park we will pay homage to the original
park and we will exactly recreate
the original castle.
This was weak sauce.
Boo. I don't buy that for one second.
It seemed like after
we've had the evolution of like the
little castle only works as part of the like
little charming nature of Disneyland. Now
that we've built bigger and better castles
it just I mean I don't know about that. I don't even want to say
better. I really like Sleeping Beauty Castle. But the
like the idea that we're going to go back. It was just
such a I see through. This is no tribute.
You just are looking for a reason to build
a small castle. And then sure enough
years later it's gone. Building
new giant castle. Right. Everybody
happy fun. Well whichever CEO was in charge
I don't know about that choice.
Well I'm sorry to tell you it was
the decaying days of the one
that we like. Yep.
Yeah. I don't believe it. I
I'm sorry. I refuse to believe it. I mean maybe they
you know maybe it was like Trump blaming
things on Biden kind of thing. Yeah.
Maybe they threw him under the bus.
It was that. Hong Kong also
surrounded by beautiful lush
green mountains. Mountains behind
the castle. And stuff so.
I want to know what it looks like in person because they
added stuff to it to make it bigger.
But I feel like maybe it looks odd
in person. Because Tony Baxter
was talking about doing that to Sleeping
Beauty's castle. They were thinking about
like what can we do. Could we make
it bigger. And they were just running
into problems with the force perspective
and just how it would look versus
Matterhorn and how it would look through. So
they considered it and they just determined that
like if we make it bigger it's going to throw
everything off I think. So they
decided against it which is probably the right
call. They talked about really. Yeah.
I wonder in what. I mean I don't know how
close they ever got. But that was just they threw that out.
Like man we could make it bigger maybe.
What would it look like. And they thought
it was a bad idea. Well this maybe
naturally brings me to something that
I've had this proposition and maybe
we'll find this to be fruitful or
we'll let it go. But something that I thought
we could do as we pay homage to
original days of Disneyland. We could also
pay homage to original days of
Podcast the Ride. Maybe do
something that we haven't done that we completely
lost years ago. Which is
bringing back the original
rating mechanism which is
I don't remember the right order but
plus it up. Keep it as is. Burn it down
for the insurance money. I think that the
class of 55 could get run through
this perspective. Because
in 70 years there's certainly a lot
of ways that you could plus things up. But also
is it more classic to keep it as is.
And also we've already talked about a lot of
you know vandalism
and terrorism happening to the castle.
Do we just go all the way and burn it down for the
insurance money? It's a good question.
Now I've read
and I don't know if this is true but I've read
that a big part of the
the castle is 77
feet tall I believe right? Did you read
that? That's right.
Which is very small when you think about what it might be.
It's not even in the top 10
structures size wise at the
Disneyland Resort. Relatively short compared
to everything else. But I think a big part of
it is that the Matterhorn would look really
weird if
you built a bigger castle.
The Matterhorn now with the perspective looks like
it's a mountain in the distance a little bit. But I
think the
building this I don't know what the actual numbers are but
you had 30 feet and then it's
the same size as the Matterhorn which feels
weird. So
if they were
like we're going to do the same exact design
but bigger but we're also demolishing
the Matterhorn and building
a bigger Matterhorn or one that's
looks in a different like I don't know if you can
make the perspective different. Then I could
possibly be interested
in burning down
Sleeping Beauty's Castle for
insurance money. It's both. This is
a pact. Both have to go.
That's what I'm saying. But come back.
Yes. And I would argue that
if you're going to build it bigger at the very least
it should look almost give the
exact same vibe as the
current one. Just make it bigger and like
make it have more. You'd still have a walk
through it I bet. Unless you want to
have a ride if it's big enough which I don't think it could be.
But I could be
convinced to burn it down
but I think you have to rebuild the
Matterhorn as well. Interesting.
But now are you
how would you feel about it's just bigger
Matterhorn and not
because I also
like the idea of the Matterhorn being way
taller. So you're saying Sleeping Beauty stays the same
and Matterhorn gets double the size?
Double Matterhorn. I'm in for that.
And again that's another really
really steep dips in there but smooth.
Well again that's a rumor
we've read is that that thing's going to have
to be torn down in the next couple decades because
it's falling apart. Yeah I was going to say
structurally it's amazing it's still standing at
all. So maybe you
have to double it in size if you're going
to redo it. I mean I think you want to compete
with today's rides. Yeah. Yeah.
Or who knows what will become
of it. It would end up being so
skinny that I think it would
just feel like this big odd
lump if you because it couldn't get much wider.
Yeah. You're right. Right.
So just like it's a it's like a big
thick pole basically
like heading up into the sky. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I kind of like it.
It could be weird. Big thick pole.
Big thick pole. And let
Josh Mayhem do it. Make it all rainbow
drippy. Yeah and you can you can
watch the big pole. There's a show
that happens but you can watch from the roof of Arthur and
Sons from downtown Disney.
Your big cigar.
Your stogie and your verve.
You get injected with tea.
You get injected testosterone
at the table too. If somebody comes around
sir will you laugh. So laugh
with all the spittle laugh
at everyone around you.
But I
yeah I I'm
I'm not so this is really
I feel like I've almost evolved in some of my
thinking. I don't want the rivers of America
to go away in Florida. I think
that's probably a bad
idea. I don't know why it had to come to that.
It doesn't seem right to do
that. I mean I understand it's
expensive to keep up the swamp
land with the water. Like that's probably part of
the part of the decision. But you could spend
a lot of money and fix it I think. I don't think
it's impossible. Yeah. But
I am not so
precious that I wouldn't
I couldn't be convinced of
demolishing some landmarks
and making cool version
cooler new versions of them. Okay.
I think. Okay. But it depends.
It depends what the new one would look like.
And it depends on the philosophy.
Any thoughts Jason about
the old ranking system.
Yeah I think this one
I'm going to go with keep the same.
I think it is charming. I think it
suits Disneyland
well.
I don't know that the newer
iterations of the company I would
trust. I got to
look at that Hong Kong castle again because
I have looked at it before and the concept
art looked very cool
of like little pieces of different
castles or different characters
homes.
And the execution and
taking something from two dimensional
drawings to three dimensional
space. That's what I'm wondering.
It just looks like a hodgepodge. That's what I'm wondering
if it looks weird in person. Yeah.
I guess there's something silly seeming
about it. Yeah I'd be curious.
I wouldn't mind and they kind of did
it's not connected in Disney World when they did
the Fantasyland expansion.
I wouldn't mind if they like made the castle
like wider. Like I wouldn't
mind if like because right now it kind of
blends into like the little
what's the where
the dancing takes place. Fantasy Fair.
Fantasy Fair. Thank you with Figaro and everything.
But I wouldn't mind if they even
like did something
that would like I don't know make
it take up more space but doesn't have to
go vertical. Maybe there's no room for
that but expanding
the like spires and more. Yeah like
I don't know. I guess you'd have to
get rid of dark rides probably.
More impenetrable. Yeah. More to fight spitters.
Yeah. I think
my I think I would do the most
subtle plus it up which is
give me room to have a drink
up there. Well I want to go to the top.
I don't like
and I you know I mean another person would be
nice. I guess I'd like to share this with Aaron
but you can only fit one
you know. Maybe it's a good place to go get some reflecting
done. I want a glass of champagne
on top of the
imagine the feeling of like you're
all it's like just
just having the tip of the
castle to yourself. So it's a
bar for one person? Yeah.
Okay. Yep. Yeah. Okay.
And it's just like I want anyone carping my
style. Even my
best friend.
Is there a bartender up there too?
No.
No you get the they give you the drink and then
like all right she's all yours and then you walk
up a little spiral staircase. Okay.
Then you just sit and think.
Just think about your life. Think like
my god it all goes by so fast.
Once I was just a kid here and now I'm at
cape age.
But they
they play a kids bop
version of closing time when you have to
leave. Kids bop
version. You don't have
to go home but you can't stay here.
Okay. And technically that
you know that's not
doesn't have to be about a bar. Like they don't have to
kids bopify it. You know that could be about a
cheeky cheese closing. It's a very good point.
Yeah.
You don't have to go home.
It's creepy.
I want to be there so bad. Just the solo.
I'm not even a champagne person
really but like what else would you drink up there?
Bourbon. Bourbon.
Alright.
I think you survived.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Did you see
that before the walk through was open?
Did you see this? What the castle
was full of?
Not Nazi plunder. Not Nazi plunder.
Cats and fleas.
I saw multiple
fleas full of fleas. There was one
door you could open. Ah! Visible
fleas. Tens of thousands
of them. Multiple people online have
said that it was full of fleas
because of the cats. So Walt went
in there to look and he got like fleas
on him.
So they were like oh shit. He opened a door
and they all vocalized
ah! Yeah.
Jumped right into his mustache.
We can thrive
in here. Yeah. Sleeping Beauty's
Castle was full of fleas
before it had the walk through.
So if we're really
being traditionalists here, if we're really going
class of 55, they should
honor that tradition. They should bring the
fleas back. Bring the fleas back.
It's a wedding day fleas.
Another castle kind of
annex. The Castle
Heraldry Shop. Did you guys
ever pop in there? Oh I've been
yeah. Where you could get family crests.
You could get like a shield right?
Yeah you could get a shield or an expensive
sword. And that's not
there anymore. It's I
I'm seeing it left in 2017.
But I
I wandered in there once years after first going
to Disneyland and went you can buy a fucking
piece of armor but it felt like that in there. Yeah.
Wow. It was like why is this
and then like of course shortly after I discovered
it was there. It was gone
because they were like no one's buying. Wow.
Very expensive. No one's ever in the year.
Wow. So if you
wanted protection while you
stormed a toxically
masculine bourbon and
steak place. Downtown Disney yeah. If you went in
charged in with a sword
and needed some help blocking the
security guards. That's where you
would have gone. Trying to cut it up.
You would have gone there.
Jason carving J into everything
like Zorro.
Did you buy it? I reclaimed this place
for innocence.
Tortilla in the honor of
Tortilla Joe. T.J.
I will avenge you Tortilla. T.J.
What for Trader Joe's?
No. No. Tortilla Joe's.
Make you proud sir.
Tortilla Jason is here.
We never put that together. Yeah.
Alright well I think that
does it. I think you survived Podcast
The Ride from all of us here. From Scott
Mike and Tortilla Jason.
More Class of 55 coming
for three bonus episodes every month. Check out
Podcast The Ride The Second Gate. Get one more
bonus episode on our VIP tier club
three. You will find all of that at Patreon.com
.com slash Podcast The Ride.
Yeah as I said what do you want from
Class of 55? Weird old Disneyland
stuff. Do you want
Tales of Walt in the War?
Do you want a full
reading of something that I
when I looked up people who
met Walt Disney in the War
it led to the always reliable
Quora results.
People looking for an answer to the question
did Hitler and Walt Disney
ever meet? Oh God.
And the answer is no.
Wink wink.
I could not
I could not find
anything because Walt gave
Lenny Riefenstahl a
tour of like Walt Disney Studios.
I did not see any
stories of her going to Disneyland and
going like oh it's like a tiny
new swatch castle.
We can only imagine
an excellent Lenny impression.
Forever
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog
production. Executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett
Bohm, Joe Silio, and
Alex Ramsey. For more
original podcasts please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever
Dog news by following us on
Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking
our page on Facebook.