Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate, where the episode you're hearing today is
actually a re-recording of this episode that it was initially recorded years ago. I'm Jason
Sherrod and joined as always by Mike Carlson. Yes, I'm here and this is a re-recording. If
you're lost already, wait a second. It's a little tease. No, I know. I'm just saying. Scott Gehringer
also here. Yeah, well I was just excited because you offered to do the joke and you said, got it,
I'm going to improvise it based on one of the six facts about what we're talking about. Sorry,
just do the behind the scenes of it. It got me excited. It got me amped up and then we got
there and it was that. Yeah, you did skillfully repurpose one of the things that there is to talk
about. There's less facts about this potentially than there are characters in it. That's true,
yeah. Potentially, but also there was more than I thought there would be. There was a lot
and this is how waterfalls work. Did you learn how waterfalls work? Well, technically. Gravity?
Kind of. Force perspective business. Did you learn about the history of wishing wells like I did? I
looked up wishing wells. Oh no, but I'm thrilled to learn about this. Were we supposed to go that far?
Oh shoot, I should have gone further. I should have learned about the history of wishing. Well,
that would have been good. That would be one step deeper, I guess. Who was the first to wish?
It was Walt Disney. Walt Disney was the first to wish. He owns the trademark on it. That's why
he got everything that he got. That's how it all came together. It was the power of wishes. Exactly.
And he taught us all and ultimately for Disney 100, the story of wish reminded us that Disney
is synonymous with wish and it reminded us how powerful a wish can be. What are the names of
wish? It was like, cause there was that, remember when we were all in Disney world and the wish
characters were starting to pop up and there was one, I feel like Griffin especially was like,
look, it's like Kroll from, it's not that. It wasn't Kroll, but you know what I mean? It was
some sound. Yeah. What was the character? What kind of a character was it? Trow. Look,
it's Trow. That's not the star. I don't know. I don't know. My mom bought my daughter a wish,
a little kid's wish table. She goes, I don't know what this is, but the table was on sale.
So now my daughter sits at a little wish table and a little chair. Okay. Am I thinking of Asha?
Look, I cannot tell you who you were thinking. There is not a character named Trow. I cannot
help you. There's no Kroll. Asha, I think it's the main character. Are you thinking of Krod
Mandoon? Mandoon, what is his name? Well, I typically am the fellow member of the Comedy
Central family. Yeah, Krod Mandoon. Krod Mandoon. I believe is a fantasy barbarian similar to Conan.
We've never, I don't think we've ever vocalized that Chris Pine plays King Magnifico. We've never
said the words Chris Pine is King Magnifico. That's true. That sentence has never been uttered. Yeah.
Sorry so late on that. Everybody was wondering. King Magnifico. I like that name. I kind of,
yeah, there's other, well, I think we would, if we found out King Magnifico was original
IP and epic universe, we would be all about King Magnifico. Well, that's true. That's a good point.
Same name. You just put it there. It's a character you can only meet. Yes. In this park. Right. For
like 10 months or so until they reevaluate. Are we doing the characters? My contract's only nine
months, so I'm a quick King Magnifico. Quick in and out. Are you doing it? Did they get you? We're
still negotiating. Fingers crossed. It's nearly a done deal. They gotta see that thing. Hey,
just to give an update, Go.com is still encouraging you to check out Wish and 2023's Haunted Mansion.
Really? Yeah. That's on the main page? Yeah, on basic HTML, in basic HTML on the main page.
Oh, that's right. When we looked up Go.com, yeah, they were locked in time. It's just a big text
page about the new things that Disney has, like Toy Story land. Wow, yeah, that's exciting. Also,
what's Dashing Through the Snow on Disney Plus? Eddie Garrick and his daughter are taken on a
magical adventure after meeting a mysterious man in a red suit named Nick. No, Nick. Nick in a red
suit. Say no more. That might just restore his faith in Christmas. This is not Tim El. There's
no Tim Allen in this. No, this has, who am I looking at? Ludacris. Whoa. This is a Disney
even better. Plus original film starring Ludacris that none of us have heard of until right now.
Wow. I like that. I mean, I like that. Ludacris is Eddie Garrick. Oh, he is. He's turned his back
on Christmas. Come on. Boy. Who's Santa? Do we know? Lil Rel. Oh, wow, okay. I like Lil Rel.
I mean, I can't tell if he's Santa or just in a Santa suit. Wait, no, is Lil Ray?
Lil Rel. Lil Rel. Are you thinking of some old time singer, Lil Ray?
I'm thinking of another pop that we didn't get. Lil Ray in the flash tones.
Also, they didn't put it up yet on Go.com, but I saw online this morning that Tim Allen did confirm
that his character in Shifting Gears is conservative on taxes. While I was setting up,
I texted that to Anthony Geo that Tim Allen's character on Shifting Gears believes that too
many taxes hurt small businesses and they're just trying to survive. Who just want to take care of
their employees, of course. But that was in a Hollywood Reporter article. We need to get to
the topic, but there's so much Shifting Gears lately. What is it with you guys? Oh, the two of
us? There's so much network television being discussed arbitrarily every week. That's true.
Jason knows. Where does Shifting Gears come from? We're back. We're so back. We're locked in.
On what? We've not fallen off network television. Oh, bad. Oh. We're locked in. I've just heard a
lot of behind the scenes leading up to the debut of Shifting Gears, and I feel invested in it in
some way. I've never seen the show other than clips and following the social media. Spoiler
alert, Tim's character, Matt, I think is having a romance with Jenna Elfman. So I'm following the
show on Instagram. All right. You know what? I had my doubts, but after that, I can't help but say,
we are so back. We are so back. Tim plus Dharma? Yeah. The Dharma Initiative? Sixth Come Royalty
together. Go.com is not telling us Checkout Shifting Gears. I'm wondering if whoever was
updating it was caught in one of the mini rounds of Disney layoffs. Well, maybe, perhaps. I don't
know if we'll be able to tell. And on his way, he was being dragged out the door by security and
yelling, but if you fire me, what will happen to the page updates on Go.com? People heard that
thought for a sec. I think we're fine on that one. There'll be hopefully seven to nine seasons of
Shifting Gears to dig into eventually on this show. So we'll have time, I think. As many as there are
dwarfs. Good. I did it. Now we're back. There you go. Hey, we're back. I'm going to be fending off
Shifting Gears tangents, I feel like, every 10 minutes, every episode until you guys work this
out of your system. You'll have a little summer break. As if that's going to stop it. But there'll
not be as much Shifting Gears information for me to consume during the summer, I think, unless they
announce a new cast. I mean, I'll say that if I could go out for Shifting Gears next fall to join
this show, then that's a whole... I could beg for Shifting Gears. Now that you're saying it, I was
ready to take the talk off the table, but now maybe I should campaign to be on Shifting Gears all
summer. Maybe if I make a big show of it. I think they're going to send something fishy in your
voice. They're like, this guy's up to something. Please. I don't know that he likes this show in a
pure of heart way. I do. I'm conservative on Tim Allen on TV. You could play Kat Denning's hinge
date one episode. Sure, I'll do the hinge date. She explains to Tim Allen the apps and he's like,
hinge, bumble, what is this, a bumblebee stuck in a screen door? And we're going to be pitching
for Jason to be a writer on next season. That's what we're going to do all summer. So thank you,
Scott, for giving us an agenda. We're doing it. We have our mission. We got to get Jason on Dr.
Odyssey and a writer on Shifting Gears. So without further ado. Fun fact about Shifting Gears,
all of the actors are the same size, so they got to stagger them for the camera. And we're back
again, Scott. With a great non-tortured joke, the cleanest. Again, you've proven your capacity
for writing for Shifting Gears. Shifting Gears. The tidiness of a good force perspective tie-in.
Opening jokes of the show. Pokéball. What about Pokéball? Tim's probably going to raise his
eyebrow at a Pokéball, don't you think? Hey, this fish isn't cooked. Yep. What is that voice?
What did you do that again? This fish isn't cooked. What is, what voice is that? That's Tim Allen
being cranky. That's Tim Allen? I don't know what. This fish isn't cooked. What? That's not it.
He was a little bit of a goon from a vague Eastern European country. Yeah, I thought it was a little
Eastern European. Wait, you do an impression of what Jason said. This fish isn't cooked. Yeah,
it's like an old guy. It had a weird like mumble to it. So you saw it more as like an old Manchester
by the Sea kind of guy. I read a little euro into it. Well, Scott, that's called giving up
before you finish saying the joke. You know. That's called abandoning it because you're like,
oh no, this is really, this is not really good. He should have said aroo. That's what he should
have said when he saw Pokéball. Look, in the room, we know we got a few hard rules about writing for
Shifting Gears and it's like, we don't do the aroo unless Tim pitches it. You know, he doesn't want
to get bogged down. He's allowed, we're not allowed. Hannah, that is not a joke, I'm sure.
That has to be real. Yeah. All right. The more I say, the more in four months, there's a
Frank and Jason get to do the Shifting Gears thing they've wanted to do. Club 3 punishment.
I know how these things go. A legend is born. But for now, let's talk about an actual theme park.
Yes. Snow White Grotto. Yes. I don't like that tone either. Why? Yes. Snow White Grotto. Yeah.
I will say sincerely, I love this area. I think it's one of the most chill places at Disneyland
and it's very charming. Well, it's a very stop and smell the roses kind of place. That's an indicator
of a non-rushed, chill, looking at details kind of day. If you stop and take a minute
over in Snow White Grotto. Basics, basics here. You're looking at the castle. You're about to
walk through the castle into Fantasyland and you say, no, maybe not. Because something catches your
eye over off to the right. There's a little lush area with some greenery and a waterfall
and some statues. And you go off that way into a little alcove sort of near the castle where
there is this very pleasant little display of Snow White and the Seven Dwarves and some animals
all rendered via, I mean, initially marble, but I think that changed at some point. But it's just
this nice little relaxing courtyard that pays homage to Snow White outside of Sleeping Beauty
Castle. So if you can get your head around the properties being mashed up, if that doesn't bother
you, then you can have yourself a moment of peace. Look at some nice old statues. It doesn't bother
me. I'll say that. That's fine. Does it bother you, the mashup? No, because I often have to do
Sleeping Beauty Castle, Cinderella Castle, Snow White Wishing. I forget who is- Who owns which
castle? Who owns which item. This is something we didn't talk about and we sort of recently did
an episode about Sleeping Beauty Castle on the main feed. That was something I wanted to bring
up in Sleeping Beauty Castle is, do you guys have trouble remembering which princess belongs
to which castle, which it seems like maybe you do? Or alternatively, do you get mad if others
get them confused? No and yes. You do. You don't get them confused and you do get mad when there's
confusion? Yes. So I'm mad at you. Because I'm sure, and I'm sure listen. I was going to say yes and
no. More normal options. We've got to get you guys back to shifting gears so you can be getting along
again. We're not on the same page anymore. We were and now we're not. Because even
we were prepping for Sleeping Beauty Castle and I brought up to Erin that we were doing that and
Erin said, which one's that? And she's pretty versed. She goes to the push. She's a parks person.
She listens to us blab on most of these episodes, unless it's about puppets, which I affirm she was
not listening to. Was that the one where you asked if you wanted to go to Backstreet Boys though?
Yes. So she didn't hear it. Oh, wow. Yes. She would not have heard.
She went more of like an in-person lecture. Like we can pop over while we're all in Burbank now.
We could bring a puppet over. Is that what you're saying? Yeah. I think that would help her get her
head around. Yeah. Yeah. No. If she looks in the keyhole of the house at some point and there's
just, there's a big puppet of Alf staring down, I think she'll welcome that into the house.
Mike has all the scary pictures. I got him for Christmas and his birthday.
What scary pictures? The Paul Winchell picture. He got me a Choco the Clown picture. These are on
episodes you were not on. He gifted me things at the end of the episode. So this is a real test.
He wasn't trying to test you, but he did both of these at the end of episodes. So I was gifted a
Paul Winchell picture with his two dummy friends on the photo. And then I was given a Choco the
Clown picture as well, including a book about a Choco the Clown that was not the Choco the Clown
we talk about. A different Ringling Brothers Choco the Clown. It seems like I really missed out.
Yeah. So, but Jason ordered it before he looked into what the book was.
Believe it or not, that name's not so unique. I just got too excited when I saw the book.
But I do feel like everybody messes up the princess. I don't think that's, I think that's
a common, very common. Yes. Yeah. But I feel like if you scoured the archives of the show,
I bet you would hear a moment of one or all of us that somebody is talking about just this,
the magic of being at Disneyland and looking at Cinderella Castle and then, then all our,
most of us go, it's like Beauty Castle. It's something we can't help ourselves from, but do.
It's a positive, it's a very positive facet of us, I think. Yeah. No, it's.
Who doesn't like being quickly corrected under their breath.
Right. About something that doesn't matter. About a pretty arbitrary.
Yeah. But whatever, it doesn't matter really.
It's a struggle doing the show sometimes. Some of the confusion I think comes from the fact
that does either castle really feel like either princess? You know what I mean?
Because if you watch the movie Sleeping Beauty, it's not really her castle.
It's a much bigger castle in the movie. It's a much bigger castle.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then, you know, Cinderella Castle, that's not her castle till the end.
Right. You know, that's not what it's called when the events of the film start.
You have to go be inside to see that there's dioramas of these and murals of Cinderella.
Right. Yes. So I, yes, it's not like she's always waving to you or something. It's not like it's,
it doesn't, there's not a big sign outside both castles that say which princess belongs to which
one. Yeah. Yeah.
But I get that. Have we like talked much on the show about,
I'm sure we have, because we've talked about Christmas parades over the years,
but when you talk about Cinderella waving, just what I immediately fleshed to is the,
there was a runner on all of the Regis hosted parades where there'd be a shot of her waving
from her coach. And then Regis would say, there's Cinderella. Where's my kiss? Cinderella,
give me my kiss. I want it. Give me the kiss. There we go. There's the, and he wasn't in it.
So there was not some forced like physical contact that was not asked for or desired from
Cindy. You know, it was just a blow of a kiss. But he never said like, Joy said it was okay.
I asked Joy. Get a hall pass. That's a phrase I Regis invented. Who's allowed to kiss you outside
your marriage? Yeah. I don't, I think that was just, that was sort of thought of as cute.
Oh yeah. I thought, no, I, I looked for it when those were happening real time every year,
that was like one of the moments that I would look forward to was Regis demanding his Cinderella
kiss. And then at some point, whenever they replaced the hosts, they like tried to like
hippify it or something by going with like younger TJF stars. And I'm like, you mean I
don't get to see Regis asked for a Cinderella kiss this year? Maybe I turned this program off.
I mean, they could have made up a little skit with Regis. Does he ever, did he ever get a kiss from
Cinderella? I mean, I don't know about physically. He got, he wanted, he wanted a, like a blown kiss.
He wanted a what kiss? He wanted a blown kiss. Like yes. Yeah. Yeah. Like through the, through
the camera, through the magic television, he had to be in the booth. I guess that's okay.
It's completely okay. Well, that's, that's a question. How do we all feel? Do we feel like
being blown a kiss is allowed? By a princess though? What if it's a princess? I don't know.
Well, I think you have to ask the question blanket. Is it cheating if someone blows a kiss at a married
man? Okay. Hold on. Hold on though. And all what, if all of our wives might be listening,
this is a real test. They're there. They need to hear the right answer or all the marriages are
over. I think if you request the kiss loudly on television, it's, it's, it gets in that territory
of cheating. Well, I think a couple of things. I think it's cheating if you grab the kiss.
Oh, and put it on your mouth? Yeah. You grab it. A kiss is blown and then you pantomime, taking it,
rubbing it all over your mouth. Yeah. That's pretty aggressive. That's definitely upsetting.
You've never seen someone like grab a kiss? I don't think I have seen a grabbed kiss before.
It's a cute little like, and then you just kind of. Wish we were on video for that. That makes me think,
you know what would be really upsetting is somebody being blown a kiss and then somebody
else gets in the way and grabs it for themselves, runs away with it, puts it in their pocket for later.
Oh yeah. A stolen air kiss. Yeah. I mean, that's, that, that's a prisonable offense, I believe.
You could reaffirm your commitment to your wife by grabbing it out of the air and throwing it on
the ground and stomping it. Oh yes. That's what you should do. Putting it physically in a trash can.
That works too, yeah. Or pantomiming like a shredder and. Right, yes. Or that might be tough
to sell. You have to say out loud, this is a paper shredder. Make the noise, shred that kiss up.
Like a Michael Winslow. I don't want it. Even just an aggressive like dodge, like a spin move.
If you got a hood, you put the hood up and blah, like no. No. That's the honorable thing to do.
I am married. You are a home wrecker, Cinderella. No kiss for me. Yeah. So I think that's, I think
we settled that. Great. All right. So any of our wives who are listening, just know we will never
accept that air kiss from anyone. No. That is how committed we are to you, our princesses.
Unless on my instance, it's from Joy Philbin. Your hall pass. My hall pass.
Joy's with us still, right? I believe. Is she? I think so. Joy Philbin is alive. I believe Joy
is still alive, yeah. Regis has passed away a few years ago. Joy's still alive, yeah. Well,
so it could happen. What is the place we can get you? Well, this will be a test of the marriage,
I guess, if you were somewhere where Joy Philbin was. If she was even the grand marshal of a
parade, which seems like the kind of thing Joy Philbin might do. I think so. I think so. Well,
be on the lookout. Is there a joyphilbin.com announcing her upcoming personal appearances?
No, I don't know. Jason, look into that. If she had an Instagram account, you would be following
it. That is true. If she had an Instagram account, you would have already tried to squeeze an episode
out of it. That's true, but you would have been following it because you would have probably
posted Regis stuff, classic Regis stuff. I don't know if it's enough. I don't think I need
day-to-day Regis in my feed. Really? Not really, no. Is there a day-to-day Regis Instagram that
I can follow? This is going to be the first episode where we don't come back to the topic.
It's possible. I think we said what we had to say. There's other interesting stuff. Jason hasn't
gotten it. We need to turn to Jason to tell us how waterfalls work. Why don't you explain how
waterfalls work while Mike and I completely check out and just look up, are there Regis fan accounts
on Instagram? Regis fan cam? You guys do that. Okay, so there's some conflicting stuff about
the creation of this grotto. There are some websites who say their eight boxes just showed
up at the Disney lot one day anonymously, and they had these statues inside. Yes, they arrived
in wooden crates from Italy with no return address and no indication of who might have made and sent
them. This is per John Hench, Imagineer, so that's a trustworthy source. I ask this though
right away, if there was no return address, how do you know it's Italy? Good point. Did it smell
of pizza pie? That must be what it was. Sauce. I read a couple places, but then there's a D23
article about it, and they credit an Italian sculpture named Leonida Parma. Sculptor.
Sculptor. Yeah. Yeah. And he... There's that little correction. Yeah. Well, I got confused
because I thought he was influenced by a sculpture. You thought a sculpture made them. Yeah. Yeah,
a living sculpture was the artist of sculptures. So they're saying that it was commissioned,
but the thing, the anecdote that keeps getting repeated is the problem was the dwarves in Snow
White were the same size, and maybe the Italian sculptor never saw it, but he had a gift box of
soaps where they were all the same size. Yes, I saw this anecdote as well, that he... And in very
much Mike and Jason fashion with the TV shows you're obsessed with, that the Italian sculptor had
not ever seen the movie Snow White and the Seven Dwarves. Go ahead, yeah. So he was going based not
on the film, but on soaps that he had. He was tributing, I saw these little soaps. I love the
little soaps. I say I make you big soaps, but the big soaps would melt in the mail. So I made them
out of marble, but I made them as white as soap. Right. I mean, that's cool. Soap white, I call her.
This is a very strange story. A man was a fan of soap, so he made eight statues and sent them to
Disney. Yeah. What is this tale? I guess it's so specific, maybe I believe it. Yeah, I don't know
what's real and what's story, like what's K-Fame, what's Disney myth-making. But it's not even that
fun to be completely made up. Right. It's stranger than you would be like, if it was just like,
oh my gosh, these immaculate dwarves showed up. We never knew where they came from or whatever.
And seven squirrels dragged them in little tiny boxes adorned with, it's like just a guy like-
And some deer with their mouths took the crate apart. That's really Snow White.
That's nail by nail. They acted as- Right. But I guess it's true. I mean, I guess-
They unscrewed the screws with their little deer teeth.
Right. I guess it's true. I mean, I guess. I guess it's so strange. It must be true.
Well, here's what I'm finding now is that something that you can buy
for $180 on eBay is a soap set for Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs from 1938. This is a-
Look at the miscoloration of this old-ass soap. Wow.
Yeah, like very yellow and red. This is very strange. I guess in very Snow White fashion,
like what happens to her in the movie, they're all in little coffins.
Oh my gosh. They're all in little,
it's like coffins of stuffing. Anyway, this is, yeah, this is old soap that you can buy,
modeled in castile soap, painted with harmless vegetable color. And it's signed by Lightfoot
Schultzko, so makers of fine soaps for over 27 years. So this is a weird old product that
you can buy. Anybody who wants this, you can buy some old soaps that look like $180.
Jason, would you wash with that soap if I got it for you?
Soap from 1938. I'm assuming it's mostly
arsenic, so I don't know. No, they said harmless vegetable oil.
They said it's fine. They said, I believe these guys.
I think that company turned into Old Spice. That's what I'm looking here.
Is that true? I think.
Oh, interesting. I was going to joke,
like what was the original company name, Scott? Lightfoot Schultz.
Lightfoot Schultz episode comments. William Lightfoot Schultz was the
early American Old Spice. Now it sounds interesting
if it evolved into Old Spice. Yes, and we're going to, you're going to
wash with each seven dwarf in the bath, each soap, and you're going to see how.
And then we smell him every time. That's right.
He shows up for a record and we try to guess which one, I'm like,
feels like Sneezy to me. That's right.
We'll guess. We'll see if we're right.
And then also just determine which smells the best.
So, you know, seven dwarfs in Snow White, so that's eight.
So it's eight whiffs adjacent that we, that each of us take,
and then we determine which was the most effective snow dwarf.
It's going to be a very exciting summer between that and the shifting gear stuff.
That's all I know. Well, because he mints,
an episode you catch the repeat. Yeah.
I know it's on Hulu, but it's not as fun because you don't see the brands and the ads.
They might've changed the ads, the brands. They probably changed the brands.
Podcast The Ride is coming to life for summer 2025.
We're talking soaps from the thirties. We're talking current sitcoms that anyone could
just watch now. That's right.
We're talking about the new tide with Oxy.
How many people are sending weird like soaps to Disney these days?
I bet they're, I bet they get weird stuff. I bet people send Disney.
I don't know if anyone's sending them the soaps.
I'm not these. So I'm just saying new soaps.
There must be a soap maker somewhere in the world who's a fan of Disney and is like,
I'm going to make soaps for Disney and I'm going to send them to them.
But that's not what happened here. This was a licensed Disney product that was soaps.
They weren't sent the soaps, but I guess the question remains,
is anyone out there such a big Disney fan that they're sending Disney character soaps?
It's such a big company. They have to get one big weird thing a day in the mail.
One of them has to be soap. That's just a guess. Maybe I'm wrong.
But in the last year, did Disney get a novelty soap in their general mail box?
They probably get, and I don't know how often, because again,
they're a massive company. I bet they get stuff from kids. I bet they get people sending things
to characters. Imagine all the mail that's meant for Santa Claus, but imagine that with
1,000 characters who kids want to write to. Like Captain Magnifico or whatever his name was.
So many people are writing to Captain Magnifico. Was it King Magnifico? I forgot already.
I'd prefer to not know. I'd prefer for this to be a game of telephone,
and that we decide now that he's Captain Magnifico.
Right. How often are you going to hang out at Disneyland by this well?
This is probably a once every five years kind of situation.
Every five years. I think it's more frequent for me, but not frequently.
I feel like it's one of the places I'll go chill out in the same way I'll go by
the Grizzly River Rapids area. So many different little trails and paths there.
This is obviously the wishing well. The grotto isn't as big, but it's in the same way where
you're like, it's usually a low traffic area. It is. It's interesting that there is something
that's so easy to miss potentially next to one of the most famous landmarks in the world.
Right, yes. I don't know what it is about it. Interestingly landscaped or set up,
that somehow it can feel tucked away despite being feet away. People are taking the most pictures
ever. It's unclear if you can get from those little side entrances to Fantasyland too.
Everything is a little bit mysterious back there. I think I forgot that you could
enter that way. You can enter Fantasyland. It is a side entrance.
Right. All that is a little obscure. Again, this is good. This is the magic.
That would be my argument. This is the magic. If you go to the left side of the castle,
you'll end up in Frontierland. You'll end up in a Mexican restaurant in Frontierland.
Well, if you go by Fantasy Fair. Yeah, Fantasy Fair.
Though there is a left entrance to Fantasyland too.
Yes, yes. There's two little
entrances to places that aren't so advertised. This one, it's all mentioned. The Snow White
Grotto is not really on maps. It's just a stumble upon.
You've got to know where to go. You've got to know where to go.
You can see it from a distance and it is interesting, but it is pleasant landscaping
and a wishing well in the waterfall. All of that was said. This is the environment
for these statues. Whatever the story actually is, whether it was just a soap enthusiast who
took it to the next level or whether Disney did actually commission these or if they were just
sent mysteriously, a further step of the John Hench situation was that Walt said,
these are great. We should put them in the park. And John Hench said, I'm worried about these
because if you look at them, they're very nice, but they're also all white. If you aren't careful
with how you present them, quote John Hench, it could look like a graveyard. It could look
like the place where we buried the dwarves. It's something that John Hench said to Walt Disney,
who apparently said to him, that's not my problem. Get that out of your head, John.
You need to think of a nice way to put these in the park. So there was a little fight.
These showed up. It was a bunch of junk. Not John, I guess they're beautiful.
They were marble originally.
Yes. Yeah. All right. I shouldn't say that eight marble statues were junk,
but it was Walt going, you figure this out. John said, I don't know. Don't these look like
headstones to you? No, you grim asshole. Figure out something nice. And thus they figured out
a waterfall and carving out a little extra nature. And then yes, as you referred to,
this issue of Snow White was built to be the same size as the dwarves.
So it's forced perspective techniques. The dwarves are at the bottom of the waterfall.
Snow White is at the top of the waterfall and she's got a small deer next to her.
So they look further away. The thing about the waterfall is that waterfalls usually in nature
are wider at the top. And then they, like a funnel kind of, you know, get narrower at the bottom.
They did the reverse where it's narrower at the top and then it gets wider at the bottom.
So your eye is seeing. Like all the forced perspective architecture that we end up talking
about where they start building roof tiles smaller and it like creates kind of a slant.
Yeah. Interesting. And the other Walt story was he's like, John, I really like this, but you know
with this waterfall, with this pond, like people are going to be throwing change in there. You know
people are going to do that. And then they settled on like, well, let's put a wishing well next to
it where people can throw change. And the change to direct people's like, oh, I don't want to throw
it in this thing. I'll throw it in this thing. And you get a wish then. And you get a wish.
You get a wish out of it. An official Disney wish. Thoughts on wishing wells, pro or pros or cons.
I haven't made a wish in a well in a long time, but I did when I was little.
Isn't that what happens? You have kids start forgetting to put wishes into wells.
Yeah. So I haven't done it in a long time.
I must have the most childlike wonder because if I see a wishing well, I am making a beeline for it.
To make a wish.
Yeah. And I'm looking for change. If I don't have change, I'm like, it's people I'm with.
You throw a credit card in there.
Yeah. I'll just throw up. Chase freedom's got too confusing.
Yeah. You can get a replacement pretty quickly.
And if you don't have one of those nearby, then you reach inside, scoops up some of the change
that's already in there and throw that back in. Or maybe pocket it for yourself.
That's okay. Well, there is a grate. So supposedly the grate is in the wishing well
to prevent mischievous children from hopping in and scooping change.
Could also be a safety thing or just a drainage thing.
When is the last time you made a wish in a well?
I don't really know.
Last five years?
If I see a fountain, I'm throwing a five.
Oh, you're making a wish in a fountain too.
I don't know. It kind of depends on the vibe of the fountain.
I might just like throwing the change in and watching this splash and seeing it settle and
seeing the other.
You'll put change in a fountain, but not necessarily wish.
Yeah, I would say so.
And can I ask what size wishes are we talking? I hope I have a nice dinner tonight. Are they
some sort of bigger thing? You don't have to reveal the wish. You can if you want, but...
Oh, I need to hear them. I want the wishes listed.
No, they don't come true if you tell them.
Yeah, but they're from the past.
I'm trying to work them into it.
I'm trying to trick them into it. Okay.
I'm trying to trick them.
I know my wish is to hear his wishes.
Yeah, I know what you want. I want it too.
I think it depends. I think it's like have a really nice rest of the day,
or it could be like a larger...
Okay. Then you go back and forth.
Yeah, love sort of thing. Now I got love locked down.
I got this little ring here. I'm all set. I'm good.
You didn't always, and maybe you have wishing wells to thank for that.
Love locked down. Whoever does that song, I don't know. I don't remember.
Not worth trying to recall.
Yeah, let's not dwell on that.
Leonida Parma, I think was the name of that artist.
That's right. I think that's good.
I wish for a little ring to have a little love in my life, and then that's how it all happened.
Leonida, what does the Parma estate have to say about this?
The what estate?
The Leonida Parma estate.
I'm assuming he's passed by this point.
Well, that's the thing. I don't know that you end up with an estate just because you've passed away.
I think everyone has an estate. That's technically what it's called.
Okay, I see.
Yeah, legally.
Estate sounds grand, but I think that's the term.
It just implies that there's people working over there, the estate.
It seems very big. It seems big in scope.
So we all get estates?
I believe so.
We all have estates.
Oh, well, there's a little wish that came true.
Even if it's just on paper. Yeah, I'm looking a lot about estates recently.
Oh, right, right, right. That's our subject.
No, no, not at all. No, but it is both a grand word and then also like, oh, this is illegal.
This is just what forms say.
I see, I see.
Just what notarized forms refer to.
I think it's because then you could say palatial estate also means
a bunch of land.
I think my only confusion is I think of it as the Michael Jackson estate.
I think of it as an entity that has enough people working for it to make a press release,
but I guess that's not true.
There is a Leonida Parma estate.
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
I'm going back to an old thing that I was really obsessed with for a while and still don't quite
understand. The statues that are there now are simulacrum, simulacra.
They are not the original statues.
The original statues were made of marble, but they started to discolor just from natural aging.
Like this old soap, yeah.
Yeah, like the old soap.
So then they replaced them with fiberglass replicas.
So the original statues were simulations of 2D animation.
The current statues are simulations of simulations.
You mean like 3D models is what you're saying?
No, no, like the original statues were the copies.
They were based on one thing, but then right now what you have is fiberglass copies of copies.
Okay, so you mean like recreations?
Is that what I'm getting confused by?
They're recreations.
I believe might have gotten, maybe they've been replaced multiple times, but
some of this was beefed up during the 1983 Fantasyland redo.
So it's what I'm looking-
Another frequent Jason wish is getting beefed up
by which you just have a nice big beef dinner.
Well, sure.
Sure.
Yeah, I mean, I was going to say like they don't, I'm trying to remember, because we have,
when I say we, I mean my daughter now, but my sister and I had Seven Dwarfs action figures,
but they were kind of hollow-y figures because I've said this anecdote on the show, I'm sure before,
I was obsessed with the Seven Dwarfs as a kid, and there were no figures.
They did not make figures when I was four years old or whatever.
And then they re-released Snow White, and I think maybe
then they started getting some merchandise back out there.
But my father, I was sick.
My father said, I'm going to go to the store.
What do you want?
I can get you anything.
And I said, I want Seven Dwarfs action figures.
And he said, all right, I'm getting them for you.
And my mom was like, they don't make those.
Why did you agree?
So we found like seven little rubber ninjas at like Walgreens.
And he goes, hey, these are the Seven Ninja Dwarfs.
Here you go.
And you bought it?
Yeah, I bought it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I was like, all right, whatever.
Ninjas were hugely popular at the time.
Sure, yeah.
But then we did get, finally, a year or two later,
like these fairly nice looking Seven Dwarfs.
And I do feel like the things I'm looking at here
look more like those.
And those looked more cleaned up than the original animation to me.
Those more look more like how they would draw the Seven Dwarfs
in newer materials or whatever, like in a newer poster
versus in the classic animation.
Now, maybe that's wrong.
Maybe these aren't newer designs, but they look like these to me
from just the naked eye.
The existence of the Dwarfs being one of the oldest properties
in the first animated film means that I think there was ample time
for them to be created in a lot of odd and upsetting forms, I feel like.
Sure, yeah.
By the time you're getting those action figures,
they're kind of rounded off in the way we do nice toy designs.
But I'm sure at some point we talked about the premiere
at the real Carthay Circle in the 30s
and how there were these costumes that were just beyond terrifying,
like burlap sacks with just gigantic, huge dilated pupil eyes.
And I saw, I was looking at photos of the Snow White Grotto.
And this is technically the reverse.
Imagine, just for a second, that you're leaving.
You're taking it in and like, oh, it's nice to have kind of a calm day
to just look at the grotto and reflect a little bit.
Well, I'm sure glad I stopped by.
And then you turn around and you see this.
Blah.
An old dwarf costume.
This is happy, I believe.
Yeah, it sure is.
One of those scary, this is a very 70s style we're looking at.
And maybe it's not, I think it's just, it's something about the position
that he's like, he kind of looks like he's about to charge at you, I think.
And the kind of head, like the old Winnie the Pooh was like this too,
where the head is like half the body, the head goes all the way down to the waist.
Yeah.
There's definitely, this is not quite how they do them anymore.
And yeah, I don't know.
It's a little upsetting.
There's a lot of scary dwarfs out there.
It kind of looks like, and I'm not just saying this because I passed,
well, I am just saying this because I passed couple today,
but it looks very similar to the billboards for the woman in the yard.
Oh, I see, I see.
I have seen this.
Yeah.
Just in terms of like greenery in the background and then like a sinister figure in the foreground.
It's not about a big dwarf though.
It's about a woman with like kind of a scarf.
It's a woman in the yard.
She's a spooky lady in a yard and she very quietly says today's the day.
Oh, I like that.
That's good.
Are you going to watch it?
Are you going to do it?
Because maybe that could be part of our summer extravaganza is that voice.
Well, it should hit Peacock, I'm assuming by the time.
Perfect.
And you don't have to go to the theater.
Summer is popping off for PTR 2025.
Reviews of horror films from three months ago.
Oh, well, you know, with that little dialogue, the thing,
the other thing I've been thinking about was just the Britney Murphy horror movie
where she goes, I'll never tell.
Yeah, what's that called?
I don't remember and I'm reasonably certain it's her though.
That's not, it wasn't like that though.
It was like sing-songy.
It was, I'll never tell.
Yeah.
The woman in the yard is kind of sing-songy.
I'm probably not doing it justice.
Summer's popping off.
Misremembered quotes from horror films from 21 years ago.
I can't remember.
Even the trailers spook me, they give me the creepies.
That's why.
Are you going to make it?
I was too scared.
Last October, you were making the big horror movie push and you got to one movie.
Yeah, I got the one and it was very strange.
And which is Halloween three, which is a favorite.
It's a fan favorite.
It's very interesting and odd, but it is.
You seem to, again, this is always, I'm always interested when you see a movie
and you have that reaction because generally you go, it was good.
I liked it.
So when you have this, when you like it, but it is, it has really unsettling.
It's got a weird vibe.
Yeah.
And on purpose, like I see why it's become a fan favorite.
So there's a horse in a horror movie.
Have a weird vibe.
I think so.
Yeah, no, I did like this movie.
It just, but I can see it in your body when you talk about it.
That you're like, yeah.
And it was so strange in ways I wasn't expecting.
It seemed like an old like BBC movie.
Can I get you to watch the two hellraisers this Halloween?
Yeah, I do want to watch.
Okay.
I know they have a lot of things to show me.
That's I've heard about that.
They sure do.
There's a lot of things beyond pleasure and pain.
I know those lines.
That's true.
You're going to love it actually.
Yeah.
An erotic thing.
I'm winking at him in case you didn't know.
Jason's going to get horrified.
Jason's going to get turned on by Hellraiser?
Yeah, that's what the movie's about.
It's about, it's like, it's a horny movie.
Yeah.
Were you turned on by Hellraiser?
No, not at all.
But Jason will be.
Yeah, but he's a freak.
You've heard him on this show.
Well, it's been established in the lore, I suppose.
Right, that's the podcast to ride lore.
Anyway.
Because I'm a square and he's a freak.
Specific thing about the Snow White, Wishing Well.
Really, that's-
That transition back from Hellraiser.
No, there's a reason.
No, go ahead.
That song, the, I'm wishing, I'm wishing.
Keep going.
Kind of gives me the creep.
I'm wishing.
That is what it's saying, does Sam.
Just the song in general.
Like, I love the Ones Upon a Dream song.
Yeah, from Sleeping Beauty, right?
I Knew You Once Upon a Dream, yes.
Yeah, with the bird, with Bird Prince.
Right, right.
That song is like light years ahead of the like, I'm wishing.
I'm wishing isn't a big fan favorite these days.
I feel like it hasn't held up as well as-
Well, it got replaced.
It's not in the new movie.
Right, oh, is that right?
Yeah, they replaced it with more of a Disney Princess want song.
So maybe that felt like some current desire to revamp it
and use more with that space narratively.
But me, I'm disgusted by all this I'm wishing slander
because I'm a big fan of the song.
Really?
Yes, because it has one of my favorite moments
in Disney animation ever.
You're down at the bottom of the well.
You're looking up at her.
She's singing in the well.
It's doing a duet with her own echo, basically.
But so you end with, to find me, to find me, today, today.
This is-
I love the prince today.
Yeah, that is the bellow.
That's one of my favorite things ever.
The today is very funny.
We got a message in a mailbag when Jason was gone,
which was like, Scott, who are some of your favorite bellowers?
And I didn't really want to repeat.
I didn't want to just do Thrill Raven's Cloth
to open the fence to the castle.
So I was vexed.
I was like, I need a new bellower to bring in.
And I'm sure it's not new.
I must have mentioned this before.
But I love to do that.
Because for just a few things here, ladies,
imagine that you're having yourself
a nice little moment in nature.
Maybe in your own backyard, just kind of singing to yourself
and just kind of having a moment of peace.
I mean, if it's just not that song,
if you're just humming whatever to yourself,
which is la da da, la da da da da.
And then out of nowhere, a foot away from you, da da da!
You turn.
Who the fuck was that?
A strange tall man is telling you.
It's a man in a flouncy shirt and a flouncy hat
with a big feather.
I do like today.
Jane will do the I'm wishing, I'm wishing.
I don't know why she's doing it.
She's got to let you do it.
Jason's the master of I'm wishing.
But then she will also do today.
I love it so much.
If you watch it in the scene, she does get scared.
And she does run away.
And he says, no, don't run away.
And then by the time she gets up to the balcony,
I guess she's had a little bit of a change.
She just needs some distance, understandably.
When a man shows up and screams into your ear,
you need a little, you need to back off a bit.
And then, oh, and speaking of like kiss blowing,
then that's kind of what happens.
Then he starts kind of a second part of the song.
And it's the other thing that I love
of music from this era from the 30s,
that A, that's what men sounded like back then.
And B, then when he kind of does his star part,
he bellows so loud that he distorts the microphone.
And it is an absolutely, like we all, we remember I'm wishing,
but his part is just like, oh, what heavenly blues.
And it's like, it's all cutting.
It's like, it's so distorted.
The 30s microphones can't handle it.
And you're watching it like, this is in one of the most
like crucial movies of all time, this guy.
And then he'll turn, like he'll watch like a,
I think she sends a bird down.
Oh, that's what it is.
It's all so strange if you actually watch it,
that a bird comes up and she kisses the bird on the mouth.
And then the bird flies down to him and then pecks his mouth.
So it's kisses exchanged through birds.
Now that's totally different.
That our wives should allow.
Blown kisses, no.
Kisses exchanged via bird.
I'm sorry, I'm a man.
I have needs, okay?
If a sexy lady kisses a bird and then the bird kisses me,
I'm accepting it, all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, Mike and I both had dogs, you have cats.
They're always giving you little kisses.
Oh yeah.
But they're not transferring.
I am constantly kissing my cat at home.
But if a woman comes in and kisses Scott's cat,
and then the cat kisses Scott is what he's saying.
Yeah.
He's saying there's a transfer of this.
That's a little way.
Some of that spit is cat, but some of it
is a sexy lady.
That's a hack.
That's a kissing hack.
Here's a way.
I want to exchange spit within the confines of marriage.
Use a cat.
It's so funny to me.
The whole thing.
And then when he turns his head and watches the bird fly away,
his face gets so weird and bulbous and distorted.
Because he was the first animated realistic man,
at least in Disney animation.
Because everything before that was cartoon proportions.
And I guess you could say the same for Snow White.
But even she's a little bit.
I mean, they did the thing where they watched a dancer
and studied her movements and drew over her.
But I think this was very hard to do.
And it shows.
It's really strange.
There's a little bit of Polar Express creepiness in it.
So much so that it limits the prince to where he
doesn't show up again until the end.
It's very strange, the whole movie,
that he appears then once,
plants himself in her dreams via bird kisses.
There's no introduction.
There's no my name.
He's only known as the prince through the whole movie.
And then he shows up when she has died.
That's a thing you also forget about Snow White,
is that it's not even like Sleeping Beauty.
She's under a spell, basically.
She might not wake up.
If you watch the title cards, Snow White is dead.
And they explain that the dwarves are keeping Vigil
and that they built her a coffin.
And they built a coffin for her.
And they go and they take Vigil there each day.
So you're watching like an umpteenth.
I don't know how many days it's been,
but all these old men take their hats off.
Every one of them bald.
That's also a fascinating thing.
Every dwarf is bald.
Are they related?
That's a good question.
Are the dwarves brothers?
We've also discussed this before.
Yeah, are they brothers?
Are they not supposed to be magical?
I don't know.
I don't feel like maybe the original grim fairy tale
has more insight into this.
No, not really.
No.
Some of them are foolish.
Well, how many are foolish?
One for sure.
I guess groupie for sure.
Yeah.
They're all a little foolish.
They're a little silly.
Doc is pretty in control.
It's going to keep me up at night.
Do you need to?
Well, it's tough because there's not one called foolish.
Sometimes happiness can make you be a fool, much like love.
But anyway, it's a really strange situation that they're all sad
and their animal friends are all sad.
And then the prince shows up on a horse,
doesn't introduce himself to her actual friends,
walks up, gives her a kiss.
She wakes up, immediately gets on the horse with him and leaves,
leaving her actual friend.
She spent so much more time with these dwarves than the prince.
She barely met the prince.
I didn't care about the prince at all.
No, he's the most forgettable.
Yeah.
Disney progressive, in a way, in the 30s,
have such an absolutely forgettable, unnamed character who is male.
Kind of a reverse of the trend.
Well, I felt that way about the prince in Sleeping Beauty.
Even though he's more, he does a lot more.
He fights Maleficent.
Yeah, yeah.
No, with that.
But I still didn't care about them that much.
No, not really.
But yeah, it steps way forward.
Wait, and he has a name.
So he's, I was going to say Prince Charming,
but Prince Charming and Cinderella.
Prince Valiant?
I think it's Prince Valiant.
But not, but that's a different Prince Valiant.
No, it's not your.
It's a Sunday comic.
Not your Sunday funnies, Prince Valiant.
Is it Prince Valiant?
Maybe it's not.
Oh, no, Prince Philip.
Shit.
Wrong.
Damn.
Embarrassing.
Again, we don't know the movies.
We know the parks.
And even then, there's still big lapses in knowledge and awareness.
I'll tell you what movie I do know,
and I don't mean to contradict myself.
But while I'm wishing the song gives me the willies a little,
you were talking about songs from the 30s.
I love from 42nd Street, We're in the Money.
And that kind of has a similar tinny, the original ones.
Like, we're in the money, the skies are sunny.
Do they sing it high like that?
We got a lot of what it takes to get along.
It's pretty high.
And usually, in productions, I believe when we saw,
and when I saw on a cruise ship at 12, and then in the movie,
they're often wearing giant coins, costumes.
Really?
Yeah.
Big coins dance and sing that song?
Big coins dancing, yeah.
And you could use those to wish.
Well, fuck.
Only in a giant well.
In a giant well.
Turn them in a wave pool.
Yeah.
I just also was like, if we're going to meditate on today for a second,
I want to know who it is.
I want to know more about the guy.
The guy's name is Harry Stockwell.
Harry Stockwell does that today.
He had a recording career outside of it.
The thing I found the most fascinating is that when he sang this, he was 35.
Wow.
This is the way 35-year-olds sang in the 30s.
Yeah.
This is a young, fashionable, hip way of singing.
And I got curious about the rest of the recording career of Harry Stockwell.
So please enjoy.
And I guess Jason, I especially want to get your ears on this song,
because it'd be up your alley if anyone.
This song is called You're Devastating.
With a crackle.
You're devastating and so far above me.
To think of mating, I never could dare.
I forgot that.
To think of mating, I couldn't dare.
Wow.
Who would dream of filling up your womb, passing my seed into your bountiful.
Blood by the birthplace.
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think you should sing that on the old ones.
I think, yeah, I'm going to have to go home and serenade my new wife.
That's going to be in your Spotify rap this year.
It'll mark it.
It'll happen.
You can find it on a playlist called The Crackliest Songs of the 30s.
40s.
It's that.
It's one of the songs from the Forgotten Lady Gaga Harley Quinn album,
where she sings a lot of standards.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
The wonderful music.
Right.
Well, yeah, I agree.
Hey, Jane, the marriage is still fresh to me.
Maybe this is corny, but I just got something to say.
You're devastating to me.
Your beauty astounds me.
Oh, two mates would be a debate within my heart.
This was the language.
She shuts door, car drives away.
Music of love.
Never seen again.
You would have, if you sang that to a woman, they would marry you on the spot.
She would swoon.
You're so devastating Lady Gaga's rendition of Owen the Saint's.
That's in the mood.
Okay.
No, that's not, I think, just the album.
That's just an album cut.
Yeah, it's the album cut.
It's a deeper album cut where you can hear kind of Harley Quinn sing
when the saints go marching in.
What happened?
I thought this movie had a $200 million budget
and then all the songs are public domain.
I guess that saves some money.
I'm surprised this isn't Jason's favorite movie.
I haven't watched it yet.
I could see that.
I think this might be her-
Joker, falled, apologist, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah.
Her tie-in record.
He's going to like it.
Was kind of unattached.
Yeah, I don't know.
Does she do That's Entertainment?
Yeah, she does That's Entertainment.
Oh, God.
This is going to be your favorite movie you've ever seen.
But I don't know if it's in the movie.
These might be the album-specific cuts.
Okay.
They do an amended We're in the Money called We're on the Staircase,
the famous staircase.
We're not dancing to Gary Glitter anymore.
Taking real big steps as we walk those stairs.
We're doing splashing, big old splashing.
Batman is not here, please stop asking.
Who?
Wait, the thing you said about they re-recorded the voice.
Yeah, the original voice actress came back.
When they redid it in the 80s.
Well, yes.
And she, a story apparently is that she's been,
much of this is 50 years later.
And I think she believes she could still hit the high notes.
Like actually, Jason, could you give us a sample
of the high notes that she was trying to hit?
I'm wishing.
That's pretty good.
That's the note, I think.
Yeah.
Well, this is what Adriana, whatever, could not necessarily hit.
And knowing that she would have to be replaced,
she asked if she could go ahead and ask someone for help,
even though she was alone in the studio.
The engineer and producer said,
okay, but you are alone in the studio.
I don't know who you're going to ask for help.
And she said, just wait.
And then she turned away from the microphone,
looked up and whispered, Mr. Disney, if you are up there,
please help me find Snow White's voice.
She returned and asked for one last take,
during which she nailed every note.
Yeah, up there.
Maybe, I don't know about that direction.
Yes, I am up here.
I was actually reviewing your SAG sign-in sheet,
and we overpaid you.
You owe me money.
As soon as you make it up here,
you're cutting me an $80 check, missy.
That inspired her.
Oh, Roy's up here.
I'm down here.
Wrong direction.
Anything else?
Do we get to everything?
It's nice.
Check it out.
They've reproduced it for Hong Kong Disneyland
and Tokyo Disneyland.
Yeah, I didn't realize that.
They redid the little grotto.
But there's a Cinderella wishing well in Florida.
Yes.
Oh.
It's a different thing.
And no statues?
I don't believe so, but that's obviously tied in
thematically to the castle.
That's more of a piece.
So eventually we'll determine if we think that's better
or if we like it, that it's two different properties.
It made a big mess when that naughty Stitch teepied
the castle and some blew in the wishing well
and then it got all wet.
What would it sound like if Stitch sang, I'm wishing?
Hooray.
I hope he toilet papers the castle again
for the live action one.
Let's do it.
Come on.
And make it a cake too.
Yeah, make it a cake.
Oh yeah, that icing's getting all in that toilet paper.
Well, I think we did it.
I think you survived podcast the ride the second gate,
which thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us in our VIP
Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus
episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
And just really quick, because we vote on the topics
in club three, I know it sounds funny for these guys
to just talk about shifting gears while I grimace for a while.
Will it be?
Am I causing it by saying this?
Probably.
But just take a hard look in the mirror or in a reflection,
like in a wishing well, as Snow White does, and think,
do I want to hear these guys talk about this Tim Allen
sitcom for two hours?
That they haven't seen.