Club 3
Well guys, it was my turn this month to plummet straight to last place in the poll with a sitcom-oriented topic.
I now know your pain, Mike, your frequent pain.
I feel no pain when Mike... I feel...
I'm maybe not even happy, but I don't even feel... I'm not upset at all.
You seem kind of proud in a way.
I think so.
To isolate that last place.
You know, it didn't feel good, and I'll tell you why.
Sometimes you feel like people don't know what they're missing out on.
That's something you've said before.
Sure, that's true.
Have I quoted you on this before?
Because I don't remember if this was on an episode or not.
There was a while where I couldn't tell...
I was like, I don't know if anybody's like...
Because you would float the Annette test balloon every once in a while.
And I think at some point I said, I don't feel like people are exactly clamoring for Annette.
And you said, well, that's because they don't know what's coming.
And then that was a very fun, perfectly good episode.
But I still am like, what was coming?
That was scary. It was kind of a threat.
What was coming was a girl with an OK voice singing some Sherman Brothers songs.
That's what was coming.
People didn't know.
Pineapple princess.
Yeah.
Well, you know, but maybe I feel some of that on your behalf.
Because in this case, this was listener submitted.
It's something I mentioned on the show before and it went straight to last place.
And I can't say I blame you.
But I think if you didn't vote for Jason Alexander's music video career, either you're confused by that phrase, which is pretty dull on its face.
But I think clearly if you didn't vote for that, then you don't know the Nickelback video,
trying not to love you, in which Jason Alexander plays a lovelorn barista who is trying to impress the girl of his dreams played by model Brooke Burns and trying to do so with impressive foam art.
He is using his foam to express his heart.
But then another barista shows up who is way better at foam art than he is.
And what I don't want to do is spoil who plays that part because either if either if we just declare we're going to do that episode or if you the listener wants to just go for it and watch it.
But I would not dare because I kind of forgot when it came up in the polls like, oh, I got to watch that again.
And I forgot who barista number two is played by.
He really drives up on like a little tiny motorbike straight into the store and like wearing like a like a fedora and a vest.
And he just like flips a sign that says help wanted the flips it as if to say not anymore.
I work here now, fills out no paperwork, just starts doing foam art.
And I when when he turns around and you realize who it is, big moment.
So all I could say is you're missing out and you're also missing out on the on a great song by Nickelback and you're missing out on no visual appearance from Nickelback.
This is made completely outside of their purview.
Do you think that with that little talk up, you could get it to a third or four like could come back in a club three or we just have to.
God, I don't know. It's still a little well, let me add to the let me add to the pot and say the reason that it's not just that one music video is that there's another.
There are count them, not one, but two Brad Paisley music videos starring Jason Alexander, one of which is also directed by Jason Alexander and stars him.
It's called Online.
The cast of this video includes William Shatner, Marsha Brady, herself, Maureen McCormick, George's mom on Seinfeld, reunited Estelle Harris and Taylor Swift.
Taylor Swift and not just in like a zoom in cameo because this was like she was still on the rise.
So it was an honor for her to be a backup dancer for Brad Paisley backup dancer.
Yes. Her and Kelly Pickler, I believe, are kind of like they, you know, it was a big slot to get a Brad Paisley video.
So I don't know. I don't want to submit the biggest chance I think that we'll ever get for any of these to sort of get their revenge.
And why I like to talk them up once in a while is that we've only done it once.
We did the poll where like a lot of old topics came back from the dead.
I think it was called Topic Rewind. Oh, yeah.
And we're overdue for that, but I feel like we sort of can't do it until we close out the current business of the poll, which once again remains the second place finisher.
Bugman does whatever he wants.
I feel like that needs to fully play itself out before we can do the topic rewind.
Did you can I really quick rewind to Jason Alexander?
I'm always the amount of stuff that he just pops up in, including motion capturing a robot in the electric state.
I baffled me with that one.
You're kidding. The smash hit Netflix Brothers film, The Electric State.
He is in it, but he mocapped a robot.
Do we know this character's name?
I'm trying to the robot.
I've been looking at you.
I've been trying to find the name of the character.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
No, I'd never heard that.
Ted Wingman.
I think maybe the guy Ted with the robot's name is Ted Wingman.
I think maybe he was like a guy in his head.
He's like his consciousness went into a robot or like, I don't know.
I don't I haven't seen the film, but I just saw behind the scenes of mocap suit.
Jason Alexander, like running around with Millie Bobby Brown.
And I was just like, what is this?
The top result when you look up Jason Alexander, Electric State is a post on the Seinfeld
Reddit where the top comment is, yeah, besides Jason Alexander, that movie sure did suck.
It just plain sucked.
I've seen movies suck before, but it was the suckiest bunch of sucks that ever sucked.
Got to go. My damn wiener kids are listening.
Turns into a Simpsons quote on the Seinfeld Reddit.
I think there's some sincere, some sincere feelings to that post.
They got to fix those results.
That's number one is the movie.
And number two is, yeah, it sucked.
Yeah, that's they should probably pay someone to get that knocked down.
Yeah, but I don't know.
I have a feeling there's not a lot of money left over.
Me knowing nothing about Electric State.
My guess would be just knowing the Russos and the way they work.
My guess would be that the budget and marketing altogether were 800 million dollars,
which of course were recouped.
They always are.
The Russos, every single one of them is the highest.
They top themselves every single time, just like James Cameron.
The world's most expensive movies.
They play all around the world.
They're global.
They sit until they're global.
And you know who's to blame for not recouping the Electric States, like all that money.
A single social media post from Rachel Ziegler.
Oh, yes.
That's always to blame.
Yes, absolutely.
She's got those lips.
So anyways, yeah, I don't know.
Maybe Jason comes back.
I'd like to see him.
He's got so much stuff.
Yeah, because I think the music video career would also include that McDonald's commercial.
The McDLT commercial.
The hot stays hot and the cold stays cold.
Jason, here he is.
He's back.
There he is.
Sorry.
He's waking up.
No, no.
I was silently watching the Trying Not To Love You video.
Oh, very good.
Oh, so now you know who the...
I mean, don't say it, but you know who Barista 2 is?
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
It's a little confusing.
It's a little confusing, but I think I got the joke.
It's a performer who's so engulfed in the part.
You question, is this a real character?
Yeah.
By the way, if you're hearing some birds and dog noises and stuff, you might not be.
But if you are, if you hear an ambulance go by, we're in a recording location we haven't
used in a minute, which is my garage.
We've been out of my garage for some time, but we figured it'd be good to bring it back
here, because we didn't want to stink up a studio at a place where it might linger for
a while.
Maybe we wouldn't consider it a stink.
Maybe these are good aromas.
I guess that's what we're here to find out, because the winner of the poll triumphing
barely over Bugman, who I think was one of his strongest second place showings.
We'll find out next month how high within second place he goes.
But a solid winner and a fun idea is this, unlicensed theme park scented candles.
This idea comes to us from Mike D. Guglielmo.
Spring is in the air.
Let's discuss some unofficial unlicensed copyright skirting park scented candles from
Etsy.
The boys can get a whiff of Caribbean waters, or passage flight, or butterscotch brew, or
ghostly manner, or the delightfully vague flume.
Well, thank you, Mike, for that.
And you got your wish.
We are now here in a zone with compromised audio quality, but, you know, good air quality.
Open air where all of these potentially conflicting scents that are laid out on a table in front
of us can waft and, you know, not bother anybody.
Yeah.
So this general area, I think we were aware of this.
I think probably we all had at least one somewhere in our collection.
But what I sense is the highest enthusiasm for this stuff, just before it was a topic,
these candles out in the world, comes from Jason.
Because you see, you had a bunch of these.
I had a bunch.
The ones I brought, I didn't realize.
Besides like one, well, maybe two of them.
And I think there's a fourth hidden somewhere at home or burned out.
Like we've actually used.
Yes.
Do you know what that's burned out?
Like, I don't know what.
No, no, no, that's right.
No, it's just funny that you made a point.
You made a point of like, I'll bring some candles.
I got them.
And then as soon as you open it, it's like a moth flew out.
Those are all the way down to the wicks.
Which shows that you're enthusiastic about.
Yeah.
Me and my partner.
Blushing bride.
Yeah.
We burned through some of these and I don't know where my banshee flight one got to.
Banshee flight, not flight of passage.
Do you know?
But you know, it's kind of the same scent as this feet.
Do you want me to talk about the ones I have?
Do you want me to start or?
Well, let's see.
Should we like to explain this area a little bit first?
I mean, I think Mike laid it out very nicely, but if you don't know this from the ground up,
there are a number of stores online that claim to kind of capture theme park scents within not just candles,
but I feel like also soaps or just spray bottles because there's so many wonderful smells in the world of theme parks.
We covered a lot of them in the fake smell final four.
So the thought would be that if some of these are simulated scents already,
maybe an outside person could make their their best guess and bottle them and sell them and you could bring them home.
And I think I'm trying to think.
I mean, I don't remember these really existing or being popularized before 10 years ago,
but I think we've all kind of in our travels in the last 10 years like maybe I've gotten one as a gift.
Maybe it seems like Mike, you've like explored them, you know, just for no particular reason,
because the idea of it is so nice to be able in the way that anything being like a warp tunnel that takes you straight to a theme park when you aren't at one sounds really nice in the way that like the right YouTube video can do it or like, you know,
having a car they Manhattan at home or whatever, approximating a food.
So the idea of it is so great and something as a smell that we desire to smell as much as the E.T. forest.
I mean, like it feels like if it worked, the idea feels better than a drug that you could just like open, open a can and just go like, oh, Dennis Hopper, Blue Velvet style.
Oh, yeah, I'm in the forest, baby.
A canister of the sense.
And you had the thing you put over your mouth and nose.
I guess if you were being given oxygen at the hospital, yeah, yeah, that would be maybe more of the ultimate.
Give it to me.
Because this is yeah, because like the you know, you're a candle burns, the whatever wax, whatever you would call it.
And then the scent gets in the air, but it's not quite how the smell is transferred from a ride.
It's usually in a canister of some kind of some sort of diffuser, I'm assuming.
Yes. Yeah.
So like little vents like that maybe are on the vehicle itself or in the environment.
Yeah. Where I've kind of encountered this before, all the resorts, the casino hotels in Vegas all have particular sense.
And on the casino websites, you can buy a candle or like a diffuser.
Is that right? Yeah.
I think for a house warming, when Jane and I moved into our apartment, I got the Park MGM like a big candle.
No kidding.
And it smells lovely.
And there's a scent company, there's a fragrance company in Vegas that sells like the copyright skirting scents hotel by hotel.
Sure, sure.
So you could get a Park MGM scented candle.
Well, I got the official like the like official on the casino website.
Smells like casino?
No, it's just kind of like a florally smell.
But you can buy like the mattresses from the Wynn, like the same mattresses they use at the casinos.
You can buy the literal bed.
Not the literal bed, but like the same sort of, you know, model.
I didn't know they were so open with like take our specific home.
Take our, well, I think it's like a $2,000 mattress.
Is it made specifically for the Wynn?
I think that's the idea.
Is that they craft, Steve Wynn crafted a mattress, went into the labs, the mattress labs, and said I want it like this and like this and like this.
I don't think it's that specific.
I think it's like the Cerda or whatever, the luxury hotel version.
Well, he specifically has Wynn at home, a collection of.
Okay, that one.
Of Wynnons and bath goods.
Is he still in charge of that aspect of the company?
It was not removed from, we are perfectly comfortable associating Steve Wynn and beds.
That's fine.
He can stay in the at home collection.
But yeah, dream beds, it says.
Wynn at home.
Wow, we worked with one of the world's finest manufacturers.
We did.
To create the Wynn dream bed.
Oh, okay.
He was in the lab.
He was in the bed lab.
Yeah.
Lomping around.
Firmer, firmer.
Less firm.
Yeah, wow.
Mattress only $2,400 and his name is like.
It's like a bunch of abstract swirls, but then it turns into his signature.
Do you want to buy a pre haunted mattress?
We've got you.
We've got you set up.
It's like the canvas on a boxing ring on the mat.
It says Wynn on it.
It probably has a couple other ads.
The problem is you never want to like put covers on it because you just want to.
Yeah, I want to see that name every time I dream.
Jason, would you sell ad space on your mattress to different companies?
Oh, like a car wrap?
Yeah, a car wrap or I'm saying like the canvas on a boxing ring or how WWE now cuts a TKO.
But then who would say it's covered?
It would be primarily advertising to you and Jane.
Okay.
I suppose.
Okay, well, I'm just asking like what brand would you feel like kind of like seeing on your mattress every night?
Well, but you don't see your I'm telling you you there's like so many sheets and covers.
Hold on.
I'm correct.
No, no, you are correct.
Hold on.
Yeah, I haven't laid it out.
I guess you're going to have a clear sheet over your mattress.
It's a Steve Wynn has developed a new clear sheet.
So now you can see the mattress underneath, but you still have the softness of the bed and the sheets and stuff.
Folding a clear fitted sheet.
That's not going to be any easier.
Might be confusing.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Like what brand do we like?
I'd be okay.
We get Taco Bell pretty regularly.
Do you want a Taco Bell mattress?
Well, if it's just like the old, you know, it's just a little purple and the bell, you know.
I'm bored with him.
What are you saying here?
Taco Bell.
I thought you would like that too.
It's not so much that they made.
It's just that you it's it's branding to remind you that when you wake up, you should get Taco Bell.
Well, okay.
If waking up, that's a good like if it was the Dunkin Donuts, it was the logo and the guy, Fred, who would make the doughnuts.
Fred, you want the guy.
Like a little caricature.
Yeah.
You want him on your bed?
I want him on his bed.
It's time to make the doughnuts.
You wake up.
Which could become a catchphrase before a certain act in this bed.
Yeah.
All right, baby.
Time to make the doughnuts.
Jason pretends this hasn't always been the catchphrase.
This isn't a massive like thought out Sherlock Holmes plan.
As if as if either of you need a reminder when you wake up to go to Taco Bell or Dunkin Donuts that day.
Oh, right.
It would just be nice.
I'm neglecting this brand.
Well, you know, also because it would just be good for like, you know, if you're doing like influence influencer style posts, you know, it's like hear me in front of the.
Which neither of you guys are.
I think you're missing out on a whole area.
Not yet, because Jason doesn't have Fred from Dunkin Donuts on his bed.
We got the Fred.
We got the Fred mattress, you know, cost about four grand.
It's worth every penny.
Get to see Fred at Fred every time I wake up.
Sometimes look over, you know, during the act.
See Fred.
I pretend he's encouraging me, pushing me on.
Was Fred.
Oh, go buddy.
Was Fred an actor or did he actually make doughnuts?
I can't remember the full details.
Long dead.
Right.
Yeah, he is long dead.
Read the Baker.
I think this was a legit.
I think this was the magic of entertainment that they hired an actor and they didn't hire him because of baking.
Well, maybe, you know, because Dave Thomas was a real guy.
He was the guy and he was in all the ads.
So well, he did own the company.
No, I know that.
I'm just saying it's not impossible that they would have put a guy that actually has something to do with it.
It doesn't appear to be the case.
It could have been like, you know, finding a starlet working at Schwab's Pharmacy.
The ad guy.
Your version of a starlet would be finding a baker.
The ad guy goes into Dunkin Donuts and he's like, man, that baker has a certain shine to him.
There's a charisma radiating from him as he does the glazed blueberries.
I guess this is Jason's dream when he moved to Los Angeles.
He thought, well, all right, step one, go to Schwab's Pharmacy.
Step two, meat producer.
Step three, Baffo Bucks.
The system hasn't changed since 1956.
That's true.
OK, it appears Schwab's is now a hustler superstore.
But there is a restaurant.
Oh, I'm confused now.
Yeah.
There is coffee.
By the way, just to circle back on something.
Google's wind dream bed ended up on something called on the forums of something called The Mattress Underground.
And here's a review from July 2022.
If you ever think to buy the wind dream bed, hotel bed, don't do it.
The mattress is made by Sealy Posturepedic and I can say is the worst mattress I've ever tried.
Very hard and uncomfortable.
They don't offer returns or refunds at all and you will be scammed with that trash.
I hope I can help someone not to waste the money there.
They claim is the best sleep you ever had.
LMAO.
So I think we may have like we may have sparked to the idea of the wind dream bed a little too hard, which I guess is just Sealy.
You see, I read a long feature article once though.
I am a little skeptical of mattress review websites because when the box mattress that ships your home, all those startups came up.
They they started there were mattress influencers and people started getting mattresses and then people started writing real reviews and fake reviews.
And like it got very like there were fines.
People weren't tell they wouldn't tell you were advertising.
So that review very likely true.
But there is a chance it was planted by a competitor.
But from the name, I think it's possible that the mattress underground is the real website where you avoid all of this chicanery that you're talking about.
The mattress underground may have risen up as a resistance in response to all this grim mattress controversy.
Some people call the mattress underground a terrorist organization, but some of us say they're freedom fighters.
So it depends what your philosophy is on some of this stuff.
I believe in the mattress underground.
I am signing up for the mattress underground.
I will leave my home and family to join the mattress underground.
People think that's righteous, a righteous cause.
That's what that Pepsi come to join the conversation of commercial.
That was a mattress underground demonstration.
Yeah, I think you know what?
I think Jason just doesn't want to lose a possible Sealy endorsement in the future.
He just doesn't want to trash Sealy right here because he wants the possibility of getting a free Sealy mattress.
Yeah, I have forgotten the names of all the mattress companies.
I forget what you're still in business and what you bought dad's on the show.
I think it's well, if we did an ad read for it in 2018, that probably means it's gone out of business.
I think they just like a lot of those companies just are cannibalizing each other, just are buying each other up and stuff.
Michael Vail passed away 20 years ago and he was an actor.
Who's Michael Vail?
He was the donut guy.
Fred is the donut.
Well, I hate to break it to you.
His real name.
Boy, this is going to upset you.
That was Sedonomous?
What?
It was a pseudonym?
Oh, wow.
Is that a word?
Sedonomous?
Yeah, I always thought that was a word.
Yeah, you're probably right.
That's a big awesome word actually.
Yeah, I've never used it either.
Sedonomous.
I don't even know if I've heard of it.
On Wikipedia, they describe him as an American character actor famous for being the longtime sleepy-eyed mascot, Fred the Baker, for donut change.
Sleepy-eyed mascot.
Amazing we haven't done more Fred the Baker talk.
There's a great like 30, I think it's an account that posts like old archive footage from is it WGHB Boston with a public TV station in Boston.
And it's all just people drinking like cups of coffee at the like one of the first Dunkin Donuts.
And like just imagining a Dunkin Donuts with like a diner counter and like ceramic china and just all these old miserable people drinking the coffee.
Would that be your version of the of the building an oval office in your house if you had the room?
Yeah, replicating that.
Replicating an old Dunkin Donuts with a bunch of old men sadly or angrily sipping coffee.
Well, that's I kind of forget where I read this or heard this.
But Tom Petty, do you know the Tom Petty coffee story?
I don't think so.
Someone was interviewing Tom Petty and he said, hey, do you want to water a cup of coffee?
He's like, oh, I'd love a cup of coffee.
He's drinking it.
And he's like, Tom, I got to tell you, this is like the best cup of coffee I ever had.
And he tells a long story that Tom Petty and his girlfriend at the time were coming back from somewhere, stopped at a diner and Tom Petty liked the coffee so much.
He bought the industrial.
He bought the same model of industrial coffee maker for his house.
And I believe maybe even had two of them.
But like Tom Petty is like, you're not the first person to say you like the coffee here.
But apparently, apparently it was just Maxwell House.
Yeah, it was just Maxwell House.
Going automatic.
It was just like diner ass coffee.
Interesting.
It's funny that this was like this anecdote got out.
Like, who do you remember where you heard this?
I think it was someone writing a book or profile on Tom Petty.
It doesn't.
Yeah, it's in Petty, the biography.
Wow.
I have a question.
How do you think you spell pseudonym?
Well, you spell it like pseudonym, but you put it O-U-S on.
Okay.
Pseudonyms.
Pseudonymous.
It sounds right.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
I was spelling it wrong.
Yeah.
Pseudonyms.
It's like pseudonym.
That's a really good vocabulary.
Pseudonymous.
Wow.
The pseudonymous author of this mystery is the example.
Well, thank you for that education.
Anyway, so I love you, Fred.
Thinking about you, brother.
We miss you every day.
We miss you in your pseudonymous ways.
I'm not saying Michael, I'm saying Fred.
So I think the other thing to highlight about the candles is that in sort of a unlicensed Halloween costume way,
they have to use all of these generic terms because none of them are Disney affiliated.
Or universal affiliated.
Well, hold that.
Well, yes, yes, yes.
Hold that thought.
But I'm trying to think of a good example.
One of mine, Park Sense, is allowed to say extraterrestrial adventure, which is pretty close.
But you sort of have to, they all have to kind of word soup it a little bit to get like passage flight.
And then if you end up on, like here I'm on Magic Candle Company's website, they have one called Banshee Flight.
And you click on that and they can't say it's a smell like from Avatar Flight of Passage.
Right.
It is a fragrance that captures the thrill of taking flight over an otherworldly landscape.
Stuff like that.
It's an invitation for your imagination to embark on an aromatic aerial adventure.
Spread your wings and embrace your adventurous spirit as you discover new horizons
and experience the thrill of taking flight over an exotic landscape today.
This is, I mean, we're going to do like equivalence of this.
We're going to smell equivalence of this.
And that'll be the question is like, does it make us feel like we are, we have answered an invitation of to our imagination?
Yeah.
Aromatic aerial.
It's a lot of pressure.
Or does it just smell like a nice soap or something?
I guess that's what we're going to have to cut.
Yeah.
I also, something I noticed, they all like, they can't, they have to like evoke the feeling, but they can't show you the real thing.
So especially Magic Candle Company on their website, it's a lot of like very AI feeling.
Like here's AI spitting out its closest equivalent to the Grand Floridian.
Right.
It's kind of a bummer because I don't think they were doing that a few years ago.
Like these designs, I think, are real designs.
But the background in a lot of the links is kind of like the AI goo art, which I don't love.
And it's unfortunate because they already had very nice like human designs on them.
Yeah.
It's also, I do want to, this is a thing I think about sometimes now because I'm so like radar focused on like, oh, AI, that's AI.
That looks like AI.
Sure.
Sometimes maybe it's just bad art.
Maybe it just looks like shit.
This is true.
It is possible.
I'm not saying this specific.
I'm just saying that this is a thought I had the other day where I go, am I just so like hyper aware of AI that now I'm just calling something shitty AI?
Sometimes could just be very bad graphic.
Yes.
But I agree that the candles themselves, you know, just what's on the like, at least, you know, I bought a few from PerkSense.
And this is just very like simple, clean, classy design.
You know, they evoke as best they can.
Like ET, I'm looking at, you know, just outline of the forest.
Yeah.
You know, and bikes going over the moon.
But they're changed.
You know, they're changed to like a kind of wagon bike that doesn't I don't think exist in reality.
They've all got it.
That looks like an Amish.
We're sent buggy.
Yeah.
No, very strange.
This might be a good place to start because I think like, you know, this, as I said, this is a smell that we're chasing.
And I feel like we have a few.
Do you have an equivalent of this?
Maybe we can kind of mix and match.
Let me read the copy on this.
Oh, trouble.
Grab your bike, your interplanetary passport and meet your friends in this rich nostalgic forest.
It's time for an adventure.
So they get a lot of quotes out.
They aren't afraid.
You know, I think they've looked into how close can we get with this copy?
And I wonder if they've looked into or just like did it.
And it's not worth litigating.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah. Because, look, universal, put your money where your mouth is.
If you have a problem with this, you have the real smell.
Bottle the real smell.
Don't let all these third parties profit from it.
Like, you know, yeah, it's their loss for not giving people something they clearly want.
So I'm going to light this one up because I'm definitely curious how close we can and maybe we can kind of compare contrast.
Can we maybe do smells before the and then light?
Yeah, sure. Let's pass it because it's sort of different smells beforehand.
Now, here's something.
Here's something that I detect as we begin smelling these candles.
I detect that we are all going to be terrible at describing smells.
Yeah, it's very hard.
It's a very difficult thing to do.
Things that you can look at.
I think you can do.
But like anybody try.
What can? Oh, this is what I'm the most nervous about about.
Yeah, go ahead.
Give it a give it a shot.
Well, hold on.
Let me just want to theater of the mind.
Yeah, yeah.
Listeners smelling.
Sniffing.
Oh, is it their nose or yours?
There's like a vanilla vanilla.
No, maybe I'm wrong.
What if Jason's killer at it?
I know I would love it if he is.
I don't know how to can I even begin?
Because I think what we'll do is like I think we'll end up doing a lot of like, you know, it's very like it's very it's very calming.
Detecting notes of my nose is already starting to get irritated.
Well, yes, this is the whole thing I was about to say.
I'm a quick candle guy.
I do not.
I do not like a candle burning for hours.
I don't.
We never do this in the house.
We do not.
We've never taken to this.
I feel sometimes the influence of my father when I was a senior in high school, but still living in the house and pretending that I was a looser, chiller person than I was.
And I remember lighting up some incense in my bedroom.
And that was going for about five minutes when my dad woke up, I think from us being asleep, stormed to my room all the way across the house and said no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
He was right.
You're a child of the 60s, Father.
You should know this better than anybody.
You have put truly in your blood.
No, I and I did kind of stick with me.
I don't know.
I you know I'd light up some incense in college or whatever, but not not not these days
I like I like you turn you light a candle for five ten minutes. You blow it out. I am NOT
I'm kind of like that too. Well. I'm terrified
Something's gonna catch on fire. I'm terrified. I'm so sure nowadays and a senior dog
Like it just makes me so nervous having that you have a sink as you have a senior dog
Yeah, I've seen you're like an old dog. Just wandering around stumbling into things
I'm like like if you have kind of a loose Ikea shelf and the dog just like
Walks into the oh, yeah, yeah, and I I just feel like guys so many goddamn books and cut
Let's just like oh, that's going up like like yeah, well this can read so much. He's got no
Basically the New York library on eBay
Much stuff in there well, then let's be let's be careful handling these I suppose. Let's not light my garage
How do we all like to light a candle mmm?
With that with a lighter. What are you?
lighter or one of the
Forever like we're not brother. I got a list okay here. See there. We go
This is
Assuming well, no, that's just that's just a cheap a bit lighter
But we can only got one a long big candlestick lighters mmm
You can just get it in any store assuming it works correctly sometimes. They're a little finicky
But I love a stick match or a book match is very satisfying well
I thought I was that's what I was wondering with you especially the way
I bet you've especially as a once-in-a-while cigarette smoker. I bet you love that match
I love it, and and I forget the the folding the match book over and pulling it you feel like you're a detective
Yeah, and you light a cigarette outside of the
sexy dames
Helping with the I feel like people have definitely why are you leaving a joint with a match?
I was like I don't know it's fun for me
Well you get a little thrill out of the
We've never talked about it. I knew I yeah, I knew it. Yeah, that's why I knew this guy had had lighting opinions
I knew the match. I knew match book 2 was part of it
I'm just gonna use this Bic with kind of a long so long and now those guys are here very hard
No, well, we're seeing that are they I haven't found it hard. I got this on the way to a
Birthday party for my oldest son listener. He is five years old now believe it
We are long this shows been going
This is a combo I used to have these and I know about the marketing
This is a combo Bic lighter and like candle shorter candlestick lighter
Martha Stewart and Snoop Dogg, I believe did
Advertisements for this for this bit
Specific bigger a different like they're like you can light up lots of things wink
That's for the odd pairing I see yeah, okay, okay satisfied well this
Children's birthday party candles and nice
ETSI scented candles for good boys
It also said to cut the wick a little bit of food. Nope. No, not even that. Okay, let's see and
And
This is not
Wasted time and as we signed up stuff
I I'll say this while we're waiting and while you're sniffing
I just bought a lighter on the way over here at a gas station and
There was a bunch of different designs on the Bic lighters and the guy looked at me
He looked at the different designs. He chose for me and said, you know, you a turtle guy
And he should and I go I am a turtle guy
And he goes, yeah, here you go. And he hands me this and it's a turtle
It's not a ninja turtle, but a like Lisa Frank look at Frank turtle. Yeah. Yeah, and I was like, well he you had my number
Also, my nose is like stuff today. Geez. Well, you're disqualified
You just really sucked that back because you look really upset. I took like a hit of it
Well, you guys almost got burned in the face this is gonna I feel like some listeners maybe know already this is heading for the first
on-air fire
One of the last times we were here the police came now fire departments gonna come this is here you go. All right
Oh, I'm careful with that. It's also because it's also tough because the smell was stronger when that wasn't lit
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking now. You're getting a lot of burning smell in addition in addition to the smell of
Fire wick. Yeah, you're getting wick. Yeah, you know, it's very fiery. I sense since notes
Yeah, is it is it better if we put the candle closer to you?
I don't know. It's also this card table feels like it could just go this feels. Yes, it could. Yes
Mmm, but you doesn't smell like it's supposed to is really the question. Well, it smells like warmth Michael
Well, go lick and off. I don't know I
You know not to jump
I have an ET one too. And I think there is I'm gonna blow my nose on Mike real quick
This is gonna be we have backed into the darkest episode
Oh my sinuses Mike Mike walked into my apartment once recently
I forgot whether Jane had perfume on or we had like a room spray. It was incense
Oh, it was not polos on I think was saying it was not perfect. I go who's wearing perfume in here. She
She burned sage a lot. Yeah
Sometimes and I said our other guy did I oh maybe was sage. Did I say something about ghosts or something?
I was like, are we getting ghosts out of here? I think you said your eyes hurt. Oh, yes
I walked in within. Oh, sorry within 45 seconds. My eyes were like burning. Yeah
I think Jason's glasses are fogging and I sense that you're kind of getting a little sniffly because of this too
I got really close to it. Okay. Also, it's not just if it's just going
I gotta say not just striking the match being a favorite pastime
but I used to love going to bed bath and beyond and I think
Like go into the Yankee Candle section go like oh, which one will I buy today? Oh cupcake
Yeah, I would smell
Cupcake candle for this Yankee doodle damn. Do I do I what?
cupcake or vanilla
and then I
Would take home and I would like he walks up. I would like a candle at like 21 22
I'd be like, I'm I'm an adult. I am buying
home goods
This is for my home. Wow, or my furnishing. This is not just I don't want just a cupcake sniff. We've
I've also I've been having the worst allergies of my Los Angeles life in the last two weeks. Also, it's been pretty bad
Yeah, it's been crazy. Like I touch my I like what is making it because it's windy or what?
I just live with spring and pollen and shit
I think I'm like if you touch my eye and it literally I was driving and it was 20 minutes of just like I need
To get I need to pull over my left eye is unusable because I've touched my eye
Not not you Mike, but Mike D. Guglielmo. Are you happy you have created the most grandma episode ever?
Let's let's trend let's use a bunch of candles to transform the boys into three grandmas. I am jacked. I am thriving
I'm locked in I love smelling candles. Yeah seem jacked though. Um, no, this is some
Jack talking about Bed Bath and Beyond about a minute. I'm just reminiscing about that cupcake can right? That's a different deal
Well, but then I okay, so here's what I know close
Is it from my van it from from over here you have the candle now by your computer it does smell close
I think it was better before the well, that's not what I'm saying
Let's light up this other one unless it's already burnt to the bottom. So what's yours yours is mine?
It was from sense extraterrestrial adventure yours is
extraterrestrial forest
This is magic candle company. This was a gift from a listener a number of years ago and thank you so much
I'm terrible with names, but thank you again for this. Do you want me to light it?
Yes
Down there I got to do it cuz I got I got the Martha Stewart Reacher you got the Cruella De Vil cigarette
Length the penguin cigarette holder looking
extraterrestrial forest features top notes of
metallic and moss
metallic followed by my notes
Middle notes of fur needles and musk all
Resting upon faith notes of balsam and sandalwood. Okay. So now a thing about magic
You know company they have these very distinct wooden wicks
So Scott when you like this be very careful as they have a tendency to pop. Ah
Yeah
Like ashes no way to stun. I have an old
I have like an eight or nine year old magic candle company candle here with different graphic
Smell like anything and this is still smell
Okay, this isn't all this is going on here
I don't think I think maybe some of this I think a lot of the magic is faded over here
You look like you do
I mean you you were saying you only can last five or ten minutes with a candle but you've been really well
You know what it Jane likes to take baths and on the bathroom counter is show light a candle and
Really the candle she's the candle fiend of the two of the candle fiend I would say and
It's like all the way above the wax. I don't know if we're getting any wax on this thing
The heat is melting it for sure
Well, hold on a sec you just lit it, okay. Yeah. All right. All right
So we have to almost like do this in advance and check in on them
We know what we should do is we should have like we should like have hotboxed each other
We should get like a tube of paper towel like a paper towel roll tube
Yeah, and then blow them to each other's mouths get a good idea. Get a big puff of it. Yeah. Yes. All right pucker up
It is vaguely sexual I suppose
It was done that was done to me maybe 25 years ago
Which is done to you
Yes, in the sense that some rowdy your friends did something like that to me and it made me feel crazy
Was it ET smell or was it drugs?
They hot they blew it at you in a tube, yeah, why'd they do that to mess me up? Okay
Yeah, did they did they ask your permission or they don't call? Oh my god. Don't recall Mike
We're unlocking traumatic memories
Yeah, you know you're right. It's hard when you trust that's what's happening here with Mike de Guglielmo is doing this with you
Like you know, we didn't necessarily consent
This is right back to your hotbox scenario. Look three is all not consenting to the top
You can surely by the way Mike you can do that without devices. What do you mean? If your lover?
Takes a hit of a joint holds it in for a second and then breeze it into your like makes out
We know what
You and breeze it into your mat then you can exhale and you will get
very high
Yes, you how much how often?
Oh, not all can you do that once like do you take multiple because one of those seems like it would be a lot
Sometimes you don't get a lot
but the thing that will really mess you up is if you
You know take a hit
Breathe a little out breathe back in breathe a little out breathe back it you will be on the moon
Yeah, but you like being on the moon
I don't the moon isn't so fun for me that version of the moon at least well occasionally
But it's a thing do it outside and then I immediately want to go into my locked home and it just turned on the television
So it sounds like you don't like it either. Yeah, this was described as this grand romantic gesture
But now you've just described coming in putting the lock on wait to make sure no
Yeah next to my loving white like I hang out with my loving what I mean, why was the lock part of it?
Huh, what is what are you worried about with the lock? I don't know other people. I just don't like other people
There's a bit of paranoia in there. Oh
I've been getting robbed while you're super high. It doesn't sound good. No, I wouldn't want it. Yeah, that'd be upsetting
Okay, so it is good though
You're describing a good yeah, yeah, you say it's fine. No, it's fun. Oh, okay. It's fun. Mm-hmm
Okay, watch that watch all of these burning. We don't have to have them all burning at once. We could blow that out
Are we done with this or don't with that one?
Let's see if we can get a good cuz I'm getting I'm getting two smells now
I'm getting two different smell profiles at once. Mm-hmm, and I just I don't want to get messed up
I just have the question that one you were just what you were just what you were describing Jason sounded like a grand romantic
Gesture, but it also seems like it goes straight into watching food that saved America
Will like pull them old mic trip just DJing music videos an old mic trick
Mike invented playing different news for fun. Tastemaker Mike showed I got this idea
I showed him so okay. Get ready your minds about to be blown as if you were getting hotboxed
I thought this was just a nice memory
Mike used to love that people over it is nice you up it is nice
It is but the old Mike trick. It's Mike's old trick. I
Sorry if you've ever found yourself watching old music videos, you don't even know who invented that for you to do me
I did it. I emailed YouTube one day Jason hadn't met Mike. He wouldn't know like 80% of what he knows
You're lucky you met this guy except for that big word he
Town and I go like I do you want to know what synonymous is
Yeah, okay. I think that the first ET candle smells better or stronger than this one
But there's also very
Talked up and I'll bring some of my candles then they come in and there's no wax left and they're all like rusty
There is a plenty of way like plenty of wax has been melted here. Sure
So I'm yes, there's not as much wax as that one, but it looks like a fun campfire. I
Guess it does look like a fun campfire. So magic candle company
They have these lovely large tins that you get to keep these lovely large tins now
They have these distinctive wooden wicks, which like I said, they do sparkle they do pop a little
But here's a tip for everyone now, you don't want to burn a candle usually it says an hour or two hours
Max on the burns before you blow them out. But if you would like to keep the container your candle is in
Put it when the fire is out and the wax is cooled down put it in the freezer
Then the wax will harden and you can kind of chip it out and then you can wash out the container
Or you can pour some ice water into the used wax and that will cause it to break up
Okay, then what do you do in the container? It just becomes why you can put a paper clips in it or a pencils or we?
Maybe knickknacks
Dry this flower. Well, not any of these containers, but maybe some other time have a taller candle
He's right about that. Why this one you could put pencils. Why this would be great for quarters if you need quarters for your laundry
This would be great for quarters. He's right orders could fit in here
Well, this freezer tip is interesting and that's something you definitely didn't learn from Mike
It that's not an old Mike trick. He did not learn that from me
Um, that doesn't smell good to me or like anything these these are not that way
ET ride that one of these I swear that first one smells closer
And this one I don't get a strong Jason is hotboxed himself blowing that out breathe it in like a lover's kiss
Exhale brother, I'll exhale I didn't have I got away from it. Do they have weed candles
Like candles to get you high. Yeah, I don't know not as far as I bet they do
They might have dabs or wax or red sand or they should because what easier way could there be to light something and get high
What would be it's got if only there was an easier way than lighting a candle which is infused with marijuana along with its wax
It's probably dangerous. I don't you want to be sucking that wax
Yeah, I don't know. I can't say if it's just there's plenty of things that say cannabis candle
But I don't know if it's just the smell versus the smell you just want that smell around more. Oh, yeah
Yeah
Is there another compare contract? Well, we can because we do we have to avatar or you have to have it's right
Maybe let's do that because you were you were talking this one up or what you're while yours yours is with a caveat
I'm flying over Fiji, which is the tropical scene from Soren
Ascent that also appears in a flight of pass
It's it's very similar and some of the websites note that they use the same or some of the same elements
Yes, the Fiji Soren smell in for avatar passage flight rise to the challenge
See fuck go relax in your link chair dot
This is if you just the idea that you would just buy this and then like relax in my link chair
Excuse me. I have what does the candle still work? Even if I don't have a link chair Jason's got a link chair
I don't know what that implied exactly, but would you like to elaborate?
Link chair directly to the Oscar Meyer store
I just learned about stocking shelves for Oscar Meyer. I just learned about a new character
Because at the Phillies game the other night
There was a pig running around like a big pig character
Running around with the fanatic and he had a Hatfield
Thing on and I learned it was a BOGO night buy one get one free hot dogs
so
Hatfield I think is the supplier
Hatfield is a hot dog supplier?
You're teaching us a bunch here, Hatfield
I thought we were going to go
Buy one get one free. Oh, okay
Hatfield I think
Wait, where's the free?
Buy one. I think it's just buy one get one. I think the free is implied. I always just said a free
I don't like that acronym that's confusing me
I thought you were going we were going with Hatfield and McCoys
Which is certainly Jason's favorite characters of all time. I guess it's not as usual
It's not as big a company as I thought but it's a Northeast like Hatfield hot dog company. Is there a McCoy company hot dog?
That you could get to. Oh at war? Yeah, no. There was not a McCoy pig taking pot shots at the Hatfield pig
Nicky's the real McCoy hot dogs. It's a restaurant. That's I think the closest we can get to a McCoy's
That's what you know
Candles that smell like rides or smell like avatar is one thing but if Jason could find the candle
Northeast hot dog company
Oh yeah
We're burning through that. We're burning through one of those a day
Yeah, a full candle a day
The I-95 candle company
Can you bottle the smell of people yelling?
Oh, no, I just I just well, you know what your your joke made me laugh and the laugh made me blow out of my nostril
And I blew out the candle
Okay, gotta light this one again. You want to you want to cook up a Fiji here? I just got a burst of
You want to hand Fiji over?
Yeah, maybe hand it because I'm running out of lighter. I'm like like Martha Stewart. I know you fucked up
I'm already like this has been used like seven times. I know my dad's down to the can. I don't know that
God am I gonna have to go in the house and get the long one?
I don't know that you're gonna get though. I got it. Are you kidding me? I know what a light a candle
Okay, it is going. Okay
Fiji is going it is. Yeah, you are you how when did you get this Fiji candle? How long have you had it?
Maybe like less than a year. Okay, they had they had a buy to get one free deal going on right now
So we were looking at new ones to try a BOGO BOGO
BOGO the acronym that uses almost all the letters of the phrase
80% it would be BOGOF
We're running a BOGOF we got a BOGOF here
Well, it doesn't work on this one because you gotta buy two get one
mmm
BATOGOF
And this one went out already well, we're all blowing them, huh
You think Jason did that a very difficult thing to do on a podcast. I think that one's just burned down
This is well, it's down like it's it's just metal. Well, just melt the metal then
Hold on. Hold on. I mean I can get this is certainly a much different smell than the
ETs you can smell that it's much more like this one smells closer to the tropical, right?
Yeah, yeah, but I still you're right. I smell them more before they're lit than when lit
Maybe you got it. Maybe it's got to like fill the room for 15 minutes that it yes, that would definitely
We're just gonna turn this into a five-hour episodes that we have time to let all the smells walk through the room
We often the ones we really like we'll just leave the lids off
Like to let it linger you kind of let it linger in a room. You've got to let it linger got to got to
So yeah the flight so these these should be the same sense because Fiji is the prominent scent on flight of passage
Which Scott and I just went on a couple weeks ago. So we have it somewhat fresh
It was so I was telling you after I was like
I think if I if I got a video of me on that ride now that I am blue-pilled
Oh, I could see what I was doing with my face like from time one doing it to time two
Which is post me understanding the movies seeing the movies
I mean seeing the movies way of water post way of water. I think it'd be a very embarrassing video
I think it would like I look like I'm like being baptized. It was it meant so much more to me this time
Well, I want some fire and ash candles they they're gonna get on the ball by that I just
I wish those screens would be fixed. No, it's not lurry shit on that, right?
We're saying we we just believe that James doesn't know
Yeah, just busy. I think if anybody told him I think we could tell him and he would get furious if we fly a
Helicopter Steve would just land straight in the middle of Pandora. You write it himself in half an hour
I'd land on one of the rocks. Oh, yeah
And then repel down
Yeah, he's got his kit with he doesn't travel without his repelling kid, right?
Yeah, so I am getting this now that this has been melted for a little bit melting for a bit
I am getting a little bit more of a smell
It it's cool I think it's I've been saying that about every candle it's closer
And this is what this is what we've ended up with this episode
It was saying that candles smell like burning. It smells like burning. This is as
Observant as we can be are there really good smell podcasts. They're really good candle podcast. Are there good candle podcast?
That's a good question. Mm-hmm. I don't know
I don't really like candles, but the guys have such a rapport the candle boys that I just yeah
The waxman that I just like it doesn't matter that I don't like candles
They make me like them there is one I
Kept seeing one on like
Reddit or message boards. I think one of the bed bath it no bath and body works candles
smells like that
Fiji
Pandora the very close. I thought you were gonna talk about that bath and body works official podcast
Which could exist which you should be the whole videos were very I don't know if they're still big
But I do remember
Finding like years ago a woman who's like I'm back from the Yankee Candle Store. Check out my hall
I'm back from
Bath and body works. Here's my hall
Soaps and candles my Yankee candle dandy
Do you want to do you want to start drifting to are the ones that are not comparisons because Mike I notice you have a few
I mean one of mine might line up with your biggest one, but I'm curious about your smallers here
Oh, you want to go with my small? I think your smallers. Yes. Yeah, this candle has a lot of dust on it
These are ancient. These are the oldest this one
Your these ones are fresh. Okay, what do we what do we got here?
So these were sent these were sent to me
I think right before we moved and I forgot completely about them
And I apologize because some nice person sent them to me and this is one of the people are so nice
I also a blanket apology to anyone who's ever sent us anything or said like a nice thing and we haven't responded
I feel bad in general cuz I'm like, ah, I'm thank you everyone. I'm so sorry
We can pretend that it's because we get sent 5,000 things right that could be a good cop-out. It's not true. Yeah
So I am trying to figure out what company even made these but we have a
Shark bait and banana breath candle here. Yes, which of course is the jaws and then banana
Breath is King Kong now. I can't really conjure any smells of I don't know. I never went on it. I
Think that along there's some water ride candles floating around the table
the match candle company for their splash candle which
mentions the scent of bromine
bromine
I've also seen dispute. We've talked about that being the
Magic smell on pirates, but I've also seen people be like nobody really knows
I don't know if that's actually ever been confirmed that that's what that is
Yeah, yeah. Well, I might have a little info about it. We'll see when we get to the yeah. Yeah. Here's
The copy contains highly themed notes of damp air and musty bromine water
Hmm doesn't sound good doesn't sound musty is yeah. No, no like that water
Well, we have some we have some stuff related to that, but let's
You want to talk about jaws or or or banana? Well, here's banana. Yeah banana breath candle
Let me go around and smell it before what's been lit
It is banana is hell. It is fake banana
It is extremely
Then that runs down but that's what the you know in the ride or in the in the tour having done it many many times
The right that was definitely the fakiest
Candiest banana smell right the same. Yeah, very handy and I am this might be park sense
I don't know because that's when you look up banana breath that park sense. There's multiple size candles
Yeah, that is called. They're called banana breath
But you also notice that different candle companies use basically the same name fake name for the scent as well
So I'm not let me know if you sent me this candle. So I'm trying to say
Take credit go public you can imagine what this is gonna smell like when it's been lit
It's not been like banana plus burning. It does smell like
My beloved banana runs candy. Mm-hmm. I will say that so on that level. I do like it
I don't know if banana is the smell I want to smell in my house though. No, not really
I don't really wanna I'm not a minion. Yeah, so you know, there's there's that
Well, let's let that cook do you also want to light up you just want to just make this a universal pair
Do you want to light up your jaws jaws and it's gonna be a variant on water?
Yes, okay, let's see that's not a bad smell without it being lit that's that's closer to like Fiji I think
Not particularly
Appealing to me someone I'd want around. Yeah. I mean what smells do we like?
What are our favorite sense is what I would ask in general?
I don't know like like fresh baked dessert in a small spit, you know
If we ever do it at at home a spoiler. Oh, it's not a spoiler cuz my son's not listening
but I think he's getting a cinnamon rolls for his
fifth birthday
Flying over here if you got a test batch, you don't want to throw away
I blew out the banana cuz I swear then you can once the smoke is gone. Then you can really get the sense
Okay, well, maybe that's that might be the way we should have done this
Where I don't where did jaws go do you have jaws is the brand? Oh, yeah, I forgot
Again, this is not a scent that I want filling my house this but this banana one
But I I find it appealing and interesting and it's maybe the most reflective of what you experienced in that, right? It's accurate
Pre-lighting jaws, I kind of liked
It smelled a little is sandalwood the smell that's like a default
For a lot of stuff. I'm not sure I fully know what is and is not sandalwood
I feel like I see sandalwood on every deodorant I purchase. Yeah, I feel like it's kind of a default
Masculine quote-unquote smell. Oh, yes masculine smell. What do you think now? What do you think deodorant wise?
Okay, when it comes to masculine when masculine smell I sandalwood is very much the aesthetic
You know you see with men's stuff. I
I like a little
Smell in my deodorant. I've been a degree man for wait since way back. We got aluminum in that
It's a degree man. We got aluminum in that. Yeah, so it works. Oh, so you are you're doing aluminum. Yeah
Okay, I'm not I'm anti aluminum as far as the deodorant is concerned
They say it might not be good for you, but it
The non-aluminum ones don't work that well. How long do you guys intend to talk about aluminum in deodorant?
We've only been doing it for about 30 seconds. Yeah, but that's maybe a bit too much for me
How long do you think the rant how long do you anticipate the real estate?
Um, I think I got about a minute or two left to talking about it. Okay, that's fine
I could check an email is I do have I mean I want to I want to get Jason sense of this is what I was
Wearing I'm wearing today. I've been wearing it's it's a very masculine every man Jack
And it's it's gel
Needs to decide is it masculine or is it faux masculine? That's what I'm asking that getting it does look like a box of wood
paneling right exactly, so I
Just wanted you don't say it is sandalwood and it is a deodorant in the end. I perspire it
What is the two? What are the two forget what the difference is, but I bought one once
I think that was just anti-perspirant didn't work. Mm-hmm. This is you guys did like the scott-free episodes
This is becoming a scott-free moment Scott. Yes, Scott's Scott's brain is just what brand will you haven't even said what brand you're doing
What do you know? I don't even know or really I literally don't know it's in there. I put it on
I don't know what it is or why I buy that's why I have zero interest in this topic
No, I don't know what I wear or why I buy it Wow really no because this is one of the biggest scent decisions
We make as human beings. I guess you're right. So I'm a decision
I make is fine move on with my day
Well, we don't know what it is because you don't know so we don't know if it's fine
Maybe it's bad who could possibly care what deodorant I wear wife
It's fine. He has no if she's the only person who would or should care and what I pick is inoffensive
Listen in three listeners. I bet are vaguely interested in what it is. I like why smell like sometimes
I'll switch it up and get the old-spice Fiji that one has a nice scent. Okay. Yes. I have done the old-spice Fiji as well
Yeah, that has a nice. That's pretty mild
I agree with you that the non-aluminums are tricky cuz some sometimes they just don't work
But I do feel like this one has been working the sandalwood has been working for me
Is this not a conversation you would walk away from at a party would this not provoke you saying?
You know what? I'm gonna grab another drink you guys want anything?
I'm just a little sensitive little scent boy when I when I was a kid
I know how to I know how to keep Scott on the hook
I'll say little boy about sensitive little scent
That's the way to keep him from jumping into the house to see his baby for a while a childhood memory. I like
Elementary school, you know as kids are stinky old school buildings were stinky and oh
my sense it
Sense of smell I would get headaches all the time now looking back. That's probably because no one was drinking water
Very rarely get headaches in school. We get headaches in school and the sense would like my eyes from the smelly kids
Smelly what was going on in Philly? I know I know kids are smelly
Smelly kids in school. Well, no looking back. I think it was mildly irate irate it
Irritated by smelly kids and then I was just dehydrated
Cuz you'd like take a couple steps at a drinking fountain. Yeah, like that's still
Weird. I haven't been getting a constant headache elementary school unless these kids keep in mind
This is Philly everybody's eating these big old meat sandwiches all that breakfast lunch and dinner
Everybody's it's it's sausage rolls pork and everyone is and bread
So everybody so all these kids smell like like they all have meat sweats. It's all day every day
You're not that far I think maybe I'm on to something it's 1915 and it's a bunch of pig pens
You have to keep in mind they all did have visible smoke or I have it all times
I have one strong memory of a smelly kid and it was cuz he had he ate baloney every day
I need a baloney sandwich in his desk next to me
So he smelled like baloney, but that's the only time so extract that and it's like every kid had a big baloney sandwich
In their desk. Yes, and Jason was going to school. Uh-huh. And it gave the baloney gave him a headache. I
I don't associate baloney with smelling that bad. I guess it was room temperature. It was eating up
Was it like a baloney or something? He's every bit of that makes me
Baloney's room temperature when I said baloney sandwich. She was like, oh that would have made the headache go away
But hey put that in the frying pan. You got you're on your I've never had fried baloney in my life
Oh, it just tastes like a flat hot dog
Did you ever get headaches from the smelly kids in your elementary school? No
You're forgetting. I I all smelling like the beach and so killed. I guess that's true. Yeah, sunny day
I smelled I wasn't drinking enough water. I was a nervous child. I was probably worrying myself
Well, that makes more sense the combination of everything I see I see
But you did present it as there were so many smelly kids and the building was smelly that you were getting headaches initially
That's why I'm stuck on it
That was the thing that I honed in on like I hate that I eat this so much. Let's light up a smelly kid candle
Um, I think I have traces of room temp baloney. This is okay. I'm gonna
Baloney candle there's got to be a baloney candle. We can get you know it
11 year old wearing a mr.
Jason at the life is the jaws I lit it and now I've blown it out and now you got a little of the liquid there
And it is really hard to trait. It's just nothing. I would never smell this and say jaws ride. Yes
I don't know what the jaws ride smells like. So is it supposed to like it's like a purplish wax
Is it supposed to be like blood in the water?
Is it supposed to like kind of blue water and blood is it supposed to be like feed you but it tastes like a hint
of blood as well
Like what does blood smell like Jaws water was purple. Yeah, I don't know
I don't know what blood is supposed to like there's metallic depending on I don't know
Yeah, I haven't smelled my own blood in a while. There's kind of like a pleasant flat earthier smell a
flat earther
No, not flatter like
Saying top notes bottom notes. I'm like, oh, there's kind of a
smell soil soil dirt. It's not a bad smell. I just yeah, it doesn't
Like there's no smell on the
Studio tour section of Jaws as far as I know not that I recall thing because it's outside also would be hard
Yeah, no, so that yeah, that's an odd one to to try to extract
I mean, maybe we should talk about these we've gone through a lot of what we brought to the table
But like just going through magic candle that has the most robust, you know, they have flying over orange groves. That's a big one
We know that's a problem. They have like desserts. They pineapple whip as they call it the non-branded version
They have a lot of smells that are like the the resorts
I guess that's something people chased into what you were saying about yeah, I guess like although they say
actually contemporary and
You know yacht and beach are all the same so they come up with different candles
But I think it's yeah different branding for that is people online have said like oh a lot
I contacted that Vegas scent brand where I was like, hey, what smell is park MGM and they're like, oh
usually the
MGM resorts most of them are all this smell. Oh, I see. So it's kind of united across the board rather than different
Okay, okay
You know Rome burning is a big one from spaceship Earth, right? I don't know if that's something I want in my house
I guess I'm kind of comforted by that smell but do I want it at home not
Simulation of smoke. Yeah, I don't really want to smell that. I think I'd freak out
yeah, I mean I guess what it's not gonna smell like it's gonna smell like what a
Darker tone earthy. Yeah, what I guess something. Yeah, I know you don't want it to smell like char. I
Would assume yeah. Yeah, just like pure smoke. I don't know and then there's one, you know
When Jane was dropping you off she brought up that she's interested in getting one called Walters office
This is yeah, maybe worth addressing for a minute step into a world of creative power
Hello step in the world of creative power
a
Passion and childlike wonder as you become filled with inspiration by our Walters office fragrance
Let the warm and spicy aroma of freshly cured pipe tobacco transport you to the most magical office there ever was
So it smells like pipe. There must have been more magical offices than
Waltz it should smell like bourbon and whatever oil hazel-george used on his polo injury. I that should be the two smells
That's what I tried to make that joke earlier and I couldn't pull the name hazel-george
Okay, I don't know if that would have helped it crush with Jane
No, no linked at you when you made the joke about Walt liking massage. It's like okay. I'm gonna go
But yeah pipe tobacco with subtle hints of honey rose and violet this one
I kind of honed in on because I thought the name Walters office was very funny
But then we've read the actual description. We're like we kind of like all those tents. Yeah, honey rose violet that all that else
Yeah, fine. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know and kind of this like a smoky old man
It's not really a park smell and it's not a smell anybody ever knew besides he and his masseuse
But maybe a Sherman brother or two if they came to him
But other than that, I don't know. I could see liking a smell of this nature
Do you think one of the Sherman brothers came in Walt's office now like ah, you know what?
My shoulders really bothering me today and he goes, you know what? Let me call hazel
I think that's an upcharge. You think so? Yeah. Yeah, I don't think you I think he's handing that out for free
I think you would let hazel work on one of the dick Sherman's shoulder. I think he would give hazel's card
Hmm for more business, but I don't think it would be a freebie and cut into his time
Yeah, yeah, although I don't know if it got the songs cranking out right
Those ivories I'm not saying he's giving out to anyone working. I'm just saying like the Shermans are like high-value. Yeah
creators at Disney
Yeah, no, he should like loose who need those hands. Those are valuable. I have Bob Gurry. He should have loaned it out
Yeah, these keys gotta be knocking those rides together with hammers. That's right
The should have been chilly is part of us also. Oh god. Yes, chilly would have been great
And and maybe so you've got the tobacco thing here and that that does feel like something that maybe you know would have been in
Walt's office and there's a smell that people chase and I I had a thought I was like since we're
Sparking up lighting a bunch of stuff here. Hmm something we could do if all parties here agree
Option that is on the table. I have brought something
It's not quite in the candle zone, but it's something that would have some aromas as part of it. We could gentlemen
light up a couple of
Big old stogies big old stogies. I have three big old stogies with me
This could be our chance to determine once and for all or to order just I'm just curious to see how you feel in
General about like a live big old stogie demonstration. I okay
I'm willing to try it. Uh-huh. I well, I did already say
All it's smelling all these candles has me a little light habit
Well, it might be a bad eyes and noses are irritated. Well, that's not maybe not a good start
But I don't have you could also give it a shot Wow Will Smith
First of all, I don't want you to pass out. Yes, I can of all will Smith in I believe the song Miami
Says he has the cigar, but he doesn't light it. It's just for the look
That is you're recording getting jiggy with it. Damn it. Yeah. Yeah, it's getting jiggy with it. I apologize light it
Yeah, I would have fucking like like, you know, remember how I'd easy on the swears
we don't swear until the most famous swear ever uttered is a
Life television cultivating a wholesome image at the time, but I think Jason should continue cultivating it. He could just for the look. That's true
He doesn't have to do it. I don't want him to yes
Yes, no, no, no that might be that might be that doesn't happen, but we can certainly pass it his way
Well, do you want to like maybe this is one you could just know without all right. All right. Yeah, great
Well, this is great. I didn't know if I'd get immediate objection
I don't know if you'd be upset just that a stogie was produced in front of you because listener if you don't know what I'm
Referring to what I've noticed is that Jason has done a lot of references over the years to a big old
Stogie and you say it with the most hate in your heart. I've ever hurt you you despise stogie
So I'm just curious what would happen. It's very funny to call it that first off and second off. It just comes from like
Years on the beach at the Jersey Shore and yes lighting up the cheapest
Yes, like shittiest and it just well Jason you'll be happy to know that these all cost ten dollars each
I'm sure a great price for a quality
I don't know. I think you're getting gangbusters quality for ten dollars
Down at the liquor store down the street and if and am I I'm correct gentlemen that it's I get them confused
But the the best cigars are from Venezuela. Is that correct?
That's as far as I know cuz that's where these are from. I don't know. Um, you pulled them out of a plastic bag
Well, they were wrapped I had to pull them out to you know, chop the
Right, you got a chopper. I don't I used the technique of scissors
Mike are you going for it? Are we gonna say we're gonna do a live stogie demonstration. Yes, we will
Yeah, it's this thing you I would I don't know the end that I cut I had to look that up
So you and you just from this you just yes puff on it. You don't inhale. That's right. Yeah
Yeah, I mean by the way, you know, no romantic hot boxing. These are
lacumanases
And I'm sure I'm sure a quality brand
I'm sure the best that you could get when you go to the when you go to the liquor store
Well, they're not I didn't want like the little cigarillos
I'm like because I think stogie the spirit of the term stogie is I believe
Like kind of big cheap ones. I think that is what it is the vibe. Yeah. Yeah, what did the groucho smoke?
I'm not sure one
This is a thing this was some of my thing of like Jason's big objection to big old stogies
But I feel like a lot of Jason heroes like yeah. Yeah, you've got I forgot about groucho
WC feels I assume he's got an affinity for baby Herman a lot of I think Jason coded characters
Well, this is the this is the what is it? What's the word?
I'm looking for here that maybe the contradiction where Jason heroes and then as well the steak and bourbon conversation
We've been having a lot of the old-time steak houses
Were frequented by heroes as well
So it's some somewhat more new school versions of some of these time
Traditions look. Yeah, I like it once in a blue moon. Hey, I really like it if I'm not paying for it, right fellas
I think all the objections to steak and bourbon will disappear if the tab is free
We should move you back. Is that just hitting that smell hit me so hard
We don't need the table move Jason back the moment I would I would take a puff off someone's I don't want to
I want you to take that home though and just in the middle of
Conversation with Jane try to light like pretend you're gonna light it up
Candles were a hit. Why don't we go out on the balcony?
This is illegal now under California laws of
How do you know is that your own balcony on your own balcony you cannot smoke in an apartment apartment in a hotel
I don't know if I disagree with that. Totally. I don't either
Although we did stay at a hotel in Napa where it's like was a balcony overlooking woods and there was a built-in ashtray
So it's like I guess it's fine here. Did I think I got it lit?
Like you got it. I haven't smoked a cigarette or anything in a very long time. Oh that stinks
This is one of your favorite smells of the day, Michael. Jason's right
Jason's right
I haven't lit mine yet. I feel like I'm at a golf tournament. All right, hold on. Mike has some outshone
You could drop the mic Mike. Oh
Michael never dropped the mic except when he has a good slam lined up
Now it might have been also though all the flakes are cut it so badly all the flakes are
I
Dropped the right was it the flakes? I have a mouthful of flakes
Oh, you might have gotten the worst what you might have gotten the one I cut the worst
Oh
God this is just a lot
I've just set us up for a live situation where Jason is being proven right look at this
Jason is vindicated here. Look at this is falling apart as I try to just hold it
I think I'm loving it fellas. I'd love just put it in for the fun of it again like the getting jiggy with
Is so good at doing the like waggling a party
About I'm doing that more than I'm sucking on it. No, no, no, no
See go see God. What does he say? What is this cute Cuban? What is it? Yeah, Venezuelan cigars $10
Got him from village liquor. I'm messing up my I keep keep wanting to sing party in the city where the heat is on
That's Miami though. That's not getting jiggy with a better song. I mean, I like Miami more
I think Miami is the better song
Those are all good songs though. Let's be right. Well, hang on just the two of us
Okay, not just see
But the men in black getting jiggy with it Miami trilogy in my mind is is good
It's nothing to be defensive about well, I will be defensive about it
I also you know my recommendation go to the samples Patrice Russian
The whispers and the beat goes on
There's like the shell came off this big cigar, this is not your fault. I gave you the worst one
Shell the protective shell
I'm a turtle guy. Yes. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I'm just trying not to blow this in Jason's face
I didn't do a good job proving my point by getting
Ten dollars. Yeah. Yeah, but isn't but isn't that the stogie spirit? It is the soggy spirit
I agree and I feel like Jason would like this spirit of getting the cheapest thing humanly possible
He's actually another and smelling the smoke. These don't smell too bad
You want it you want to near you a little bit
Dust again blame me here
There's a good
What do we feel about this stogie
What do you think?
Jason's coming around on big old stogies, but we have lost Mike
The worst possible one you're wearing a prank cigar. I've been given you're wearing a brown windbreaker right now
So you're kind of set for that. Um, I
Noticed the pieces. Yeah to not notice all the pieces
I can't gonna hug your daughter and she said she's gonna say daddy. There's pieces of there's pieces of cigar
Did you roll in the leaves daddy? I
think I like like 20 seconds of smelling that but like
Imagine
Working 45 minutes an hour. I would agree with that
I would it does remind I'm like where have I smelled this the most and it is when I go to golf tournaments
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that is where they really come out which have gotten so they when I was a kid
They were a little bit pleasant to go to they've gotten so ludicrously expensive and parking is so insane and cigar spells have gotten really out
of hand and the golf the golf tournament hot dogs have gone from like
$3 to
$25 right bonkers. It's so unpleasant. There was an f1 event. I was reading about I think in Miami and it was like
$300 for fish tacos or something
We could wrap up the cigar portion of the festivities, but you know what Mike while you
Process this and get everything out of your mouth and try to clean yourself off
I think a picture with it to go ahead keep going. Yeah. Yeah
Well, I was thinking I think that you should not have the hate
Well, maybe you know what you just kind of let out is that you kind of like saying the word stogies
And I don't think this is any coincidence because do you know Jason that the word stogie comes from?
Conestoga, Pennsylvania
Lancaster County term you didn't know that you did know that. Oh, no. Sorry. It's just been I'm familiar
I know
In there yeah Conestoga is where one of the first cigar factories in this nation was it's an Amish tradition
And in fact the wagon drivers in that time were called stogies as were the durable shoes that they wore
Why stogie?
I'm feeling cold and tired to grab me a pair of stogies you'd say
I also feel like you should embrace the term because you love a big old hoagie
Well, so it would follow you might also like a big old stogie and he loves bogey Humphrey Bogart
He loves him. He loves big old bogey or Humphrey as sometimes he's called in a while. They call him that
Well, this is yeah, I this has been fascinating how this is played out that I think Jason is sitting here
Like it like calm collected Mike is a mess. You do. Yeah
Destroy the part it's I wish I'm trying to be cool man. I try and I we we might be
That I see a couple more candles on the table, but if anyone wants a clean scent
To kind of cleanse the palette this one
I got and I think it was when the
H2o soap seemed like they were going away. This one is called sea salt and h2o. So that's the Disney brand
That's a Disney brand of soaps which they just bought the formula and put their own name on now, right?
Well, and that's do you and you feel that's a very similar sense. Yeah, I think this is pretty close
They have a lot of varieties of soaps
But I think this is kind of close to the sea salt one. That's pretty pleasant. Yeah doesn't match the stogie though
I'm never smelling anything else again. Get me spider-man
I'm trying to think famous stogie smokers in fiction. Well, he's got to look up all those
Cigar aficionado covers, you know, oh, yeah, David Letterman and right. Oh
Belouche and below. Yeah Belouche Jim
Yes. Yeah, this is well, yeah, doesn't it being in this garage doesn't it?
Kind of transport you to if you were getting to hang with the Belouche himself. Oh, man
I feel like Danny I feel like Danny Ackroyd has a cigar once in a while with the when he cracks a head
Yeah
You know
Light a stogue. Yeah
Yeah, but
No, this was this was bad. This is very bad
I wonder how much we would sense the difference or in G
Do you feel like you might enjoy an expensive cigar and would it even be worth the attempt? I mean would it be worth it?
I mean
For the pictures, I guess for the fun of it. So you post those on Instagram
Guys a high-roller. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Wow. I get those clicks
Like I thought Mike only smoked the human aces
Turns out he'll throw down for cigars. It's true
But I mean maybe I mean look if there was that cigar bar or whatever it was called at City Walk in Orlando
I was a guys with Z. Yes, I would definitely still try one there. Yeah, but it's too bad
We definitely would have found ourselves all lighten up at cigars
Fun episode the Disney Springs
Cigar shop closed not that long ago. Mm-hmm, right and I think it survived all the different
Shopping village downtown at Disney the various iterations. I think it was there for a while
Listeners, there's still a place to get cigars in or near a theme park
Do you know a question is that that would really you know? Yeah
That would become under our purge by the Ben and Jerry's on I Drive is there a store called
Siggy's like a fun funky cigar store or can you get like cigarettes at a gift shop at Six Flags?
Yeah, I don't think so. Maybe six do any characters in Six Flags attractions
Yeah, probably yeah, wait don't they all bugs bunny was like a lot of cigars like to blow up his villains
bugs has a
He should have a like a cigar room wing on his house
And a humidor
Smoking area at Six Flags is they just give you an old mascot head and you just smoke in here
Yeah, that's a hot box. Yeah, it's a hot box. They miss his taz
Pull up a tweety head. This is good. I do like this. I do like this. I don't know that
I know h2o sense. So the smell so far that first flight of passage
I think is the Fiji which I like I don't mind see salt might be the most functional one. I might yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna go up
So I'm gonna go back to maybe let's let's handle these last few these were these ones might be related Mike
You have one that's kind of a common area. I think of oh, yeah
Theme park smell which is pirate water you're chasing chasing the Pirates of the Caribbean water
And then I have one that Mike called out in our assignment as he put it the delightfully vague bloom
I think these are meant to be kind of the same thing because I see some pirate imagery here in flume, right?
But that is about as copyright skirting as you could do. Flume is really mysterious
Is that like a splash mount like magic handle company at splash? This is flume
Well, let's say no because it says escape cannon fire or end up in Davy Jones locker
All right, take your boat to the lady in red, but watch out for rowdy pie
I'm gonna say it with
Watch out for rowdy pirates. You're only after one thing something a ratty rum
I'd love to do bits with my cigar, but it's literally will fall apart in my mouth. So I can't I would love to though
This is cracking apart. It is sort of akin to like just eating a bunch of like breakaway wood
It's like you just put a like a falling apart cork in your mouth
It's like you popped it out of a wine bottle and like it's decaying already you put it in there
Pieces of cork are very nice. Okie. Yeah, I'd love to I'd love to do bits with it, but I can't
Don't do anything
We've already put ourselves on the line for this one. Let's compare it. Let's pass around flume and pirate water. Let's compare
Yeah, your pirate water is as old as the pirates themselves
Dusty but it's been a bunch of how you open the lid and a bunch of powder came out
Yeah, it's very but it has been used recently. So I guess maybe it was just I don't know
You can still smell sort of the gist of it
I've always rubbed the way you're rubbing your fingers around like it's chew
I don't want to like set off like duh, like a dust fire if I light it
I don't know. This is disgusting. It looks gross. Yeah, I agree. So gross. I didn't really I just was closed
So I picked it up and last gross too
It's not
Flume is kind of a pleasant room scent. Yeah
Yeah
Stare this shit down Jason. I think that smells better than flume. Honestly flume smells a little plasticky to me
I do not like I do not like your pirate water
Well, wait a second till I burn all the dust off to it and then maybe the scent will really come might be part of it
I don't make it smell like the Haunted Mansion. This is a whole other area that we didn't get we didn't we didn't get anything like
Ghostly man or yeah or spooky residents or whatever the hell you call the off-brand pirates
So we don't have and what I don't know what smell I'm after in Haunted Mansion anyway, exactly
Yeah, besides the gingerbread house when it does a solid. There is like paint some old
I don't know like it's there's some smell to it that I cannot explain in Haunted Mansion
But you know what we were talking about we were on when we went on Tron. There's a smell to newer rides
Oh, yeah
And I smell it on Guardians and I smell it on Tron and I don't know if I smell it as much on cosmic rewind
But there is some sort of I don't know if it's plastic or new paint smell
Stores in epic universe you noticed on new park. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. There's some new park smell akin to new car smell
You're saying yes, it's it's not it's definitely some artificial plasticky paint smell
That's probably toxic, but I do now like it because of its association with newer theme park stuff
That is I would like a candle of new park smell. Yeah, you guys see the speaking of epic universe. Did you see?
the rumor that
Well, it's not a rumor because it happened but the rumor of how long it's gonna go that the Captain Kakao stuffed animals
Were removed from the stores during some of the previews. I did see this because they were worried they wouldn't have enough
They were just very popular
It's just very cute. Wow only
Remnant of the
Lore if that lore truly is dead, we'll see I wonder if any comes back or if they revamp or
To make it more accessible to a regular person. Yeah
There's a door with a cute tiny little door which is meant to be Captain Kakao's
But then there's a smaller third door built it and I'm like, who's that third door for?
Doors, where are the doors in one of the celestial park shops or restaurants a third door is like dog
Captain Kakao's dog. I guess or is Maya the Explorer little I don't think it looks like a mouse
I look like a mouse. Is there a mouse then?
When I see
The smell old bloom. I almost want like in an industrial smell
I want it to be like this is what it's like to like be a scuba diver who has to do repairs at Pirates of
The Caribbean. Oh, that's yelling it out and spelling Mike. I think what's right about that. Then you got to give it a second
Yeah
Pirates might be closer
to
The ride flu might be more pleasant in terms of like a pleasant plasticky smell
Hmm. Yeah, I I mean this I've smelled this a lot. I don't know that it's the ride
No, I don't know that it smells like the right at all
I really don't think any of these and maybe avatars the avatars get banana breath. Yes. Yes, but it does
It's not I ever want again. No, no, right. So it is
Impossible I think to completely recreate the conditions for which you smell
It's just too vague and it's like even the even if you took the literal smell it wouldn't be the same room
It wouldn't be as lived in it wouldn't be these mechanisms that have been here since
1967 or
Toxic shit in the walls or the water the mold or the who knows exactly what the Legionnaires disease
Events at Disneyland some of it comes from its its smells that are accrued from a time where
coding was different where like, you know, like it was
Looser legally the kinds of rooms you could bring the general public into
I do not like flume
This is funny because I think flumes on my I really for some reason I find it unpleasant
I think I like flu. Do we have it? Does everybody want to pick a winner?
Are we saying what we like or what we think is accurate?
Either one that first was it was this one?
I think it was this one that I like sense which I brought to the table passage flight. Yeah
That's up there
Yeah. Yeah, I am a fan of flume. I gotta say that's interesting like weird blunt one
That was it is presented like a dare by Mike. I don't mind flume. It is weird. It is weird cuz like
there are plenty of sense that are not like
Sometimes if I like walk by somewhere and somebody's smoking I do miss being in a bar filled with cigarette smoke
Even though that is an unpleasant smell and especially when you get home
Your clothes we've talked about this before like in our early 20s
This was still happening and we'd go to a college bar and it was a bar full of cigarette smoke
Mm-hmm, and I kind of missed that smell to some degree. I'm glad that that's not the case
Oh, I see. I'm wondering if that's an Illinois thing because I don't think Central New York
I don't think I ever had that in college. There was no bar full of cigarettes smoke
Did they get rid of it a couple years earlier maybe that's what I'm thinking maybe they passed it early because we go to like
You know, I'm trying to think like whatever downtown
Bar it was just like so crazy how bad the cigarette smoke was in there
Mm-hmm, but then that was gone within a year or two and then by the time I was out here
There's something about it. Yes is like, you know kind of like secondary
Infusion of environment that there is some like, you know, you know yourself
Yeah, there's yeah, that's that's something and like even like a gasoline is kind of a good smell
Yeah, like gasoline kind of a good smell and then well, that's a smell from jaws actually
I don't I don't mind a little bit of distant like a fire is about to start
Yeah in my theme park environments and then like opening a new toy is so
Plastic e or paint smell and it's certainly not good for you. But man, is that a nice smell? Yes
I love that plastic smell
so it is interesting because it's not like I'm I guess well my point is that I'm not so adverse to a
Smell that's weird and bad. Sure. Sure. It's just for whatever reason flume is hitting me and I'm like
That's not so I may be leaning flume weirdly you like avatar Jason of what we sampled here
Passage flight or flying over feet that similar
Apple melon bergamot I think is how they described it
Yeah
I like that smell if that's the agree
I mean I would like round up and say that if we're calling the group favorites the the avatar smells
Yeah smells because you know flume is only maybe I'm only thinking of it because it's recent. Yeah
It's kind of hit-and-miss like we did a grocery store pick up
We end up with all these plastic bags and I was like, hey these kind of smell good and then
I'm sitting next to one and I'm like I need to
Leave the room cuz now I'm starting to feel bad like it's starting to be overwhelming. Yeah
Yeah, and now
Mike would you like to revisit Stokey now that it's been sitting around? What do we think about like?
Rotting for 15 minutes Stokey as opposed to you mean fresh out of my plastic bag stoke Mike
This is brand new or no, I'm supposed to take this with yeah
You got to take that with you because you got it out mid can I have a plastic bag to keep it in?
So I don't absolutely I'm a man who lives to serve take my plastic bag my good man
The burnt part it just smells like a burnt piece of wood or something. Yes. No, this is not good
Not good. I should have maybe gone for but I also I think that the difference between how we all felt about a $10
Versus a $300. I don't think you should have done that
I feel like I see but I feel like I see friend of the show Matt Cardona smoke a cigar in his hot tub
I'm on Instagram or whatever. Maybe if we're in Orlando, I mean, I'm not saying he's gonna buy us to the tub
I'm just saying maybe he knows where to go in Orlando
Could we are you allowed to smoke a cigar on the boardwalk? I don't know
Usually public smoking areas in theme parks, but he but that's the hotel
Yeah, the hotels have a sign smoking areas. Okay, so the answer is probably no, but probably off to the side
There might be a little section on the boardwalk
They try to keep it away from places that are it's like you don't get like scenic views in your smoking areas
Right is too bad. Oh what you'd want but I guess I'd I guess I want to be in those places without
Dense smoke. Yeah, when I stayed at the Beach Club a few years ago
There's was like a lot of reeds and some fountains and stuff. So that was still pretty scenic. Okay
Okay, they let they let smokers look at something besides an alley. Yeah
well, I was looking at the Universal Orlando app and it seemed like they moved the
Smoking area from the dead center of Celestial Park to like the side of stardust racers
Wow, like it seems like where a dumpster would be
Geez they had like a prime spot, I guess dead center of the park
I can't even hold this without it peeling apart. It's so funny that I gave you the worst
There was one where I was like, I fucked it up and I even thought like I should take that one instead
I wasn't thinking I'm handing it out and but it is perfect for you. Like you prank your luck and mischief that you yes
That is true. I wasn't trying to explode you. I swear. All right, and I guess thinker. Um, anyway, I
What one little?
remaining thing is that I got a little I mean one thing we haven't really talked about is like
The process here and and if you know, maybe we have our questions about like how accurate they're able to get but you know
Some of the some of them are impressive and I I just don't know
I
Didn't know like what it's like putting these things together and how these smells are extracted and how they chase them and how you end
Up like how the actual stores, you know that makers
You know what what allows the do they have to do research and how close can they get to the real smells?
Just like what is the process there?
So I went to one of these
Etsy stores I sent just a DM on Etsy to one of the actual doors that makes these things
Yeah, called scent simulations
I sent him a message and asked if like could I just ask you a couple questions about like kind of the process here and
The owner was nice enough to write me back
His name is Beaumont G. Mannheim and he sent me a little voice memo that just kind of like takes us into the process
So this could be education just in terms of like how these you know, what the process is actually all about
Hey Scott, it's a Bo
Beaumont G. Mannheim
And I just want to thank you for reaching out. It's a real joy making these candles
the olfactory glands are actually
the strongest of the
sense memory glands
and the best way to
Reach them in your house through the candle and candles start with wax
There's a thousand colors and a thousand types of wicks
But the wax I would say is the heart of the candle. I always say quality wax quality candle
At scent simulations we use soy, paraffin wax blend, which I think helps you achieve the strongest scent throw
So it gives you a longer burn, but with the paraffin you get those
quality
Hydrocarbons, which really unlocks the strong scent for the hot throw. I always say you don't want to focus on the cold throw
To the detriment of the hot throw. The hot throw is really where the scent lives
Now as far as favorite scents, I would say it's up to the candle maker's imagination
Pirates of the Caribbean water. What you're using is a little bit of a stale moldy scent, but don't worry
It's not actual mold. Just mix that in with hard water the kind that you would find from a sprinkler
You kind of deconstruct that naturally using the soy
The same would go for yacht club towel scent
A candle can really I guess smell like anything. We've done candles that smell like an orange grove
For those of you who like sorin
It's kind of the same deal that they use for that or an ice cream parlor
Calm ocean breeze, popcorn
Even the scent of
I'm coming club three. You can't hide forever
Oh my god
I've guys. Oh, I am sorry
I first I did a poor job cutting the cigars and then I didn't listen to it and no you didn't prior before
I got scent simulations with some kind of sting operation. Whoa, you're tip
The kindly candle maker
Beaumont G. Mannheim the whole time was bug main. Oh my god. I feel so deceived right now
Jesus no way. I felt right it. How did I just happen to gravitate towards that particular store?
I owe you guys a little power. I'm really at that
He's what much like bugs bunny as we've been referring to in his rascally ways
This gosh jeez just like you know the way he's able to you know use various
Disguises to get an omer fudge good graces and then BAM
He just he waltzed right in here as a nice old kid
Wait, I mean what Jason you must have been into were you were you enjoying those tales of candle making?
I very much was enjoying it. But as I was reading this can I was like that's weird. There's no mention of scent
simulations on here
Well, I don't know. I mean, yeah, like it's I it's weird that I didn't end up feeling like I should buy from sense simulations
But that they were the one that I yeah decided to DM and I get I mean, you know, I
Guess if I had ordered one I would have opened the can
I know just would have been just a a little bug with a skittle scattled right out of the canister
This is I'm gonna report this store. Yeah to Etsy sense
Do not buy from do not buy the wind mattress the dream mattress and do not buy from sense simulations because Beaumont G
Mannheim is not who he's a charlatan. Yeah, Jesus. Okay. Well, I don't know where that takes us
I like boy what a what a tease for next month's poll
I know I don't know how that's gonna affect things
But he's got he snuck right in here and I got lit, you know, let's get out of here
I guess for any other yeah, I don't want surprises with her. Yeah, Jesus Christ
Or I have more particles in my mouth from the cigar
Particles in your mouth
My my olfactory senses are working over time as are my tear ducts and now my brain's working over time
He truly can be any yeah, he could be around any corner
Yeah, they're way who know there there could have been guests who've been on the show
Multiple times who were all just like surprise
Yeah, like where we've been planning it for years
Like what if we found out there is no Julia Prescott she and she has been bug main
Oh, yeah guys this entire time Marvel's planning or invasion Jason. Uh-huh. They were they were yeah scrawl, but
Yeah, all right well where I guess in any up there you never know when the book could strike
But if you want to vote for the bug to strike
Next month's poll is on the way. We need your new topic suggestions
And otherwise you survived podcast the ride. Thanks for subscribing to club 3
Your bravery saved the podcast. Well done freedom fighters. There's no panel. It's the smell of
Intimacy. Yeah, it was prime. Oh, maybe I'll work on it. Just a big romantic hotbox you saved our planet
Well done my oh
He blew smoke into the car
That would rule. It's suck my smoke Michael. That should be a fan fest nights
Thing we're only for fan fest you pay the extra money. He blows his exhaust
exhaust at you
But straight from my engine
I've been cooking it up all day just for you, Michael. You're welcome