Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate, a fun, frivolous time full of jokes and frivolity.
No!
This is about rules, hard, fast rules.
This will be entirely organizational, joyless, functional, formal, what needs to happen.
This is basically a Senate meeting.
This is notes.
The committee meeting, yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
No, this is figuring out parliamentary procedure.
I'm Scott Gardner, prepared to be all business and not funny business.
I don't want to hear any from you, Mike Carlson.
Nope, no jokes from me.
All serious chat and serious discussion.
Only serious chat.
Only.
And don't call it shitter chatter, because that's too fun.
Too fun.
Serious chat.
Serious chat with Jason Sheridan as well.
I like a correct, proper offices run.
This is serious business.
Chitter chatter for the break room, and break rooms are different than offices.
No, this isn't.
We are not discussing the best break rooms, the best fake break rooms in theme park history.
We're discussing fake offices, and we're kind of trying something here.
This is basically us trying to expand our big sports programming of the fake office
Final Four with some pre-show material, some pre-game material.
We here are doing something that we would usually reserve for off the air.
This might happen via text messages or just while we're cleaning up equipment, but we
thought you, the listener, deserve transparency.
You deserve to learn how we landed at how we're going to make the fake office Final
Four work, what is within the confines, what is out of the confines, how we determine what
actually constitutes a fake office.
Right.
It's very exciting.
This just felt like when we started discussing it, it was just too exciting to not record.
You know what I mean?
It felt like, well, this is kind of part of it, isn't it?
What even an office could be defined as, I suppose.
What things are, what things aren't.
We don't even know necessarily where we fall on these topics.
Not necessarily.
We're going to find out today in real time on mic what we believe is an office.
In a way, the most real and vulnerable episode of Podcast The Ride, you're going to see into
our process.
You're going to see something that Jason is often desiring to do, which is how the sausage
is made.
Right.
Exactly.
I feel like that usually manifests at just, you just want to say what day of the week
we're recording the show, but we're close.
I think it's kind of that.
It's close.
A little peek behind the scenes and then also, you know me, I'm always thinking about sausage.
The magic of the warehouse.
Your true wish is to see how actual sausage is made.
Behind the scenes stuff is number two, sausage number one in terms of things I like.
Well, I guess that's not to get off track here, but have you ever seen how literal sausage
is made?
I mean, oh, in like one of those Food Network or how did this get made or unwrapped kind
of shows.
Sure.
Yeah.
I mean, it's basically just the filling and the casing.
But you've never been to like a factory.
I don't think I've ever been to a meat processing factory.
I've seen how chips and pretzels are made.
I've certainly seen how Hershey chocolate is made.
In person.
Yeah.
You've seen pretzels being made in person.
I went to a pretzel factory.
I literally went to, not as Simpson's reference, I went to a pretzel factory once.
What are you talking about, the cracker, the reference to the cracker factory?
Yeah, that wasn't a pretzel factory.
That was a cracker factory.
Yeah.
You're thinking of the pretzels on that baseball episode.
The pretzels and the cracker factory.
I'm sure there were crackers also made in this, but I don't know that we've done a long
discussion about the snack belt of southeastern Pennsylvania.
It's almost surprising that we haven't, and that seems like a very viable birthday shot
for you.
I believe it's called the snack belt.
Oh my god, birthday, happy birthday.
Yeah.
But yeah, there's a lot of snack bakeries and factories and stuff around there.
Okay.
We've got to make it to the snack belt.
I'm excited about the snack belt.
I'm trying to find a viable sausage factory tour for you to go to.
I found one in, this looks like Milwaukee, Oosingers, you ever had any Oosingers?
I don't think I've had Oosingers.
Haven't had the pleasure.
Well, unfortunately it says, unfortunately you won't be able to tour the factory due
to food sanitation requirements.
This might get in the way.
My fear is that this is one of the things we lost to COVID, the ability to tour a thriving
sausage factory.
Perhaps.
I know in the Glendale-Burbank border here in Los Angeles, there is a German deli, which
did you go, is that where you inquired about sausages when we made?
There was a different German, more in the La Cagnata area where I got my base sausage
for the Ronto Wrap challenge.
Where'd you get yours, Mike?
Probably like Albertsons or something.
I think I went, oh, I don't even remember.
I do think I got some elevated, some was slightly elevated.
It wasn't as bad as maybe Ralph's, but maybe.
No, I went to Ralph's.
I was trying to make it at like a Kroger.
I was trying to see if I could assemble it with the ingredients you would just buy at
a basic grocery store.
And the answer was no.
It was a thought exercise, not that you just wanted to go to the regular grocery store.
And spend less money.
Well, I did know where everything was, but we all took different approaches.
We sure did.
We did.
If people could make it at home.
Anyway, there's a German deli and like sausage store that I believe supplies some.
Oh, wait.
Like German beer halls and stuff.
I got one, the Vienna, you could, we could all go to the Vienna beef factory tour in
Chicago.
Oh, that's your stomping ground.
All right.
Well, we'll go do, we'll go to Chicago and that'll be our first stop.
That'll be our live show topic in a Vienna beef factory.
We'll do it at the factory.
Yeah.
Shouting over industrial machines.
So anyway, okay, well, we will, we will all together see how the sausage is made, literal
sausage.
But in this case, you're seeing, you're hearing it metaphorically.
So let's, there's some stuff to figure out here.
And I think, you know, I'm not trying to take a leadership position in this discussion,
but I thought that there's maybe a few things worth laying down.
One is I think that we don't need to end this episode having the full final list.
I think we could have most and maybe should have most.
And I think we'll, we'll just naturally end up with what we think are the best fake offices
out there.
But you know, if, you know, you, you want a little bit of extra time to, you know, massage
the details and we need to sleep on it because this is going to be keeping us up at night.
And you want a little suspense maybe in what becomes the final 16, the final more.
That's something to discuss within this episode, I think.
One big thing that I, I believe and that I've believed that I think makes for a successful
one of these final four episodes is a little bit of suspense.
And I think that as we do this, well, not sacrificing entertainment value, we need this,
you know, this shouldn't be too dry, but also as we think of some of these offices and discuss
some of these offices, I think it's also on us to keep it in our pants a little bit.
I don't think if we get too excited about one of these fake offices, it's going to be
too clear that that's the one that's going to go all the way.
I think one that was a little bit flawed, although the episode might've been fine.
But when we started the fake smell final four, there was no question that that was going
to be the ET four smell.
I feel.
Sure.
Yeah.
And I think that in landing on any of the, and now I don't know, I don't think we have
one of, I don't think there is a clear winner here at the outset, so I think it's okay in
that regard.
But I got my eyes on both of you little Spidey boys.
I'm a little worried.
I've got a couple of favorites.
We're going to tip the scales a little bit too much.
Well, how about we get rid of it?
That's in.
Spider-Man is in.
Oh, no, no, no.
I know it's in.
I'm just saying.
We don't even have to talk about it.
Sure.
The fake Daily Bugle building and the amazing adventures of Spider-Man Q is it.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
No, we know that.
Yes.
The other big one, I'll say, is in the Men in Black headquarters, the Men in Black alien
attack.
Yes.
I think some of these, I mean, some of these we spelled out kind of as soon as we were
discussing the mission of the episode.
This came up because of Tiana's office in the line for the new Tiana's Bayou adventure,
which I think that, you know, it needs to be in.
It's very fair.
It inspired the whole tournament.
Right.
But, and I think, and we can keep doing this, we can keep naming specific ones, but I also
think that there's some bigger philosophical debates that need to happen here a little
bit.
When we say office, what does that mean exactly?
And here's what I, and then probably there's some granular definition of office, but here's
something that I don't want to happen.
I don't want that an office that's a perfectly good and viable office, but that's like one,
it's one little one, ends up paying the price because there's another one that's a big multi-room
giant office, you know?
Doesn't that seem unfair?
Do you have an example specifically?
Well, like, think about, like, one that probably should be in is Indiana Jones' office.
I would agree.
Yeah, I agree with that.
But I, now, you know, we'll think about that.
Wait, you mean the makeshift one after the Sala movie in the queue?
Yes, that is what I mean.
Okay, yes.
Okay, Jane and I were talking about this last night because there's a number of kind of
makeshift offices.
Jungle Cruise kind of has some stuff.
Yep.
That's in.
Expedition Everest.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
I think this is a big area.
It definitely is the makeshift.
Yes.
The, like, done on the site, the site of the archaeological dig or the expedition or whatever.
The little pop-up office.
These are some of the strongest contenders, I think.
I think those are very fair and outside of the box in terms of, like, the full Daily
Bugle office, you know?
But I think breaking it down what we hit upon is, like, if there is a desk and there's paper,
you could conceivably call that an office.
I think so.
I think these are important aspects.
Yeah.
And, yeah, the other things, yeah, they don't need to be shelves.
That's in the eye of the beholder, you know, whatever, like, specific other things.
But the desk does seem pretty crucial, I think.
I think the exciting thing, especially in the actual March Madness tournament, is, like,
when a 40 seed knocks out a two seed, like, the 40-rank team, I think University of Connecticut
looked like they were going to knock out number two as of today when we're recording this.
And so I think unconventional offices, wild cards are always so fun, wild card teams in
playoffs.
Certainly, yes.
Now, we have never done things by the, this has been, every one of these has been so ignorant
to the way these things actually go.
Calling it Final Four is not necessarily correct.
Right.
I'd say it's not at all, but it's just, F sounds good.
The alliteration, I think, is the reason to do this.
Here's a rule.
What if, here's one I think we should just set now.
Any commenter who points out that we don't know anything about college basketball is
banned from the show forever.
Is that correct?
Okay.
What if they're new and they didn't know everyone's already said that?
Doesn't count.
Oh, okay.
There's gotta be, we gotta be firm about this.
Okay, I guess, yeah.
You're out the door.
No, but I, you know, yeah, the notion of the seeds, we definitely haven't done that.
But to me, that's also, as soon as you start, because if you've, if you got seeds, right,
and you've got, like, what you consider the best one, wasn't that too much of a preview?
Is that not take away the suspense of, because then you'll go like, well, number one probably
is still gonna make it all the way through, right?
Seems unlikely that these aren't games that are being played.
Yeah.
If there's one that we clearly think is the best office, it's not gonna not become the
best office by the book as we talked about it, right?
Right.
Unless, unless somebody has a riveting argument, perhaps.
This does happen.
I feel like I've done, I feel like we've had it.
I feel like it's happened.
There's been surprises.
Yeah.
Certainly.
There's stuff that comes out of my mouth.
I don't know.
I discover in real time.
I think one thing we could try that is closer to the actual tournament is, like, the collector's
office is probably a one or two seat.
They literally call it an office.
But here's the thing, though.
Does that pair with the weirdo?
No desk.
Is it an office?
There is a desk.
There is a desk?
There's a desk in there?
Where's the desk?
The desk has the excess tech memo on it, doesn't it?
Oh, you're talking about in the like the pre-showroom with Rocket?
Yeah.
And that's, is that his?
That is the collector's office.
Right.
Isn't it?
Oh, wait a minute.
Yeah.
Oh, there is a desk.
Oh, geez.
Well, what do you know?
Ah, okay.
But because they refer to that as his office, that might be in the early contender for best.
But then a makeshift office should probably be paired with that.
It shouldn't just be collector's office versus Daily Bugle.
That's, those are offices.
See, we're already doing exactly what I didn't want.
We're already saying what we think of the best offices.
I think this is what I don't like.
No, no.
I'm pointing at ones that are specifically referred to as office.
Oh, that is what they are.
You're saying the most obvious offices.
Yeah.
Because office is in the, yeah.
Office is in the title.
Well, it's, it's tricky because you could do it how they do it, but that, but the reason
things are structured in a tournament is so exciting stuff happens later.
That's that's the way I feel like, but you know, we don't do things conventionally.
So I don't know.
When we look at this list, we're going to say, well, what does it mean?
Maybe we have 16 whatever heavy hitters and they're all just going to be big matchups.
Yeah, possibly.
I think that's okay.
I don't think we're going to know.
They're all tied for number one seed.
I don't, that's possible.
I mean, this is a thing I think we've had in the past is where we love all of them.
We love all of them equally.
What do we do?
We have to kill babies, you know?
So, right.
So who knows when we see this list, maybe they're all just sort of on equal footing
in concept and in theory.
So I don't think we can decide this until we look at the list.
Can I throw out an oddball that I want to see people's thoughts on?
Is Madame Leota's room technically her office?
With the floating stuff and there is a table and chairs, you know, floating like trumpet
and stuff.
Floating trumpets, tarot card kind of thing.
So like that is kind of where she does her business.
And again, if you were paying Madame Leota, if you were going to get a reading, you would
consider that, huh?
But is there an office also on the Haunted Mansion, is there more of a traditional office
in the Haunted Mansion as well?
I was thinking about this and I'm not so sure.
In the, I guess not the attic, but where are their books?
Well, there's a library, well, because that's what I was thinking, are libraries considered
offices because the pre-show in Terror of Terror is like a library.
Desk, desk is the line.
There is a desk.
Paris, by the way, I didn't realize there was a desk in that.
Maybe it's just, if it's crowded, if I was looking at photos where I didn't see a desk,
I feel humbled and ashamed.
And if you make fun of me for not noticing there was a desk, you're out.
It could be a credenza.
It could be.
It's a very narrow desk.
This is, it's kind of an interesting, desks are sort of odd.
I think the reason you don't see it more is that like, you know, a good mature desk is
pretty, pretty huge potentially.
Yeah.
I don't want to send people into a room.
I think that's why they're often like sealed off or that there's like a little like little
net around it.
Old school, kind of like typist desks were often very small.
Let me bring this up though.
A doctor's office is not necessarily a traditional desk in a, I mean, there's some like, there's
a flat surface generally, you put things on, but it's not like, and there's a computer
often times, doctor's office, chiropractor office, you know, so it's office doesn't
necessarily have to have a desk.
It is where they could do their job.
Now, Madame Leota has got a little table to do a tarot reading or something.
That is technically the office that is if, if that's where most of the work is done,
then you are correct.
She does do her work from within the table is her desk and she does her work from on
the desk because she is a head, depending on the version we're talking about.
So I don't know if there's any language in like official Haunted Mansion lore that says
before when Madame Leota was alive, what that room was, but I suspect it was similar to
what she's doing now.
Can I say something that I think, because this is some of what I wanted to discuss is
the definition of what's in office.
And Jason, you've really thrown me for a loop here because I, I'm pretty stuck on this
one.
It could be.
But like, here's an example.
Here I think is this is the extreme of you keep heading that direction.
I don't think Rise of the Resistance is an office because the stormtroopers work there.
No, that's a military fort.
You mean as far as when you enter the ride the first time off the ship?
That is a big ship.
That's not, no, that's not the same thing.
No, I don't think so.
That just seems, I just wanted to present that as the extreme of the, or keep going,
you know, Oga's Cantina isn't an office because Oga works there.
But you wouldn't say, but if it's a dedicated, an office is just, generally you call it an
office as somebody has like a dedicated workspace.
Stormtroopers do all sorts of things.
They have all sorts of duties.
There might be an office of a stormtrooper in there somewhere, but we don't see that.
Maybe they sleep also.
Where does a stormtrooper sleep?
Have we never seen that in a movie?
We started getting a little, the force awakens, we saw them take off his helmet and do a little
bit of business.
Yeah, you get a sense of where they are before a Star Wars starts.
Yeah.
They're in some bad little...
There might be something in Clone Wars where they're sleeping somewhere that I can't remember.
What's a stormtrooper's bed like?
Yeah, it's probably like a cot.
Is it not like just a cot sort of thing?
No, it's probably kind of no frills.
But we're not doing sleeping areas.
We're doing offices.
Unfortunately.
What about the room where the Rey projection is in the pre-show?
Whose office is that?
Yeah, whose office is that?
That's, I guess, the Resistance, the communications room.
That's a shared room.
That's like a WeWork.
Yeah.
The closest you could say is that room with the plans on the wall where they made a makeshift
office out of, but they would probably say that's more of like a ready room.
Command center?
Command center.
Something like a conference room.
A conference room could be part of an office.
Yeah.
This is...
And we can jump all around.
I don't think we've hashed this out, but another point I was heading for earlier was the thing...
I don't want Indy's office to be punished because it's one mere office as opposed to
Men in Black, which is a multi-room.
You know what I'm saying?
What's the difference between office and office building?
And we have to...
Yeah.
We can't start veering to some just because they're bigger and have more parts, right?
Don't you have to judge them based on what they are and how they succeed?
If it's only attempting to be a recreation of a little makeshift office, you can't say
it's not as good as this office because that was meant to be a big office.
I mean, unfortunately, I think we're going to each have to take that decision into our
own hands when we do the actual deciding.
I suppose so.
I think that's just going to be up to us.
It's hard to ignore big.
It's a lot of what's great about Men in Black is it's big.
Right.
It's going to seem like, oh my gosh, how is anything going to beat Men in Black?
But I think we're going to have to work that out.
That's a decision between us and our God, essentially.
Well, then I can't enforce that as a rule.
That's my own thing I'm putting on myself.
Yeah.
We're getting a little philosophy on you right now.
You're revealing a little too much.
I just don't want to be unfair.
I don't want to be unfair to a nice little office.
Virtuous thought, but I think what is fair in this world, in this deciding world?
Now, a couple of things.
One, there are, like every year, new attractions opening all over the world, and like I feel
like with the fake rock Final Four, a bunch of new fake rocks came out right after that.
So I don't want to talk about hypothetical offices not yet open to the public offices.
I think that's off the table.
Well, we did put the Galaxy's Edge fake rocks in the fake rock Final Four despite them not
being open.
It kind of sank because it's hard to pick something that's not open.
But I think if you reevaluate it while I think those are fine rocks, I don't think it was
ever going to go all the way.
Now, is there an upcoming office that you're excited about or that you feel like has to
be off limits?
Is there an Epic Universe office?
Are there any offices?
Are there fake offices in Epic Universe?
That's a good question.
I bet there's a fake office in the Ministry of Magic somewhere.
Yeah.
Now, that's definitely an office building.
I guess.
And they've teased, I mean, Dr. Victoria Frankenstein's manor.
Yeah, I bet Victoria Frankenstein has an office, technically.
Vincent Various has opened up his workshops to us.
So there's a workshop, an office.
Workshop might be an office.
That's close.
You've got to look at it.
We haven't seen this.
Is that a place you can go in Epic Universe is Vincent Various' workshop?
I believe he's most of the shops and restaurants.
I don't know anything about this other than I know that like, yeah, it's like his, Celestial
Park is his zone for exploring and learning.
But it's also a place to eat pizza.
It's also a place that he's selling pizza as well.
Well, if it's been converted into a pizza place, then it's not an office.
But we don't know, we're talking, we don't know.
This is speculation, just whatever teases and stuff they put out in press releases.
More modern, quote unquote, office is to give credit to the other Spider-Man ride, the web
headquarters in web slingers.
Sure.
That seems to be an office.
It's headquarters.
Yeah.
And now I think for me, what's going against that and that of the web quarters would be
that it sucks and the ride sucks and I hate it.
Okay.
But that's your decision.
That's a personal choice for you to look down upon the office because the ride happens to
be bad.
It's true.
You can assess the quality of it, but come on, we're going to web quarters.
Right now, imagine that, all right, conjure that in your head.
Is that getting in?
I don't hate it.
I think I might like that office and the vibe.
Which one are we talking about?
Well, what do you want as far as office?
Do you think it's the pre-showroom?
That's not as much practical stuff in there.
Well, but then this gets to like, is a workshop an office?
So you're saying it could possibly be the whole thing because it's a whole creative
campus.
Now I like those lockers, I like the little inside things in the lockers, but would you
consider all of that the office?
I think.
No.
You at least have to, if we're narrowing, and I am a proponent, by the way, of narrowing
to 16.
I don't think there's any reason to go past 16.
All right, all right.
I think I'd be surprised.
So if we're tightening up like that, then I think you can't start having something where
you don't get to look into an actual office.
They got lockers?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
I think you have to veer with those 16 to the ones that are the most office-y.
I think this year, too, we're also putting this out so people can offer up suggestions
for stuff we may have not considered or gotten.
Yeah, maybe, but by the time this comes out, they might have already, it might be too late.
But I did ask people online.
Oh, sorry.
Yes.
That is true.
Okay, there we did that.
I will say some people, we did it in advance.
Yeah, okay.
I'll read some of those.
That probably would be a good idea.
I just don't know when we're going to record it, so I don't want to start promising that.
Sure.
Yes.
I will vote.
If there was one great central-looking office in Spider-Man, the California Adventure one,
I would say yes.
But I guess I'll say no because it's too vague.
Did you mean the Tom Holland room?
The Tom Holland room, yeah.
That's a lot of screens.
There's fun.
I like the pre-show fine.
I do, too.
You know what?
Yeah.
But I like the lock.
I like all that stuff leading up.
I like the lockers.
But I guess it's not ... There's not a central, oh, there's that room.
There's fake doors.
Yeah.
Right?
Fake office doors.
But to other fake ... I mean, you can make your argument.
I don't think that counts.
Yeah.
I guess it's out.
I think it's hard to compete as just a door, and we're going to find that here and there.
There are some ...
Well, it's got to be a special door to include it.
Something that people have said is the doors that lead to the flubber lab.
Right, right.
That's in the New Journey into Imagination or ...
Yeah.
But I think ... I don't know.
I'm not sure about door with the fly ...
It's going to be tough to just get it to be a door unless, again, it's a very special
door.
Yeah.
I kind of need to hold ... Over web slingers, I would go with the monsters.
Why Consolidated the Rescue, because don't you go through the ...
This is a big question.
Company?
Yes.
I mean, you're definitely in the workplace of Monsters Inc., right?
Yeah.
And there's that, and there's also, as Paul Durso suggested, there's Ride and Seek in
Tokyo.
Right.
What he sent was like a reception desk.
Reception?
What is a desk?
I don't know.
Yeah, but that's ... Yeah, I think no on reception desk.
Yeah.
Huh.
I think no.
What, is that upsetting?
Well, I don't know.
I hadn't really considered that, but yeah.
I think they're going to have trouble going all the way, because I think what we're going
to start liking is level of detail, level of lived-in-ness about these spaces, and there's
a minimal nature to a reception desk, or there should be, if it's not this.
But Roz would probably call her desk her office.
I don't know, though.
I don't think if you're a receptionist at a doctor's office, you would call your desk
your office.
That would be weird.
It's more of a lobby.
It's part of an office.
Hence my discussion.
Hence me proposing.
Right.
Are we viewing office as a one-room office, or are we viewing it as a big campus?
Yeah, doctor's office, but then the single rooms, like office number, I guess you wouldn't
say office number eight?
You're right.
It's a room that you're in.
And then there is the doctor's office.
When you say you've got to go to the doctor's office, does that mean when you get the meeting
with the doctor in the room where his desk is?
Or when you're getting checked out, is that the doctor's office?
I don't know if it is.
Is this even a problem?
Are there any doctor's offices and rides anywhere?
Oh, that's a good question.
Yeah.
Is there any fun doctors?
I mean, Doc Brown?
Yeah, Institute of Future Technologies.
I don't know if you go through an office there is some of the problem.
We are back, Kids from the Future, there's sort of an office.
Oh, I would love to.
If there is one, then We Are Back, Kids from the Future is in, for sure.
See, you said only 16, because I'm occasionally having trouble thinking of 16.
Oh, you can't get to that number.
So we're back, Kids from the Future.
We are back.
We are back, Kids from the Future.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
People didn't know what you were talking about.
The new House of Horrors, that's the H.H. Holmes, is his office present in that walk-through.
I don't know, we've got to look that up.
I've got to see if there's walk-throughs.
Well, here's what, by my count, there's seven that are in, for sure.
Indiana Jones, Men in Black, Tiana's office in the line, Spider-Man, Daily Bugle, Expedition
Everest, Jungle Cruise, and Guardians, Collector's Office.
Okay, so let's turn to the listener suggestions here.
Maybe Josh Smiley is a good place to start, because it's something that we've talked about.
Indiana Jones, Jungle Cruise, Treehouse, the Adventureland office has always piqued me.
Okay, so there's a Treehouse one.
That could be worth considering.
I've got to look at it.
Let's not make any guarantees here, but Treehouse's office would probably be good.
I am in favor of that.
I just can't place it offhand, but we should all look at it.
Is there a specific one, like in the Tarzan version, or in the Swiss Family version, or
the new version?
That I'm not sure.
Oh, well, that I, yeah.
Well, this will be a waste of time to figure it out, but we'll put eyes on the Treehouse
office.
Hopefully a Treehouse office.
Do deal with it.
I mean, yes.
I like that I've done it.
Have you guys, you have not walked the new Treehouse yet?
I have not, no.
Neither of you have.
No.
I've done it a couple of times.
I'm a big fan of it.
Really?
Great.
Better than what was there?
Better than original?
I think it's, well, I don't know about original, but I like a lot what they've done with it.
Sure.
And I think it's fun.
And I do think it feels, it feels fresher than Tarzan felt.
You don't say.
In the year 2020, whatever.
Pan flute instrumental.
Yes.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
There's a lot of nice touches.
Again, I'm glad it's still there.
They figured out a way to save it from the nudge.
Yeah, really.
I'm surprised the way is just adventure land treehouse.
It's weird.
Inspired, again, we'll talk about that on its own episode, but like inspired by Swiss
Family Robinson.
I don't know why.
There you go.
That's what it says.
Anyway.
That's a real like, and this movie is not about Buzz Lightyear the toy, it's Buzz Lightyear
the man.
Yeah, yeah.
If there are any great offices in that movie, I guess those won't make it to the park, unfortunately.
Candy TV.
Badger's office in Toad Hall.
Yeah, that's, yeah.
That's like right when the ride starts, right?
That's like one of the first rooms that you go in.
Yeah.
I mean, should we?
Is that a library?
Well.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I think if you got a desk and somebody's working at the desk, oh wait, full quote, Badger's
office in Toad Hall is solid, just needs to fix that suit of armor, that's what Candy
said.
Because it keeps falling over.
Always.
I mean, again, I don't want to, you know, we can assess some of these, we're going to
have to bounce some at the end.
I mean, if you want me, there's, I have immediate reactions to it.
It feels like you don't want that.
No, I do want it.
Oh, that's you wanting it?
Oh, I want it.
Yeah, I think I might too.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
What?
I don't know why I read that as like, I don't know, I don't know.
I was being, I was trying to be like, oh, should we, should we reveal it later?
But I guess, no, I'm in.
I don't know.
We've got to be efficient here.
You were going through your mind palace to try and find a room.
I was, yeah, walking through it, strolling.
Ben Donan, Jimmy Fallon is set in 30 Rock and most of the theming is office core.
Yes, but.
Yeah.
I think you don't have an actual room.
It's not that I recall, right?
Oh, that's a question.
Is the, oh God, what are the names of the?
The B-sharps.
No, it's not.
No?
No.
Oh, fuck.
Nor is it the Depperdans.
No, because I didn't have it in my head either.
It's the ragtime gals.
The ragtime gals, thank you.
Now, is that room where, is that the ragtime gals office?
No.
Because that's where they do their ragtime, their acapella work.
Just checking.
I don't even remember a card table.
I don't believe that either.
Animation Academy comes courtesy of Ethan Bradlow.
Now, here's the whole thing.
There's a lot of real offices in various and especially behind the scenes kind of a tray,
animator desks in the magic of Disney animation, but real offices are not fake offices.
However, the Animation Academy in California Adventure, where you do a little live show
presentation, that is an animator's desk.
There's a bunch of books.
Yeah.
There's a big, there's a very like 2001 computer screen.
Real HP is what I'm looking at.
I mean, I don't know.
I think that's an office.
I know some of it is where we, the audience, sit, but at least this wall is an office.
Yeah.
I think that's a great suggestion.
Okay.
But let's say that's in for now.
I think we're just building a list of possibilities.
Yeah, sure.
Maybe we end up bumping something here together or that happens between now and the main feed.
Right.
The main event on Friday.
Okay.
Let's see.
Well, maybe now we get into, oh, here.
Well, how about this?
Journey to the Center of the Earth from Jason Muir also has a kind of a, that's more in
the realm of like makeshift.
It's a little one knitted off in the queue.
Yeah.
I'd have to look at it to be sure.
I looked, I did a little glance at it.
Okay.
You think it's in?
I think it's in.
I think it's nice.
It's a nice one.
So now we get into, this is something that we talked about, I think maybe when we first
had the idea, one that's near and dear to my heart, Tony Ricotta, Tony Got Awesome,
Mickey Mouse's den where he goes if he needs to make a call.
Of course.
Hmm.
Is a den an office?
It is a home office.
Look, I looked up the definition and it certainly can share a lot of the functions of an office,
a den can.
So I think you could make an argument that he does a lot of the same type of business
that Mickey might do in an office.
Yeah.
Look, if he needs to make a call.
He uses a den.
He uses the den.
But it has the desk, it has his stuff that he works with there.
I say yes.
I think it's at least on the, what do we call the preliminary list?
I think it's on the preliminary list.
At the least it's on that, but yeah.
Just Mickey calling AT&T, my bill went up for no, I don't quite know why.
I thought it was locked in price wise.
This is a question I have in general because I have two other suggestions here.
Because of space limitations, just because somebody doesn't have a big house or a big
living area, they're going to need a little section of rooms to do work.
So are they allowed to say this is my office even if it doesn't have four walls, even if
it has things in there that might also be in a part of another room if you had a bigger
house?
Well, you know, wouldn't it be the post COVID Zoom era in order to say yes, that we've all
had to make makeshift offices in odd spaces?
What are you specifically thinking of here?
Well, Minnie's house, Minnie has a room that has like her dressing kind of table and like
kind of a chaise lounge and it has a desk with computer.
That is a room where Minnie is doing her work.
Her computer is right there, but it is also her like dressing or her bedroom to some,
I don't know if it's her bedroom, but I'm saying she's doing office work in there.
Why would the computer be in there?
It's a whole office.
It's something of a home office.
I mean, if you're going to count Mickey's, then maybe you got to count that.
I was ready to say that it feels like more of like a parlor.
That computer though.
But the computer does shift.
That's where she's doing her work.
But she doesn't have the luxury of space for some reason.
Hopefully Mickey should have taken care of her and given her a bigger house.
But he didn't.
I don't know why.
But he still, I mean, it is very generous.
Well, first of all, you're making an assumption that he bought her the house.
I guess that's true.
But they lived there before in the lore of Toontown, I suppose, now that I'm thinking
about it.
They just happened to live in Anaheim and then they finally opened the gates.
I've got my own money, Mickey.
I don't need your blood money.
Her hands are clean.
It's the ultimate gift than any.
If they are married, and this is unclear, but if they are married, the best gift you
can give to your wife, a separate house next door.
A separate house next to yours.
I guess that's true.
But maybe they're not married in the in-park Toontown canon.
I don't think they are.
Or they started dating and they had the separate houses and they thought, well, let's essentially
move in together.
But why would you have less space?
If you own, if you both own, keep your house.
If you both own and if your houses kind of look like you physically, maybe keep the house.
Yes.
Now, this same sort of line of thought, let me take it a little farther, is Walt's apartment
on Main Street in office.
He would do work.
There's pictures of him on the phone in there, obviously also pictures of him entertaining.
He would sleep there.
He and Lillian would sleep on separate parts of the couch.
That was a multi-purpose studio apartment, essentially.
So there was a little area with a desk.
You can see in this, at least this picture, where he's on the phone, where he would do
his work.
But that's a real.
That's real.
Yep.
Jason's got it.
It's real.
I guess you're right.
It's not fake.
Damn it.
I guess you're right.
Office, yes.
Fake, no.
He would actually do real work.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
You're right.
Is there a fantasy version of Walt when you go in there?
Is it a fake office now that he's not doing real work in it?
The lamp is fake because they made it up two years ago.
Well, that's right.
But I'm just saying, now we are celebrating the fake Walt Disney up there.
It's too heady.
I don't know.
I'm going to think about it.
Here's a coming soon office.
The Walt animatronic appears to be in the recreation of-
Oh, from his office.
That is a very good point.
That is a simulation of Walt's actual office that is hermetically sealed.
That is true.
Interesting.
Good point.
Walt Disney animatronic.
That is an office show.
But that doesn't, we can't see it.
It's not real yet.
So maybe-
Right.
And what if for budget purposes they cut the set and he is not in his office anymore?
We got to get this chalkboard out of here where we're spending too much money.
What if he's just sitting in Lincoln's chair and he stands up and it's the same backdrop?
To save money.
He's sitting on Lincoln's lap.
We cannot move this.
He would like to spoon hydraulic fluid.
Well, they could have got budget cuts.
He's just passed out.
He's sedate.
There's a little trail of drool coming out of his mouth.
Yeah.
That would be fun too.
Now you raise a very good point here.
I feel like, I consider this more of a backdrop than an office.
He's leaning against it.
It's kind of a one wall of the set and maybe not even the full wall.
I might bounce it, A, that it's concept, that it hasn't opened yet, so we haven't been able
to really breathe it in yet, but also I just think it's not going to have what it takes
to go all the way because it's ultimately, it's just too one wall.
I just don't know how that's going to survive.
Yeah.
It's a nice office though.
I would have to see it in person.
That's the only thing.
Yeah.
I would have to see the final thing.
Honestly, there might be a lot of curtains implying a room.
Perhaps.
It might be him leaning on a credenza.
Perhaps, yes.
And one blueprint as opposed to that kind of more elaborate stage picture.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, it's something to consider, but that feels like it's teetering on the edge, I think.
Let's see.
Let me go to, I think there's another one in the same screenshot.
Oh no, that's the den.
I think this is probably the time to open up this discussion because Randy Renstrom
asks out loud something that we're going to have to talk about at some point, and it's
this.
Do labs count as offices?
If so, avatar flight of passage.
I believe.
Are labs offices?
Yes.
Okay.
I think so.
Well, I think that one, there are desks with papers shattered.
There's so many desks in that one.
Yeah.
But you get into, is a lab an office?
Is a workshop an office?
Yeah, that desk is a big, might be the deciding factor.
I think we're going to have to look more closely at that queue.
We're going to have to decide.
Well, I think that's right.
And I think, I mean, if it's a lab and it seems like people just kind of float in and
out, there's certain labs, I assume, where it's like, there's not a great sitting area.
You go in there to do just the work of lab work.
But then there's also, yes, the avatar one, it seems like it's lab hybrid office.
It seems like it's half and half.
You do your work in there, but also you could maybe run an experiment or two.
There's so much desk stuff, so much stuff on the desks.
It seems kind of a hybrid of lab office to me, that specific one.
And I bet a lot of labs fall under that category.
Okay.
Fake labs.
Because it feels to me like either they're in or they're out.
If we have a 16 that we like that doesn't include labs, then maybe there's no labs.
But maybe the labs deserve to be in there more than some so-called offices.
Yeah.
It might be like if a walled animatronic fake office were representative of the soon-to-open
And there was one like avatar lab is representative of labs.
Yeah.
You're saying only one lab.
The best lab represents the sector of labs.
That has a lot of-
What about like it's Dr. Seeker?
Have we seen any Dr. Seeker lab and dinosaur?
Do we?
I don't think so.
I don't know if I'm saying it out loud.
Well, here's another question, and I know my personal answer to this.
Do these all have to be physical spaces?
Or if there's an office that's really good that's like in a movie or a video that you
watch, does that count?
You have an example in your head, I think.
Oh, do I?
That's what I assumed.
I don't know that you do.
Well, how about when you fly into the office building in Transformers, you whip through
that floor in and out?
Oh, I never even thought of it.
I was looking for a good Transformers one, but that is an interesting office.
That's a real office or only like skyscraper-y type office.
But I think it's out because I want physical spaces.
I don't want it.
I think just like now we're in a different area.
Now we're in like set design, production design of a movie.
Yes.
It's fun to have more tactile.
I would love to put it in the maybe pile right now though.
I'll put it in the maybe pile.
To not completely take it out of the equation.
Doc Brown would go also in the...
Because you don't really go into his office, but you see him trapped in his own office.
So that does that...
I don't know.
It just feels like a different genre.
Footage feels off, but is there an office room in the Transformers queue or is that
Military Fortress?
I think Military Fort is out by and large.
But I am...
Because we're no fans of war.
That's right.
I am sitting here racking my brain about like there must be some sort of whimsical office
in Islands of Adventure.
My beloved Islands of Adventure that I am forgetting.
Like Popeye's office?
I was trying to think if there was a cartoony office.
Now there used to be an internet cafe of course, but that was real.
Is there something in Port of Entry or Poseidon's Fury?
Probably out of makeshift Adventureland-y kind of office.
Poseidon's office.
No, no, like Taylor, Taylor and the doctor.
But is that an excavation site?
I have to admit, I like that attraction.
I did not have Taylor at the ready.
I knew about it.
Taylor is the team member who guides you through and it's always stuck with me because it's
gender neutral.
So it can be a guy or a girl.
Oh, sure.
Whoever's playing that part.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
I got to think on this.
According to John the Mon, Bluto's office from Popeye and Bluto's build rat barges.
He's even got a cannon shot through the wall that goes through multiple walls and ends
up in a pole.
Oh, well then that's in.
Okay.
Yeah, Bluto's office.
I knew there was something there.
Bluto's office.
Yeah, and look, I don't want to tip it, but Jason just, we found our winner here.
Guys, I said keep it in your pants, boys.
Okay.
Another does this count as an office in the lab territory comes from Amanda Hasaka and
that is the lab of the cool seventies spaceship earth woman.
Yeah.
She has a computer in there.
I forget.
Well, it's a bunch of old school computers like the, you know, the big old light up machines.
This looks like a dedicated workspace for her.
I got to say there's a phone, there's a light, there's a ledger.
It's in.
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, that one's.
Yeah.
Great.
I feel like a fan favorite.
Fan favorite.
But wait.
But I didn't say necessarily.
Cool girl office.
Okay.
Another one.
This is a, this is kind of a mini one in a queue.
This is from a Jacko B graphic who's related to wall to see graphic is a little avatar picture
and they're so fittingly Muppet vision security office.
What we see here is a different genre kind of, right?
It's a security office.
It says back in five minutes.
I can't read whatever the sign gag is.
There's stuffed Muppet babies between the bars and we're losing this baby soon.
So it might be a nice way to honor.
It's pretty small.
You got some, what I like is that I think we're going to be looking at like how lived
in are these.
And here you got like a coffee.
You got a banana.
Oh my God.
Wait.
And if security offices, then there's a one that I love, which is officer Zizek's.
Oh, right.
Reads you at the end when you arrive from your start to his flight in Japan.
Right.
And then I also go is Tony Solaroni's big mechanical is that that is his workstation.
Do you consider that an office?
I don't know.
What is it?
It's just this weird machine floating, helping make the weird machine.
Yes.
Pizza.
It's a big pizza sorting machine, but it is his desk and it is where he works.
Yeah.
Is it a whimsical?
Because if you were working in a factory, you wouldn't necessarily say you were working
in an office.
Yeah.
It's more factory-esque.
I guess.
Yeah.
Sadly.
Maybe so.
It's a workstation, but to workstations, especially if it's shared, you know.
Let me.
Although my sense is that Tony Solaroni does it all himself and that he has to pull 24
hour shifts.
Probably.
And his wife calls and yells at him for never coming home.
That's probably right.
Let me ask this question.
When you're on Space Mountain and you see a human being as your ship is going toward
the lift hill and when you're going to take that right and you see a human being in that
little office above, I believe that is a practical place, but I also kind of imagine it is also
thematically made to think that you are seeing somebody that's going to send you to space.
It's both practical and it is also suggesting to you, well, this person is sending you into
space.
So in some way, it's not a real office because it's mechanical.
It's for the ride, but thematically, it could be potentially a workstation for an astronaut.
I don't know.
I think it's too much actual function of the ride.
Too practical operations.
I'll say you don't see in there.
How's that going to survive?
We don't know what's going on in that room.
We don't.
So we have to imagine.
So I'm just asking questions.
No, no, no.
It's worth bringing up.
Certainly.
That's what we're here to do is to debate.
Do we think Muppet Security Office in or out?
I think that's in.
Yeah, that's in.
I think I need to look.
I might still put it on a maybe.
I'm going to vote in the maybe category because I think there's better ones.
But I think maybe too for Officer Zizek's.
Yeah.
I got to remind myself what that looks like.
Now, this one's going to be tough, I think, for anyone to make the call because it's kind
of where I'm going off of one weird old photo and seeing it on my laptop is not going to
give you guys the sense of it.
But this is from Traveling Salesman at Open Mother's Mail.
H.G.
Wells' office in Knott's old Kingdom of the Dinosaur's ride.
What other fake offices have time machines in them?
And I will show you this very cartoony mannequin.
There's a bunch of tubes.
Oh, hell, you know what?
The longer I look at it, it's in.
That's good.
It's in.
It is good.
Shelves, desk, it has everything you want.
It's not made by one of the primaries and it's maybe not a ride that we know incredibly
well, but aren't you rooting for underdogs in this thing?
Sure, of course.
Here's a real 16 seed, but I think it might have the gumption it needs to take it all
the way.
Maybe it does, yes.
I'm voting for H.G.
Wells' office.
I think so.
What about a couple of ones here, thinking about dinosaurs.
Dinosaur, the Institute?
I don't know.
Is that more museum?
I mean, it's certainly a museum, but is there something in that?
That's what I was actually hadn't thought about until just now.
We see footage, but yeah.
I don't know that you got like a real workspace in there.
I could be wrong.
I don't have it memorized by any means.
The Google image is not providing anything too satisfying.
I'll zip through the YouTube to see.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Okay.
Other dinosaur office, Jurassic Park River Adventure or Jurassic World Ride.
Is there anything in those?
I don't know.
Now I'm trying to think.
Do we get more into the command center that is thematic, but also practical like Mike brought
up?
I think we're in the security zone.
Yeah.
I mean, security is kind of a weird area.
It really depends on if you can see in there.
I think that's what's really going to ... I just don't ... You know what?
I don't want to waste the time of these competitors if I feel like they don't have what it takes
to ... I think you just need to be able to see stuff for it to be able to compete against
hyper-detailed offices.
I think labs and home offices and libraries I'm sold on, I think labs and security offices
I need to see.
It depends.
It's like a gut feeling.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
We'll only see.
Dr. Seeker is in a lab slash office in the pre-show video, but I don't think there's
a great practical part of the line.
But that's footage.
It's a cool-looking office in the footage, so you could make ... I would put it in maybe
perhaps, but it's not ... What do I call it?
Dinosaur?
Dinosaur lab office.
Okay.
I mean, he's got a workstation.
It's a big room, though, too, so I don't know of many multiple people.
It's more of a we work ... I don't know.
It's tough.
I'd say maybe, and we'll revisit it.
It's possible.
Let me show you Officer Zizek's ... I mean, it's kind of a more robust room than you might
expect.
Yeah.
It is a spacey future desk.
However, if you put this in, does this not set the precedent that you would put in the
Patrick Warburton droid from the Star Tours line, and that doesn't feel right to me?
I would say no.
That's not right.
No.
That's glorified TSA.
Yeah.
But does this feel more ... The fact that he's got snacks and stuff.
That feels more like a Space Age cubicle.
Yeah.
That's true.
It does.
I could see that going in.
I'm more likely to say Zizek's than Tony Solaroni.
Yeah.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Right.
Getting some Japan only is good, I think.
So we're saying maybe Officer Zizek's?
It could be ...
Maybe Officer Zizek's.
Yeah.
I'm going to put that in the maybe.
I'll put that high in the maybes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here's maybe an oddball.
It is the Batcave Batman's office.
Well, you're talking about the Batcave, you're not talking about Bruce Wayne's real office.
No.
Those are two separate things.
Right.
Now, there's Batman rides all over the world, some more detailed than others.
That's true.
There are representations of Wayne Manor, and I feel like there's representations of
the Batcave.
Uh-huh.
It's got to be the right ... Now, look, I think something going against it right away
is that none of us can conjure one of these in our head.
Yeah.
It was really great.
What is even the best Batcave in the world?
Is the one in Dubai?
That's a very good question.
It might be, but then who really knows ...
Yeah.
I don't know.
Okay.
Hall of Justice.
Is the Hall of Justice the Justice League's office?
Justice League.
I don't think so.
Buildings.
They're that cyborg animatronic.
That's not an office, though.
That's more of a receiving room.
It's a big room.
Unless there's ... Unless there's something I don't know about that's Aquaman's desk.
I want to see Aquaman's coasters.
Yeah.
Scott, we would know if there was an Aquaman somewhere.
Come on, now.
Yeah.
I would hope.
You've dreamed your whole life of seeing Aquaman's desk.
Aquaman's wet desk.
You can't be too picky with that wood.
That's going to work.
Oh, that wood is getting worked in a week.
Yeah.
Let me see.
Oh, I feel like I had a few ... Oh, oh.
Now, you know what might be an office?
You don't really think of this as a ... But there's a desk, and there's a lot of books,
and I'll tell you what I'm talking about.
I really got to stare at this ride through again.
I think Bowser has an office in that fortress.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
The particular video I was watching was so zoomed in and focused on details that I got
a little bit disoriented.
Again, I try to miss that queue as hardcore as I can if I'm getting on that ride, but
I think everybody agrees that while that ride has a lot of issues, that the queue is pretty
spectacular, and the parts of the queue are spectacular.
Would that not be an interesting way to honor ... Should we leave this at, we'll discuss
after, but if Bowser's office feels worthy, if we all decree after the fact?
Yeah, the queue's really good.
I think that one is a good representation of what I was searching for with the Batman
and Justice League, which is I don't think we can eliminate whimsical offices.
No, they might be ...
Be it officers' ex or Madame Leota.
We have not really landed, I would say, on a call on Madame Leota.
Maybe we'll have to hear the whole list, and we should maybe be heading for the door so
we can actually yay or nay these things.
Maybe some will remain a debate, and then there's the suspense for Fray and I was going
to strike midnight on Friday, and people will be wondering, God, where did they land on
H.G. Wells?
Yeah, of course.
I hope anybody's able to get some sleep.
Restless nights.
Let me add some others.
I did the YouTube screenshots.
There are definitely offices in Zootopia, in the new Zootopia, or H.G. Pursuit.
Now it's a desk, but it's cartoony desk.
I'm not sure whose desk we're looking at here.
It might be the Fox's desk.
I don't know.
It is a desk.
Yeah.
I don't know if anyone's excited about it.
I think cubicle counts as desk.
Certainly desk.
Certainly, I'll say office and put it on the maybe for sure.
Yeah.
It might just get bumped due to unfamiliarity.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I mean, Zootopia is so much of like a mundane life, so there's so much-
True.
It could just be disadvantaged in that regard.
Right.
Less whimsy in some ways, even though it's animals.
Is there an office in Mystic Manor?
Oh.
Ooh.
I think there is.
I believe so.
Well, then I'm going to have to put that in the file of need more information, because
I'm sure whatever it is is very cool.
I just don't want to make you the listener sit here while we flip through ride videos.
That's a very good thing to consider.
This is also a little bit tough to ... I'm just showing you a YouTube thumbnail.
Ghost Town Alive, Knott's Berry Farm.
That's a whole other genre of office is the old west office, the office showing you what
offices used to be like in the past.
Right.
Hmm.
I'd have to really get a good look at it, but I think you want diversity here, right?
You don't want all modern offices.
You want a mix.
You want comic book offices going up against old west offices.
Yeah.
Wouldn't that be fun?
Whimsical animal office versus simulation of office of the long ago past.
Right.
I feel like ... Are there any offices in ... I was trying to think if there are office representations
in any restaurants out there.
Are there anything where this room is meant to be an office?
For example, is there an office somewhere in Skipper Canteen?
A lot of rooms in Magic Kingdom.
Is the secret room, is that a secret office?
That's a good question.
It's a lot more in the den study kind of area.
Right.
I'm not really sure.
I don't know the rooms well enough.
Yeah.
Well, like see stuff, like see society exploring adventures.
I was also looking around Tokyo, see stuff, and I didn't really see anything.
Are there any offices in Pirates of the Caribbean?
Like are any of those places where the skeletons are kind of offices?
I don't think so.
I just thought I'd ask the question.
Again, I would have to look, but Confisco Grill at Islands of Adventure at the end of
Port of Entry, it shares a lot of whimsical qualities with Port of Entry, and there's
representations and artifacts from many of the islands.
Is Confisco's office in there?
I know you want it bad, but you really ... We can't.
We have to be honest here.
I know.
We'll have to look into it.
So we're going to have to make a separate list that's like the to look into, to look
into it very strongly.
Right, right.
Because yeah, some of these are just ... There's so many things and some things you haven't
even considered before we start recording.
Yes.
Yeah.
If you go, oh shoot.
Does Dr. Doom have an office on his Fearfall?
You are ...
He might.
You are in a Latvarian embassy.
Right, but he should have an office in there, right?
So there should be offices.
Yeah.
Because there's some fun stuff in that queue, short, but perhaps we had to look into that.
I might be getting to the end of my questions.
I think I'm getting close to ... Let me make sure I'm not missing ... Oh, oh.
Maybe one big question here.
Would we ever consider including a fake recreation of the Oval Office?
These exist in presidential libraries across this country, and I've been to a number of
them.
I've been to the George W. Bush Presidential Library, and I liked that you're in that Oval
Office, and it has a view of a nearby Twin Peaks, the sexy restaurant.
You can see that from the window of Bush's Oval Office.
There's also a Reagan Oval Office in the Reagan Presidential Library.
Sorry, where is the George W. Bush?
It's in Dallas, Texas.
But the Twin Peaks ... When you look out the window, you can see a sign for Twin Peaks,
the sexy restaurant.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was thinking about the Double R Diner of the city of Twin Peaks, the town of Twin Peaks.
Oh, no, no, no.
I mean ... No, you're talking dirty restaurant chicken.
Yes, that's right.
They call them restaurants.
Restaurants.
That's a good term.
I forgot that term.
Yes, indeed.
Yes, that's what they call them.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember.
I think there may be a fake Oval Office in ... Maybe there's an LBJ Presidential Library.
Would we ever have one ... I think we could pick one of the bat.
Off mic, we'll figure out the best fake Oval Office.
The best fake Oval Office.
Oh, okay.
It looks like ... That could go in there.
It looks like Nixon.
It looks like LBJ.
Reagan.
Carter.
Yeah.
Truman.
A lot of them have.
George H.W. Bush.
George W. Bush.
Clinton.
There's so many, but how do you begin to determine which one's the best?
I might say the best one would be how many restaurants can you see from the window, but
there's a lot of criteria.
Conservative pollster Frank Luntz has an Oval Office in his house.
What?
Yep.
Look it up.
It's big, too.
That's so dumb.
Yeah.
Sometimes.
Well, I kind of want to go with that one.
Maybe that's ... Frank Luntz's Oval Office in his house.
Frank Luntz's ... Frank Luntz, here he is with his Oval Office in his house.
The picture.
Here, he's recreated the Oval Office.
Oh, it's that.
It's definitely that.
Okay.
It's Frank Conservative pollster Frank Luntz's Oval Office.
Wow.
Yeah.
And it's okay.
He's modeled after Kennedy, but the phones are from the LBJ administration.
This is probably the best of all.
Sometimes I worry I say too many things out of left field, but Mike, you might be running
in the ... in the lead for the most absurd thing said in 2025 on the show.
I'm surprised.
Frank Luntz has a recreation of the Oval Office, conservative pundit pollster.
I don't know anything about Frank Luntz, and therefore, please, listener, consider it.
I'm not ... I could not be giving praise to Frank Luntz because I don't know anything
about him.
If he's a conservative pollster, I probably don't like this guy or agree with this guy.
However, as I flip through this article, he's got a lot going on in his house.
Frank's newsstand is ... he has a full fake newsstand with like old Sports Illustrated
TV guides.
He has a big 70s TV network style TV schedule, but that just lists his favorite shows.
You know what I mean?
If you're watching The Late Shift or something, and you see executives putting the show ... like
what's going to be on at 8 p.m. and what's going to be on ... so he just has this thing
that's just all his favorite shows.
Happy days.
Jason would have that.
American Idol.
Marlowe's Place made the cut.
Barbra Streisand's fake basement mall gets all the press, but Frank Luntz's recreation
of Americana offices are ...
Well, and you know it's real too.
There's still a lot of debate about the Streisand mall, but this we know is a real ... here
I'm looking at it.
I'm looking at the real baseball mitt used by Robert Redford in The Natural.
Did you not find the weird ...
Wait a minute.
Oh my God.
The next one I clicked on ...
The weirdest thing he has there?
Well, this isn't the weirdest, but it's the most exciting for me.
It's the equalizer that recorded pet sounds.
Oh, I didn't know you had that.
Oh my God.
You always know what they ran pet sounds through.
That's nuts.
That's a Portlandia sketch of all these items and environments in the studio.
They use this on pet sounds.
They use this guitar stand on pet sounds.
What's the weirdest thing, Mike?
I got to know.
Hanging in the bathroom next to the Oval Office is a version of the infamous blue dress worn
by Monica Lewinsky.
Oh, what the fuck?
Out of his fucking mind, this guy is.
What?
Yeah, I don't know.
A recreate, just the exact type of the dress?
I guess.
What the fuck?
And he owns a pinata that is supposed to be Hillary Clinton.
And he owns ...
Oh, and a Trump.
And a Trump.
Both sides.
And he owns the dress, but he won't tell us if it's black and blue or white and gold.
He's got a diner too.
Frank's diner.
There's so much ... What the fuck is this house?
I don't know.
We got a lot more to ...
I guess it's its own ...
He has a Lincoln bedroom in there?
It's its own episode now that we're really digging in.
Frank Luntz's house.
Yeah.
I'm going to go ahead and ...
Well, I'm locking in Frank Luntz's house.
That's his picture.
I'm going to go ahead and say this all is maybe a little weirder than avocado toaster
dyeing your hair blue.
No, what are you talking about?
That thing clouded on lefties and young people.
This normal conservative man who wants to be looking at Monica Lewinsky's dress every
day he wakes up.
Nothing wrong with that at all.
Nothing strange at all.
I am going to start making a list here.
We can say yay or nay, but it's something ... I believe that we now have ... I'm going
to say here's what I believe are the locks.
There's ones that I think we're going to say are locks, but I want to check and be sure
because there were seven that I addressed earlier.
You want to just go through them quick here?
Yeah.
All right.
Indiana Jones.
Yes.
Or just tell me if you disagree with any of these.
Indiana Jones, men in black, Tiana Spider-Man.
All in.
All in, yeah.
Expedition Everest, Jungle Cruise, Guardian Collector's Office.
Maybe this we need to look at actually, Treehouse Office.
I think it's in.
I just don't know the office.
You can look it up.
I'm just saying I believe it's in.
I want to settle on which one.
I agree.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
I will say requires discussion.
Off air.
Sorry listeners, you don't get to hear everything.
Sometimes we need privacy, like when we go to our little Lincoln bedrooms to have private
time with our Lewinsky dresses.
Right.
Badger's Office from Mr. Toad's Wild Ride.
I'll say yes.
Yeah.
We're at 10?
No, not yet.
If I'm moving that up, that takes us to eight.
Animation Academy.
Doesn't feel like we're sure.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Journey to the Center of the Earth.
Yes.
Okay.
I don't know.
Jason?
I got to say it.
You got to say it?
It seems like you guys are both on board.
Well, requires discussion I think.
Look, as I said, we don't have to solve this all.
Mickey Mouse's Den.
Yes.
Minnie Mouse's Office.
Of course.
Yes.
Okay.
They're both in.
Have to be.
All right.
I don't know that.
I want to put them head to head though.
Well, that's a whole other thing too.
That's a whole other thing.
Yeah.
The lunch also has Colonel Clink's uniform from Hogan's Heroes.
Bluto's Office from the Popeye.
Yes.
Okay.
The heartiest yes from Jason.
Yes.
At some point though, we can say yes all day, but we may have to bump.
Well, we'll see.
Spaceship Earth Cool Girl Office.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's see.
H.G.
Wells Office.
Yes.
That was very whimsical.
All right.
That's it.
Okay.
And finally, Frank Luntz's Oval Office.
Of course.
Might be number one.
Oh, shit.
We've got a winner.
Oh, no.
No.
I was against.
I was saying keep it in your pants until now.
Now I am allowing being really excited about Frank Luntz's house.
Okay.
So now I'm going to move to here.
See, it's going to get a little dicey here.
Now we have to really decide is Flight of Passage in office or not.
Because we still have those Requires Discussions.
Do we by default have to move these to the Requires Discussion category?
Flight of Passage.
Yes.
But are we saying in?
Because at some point, they can't all be in.
Well, we'll have to do that off.
It can be in in the mass list, the big list.
Okay.
That's going to Requires Discussion.
Sorry, guys.
I've got to keep going.
I've got to wrap it up soon.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Okay.
Bowser.
Yes.
Okay.
Zootopia.
I say no.
I say out.
Mystic Manor.
Got to look into it.
Yeah.
Look into it.
Okay.
Officer Zizek's Felt on the Fence.
Discussion.
I would say yes.
Okay.
Let's see.
First Town Alive.
Sheriff's Office.
I think that's in.
I think it's in.
Okay.
Zootopia out.
Walt's Office.
I think that's out.
Out, yeah.
Transformers Office.
You fly through.
I think out.
Out.
I think it's too competitive for Muppet Security Office.
Yeah.
I'm comfortable with that.
It's just not big enough.
It's not big enough.
Or we have to settle on Muppet Zizek's.
Is there another security?
Sheriff's Office, maybe.
I think it's too competitive.
I don't think we can consider these.
It's just one security office.
Yeah.
I think we have to be hard-lined at some point.
Right.
Dinosaur Lab.
Yeah.
And finally, maybe a good place to end.
Is Madame Leota's chamber an office?
I think maybe it worked better as a discussion point to get the ball rolling.
Okay.
Well, that's very gentlemanly of you to withdraw.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I think it's too competitive once we sat down and looked at options.
Okay.
Well, then we've got a number of locks.
I think there are 12 official locks, and then we might have to play with the final few.
Yeah.
But I think we're at a good point.
I guess the big thing then is, I don't know how to pair them up.
No.
That's a little bit of a tough thing, because we have paired them thematically before.
Yeah.
But is it randomized?
Do you go through the entire conference that is Little Makeshift Offices and Adventure
Rides?
Or do you?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Might have to offline?
I think we have to offline it.
Might have to sleep on it.
Okay.
Well, yes.
Look, we still, I think, have the right to stare at this thing to consider it carefully.
Yeah.
But I hope that you enjoyed a little bit of this peek into our process.
Sure.
Kind of like hanging out in our office, right?
Hey, yeah.
How do you do it?
I'm excited to see, off, Mike, which of us will be the first to text on the group chat,
the group text.
I had a thought, or I think this is out, or I think this should be it.
All right.
Okay.
And should we be transparent and release all of these notes?
Or just make them available for public record, like you would in a presidential library.
To be able to board the public.
Yeah.
Sure.
We'll see.
I don't know.
I'm not really a Frank Luntz type.
In the fairytale, too.
In the oval.
His fake oval office.
That's not interesting to me though.
What I want is a wax figure of Jimmy Karn.
Oh my God, that would be even better.
That he had specially made and that he dresses up in Monica Lewinsky's dress.
Yeah.
Like that painting in one of the Epstein properties of Clinton in the dress.
Did that really?
Yeah, that's a whole thing.
Oh, yeah, that whole thing.
We don't have time.
It's at the ranch.
Yeah, yeah, no.
We'll do the- we'll review the island later.
You Survived podcast the right.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
If you wanna dig even deeper, join us on our VIP,
Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
Hey, join us on Friday for the big show.
Buckle up, grab a beer or two, unless we're against that.
It seems like the kind of thing we might be
against people drinking while they listen.
That seems like the kind of period and shit
one of us would have a problem with.
Not my business.
All right, nevermind, all right.
My business, though.
Actually, I agree.
No, no drinking.
Listen sober.