Forever, dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain incredible
anniversary ribbons, colander nightmares,
wrist punishing rides, and big coat tea smuggling.
We return to the Disneyland Class of 55
for an episode about the teacups.
Hey, it's a very merry Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, where conversation goes round
and round in circles and leaves you feeling a little bit nauseous.
I'm Scott Gertner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
Let's do that order.
I but and occasionally we put in a guard.
So it's harder to go round and round.
We do.
And what does that mean metaphorically?
And the metaphor of the show?
Uh, I haven't quite figured that out.
Is that one of your cards?
One of the guards is like one of Jason's comments that calms
the listener's stomach down from feeling too upset by the other discussions.
No, mine are the chaos comment.
So I don't know.
You never know.
This guy might bring up Dr.
Odyssey for 10 minutes.
You never know the chaos that comes.
Mike Carlson. Hey there.
I'm here. Yeah.
I just I you know, who knows?
I think every different type of like any person could be allergic
to any one of us at any time.
You don't know as far as allergic or just make we could.
They could feel motion sickness from the allergic type you say.
Well, allergic in the sense to the type of conversation
one of us would have often.
You know what I'm saying?
But we're all nice.
That has nothing to do with it, though.
I'm just saying that you are nice, but I'm just saying once in a while,
maybe the discussion, somebody listening says,
I don't want to hear about this, you know, old time.
I don't want to hear about some old stars, a state sale.
You know, I don't want to hear about this.
And they go, I'm turning this off.
Maybe they don't puke, but they do feel angry at Jason.
But they he's the person might still know that you're nice.
I guess I have noticed something like this at even the mere mention of Bugman.
I guess that's a little familiar to me that even saying these two words
that are just seven letters that are seven letters in English language
that, you know, like that we've always used and will continue to use.
Yes, somehow these letters have this power to just every drive people mad.
Everyone has it were right.
Everyone has their own different set of words and topics
that they might say, oh, it makes me angry.
Like people hear me and I'll be like, I want to talk about Long December
by the counting crows and they'll be like, oh, no more and turn it right off.
Well, what you're referring to is me.
You're referring to one of your co-hosts.
I wasn't going to say it, but you're allergic to a lot of stuff.
Jason and I say on a regular basis.
I know. Yes.
I just want to talk about the Hedy Lamar's scientific discoveries
that would go on to form the basis of Wi-Fi and radar.
Well, and I just want to talk about the song Johnny Depp wrote about Hedy Lamar.
So that's a different thing, too.
So we both are in the same zone.
Still the Johnny Depp album.
Still, yeah.
What if I were to tell you I did not intend to set you up for that?
Oh, I was there was no doubt in my mind you did not mean to set me up for that.
That was pure Hedy on that was.
Yeah, I'm all in on Hedy.
No, I wasn't looking.
I didn't think that was a lot.
But you were lobbing that thing up for me to smash.
Well, I just I don't like the idea of allergy because that seems that seems sure.
I hear you.
You're a bit of a host.
I don't know. There's no pill that we can prescribe.
It's going to fix that.
What's the weaker aversion?
Food aversion?
Food averse.
You're not fully allergic, but it sometimes doesn't sit well with you.
Is that the term? I don't know.
I guess it doesn't sit well with you is this thing you say about food a lot, I feel like.
So that might be your term.
You know, teach their own.
Something doesn't sit well with me.
I do remain confused with how that Taco Bell made you numb.
It was Chipotle. It was Chipotle.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Taco Bell made him numb.
Taco Bell sauce.
There's too many things lately that hurt him.
That Chipotle made me bloated for two days.
Yeah, I felt bad.
Two straight days of bloating from Chipotle and then Taco Bell made you numb.
Two days is a long time.
It was it was pretty bad.
Huh, huh.
Could you see the bloating or you felt bloated?
I felt bloated.
You felt pregnant.
You wondered if you were pregnant.
I was pregnant with a burrito bowl.
A burrito.
I like the way you said that.
Burrito.
Yeah, it was just the bowl.
The bowl made you bloated for that's kind of a small animal.
And we, you know, I think they you can get the tortilla on the side.
And that was just really gummy.
And remember, we've gotten the incorrect order and they're just like, just keep it.
And we're like, this is not.
Well, I don't remember.
I don't remember that.
This is good.
Surely you do.
And remember from that classic tale.
But we yeah, we didn't really dig into it much because our correct order that came was so unpleasant.
Well, look at my opening joke has just proven this is what I was saying,
is that the conversation ends up making you a little bit nauseous because we often describe being a little bit nauseous.
Right. So, yeah, it all ended up in the right place.
It all went round and round back to where we started.
Literal nausea.
I guess it takes us right back to the to the opening and to the the point of today's episode,
which is the teacups, the goddamn teacups.
Wow.
It's podcast.
The Ride is doing the teacups.
This is a big deal.
Year eight here.
Disneyland teacups.
I mean, are you putting up a border where we can't talk about the other teacups?
When are we ever going to do the other teacups?
I'm leaving it open.
This is what I'm allergic to is this kind of thing.
It's class of fifty five.
Once again, you're on podcast, the ride and the others weren't built.
The others weren't built in fifty five.
It's well here.
It's class of fifty five.
Really up to me when we when we cut that off.
I'll go longer.
You'd be fine.
I'd be happy to hear the whole thing.
The entire gets sued by the man himself.
You know, he's sort of I got curious knowing that I was going to play that.
What what Hagar has been up to lately, recording wise, because that that seemed
like something that could be the great Sammy Hagar, of course, the red rocker.
Mm hmm.
Who does that song that because you have red hair.
I don't think not really.
No, good question.
I don't know.
No, I'm here, right?
Sunburn.
It could be from Sunburn.
Did he wear red a lot?
I feel like you have to wear a red jumpsuit.
Yeah.
Anyway, I got curious what he was what he's been up to.
Like, what are the last couple of records?
And he is he has a band now called Sammy Hagar and the Circle.
Oh, yeah, I know the circle.
You know the circle.
OK, well, do you know they're this is sort of in the Johnny Depp area is
like an all covers album that he put out called Lockdown 2020
that is entirely covers of like Won't Get Fooled Again and Heroes.
Heroes, I believe, also covered by Johnny Depp frequently.
Yeah, of course.
But but with one original called Funky Feng Shui.
So at some point, I might I don't know if it's going to be too confusing to
in the class of 55 drop, start inserting just a little taste of funky feng shui.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it might be a lot for the listeners to connect the dots down the road.
He's got a band, too, with the like Sammy Hagar on the Wobbos or something.
He also, I believe, is another one.
And then he's also got a slightly different band for his Van Halen Tribute.
I mean, he was in Van Halen, but he has a Van Halen Tribute concert.
And I think he replaced a guitarist with like Joe Satriani.
But it's the same band as the circle with like Jason Bonham,
John Bonham's son drums.
And then Michael Anthony, I think, plays bass from Van Halen in the circle
and in the Van Halen Tribute as well.
He's got a lot of things, a lot of irons in the fire.
But here I'm looking at the website of Sammy and the Wobbos,
which has a female member and the photo.
I didn't say anything about the Wobbo Wobbo membership.
Well, Mona Nodder seems to be in Sammy and the Wobbos.
OK. And they introduce her.
This is all of our introduction, I guess, to Sammy and the Wobbos,
is that there's a group that the whole all the band is there.
But it's the female member who's standing up at a urinal
and Sammy and the other guys are going, what the hell? OK.
What's all this then?
I mean, is it a girl is I'm just going to give a Sammy credit.
This is some sort of progressive statement he's making.
That's what I'm going to hope that what it is. Yeah. Yeah.
And then how do you then how do you calculate into that
the drummer who is not paying attention to the situation anyway?
I don't know.
I mean, two of the Wobbos are responsive to this female urinal situation.
He thought this was a test photo and then they ended up using it.
Yeah, it was just everyone else looked better.
So they wanted to just go with that one.
I think it works that David's just staring off.
Yeah, I think it's interesting.
OK, it shows he marches to the beat of his own drum.
And he is the drummer. Right. Which is what you want.
That's perfect. Anyway, we're doing a great job of staying on topic
with the class with the class of fifty five.
Yes, this is an opening day Disneyland attraction, July 17th, 1955.
And that's when we are going to be covering
opening day attractions throughout the year.
Opening day madness and nonsense as Disneyland celebrates its 70th anniversary.
And it's also a good excuse, I think, to check in here and there
on Disneyland's 70th anniversary, which is not officially begun yet.
But what we are starting to get is little glimmers of information
about what this celebration is going to entail.
That's something that's happened since the last class of fifty five that we did,
which was Sleeping Beauty Castle.
Back then, we were just speculating.
We were flying blind.
Now we know some of what Disney is offering.
Do you guys see any of this?
I'm sure I. Announcements of what's coming.
You know what? I probably have.
But I'm I'm wondering what the ones you're going to say are.
Well, I mean, there's so many that I don't even know where to begin.
Well, like we talk like the refurbishment of the car.
They circle is undergoing like they're underway.
That's not even one of them. That's not what you're talking about.
OK, so that is like there's sort of art of what it will look like
with sort of different trim around it, like repainting it.
Well, it's not a Disneyland anniversary if it's not like hanging new ribbons.
That's what a lot of their anniversary stuff is.
New ribbons, a little bit different colors.
They've never done the shade of maroon on the castle before.
Right. Slightly different color t-shirts and sweatshirts.
Yes. And new outfits.
Popcorn buckets that they would have done anyway.
Well, well, yeah, I think that is that's definitely one that I noticed
was new outfits for the characters that I pulled this day.
I did you have you seen the new outfit?
Oh, yeah, these have been out for a long time.
Oh, these are the same ones you're talking about.
OK, are you talking about Mickey with his not symmetrical coat?
Yes, yes, yes, that hangs down longer on one side.
Yes, that's been out for a month, actually.
So I hate to I hate to make you feel bad that you've missed something important,
but that's been out since early in the year.
Is Mickey doing a half tuck now?
It's not a tuck. It's a long here.
Jason, do you not see the code either?
I didn't know about the code either.
Look at this coat, Mickey, on the right side, the coat goes down longer
than on the left and he's not tucking the left.
He just has a like a symmetrical coat.
That looks like a manufacturing error more than anything.
Then then fashion or style, some sort of style.
What? Oh, good.
I was going to say he's kind of got like great, like blue
that that turns into purple pants.
He's got big, bright yellow shoes,
but they're more like sneakers than his normal big, solid yellow shoes.
Well, here's what here's what I think about what he's wearing.
And I don't know if you've seen the group of what everybody is wearing.
I have, yes.
I think this is all I think they're aiming for you with all this.
I think, yeah, I fucking love this very colorful.
I would like to wear all of this.
Yes, I agree.
I mean, it's a little bit too much for me just to wear to Ralph's maybe.
You don't have sparkly swirls on your pants and bright yellow shoes.
But if and like and and I don't like
the dazzled berets, which is what Donald seems to be wearing.
Yeah, Donald. So Donald still has to know pants, which I like.
But it is a very, which I also wouldn't recommend for going around.
No. And Pluto just has a sort of stylish collar in the same style.
I like Donald shirt.
And then many has a really many probably looks the coolest
of all of that, because it just you would wear that in a normal
non anniversary year, I think, too.
In what in what photo would you not say many looks the cool?
Well, that's true.
But I'm just saying specifically, this one, like even maybe kind of blends in.
It's the same style as the rest of them, but it almost kind of blends in.
It is not as flashy as the others, I guess.
But yes, I would wear.
I would love to wear one of these pieces, just Mickey's shirt,
just Mickey's pants.
But would you if you were if you well, you didn't put in your list
the asymmetrical coat, would you wear the asymmetrical coat?
I it depends on what you call like a cost,
because I don't want to spend like 100 north of 100
on an asymmetrical coat that I'm only going to wear once in a while.
But what if what if you're you know, sometimes you go to events
where fashion is specified.
This is a black tie event.
What if you get invited to an asymmetrical coat event?
Oh, of course I would wear that Mickey's asymmetrical coat.
Yeah. Cut to a lot of people with nice coats like, oh, shit, I didn't realize.
And I got to be there in an hour.
All right. Snip, snip.
And they just have to like take a giant wedge out of their own jacket.
Well, yeah, you don't want to stand out in a bad way.
Yeah, no, thirty, thirty five dollars old Navy version of this code.
I'm in, I think. OK.
And then and then, yes, I would wear only at specific events.
Now, I'm interested in the fact that there's a practical zipper
up near Mickey's head.
Like, why does Mickey need a pocket on his 70th anniversary wardrobe?
It's just interesting to me because like none of the other characters
have any pockets, literal pockets, as far as I can tell.
Yeah. And then he has a zippered pocket up by his head.
Lighter joints. I mean, that's getting high.
Yeah. The pills of ecstasy.
It's barking up. Seventieth.
Seventy pills in here.
Ollie. One for each.
With all my friends.
Yeah, this is weird.
I don't know. It's an interesting style choice.
I've worked my ass off for 70 years.
You're telling me I can't enjoy a little E for 70.
I got cash and Molly in here.
Got five hundred dollars in bills, non non sequential bills.
They're dirty, you know, they've been washed, you know.
It's yeah, well, I guess it could have a cell phone in there, I suppose.
It doesn't look like anything's in there from the look of it.
It just looks kind of flat now.
But, you know, you'd want to have the option.
Yeah. But it's a yeah.
And the zipper is a regular zipper, too.
It's not like a little lightning bolt or a little sun or moon.
You know what I mean?
If it was the spirit of this feels very much colorful,
but then also there's a lot of stars and moons.
Yeah. And the design, you would think that they would want to make the zipper
very specific. That's right.
We've made it 70 years American history.
We're an American institution.
And you, the guests, multiple generations have passed through these gates
and you've passed it on to your children and their children and their children.
And to say thank you, we just want to tell you, Mickey has a zipper now.
Mommy, mommy.
I think he's got an affectation zipper.
It's not really practical.
It's just visual.
He's got a superfluous zipper, mommy.
There's no need for it.
I love this. Happy 70th. Happy 70th.
Mommy, let's go watch the Walter animatronic again.
Let's go to Walter's office like our candles.
So I yeah, I like I like this is this is exciting stuff for you.
How do we feel about I like that?
I like this degree of announcement of Disney announce it,
not just announcing that there will be a song, not saying here's the song.
Right. They have announced Celebrate Happy, a new song
performed by the Jonas Brothers. Right.
We will be getting stay on alert, everyone.
J alert. The Jonas Brothers will be striking any day now
with a new song to help you celebrate happy. Right.
So that's it. Yes.
So we already knew about the new verse.
As far as a small world is concerned, I need a little more explanation.
You're going to leave it there. Yes.
The new verse. Yes. I'm a little slow today.
Sorry. But yes, the new verse.
And it's a small world.
I've heard that small world is now delayed.
They're installing some new figures, but they're also installing the new verse.
OK, so that's going to take a few more weeks.
I read that long as it takes to install a verse.
I don't know. But it's it's been delayed.
The new verse has been delayed, I think, into May now.
I think it was going to be open maybe this month, actually.
OK, so much is retrofitted there.
They have to figure out how to flip an MP3 to a WAV file.
That's probably right.
Something close to that is, I mean, probably it's like
it's running on a record album, I think, probably.
Well, now they're up to Windows and you think so.
OK, you recall that one.
Yeah, yeah. So, yes, it's
there's a lot of stuff going on. New verses, new clothing.
Yes. What else? What else?
And just to be clear, because I looked up, like, does the song exist?
Did they even release a preview of the song?
And they did not.
But what's confusing is Jonas Brothers already put out a song called
Celebrate a couple of years ago.
So Celebrate is not celebrate happy.
Oh, wow. Clear. OK, that's that's that's tough.
That's a thin slice for them to have to
you try to reinvent what celebrating means as far as Jonas Brothers.
So it's not like Candle in the Wind or something.
And they just know.
No, I don't think so. OK.
Hopefully happier than that.
It's about celebrating. Yeah. Yeah.
Different.
Elton's doing a new version for Walt.
What's that?
He's doing Candle in the Wind for Walt.
Yeah, Candle in the Wind. I didn't hear.
He's he's just a little bit late.
Performance on the what was it?
The Christmas parade.
Everyone was like, that was really good.
It was pretty good.
This kid's got something. Yeah.
Got anything in the pocket? Mm hmm.
Could you write a song about a man who died 70 years ago?
Could you rewrite a song?
You should really do. Yeah, he should do more.
There's a lot of people.
There's a lot of people who died.
A lot of legends.
And he's only written about two.
Yeah, come on. Lazy, lazy.
There's a we're getting a special rendition of Rainbow Connection
for World of Color performed by Boys to Men.
Yes, I did see that in a new original song called Makes Me Want to Move.
I can't tell if that's boys to men or if it's performed by no artist.
Will it make us want to move?
Time will tell.
And then this one, I'm I mean,
I let me like take a deep breath just to the quality
because I won't be able to get through the sentence.
I don't know if you guys have heard,
but ahead of the first World of Color happiness showing guests
inside Disney California Adventure can vote on the Disneyland app
for one of four different emotions, sadness, anger, disgust or envy
to see which is featured in special scenes throughout both day's shows.
I get to we get to choose.
Wait, hold on. Democracy works.
So what did you understand about that sentence?
I was very clear.
I understand they made two versions
and they've created a fake voting system that does nothing.
Well, I don't for I think it's four versions inside out.
Inside out has a land of the world inside out has invaded World of Color
and four of the characters, not Joy.
Joy is not in this list.
Joy's side emotions only.
OK. Sadness, anger, disgust and envy.
You get to pick which one is are you feeling disgust today?
And you get to put disgust in the show.
Huh? So it's the majority wins.
Yeah, I guess. That's what they're saying. Yeah.
What you get to be one of one of a bunch of people voting on the app.
And we know the app and we know this is going to be a very clean voting system.
We know that it's going to be easy as hell for you to register your anger
by putting anger into the World of Color happiness show.
Won't the same thing win every time
because it'll just be the most popular character from inside out?
Maybe. But I don't know.
Maybe not. You know, like if if if we're you know,
there's some days where we're feeling particularly angry about the state
of this nation.
Oh, you think that maybe we're feeling or we're feeling disgusted
by the state of this nation or feeling envy on behalf of other countries.
So we're not dealing with what we're dealing with.
I think it's how how is the news striking the general populace
every day when they're going to Disneyland?
Uh huh. How does that reflect in their votes?
I think people have been there all day.
Sometimes by the time it gets around to the nighttime show,
anger and or disgust might already be an emotion they're experiencing
because they're because they're tired, they're tired out.
And those I love I love my kids, but they are a handful.
Gosh, they are a handful.
I'm disgusted by the behavior of my children.
I'm just I'm today. I'm voting disgust.
Opened all those ketchup packets and he knew he was just going to use one.
So then it's just a pile on the plate and then I got to take it to the trash.
I like this picture. You're painting the Disneyland, dad.
It was pizza. Why do you even need ketchup?
Just wanted to play with it, dammit.
That was not a good ketchup opening.
Stinks like Heinz.
My stinky kid, my stinky ketchup kid.
So mad of this kid.
This is a it's a phrase that you're saying would disgust,
but I could easily see either of you saying, now, when I was growing up,
I was a little stinky ketchup kid.
Jason was this little stinky kid.
I was a big ketchup kid.
He's the one with all the stinky kids around him, as we've established.
Well, this is that was it was a club three.
I don't know. I didn't hear that breaking news on Club Three.
And if this doesn't get you over to Club Three, then I don't know what will.
Breaking news is Jason would sometimes get headaches at school
because of how bad all the kids around him smelled.
The kids smelled.
There was very little ventilation, obviously no air conditioning
in that old, you know, worst progress administration building.
And ultimately, it ultimately goes back to the 30s.
Your headache was born in the 1930s.
Yeah, my headache and the conditions.
And it also led to the conditions that, you know, in the poor nutrition
in this nation that caused those children to stink.
That's a good point. Yeah.
It all makes sense now.
Curse you, FDR.
The dairy surplus that America constantly has, you know,
all those all that extra cheese and milk produce that the schools have to take.
And the kids were secreting the milk and cheese, do you think?
Well, no, it was the lunch, the lunches, the school lunches,
and then they'd all be farting and smelly from all the dairy.
And do you think is this a problem that persists to this day?
Do you think this is a problem that why didn't Mike have this problem growing up?
Was this like your area specifically?
No, this is countrywide, like the farting.
School lunches had a lot of cheese and cartons of milk for the default drink.
And because that was just from so much
surplus dairy and government funding for dairy farmers.
They forced all of us to eat so much dairy.
Now, this is a facet of this conversation that didn't come up in the Club 3 episode.
Was Jason's blame of the government for the stinky children in his classroom?
Well, looking back, I mean, it was more like the parents just hadn't been like,
yeah, we should probably get you bathing more,
would probably get you a deodorant stick.
Here's here's a question. Yeah.
Did were you part of the problem?
Were you a stinky kid yourself or were you the lone not stinky kid?
I think my mom did a good job of like, you need to start showering more or bathing more.
What ages does this have to do with nutrition?
This is like nine.
This is no, these are all systemic. Never mind.
It's fascinating because I just wasn't my other than the one kid that sat next to me
for a couple of months in third grade that smell like baloney.
I don't have a strong memory of like those my classroom stinking a lot.
The kids stinking.
I did. I've always had kind of a sensitive sense of smell.
Either my nose is stuffy or I just I have that smell hates me art.
So I would have to be a baloney kid.
And I would also be curious if you were to go, go back home, go to that classroom.
Would you find that the ghost of the smells?
I think the building was demolished and rebuilt.
Oh, my God.
There was at least an opportunity.
Plasticy, you know, more air conditioning and current habits
caused the children in that area, like kind of matching the demographics.
Are they still as stinky?
Well, they now they all just smell like Mr.
Beast's feastable chocolate bars.
The nasty chocolate bars that always seem to be on clearance
that people are posting pictures.
Every single child, every single store.
Can I trade? Can I trade your beast for my beast?
Well, we got the same beast.
Yeah, I want to feel something.
All right. Well, again, well, again, we've wrapped back around to the nausea.
We've talked about Jason's stinky kit.
I do. I do think it was starting to go bad.
I'm going to get four hundred thousand dollars if I can put up
with a month's worth of stinky kids. Mr.
Beast told me that that's the subject of that's what entertainment is.
Mr. Beast's stinky kid challenge is the next show.
He's lying, though, because it's four hundred dollars in Robux.
Like, I don't know what to do with Roblox, Roblox, whatever.
It's cool. Yeah, I do. I have one more question.
Do you because you seem to answer to my question
that you were the lone non stinky kid out of what?
30. Would you would you agree with that?
Or do you think there's maybe like four or five who are not stinky?
No, I think we all took turns being a little stinky.
You know, kids start to sweat more and your body starts to change.
And there's some stink, you know.
I feel like my memory is maybe junior high is when I started becoming aware of
maybe that's just maybe my awareness.
But that's when I really sort of remember like, oh, now it's time to really
like fix hygienic.
And yes, maybe somebody smells a little bit.
I don't recall it so strongly in elementary school.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, maybe that's my maybe that's me.
I don't know. Jason is good.
Jason goes back like Martin Sheen in Apocalypse Now.
Just a cold sweat middle of the night recalling the stink.
Yeah, I'm lying. Eyes wide awake.
Ceiling fan slowly rotating.
I do imagine just you in a room full of pig pens from peanuts.
Just think lines coming off of all these kids.
I bet. Yeah. Right.
Which I remember, of course, we met.
We met Pig Pen at the livery stable at Knott's Berry Farm right before the pandemic.
And he he didn't.
He if he smelled, I didn't notice because all those farm animals.
He smelled fine.
Well, stinky.
I don't think that they would make the costumed character
stink in order to complete the illusion.
This is not something that you find a lot in theme park mascot characters.
Yeah, that's a good point. Yeah.
But it would have been nice.
It'd be an interesting innovation and something that they could do for the 70th.
Let's say like, sure.
Colorful, fun clothes.
What colorful, fun smells are these characters bring to the table?
Right. What are the what does Pluto smell like?
Let's be honest. Goofy should smell a little.
You know, he doesn't like take care of himself so well.
He's very chaotic.
And I'm not saying it's a specific type of smell, but like whatever.
He forgot he was cooking or something.
And he like got a bunch of batter all over him.
And it's just been drying on his pants and he didn't notice.
I forgot to change.
I was doing worse.
I was going to say I was too invested in listening to kill Tony while I eat my batter.
Oh, he's problematic.
Oh, no, Goofy.
No, I think it's a little bit of Bane, but a little bit of Lorne Michaels.
Hello, Mickey Mouse.
My skis don't go on because they're ready to go on.
All right. Well, let's bring it back.
So a lot to look forward to for the 70th.
We will keep giving you these updates.
We will check in as soon as the actual Jonas Brothers song has been released.
Yeah, I am excited.
We'll try to be more timely, Mike.
I'm sorry that these clothes have been out for.
Although, you know what? I put the blame right back on you.
You could have been talking about these clothes all year.
None of them are the ones who dropped the.
You would have been allergic to the discussion if I had brought up the clothing, I think.
And by now, you would have been really allergic to it.
Also, let's call it out. None of those clothes platinum.
Well, but that is true.
No, it's true. But again, the idea of platinum is a thing
that Mike made up that is not anything they were ever going to do.
Yes, the platinum celebration.
That's why you should have brought it.
You should forget that I made a platinum celebration.
I thought we looked up what the 70th anniversary of a thing,
of a marriage, but that doesn't mean that Disney ever thought of it.
But 60 was diamonds.
Yes, that's why I said that the 70th will be a platinum.
That would lead to the discussion.
I guess, but that doesn't oblige Disney.
They've never said it's obliged.
They've never called it the platinum.
Because they did the wood anniversary.
They did the paper anniversary.
Who on earth has ever followed these?
I don't know.
The poor wife who's getting so paper, I get.
And we have to do it by the books, darling.
I get a paper necklace this year.
Yes. Yeah.
We were pouring on our anniversary and my gifts melted.
All right. Well, there's no easy way to transition.
So I will just hard pivot back into the topic proper today,
which is this is a discussion that we have to have, I think, is that there's,
you know, if we're being all if we're being all proper and by the books,
then we call this episode Mad Tea Party. Right.
But who on earth has ever called it that tea cups?
Yeah. The tea cups is what we are talking about, which.
And I think there's a lot of firsts with this attraction,
and I think that is one of them.
I think the this is the first attraction
that has an official name that no one uses.
That's a good point. Ever said, you want to hit Mad Tea Party?
It is like it paves the way for Tiana's by Tiana's bioadventure
for names that will never be, you know, used in full.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Well, Mike hears that he's like, are we going to hear
an Imagine Dragons cover tonight or a Hoosier cover?
When I hear Mad Tea Party, when you hear Mad Tea Party,
was his name Hoosier?
Hoosier. Hoosier?
Oh, I didn't even know he was talking about he was so off.
Yeah. Oh, Hoosier, I guess.
Are we going to hear a cover of a speech from the movie Hoosiers?
I guess Hoosiers is that a movie.
Yeah. Well, that's a team, a college team. Yeah. Yeah.
It's not the name of that artist. Hoosier. Yeah.
Hoosier. Yeah, now I get it.
By which you're referring to, I mean, I knew we weren't going to make it
too far with that Mad Tea Party coming up.
Mike's favorite band in the world.
It goes, it goes Mad Tea Party, Beatles,
Led Zeppelin, Sammy and the Wobbos, Sammy and the Wobbos,
Sammy Agar in the Circle, Jonas Brothers, but just Celebrate Happy.
And then Hoosier and his band.
By the way, Hoosier's band, Hoosier and the Hoosiers.
Sorry to dwell on this, but I don't know that.
Or is Celebrate Happy going to live up to Come on Everybody, Get Your Ears On?
Well, that is an interesting question.
I don't remember what that is or when it's from.
It's from Mickey's Mix Magic.
Yes, it was a song that I forgot was an actual like song that they put.
I thought it was just from an ad campaign and then it was in the mix magic.
It is also on Spotify.
So you can hear it.
Yes, it was not as it was just it was for a show, though.
It was not for an anniversary.
So I can't hear it, you're saying it is available to be heard.
Yes. Now, well, Scott, careful.
You're going to drop your phone.
You're getting it.
But I guess I could have been listening to the song for months
and knowing about Mickey's a regular coat. Yep.
I should just I should get off the band.
But I did knowing that the band was going to come up.
I was like, can I find a song by this band I haven't heard?
And then I looked it up and I found them doing a cover of Razorglass by Pink.
Yeah, I've heard.
Oh, I've heard. Yeah, I don't.
It was the funniest thing to me when you were you've been talking up
and this was a band that played at an event in California Adventure.
That's like a crazy that's the Malice in Wonderland meets Evanescence,
a G rated rave, top hits from the 70s through 80s through now. Yeah.
And I still find it so funny
that when they appeared on a very public stage before D23,
that multiple people were texting, what the hell is this shit that Mike likes?
It was we were those were bad streams.
It wasn't an official live stream that was plugged into the music, the soundboard.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, then how do you account for the person who was in the room
who texted me the same comment? Where were they seated?
Were they seated by the band or were they seated?
Because depending on the room, they were used to arena sound.
They play smaller venues.
So that was unfair. Right.
They didn't get to properly do the sound mix.
It's a hockey arena.
You know, no acoustics in there.
Yeah. No band has ever sounded good.
I think everyone can attest.
No band has ever sounded good.
The only song you can even hear in there is Blur's song number two.
Song number two. Also known as Woohoo!
It's called Song Two.
I don't know. It's called Song Hoosier Two.
I thought the fact that I was pretty close, pretty good.
You were pretty close on that one. You did get the number right.
I like that. I'm a big Damon Albert boy.
OK, I look, I hear you.
Can you say you're a fan, not boy?
What is this boy?
Why do we do this?
We are adults.
You are so close to 40.
You're not an anything boy.
Song movie, the movie 43 song, the song number two.
Well, that sound appears on the criteria channel that is not in the title.
It will be added.
I'm a little article adding boy.
Yes, yes, that is what he is.
A little article adding boy.
Mad Tea Party.
This is we're going to have to focus up
because and they look because there is a lot to talk about here
because keep in mind, maybe you haven't thought this through.
This ride goes round and round, right?
So that's two giant facets that we have now an hour remaining to cover.
I don't know if we're going to get to both.
Maybe we only get to the first round.
There's multiple turntables in play, too.
There sure are. And this it's been in a different spot.
It's moved. It's moved.
And you know, the original was manufactured by Arrow
Development, as many early Disneyland attractions were.
Cool street phrase.
And you know, no, Arrow Development put that that motherfucker together.
Not aerodynamics.
That was the company's later name, eventually bought up by SNS,
undone by the complications of building X,
the rotating ride at Six Flags of Magic Mountain
and the unbuilt stratosphere roller coaster.
They were undone by that. What is that?
Just like they didn't have a lot lined up after that.
And they were kind of put all their eggs in a basket.
There is a great storybook amusement video on this.
And there is an expedition theme park as well about unbuilt
and built stratosphere stuff.
Of course, stratosphere, the big Space Needle looking kind of casino
that used to have a roller coaster that would circle the top of it.
A nice badly put together roller coaster.
Oh, long gone, long gone.
And never built the one, the roller coaster that was going to go down
the side of the building and across the road.
Residents were not wild about that idea.
Sure, sure. Sounds cool, though.
Well, it's similar.
I mean, like, look, it was uncharted territory in building the teacups.
So you can, you know, maybe you don't blame them too much.
But this I think it was kind of poorly put together back then.
So probably something we all ran into.
But like, what's like just as we dive in here, this is this is truly a fundamental.
It is it is a big one and not just a big one for Disney,
but a big one for all the various parks that ripped it off for years and years.
There was even a part of me that was like,
was this was this a type of ride that existed called the teacups?
And then they took it one step further by making it
literal teacups and to play into Alice in Wonderland.
And the answer is no, they nothing was ever called the teacups before this.
And everything else that does that, because plenty of other theme parks
call all these things teacups, it's all ripping Disney off.
And you have to this.
It seems odd that it's an area where they have not been super litigious,
where it seems like they could and would be.
Yes, that's true.
I mean, it feels like, yeah, it feels like to invent this,
which now just feels like part of any park.
Like it feels like having something that looks like this in every theme park
is just like, that's what you do.
It's like law that you do it.
But since Disney started it, you would think that they would be a little more
like, no, that's what we invent to making people dizzy.
Like this is what we invented. Right. Right.
But there is a big thing they could take off the table for competitors.
Although I think I saw somewhere that they don't own the patent on it.
So I think they can't stop people from doing a ride of this nature. Right.
Because maybe there was one, there were maybe there were a few
that existed before, but nothing that called it teacups.
I think what they have a patent on is like the design, the type of cup.
Right. The type of squiggle that is on the side of the cup.
So you could do like a glass, like a clear glass,
like you drink water out of and you could spin people around in that.
Yeah, because it doesn't look like a teacup.
And I think you could just have a general bucket, but still call it the teacups.
But I think maybe I don't know, I could be wrong.
I don't know what the I don't know what the copyright entails,
but maybe you can't do handles.
Maybe you can't do little plates, saucers.
Maybe you can't do saucers.
But only Disney can do saucers.
You could do like little dishes, like little like a dish, a candy dish.
It's hard for me to picture how a plate is different than a dish.
Well, it's like a little bowl, a little bowl, a candy dish would be a little bowl.
A candy. I was going to say dishes aren't.
Yeah, no, the concept of dishes themselves.
Yes, there's a lot of things.
But like a dish or like a dish for like a cat or they sometimes call dog dish.
It's a little bowl. Yeah.
Jason, is there another thing that you would want to be spun around
in a big version of some sort of kitchen dish?
Kitchen. Well, we have saucer and teacups.
So those are off the table.
That's off the table, right, because we can do that.
You just mentioned water glass.
So I guess that's all glass bowls.
Is there any other maybe like a colander?
You could spin and then go through the go through with the end.
You go through it. Yeah, you would be.
Oh, OK. I guess they kind of already have that like a gravitron kind of.
Well, I was going to those water slides where you kind of go around
the big funnel and you go out the bottom.
Oh, OK. Yeah, I guess.
So I think that's a different ride.
I think you spinning around a colander coming out of one of the holes
is a different ride than the teacups.
Yeah, I don't know how they aim you through the holes.
That's I think it's just like hand up and it's spinning through. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't think it's there's much precision in that.
A dinner plate.
You potentially you could fly off. That could be fun.
You're putting the most dangerous terrible at fun.
I think it's something simple here.
Well, if you want to, if you want to, if the way you want to go out
is flying off a giant dinner plate into an audience and a crowd.
Wait, why is there a crowd?
They're waiting to go on the ride.
Could be some mattresses or like, oh, OK.
Well, I was picturing the way you were you wanted to go out.
So that's the plan.
The plan is for people to fly off and then land on mattresses.
OK, this is a really haphazard.
Yeah, I was hoping you were going to say,
like, oh, a juice glass or something you were going to answer.
But you're coming up with a bunch of action park style rides here.
Juice glass, awfully similar to water glass.
It is a little more ounces.
You're right. Or like a sippy cup.
Two handles. Yeah.
Like a baby sippy cup or a toddler sippy cup is good.
Or being, you know, like an adult version, like, like, you know, one of those.
I don't drink a lot of Moscow mules, but I like glasses.
Copper mug of some kind.
It'd be nice to those were like, like, those were like shimmer in the sun.
Yes. Would look very pretty.
They'd look good under moonlight.
It'd be a nice, like adult way to do it.
The sun would probably damage the copper pretty quickly.
I mean, you could probably figure out a way to paint it.
It's for if it's faux copper.
But yeah, sure, it doesn't have to be legit copper.
But that is that would be that would be cool.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, for a full, like alcohol themed theme park.
Duffland. Yeah.
Like a bro, like a bro park or something.
Put it in there.
I don't know if they're going to attract bros to the bro park.
I think bros are maybe going to rebel against maybe the notion
that this is where they're supposed to go. Maybe.
But then I don't know.
I'm not a bro.
And I haven't known a lot over the years.
Yeah. I can't get into the head of one.
Well, let's ask the bros out there.
Would you go to a bro park where you could get in a big copper mug
that spun you around?
Yo, bros need your feedback, bros.
Are you listening to this to this show?
And you're a bro.
If first of all, why?
Secondly, when you're done picking all the sauces for your big wing box,
you know, fucking bros getting big wings.
Getting some brew, getting a 30 rack of keystone.
I mean, you know, I mean, you're right about the bros getting their wing sauce,
but don't you and I like to get our wing sauce to say you love your chicken
guy's sauces. Oh, that's true.
What's the difference?
Those are genteel dipping sauce.
Oh, it's a different thing than the other round of sauce they're getting tossed.
But I'm a B-dubs guy.
I'm a Buffalo Wild Wings guy. That's true.
I'm a buffalo. I'm a little Buffalo Wild Wings boy.
I'm a little sauce boy.
This is this allergy that you described before.
There is no worse phraseology.
So it truly is.
I think I think the hairs inside my ear all stand up.
Yeah. Well, I try to block the words from getting in there again.
Look, you don't understand. Mike's still young.
He can still go.
You do. Oh, he does understand that.
He does know that.
Well, yeah, I've been made to understand it from how often it's been said.
I grab his wrist and I let go.
You're not leaving jelly rolls until that door closes, locks.
I do think I guess all this to say, I do think the teacup perhaps is the best
of all the different things in a kitchen you could ride in and spin in a circle.
I would have to agree.
Yeah, I think it makes
it makes sense within the storytelling and makes sense in the world.
And I think that it's a you almost have to.
You know, look, this is like,
you know, maybe there's more like excitement about a big e-ticket type
attraction and maybe there's more bean on the bone to talk about
even with a big e-ticket attraction.
But I've really I don't know if it's just a parenting thing.
I don't know if like now bringing
young children into the parks has affected my thinking.
But I think it has because you gravitate to different rides when you do that.
And this really struck me a couple of weeks ago when we talked about Epic
Universe and how much it all clicked with me.
Yoshi's Adventure is a ride that seems like nothing on its face is like
the heart of the land.
And you wish they had a lot more of these.
I do. I think there is some just like basic fun and creativity to.
All right. One of our most popular movies we have to represent
is Alice in Wonderland. What are we going to do when we put people in a car
that takes you through the scenes of the movie?
I mean, yes, they ended up doing that.
But even that you're in a big, cool caterpillar.
That's neat. But like that we're going to abstractify the movie
and put not not just have you be a passive participant
looking at characters and scenes that you aren't a part of.
But you're in the you're in a cup.
Yeah, you're in the tea party.
You are the tea. Right.
And I really and I do think this is a kind of thing that gets lost
in kind of the more when the when the narrative is fleshed out in the stories
like in a rise, the resistance or not.
I'm sorry. In a galaxy's edge or an Avengers campus or whatever.
That when the when the narrative is too strong,
you can't there's not opportunity to just have a silly, stupid ride
that doesn't make any narrative sense, but that is great fun for everybody.
Is that does all that make sense?
Yes. I think what you're saying is that they're like, especially in the last
10, 20 years, the obsession with the idea of story.
Yes. And the story is immersed in this world.
And what this has led to some wonderful things.
But I think there's also like a place for your.
Yeah, you're in the you're in the tea.
You're like, yeah, you're in this silly vehicle
and it's fun what it does to you. Right.
Now, obviously, Cars Land, Radator Springs did a great job with.
I think Radator Springs took the
teacup style, D ticket, C ticket, wherever you want to call it,
and like updated it, took it like, you know, into the new millennium
to the next level.
And I just wish that there were I think we
parks should not neglect this kind of thing where it's like, yes,
it's simple, but it's effective.
People have loved it just as much for 70 years and always will.
Yeah. I mean, there should be like a Star Wars land.
It should be like, yeah. And you ride a lightsaber like it doesn't like it.
Yeah, I know.
Like, I know.
Like, there's got to be something like that.
Yeah, it's just too.
Is that it? Or what if you're what's there?
What's their chess?
Is there something with that? What's the what's the hologram chess?
Yeah, but there's some other there's some sabbath.
Is that it? That's the card game, the holographic chess games.
Yeah, that's what it is.
What if you were one of those?
What if you were moving around?
Oh, that would be awesome, too.
That would be really sliding around from and like knocking other figures.
Yeah. Yeah, that's fun.
I think like I think people in the 50s did not ask.
But how does this work in terms of the broader narrative?
I think they said I get to be in a teacup that spins around.
Sounds great. Sign me up.
Yeah, I think this what is the story?
You know, what's the story behind this can be helpful.
But like it has like infected.
Like, what is the story of this gastro pubs?
Like, what is the story of this clothing line?
Yeah, you know, sure.
There's too much, especially theme parks.
There's too much logic in of everything instead of just.
You know, figuring out what the coolest version of every room is
and the coolest version of every ride in space.
I think I said this before on the show and a Tony Baxter interview.
He claims that Mark Davis was complaining about people
calling ride stories and going, they're not stories.
Wow. They're just stuff happened like fun stuff happening.
Like he was really irritated by it.
I think Tony was using it to illustrate that he felt similarly about it.
I think of the same interview, he was also talking about how
Jar Jar Binks should be in Galaxy's Edge.
And even though Jar Jar Binks was like controversial or people
didn't like him at the time, people he was like, people would go nuts
seeing Jar Jar Binks in Galaxy's Edge.
And he's absolutely right.
That's definitely 100 percent right.
And yeah, well, he's he's Star Wars.
Goofy is what he is. Yeah.
And I'd love to see him there.
And I'd love to see what colorful vests he's wearing, of course,
for the 70th anniversary.
But there's a lot less of that these days.
I feel like the thinking is more just like
the perfectly crafted narrative.
And the ride is so makes so much sense.
And this right connects to this.
And some of that's cool.
But some of it's just like, I think we're missing out on
just like the most fun version of things.
Yeah. Yeah. And I don't.
Yeah. And it's not bad. Yeah.
Well, it's where you think it's not always better.
What's where you got to be thankful for this this perennial and this?
Like I don't like isn't Disneyland really built on the back of it?
Like when people were leaving that place in 55,
and I'm sure there was a lot to complain about in that first day
and that first month and all that.
But I think the big headlines were, oh, it's cool.
There's this one thing where we fly around an elephant.
It goes around around this other thing.
We sit in a teacup and it spins around and around.
It's really where they're not these.
And maybe people were as excited about, you know, what are the big like?
What did you leave?
What was as we as Epic Universe opens?
Yeah. And knowing that all the all the heat and all the pressure
is going to be on Potter and the monsters.
What do you think people were leaving Disneyland talking about?
Was it was it this?
Was it Jungle Jungle Cruise?
Pretty like new immersive that like that might have really tricked people
in terms of I don't know what they I don't know how they made a jungle train.
I bet the whole thing, though, since it was so crazy, too,
there was just nothing.
There was nothing like it.
So I can imagine everybody a different thing.
Now we're so we're so jaded with all of our themed entertainment.
Now we require it picking things apart a little more.
But I have to imagine people like, hey, look at that thing they built,
that big crazy thing they built.
Yeah. Yeah. This is this is wild.
Yeah. I think one thing I'm looking forward to that seems like they got
right in this sense for you mentioned Epic Universe in,
you know, the monsters area.
It's like, yeah, Igor is here and Dracula and Frankenstein and the Wolfman.
Yeah. And fuck it.
The creature from the Black Lagoon and the Phantom of the like.
Everyone's here. Yes. Yes.
And they figured it out with the construct of dark more.
It's just yeah, it's still it is still technically it's a coherent story.
Even if that, you know, you could poke holes in it if you thought too hard.
But do you want to think too hard or do you want all the monsters to be right?
The movie Dark Universe, the line of movies that never got off the ground
where it's like, OK, and so there's a mummy,
but it's not Tom Cruise at the beginning, but maybe by the end.
And Dr. Jekyll and Mr.
Hyder there and he runs a secret like shield organization.
This is going to be Frankenstein.
This is going to be Dracula and blah, blah, blah.
And it's like, that's so complicated than just this ride is all the guys.
Yes. Yeah, yeah. I think they've got the right idea.
I mean, we haven't got to do it yet, but it definitely seems promising.
In one of the like alleyways near one of the windows,
there's like a whole audio track playing of Dr.
Jekyll and Mr. Hyde getting into an argument. Oh, wow.
There's a couple of minutes of like, what are you doing?
You're out of control.
Like in this whole like dramatic thing, there's a sign to for like, oh, yeah, yeah.
Dr. Jekyll apothecary.
Yes, ever. All the all the characters are there.
Smart. And they have yes, they have figured out their logic for it.
Well, I don't know if I don't know.
I don't know if I'm just trying to hamfistedly go back to what we're talking about.
But but that is like they also had the right idea with Fantasyland where they don't go.
But why would how would Snow White know Mr.
Toad and you're saying their neighbors and that there has to be some construct
that allows you to jump from realm to realm at like or I don't know.
This is just a place all storybooks live. Yeah.
All the princesses are here.
They didn't. Yeah, they didn't ever think.
Yeah. I think Dumbo is in Old England.
That's fine. Right. No problem.
Is this an necessity of invention kind of thing where it's like we have the space.
We don't have much time.
We have some money.
Hopefully more money is coming.
Yeah. I mean, I just think they weren't.
It's just that I mean, we like completely like theme to one thing.
Big lands. Yeah.
But yeah, it was not.
This was not a there was anything that's sort of like in a book.
And I've got look, I've complained.
I don't like who would buy you country.
But I think that's because by you country is too specific.
Sure. Sure.
If we mean that retro, it is been retrofit so many times.
Yeah, they've changed the name of it.
I'm just saying that like that bothers me now because the land is so specific.
Fantasyland is a pretty broad name.
What does that even mean? Really?
Other than just fictional.
Yeah. I guess fantasy is in that way.
Like it really does give it.
I almost feel like maybe what we just want is a new fantasy land today,
one that doesn't take itself as seriously.
Yeah. It is just kind of like and plop.
It's all here.
But it's sort of what like Soos landing or whatever would say that's all here.
It doesn't matter if the characters never met or wouldn't know each other.
Just put them all there.
I guess Fantasy Springs is the souped up version in Japan.
Yeah. Fantasyland where it's still little mini lands
connected, they're still not.
I think they're still in the mindset of like land or mini land
because it does feel like, yeah, are we ever going to get just a land opening up
that is multiple?
I mean, I guess kind of that area in Animal Kingdom that's got Indiana Jones
and oh, sure, that seems like a good mishmash.
Yeah, that's yeah, that's closer to what I think we're saying.
We're saying we like our mishmashes.
We can still do mishmashes.
And actually, well, let me let me tie things together with Epic Universe
and teacups and another another first that I think the teacups does,
because I thought Epic Universe did a great job of using attractions
as the kinetic energy in the land, as like, you know,
things work if you're not on the ride because you're watching it pass by
and it's fun to look at.
And it obviously works to be on it because it's fun to be on a ride.
And I think the teacups are probably an early attraction
where it is sort of this kinetic sculpture
as well as a being a fun ride to go on itself.
And I'm sure that was evident in day one.
But what you didn't have in day one yet was attractions up in the air.
And by the time you add Skyway and Monorail
and I guess Matterhorn, you catch glimpses of it, but that you can like
that you can look down on this thing and that it's well designed
just to look at as well and that there's psychedelic swirls
and the and the colors are fun to watch and just like watching the mecha,
watching the mechanism, watching the turntables.
Yeah, it was really neat.
So I think like, yeah, I don't know.
It pays it pays the way in that regard, too.
It's just a cool experience to look at it.
Yeah, I mean, I hate this episode turning into a complete
just complain about everything else episode.
But that is where my head is at now, because I'm like Spider-Man
ride in Avengers campus.
It's like that ride is OK.
Some people say bad. I say OK.
But would it have been better for them to build?
What is a very expensive ride that ride?
Or would it have been like make some like little swing ride
with some like cheap, like simple looking buildings
that makes you kind of like dip in and out of the buildings?
And it's like your web.
Yeah, as if your web you're swinging and there's a couple static figures.
But the movement of it looks cool from like the streets.
So you get the swoop that Spidey and you get the swoop.
And it's just a simple ride.
Yeah, probably a lot cheaper than what they put in there.
It gives that zone a lot more energy.
People take a lot of pictures.
People take a lot of pictures of it.
And it ultimately is at least as popular as what's there.
That does sound really doesn't.
That's like there's got to be some little premise.
And then you've got that going all around the land instead of this
like kind of clinical.
These are offices.
These are where I go to do work. Right.
And I'm sort of basing it on that like patent that they put for like
a crazy looking swing ride that never got made
or hopefully will eventually get made with like big practical buildings.
But like make a kind of kiddie version of it.
And I don't know, maybe it makes the land better.
Yeah, in a way. Yeah.
And it's not as complained about as the ride is now.
Yes, possibly. Yeah.
But let's let's talk basics here.
Let's make sure we get just like the stuff out.
We got 18 cups.
We got three big turntables.
Let's not forget those plates.
We got those little plates as well.
Handles only because you can do those handles.
Yeah.
Step plate steps that you could trip on.
Yes, very easily. Yes.
Yeah, I'm always cautious.
Everybody should be cautious with the kids.
That is a kid. Oh, yeah.
The height of a kid.
That's a magnet for for a slip.
I had not thought about how the breakdown of the spinning happens.
That so your cups can spin.
The cups go counterclockwise.
They are then there's three turntables with six cups each.
Those all go clockwise.
Then all of it is on one big turntable, which goes counterclockwise.
So you got a lot of competing directions,
which I don't think I really clocked or appreciated is part of the dizzying effect
that you're spinning in three different ways, essentially, at all times.
Yeah, I guess I mean, it makes complete sense.
But I guess I never thought of it in that way.
But it definitely felt like you're going against the grain.
It doesn't feel to me.
I don't know about you guys.
And I don't ever feel that dizzy on it.
This particular thing doesn't make me dizzy or queasy
in the way that guardians does a little bit.
This is a good question.
How much does this affect?
Because it like it's there's the I think the notoriety through the years
of that this is the queasy maker. Right.
This is like don't get on the if you were writing a sitcom joke about Disneyland
and you didn't know anything about Disneyland. Right.
It'd probably be something about barfing when you get off the teacups.
Yes. How do people how do people feel?
Has this ever affected you in a in a nauseous way?
This was a big childhood favorite of mine. Right.
And would be at Disneyland or be a smaller park knockoffs.
And I wanted to spin it fast.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. You know, I think when I got older,
I did have the impression of like, were these always so hard to spin?
Now I learned I guess I never really thought about why.
And learning about this. Yeah.
Reading about it, it was like a purposeful choice after
someone fell getting off of one.
Yes. Or I think I think somebody stood.
I think a kid stood up and flew out of the thing.
Something that they, you know, like theoretically, if you were sitting
because this ride does not have seatbelts. Right.
And theoretically, gravity should keep you inside.
But that is undone if you if you're going crazy with it in 2004.
It's made more difficult to spin fast after a disabled rider
lost his balance and slipped from a teacup. OK.
So you could go like as fast as you possibly wanted before 2004.
Like your strength was the only thing holding you back.
Well, kind of.
This is also part of the history.
And you guys probably ran into this, too, that if you go all the way back
when the park opens July 55,
there is literally nothing stopping you from cranking this thing up
as fast as it can go.
I think in the early days, also, maybe they didn't limit
how many people could be in there, because I think there's
photos where you could see six people in.
Yeah. Or I mean, it's you're limited by just how many can physically fit.
But I think maybe they keep it in the four range.
Now, I don't I don't actually know that.
I don't know. But I think I think six people could jump on there.
And there was absolutely nothing slowing it down.
So you could just spin and spin and spin and spin in the reveal of the ride,
the reveal of the ride to an ABC television audience in the opening day.
Special. They kind of like
the characters run to this ride and they run over here and they run over here.
And the Alice in Wonderland characters run onto the turntable.
And you see the March hair just like nudge a cup.
And it like it like it spins so fast
from being like accidentally touched for balance, basically.
And it really gives you a sense of how this thing you could just crank in 55.
You could go really fast.
You buy tobacco on Main Street, no gum, no gum, no gum and no booze.
You're saying that the things you were allowed. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're saying gum was the least dangerous perhaps of the three.
I'm just saying like Walt said no gum.
He said no booze.
Yeah. So you had to. Yeah.
You couldn't you couldn't drink.
You had to get the natural high of spinning really, really fast in there.
So I think that led to probably a lot of early
vomiting from people who had never been on anything remotely like this
and you had no built in measures to stop themselves from doing it.
Yeah. I think it also led to a lot of wear and tear on the attraction.
This is some of the history and backstory that you could find is that
very early on in the first month, they are sending welders
to weld the ride back together for two hours a day every day.
That is that is the amount that this thing was just cracking apart.
Due to zero regulations on the spin.
Yeah. Now we go to an often looming figure in Disneyland history, Bob Gurr.
Bob Gurr helped put this together as well as everything.
I think the entire thing was hanging on his shoulder.
He was just he was like, you know, the handyman in the building.
Anything breaks, you call you call this one guy
and it might not get fixed for a while because it is all on the one guy
and he's got a long list and a bunch of other buildings to go to. Right.
So that is what Bob Gurr seems like for early Disneyland.
And he describes having to fix the thing and like, try to get like,
get under the hood, basically, and figure out what the hell is going on.
Why does this thing keep cracking apart so often?
And he describes doing this, getting under the attraction
while the ride is in motion.
Now, I don't know what you got under there.
I don't know. Maybe maybe it's very comfortable.
Maybe you've got 10 feet down there.
I don't know. But my suspicion is you do not.
These guys are built differently. Yeah, yes.
When men were men, you see.
Yeah, completely insane.
And then there's a there's a recent video because Bob is still with us.
And he like a like a month or so ago
went on the teacups for the first time.
And the person he's with is like, what do you mean?
You've never been on it.
And he's like, I don't know.
I look, I built the thing that made me want to go on at the least.
Never had any desire.
I know too much.
And then interesting in the video
that he he has a very particular method of spinning.
He's like, I know how to do this for maximum pleasure.
I know when to do it and I know when to stop.
And they're like, how? I built it.
All right. Just know I know from looking.
I like so Bob Gerr said, if you watch this video, he like his method,
because you might think just spin and spin and spin and spin.
And maybe that is the most pleasurable way to do it.
But Bob Gerr, having never been on it, just like is here's my
here's my method. I don't know what it is.
Did he explain? He didn't explain it.
It'd be hard. It was hard for me to parse.
And I think you'd have to watch it to understand.
But it was not dissimilar from what I do these days.
I think I'm a kid and I'm just spinning and spinning and spinning.
I think now what I like to do is like put in a big run and then like
he's off and then like kind of like not worry about it for a second and just cruise.
And then we lose a little bit of speed and we come back to it.
We crank it up again.
But I like I really like all right.
Like sprints, sprints, sprints, sprints, now relax and and so on and so forth.
Because it's nice to just like, well, it's fun to spin.
It's also fun to like just lean back, put your arms up on the side,
just kind of just just cruise, just just let momentum do it.
Because you can really tire out your arms completely.
Yeah. Yeah. Which is why I mean, I mean, you must have done this with your brother
instead that like if you're with another kid and or a group of kids.
Oh, yeah. And you can just collectively
use all of your little energy.
Yeah. And just and probably not lay back and enjoy the sights.
Just try to get that thing going as fast as you can.
Seems like fun. That's right.
Yeah. Every time there was a bunch of kids, that would be the case.
Yeah. I think classic Disneyland experience, I think.
Yeah. But I'm more what you're saying now.
I don't I don't need to go nuts with it because I also like to like
give me a second to like take in the Matterhorn just like and kind of like
enjoy because it is always spinning, even if you want to spin it.
Like, let me enjoy the wide.
Let me let me do the macro spin now.
Oh, yeah. And do the micro spin.
Well, and especially if it's a night.
Yes. Oh, my gosh. It's great at night.
Disneyland at night. Yes.
The lanterns that were added are wonderful.
I think the placemaking here is fantastic.
Yes. That they created this little Alice mini land
because Alice I've said before, I think might be my favorite of the of the dark rides.
And I really like it.
The exterior and the caterpillars are coming in and out.
And I like that it's all in the shadow of the Matterhorn.
I like that monorails are passing by and storybook land.
Those boats are launching.
It's kind of that like I can get a little stressed out in main drag
fantasy land, you know, because it's like two rides here, two rides here,
like lines that pile up real fast, carousel clogging up the way.
And I kind of like let me relax a little.
Let me go over to chill fantasy land, too.
This is your side nook.
Yeah, we were. It's more like pastoral, you know?
Yeah, I know.
And then you can get out a little bit easier that sort of toward the
yeah, out toward the convenient Alice bathrooms with a lot of built in
wall seating, one of the best.
They put them back in the best bathroom.
You hear all kinds of your music from every direction.
It's all kind of different. Yeah, that is a fun.
You get a fun carnival kind of atmosphere.
A bunch of different cues coming in and out.
Maybe a little monorail honk.
Maybe I hear a little bit of Swiss Alps music from Matterhorn.
Yeah, it's just it's a magic zone in the park.
I agree. And I think you got to credit Tony Baxter for this unless he
who knows the breakdown of what people do in these land overhauls.
But this where the teacups are now is a post 83 thing, a post new fantasy land
thing, because in the 50s you go through the castle.
That's carousel right there.
And then it's teacups right behind it.
Barely any room between and I think Dumbo right in there, too.
Dumbo move is kind of a flip almost where the carousel is.
Now is where the teacups was.
Yes. Yes.
I believe. OK. Yeah.
So then they just yeah, the carousel moved.
But it was sort of like early teacups seem maybe a little unpleasant
because you don't have the lighting fixtures.
Yeah, there's nothing above it.
Yeah. Yes. Yeah.
When and it is just it did seem like kind of like a big open
hot kind of area. That's true.
I think they didn't paint it originally.
And it was just kind of brown wood.
Gray. Yeah. Yeah.
And then they paint it the spiral.
Yes. Underneath. Yeah.
Red and yellow, which may look cool for Skyway.
I'm sure. Yeah.
Yeah. But I don't know.
I think that I think that move had some some magic to it.
I think that I agree. New little nook is.
I think where it moved to was kind of empty space. Right.
Right. From what I saw.
I still think you have visually,
especially if you're a kid, you walk in and there's big teacups.
It looks the old version still looks pretty awesome.
If that's your expectation, like.
But yes, the new version added an extra layer of of Disney
magic to it, for sure. Yeah, I believe.
So the teacups are in five of the six
Magic Kingdom Disneyland style parks. Correct.
I don't think they're in Shanghai. Yeah.
This is the only one that's uncovered by like a pavilion.
Yes. Yeah.
Which the pavilions kind of help.
They can run in the rain because covered. Yeah.
And the hot beating sun.
It's some relief, some shade from the sun. Right. Right.
I'm going to do a little gotcha.
I've been looking up. I've been looking at some maps.
I've been looking at some overheads.
Was I wrong about the carousel? Wrong about the carousel has not moved.
I think you are. I think you're thinking of unless.
Oh, wait. Or am I crazy?
Was it? You know what? I can't tell what I'm looking at.
I don't know if it was Dumbo that was right past the.
No, wasn't it always carousel?
No, I think it was always carousel. Yes.
Yeah, that is correct.
What did they read then on Yesterland?
Maybe I misread something.
Well, I've seen that it's like the only attraction that did like a full flip.
But I think what that is, is the flip of Dumbo and
and teacups. I believe this is what I this is what I am seeing.
Um, did I need to say that?
Was that a fight that I needed to win? No.
I guess. I like to be accurate.
Yes, it was.
We need to. I think.
OJER needs to be pronounced correctly and I need to know where the teacups were.
I think Disneyland Fantasyland, I feel like it's a sort of thing.
People think, well, this has been there forever.
This has been just like this forever and it has been there since 55.
Yeah, yeah. But it's but it's important to correct those people
and say they're wrong. They're dead wrong.
And it's important to shame them and make make them know where they're incorrect.
Yeah, I don't know. I'll look it up.
I think Disney World to you might be confusing stuff.
And Disney World Fantasyland, expand it in the 2010s.
Maybe stuff open and closed.
Mad Tea Party was located where the King Arthur Carousel sits today.
That's what it says on Yesterland. OK, so.
But I do think here I'm looking at I'm looking at 59.
This is just a piece of art, by the way.
But what I'm looking at is that you walk in carousels right there.
Now, maybe Carousel moved a little bit, maybe it backed up a little bit.
That might be what happened. Yeah.
That might be what it's saying then. Yeah, yeah.
I I wish I'd put a financial value on this correction, though.
Oh, you wanted to bet? Yeah.
Yeah, it's too late. It is too late.
I mean, you can't bet in reverse.
No, it wouldn't really make sense.
I think you just have to look in your heart and think about what you owe me for this.
But isn't it unclear? It's unclear versus this.
So I don't know if the bet would have completely gone through.
Well, I could be if we not.
Maybe we haven't officially solved it yet.
I don't know that we've officially solved it.
Well, look, and to go back and like be looking at different.
I already got I got so many tabs open.
I still got wabos open. I got locked in.
Yeah, no, I hear you open.
And we should still keep talking, I guess.
I guess so.
What do we think about Disneyland as opposed to the other version,
especially Magic Kingdom version?
Well, I like the little pavilion that Magic Kingdom is kind of in.
But I like the lantern.
I mean, the lanterns at night are really lovely.
Yeah. That said, can operate in the rain.
Has to do some cleanup after a rain, you know, still the case.
Or is that an old is that reported?
But I feel like I've been there in the rain and it is it might be heavy rain.
But there is some something with the turntables in the rain.
Least in the past. Right.
I mean, I think it's better open air. Yeah.
But yeah, I'm not mad at it with the thing, with the coverings.
But yeah, I think it's better open air. I'm mad. I am mad at it.
I think that they're cowardly to put those overhangs on.
Disney World did.
Actually, Disney World opened, I think, with it open air.
And then a couple of years.
Well, with the weather and the hurricanes, they decided maybe we need something.
And I think that's a fear based move.
And I think you can't, you know, you can't run forever.
And I think there was a lot of cowardice on the part of those people.
Scott's been watching a lot of Silicon Valley
hustle grindset, you know, can't live a fear based life kind of stuff.
And, you know, yeah, yeah.
I think that they should we should start our own
like Save Splash Mountain campaign to get rid of that covering.
We should do a whole like, yeah, a petition.
There was when they, you know, made it harder to spin in the early 2000s.
I saw an excerpt from like Associated Press, Sacramento Bee
about like people like, it's just not as fun.
You know, it's all these lawsuits and everyone's so safety conscious now.
And it's like, God damn it.
History really does rhyme. This shit never changes.
Wait, wait, go on.
I mean, I mean, just every time there's a change, people go like,
it's just not the same as it used to be. Sure.
Yeah. But aren't we here complaining about all the new shit they've done lately?
Well, I think I bet more of a problem.
Finally, though, we're right about that.
The thing is, yes, everyone who did it before was not right.
And that's what makes us special and cool is that we are right
and everything we say is right.
We have we're precision complainers, too.
We complain about the exact right things to complain about.
It's like Tobias Arrested Development.
Has that ever worked before? No.
But this time, this time for us, it might just work.
Similar, yes.
But yes, I think open air, cooler. Yeah.
Nicer. But yeah, the other ones,
they want to save money, I bet.
Save maintenance money.
You think it's that, too?
Well, probably, I mean, if it's if the if it gets a beating during a storm,
they're probably covering and they can run it, I guess, during a storm, too.
That's why guests shouldn't be fear based either.
We need it is our duty to go on this ride in the rain. OK.
I'd love to go and then you get the closest to an actual teacup
experience if the if the by vehicle is flooding was filled up.
Yeah. Uh huh. And your waist deep in water, dirty water resembling tea
smacked in the face by dirty teawater.
Wow. Yeah. Yeah.
Jason, what liquid would you want in your teacup?
If you could choose, if you had to do the ride with a liquid.
Michael, I I feel like I would put tea bags in all my pockets.
It's early in the day English breakfast, late in the day, like chamomile.
OK, I mean, I'm just saying you don't have to do this on the slide.
This is an official Disney sponsored event
where you could just put in Diet Pepsi if you want it.
You could do the ride with Diet Pepsi.
Well, I think the bubbles would be irritating. That's fair.
Even on a two and a half, three minute orange juice.
Well, that's definitely going to be irritating.
Yeah. Cranberry juice.
I also I like what he's thinking with his first answer, too,
which is saving money on expensive tea,
but not having to buy tea at the parts by bringing your own from home,
letting the teacup fill up and then just sopping it up from the inside.
You got some milk jugs like, OK, you can bring that home for later.
Yeah, you can scoop it up like, yeah.
All right, needle, I'm moving slow.
I get now the teacup and then just out of a backpack,
just start scooping the tea in the milk jugs. Yeah.
And then you're just then you're just leaving.
Then all you have to do is leave the park with just a just a conspicuous
backpack that you just play it cool and pretend that you don't have
eight full jugs in there. Yeah.
Of dirty of of tea bags mixed with rainwater.
You just get like, oh, I'm I'm a sponsorship from Lip Dead.
The official tea of Disney.
I've got the Lambie. I've got a laminate.
It says Lipton on it.
Little Lipton boy.
By the way, that's a little Lipton boy I love.
And I love saying I'm so sick of saying the big complicated word laminate.
Why? There's never been a cute nickname for laminate.
Lambie. Adorable.
Lambie is cute. Yeah, you get a Lambie.
You go backstage for the Wobbo, the Wobbo gang.
I got a Lambie for the Wobbo show. Yeah. Yeah.
I know I do like this, though, and then I like that two months later,
maybe you have a friend over.
You want to actually, you know what the let's keep hanging out.
You want to come up. Are you thirsty?
Yeah. You want to drive 90 minutes to Anaheim and help me with some.
Well, I'm saying this is I think that you're like you're just in your apartment
two months later and like you want to come up there.
You want some tea or something? Yeah, I do.
And then they're drinking like, oh, this is delicious.
I really like this. Who makes this?
Well, it's funny.
I put a bunch of tea bags in my pocket to Disneyland
and mixed it with rainwater two months ago.
They called me the human teabag
and there's nothing around.
I don't mean that in any sort of suspicious sexual sense.
That said, I do mean that in the in the sexual erotic sense as well.
I'm just saying separately.
Two different things apply. One name, two things.
Do you was the did the skyway go right over the buckets?
Could you have dumped scalding hot water from the skyway bucket
into one of the teacups or is it a little bit to the side?
I don't know the geography of that sugar, at least some sugar.
Could it have been?
Could you have run an empty skyway bucket with hot water,
tipped it, dropped it into one of the teacups?
I think you are in prime position. Yeah, yeah, I think so.
And then the next one, you need a little bit of projection.
It's not directly under you.
And then one of the buckets would have a bunch of sugar
and we could have honey in another one.
You could sort of make your perfect tea.
So you're terrorizing the teacup riders.
Well, in my mind, it's sort of a fun, cute little thing.
You don't have to have a rider in there necessarily,
is that you could like make tea, make tea perfectly with two rides.
It would be kind of a cute Rube Goldberg style.
So this would have to be arranged with the with the park.
I think so. Hours.
But I guess you could do the gorilla version of it with people
with somebody who says a bucket of scalding hot water on the skyway
and dumps it into dumps it out of there.
And then somebody throws handfuls.
Well, that's why Obama's friend got escorted out of Disneyland.
But Obama got escorted out
because he was puffing on a sea.
They were trying to teach up. They're trying to.
Yeah. Yeah.
Excuse me. No, no drinks on the skyway.
Oh, no, it's fine. This is.
Oh, you mean my my gigantic bucket of scalding hot water.
This is this is a therapeutic.
I'm going to put my feet in this on the feet are killing me.
I go ahead, sir, to be able to walk for the bunion treatment.
Oh, very well. OK, I didn't realize.
What else about this?
They also are in terms of early day aggro cups,
which I think it's I think it was either late 55 or 56
that they added like breaks, like something to like a max speed.
But you got a good six months where you could just go
as fast as you cared to go.
I knew there was something left off the checklist.
What do you mean of building building the teacups?
Oh, I forgot to write the word breaks.
I put everything else.
There's very funny old archival footage of the Disneyland band
riding the teacups, like one instrumentalist in each one.
That's fun. Yeah, I like that.
They also did when this thing opened, half teacups weren't decorated.
They didn't have doors.
You didn't do it. There wasn't the disk inside.
So you just had to find another weighted.
I guess. OK, so that stopped people from spinning just crazily.
Right. You could just you just because how else would you do it?
I've definitely written some off brand teacups without the doors. OK.
It's just the whole and like the get Gravitron with the spinning.
You're being pushed back. Yeah. Yeah.
You guys ever been anywhere?
Because I feel like I found this.
I found this at Knott's.
I think I found this at Elitch Gardens.
Have you been anywhere is it's it's kiddie rides, especially
where you have to be it's it's like the the person at the grocery store
on like taking the the the cap off of the bottle, off of the liquor bottle,
where like only the special little key does it.
This is a thing on rides that likes the ride operator, who also starts it,
does the announcement at the beginning, then has to go around to every
single person in the ride with their special key in order to let them out.
You ever been in on anything like that?
I feel like I think I have.
Is that just a simple clock key, though?
A clock? Well, I don't know.
Do you know what a clock is a clock?
Like if you
are winding a clock
like an old fashioned like mantelpiece clock, I got I have one in my office.
You have a clock key.
I I've not bought in the clock key because the mantel.
We had one on like the fireplace when I was growing up
and you had to wind it like once a week or every couple of weeks or something.
I'm going to say that that like the swing ride doesn't operate with a clock key.
I think, you know, there's different sizes.
A clock key on Amazon.
You can buy clock keys.
Is a clock bigger than a normal key?
Wouldn't it just be a regular key that just does a different thing?
No, it's it's kind of like it's like a tubular.
It reminds me that's that's all of a very specific type of.
Yeah, not just a weird shaped key.
OK, this this week.
But the thing is, with like an old style clock, you have to wind.
It will chime every hour on the hour and sometimes in the half hour.
Do you have an old do you have an old clock?
Or I did when someone was moving out and left a bunch of stuff,
you know, where people leave like freebie stuff.
OK, how big is this clock?
Oh, OK. Not a full grandfather clock.
No, no grandfather clocks, I think, operate differently, but you might have to.
There are keys for grandfather clocks.
There are key. OK.
I recall my grandmother having a grandfather clock that had a key you would insert.
Michael, stop eating the grandfather clock key like Ducky, the Disney duck.
Oh, the official magic.
I wasn't here for that episode.
He eats a key.
Yeah. So Ducky is the official magic key
mascot for Disneyland's magic keys.
And there's a story that Ducky lived in Disneyland and loved it for many, many years.
And then a couple of years ago, he ate a key at the bottom of the river.
And bottom of the moat, bottom of the moat.
He ate it. And now he can go a lot of different places in Disneyland.
That is what they said.
The narrative really was complaining about story.
This is a real shitty story.
It doesn't make any sense.
Ducky seems to exist primarily on Instagram reels and some website posts.
But Ducky, he ate the key for no reason.
We don't know why he ate the key.
I know that you did this episode and I saw people saying, what are they talking about?
I cannot find the source material.
There are about three Instagram posts about Ducky.
And I wanted to get on top of it before anybody else did.
Well, that was also I think a good like Scott's gone.
Ducky time.
Ducky gets his due.
Yes. Come on out, Ducky.
Scott and his allergic ears.
We can be little Ducky boys.
That's the kind of thing you get on our Patreon.
This is what you get.
You get to hear about Ducky, the Disney Magic Key Duck.
Ninety minutes about three videos of a duck that are impossible for you to find.
We have another one where we I was like, hey, you're rubbing your hands.
Yeah, it wasn't rubbing.
Well, because I was Mike, we were driving home from here once, I think.
And I was like, what about an episode of this?
And he was like, yeah, I also was thinking about that.
What was it? Maybe when Scott's.
No, I'll tell you later.
I'll remind you later.
Oh, just come tell him. Yeah.
Statue of Lou Wasserman.
Statue of Lou Wasserman herself.
You're not going to believe the statue of Lou Wasserman at Universal.
He disappeared right after he moved to try me not to even checked in on Lou Wasserman.
These motherfuckers be so crazy.
As soon as their dad, the narc is gone.
They start rubbing that, you know, we can do we can do the statue of Lou Wasserman.
What is it? Where where was this?
This was originally in Universal Studios, Florida,
kind of as the San Francisco area transitions into New York.
It was moved to open up the space for like crowds and parade floats.
And now he has since gotten a pedestal in the Central Park area by the water.
But at some point, he disappeared from there.
And so I don't know if he's been put back.
Lou Wasserman, of course, an early head of Universal
Films, something like the development of the ride.
Well, we haven't done the episode yet.
Guess what? I just tricked you.
You just said all of the pertinent information in the episode.
There will be no episode.
Back to the teacups.
Have you seen the I found a website of a bunch of knockoff teacups that you could get?
Yes. I have I have a couple.
Well, these are the one I have doesn't have any fun names, but it's like
it's like Sino rides dot com.
And you can buy S.I.N.O.R.I.D.E.S.
And you can get like this is for like renting them.
Yeah. Oh, I see. Or sale.
I mean, I have not seen Sino rides.
Like you can get one that kind of looks like you've got like paint
coming out of all the cups.
It's like very carnival style.
Jason, you're looking blue and red and it looks paint is.
Yeah. Teacups, I think.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm looking up for water and shit.
You but you guys have your fun.
And the real fun's over here.
Yeah. And there's a fancy there's like you can get like a fancier
like teacup ride with like, you know, this is more like
very grand. That's what you would take the queen on.
Right. Exactly. This is the queen's teacup ride.
So, yeah, there's it is often like a flat ride.
They call me usually, you know, it can be put on a flat move.
Yeah. So there's a lot of different.
Yeah. The knockoff versions.
I guess, yeah, they want you to buy this.
They don't want you to rent these.
These look like they want you to permanently install them.
Ones that I've found.
There's one that used to be at Fiesta Village at Knott's Berry Farm.
I don't think it's still there anymore.
There's the one called Hat Dance in a sombrero, I think.
I went on this one in Gilroy Gardens.
This is one of the like more odd, fun, just simple rides ever.
Garlic twirl where you're in a big garlic
not bulb, bulb, bulb, I think.
Garlic knot is like a thing.
You get an Italian restaurant.
That's a good idea, though, too.
Yes. Yeah, yeah.
You're in the mechanism that's like getting all of the seasoning
onto the garlic knots.
Oh, yeah. Well, is are you saying this is at Gilroy Gardens?
No, no, no. These are raw. This is raw garlic.
Oh, OK. But a hypothetical garlic
knot ride would be good. Yeah.
In a Pizza Hut theme park.
Oh, now I've got a lot of ideas immediately.
Well, they should really do honestly.
They should do the what is the yum brands?
It should be it should be yum lands.
Yeah, I would I would help them with portals that take you or like the
if you're in, I don't know what like
I don't know how you get from one or the other, but the realms of KFC.
Well, OK. Well, hold on.
I'll fight you to get my idea out first.
Oh, you go ahead.
Then you both say the same thing at the same time,
even though it's sentences long.
Well, if they're different lands, I think they should take inspiration
from the old boat ride that was at the Luxor Hotel and Casino
that would take was practical, but also a boat ride.
It took you a room. Yeah.
It took you around the casino floor.
So if you rode a river Pepsi around the outside of the park
and you could get off at each land, similar to the Disneyland Railroad,
at every young brand.
Yeah. Yeah. Go to the Colonel's Kingdom.
That's good.
I was going to say you get into you can either come into Pizza Hut land
or exit Pizza Hut land through a big stuffed crust tunnel.
Oh, that's great.
Which is, yeah, like they're hollowed out crust with a little cheese on the walls.
Yes. Yeah. Well, and I guess one big tipped over bucket, obviously,
for Colonel's Kingdom. Yeah, for sure. Yeah.
Who would you want to see reflected in Pizza Hut?
Are there other characters from pizza?
And we aren't even I forgot Taco Bell.
I mean, yeah, obviously, that's all right.
That's a whole thing.
Scott, do not ruin this for us.
Pizza Hut, do not ruin this with big New Yorker mishmash stuff.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I thought you were getting to Donald Trump being the spokesman
for Pizza Hut, the big New Yorker.
I was not.
No, I can't say that was on the front of my mind.
But what do you?
Well, I guess because you say because he asked where,
like if there were any characters in the first character
you thought it was Donald Trump.
Yeah, because I couldn't remember it like a Burger King's Kids Club.
Well, right. Pizza Hut is low on is like big famous mascot characters.
But that is so funny that the one mascot you think of when Pizza Hut comes up
as the president, the Book It logo.
Well, what about the Ringo Starr Pizza commercial with the monkeys?
That's a famous. Oh, I'm sorry.
Mine was too obscure.
Yeah, I think we think everyone.
I do remember it.
But I didn't say that's like as popular as the Noid was from Domino's.
I'm just saying.
Well, OK, so that would be that would be a facet of Pizza Hut.
Land is the walk around Donald Trump with a sign somebody else.
Somebody's walking next to him with a sign with an arrow
that's an apology sign that says this is Trump due to his appearance
in a Pizza Hut commercial.
This does not reference his presidency. Right. Right.
Don't be mad.
It's a good. Yeah, that'll fix it.
I mean, it could be the Chinese Donald Trump.
What? The guy.
There's a guy in China.
What's happened in the last five minutes?
There's a guy in China who does a very good Donald Trump.
It's very funny.
How does that get around the issue? He walks.
He can be OK.
He can be the character.
Pizza Hut ad. We will do a Chinese.
We will do the Chinese Donald Trump.
No further explanation.
Shouldn't do any teach shows people the size.
And he works at the American Pizza Hut Park,
but no one's mad at him because he's not.
What is the type of online where you find the things that we've never heard of?
Well, this is pretty popular.
This is a tick tock.
Cut to comments.
Jason is right.
He knows the thing.
And I guess God are dumb.
They don't know the thing.
And also all the sex things he mentions, Mike and Scott should know, too.
All right. We should.
If we commit to how we're going to,
although I think I think yum yum lands is worth flushing.
That's a whole nother further in the future.
But if we're going to stick to the construct that we have done for Class of 55,
where we have brought back our old mechanism of, you know, keep it as is,
plus it up, burn it down for the insurance money.
How do we feel after 70 years of the teacups?
Yeah, I mean, I really was thinking about this of like, what is any
what is a way to plus it up?
It's hard to improve on perfection.
I guess maybe you could make the mechanism a little easier to turn it somehow.
Yeah. Like the way you bring that back a little bit like the way you turn it now.
Yes, there's a lot of resistance and it does feel like you work
have to work pretty hard to turn it.
Is there a way to make you turn it?
But that doesn't it's not like you actually are using like one to one energy
to turn it with resistance.
Is there a way to just kind of like turn it and make it feel like you're turning it?
But there's some sort of motor underneath that's actually doing the turning
that doesn't make it as hard on your wrists and your arms.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, I guess, like, like, don't like right now you are wanting in the work to turn.
Yes, I guess it would be fake in some ways.
I'm not saying I want I'm thinking about this, like, because, yeah,
you if you really want to go fast, it feels like you get off with sore arms.
Hi. Maybe that's not good.
I'm just saying that you could change it to make it was probably an easier mechanism.
But I think we overrate how sore you get on these.
OK, it's not so bad news.
And then we did the canoes.
And I'm like, what has everybody been complaining about?
This is not so the canoes.
I got Mr. Strong, man.
I just think it's not a little more of a workout with the canoes and the
key cups. Yeah, certainly. Yeah.
But I do feel I do feel it on whipslingers.
Another complaint that I do feel very exhausted.
But I guess that's because that's nobody's guiding me.
No mechanism is I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
I just throw my arms around and I guess I do it in a way that hurts.
When Kermit's upset, that's what you do on Spider-Man or excited.
Often excited.
Well, nothing destroys my arms like Toy Story.
By the end of Toy Story, my wrists, my wrists and my arm feel feel crazy.
Yeah. I'm going so fast.
I'm going so hard on that.
I want to win so badly that I'm going I'm going sicko mode.
That's what I'm doing, which I'm going to guess gets you the fourth one up.
Yeah, I'm not even the only one that is possible to get.
I know it's if you work incredibly hard once in a while,
I will get a couple of the secret things that open up the up the boards.
Yes, those are fun.
And if you get those and I can do pretty well, then maybe I can get up the third tier.
Yeah. God, that's so difficult. Yeah.
So other than that, it's like the ride vehicles are perfect.
The setting is pretty perfect.
The music, which is kind of like it's very, very fun
and is very Alice in Wonderland appropriate.
It's the unbirthday song.
I suppose once in a while they could give me a different song.
Now, it doesn't have to be a popular rock and roll.
So it doesn't have to be Pink's Raise a Glass.
It could be a different Disney song, perhaps.
But from Pink's song, any pink song, any pink song.
Get this party started, whatever it was called.
I know four or five pink songs.
You want an after hours event that's all pink songs
and the limiters on the teacups are removed.
Yeah, well, I want a reckless night at Disneyland or something
where you pay two hundred dollars and you sign a waiver.
And then but I don't want pink force.
If it's reckless night, I don't want I want something crazy being played.
You want to purge.
I want Slayer being played while I'm on the teacups or something.
That's that's a different vibe.
You know what? It's funny.
You mentioned this because in pre thinking about what a plus it up might be
and also in looking up a weird off model,
not off model, but just other places that have done teacup type attractions.
Six Flags Great America is the one in Chicago.
Yes. They have a ride that during the day is called Chubasco
and it's a pretty standard teacup.
I would say with some notably good cups and a big it's what I'm looking at.
It's too dark to see what's in the middle.
But just good, like, you know, glassware sculpture in the middle.
But at night or at least at Fright Fest,
they have remade it and do something called Terror Twister.
And let me give you guys a vibe for the listener.
Just picture very dark lighting strobe lights and then this kind of music.
Oh, that's it's like purple lighting.
What is that song here?
I don't know what the song is off hand.
It is called My Invisible Friend.
They also seem to play something called Wolves of Darkness.
OK, that's a scary title if I ever heard one.
Yeah, but I could see that did just open up with Six Flags can do it.
Doing like a scary, an after dark version of the teacups
where you feel as though you are trapped in some kind of horrible saw mechanism.
Yeah. And almost made to spin like if someone's yelling at you faster, faster.
Yeah, make it.
I think it's it very easily, I think, lends to terrifying experience.
Yeah, I think so, too.
I think music, especially the music and a little lighting change could really do it.
I mean, a full fantasy land Halloween villains overlay.
Yeah. Some kind feels like a kind of simple idea that would be very popular.
A lot of villain songs.
That's true. Yeah. Lines or speeches or stuff.
Is there one that sticks out to you that you'd want to hear on the teacups?
Oh, probably something from Wish.
Oh, OK. Is there a villain in Wish?
There is a villain in Wish.
I forget who the villain is.
Because I want to hear what's the opposite of a star, the moon, the moon.
Oh, my God. Big, scary moon wants to eat the star.
Yeah, that's perfect.
I'm glad I haven't seen Wish too scared.
What about Hellfire on the teacups?
Oh, there we go.
Oh, and then it kind of becomes what is it within?
Like then you're kind of like you are just inside the tumultuous feelings of
your inside lust.
What's his character? What's the Frodo Frodo Frollo?
I don't think it's Frodo Frodo.
I think it's Hoosier.
Frollo is close, Claude Frollo.
Oh, so all right.
So the overlay is Claude Frollo's erotic nightmares.
Oh, God. Yeah. Yeah.
And then you can you light it with fire colors, right?
Just put some orange and red and then like, you know,
sexy silhouettes of Esmeralda.
Yeah. On the side of the of the Matterhorn.
And there's maybe, you know, maybe there's something phallic about that.
That's like, you know, the the it's not explicitly said,
but if you want to imagine that the Matterhorn is Claude Frollo's misshapen dick.
I mean, I do want to imagine that.
You stupid fool.
Like the Matterhorn is just I was going to say it's him.
It's a giant version of him where it's his big mouth when it's goofy hat.
Hellfire.
You know, we've never we've recently, you know, we've talked about,
like feeling like we want rides with different emotions,
not just thrills and chills.
And we were talking about wanting to feel melancholy, sadness, sort of tranquility.
But we really don't have a good lust ride.
You don't have a ride that really simulates lust.
Well, we have nights and white satin, but it's gone.
All right. But that wasn't was that lust.
Did you feel lust? That was more of a no.
Were you when you were thinking like some candles turned the lights down?
Oh, you think that we just discovered Jason's biggest make out.
Oh, yeah. Wow.
That's what not a lot happening at those dorm rooms.
One of the new always blow it was blurring and he's playing nights
and white satin again, and I heard a door slam.
That's one of the more newer songs you've been listening to, though.
More recent pre Jane before before all the twenty
twenty's music and he's parking back up.
I hear bugy, woogie, woogie, woogie, woogie, woogie, woogie, woogie, boy.
It's just I'm just too excited by my songs.
Anyway, yeah.
No, I think that's it.
I think it was the name of it again.
Just for my
Claude Claude Frollo, they are the erotic nightmares of Claude
Claude Frollo.
We need a Frollo ride in a park, an American park.
And it just ends with a blood curdling scream.
And you're left to determine, is that him like
like stabbing himself in the heart?
Yeah. Or ejaculating.
It is up to choose your own adventure.
Yeah. Yeah. Your interpretation.
I did a search on Twitter.
It seems like the Lou Asterman statue came back at the beginning of the year.
But as of late March, it's gone again.
I was correct.
People keep stealing it.
Is there a is there a whole thing?
Is there a high school graduating class
that Dr.
Philips high school right behind Universal is playing some?
Oh, thank you. It's like a whole senior prank.
Yeah. Seniors rule every year in Orlando.
There's a senior prank to steal the on rival school.
Universal Studios. Right. Yeah.
I mean, oh, man, if you're a high school senior,
oh, what I wouldn't give to get my hands on Lou Watson. Yeah.
Seniors rule Lou Wasserman drools.
Well, that's true. All right.
Unless there's closing thoughts on the way out the door.
I think you survive.
I guess the ride.
Well, I was just going to say capacity wise,
I feel like I couldn't see a good number because I think per ride,
it said 72, which be four people per teacup.
That's too many.
All right. I don't think that's too much on that note.
You survive. I guess the right.
Maybe it's too. What is it?
How do you feel about that?
I think well, and then I saw 1,400 people per hour.
And I'm like, that's I feel like if everything's running exactly
like the ride is exactly as long, it takes everyone
like 90 seconds to get in and out.
You know, hell fire.
This false capacity makes me burn.
You survive podcast the ride
for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast the second gate or get one more bonus episode
on our VIP to your club three.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
What else do you want to hear as far as class of 55?
Is there weird bullshit that didn't make it very far past 55?
Let us know.
I if you want your thoughts on Yum land as well.
Brands land. Yeah.
Oh, that's well, that's the whole.
This would be the most easily greenlit theme park on earth.
I'm surprised that there hasn't been something like it. Mm hmm.
Yeah, it's so exciting.
The thing is, but it'll start with a bunch of ride ideas
and then it'll end up just a bunch of rooms where you look at facts
about the company and it's, you know, and and to bring it all back,
our company's story, our company's value and our company's story.
Yeah. So starts a big chicken bucket and then it just becomes.
Here's how KFC enables people to live their chicken stories all across the world.
Bronze statue in every land.
Colonel Sanders and one, the late yoke hero talk about dog
and the other we don't we don't think enough about how he's sorry.
Glenn Bell, you lost out.
Everyone's forgotten about you.
All right, P.
Pour out a hot cup of tea for Glenn Bell.
Oh, Mike's favorite talk about water is called.
I got a cup of tea.
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcast dot com.