Forever!
Dog!
Warning!
The following podcast contains late-night Woody Woodpecker business, very bad pillows,
and the citizens of Bluffington.
Personal stylist and my new wife Jane Clare joins.
It's me!
How did you get in here?
Shoo shoo!
Baby!
It's Doug Live on Podcast The Ride!
Well, don't you dare.
Let her do it.
No!
If you want to do it so bad, then you get your joke out.
Okay.
There's your chance though, Jane.
Jump in.
Don't you dare.
Yeah, I like this.
I like this.
We're shaking it up.
This is good.
Yeah.
We're recording now.
This is part of it.
Yay!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the show where we try to embody the nobility of the humble
quail.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
I'm here and I'm feeling humble, I guess.
Humble and noble.
And Scott Caron.
I know, I try to stress the noble side more than the humility, with a lot of facets to
cover.
There's a lot of nobility in what we do, and that's something we really need to dwell
upon more.
Yeah.
Look in each other's eyes.
We're essential workers in the media, as we learned a few years ago.
That's true.
That was a good, I'm like, what from the world of Doug can a joke be pulled out?
And that was a very surprising one.
Yeah.
Excellent work.
Thank you.
All right.
You didn't quite slip it in there without your, as you said right before I started recording,
blushing bride.
My beautiful blushing bride.
Let me bring her in.
How often have you said that out loud since it happened?
I said it now because I knew it would make her smile.
My new wife, my love, Jane Clare is here.
Hello.
Hi.
Welcome back, Jane.
Hello.
Congratulations.
No, obviously we've seen you, but we haven't seen you where it counts, on the air.
So here now with people listening, congratulations on your recent wedding.
Thank you so much.
You have said blushing bride a few times, in a cute way.
Oh, thank you.
You have.
It's cute.
I like it.
Also, I want to say, when he called me the ball and chain, I thought it was so funny.
We say that all the time, the old ball and chain.
It's fun.
I didn't take it personally.
Oh, I figured.
No, no.
It's a thing.
I forget what episode that occurred in, but I just thought it was funny to hear that phrase
after a long ... He's really milking it about your styling and your ... I think we were
too offensive to the computer program, where you pick Minnie Mouse's dresses, and Jason
needed to inform us that styling is actually complicated in art.
Very complex career.
That Minnie Mouse computer, I think, really disrespected it and kind of infantilized it
in a way.
I'm glad these things were corrected.
That's true, yeah.
Look, Jason likes the old-time language, too.
That's true.
Were you a fan of the old-time language before getting together with Jason?
No.
Pretty quick, no.
He's talking so much about the 1920s.
I like it.
It's always so funny when he says something sincerely, and he uses a phrase.
I have to go, could you explain that, actually?
I'm trying to stay sincere, but I don't actually know what that means.
Do we have a good one?
Let's put you on the spot.
The other day, I said something about radio silence, which is a common phrase.
That's not really what I would consider.
No, but I was talking about the origins of, like, you never want silence on the radio.
Is that what radio silence is?
But that's not what I would ... worse for where?
I don't even know.
He says worse for where a lot, but that one I kind of know now.
Like, Gone Mole, he'll say.
Oh, yeah, that was unfamiliar to me.
Well, you just hear mole, and you think shopping mole.
Whenever it was first said, I did not have gun mole at the ready as the primary use of mole.
I actually am not aware of what that is.
This is what you are to him now.
You're his gun mole, right?
Like a gangster's girl.
Like a monster's girl.
Jason is a gangster, and you're his girl.
Big jacket, leopard print.
Fur.
Yeah, a big mink stole.
A lot of red lips.
What anniversary is the mink stole anniversary?
I don't know.
What is Jane Getter mink stole?
He's going to forget anyway.
Jason's the squirrely gangster, apparently.
Hey, what are you doing?
He's the distraction.
How often are you listening to Podcast the Riot, and you hear him say something that younger people say,
and you feel like you're responsible for his knowledge of modern slang?
Once in a while?
I love you guys so dearly, but I do not listen to every episode.
We're not asking that.
We're not requiring that.
We're just saying if you listen, ever.
You've said a few things where I'm like, oh, that's funny.
We were talking about that the other day.
I don't know.
I can't think of anything off the top of my head, but yes, that has happened before.
It's just a strange blend that we have with your husband here,
where it's a high degree of knowledge of slang from 2025 or from 1925.
You just don't see this blend, I think, very often in people.
I can only assume that the 2025 comes from you.
Thank you so much.
And yes, I think that is an accurate statement.
Thanks for bringing him to Modern Times.
You're welcome.
Also, have you been...
I don't know how I feel about him in Modern Times, honestly.
I don't care for it.
I prefer he didn't know anything.
I think you've really stoked the fire of Jason being a man out of time.
I think that's kind of the...
That's the brand that I've tried to cultivate for him.
Sure, and I've cultivated by just existing.
That's right.
With a myriad of obscure interests.
Certain companies have more than one brand.
That's okay. Hot Topic is Hot Topic, but also Box Lunch.
So Jason is now Hot Topic and Box Lunch.
That's actually a really good analogy.
Hot Topic definitely is from the early 1900s.
Right, right.
Box Lunch is really modern.
Really old-timey.
If you're going department store, he's Hot Topic and he's Gimbals.
He's some out-of-date brand.
I only know that from the movie Elf.
Is it an Elf? Really?
Because it's like a Macy's equivalent.
I don't know the context in Elf, admittedly.
I know just from Simpsons jokes.
He gets a job there and he overhauls their Christmas section one night.
They're like, did corporate come in and do this?
And he's like, I did it all overnight.
Anyway, that's how I know Gimbals.
It seems like you might grab Gimbals catalogs from eBay or something.
I know.
I have a good one.
So the other day we were leaving the house and he went, oh, we have a package.
He goes, oh, that must be my history of Kmart book by blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I went, God, I love you so much.
But I was like, you little weirdo.
I bought a book about the rise and fall of Kmart.
And I was like, all right.
All right, babe.
Local historian who lives in the Midwest and I was reading,
if you're aware, I found him on Blue Sky or Twitter or what.
And I was like, oh, that book sounds very interesting.
I'm fascinated by like the rise and fall of like the big box store, department store.
We've barely even scratched the surface of like the ones I grew up with.
James Way, Clover, Bradley's, Kaldor.
We have not.
We've got to handle each of these as their own thing.
How often does Jason bring up Clover, Bradley's?
No, no, comma, comma.
There's commas in there.
Clover was what?
Did you think it was Clover, Bradley's?
Yes, that's exactly what I thought.
I was about to Google Clover, Bradley's.
I'm not quite familiar, to be honest with you.
I don't really know about these.
This does not open the door.
No, I'm just kidding.
Oh, OK.
Oh, what is that phrase?
What?
This does not open the door to a new conversation.
Discussing.
Do you know what that was?
No, I just see it.
Open the door?
Are you guys serious right now?
That's pretty common.
I mean, I understand with context, but I've never heard it sort of said like that.
Open the door to, oh, really?
Wait, this is a valuable thing.
So I could say, Mike, this does not open the door to future puppet discussion.
This is a very valuable phrase for me.
All right, I'm going to keep this right at the forefront.
This is the weapon I've needed on this show for a long time.
Forgive me.
Isn't that sort of a passive aggressive statement?
I don't care.
It can be aggressive aggressive.
I need it.
I'm using it.
I need doors to close on puppet talk and a myriad of other things on this show.
Closing the door on any further 311 discussion.
I would love that.
I don't like that this even came up.
311 currently isn't a major runner on the show.
But after any episode, it could be.
What is 311?
311's the soul of the 90s.
From the 90s, yeah.
I don't know.
Sorry.
Come original, down.
You know, they had a.
All right, Mike, we're closing that door.
We have a lot to get to.
Oh, I love it.
This has been a valuable door.
Opening the door, closing a door.
But opening the door to Clover at New Jersey and Delaware, a discount chain.
No, you're right.
No, go ahead.
Let's open the door.
Mike, say what you're going to say.
Go through the door.
I don't want to.
You reopen the door.
No, I don't want to reopen the door.
All right, fine.
Do you want to talk about Clover or what was the other one?
Bradley's.
James Way.
Or James Way.
Or does this all go against James Way, which I assume would be talking about your wedding?
Yes.
I mean, that's what we were, you know, the episode called Doug Live.
And we will talk about Doug Live, a very important theme park show.
Hold your horses, Doug Live heads.
Don't, like, cool it.
These people got married, all right?
This needs to be discussed.
Yes.
Relax, Skeeter heads.
My first question is, is this behind a paywall?
No, this is made feet.
Okay.
Would you like it?
We can move it.
What do you want?
Obviously, I want made feed.
I love attention.
And I'd love for you guys to follow me.
I'd love for you guys to comment.
We're getting plugs now.
I need the serotonin.
So, like, please like my shit.
I'll just say probably less since it's not behind a paywall.
Not less, but less.
Oh, no.
What were you going to say?
What were you going to get, like, out there?
Like, what are you going to?
I get very personal very easily, and sometimes I share too much.
But we can edit, you know.
Okay, that's true.
Okay.
Tell us.
Don't hold back.
We're in the room.
We want to hear it.
You can ask later.
There's a few more people on the main feed.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
It's a massive difference.
Thank you for listening.
That's not so crazy.
All right.
Well, where do you want to start?
Well, let's talk about the wedding.
Where do you want to start?
I guess it goes back to the fall.
So, in the fall, we took a trip to Jason's parents.
We were at his mom and stepdad's house.
And we both were having a little, like, edible fun.
And we were like, should we get married?
Well, I was going back even further, because we were having coffee outside.
We're going to be here forever.
It's an idea.
This was such a wild idea to get married.
Only drugs could have inspired it.
No, no, no.
We were having coffee outside with my mom, and she said something offhand about marriage.
Oh, she's like, sorry.
I don't want to mention marriage.
She's like, sorry, sorry.
I don't want to put any pressure.
And we were like, no, we've been talking about it.
Like, you don't have to say it like it's like a...
Verboten.
Well, wait.
If you've been talking about it, then you've got to go back even further.
Oh, God.
What did you start talking about?
We've got to go back to the very beginning.
Look, I love my wedding, but I really love Doug Live.
Okay.
When it's up to you, then you have to, I think, personally scale it.
That's, I think.
Because we could talk about so many steps.
Okay, yeah.
So we kind of came up in conversation that night when we were getting ready for bed.
We were like, should we get married?
And he was like, yeah.
And I was like, should we try to do it on our six-year anniversary?
And I was like, when we get back, do you want to go get rings?
And he was like, yeah.
So the week we got back, because I had already picked out a ring because I went with my friend
Alexis.
Shout out, Alexis.
She's getting married in August.
Now, when did it start for her?
When was the first Alexis started talking?
Well, this is good.
I've got to close the door on this.
Close the door.
Yeah, we're going to close that door.
Love her.
All right.
I had already found a ring I like.
And I was like, hey, I know the ring I like.
And we kind of had an idea for his.
And we just went and picked out rings and had them sent out for resizing.
And then we were like, OK.
We always kind of wanted to do a courthouse thing.
I have never really dreamt of having a big wedding.
I think it's just a very personal thing.
I don't have a ton of family.
No one lives out here.
And truthfully, I don't like enough people to pay for them to come to an event.
I'm not trying to pay thousands of dollars.
I keep my circle tight.
I have five really close friends.
And it's just like, I'm not trying to do all that.
You need to know this about yourself.
So five would be the cap if you were going to.
I mean, the cap became zero.
Well, it became one.
It became one.
It became one former podcast guest.
A photographer and former podcast guest.
And then he was our witness.
Let me be clear, Andrew.
You're never coming back.
You're a former guest.
One and done.
Doors shut, Andrew.
I just meant he had been on it before.
Friend of the show.
If we're going to examine language ticks, we're going to be here all day.
We have been doing that.
We are.
We've been doing that for eight years now.
Anyway, as you were saying, darling.
Thanks.
So he was also our witness because then we saved $20.
If you don't have a witness.
Oh, I see.
I see the scheme here.
No, no, no.
No, it was sweet.
It was really sweet.
I feel like we're both friends with him now.
You've known him longer, but he came my birthday and we both knew him, so it felt appropriate.
I say he came my birthday because again, I keep things tight.
I don't invite a lot of people.
The jewelry store also told us when we were figuring out the rings, I was like, all right,
are there sales going on right now?
I love that this happened.
Oh, me too.
She said it.
She said it too.
We both asked about it and they were very cool.
She went like, well, not right now, but starting this weekend.
Like she's like, if you can come back in a few days.
It was like 30% off or something.
Yeah, it was hundreds if not thousands of dollars in savings.
So I was like, yeah, of course I don't mind waiting a few days.
That seems very silly.
Sure.
Yeah.
Great.
So we got that.
It was pretty cool.
And then some stuff happened.
Some not so fun stuff and things kind of not got pushed off, but we were kind of working
through some stuff.
And then eventually I was like, okay, let's figure this out because you have to first
get a marriage license, which is its own appointment.
And only certain courts in LA are eligible for these kind of things.
So we really wanted to get married at the Burbank courthouse, but it's not one that
you can get married at.
We ended up going with Beverly Hills because I think Van Nuys was technically the closest,
but for pictures, it's not really like as pretty over there.
And Beverly Hills was like maybe five minutes farther away.
And I know Beverly Hills a decent amount just from work.
And I knew kind of where that courthouse was.
And I was like, I think this could be really pretty.
Let's go get our license there and check it out.
And so we did that.
And then when we got there, you schedule the wedding, but they only do it a few days a
week.
So we kind of looked out.
Originally we were going to do, is it March?
March 14th.
Oh my God.
I was about to say six.
That's not our anniversary.
It's not our anniversary.
March 14th.
What a puff.
What a foul it could have been.
Oh boy.
Jason's in good graces now.
Say blushing bride again.
Lay it on thick.
You just wait.
The episode is done.
You're doing great, blushing bride.
I wanted to get married on a Friday.
I don't know why.
I just really liked that.
And the 28th was available and two and eight are my numbers also.
So it just felt right.
And they were like 10 45 a.m.
And I was like, sure.
Sure.
Why not?
It's a 15 minute slot.
The perfect time for love.
Traditionally.
You can look that up.
You could look that up in books.
And it is very fun the day they do all these ceremonies like back to back to back.
Because all the brides and grooms are coming in and out.
You're seeing each other.
Everyone's waving and cheering each other on.
You see the Star Trek ones.
You see the old timey western ones.
Are these all the themes going on?
I mean I guess that's more Vegas probably.
I think you're allowed to do whatever you want.
I mean you have to go through a metal detector.
So it's probably best not to have even prop weapons.
A Klingon war blade?
Yeah.
You're something blue.
Can't be a blue pistol.
OK.
Yeah.
It can't be a detective special.
It can't be 38 blue steel detective special.
This is a problem for mobsters in their gun malls.
You cannot get married in a cordless.
You probably wouldn't want to get married in a cordless if you're a mobster or a gun
mall.
Do you wait in an area with everybody after the metal detectors?
You go up to it's all on a certain floor and there is like some hallways and there's a
big patio.
That's the other thing.
If you're looking for great views of the city there is this beautiful balcony patio at
the Beverly Hills.
I'm trying to figure out like layout wise how it appeals like you know compares to city
walk or a theme park.
Quite small.
It's on the fourth floor and it's the whole floor is dedicated to weddings but it's not
huge.
You basically get out of the elevator and it's just one hallway to the left and there's
the office two restrooms and the chapel.
We're going to be able to rob this place by the time we're done.
We're going to know the exact blueprint layout.
That's right.
I don't know that there's anything there.
There's pens.
I want the pens.
I'm taking the pens.
You could.
Everybody shut up.
No I'm just kidding.
I'm sorry.
You're the blushing bride.
Fine.
You can tell us to shut up.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
No there are props in the room you get married.
It's like a photo booth.
Essentially yes.
So the room you get married in is not like a typical courthouse room.
Like I thought it would just be like that.
No.
This is just a regular ass room but one of the walls is painted like neon yellow and
it says love is love really big and then one wall says like and they lived happily ever
after with like stickers.
Wow it's like Disney.
And then another wall just has this big like heart picture and then in the corner there's
a fake wedding cake and champagne flutes.
So and then there's like green wall like green those um leafy green what do you like
grass?
Like influencer walls.
Yeah like flowers.
Not quite a step and repeat.
And fluorescent lights.
So I will not be using any of those pictures because it looks awful.
Famously beautiful lighting.
No it looked so bad.
But the uh she wanted to judge what was her title?
She had a very complicated like superior woman.
You're going to need to produce it on the podcast or the wedding is not legal.
I couldn't I asked her like multiple times because I just assumed the title would be
judged but it's like.
You asked her multiple times.
I asked her.
Once again ma'am what is your title?
Is this binding or not?
Because I wanted to know because I was interested but she was very funny.
I loved her.
I thought like I really exaggerate because I was like we're going to walk in here.
An old white guy that I probably don't like because I just don't like men in general.
But I was like give me some old white guys.
I'm sorry I'm sorry for the room you find yourself in there.
That's okay.
I have some except.
We're actually we're kind of boys that never grew up on it.
Kind of.
We're not old.
Don't you dare include me in that.
Peter Pan.
The last thing I want to be part of.
But no I was so I walked in and it was an older woman of color and I was like this is the
exact opposite of what I thought I'd be and I'm so happy.
She was really really sweet.
When we were doing our vows we kind of just did them off the dome.
I was like if I write something that's not really how I roll I'd rather just say some nice things.
And we do have Grissom took a cute little video of it.
I feel like I should play a little audio of the vows or something.
Like they're really sweet.
Oh.
But is that too personal for you?
No but do you have the time code?
Yeah because remember we sent it to my mom and sister.
They edited clips.
Meaning back from the microphone.
Well we don't we don't need to do it but essentially.
You can send it to Mike and he can cut it in.
OK.
That's true.
Yeah you can give Mike work to do.
No it's just really it's really really sweet.
And I started crying a little bit and she like gave me a tissue and like it was just really really sweet.
Did Jason compare you to did he say that you have the proud nobility of the quail?
I fucking wish.
That would have been awesome.
That's why when you're going off the dome you're not going to get a phrase like that.
She told me weeks before like OK you don't have to write long vows or anything.
But no bits please.
I was like our wedding is a zero bit.
Don't make this a bit.
Well and then you texted all of us including Erin and Lindsay and all of our responses included jokes and bits and you got mad at us for doing.
I did. I said y'all can't take nothing serious can you.
And you guys were like no and I was like man I hate this.
Lindsay herself said no.
But Erin sent a lovely photo of a Mickey and Minnie standing next to each other with giant dilated pupils.
I thought that was a lovely wedding sentiment.
Yeah.
No you guys were really funny.
You guys are so funny.
We're cooking now.
The bride's blushing now.
I love you baby.
You said that as if you were about to jump off a roof.
The ship was going down.
Love you baby.
You never know really.
You never know.
So yeah I said no bits please don't make our wedding bit.
We had one tiny bit in the pictures with the emergency exit that you really wanted to have.
Yeah.
I made one gentle joke in the vows but it was tasteful.
It wasn't a bit.
Bit crosses the line.
Does bit to you mean just like now a little voice is being effected.
And now listen missy is that the.
What are you avoiding with bits.
I was yeah I mean I was going to get introduced by a simple southern lawyer and then turn around and then turn back.
You're going to have a Matlock performance.
I now present this man to this here woman.
Ladies and gentlemen of the wedding witnesses.
It might have been nice.
Yeah I did not do that.
No the vows were really really sweet.
Like genuinely I'm so glad I saw him pull out his camera and I was like oh I'm really glad he did this because it was really really sweet.
They were just quick.
Yeah.
That's nice.
It was really nice.
And we'll get the file over and Mike get cracking on Mike.
I'll do it.
I literally have the clip.
I'm going to send it to my mom and sister.
All right y'all little boys talk amongst yourself do your little do your little skits.
Give me a sec.
I do have a funny story which was two days before I ordered a suit online and that week I took it to Milton E.D.'s to get tailored and we went to pick it up.
And who is the first person I see in the dry cleaners is Derek Waters.
Former guest.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Former guest Derek Waters and I was like oh we're getting married.
You know he was very excited for us and he goes are you doing it at Disneyland or Epcot.
So got my ass.
Fair question certainly.
It's a shame none of us did you know.
Add that out of the three.
You know because really you could doing a quick thing.
You could get someone that's ordained kind of secretly not even secretly do it at Epcot in a very nonchalant way that wouldn't draw attention and you wouldn't have to pay like the thousands upon thousands of dollars that a ceremony would cost.
There's a way to do it discreetly like dumping ashes at Disney World.
You can do whatever you need in your life at Disney as long as you do it discreetly.
Where would you Epcot specifically.
Where in Epcot would you want to get covertly married during whispered during American Adventure while I watch Mark Twain and Ben Franklin shake hands because that's a good answer.
It's a bonding forever just like those men are bonded in the history of this great nation.
Okay great answer.
My answer is after Sugar Ray is done performing every morning at the Garden Rocks stage in front of the American Pavilion.
Do a quick thing where somebody the ordained person just does the ceremony real quick.
I thought you were going to say having Peter Noon say hey something's on fire over there.
Well that would be a second.
Burning passion of love.
Yeah.
Hey those two are getting married.
Back to singing Mrs. Brown.
But then you get caught you don't want him to see that.
I want Peter Noon to see it.
You don't want Peter Noon ratting you out.
Yeah he's a rat.
You're right.
I don't trust him.
I found it.
Okay.
It's probably a minute or two so I can not play the whole thing or I can and you can edit it.
I mean two minutes off of a phone does seem like a tough idea.
Whatever if the audios I mean it's up to you.
I'm going to play all of it.
Sure.
Because I want you guys to hear it.
Because it's really really nice and then you can honestly edit all of it out if you want.
Oh I don't want to cry.
I just want to say it's such an honor to be your partner and I'm so happy to officially
become your wife and be my husband and you're so strong and I look up to you so much and
I just think that you're so great and I'm so lucky.
I love you so much.
I don't want to cry.
I love you.
Jane I love you so much.
I said from the very beginning from our very first date that I could tell you a very good
heart and like any relationship we've certainly had our ups and downs, our prosperity and
our adversity but we stuck it out and I just love you so much and I'm so proud of you and
I can safely say this was the most positive online dating experience I've ever had.
That's a bit, he did a bit, he got a joke in there.
It was a joke not a bit.
That's good that he got, he was still himself.
That was a tasteful joke that everyone liked.
That was nice.
That was very sweet.
That felt like scolding us for what we were imagining.
Not like I wanted what you guys would do, your skits.
I knew she would like it and that was the most important thing.
Well that was very nice.
That was very nice.
Thanks for playing.
No I couldn't get through, we did a little thing in the living room when we got married
and I couldn't get through it.
Lindsay was rock solid.
I couldn't do it.
You were crying?
Yes.
A little emotional baby.
I'm very emotional.
No one knows.
I'm not.
This stern.
Shut the door Mike.
This facade of Mr. Tough Guy.
I don't want to hear it okay, toughen up.
Mr. High Tea over here is kind of emotional.
Is it related to my high tea?
I don't know.
We don't know.
It's related to how much blood you lose with constant checks of tea.
That's right, it's possible.
Check me again Doc.
I'm anemic as well as having high tea.
Are you anemic for real?
No.
Oh okay.
No, no, no.
I just have normal tea.
It's normal, it's average.
It's not piping hot?
Well, when I'm spilling it, it is.
See, that's a current thing.
That's not that new.
That's an old phrase.
It's over ten years I think.
It's not like locked in.
Everyone's locked in these things and stuff.
I know locked in.
I know what that means.
I know LFG, but that's old.
These are old.
Yeah.
Your dress, you have not mentioned.
Oh.
Your dress.
So I made my wedding dress and I was really happy with how it came out.
I originally was not going to make my dress, but I was ordering all of these kind of short
courthouse wedding dress vibes and they either were super cheap or fit me weird and I was
like, oh, I'm going to have to get this really altered.
I was like, I can probably alter this myself.
I was like, if I'm going to do all of that work, why don't I just see if I can make it?
I prefer not to use patterns.
I like to just go for it and do my own design and kind of build it on my body.
The first month I made a dress and it ended up falling apart, so I actually restarted
and with the dress that I finished with, I did it in one month.
So I was like, well, that was crazy.
But yeah, it ended up exactly how I wanted.
I was really, really happy with how both of us looked on the wedding.
I think it turned out great.
Yeah, you both look great.
Thank you.
Wonderful photos.
With that experience, would you recommend that if Mike or I were to renew our vows,
should we take a stab at making our own tuxes?
Absolutely, you should.
I said that jokingly.
You should.
I will speak for myself and say that's the worst idea.
I'd love to see what mess y'all came up with.
It'll be all patchy.
It'll be like an old hobo from the movies.
It's cute.
You can make patchwork work.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe I will do it.
Maybe I will make a suit.
It seems fun in concept.
I don't think I have the time.
Sewing is really fun.
I get very, quote unquote, locked in.
Jason will be like, I can't wait until you're done with this dress.
You can hang out with me again.
Because I would spend the entire day working on this dress.
That's one of those things where you have to have a lot of focus.
And I'm not always good with that.
I like to draw a lot.
But to be really good, you've got to have so much focus.
And it's bad.
My brain is bad at that.
Yeah, I mean, I'm not amazing at focus sometimes either.
But when it's something that I'm very passionate about,
it comes a little differently.
Sure.
You know what I mean?
So yeah, thank you for mentioning that.
I was very happy with that.
The night before, if you want to talk about this,
we stayed at the Beverly Hilton.
The historic Beverly Hilton.
Oh yeah, we have stories.
I forgot.
Are we going to get to Doug?
That was fun.
It's up to you.
Yeah, it's up to you.
The ball is in your court.
We can talk about the wedding,
and then maybe we'll take a quick break.
Yeah, I have to use this.
And then come back and talk about Doug.
Okay.
Let's get to fly through this,
because now I'm like, okay, let's get to Doug.
Okay.
Not that I didn't love my wedding.
So we stayed there, and we were like, oh, this will be great.
Kind of like a chill, fancy restaurant.
And we walk in, and there are just people everywhere.
And there's clearly an event going on.
And I'm already stressed out,
because I didn't start my Alexa Pro yet.
That's why I was like, do I talk about that?
Well, and I am just fried.
And he's just fried.
I'm just mentally fried a lot of times.
And so I'm stressing the hell out,
because there's people drinking and stuff
up at the front desk where I'm trying to get to
with him in the wheelchair.
And I'm like, no, we're actually checking in.
I got crazy.
Did you yell at people?
It was so loud.
It was literally so loud.
There were hundreds of people.
Well, because what was happening was the GLAAD awards
were going on that night.
And the Beverly Hilton also home every year
to the Golden Globes.
So they have a very large event thing.
There's a big party going on in the lobby.
But it wasn't really a party.
It was the line to get through security and red carpet.
So we also did see a few people were like,
oh, I know who that is.
But then when we went to the other side of the lobby,
where the lobby bar and gift shop were,
there was no one.
So is that where you hung out mostly?
For a little.
Yeah, we hung out a little.
We met a very nice bartender.
And he was talking to us about, we were all talking about baseball.
Yeah, Dodgers gave us a lot.
How long were you sort of stuck in a line?
How long were you stuck in the GLAAD awards?
As little time as possible.
I was like, we just got married.
Kind of like, wink, wink, do we get an upgrade?
And they're like, do you want an upgrade suite?
And I was like, yes, I do.
Elevators are over there.
I was like, zoop, I just want to get to the room.
OK.
There was an upgrade?
There was.
How did you do the upgrade?
Well, because we initially got a two bed,
because when we do hotels, we love our own bed.
Like, I just want my own bed.
And I was like, night before our wedding, I want my own bed.
And they're like, do you want this upgraded giant room
that's a king bed?
And I said, yes, I do.
Thank you so much.
And the balcony was like triple the size
of what we would have had.
And I was right over the port cachet,
if you know the Beverly Hilton layout at all.
So we were just kind of like right above that.
So that was fun.
And so that felt very special.
You know, they had like robes and slippers.
And like, it was just so luxurious.
Again, I had been there before for work,
but I've never stayed there.
So it was fun to be like, oh, I'm the special one.
Like, I get to stay here.
I'm not leaving with bags and garment bags of clothes.
Have you worked award shows at the hotel?
No, I've done like fittings there
for people who are doing award shows,
but like pre-award show, not night of stuff.
I love stuff.
Well, what's funny though is Ashley Crystal Hairston.
Yes.
Shout out to her.
Former guest.
Former guest, icon legend.
We love her.
I am now styling her, which is really, really fun.
I love her to death.
It kind of just happened.
And now we're like, I love her.
And originally, she was going to go to the GLAAD Awards
because they were nominated for the Fairly Odd Parents
reboot that Lindsay K tie.
That's my love.
My love.
I say my love so much.
We say that around the house so much.
Yeah, it's iconic.
Now, I know it's been a little while,
but I would just like to hear it.
Would you mind?
We say my love a lot.
Would you mind calling her your blushing bride?
Right now on mic or in the future?
Just imagine she's listening.
No, no, no.
I'd like it to be on mic, please.
My blushing bride.
Is that good?
Yeah.
It was better than I could have imagined
because I had that liltz.
The liltz is what really sells it.
Because you know what that is?
That's the high T.
That's when you really channel the T
in the word bride.
That's right.
You're getting into Lovitz territory
with that.
Lindsay, my blushing bride.
My blushing bride.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Anyway, I'll wrap this up.
I just, I like.
Well, yeah, I have a Jason.
Very Jason.
Jason has a Jason story.
So initially she was going to go,
and then a few days before she called me,
she's like, they're not paying for us to go anymore.
So we were both really sad.
She had some really cool looks lined up.
And then they won, and I was so mad.
But the irony was, I would have been there
for the awards, or I could have gotten her ready
because I was already going to be there.
So I didn't even, just kind of worked out that way.
You could have split time between Jason and her.
Yeah.
Is what you're saying.
I truly would have.
Just leave him over in that bar area.
It was a very long room.
It's quiet.
The sports will be fine.
You know?
A very long room and long balcony.
So I could have made myself scarce.
Oh, it was, yeah.
The bathroom was huge.
It was all giant.
So I was like, oh, I wish she would have been able to go.
It would have been nice.
Yes.
We ended up at the Beverly Hilton,
and they did not.
And that was very surreal.
The irony.
Okay, you can go now.
Okay.
Here's the thing about the-
You may talk now, husband.
Yes, wife.
Thank you.
Here's the thing about the Beverly Hilton.
Here it comes.
Here we go.
Let's see the bill.
What did it cost?
Is there any talk about the bill?
Is there any of the charges?
Is your neck okay?
You were shaking your head when I said that.
Let's keep an eye on that.
Wedding night, bills.
All right.
Pre you.
The worst pillows I've ever slept on.
It was not good.
It was gnarly.
It was surprisingly bad.
You're on blast, Beverly Hilton pillows.
What about the pillows?
They were just hurting my neck.
Yeah, they didn't really move much,
and they were quite thick and lumpy,
but they didn't have much cushiony to it,
so it was just a really uncomfortable rock
that just didn't-
You goddamn pillows.
Do you realize whose heads are on top of you?
This is a husband and a blushing bride,
and you don't give them support?
We missed a giant part.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
We've got to talk about this.
I'll talk about my stupid thing,
and you talk about your big thing.
So I could not sleep.
It wasn't pre-wedding jitters.
I am just like, I'm trying a pillow,
I'm trying two pillows,
I'm moving them around,
I'm throwing them on the ground,
I'm balling up a sweatshirt.
I could not sleep,
so at some point I'm just on my phone,
and I ended up on eBay,
and I bought a $4, $5 Woody Woodpecker
Islands of Adventure opening year pin,
and I'm like, I can't believe I'm doing this
the night before my wedding.
What?
I can.
I can, first of all.
I love that.
Anything but that, I'd be surprised.
What time are we looking at?
Is it 4 a.m.?
3 a.m.
3 a.m., okay.
Wow.
Did you take Nyquil or anything?
No.
You've got to be happy, Jane,
that it's the night before.
He's getting married in the morning,
and he's up at 3 a.m.,
thoughts rushing through his brain.
You've got to be happy that it's not like,
who else it could have been?
Past loves.
It's Woody Woodpecker from Islands of Adventure opening.
Luckily it wasn't Winnie Woodpecker.
Oh, then you'd be in trouble.
Oh, well.
I'll pass.
I'll pass, yeah.
No, I was like, yeah, man,
whatever you want.
I did not want this wedding to be stressful.
That was the thing.
I was just like, yeah, okay, cool.
Yeah?
Did you fall asleep immediately
after buying it?
A little while later.
Okay, so that didn't immediately put you to sleep.
No, but it certainly calmed you.
Calmed me, I think.
That's the night.
Wow, wow.
If that's what you need to enter.
I think it's cute, actually.
I meant to bring it today.
I totally forgot.
When I started applauding and stuff,
what I assumed was that you were getting into this section
about how much the parking cost
and the hidden fees with the room.
Well.
Here we go.
Now we're doing it.
There are a lot of fees,
but I was prepared for that.
But then, after the wedding,
we went back to the apartment
for the rest of the day and the night.
And then we stayed a couple nights
just at Hilton in Burbank,
just at Hilton Garden Inn in Burbank.
And they were hosting the GLAAD Awards Night 2.
Well, hold on.
Well, don't get ahead of us.
It's very chill.
The food is shockingly delicious.
It's really good.
It's really good at the inn hotel restaurant there.
But yeah, so your big thing that kind of, thankfully...
Well, you didn't get to what at the hotel we ran into.
Well, we'll circle back to that.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
So on Thursday, when we're about to head
to drop Garfield off at boarding and last minute things
and then go to the hotel to check in.
So Garfield, unfortunately, you guys,
he's getting quite old.
He cannot see.
He does not like to be touched.
It's gotten really, really sad.
He's still our sweet little boy,
but it's not been easy.
I didn't realize that.
Yeah, it's not been great.
But I mean, he's okay.
But you can tell he's probably like 11 now.
That's not even that old,
but it's like an older dog.
He was sleeping very cute in a beanbag chair when we left.
That was cute.
So that was great.
Did he go up to the computer
and buy himself a Woody Woodpecker as an adventure tent?
No, he can't see.
The other day, our, not entertainment system,
but we have a block of cubes.
The Ikea Calax.
And I'll just see him,
and his head is just in one of the cubes,
and he's just standing there.
He just can't see, and he'll just stare at the wall.
It's really sad.
But anyway, the reason I say that is because I was trying
to get him in the car, which is impossible now
because you have to pick him up, and he bites.
It's really stressful for me.
So I'm putting things in the car, and he gets away.
He's on his leash, but he runs away.
And I was like, oh, crap.
Why did I censor myself?
Oh, fuck.
So then I open the door, and I turn.
And we're in our parking garage that has these giant columns.
And there's one right by my car.
And I turn, and I full force ram my head into the pole,
like full body weight.
And I immediately start crying.
And I have a very high pain tolerance,
and I was so shocked and scared
because it was literally like turning and running into a wall.
And I was like, Jason, my wedding pictures!
My wedding pictures!
I'm going to have this big purse!
I can't fucking believe it!
I worked so hard on my skin for weeks,
and now I hit the pole.
I'm freaking out.
I'm in shock.
I'm in utter pain.
I'm like, am I going to have a good cushion?
But you did flash to the pictures before you flashed to...
Yeah, a fucking horse like this.
Do I need to go to the hospital?
Are you kidding me, guys?
I did red light therapy.
Oh, red light?
I want to do red light.
Michael, I meant to tell you, it actually really works.
I have a little wand.
A door is open, everyone.
It's the only thing I notice that changes my skin
if I use it every day for like...
Really? Oh, I'm excited about this.
Please, no.
Like, absolutely 100% red light.
Give him your red light guy.
No, no, I'll get a hold of it.
I'll work on it.
Mine was a gift, actually, from a styling event.
So, technically, I didn't buy it.
But it works really well.
You have to cough that up yourself.
I did not work for weeks on my skin
to have a fucking bruise on my forehead.
And by the grace of the wedding gods,
for whatever reason, you could not see it.
I could feel the fuck out of it.
But it was just right at the top.
Oh, my God.
Like, huge.
The most clear area of skin on your face.
Oh, yeah.
Completely available for a cartoon.
I was like, oh, God, this is gonna be awful.
You couldn't see it.
The only time I could see it was when it was healing.
It was just this yellow circle.
Like, it still kind of hurts.
And this was two weeks ago now.
Two weeks ago Thursday.
Yeah.
So that was just like a terrible start.
And I was freaking out.
I was already kind of frantic
because we were, you know, taking Garfield
and that's the whole thing.
So I was like, oh, what a great way to start this,
like, wedding adventure.
I'm like, concussion, potentially?
Let me drive to Beverly Hills now.
Yeah, she was really shocked and upset.
And she's like, it's kind of bruised.
It's gonna have bruised the pictures.
And I'm trying to hold our hands
and trying to remember concussion protocols
of like, did you lose consciousness?
Let me see your pupils, blah, blah, blah.
Do we need to go to urgent care?
Yeah, look in the light.
Did they die in the light?
Yeah.
But you said it was okay?
It was okay.
Dr. Sheridan ruled that it was fine.
Well, losing...
I've been watching a lot of Dr. Odyssey lately.
I can get you through this.
We actually are behind a few episodes.
Maybe I can't get you through it.
I'm behind a few episodes, but I'll try.
I'm behind a few episodes.
Look, I've eaten shit a few times the last few years
and I've like, on the phone, like,
seeing if I need to come in.
Sure.
You know, they do a basic questionnaire.
Like, the main thing is like, did you lose consciousness?
Did you blackout?
Did you have spots in your eye?
In this case, do you remember Doug's last name?
Do you remember the town that he is from?
Puddy, Puddy.
Puffington, Puffington.
21 Jumbo Street.
What is Doug's home address?
It's a very important song.
We'll get there.
So, yeah, that was kind of like a startling start.
I'll say.
Wow.
It was really scary.
And then I'm like, time to drive to Beverly Hills.
Like, I guess I'm just gonna go.
And it ended up like being okay, relatively.
But like, Jesus, that hurt.
And it just scared the crap out of me.
I was immediately just like in a wall.
Like, I was so startled.
I just started crying.
So I just wanted to mention that because we were like, why?
How?
Like, I was like, I worked so hard on my skin.
It looks great.
This is not fair.
Like, I was so mad.
But the skin, if you hadn't worked as hard, maybe it wouldn't have absorbed the...
I think the red light made you...
It helped.
What a good point.
Yeah, I think so.
That's a really good point.
Yeah.
It does make your skin very plump.
Maybe that proves with enough red light therapy, you can purposefully bang your head on a concrete
pole.
It makes it strong skin.
Yeah, yeah.
And you'd be fine.
Yeah.
Like, I literally just like touched it and be like, oh.
And I'm like, oh.
It hurts a lot.
I'm sure.
Like, it hurts a lot.
Anyway.
I'm convoluted.
So we stayed at the Hilton.
It was kind of a gloomy weekend.
Yeah.
Weekend.
And we're like, oh, the hotel's like empty.
We have a place to ourselves.
And we were just kind of walking outside.
And they had a fire pit.
We came back inside.
And there was just a giant...
There was a Greyhound parked outside.
Inside, there was just a giant high school cheerleading squad and all the parents and
chaperones.
And...
And the what now?
Chaperones.
Just say, chapel-rone.
Chapel-rone.
Then it's right.
Yeah, there was a bunch of chapel-rones.
But then all the cheerleaders and all the chapel-rones.
But when I tell you, it felt like wall-to-wall of the lobby.
It wasn't just like a circle.
I walked in and I went, God.
Oh, God.
Not this.
And we tried...
Sorry, I'm...
Sorry.
But the other thing I learned that weekend that was, in hindsight, kind of embarrassing.
But look, I'm on a lot of medications for various things.
And Mike's birthday a few weeks before, I had a single beer and I was fine.
I had a gin and tonic and it just...
My body...
It just felt like it had four gin and tonics.
And that happened the night before the wedding.
I thought, well, it's probably just exhaustion and jitters.
And then a couple nights later, we walked into this lobby that had previously been no one in there.
Literally.
And now it's just...
This is not...
Which hotel are we at now?
That's not...
That's the one you...
The later one.
Yeah.
I tried a couple times.
But we walked into the full lobby and it's like, all right, let's get drinks.
Same thing happened.
I am just dizzy.
I just don't feel well.
But when you see a crowd or was it before that?
No, I'm saying the gin and tonic.
It interacted with whatever I was on.
And so, yes.
So for Epic Universe, I am going to be a messy little soda boy, not a messy little gin boy.
Not a messy little...
Scott and I are going to...
I'm sorry to say, Scott and I are going to be pounding shots when we're at Epic Universe.
Well, if it's...
They had a hammer.
Jane, if you want one.
She knows.
No, no, no.
Honestly, I don't drink.
I also had one drink, but I don't drink.
I don't like it.
I also have medications in effect.
I feel awful.
I don't enjoy it.
So it's not like I miss it.
I hate it.
That's a bummer.
Yeah.
Well, you can't do it.
It really makes me feel awful.
One drink and I'm like, my stomach is killing me.
You know what?
This is me with edibles.
Me with edibles too, unfortunately.
Yeah.
See, I'm the opposite.
Weed is...
Different paths.
Takes all kinds.
That's right.
Well, we're going to do...
We're going to play beer pong with Vincent Various in Celestial Park.
No.
Wait.
Well, that character is not happening anymore.
Is that official?
Do we know that?
I suspected that.
No, I'm telling you.
I know for a fact it's not.
I hate when people don't believe it.
No, I'm not...
No, I'm just saying I suspected that it was.
I'm not saying I don't believe you.
Yeah, I said it was.
But you have this...
You have this intel that it's Vincent Various.
I have inside information that...
Is Vincent Various...
What's the Star Wars character who didn't make it?
Admiral Constable Zuvio?
Is Vincent Various the Constable Zuvio of Celestial Park?
We knew what Zuvio looked like because we had a toy of him.
I don't know that we...
We didn't even find out what Vincent looked like.
Somebody was cast, so there might be a picture of him somewhere, but it's not public.
The tea is, they worked and rehearsed for all of the Celestial Park entertainment for
10 weeks, and then all of a sudden they said, all of this is scrapped, goodbye, and they
just cut all of it.
Jesus Christ.
So they were supposed to have a lot of stuff, but...
Yeah, that's what we heard.
We heard some people saw it.
At this rate, if it truly has disappeared, Vincent Various will immediately move into
the ranks of Mighty Ikhwan, one of these things where the only available results are us talking
about.
Because we're the only people who seized on it in time.
We should really try to get Universal to sue us by putting out a series about Vincent Various.
Try to feel like a narrative podcast or a show, we could shoot a show.
The Jason references from time to time Chinese democracy when Guns N' Roses had...
Guns N' Roses album.
Guns N' Roses had long said they were going to put out this album called Chinese Democracy,
they never made good on it year after year, but ultimately the offspring said, we're doing
it.
We're putting out an album called Chinese Democracy.
That's their sense of humor.
Snooze you lose.
Which I always thought was funny.
But that's what we got to do.
It's like, okay, if you own Vincent Various, do something with it.
Put him in the park.
Otherwise, it's up to us and our great imaginations to imagine adventures for Vincent Various.
What does he do?
What would he have done?
Well, he was...
Sorry, you know the answer?
No, no, no.
I had something else to say.
So please continue.
Oh, I was just going to say that I think he...
This is dangerous because there might be 15 more minutes about Vincent Various.
I'm just going to...
Just letting you know as a courtesy.
This episode's going to be so long.
I'm just saying that Vincent Various, I think he was like sort of in charge of all the different
establishments in Celestial Park and to, you know, he was...
He refilled the soda for the messy little soda boys.
He will...
Yeah.
Well, he would have somebody probably do it.
He's in charge.
He could summon it.
He's...
All right.
So he possibly...
He accepts the time cards for...
But Captain Kakao at Maya the Explorer traveled the cosmos trying to find treats for the...
Right.
Well, these guys got to be cut too, right?
Well, no, but they're on the merchants.
There's already...
But Maya's got to be out.
There's no flush on Maya.
Maya might be out too though.
I don't even know who that is.
I only know because I Googled something to do a specific joke about in our episode about
this.
Well, we're going to...
We own Vincent Various now as far as I'm concerned.
Yeah.
Unless Universal does something...
We'll give them eight weeks.
We got it.
We own Vincent.
Eight weeks from now.
If they don't do anything...
I'll see if I can find out any information.
Here's what I'll say.
Orlando live show.
Yeah.
Vincent Various will appear at our live show.
That's a good thing to just declare right now.
Yes.
You will.
Guess what?
Maybe the big dog in town isn't going to let you meet Vincent Various, but that's a podcast
that I promise.
Podcast the right.
An art show?
Yeah, we make good on that.
I don't know which show of...
There's two shows.
What kind of entertainers would we be if we didn't allow you to meet Vincent Various?
You will meet Vincent Various at the Podcast the Ride live show.
We are playing with fire.
Comcast NBCUniversal is going to send the woman in the yard after us.
We're going to be fucked.
Comcast, you bring that woman in the yard.
Bring it on, I'm saying.
You're going to be playing with your Ninja Turtles and you're going to hear, today's
the day.
And then you're fucked.
Well, then we will take control of her as well, this character, woman in the yard.
That movie is actually really sad.
I bet it is.
It represents trauma.
We're going to make it fun.
Can I just have a quick idea for something they could do with these characters that might
be cool if they were able to budget-wise or whatever, be really cool to have them as atmosphere
characters in City Walk to kind of share celestial park vibes and get people interested in the
park and incorporate it a little bit?
Would that be kind of cool?
We would like it.
It would be cool, but I wonder for dad who wants to have a couple of beers at the NBC
bar and grill, he might be a bit confused.
Yes, somebody snuggles out of the hot dog hall of fame and like, you there, you look
like a man who might be interested in what lies beyond.
What if I told you there were five portals nearby?
Why the name's various.
I have a house at the end of the Andromeda Strain.
Why, sir, right this way?
I like original characters for the preview center, like, it brings people in.
Bring me to the greatest preview center of all time.
I'm just saying, I feel like that could be, and no, this isn't related to what we were
talking about, but.
My car is a moonbeam.
I love that.
This is great.
All right.
There'll be three Vincent variouses you will meet at the podcast.
Various variouses.
Vincent.
Meet a various.
Various, various.
Sort of a variouses.
Vincent variouses.
And they're all Dream Finder-ish.
Hello.
Well, with the tesseract and time portals, we all exist simultaneously.
Thank you, Vincent.
Yes.
In various stackable dimensions.
I eat three rainbows a day.
All right, so I'm going to reel this back in a little bit.
Sure, yes.
Okay.
The door's cracked open a little, but we're closing it.
I'm not shutting it, but let's kind of mute it.
No, I'm just kidding.
Okay, we can close it.
I feel like.
These are the kind of bits you're avoiding.
I literally sat here and I went, I'm going to give them a little bit of time to do this.
Let the boys run around.
Get their energy out.
Everyone likes this.
They're feeling ramy.
Get it out.
People are going to be psyched.
There's going to be a line out the door at the tin roof in Orlando to see Vincent variouses.
There's going to be a line out the door to see you guys.
People love you guys so much.
Yes, that's true.
Definitely.
But there's going to be an extra.
The line is going to dwarf our line.
Suddenly it's a line of thousands.
It's what the theme park would have gotten.
Exactly.
But we get it now.
It's ours now.
We're going to create such a fire hazard.
There's going to be a bit.
That room full of cheerleaders you guys are complaining about.
That's going to be nothing compared to all the Vincent various fans.
The 2,000 people trying to fit into a venue meant for 300.
That's right.
Well, it'll be a good show.
For no fires, Vincent will protect us.
I can ward them off.
I control ice.
Did we forget anything?
That's part of me too.
About the wedding?
The only thing I was going to say is the cheer parents after everything died down were at
the bar watching the videos and clearly like, oh, that couple's not going to stay together.
They're like having problems with their together because of their kid or like that crazy mom
is yelling at the other crazy mom because of this.
So we were kind of just observing at that point.
Like these parents are kind of crazy.
Was there any of that even at the at the other hotel of like, oh, you said you noticed a
couple of people.
Were there any there were famous people there?
Were there other people you were sort of like, oh, we'll do people watching while we're
there.
I did not.
We didn't.
We didn't catch anyone.
And then the bar, everyone was just kind of like chilling, watching the Dodgers.
So it was more you were more watching the parents of the cheerleaders.
It was just funny because we were at the bar and I'm like, oh, Jason, I think these are
all the parents that are having their various reactions to their life being.
They all just seemed exhausted.
All watching the videos.
Sad life, a ride on a bus.
It's a long day, a competition day.
I think it was that they said it was that the competition was at William Burroughs High
School.
John Burroughs High School.
John Burroughs.
Excuse me.
William Burroughs.
That's a good guy.
He always got Frawley on the mind.
Just a little.
William.
Always.
That's true.
Dreaming of him on his wedding night.
Was there any, but there wasn't any commotion like as far as in the middle of the night,
like both of these groups, were they like, there wasn't like girls cheering down the
hall at midnight.
They were a little noisy.
You slept through it.
Really?
You didn't hear them.
In the hallway?
It's just kind of going to and from the elevators.
They were chanting.
They were spelling everything they could get their eyes on.
These cheerleaders can't stop spelling shit.
E-X-I-T.
Exit, exit.
H-I-L-T.
Hilton Garden Inn.
Ho, ho.
You're a little too good at the cadence of that.
Were you a cheerleader?
Does he do anything so?
I'll start busting out the old videos.
Amazing.
Oh, oh, this is what I was going to say.
We got off the elevator and all of the elevators kind of look out to the pool and we were like,
oh, the pool.
And I turn and look and it is just flooded with teens.
And I went, oh, God, the teens have taken over.
And then I turned around.
There was a cheer dad and he was like, yep, there's 46 of them.
Like, it was just so funny.
So I was like, oh, God, they're like infesting.
Infesting.
They were everywhere.
And it was just so funny because the dad was standing there like leaning against the wall
with a drink like, yep, there's 46 of them.
He was like ready to go.
Quintin Jaws or something.
Yeah, there's 46 of them out there.
It was just so funny.
You would have rather that the hotel had bed bugs.
It was going to be infested by anything.
Yeah.
It was easier to deal with.
I checked the beds.
I always check the beds.
How do you check?
Do you check the corners?
You pull back the sheet.
Because you would see them, you're saying.
You can check the mattress.
Right.
I was just wondering if you had like a machine or something that could do it.
No.
You can get a cheap blacklight pen, but that's different.
You don't want to do that in a hotel.
No, no, no.
Yeah, you don't want to do that.
Plausible deniability is the way to go.
You know it would be really, you'd never sleep in a hotel again.
How did it get here?
How'd that big splash get up there?
Yeah, it would be shocking.
Can they crawl walls?
How would they do it?
Yeah, no.
I don't want, even in the nice hotels.
Yeah, especially the nice.
Especially the nice hotels.
Weird stuff goes down.
Oh, oh, oh.
At Beverly Hilton, we were on the same floor and mirror rooms down from where Whitney Houston died.
Multiple, multiple people in the elevators.
Multiple people were going to visit.
Like it's a really big thing.
I believe that.
We're like going to check room 434.
So people stay in that room?
Yeah, 434.
I think it's been fully renovated and stuff.
Room 434.
Did they tell people, like by the way, here's your room key.
Just so you know.
No, it's just pretty infamous.
Yeah, but people obviously are in there every night.
Yeah.
But would you, I feel like if I, hotel staff, I think you would not encourage telling people that.
But some people go to see it.
Sure.
And it's like an attraction.
But I see what you're saying.
We don't know what room JFK Maryland got.
If they were on a chocolate bar.
Oh, Maryland and JFK would go there to fuck.
Do you think they had many different, I assume if they went more than once, they would have different rooms?
Or do you think there was the same suite there?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't really know, but they were.
Did they also go to Frank Sinatra's Palm Springs house as well?
Yeah, probably.
I'm sure.
I don't know.
As far as I know, I think they went to that.
You know more about this than I do.
I don't know.
I just said what I know.
You got a big leap of info on this.
They just be fucking, you know.
So in the room, there's a candy bar at the Beverly Hilton and it has a black and white picture, like you could buy it, of JFK in Maryland.
Oh, really?
And then a documentary about, what was it, JFK started playing on the TV and I was like, I'm freaked out right now.
This hotel is haunted.
I started freaking out.
Remember that?
Yes.
Because I was like, oh no, he's coming through the TV.
He wasn't killed there.
Just don't go to the courthouse in an open top car.
Oh my God.
No, no.
Avoid the-
My beautiful pillbox hat.
Don't book the Ambassador Hotel.
The hotel in Burbank, I did watch a lot of my favorite, The Food That Built America.
This is a romantic wedding weekend.
I like that show too.
She was dead asleep.
She likes it too and then she fell asleep.
One day I slept the whole day and I kept apologizing and I'm like, I'm sorry.
What's the whole, you mean literally from morning till night?
I slept a good chunk of Sunday.
Like I really did because I was just so fucking tired.
Oh, we did, keep adding these things, I don't know.
The day we got home from the wedding, Friday, it was still early in the day and I immediately asked for alone time because I was so like over-stimulated.
So we got married.
We took our pictures.
We came home.
We were like, oh, that was crazy and I went, so can I have alone time now?
Because I just need to like decompress and he was like, yeah, sure.
And we just went our separate ways for a while.
And I just think that's funny.
And then we took a nap.
I don't know, I feel like I'm sucking on this podcast today.
I feel like I'm not killing it.
You're doing great.
Tell her she's blushing bread.
Yes, beautiful, beautiful blushing bread.
Beautiful blushing bread.
I don't know why is that.
Come on, Jack, come on.
Joe Biden.
We came home, put on sweats and watched like Ordinary Adventures or Miss Tomorrow, whatever we always put on.
I was just like, all right, everyone leave me alone.
I was like, I don't want anybody talking to me.
I want a full log of everything that was watched.
I think you owe the listeners every single piece of material.
There were some ancient aliens in there.
We watched Family Guy the night before our wedding.
We did watch Family Guy.
I was worried some of these were going to fall through the cracks.
Walk off, Scotty.
Fuck the fuck off, man.
Some listeners living vicariously through Jane right now.
I will leave this room and you can finish.
Jane needs alone time.
No, but actually what was funny is Family Guy, the TV was so big and you could see it from outside because I stepped outside to like smoke.
And the way our room was you could see right into it with the windows open.
And I was like, you can see the Family Guy TV that we're watching from like outside.
From downstairs.
And from like the freeway.
I feel like they could see it because the TV was so big and I just thought that was funny.
So people like walking on the street could see Quagmire or something.
Oh, yeah.
There was a lot of construction going on around the hotel.
It was like so big.
I was like, I'm watching this from outside.
Right.
Yeah.
So we watched some good Family Guy.
All right.
Well, I have to use the bathroom.
Well, let's all piss and shit and then we'll come back for some talk about Doug Live.
Okay.
Now, now that that's all out of the way.
Boy, that was rough.
Do not go in there.
Oh, they're shitting and pissing.
Right.
Yeah.
That's not what you meant.
I don't know what he meant.
That's what I thought he was referring to.
That's what I thought he was referring to too.
I showed you at the wedding.
Never mind.
We got through all that.
You were acting like it was so hard to pee.
I'm just glad you liked it because something I like to do is just like when I'm with my
friends, just like say Jim Carrey quotes and get everybody to crack up.
Yeah.
It really was.
It's just something I do.
I don't know.
I'll keep doing it.
I'll try to weave one more into the episode.
Smoke it in.
Yeah.
That should be easy.
Okay.
Now, let's talk about Doug Live.
Ren, just the basic facts.
Doug Live ran.
He's very mournful here.
Let's talk about Doug Live.
Look, we both have a lot to say about Doug Live.
Okay.
We're joking.
We'd keep it succinct.
But Doug Live ran at Disney MGM Studios from March of 1999 until 2001, I believe May of
2001.
Short run in the theme park.
Short run.
Yeah.
This was a live musical experience based on what at that point was called Disney's Doug.
Yes.
It was one of the fundamental primary Nick tunes.
Part of that original hugely popular block with Ren and Stimpy and Rugrats.
And then kind of a strange thing where Ren and Stimpy fell off and moved around for the
various reasons that it did.
And Rugrats, still one of the crown jewels of the Viacom empire.
Doug moved.
Weird.
Like, whatever moves from Nickelodeon Disney.
So there was this strange, like, I think they did four seasons on Nickelodeon.
Yes.
And then it switches over to Disney.
They bought the production company, seemingly.
And then they start airing it on, not on cable anymore, but it gets the bump up to network.
Doug went network on ABC's One Saturday Morning.
Yes.
And I was a huge Doug fan on Nickelodeon.
I loved it so much.
I remember the premiere of Doug and Rugrats and Ren and Stimpy.
I definitely remember my childhood before and after.
I remember explaining to my dad, there's these new things now.
There's these shows and it makes me very happy.
My childhood is better now because there are the shows.
Nickelodeon had original cartoons.
They'd never done that before.
They showed a lot of Hannah Barbera stuff.
It was all Inspector Gadget.
It was a repurposed Inspector Gadget.
A lot of Gadget.
And a weird show with the koalas.
But now, Nick is doing its own things.
But one of the main Nicktoons becomes a Disney thing.
It's crazy.
It becomes a Disney thing.
I specifically remember the premiere.
And the weeks after, I'm like, this block is, they're all on on Sundays.
I have to go to church.
And so I'm sure I was taping them.
So you mean the new Doug?
No, the original Doug.
The original Nickelodeon Doug.
Oh, okay.
Premiered in August of 1991.
Okay.
And I also premiered in August 1991.
Oh, yeah.
So we've discovered that my introduction to Doug was Doug Live.
I was too young to know the show.
I was wondering this.
You were probably more, you were more of a Disney Doug.
That's where it falls off for me.
I don't know what's going on on Disney Doug.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know anything about Disney Doug.
I knew a little, but I always viewed it as kind of a false Doug.
Whoa.
These are fine words.
What do you think of that, Jane?
This is opposite subtract.
Go ahead.
To be honest, I'm just like, yeah, that makes sense.
I don't really have anything to fight about because I'm just so much younger than you guys.
So it's just, I'm so much more youthful.
So honestly, I'm really patient with you guys because you have a different lived experience than I do.
That's true, yeah.
You put up with us older men, these old, we're just a couple of, a bunch of older men.
I thought you were boys.
Well, we say that to masks that we know, we're old, old men inside.
Not talking about skincare five seconds ago.
Have I pointed this out that either, because you obviously do the thing of like, you know, appearing youthful and hip.
But there's also a lot of time, and I especially noticed it while I was gone, that you do a lot of like,
well, as an older man, now that I'm aging, now that I'm getting a little bit older in years.
Thank you, Jane.
You really fucking got his ass.
You really knew.
Jim Carrey and Mike.
But that's like, you either fall into like overcompensating or like over saying that you're old.
Yeah.
I think that's probably right.
I don't know.
Finish it.
It's on your mind.
It's where we need all that red light to blast out of your brain.
It is on my mind.
If we could, yeah.
Well, I want the-
That's how it works, right?
It's the eternal sunshine technology.
Just get the fact that how old I am out of my head.
It's not, you don't want to reverse aging.
You just want to get rid of the part of your brain that is aware of the aging.
Yeah.
Seems like it'll come back.
I think when you're in your 80s, you'll remember you're aging.
We'll get you on a, we'll get your Roblox account, you know.
We'll get you-
I don't want to go back that far.
No, we'll get you in the Minecraft movie screenings.
You'll be throwing stuff.
I think I can get fooled into thinking I'm like eight.
Yeah.
You play with toys, it's probably not going to be that hard.
Yeah, but they're characters from 40 years ago.
So it's confusing.
God.
It'll be confusing.
So, yeah, so Doug was very big for me when I was very young.
Then we switched to Disney.
I was like, okay, Patty Mayonnaise has a new haircut.
That's fine.
I'm sure some people saw it-
It's not a Felicity situation.
It changes everything.
Scott, I was just about to say, I'm sure some people-
I thought that was fine, but it always bugged me that Doug's sleeves got slightly longer.
I was like-
I didn't care for that.
I saw a picture of it.
I said, this is not for me.
I don't care for it.
They're trying to, this isn't Doug.
Doug is awkward.
Not Doug to me.
Doug wouldn't do this.
He's out of step fashion-wise.
I'm on the way to see Mystery Man at the movie theater.
I don't care about Doug.
This is not my Doug.
Generations Doug.
But then after a while, as I was looking up all these timelines,
Disney buys Jumbo Pictures right around the same time they buy ABC.
They're like, we'll put Doug in our Saturday morning block.
By the time Doug the musical premiered, and right around that time Doug's first movie came out,
I would have been 13.
Five-year-old and 13-year-old, while I clung to a lot of my interests,
I was already kind of dug in on the Fox.
Dug in hat.
Doug.
Doug Funny in on the Fox.
No, it should have just stayed a duck.
Okay.
Come on.
Polishing Bride's right.
We're going to talk, Melissa.
I don't...
Listen, ball and cheese.
Okay.
We fight so much.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know what that meant.
That had such an air to it.
I don't know whether to believe it or not.
We really don't fight a lot.
We're very good at communicating.
Yeah, we communicate pretty well.
That's good.
I was already kind of had my heels dug in on the Fox Kids Kids WB war.
There was a war up between?
I feel like there was a war for Saturday morning ratings because CBS Kids and ABC Kids block,
they were both also doing cartoons, but mostly Disney stuff.
You wanted to be brand loyal.
Yeah.
Now that said, Recess was pulling me away.
I was a big Recess kid.
Oh, huge Recess kid.
Yeah.
Love Recess.
What year does Recess premiere?
Because I feel like I miss Recess.
Mid to late 90s, I feel like.
I've never seen an episode.
No, I don't know.
Really?
Jack about Recess.
Oh, it's so good.
Who's the voice of the main kid?
He's a famous...
There's some famous younger actors.
97 is Recess.
Okay.
I was like six.
Original Doug Voice, by the way, Billy West, longtime voice actor Billy West.
It's such a sweet, vulnerable performance.
I think that probably we all hooked onto to some extent that he is this awkward, shy kid
who imagines being less awkward and less shy.
Whereas so much of Billy West's work is more bold and crazy.
I guess Fry is on the awkward...
Fry is in the zone.
Fry is kind of a grown Doug in a way.
That is a good point.
But it is such a...
I don't know.
It's very soft, tender kind of performance.
And that just really shows his range.
Lives in his head a lot.
Doug always imagining himself a superhero or a secret agent.
Big imagination.
Journaling a lot.
More confidence in the...
Kind of the original Walter Mitty.
That is a fictional story from the 40s and 50s.
We're going to put a hit motion picture of...
A hit stiller?
Yeah.
Do you have...
Here, I guess, how am I going to put this?
I don't have so much attachment to Doug now that I'm like, oh, I got to show this to my kid.
There's other cartoons that I feel like I'm still more attached to in my adult years.
I'm saying, is this similar to you or do you really have a strong attachment to Doug?
I don't really remember a ton of the original Doug either.
I was looking on...
Like, you can find Disney Doug on Disney Plus.
You can find the movie and the few seasons of TV.
But not original Doug, you're saying?
But original Doug, I don't know if it's up...
I'm sure they're all up on YouTube.
I know Quail Man.
I know the names of the characters.
I know Banging on a Trash Can.
Yeah, Banging on a Trash Can.
The Beats.
I know the Beats is a concept, but I don't know that I can name an episode for.
I don't remember an episode.
And I had really lost a lot of the character names until this episode came up.
I recall them now.
Yeah.
I know Skeeter.
I know his friend Skeeter.
Skeeter.
Roger Klotz.
The villainous Roger Klotz.
That's right.
Patty Mayonnaise.
I wish we didn't have to meet him in Doug Live.
I know.
But unfortunately, he's part of the...
Unfortunately.
Interesting fact, there's some cool projection stuff going on in this.
And Skeeter and Roger and Patty kind of come out of the projection.
Goosebumps every time when I saw it as a kid.
Fuck.
I was like, oh!
Like, every time.
Wow, really?
How old were you when you saw it for the first time?
I don't know.
What does that work out to be?
I guess 99 or 2001.
99.
Well, just do the math backwards from being so much younger than us.
Just start there and then go back to 99.
I was like six months old.
No, yeah, probably like eight or nine then.
I feel like I was younger than that.
But, oh, every time.
I was so fucking stoked.
Wait, sorry.
Doug is journaling or drawing as he is in the opening of both iterations of the show.
And he draws his friends and then they burst out of his notebook pages and live on stage
in front of you.
It was so cool.
That's probably the biggest special effect production value of this show.
Yeah.
So Goosebumps always.
You saw this a lot.
Tell us about your connection.
Like almost every weekend.
Because when I was little, we lived in Orlando from like five till maybe 10, 11 years.
And we had passes and my whole family would go every weekend.
And we always saw this show.
This show was really sentimental to my whole family.
We still sing the songs.
I went, Mom, I'm going to do this show and talk about Doug Live.
She went, Oh, my God.
And I was like, Mom, no, I think everyone hates it.
She was like, why?
And she started singing one of the songs.
I was like, I know.
It's really devastating.
She got sad.
She was like, really?
I love Doug Live.
And I was like, I know.
Well, do we think people hate it?
At the time, again, I was 13, 14.
Like I was leaving middle school, starting high school.
So I think I was a little like stuck out.
I don't know.
Punk?
Yeah.
So you were saying you didn't like it?
Because I never saw this at the park.
Oh, I saw it.
You really didn't?
No, I didn't.
I know it was there.
I saw it once or twice.
And this eventually theater became the American Idol experience.
Yes.
Well, between Doug Live ended and Doug Live was replaced by nothing.
It sat vacant for seven years or so.
And then it was replaced by a pretty disliked attraction.
There's no way it's close, I don't think, to American Idol.
I don't think to American Idol experience as far as dislike.
And now it's like, it's one of these Frozen things.
You'll know we're getting to the end when we do the episode for the first time in forever.
Frozen sing a lot.
We're like, we are out.
We are out.
We're out of fucking restaurants to talk about.
It's true.
Jason, you didn't like Doug Live.
You have a memory of not liking it.
Yeah.
I think when I first, when I saw it at the time, I didn't love it.
We watched a pretty decent video rip of it last night.
And I was like, okay, I kind of like this.
And I think I really appreciated the audience participation.
Let me ask, did you or any of your family ever get picked for the show?
No.
And I would have been so scared.
You guys, there's a part where they all come down to the front of the, like, audience,
like just off the stage.
I was like freaking out.
I was so scared of Roger.
I would like tuck my legs and I'd be like, I don't want to go in here.
I don't want to go in here.
So no, I would have been freaking out.
Well, he's terrifying looking.
The green makeup and the nose and he's like.
And you were probably also frazzled by the fact that in the cartoon animation on the
back of the set, he's wearing his attire from Disney's Doug.
But during the show, he's wearing his leather jacket from Nickelodeon's Doug.
And that's a pretty big oversight.
You could change wardrobe when you jump out of a notebook page.
I don't think so.
I don't believe it.
Get your animation in check, funny.
Geez.
Nice.
This, here's what, is this controversial to say that I find all the characters scary?
No, I got it.
They all have an odd.
Now, I'm not saying I don't like it because like I like Zubili Zoo, this old show that
had a bunch of scary looking animal characters.
I've heard of that.
I don't know it.
It's old.
You wouldn't.
I'm not saying this with them through time.
Nobody, we aren't bringing Zubili Zoo along for the ride.
Not yet.
As time marches on.
Well, we might be, but.
Not yet.
But yeah, so I'm not saying it's not a bad thing.
I'm just saying that like when I'm watching this now, I go, God, these are all unnerving
characters.
Well, because they make, and if you're unfamiliar with Doug, it's like, you know, like The Simpsons,
it makes color choices with the characters, crazy cartoon color choices.
Yeah.
So if you iterate something like this in a live setting, you have to decide how to represent
the weird, kooky colors that all of the characters are.
And you've got like, you know, you've got like Roger is green and Skeeter is like aqua
and Patty is kind of orange.
Orange.
They go sort of orange.
And when you put them, and then, and then the dog Porkchop is like, he's like a light
gray.
So there's a lot of face paint going around in general.
Put them all together is a lightly terrifying nature to this.
I'm not saying it was the wrong decision, but you know what?
It's somewhere between the fact that there's like, there's like also a lot of weird smoothness.
I feel like Roger especially is like, he feels shaved on the sides.
He's got like a Macklemore thing going on.
He shaved on the sides.
And then the makeup covers his real eyebrows and then false eyebrows are drawn on top.
And then Skeeter, a choice I don't even recall from the cartoon is that Skeeter only has
one eyebrow, but they keep this alive in the live production.
So he has this odd just floating eyebrow that feels like it was left on by mistake.
I know, but like from the audience, I feel like it works because that stage is really
big and it doesn't get filled completely.
So I feel like it reads from the audience.
But if you're taking a backstage picture, it's going to look funky.
When you group them all together, when you clump them, it's like, oh, that's a lot of
paint.
It wasn't meant to be a production that they film.
This is all from home movies we're watching now in hindsight.
They were making the characters just so they would appear correct in the audience.
Yeah.
It's not.
I mean, do you think the Zubals are scarier than the Doug Live people or are they on par
from Zubali Zoo?
I mean, these are more cats like these are like Andrew Lloyd Webber.
They're a little like cats.
They're a little Starlight Express.
Yeah.
And they're called the Zubals.
I don't think I knew that they were Zubals.
They say it in the opening theme.
Zubali Zoo.
Let's introduce the Zubals to you.
Ben Verene is one of those Zubals.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
I think there's just a lot more going.
Oh, cool.
A lot more going on.
Jane's like, yes, turn it around, please.
I don't want to see the Zubals anymore, please.
Ben Verene.
That's why I'm like, yeah, that's great.
Also, shout out to cats.
Shout out to Betty Buckley, my girl.
We love her.
Icon legend.
She's cool.
But was she ever in Zubali Zoo?
Fuck off, Michael.
You got one, too.
Oh, boy.
About even.
It's from love.
Jason got one, too.
I'm just kidding.
We're all, everybody's getting it.
Mike deserved that for not turning the laptop around.
I need to make sure you have fully absorbed each Zubal.
I'd also like to say, can I just vocalize, I love Zubali Zoo.
And I'd love to do an episode about it.
I hope this is the way that I could get out of doing an episode about it.
So I wouldn't be mad at all if we did an episode about Zubali Zoo.
Next week?
I think we should do one next week, baby.
The loud words he's saying are good.
They feel good to me.
They feel good for me to say.
I feel good when I look at that picture.
I'd feel good if we set one up soon.
I like everything that I'm hearing.
Did you all know that Porkchop is supposed to be a bull terrier?
What?
I didn't know the breed.
No, I did not know that.
I looked that up, and I was very surprised.
Like a Spuds McKenzie kind of.
You looked it up?
Where did you look it up?
Just on Wikipedia.
I just kept following rabbit holes and Wikipedia and fandom.
Yeah, I didn't know.
You know what?
I won't breed what I even imagined Porkchop was.
I don't know.
It's just dog.
Just cartoon dog.
Like a mutt or something.
General.
Breed.
General dog.
So yeah, it makes sense.
Yeah, when they do like...
I'm trying to think.
There's like peanuts.
When you see like You're a Good Man Charlie Brown or something,
they didn't decide...
I've seen this show a couple times, You're a Good Man Charlie Brown.
They oftentimes don't make a big paper mache head
that would mimic the peanuts characters on stage.
But they have to sometimes.
The costumes don't really over the top.
They do the shirts and stuff, for sure.
The shirts do the heavy lifting.
But some production out there must have done big scary heads.
Do you think so?
Where they take a lot of pipe cleaners
and put them together to make Charlie Brown's hair swish.
Well, there's a sketch.
There's a Saturday Night Live sketch, right?
With Martin Short or something.
Did they do it?
Yeah, yeah.
I can't think of...
That was pretty good.
Did they do the heads in that one?
They did the heads.
There's a much older sketch with Brendan Fraser,
where...
I fucked that up.
I always forget Fraser Fraser.
Fraser.
You said it right.
So I did it right.
But it's so weird that he didn't say it right.
It's a Pepo Pepo thing.
But where they did crazy make-up,
to purposefully terrifying effect.
Right.
So I get the choice.
It's just funny now watching it on grainy VHS 25 years later.
I just think you could have skipped the fact
that the Doug characters have crazy colors.
Because Doug himself does not.
So Doug is just normal.
Well, what do you think?
I think that that's a very beautiful way
of kind of showing him as the lead
and all the colorful characters in his life.
Sure.
Metaphorically as well.
Because he's kind of new in town
and he meets all of these groups from all stripes.
Not even necessarily like they're kooks,
but I think it's a cute way to go like,
it's from this person's perspective.
I don't know.
I just thought about that.
I was like, oh, this is actually kind of cute.
Maybe it's just to kind of represent the...
His family is all kind of regular.
Well, what's funny is...
They're like regular, but the neighbor's purple.
He feels like he doesn't fit in,
but he's the most quote unquote
stereotypical normal looking person,
which is also something I think worth thinking about.
Well, I think it shows you the...
I think I attached to Doug from the vantage point
of the stuff in your head
and how the stuff in your head can swally up
and stuff that you don't even need to be thinking about.
It doesn't need to be wearing you down.
I mean, for example, that the entire thing
is his secret crush is on Patty Mayonnaise,
and how can he ever tell Patty Mayonnaise that he...
How can I ever put this together with the girl
who's exceedingly nice to me,
with me every day at all times,
affectionate to me,
sweeter to me than the other boys?
It's funny that the unrequitedness is the runner
where like, oh, Doug, oh, Doug, come on.
It's right there, Doug.
Basically, you're a girlfriend already, Doug.
Just do it.
But that's the kind of kid I needed.
And I know you were this way too.
I was just like needing...
I need like all...
Like a regular kid might just need like a vague green light.
We need like 100 levels of green light to know to...
Can I say this?
When watching some Doug...
No.
Well, just allow it,
and I can cut it out if you don't allow it.
Okay.
I empathize with Doug so much
and what you're saying about Doug,
so much so that I can't stand Doug.
I don't want to watch him.
If you just go back to like,
this is young me a little bit.
Because he drives me insane because it reminds me of myself
and I'm being serious.
This is...
Wow.
He's so...
Come on.
God, don't act like such a loser, Doug.
This is the dialogue I was having today
when I was going through some stuff.
You might as well be saying Mike.
You might as well be saying...
Yes.
Wait, we dislike what we see in others
when we see ourselves.
Yes, so I'm annoyed with Doug
because he reminds me of a loser-ish me.
Wow.
That's heavy.
I very much loved TV's and film growing up and I...
TV's and film.
TV and film growing up.
Sure.
And it was all this stuff about kids,
boys having crushes and unrequited crushes
and if they say they like someone,
they don't like them.
Their life is over.
And it wasn't until I was much older
that so many of the people writing this
were antisocial weirdos.
Were like, ah, I will either show my childhood
in an affectionate way or I will be like,
I'll write when I never had to.
You know?
Well, that was scary.
Yeah.
It was ominous.
How does it feel to be...
You're having anxiety watching the show
because you connect to Doug so much
and here we are on your post-wedding episode.
Does it feel nice to feel like there's a happy ending
to the story as if Doug and Patty had gotten married?
Yeah.
I found my Patty mayonnaise.
I did briefly get out of my own way.
Sure.
That's nice.
Because I put myself there in the way
and I said, you are not getting past this.
I'm in the way now.
This is your life now.
This is my way.
I'm just kidding.
That's kind of nice.
Yeah.
Our first date I said, oh,
what do you think you'll have for lunch?
And you just grabbed my ear and was like, come on.
What?
Enough of this business.
I was so...
I'm a very different person now
because I had a lot of therapy,
but I was very nervous
and I never wanted anyone to spend money on me
because I felt terrible.
So I was like, just some pita bread.
I didn't even order a meal
because I was like, you don't have to spend money on me.
Did Jason also say, though, keep it under $10, please?
Hey!
No!
All right, just wanted to check.
I was like, I don't want him to spend money on me.
I'll just get something really cheap.
Well, I get that.
I understand that.
Where were we?
Can we get back to the show?
Like the live show?
Yeah.
I feel like I have a lot of cool perspective things
from a theme park performer perspective
that I noticed.
Oh, please.
I thought was really interesting.
The first thing I noticed was
there are five on mic characters,
and then they bring on audience participation.
A few things of note to me.
To me, that goes, hey,
we have the budget for five equity performers.
Figure it out for the rest of the performers.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, those rubes in the audio,
they don't know they're supposed to be getting paid.
It's the same money.
We can't pay four beats every night.
Let's get audience members.
Okay, they're in this one scene.
They're not paying people to do that,
and they're not on mics.
It would be a different thing anyway.
I'm like, they're not paying people for that.
I forgot that they were the adult audience members.
My next thought was,
they would never put people on a turntable
with props willy-nilly like that.
Never!
They would never do that.
When I did Fantasia on the turntable thing,
I had to practice it a bunch of times for safety.
They would never throw people on a turntable.
I'm serious.
They would never do that.
That's interesting.
Okay, okay, yes.
Parents are picked in an embarrassed dad dance competition,
and the reward is that you get to be the band, the beats,
and some of the show is oriented around a big beats concert.
When they appear,
they are revealed via a big turntable
that shows the concert set.
I'm not saying it's dangerous necessarily,
but that stuff has to be rehearsed with a turntable.
Interesting.
It probably is a little dangerous.
I wonder how they got away.
Was it just a less regulated time?
I know it was.
I know that not long after,
what I associate this era with is Disney
starting to get a little more careful about this stuff,
and just things like there's two tiny steps
that lead you up to the wishing fountain
behind the castle or whatever.
Better put bright yellow tape on that
so nobody trips and falls and sues us.
That kind of thing was starting to happen around this time,
maybe right after this time.
This is the fact that there's a bunch of parents
on a turntable.
It is a pre-litigious Disney move.
I feel like they would never just throw people up there
like that.
That's interesting.
That stood out to me.
Risky.
Threat lawsuits always around every corner with this show.
And then I always had a little crush on Doug.
I always liked little nerds that you'd never know.
What?
What's up?
I always liked cute little nervous nerds.
You're not really nervous.
You're quite confident.
But you still are very cute.
Thank you.
Well, BDE, to quote the previous episode,
to quote former guest Jane Cleary.
Hello.
Yes, my husband has a huge personality.
Oh, OK.
There we go.
I am very satisfied.
Oh, boy.
He was just talking about the energy.
He was talking about the energy, to be fair to Scott.
I was talking about the E and not the D.
He said the E.
I didn't even say it was B.
That's fine.
I mean, whatever you want to say, it's fine.
I was talking about the E and not the D.
I don't know if there was B.
I like to try to make you two as uncomfortable as possible
sometimes.
I love it.
I don't take much.
That's why I.
The secret to me, as the Hulk would say,
is I'm always uncomfortable.
You're so funny.
So I always like that.
I'm going to jump to talking about the music.
Is that OK?
Please.
So before we get to what we listened to this morning.
Right.
The music really hit me in a way.
21 Jumbo Street was always so nice and made me
feel so many different feelings.
So that music really did hit me.
And yeah, I remembered so much of it.
But I'm like, yeah, that song in particular,
I think it made me feel so happy.
I don't know.
It was so nice.
That's nice.
This is kind of opening number, and it's reprised at the end.
It's sort of the meet the cast.
The show is happening in full now.
Yeah.
I also like the anybody else at all.
The anybody else at all.
When Doug's like, I wish I was not me, you know?
I like that one.
Do you feel like you're looking at these songs better
than a theme park musical might ever have a right to be?
Like they stick with you longer than?
I'm not going to go so extreme on that.
But I will say there was a lot of heart in 21 Jumbo Street.
I don't know.
I think they captured the vulnerability
pretty well in that.
21 Jumbo Street is the best of the songs.
I think so too.
That's the only one I remember from watching this.
Yeah, this morning we listened to a podcast
with the two writers of the music for the show.
And it was really, really interesting.
The best part was when they talked about Eisner
coming to watch it.
And Scott just leaned forward.
Scott just like leaned forward.
Let me be clear.
I've been leaning forward through it.
It's not as if I was back the whole time.
No, no, no.
But you were like, oh, what's up?
I played it cool, though.
I wanted to lean forward.
So they said.
You're always uncomfortable
unless Eisner is being talked about.
Oh, I feel good.
I just like because we always talk about like,
do we think Eisner had to approve this?
Did he have to watch it?
The fact that he came and watched Doug Lime.
I was going to say, I have information for you.
The sale of the Jumbo.
What the company's name?
Jumbo Pictures.
Did Michael Eisner say Jumbo Pictures?
He had to have.
Jumbo.
So anyway, go ahead.
So when they were going to have him come to the rehearsal,
they made a huge note and a huge thing about
everyone wanted everything to be perfect.
They were straightening things on the wall.
They had all these like things laid out for him
because they were like so nervous about it.
I just thought that was funny.
But when he watched it, he said,
oh, you need to put in a radio song like for the beats,
a beat song.
You need to put in a radio song.
And they were like, that was our note from Eisner
and thought it was really interesting.
They also talked about Fantasmic opening around the same time.
And so they got to go to the dress rehearsal for Fantasmic.
And I just thought that was really cool.
And it kind of inspired them in how the animation
and the live were combined.
And something else that was really funny,
they said, is they were rehearsing in the parking lot of MGM.
And when they were on break,
there were these two bushes that they would go through
to go into the park and ride rides
and then come back, these two composers.
Whoa, wow.
And I was like, oh my God.
There was a security breach.
Truthfully, it sounded like they were like,
yeah, we would just go ride some rides and come back.
Wow.
But they were hired on just to write the music.
And they weren't even invited to the opening and stuff.
It was like, for hire, OK, you're done now, bye.
So they were like, we weren't really included
in a lot of that stuff.
But yeah, I just thought all of that was quite interesting.
And they wrote so many more songs, apparently,
which, yeah, that's usually what happens.
Their names were Jeffrey Lewidan and William Squire.
And they were interviewed on this podcast called
The Tiara Talk Show, which has come up in the past.
But specifically, they said the Fantasmic dress rehearsal
was the middle of the night in the park.
And they sat directly behind Michael Eisner to watch this.
So he gave notes.
It was in the same span of time where he saw Dog Live
and Fantasmic, and where he's given out
those genius little nuggets that would help
to cement these shows as legendary.
And when they are putting in a radio thing,
that is an early episode of the Nickelodeon Doug,
where Doug and Skeeter win tickets to a beats show.
And then Skeeter gets grounded and can't go.
And Doug the Ops hang out with Skeeter.
They go to the mall shop, and the beats show up.
So maybe Michael Eisner had seen this.
He goes, you know the one with Skeeter where he gets grounded
and Doug and him are going to the beats?
We have to do something like that.
It's a great episode.
Have you seen it aired in 1990?
Well, let's jump the shark since.
Frankly, I'm disappointed with Disney's Doug.
I thought they peaked back then.
Disney's Doug.
I'll sell Jumbo as soon as I can
if the quality doesn't increase.
Breck loves it.
He's 20, and he loves Doug.
They said that even before the Disney sale,
they were working on some sort of Doug musical thing
that Jim Jenkins, the creator of Doug,
was hoping to license out to schools and stuff.
For school performances, which I did think was actually real.
I'm like, oh yeah, that kind of sounds right.
A touring.
Either for a touring for people to come to schools
or I guess people to put it on buzz.
That is a good children's entertainment touring show
if they flushed it out maybe a little bit more.
I crafted it to be doable for middle school budgets.
Yeah, all that stuff.
Nice little play that people can put on easily.
But then every middle school would have the choice
of do we do the face paint?
Can we afford the face paint?
Are people going to be afraid of the face paint?
Jim Jenkins, by the way, if you look him up,
Doug is very autobiographical.
He's been very clear about that.
Even the name Patty Mayonnaise was a portmanteau
of girls he had crushes on.
Sally Mustard.
Yeah, Sally Mustard.
Oh, you know her too?
She was a latte.
I just saw her.
But if you look at older Jim Jenkins,
you still look like an older Doug.
He kind of has a Doug vibe about him.
Honestly, I'm shocked we haven't gotten a Doug reboot.
You know, Doug and Patty are married,
and you're their kid.
I mean, we got that with Boy Meets World.
There's been no talk of new Doug?
I haven't seen any.
He perfected it with the live show,
so you really just don't want to touch it at this point.
You're always going to be chasing Doug live, yes.
Yeah, why even try?
Yeah, well, I mean, look, I'm glad.
I don't want to see Doug ever again.
Is this a personal thing?
Yeah, it's too dark for you.
I don't want to see Jim Jenkins' face
that looks like old Doug.
That's really what I don't want to see.
It reminds me of myself.
If your daughter starts watching new Doug
on Disney Plus or whatever,
and then you scare her by standing up and saying,
stop that Doug!
Yeah.
Get your act together, Doug!
Right.
Throw some nuts, Doug!
Come on, Doug.
Mike throws a plate at a woman.
Yeah.
Sit to this!
You're 49, Doug.
You shouldn't be awkward anymore.
Work on yourself.
Sorry.
There you go.
We also were talking about,
when I was saying there's five roles in the show,
because Roger doubles, obviously,
as the bad guy in that one scene,
which, as a kid, I was fucking terrified of, by the way.
Oh, yeah.
What's his bad guy name?
Dr. Professor Rubbersuit?
Yeah.
Is that right?
But I was like, what is the most involved,
not really involved role, but I'm like,
what would be the hardest track for this?
And I was like, well, Doug's on stage the whole time,
so probably him, but I went, that fucking dog,
he is doing stage crew work while he's performing,
and very physical.
So while he's not singing,
when the quail, the head thing falls off of him
when he's putting the helmet on
and the quail man's belt falls off,
you see the dog sneak in the background and grab it,
and then when they do the quail kid,
he leans forward and they use his mic.
So he's kind of structurally,
he goes and grabs the tickets from the radio guy
and brings it over,
and I'm like, this is a really interesting track
because it's physical and you're doing like logistics.
And then I was like, Doug's probably the most demanding.
He's only off stage for like 30 seconds
in that one scene with Patty and the green guy.
And so I'm like, oh, okay, I guess him.
I feel like Patty is probably the chillest track,
which would have been really awesome to do
if I had been old enough,
because she, I also like that she's kind of the one
who's like, you guys are all fucking crazy.
Okay, see you later.
She's not like the straight,
well, she kind of is like the straight man, honestly.
Can I ask a question?
When you say track, is that-
Oh, sorry.
Like the role, so like-
I assume that's what you meant.
So like in Beetlejuice, my track was Fantasia.
But like a track for Roger, your track is still that
and the radio host, that's one track,
even though it's two characters.
Is that the same guy?
I didn't realize that.
Are you joking?
He's the radio guy before he's Roger?
It's three.
He's the radio guy.
Oh.
Radio guy.
But that's still one track.
It's one actor's track.
So that's if you're like, if you're sharing roles,
if you're like, you dip off to do this thing
and then you come back to this thing.
It doesn't have to be that.
You could be the same character.
Doug is a track.
Sure.
Is that a Broadway term or a theme park term?
Both.
Okay.
I mean, I guess.
I use it interchangeably.
But like for Broadway, a lot of times ensembles,
there'll be different ensemble tracks.
And ensemble typically plays various things
throughout the show.
So like track, dance track one is like,
oh, I have to remember that it's different
than dance track seven.
I give those, not those people,
people in ensembles who do cover so many tracks,
like I give them so much credit
because it's also slightly different sometimes
that you have to remember, oh wait,
I'm doing this track for this.
And so that's what I mean when I say,
like roll in the show maybe.
Sure, sure.
I assumed, I just didn't know.
No, no, no, yeah, I am.
I didn't know what it was.
So you might, you would, if this was still around
or had been when you were able to be in these shows,
you maybe would have wanted to be Patty.
Oh my God, yeah.
Or is Pork Chop a gender neutral,
I feel like it.
I guess it could have been.
I feel like I saw pictures of female Pork Chops.
Really?
I guess it could have been.
I'm not sure, maybe.
Yeah, I would have killed to be Patty Mayonnaise,
although I'd be scared of Roger.
I'd be scared when he's the bad guy
and I'm standing on the thingy, but.
There's a pre-show character too, right?
Doing like trivia with the audience
and getting the kid and getting the adult.
I don't know what character, but.
Yeah, just kind of has like crazy dress on.
They tell you when the bad guy comes out,
go boo, boo, and when Doug wins and he's the underpants,
like yay, yay.
I did, I came across on the Doug Wiki about the show.
There was an interesting set of comments.
No.
On March 3rd, 2018, someone said about this show,
it's gone now, isn't it?
And then someone replied on March 28th, 2023,
yes it is.
It's okay.
So that's it.
Just a five year difference.
Five years later to get that yes it is.
You are correct.
Checked every day, every day.
Every day.
Until finally somebody, yeah.
There was nowhere else to find.
It's not the closure I wanted.
Yeah, but you know,
well they waited for five years for that.
So yeah, I certainly appreciated more watching it now.
When I was 13, I was a little like,
I didn't love that.
Wow.
I think that's interesting.
I don't know.
You actually remember this
and you had a natural reaction to it at the time.
Yeah.
And then you attribute it to like snobbiness or something.
I just, I don't know.
Puberty, moodiness.
You were a purist, a Nickelodeon dog purist.
I was kind of a dog purist.
I feel like it's more that.
Yeah, but you were like.
Like I kept trying to show you last night
and you were not interested.
I was like, look, his sleeves used to be shorter.
This drives me nuts.
Okay, no, no, no.
I'm not making this up, Jay.
I thought you were specifically just talking
about the live show.
And I was like, yeah, it's cartoony.
Well, no.
It's oversized.
It's three quarters, but it's just a t-shirt.
Well, yeah, no, it makes sense in the live show.
Fuck with me.
You got it coming.
Watch out.
You can hear on Mike just for the theater of the mind.
Oh, she's cracking her knuckles.
Oh no.
Wasn't there an episode while I was gone
where you guys talked about how you want like a strong woman
to throw you around like the X-Men?
Yeah.
Did you hear that one?
Oh, yeah.
Is that something that you already discussed
in your home lives?
Oh, yeah.
I am quite strong.
She's very strong.
And I like to say I'm made of glass and popsicle sticks.
Yeah.
Sure.
These are not good materials.
So I, yeah.
Vulcan.
What's the character you want?
What's the character you're chasing?
Buff.
And what's the laser one?
From Generation X?
Generation X, yeah.
Oh, god.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
All right.
I'll look it up.
Or we don't have to look it up.
Or we could go with Buff and that's the end of it.
Go with General.
Yeah.
I think you're the buff.
We're good, James.
We're good.
No, no.
I'm getting this.
All right.
Oh, god.
I can see him in his spiky blonde hair.
Live show-wise, like is this of all the things
that have closed over the years,
would this be your number one to bring back?
No.
Oh, no.
It wouldn't.
Hunchback.
Hunchback would be number one.
For fucking sure.
You love that Hunchback show.
I was going to say I would jizz my fucking pants.
Wow.
If the Hunchback of Notre Dame show came out,
you would jizz your fucking pants.
Don't even talk to me like I'm getting excited.
Don't even talk to me about it.
Because the actual casting that could happen
where they do traditional, not traditional,
but they stick to the right ethnicity of the characters,
which they would do now, fucking sickening, man.
Don't even talk to me about it.
I'm going to cry.
It's too overwhelmingly awesome to imagine.
This is a positive feeling, but it's overwhelming.
I literally am thinking about it, and I'm like, I will cry.
Similarly overwhelming.
Little tears are happening.
It's Buff and Refrax.
His name was Refrax.
Is this a guy?
The quickest way to fight those tears
is to start talking about Buff and Refrax.
Does that balance you out?
Yeah, that's guy who has x-ray vision and laser eyes.
Wait, wait, that's who you want?
You want her to be like Refrax?
No, she's Buff because she's strong, and I'm Refrax.
You're Refrax.
You're the Refrax.
Not really.
He's kind of a creep.
Oh, Shane.
Because the comic book characters.
Did you know what happened on that episode?
What?
That episode we pitched an idea for a mutant based on you
that already was a character that I didn't realize.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I don't remember.
I pitched an X-Man.
That's what I should have been here.
Scott made it 10 minutes in that episode when he was not on it,
and he could not finish it for sure.
That was the most difficult one.
I, at the end of the episode, pitched an idea for a mutant
called Soft Serve that Jason could play
that would have a different flavor of ice cream
coming out of each finger, and we went through
which flavor each finger would be.
We did all 10?
We did all 10.
I forced him to do it.
I put him on the spot.
In an episode I never heard, you just named,
you assigned ice cream flavors to fingers?
I gave him a time limit as well.
I put him under the gun there in that one.
And I beat it.
I nailed it.
I mean, it wasn't.
It was like 60 seconds.
That's my baby.
Thank you for your support.
I love you so much.
But apparently that's where we're getting X-Man.
Really?
There's an X-Man named Soft Serve that shoots ice cream.
So I either stole it and didn't realize I stole it,
or it's just parallel thinking.
It's just too many mutants, I guess.
You see, honey, Chamber and Husk,
the original comic book characters,
were too expensive to do TV.
And that's our time, everybody.
So when we're down, Doug Live.
No, what do we want to get at about Doug Live
before we shut the door, to use the term?
It was kind of my introduction to the stage Fogsmoke
and the smell of it.
So that was also very visceral for me,
like, thinking about that.
Yeah, I don't know.
I loved it.
I have very fun family memories of it.
And we were really sad when it closed.
And I get that a lot of people, like,
hearing your perspective of it,
not knowing about the Doug series as much,
I'm like, oh, yeah, that makes sense.
It's probably weird.
But if you're only seeing Doug in that perspective,
you're like, oh, this is wonderful.
I like this music.
And Doug is so cute.
And it's so romantic at the end.
And they end up together.
And Patty Menaise is kind of annoying.
And a little, not jarring, not like...
Flighty out of it?
No, that was the last one I couldn't remember.
I remember going, flighty?
I don't know, you guys.
Someone else talk.
OK, well, can't do.
We haven't talked about Doug's hair spikes.
That's a, I said that Doug is normal
because he doesn't have face paint.
But also, the way they represent his cartoon hair
is to just take regular hair and slick it down.
And then he looks like he's in, well,
I'll say the offspring again.
He looks like Dexter Holland a little bit.
He just looks like a 90s spiky guy.
Well, because cartoon Doug has like six strands of hair.
Right.
But rather than weird wig,
the wig choices are interesting.
They just spike his real hair.
Roger, they put in,
it's like a red wig with curlers.
It's a big set of curlers.
And then, as I said, like bald on the side.
I'm terrified of Roger.
No, Doug is definitely wearing a wig.
That's not his real hair.
Well, look what I'm looking at right here.
I think we got some slicked up,
some big old, like, gelled up hair, I want to say.
Hmm.
Oh, that's really tough.
I don't know.
I mean, it could be a big wig, I suppose.
But it is very Beakman.
It looks like Beakman from Beakman's World.
Yeah, yeah.
There you go.
Yeah.
Did Michael Eisner know who Beakman was, do you think?
It's the competition.
I curse him every day.
Can we do an episode?
That's why I got Bill Nye.
To fight the scourge of Beakman.
I love Bill Nye.
Can we do a Bill Nye episode?
We could.
I don't necessarily need to be on it,
but I love...
Still would.
Still would do.
When he shows for the oil companies
on Universe of Energy?
Still would do.
You could talk about him there.
Still would do, Bill Nye?
I want to fucking stove it.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, Jesus.
Here we go.
Is he...
So we didn't know we were winding down here.
Now we're hearing you want to fuck Bill Nye.
I don't know so much, but I still would.
Bill Nye, really?
Whoa.
What was the formative Bill Nye TV show
where it was like, oh, wow, Bill.
Yeah, that was my...
I'm just saying, what was Universe of Energy?
Yeah, what's the kind of thing you would do
that implanted those feelings?
When you picture the Bill Nye of your dreams.
I don't know.
I just think he's got this weird swagger.
I'm glad we moved in together,
because if I recall, he used to live
in my old neighborhood somewhere.
Did he?
Because him and Ed Begley Jr. were neighbors,
and they got into a war to make their houses
the most energy efficient.
Oh, my God.
They're big environmental guys.
You know, Ed Begley Jr. was taking the subway
to the Oscars.
Well, have you seen Bill Nye swing dance?
Yes.
You have?
I believe I have.
Yeah, I just made a face,
because if you see that...
Just saying.
I mean, look, he was on Dancing with the Stars.
He's really good at swing dancing,
and you've got to know how to move
and different things.
Can I ask, if it's too personal,
did Jason know that Bill Nye was such a...
I always told you I thought he was cute.
I was always like, yeah, I've said to you,
like, yeah, I would.
Still would.
Sure.
So you flashed it.
If you hadn't moved, you could have been
walking around the neighborhood,
and Bill Nye was there.
And then he rolls up on an electric bike
that's even more efficient than...
Probably the most efficient bike is not electric.
What I'm saying is,
a better bike than Ed Begley Jr.,
and then your eyes go grazing over,
ooh, oh, you don't say.
I feel like I would have been too nervous
to say anything.
And I'm just trailing behind her.
Like, now that's the restaurant
where Beretta went back for his gun,
where he said he didn't kill his wife.
Mattel.
Yeah.
Robert Blake?
Yes.
Right?
Yes, that's his name, yeah.
I think you know him as Beretta first.
I couldn't pull the name Robert Blake.
Robert Blake.
But I could pull Beretta.
And of course, the Universal Sheraton,
the inspiration for that,
stayed there for a while.
The inspiration for what?
For Beretta.
It was the inspiration for the show Beretta?
It was a different cop guy.
A cop guy who had written a book.
What, you're talking about Telly Savalas?
No, no.
The...
I forget.
Oh, God.
It's complicated.
I forget.
It came up on the original City Walk.
Is this about Chamber or Reflex?
I don't know any of the words
y'all been saying in the last minute, by the way.
Well, we're trying to figure it out, too.
No, I got a little lost there.
If you figure it out, let me know.
I just wait.
The hotel was the inspiration for...
No, no.
The man, this former super cop,
wrote a book, and they were adapting it to a TV show.
The TV show got reworked after the first season
and would go on to become Beretta.
Okay.
Wait, what does the hotel have to do with it?
Yeah, what does the hotel have to do with it?
He stayed, he was one of the people who stayed in that.
One of the celebrities listed as staying...
Was the super cop.
Yeah, the super cop.
The real life super cop behind Beretta.
Quote unquote.
Jason...
How in the world did this information...
I just really want to personally thank you
for letting us know all that information.
Jane herself blessed Jason harder than either of us.
Wow, the biggest mic drop.
You spend less than two hours with them.
You start nailing my ass.
But I also nailed their asses.
All right.
That's an ass nailing to go around.
Which is why we like that.
I love ass play.
Jane loves ass play and that's why we have her.
Is there anything else to get or do we start winding it down?
Do we say on that note, Jane Clear,
you survived podcast The Ride,
and thank you for coming to us
and bringing us your fond memories,
bringing us your wedding tales,
and for nailing our asses.
I will nail your asses any day, boys.
Watch out for this video.
You got it coming to you all the time, Mr. Sharon.
What is that?
This is Lookout Bear from Zubli Zoo.
I don't like his pose.
His pose is freaking me out more than anything.
His name is Lookout Bear,
and he's kind of hitting the dab, honestly.
His head's not in the elbow.
It's very far.
Not 100%.
All right.
Let's access the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Well, first, can I be sentimental for a second?
I just want to say I really love you both,
and thank you so much for always helping us out
and the extra things that we need between Jason and I,
and even though I fuck with you guys so much,
I really appreciate your friendship,
and I just wanted to say that.
You don't have to.
Likewise.
Oh, thanks.
Jeez, appreciate it.
And I just want to give Jason a shout-out,
because this MS has kind of been kicking his ass,
and he's pushing through
and trying not to let it defeat everything,
so I just want to be sentimental for a minute
and tell you guys I love you all.
Thank you.
As far as gift shop,
I'm a stylist, as we were saying.
You can find me on Instagram,
janeclairstyling.
It's J-A-Y-N-E, C-L-A-I-R-E.
Please reach out to me.
I'm also on Twitter.
I have like 30 followers or something,
but I'm always looking for new clients.
You want those numbers up, don't you?
Please, you guys.
Listeners, help Jane out.
Please, I really want you.
On the dying website,
trying to get those listeners.
The what?
The dying website.
Oh, yeah.
But no, I do event styling
or just personal styling, closet stuff,
and so reach out,
or if I've started doing these YouTube videos
that I'm just kind of throwing up onto YouTube,
so let me know if you like it.
You broke down wedding look,
your other styling content?
Yeah, yeah.
I asked on Instagram the other day,
and some people really gave some good suggestions.
I think one I'm going to try to work on
is a video showing how to look cute in a theme park
while still being comfy and it being reasonable.
I feel like I'm going to have some controversial opinions.
There's one I already have.
Please, go ahead.
Well, okay.
Here's what I'll say.
I don't love...
Again, I'm not judging you.
The whole thing with my styling is,
if you want to wear it and it makes you comfortable,
okay, I'm not going to tell you,
but if you ask my professional opinion,
I'm going to give it to you.
You know what I mean?
So if you're asking me about that,
do not wear the theme park shirts.
It's like Jason said, wearing the band tee to the concert.
It doesn't ever look cute.
It just looks silly to me.
But if you love it, all right.
Can I ask a question?
Yeah.
When we were all together at Epcot Center
a couple years ago
and I was wearing a Mickey Mouse
and Minnie Mouse yellow shirt,
would that be a faux pas in your mind?
I don't think necessarily.
I don't like the gaudy, like so much going on,
like a vintage shirt.
I would be okay with, like Jason and I
have a lot of vintage theme park stuff.
And if anything, I would say something more basic
or something vintage.
I just, I hate the gaudy shirts that are like, you know,
I just, I've seen so many at Epic
and I'm like, guys, this is so...
Like you can look really cute in a theme park
and it doesn't have to be one of those shirts.
So I'm here to help.
Would you, with the shirts you're talking about,
would they be okay in regular society?
No, but...
It sounds like you just don't like these shirts at all.
Well, that's also kind of true.
Yeah.
Now if I, if you were to see me somewhere
and I was wearing a shirt that had clip art of wine glass
and then on top of that is the headgear
that the Evil Queen from Snow White wears.
And then it said in a really almost unreadably cursive font,
mirror, mirror on the wall, who's the drunkest of them all?
Would that be a cool clothing item to wear
or would you advise me against that?
I advise against all of those.
Look, if you want to look chic, don't wear printed stuff.
I mean, genuinely, I like vintage printed stuff,
but if you don't want to look,
like if you want to look put together, wear solids.
Do not wear gaudy shirts.
Okay, I want to show you a picture.
And I've been just faving Vintage Islands of Adventure
and Universal Escape shirts on Depop.
Again, vintage to me is a little different.
I don't like these new prints.
I'm not trying to be an asshole.
I really am not.
But people are asking me,
hey, how do I look cute in the theme park?
How do I look cute in the theme park?
I need to show you a picture of that shirt I'm talking about.
I want to know what you think about it.
Okay, well, then I'm going to do the plug.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
Counterpoint.
Dave Toma was the detective name.
Jason, come on.
Super cop Dave Toma.
Dave Toma is the state of the universe.
My God.
Well, Jane, aren't you glad that he finished that fact?
Toma was the TV show.
That was going to take back that taking him to task.
Toma became Beretta.
Well, you know, to pay off all the threads in this episode,
wait, tell me that fact one more time.
Toma became Beretta.
Re-he-he-he-he-ly.
Whoa.
There we go.
We got it all in.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
I don't get it.
No, this is The Second Gate plugs.
If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on The Second Gate
or on our VIP Patreon tier club three
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and a regular episode's ad free.
All of that is at patreon.com slash podcast the riot.
And of course, excellently printed shirts on our T-public.
That's true, yeah.
The printing's so good.
It would totally pass muster as far as Jane's.
You could wear that to our live show.
But that's not a theme park section of the theme park or something.
Okay, okay.
So then we're fine.
Okay, Mike has produced his shirt.
Let me see.
Are we ready for this?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I was wearing at Epcot.
It sounds like a no, folks.
Silence.
It sounds like you got a no.
Speak volumes.
Is it a reprint or a real vintage shirt?
Well, shouldn't you be able to tell?
Because I think it's a reprint,
but I'm asking you so you can be a little embarrassed.
It's not a reprint at all.
It was a new shirt on Shop Disney.
Okay, so that's a new shirt.
It's not a vintage shirt.
It looks kind of vintage.
Right.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Vintage or anything.
But did you know or is it more about the status?
What do you mean?
Is it the status of owning something that's vintage?
Is it the idea of something being vintage
or is it actually the way it looks?
Both.
That's what I thought.
Okay.
Also, everyone wears the same fucking shirt.
Do you want to look cute at theme park?
Do I wear the same fucking shirt?
I've never seen another person wearing that shirt.
That's unique.
And there's a reason, Mike.
No, I'm just kidding.
Wow.
And right down at the end, the ass nailing has...
I've been nailed.
We have one final nail of one final ass
right at the exit of the episode.
In my little wooden seat.
You've been nailed square in the center
of your little wooden seat.
And with that, we not only shut the door,
we slammed the door on this entire conversation.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page on Facebook.