Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to your podcast, There's No Turning Back.
I'm Scott Gardiner, joined by Mike Carlson.
I'm here and I'm feeling it.
I'm feeling this.
Even though it's been a little bit of time, but you still feel like I was worried that some of the magic would dissipate, but you feel like you're tapping back in.
Yeah, I am. I listened to the song on repeat as I came here.
I drove in the car today.
That'll do it.
And spun your car in circles, donut after donut.
Yep.
Yeah, donuts in the parking lot and on the road.
Bought a big globe and put it in the center of a church parking lot.
And I had the Eternals on in the car.
On the laptop.
So one of the giant Celestials was.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, a Celestial is in Eternals.
I see. Yes, yes, they are.
I must have fallen asleep.
Believe it or not.
Too early to figure that out.
Jason Sheridan, welcome.
Hi, I'm here too.
You know, the Eternals got like a marquee crossover a couple of years ago in the Marvel comics with the Avengers and the X-Men.
And the impact was like you dropped a pebble in a lake.
I feel like I feel like it did not move the needle.
For our pals, for Kingo and Sprite, these are these these guys can move needles miles at a time.
Yeah, they can move needles with their minds, right?
That's what the Eternals do.
That's right. Yeah, I got it.
Jason took a time.
Yeah, Jason do shitting on the Eternals.
No, no, that they even lost.
They did not announce them on the doomsday in the chairs.
They did not announce any of the Eternals on the chairs.
Do you know the chairs?
Oh, yeah.
You've heard of the chairs?
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they're not all these all these all these Marvel actors have mentioned.
There wasn't it didn't just go to one that said Sprite.
It didn't have a no, it didn't.
So we'll see that.
Maybe it's a surprise.
Yeah, yeah, that's why I think I this is how much I'm not even thinking about what I'm on, how much my focus is different with this ride.
With Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Ruin is that I don't think I realize until right now this is a Marvel thing that I love.
Right.
That's how much I just don't even I'm like maybe not paying attention to like the story or any of the specifics of what's happening.
It's like I guess is that weird that like 90 percent of my enjoyment has nothing to do with the Marvel of it.
Isn't that the whole thing with this podcast in general?
It's a recurring often happens and that we can be tricked into liking almost anything as long as it, you know, it moves us around, spins us around, moves us physically, moves us, moves us emotionally, which I think we're going to talk about today.
Well, I said in the I think when we were walking through the queue, I said, isn't it funny that James Gunn is responsible for the tone and the fun of two major rides?
Yeah, that's the way you think of like movies now.
At least I think of movies that way now is that if they're hits, then they can be rides and that's the way we get big, expensive, cool rides.
And it's just because James Gunn took a meeting in whatever 2013.
And I don't I don't know if the muse I think he put the music like the needle drops in the script that was there.
OK, so like there was a script, I think somebody had I forget a woman's name, Nicole, something I think had had like pulled the Guardians of the Galaxy out of the Marvel, like sea listers and was like, oh, this might be interesting.
And then James Gunn came in to like get a directing job and then he rewrote it.
But it's because of that now that we have two rides like this and that going forward now is why you have to root for the box office of certain movies.
We really do.
If Fantastic Four is kind of cool looking, it doesn't matter if you like the movie, but you have to root for if you like the aesthetic, because then we will get a ride or a Tomorrowland redo.
Well, look, the Minecraft ride is going to be terrific.
That was a hit.
Sure.
Who made who made who made Minecraft?
Do we know?
I don't remember that can make rides.
Yeah.
Or is it in one of the dead zones?
It might be in one of the dead zones.
Is it a Warner Brothers discovery?
That's a nice thing.
We don't have to root for anything on the Warner Brothers.
That's true.
Although they sometimes work with Universal, I guess.
Yes, true.
So you can, but it feels less I can't tell right now if we have to root for Ketchup Entertainment, the company that saved the Coyote vs. Acme and that I think put out the other one.
I don't know where the theme park alliances of Ketchup Entertainment are.
I don't know.
But if we get Ketchup World somewhere in this country or abroad, I could see that.
That becomes Ketchup World Abu Dhabi.
Yeah, it might happen.
This is a wonderful tie-in with the Heinz company.
You'd have to think, where does Heinz manufacture out of?
Well, it was originally based in Pittsburgh.
Okay.
Well, then maybe that's a good thing.
Maybe they need to embrace their name.
I don't know who they are or why they're called Ketchup Entertainment or why they are saving the Looney Tunes, but I like what they're doing.
And maybe they plant in Pittsburgh, just make it a Ketchup town.
Sure.
And then it's like half a Hershey-style factory tour and half all of our favorite characters from the Ketchup Entertainment.
Yeah, sure.
Also, now I'm having this thought as well.
Part of the reason there's Guardians Galaxy rides is because of the deal with Universal,
where they can't make Marvel rides based on the characters that are represented in Islands of Adventure.
Guardians are not there, so that's the loophole.
Are the Eternals anywhere in Islands of Adventure?
I don't believe they are.
Like if they're even on a cup.
Right.
Well, they might be in that big, like the crystals with the paintings, the big events.
I bet they're not.
I don't know that they are.
So I bet you could do an Eternals ride in Florida.
That's a guess, but that could be another Marvel thing they were allowed.
So I may have to take all of this back.
That's what I'm getting at.
And start embracing the Eternals.
Right.
Start playing with the many, many toys that Griffin has bought for my children.
At least 30 different Eternals toys.
Yeah, right.
I'm not a toy collector like you.
Right.
So I think like the majority, not the majority, but a solid percentage.
I guess if he had up all my son's toys.
I don't know.
Like 10% of the toys in the house are Eternals toys, thanks to Griffin Noon.
A lot of ironic toys.
But I have to lose all iron.
It has to all become incredibly sincere.
If I could get a launch coaster that shoots me through a portal
that turns me into a perennial 12-year-old like Sprite.
Yeah, right.
They found the Eternal Youth.
It's kind of a cousin of Indiana Jones.
The making of me type of a ride.
Oh, yeah, great.
Yes.
Let's get really specific with the language.
And really like intimate with the language.
Right.
What it takes to keep Sprite 12 forever.
Yeah.
Let's get that same writer to write all that copy.
It could happen.
It's some sort of boy who never grows up.
That's good.
I feel like missing something.
It's right there in front of me and I can't put my finger on it.
But the Guardians of the Galaxy, the aesthetic and the vibe.
Wait, I have a question.
Did you mean Peter Pan or did you mean Clifford?
Because we have two competing.
Well, I was joking about Peter Pan, but definitely more preferential to a different boy.
I went to Clifford because I'd rather go to Clifford,
even though Clifford is also incredibly creepy.
Well, it's got a theme park.
It's got a theme park in there.
Yeah, it does.
Oh, yeah, exactly.
But I was just saying because the aesthetic of the Marvel Cinematic Universe is a little bit
dry in some ways, especially if you're doing the Avengers campus aesthetic or whatever.
But this, because this was a hit, we get a fun thing that is close to
excitement of a comic book that Jason and I are so fond of.
And because of and where I still don't care about it, particularly with that,
because of the choice that James Gunn made, it is basically all just turned into a new, dare I say,
dare I look you in the eyes, Mike, and say, better rock and roller coaster with maybe, maybe,
and I don't want to start things off on a sour note, but maybe.
I'm just going to throw this out here.
OK, go ahead.
I can't even do it. I'm going to look at Jason and say, yeah, fine.
Yeah, what's up?
Better songs.
Maybe the music.
Maybe none of the Marvel matters.
And it's just that we get a rock and roller coaster with songs that,
if you can imagine, are a little bit better than the music of Aerosmith.
Well, it depends.
The vibes are different.
It's a different vibe.
It's just different.
Let's not say better.
Let's just say different.
OK.
There was, I mean, some of this groundwork.
The reason it's not in Islands of Adventure, it wasn't until the mid to later 2000s
that they kind of revamped Guardians of the Galaxy, that they were brought back to prominence.
And a lot of the characters that ended up in the movie were in, like, the comic,
but they didn't have the fun soundtrack on it.
But there's no songs.
There's no fun songs.
And there is, I feel like, less of an aesthetic.
It's really all I care about.
I can't, I think this time, the second time going on it,
I paid less attention to the story than ever.
I sensed that a lot of people on the line were doing the same thing.
Well, that's another-
After all that, none of it mattered.
All it just, all it boils down to is that this is a very good excuse
and a very good construct for a very good ride to play very good music.
And that's what we're here to focus on and to talk about.
Yeah. Yeah, the people in the pre-show rushed to the door.
Yes, this is a new thing that we've noticed, yeah.
And boy, it felt like festival disaster type energy when people-
Go, go, go, to the right, all the way to the right.
Got into that pre-show and ran to the place they knew would be the exit eventually.
I was like, oh, whoa.
I was like a little taken aback by how aggressive everyone was being in that room.
And they did not want to watch the rest of the pre-show.
They just were like, get us on the ride.
I do this a little bit when getting in the Haunted Mansion elevator.
I feel like I sort of know where the doors are.
You have to acquaint yourself in one of the two elevators to figure out where exactly.
And I messed it up in Florida.
That's something I found.
I didn't know where the door is in there.
I didn't know either.
I'm not acting like I'm an expert.
Okay, okay, a few.
I'm not an expert.
But we did go in the Haunted Mansion and we did see the Hapox Ghost
before the Madame Leona scene.
We don't have time for that.
Are you crazy?
It sucks.
It sucks shit.
Anyway, let's keep going.
It's further flushing out of why it sucks shit.
She doesn't call the ghosts and he's there.
It doesn't make sense.
I hit the microphone so bad.
Anyway, go ahead.
Okay, what we are here to talk about is this is sort of a follow-up
of our recent whirlwind Orlando adventure.
We talked about it on the main feed of this incredible opportunity
to check out Epic Universe early before.
A phenomenal experience.
Really cool to get to do.
But we did pack in a speed round of Disney World the day before.
And what this episode is is focusing on what I think we would both agree
is the singular best thing that occurred on that day.
I don't want to say-
Ride-wise for sure.
Yeah, yes.
I don't want to make it compete against things that happened at Epic Universe.
A lot of great stuff happened at Epic,
but a lot of great stuff happened during the day.
Yes, yeah.
You saw a hero of yours perform music that day.
Oh, that's right, yes.
So there's others.
Many things happened is all I'm saying.
Yes, yeah.
Well, it was a great day for music and Epcot for sure.
But yeah, I mean, all told, I would call this an all-time great Disney World day.
I don't know if you would go so far as to agree.
It was for me.
For a day where I didn't have family there,
where significant others weren't there.
That's good.
I love that.
Yeah.
Day for the boys.
The boys can do it too.
We don't need kissing and smooching in order to make this an awesome day.
Oh, thanks.
No, yeah, boys' day, bachelor's day.
That's right.
I mean, it was just a wonderful, it was a really great time.
And I felt like luck was on our side in general, which I think factors into what was going on here.
And I guess this isn't luck.
Some of this is the generosity of a kind soul.
But I think a little bit of context to say here is that, yes, thanks to somebody's generosity,
we ended up with some fast passes.
Sure did.
Yes, we had a little bit of help, a little bit of a Disney bump,
a performance-enhancing drug that let us kind of do some stuff that we wanted to do.
And in having that at our disposal at Epcot Center,
you had precisely one plan of how you wanted to use these.
So would you like to say what your plan was?
Well, I just said, you know, I want to save fast passes just for Guardians.
And we had special, these were, we had, we could go on multiple times.
It wasn't, sometimes with a fast pass, you can only go on the ride once.
One ride per, yes.
But I was saying like, I want to do, my number one thing I want to do at a Disney World Day
is to get a certain song on Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind.
Yes.
Just because that felt like, well, that's going to be a unique thing.
Because we didn't do any other rides that I have never done before.
This just felt like the singular thing I needed to do.
And it's still new to us.
We only, we went on it once before.
Only once.
And so very excited about the ride, but really excited about the specific goal.
Let's talk about the song.
The song is of the six that are, and if you don't know, or just quick refresher,
I think everybody does, but much like Guardians Mission Breakout here in California,
there is a randomizer and you can get one of six songs that change your experience.
And these are all sort of from the 70s and 80s.
I guess some 60s in there, at least in the West Coast.
But you don't know what song you're getting until things kick in in a big, exciting way.
Here in California, it's when you first get shot up, kind of right before.
Yeah, yeah.
It plugs the Walkman in.
Does it click in at the, okay.
So it's a little bit before you first get shot.
And he gets things rocking and he clicks it and then it starts.
Oh yeah, it's still some like suspense music a little bit.
And similar here, you get the same opening every time in this sequence with Eson.
Yes.
What's the name?
The Celestial.
Yes, Eson.
Yes.
And this moment, I don't know, I can't, I should have listened to the whole First
Guardians episode.
This, I can't overstate how much the moment you're talking about
is like an all-time great theme park moment.
Yeah, yes.
It really is the sort of moment, you remember the moment before when all,
like the big bang happens.
The big bang happens, yeah.
And it's silence and then you shoot back as the,
you figure out what song you're about to hear.
And it really, due to the nature of the big bang, all sound is sucked from the room.
That's what's so cool about it.
It's like exceptionally designed regardless of which song you end up getting.
And it just creates a perfect bed for whatever is going to kick in,
whether it be a raucous dance kind of song,
or in this case, something a little bit more emotional.
Quick reminder, some of the songs,
Konga Gloria Estefan, Trance Disco Inferno,
which is what we got the first time, Disco Inferno,
Flock of Seagulls Ran So Far Away, One Way or Another,
Blondie, September, Earth, Wind and Fire.
But the song that you had the goal,
I think this was said before we even got down to Florida.
Oh, I've been saying on the show for a long time, too.
There you go. Okay, okay.
Yes, I think I forgot this has been a runner on the-
I think I pegged it the first time when we did this episode.
Okay.
Because this is just, I've been, I've known,
I shouldn't say, because I'm tipping what we think about it already,
but I knew that's the one, that's the special one.
Not that I like all the, I really do like most of the songs.
Yes, yeah, yeah, I know.
I'd be happy to get any of them and I've been happy to get Konga before.
I just knew that was a little different.
I mean, I ran is a little different, too, but I haven't done it yet,
but I knew this one.
Yeah, yes, you called it a while back.
The song is Everybody Wants to Rule the World by Tears for Fears.
You had a feeling, you had a special feeling.
I've always been extremely fond of this song.
I love this song.
Yeah, yeah.
Seems like the same for you.
Yeah, it's more and more in my adult years, honestly,
because they used to play, I think they said this,
they used to play this when they would just show you the traffic report
or the weather on the look like the morning news
that I would watch before school every day for years.
And it just like played and it was sort of background music
and I didn't dislike it.
It just sort of, it didn't strike me as like,
oh, this song is really good until I was older.
It was in a boring like car commercial,
like that intro I sort of took for granted.
I think I maybe just thought of it as like same with the,
you know, the who song Eminence Front?
Yes, which is a cool song.
Yes, really cool song.
I maybe, we went down to that thing Desert Trip.
I think maybe I didn't know that that wasn't like a song
from a car commercial until they were playing it at that show.
And it was cool.
We got to see the who.
It was a cool version of it.
It was really cool.
Like I was really impressed with that.
I dug into that as soon as I could after.
I was admittedly ignorant of that song, but similar.
I think I just like, I know this music,
that's from a commercial or something.
Yeah.
Had not let it live with me as like incredible,
emotional, evocative piece of music.
It's so great.
I've been fond of it for a long time,
but I still hadn't really clocked that like,
oh, I would love to have that song be married to this ride.
I think it took you saying it as a goal
for me to start getting on board.
And even when you said I want to use these,
I want to just like try to go on this ride a couple of times
with this goal in mind.
I was like, huh, maybe.
Well, do I really want to go on it?
Am I capable of going on it a bunch?
This is a very dizzying ride, as we have found.
I was a little bit like,
I don't know if I could do this three times in a row,
although should we be so lucky?
It's like, I'd want to figure it out.
That is a great song.
I was just going to say, like my association with it,
round 18 or 19, it is in the Grand Theft Auto Vice City soundtrack.
There's a lot of great songs on that.
Yeah.
I mean, it's multiple.
The set of the full soundtrack at the time was like a number of discs
because each radio station had different songs.
So it was between six and eight discs.
So you've killed men to that song.
Oh, I've killed.
I've driven in, seen the sunset, the digital sunset.
I believe.
All right.
I looked it up and I am right.
Another song I'm really fond of, Call Me by Go West.
That is some evocative mid-80s, mid to late 80s angst.
Really love that song.
I think I didn't know it until...
I Ran So Far is in that.
I Ran So Far is, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
The new one.
It's called I Ran.
It's called I Ran, yeah.
The new trailer for Grand Theft Auto 6 has a Tom Petty song in it.
Love is a Long Road, which has got really great 80s synthesizers at the start of it.
Oh, okay.
So there's those keeping...
You've probably heard it.
Because you're finally back in Vice City.
I think so.
I think that's what it is.
At least it's one of the cities in the game.
Anyway.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
With new technology, you can have multiple cities.
Sure.
Bigger, bigger CPU.
Yeah.
Bigger cities.
They're getting pretty big, yeah.
They're pretty big.
Anyway, so I still like...
Though I love the song, I like your goal, but it was kind of like...
As the day went on, and it was a pleasant day in general,
where we were hopping around parks and having a great time.
Luck on our side, as we said.
Everything was just working out how we wanted it to.
Everything was hitting for us, and this was getting towards the end of the day.
And as you kept mentioning this goal, I started to get so on board with it.
I wanted it for you, and I started to want it for me.
I started to wonder, will I tap into the magic that Mike seems to be thinking he will feel
from this marriage of ride and song.
Look, we can keep building suspense or whatever, but I think we already said...
I puked.
...the deal.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And where it went was...
And the ride of Puked.
You puked so much that the ride had to be stopped midway through,
and everybody had to get off, and we didn't get to hear the whole song.
Yeah.
You puked during the launch, and thus we heard the intro, and that's all.
Right is the thing.
It's straight on.
Nah.
Like a chemtrail of puke.
Look, as we've learned, they've got water bottles and hand towels on standby.
There's benches and garbage cans.
It was also nice to get another shot at the ride.
Obviously, we loved this ride very much.
From the get-go, it absolutely blew us away on a trip where a lot was new to us,
a lot of the last few years' worth of stuff.
And it still managed to live at possibly number one, although I know Velocicoaster's big for you.
Two chickens.
So for me, automatic advance to number one.
But there were some distractions going on when we did it before.
Yes, there was some sickness in our party right away, which happens.
And you understand why.
I think everybody leaves this thing at least a little bit dizzy.
A little dizzy, yeah.
Yes.
There was also the distraction of Mike's hat, the insistence that you keep the hat on despite
there being pretty obvious you should have taken the hat off.
I don't know if there was an insistence that I keep it on.
I think I just had really not even clocked that I needed to take it off.
I don't know why.
I don't think I would just think—
I feel like I take my hat off on the—
I usually do.
The train at Travel Town, the train that goes around in circles in Griffith Park here.
I said it was my fault to the guy who was rude to me as we got off.
I told the employee, like, ah, it's my fault.
I forgot to take the hat off or whatever.
And he's like, ugh, like he got really—
It was enough.
Yeah.
Admittance of fault isn't—
Yeah, he was just rude to me.
Still a pain in his butt.
Whatever.
He didn't have to go look for—
I don't think he went to go look for it.
But they have to look every day.
We don't know, by the way—
Oh, no.
Okay, we do know—
You lost it on the very first moment, correct?
On the launch, yeah, yeah.
So that's a distraction right away.
Your first time going.
I was going to say it'd really be—
Maybe he was mad because the hat got blown on top of the globe at the end of the ride
and was just sitting perfectly—
I mean, that would be nice.
Which might be kind of cute.
It would be cute.
Great Easter egg.
Little Mickey hat on top of the globe.
I think it was on purpose.
Yeah.
But all of these a little bit of distractions the first time going.
Now, what was exciting the first time is that we got Conga, which was my goal.
For some reason, I was really feeling Conga.
Is it my favorite song in the list?
Not necessarily.
I just—something about—I don't know.
I just wanted that party.
That just seemed like a fun time, and it was.
Yeah, yeah.
I've never sensed that this is anybody's favorite song in the lineup of six.
Right.
But I—you don't always want the greatest necessarily.
You just—what I was in the mood for that day, it delivered for me.
But it did leave us—it was good because it left us wanting.
It left us—like, we feel like there's songs that could take this great ride
and really kick it into overdrive.
This was an incredible experience.
I can't begin to say how much—I don't even want—like we were saying about
the Lara Smith argument.
I don't even want to say better.
I just want to say different.
I want to say it was a different experience on levels that I was very surprised by
because it took what in Conga mode was just a big, raucous party of a ride,
and it turned it into just a highly emotionally charged experience.
Yeah.
It just—it was so moving to me.
It was less of a roller coaster and more of like a very active sound bath.
This was like deeply therapeutic.
It was a way to feel a song that you love on a whole other level that I—it was so
shocking to me.
So when it happened, I was excited that you got your goal.
Because we got a first try.
First try, we did it.
Okay, yes.
The big bang happens, it's quiet, and then when you're—that little part of it that
starts that song.
And I was like, whoa!
Because that's a, you know, what?
One in twenty—no, twenty.
That's not twenty.
One in six.
One in six, yeah.
But even—but there's other things.
There's other factors at work here.
I got curious about like, is there a way to game it and to try to time out what song you get?
And I mean, the short answer is no.
Technically, it is a loop.
I think they all do play in an order.
Like if each car is like, all right, now it's Iran and now it's Kong or whatever the order is.
But they also arrive at different loading platforms.
They, you know, you can't control delays or this one has to go through without people on it.
Like there's a ton of, you know, vehicles get pulled and put back on throughout the day.
So even if you went to a team member and said, hey, is there a way I could arrange Tears for Fears?
I don't think there is a way that they could do that.
Yeah.
So it makes it even more of a feat, more of a miracle.
It might be more than one in six, due to that reason.
Sound systems are also not perfect.
So I am sure there are people who have ridden and the sound is cut out.
That would be a startling ride for silence and just hear silence on screens.
Uh-huh.
That'll happen sometimes.
Yeah.
In Florida.
They just meet, oh, in Florida.
Oh, in Florida it just never has.
Yes, indeed.
Yeah.
You just get to hear that clunk.
The Christmas.
Oh, they do.
Yeah, that's awesome.
If it's not on board, they just run it through the whole room.
Yeah, I think that's what it is.
You can't have it only be on board on the car just for that.
But yeah, that's a part of building suspense, I guess I forgot,
is that it was a very lucky day for us.
And then finally.
And the ride broke down.
Yes, well, that's what we were starting to say.
Maybe our luck has run out because we were so close.
We were through, we were past the pre-show.
We were past the room where everybody just runs to the side now
to try to board the coaster quicker.
We had made it through there and we were in this kind of airlock tube kind of zone.
You're not on the loading platform yet.
You're up on the level above, but you can see cars coming in and out.
And we saw cars load and then we saw them not leave.
We saw them stuck there for a while.
And then the group disembarked entirely.
And there was a big, oh, that spread all the way back from the people closest to it
to us pretty far away.
And a grumble began and it started to feel like,
is this the time where we don't get on this thing?
I guess that's the end of the luck.
But we were patient.
We waited it out.
We believed in your goal enough.
And sure enough, it was only like a 10 minute think.
Yeah, it was not bad at all.
Yes, because we were going to bail.
We'd come back maybe at that point.
But yeah, we were going to bail and it happened.
But you think about it now, if we had bailed
or if it hadn't happened in that exact or if that car had not gone out then,
if they hadn't run empty cars through at that exact moment,
it was all conspiring to give us the song that we were after.
You know, it's fun to think about stuff like that,
but then you could also drive yourself insane.
You know, like if I didn't do this at this moment,
what would have happened to my life?
Oh, my God.
I think some things you think are regretful,
some things you're ecstatic that they happened in this way, you know?
And suddenly the guardians ride becomes a sliding doors ride.
That's right.
Exactly.
Maybe we're dead.
Who's sitting on that?
Ketchup Entertainment?
Can you use sliding doors ride?
Yeah, absolutely.
But it all worked out.
And I guess that's a couple of pieces to break off here.
With you having had this desire for months, for day, for that whole day,
when it happened, when the sound perfectly clears
and those magical ethereal opening notes begin,
because the song starts out on such a high note
and it has to, any song for this ride,
you really got to think about how difficult it must have been for them to narrow it down
and to get it to these six.
And they're all successful in this regard that it has to,
you have to know what it is from note one.
Oh, yeah.
There's a lot of great songs, a lot of classic songs anybody loves
where you don't necessarily know it from note one.
Right.
That is sort of the goal of any of these.
It has to be.
And it has to have a lot of sections and movements, which this obviously has.
And it kind of has to get to the point, too.
It can't be a song that just meanders and is cool for 45 seconds
and then the awesome part kicks in.
Yeah, you can't have that ramp up.
Yeah, yeah.
It's got to just go.
You can't have the long version of Prince's Erotic City.
You've got to have the three minute version, not the seven or eight minute version.
Although I'd say that's cooking from the gig.
It's funny.
I've been on a big Prince, not that I'm ever not on a Prince kick,
but especially, I was listening to the long one today.
Oh, I love the long one.
The long one's my choice.
Your cherry baby, that's, oh my God.
Yeah.
Yeah, the long one is more like the lead up to Billy Jean or something,
longer than Billy Jean, but all the parts get to come in
in their own little section or their own little showcase.
If you see it's the 12 inch mix or the extended whatever,
and you're getting this.
If you see seven minutes as the runtime on a Prince trick,
you're in good hands.
My dad once said, I don't like his songs.
They're too long.
I was like, how did you have me?
How are we related?
I could not feel more different on this point.
Yeah, I want 10 minutes.
I want north of it as long as they can go.
But anyway, so that just makes it, it's exciting musically from the get go,
but also just to hear those notes and go, oh my God, it's happening.
It happened.
I felt I felt such like brotherhood, kinship, pride.
I like I reached over and patted you on the back.
Oh, yeah, I remember now.
I was like, I have I feel the urge to give just like a loving arm around.
Like you did it.
Yeah, we did it.
Something that I feel like I have not felt a thing like that with you
since you said we're having a baby.
We're not huggers here, particularly.
I wouldn't say much.
I don't mind it, but I'm not the one who ever initiated.
No, no, not really.
And in that moment, I was like, I got to give you a hug.
I can't not give you a hug.
Is that can I give you a hug?
And it felt like a sequel to that.
That's equally like I have not had the I must try.
I must touch Mike in this moment.
I didn't mind.
That's nice.
It felt it felt nice.
You know, we do these things day in, day out.
And it felt nice to have this magical moment.
Right on a ride on a specific ride.
Sorry you weren't there, Jason.
This is where I have to know.
Here we are.
Here I am going on.
And the brother, the kinship that we felt.
Two minds became one.
I'll take solace in that I was busy getting married.
Two became one on the ride and then two became one marriage.
Wow, yes.
Everlasting unions.
Yeah, the Spice Girls song was too big.
That's probably a sex song, right?
That two becomes one only for a 12 year old.
It's a sex.
The tamest sex.
Yeah, that might be like I never needed love before.
That's the song.
That's I'm going to make.
Yeah, they say I'm going to make love to you, baby.
That's the song.
As I said, it's a team song.
I'm not saying it's the dirtiest song.
It's a nice song.
More often, it probably got used for like two 13 year old
slop, like pecking on the school cafeteria dance floor.
Yeah, I'm sure they pecked.
Sloppy peck.
It's a 13 year old peck.
Sloppy peck because they're nasty.
13 year olds.
They are.
They are not looking forward to having them in my house.
Yeah.
Well, this is great.
You got on the first try and then I bet you ran through
the other fast passes on living with the land.
Because what's more exciting than hydroponics?
And seeing a sign that says okra.
Seeing a guy with a lap car put his clipboard in a desk drawer
and then go up 530.
Time to get home.
And seeing a bunch of dust between two tanks.
We got to do the seeds tour next time we're there.
I think we should.
Behind the seeds tour.
You're trying to bring me down from this high.
No, I know you're high.
As quickly as you're trying to yank me back down.
It's funny you're saying all this too because I remember
thinking, oh no, Scott's more excited than I am.
Like I almost felt like I was betraying the moment
because you felt more excited.
Like you were more, you were exhibiting it more than I was.
Not that I wasn't excited.
I was very excited.
But then I was like, oh, I know, I almost like I want to enjoy
but I almost like I felt insecure.
I want to match, trying to match as well.
So I'm glad you felt that.
I appreciate you saying that.
I didn't feel any lack of it from you.
Okay, good, good.
Maybe sometimes, maybe your passion can become
kind of a transitive quality sometimes because
I think I definitely ended up more enthusiastic
about Avatar than you.
For many years, you were the Avatar Torchbearer.
That's true, yes.
A very viable title for a future film, The Torchbearer.
Can I?
Avatar 7, The Torchbearer.
Now would you admit now, and again,
now that all this good will's here,
maybe I shouldn't put you on the spot like this,
but Jason Sheridan called me something a couple weeks ago
in here that you didn't see.
Oh, I was just thinking about it, yeah.
He called me a tastemaker.
Oh, okay, I was like, oh, I hope I called it something nice.
He called me a dirty son of a bitch.
He called him a bleep.
No, that's the, I don't, people should not use that term
and need to stay engaged.
Jason did look scared like he said something mean about me
and I was like, oh.
I was like, what would I have said a few weeks ago?
He said something so kind.
I did.
He said he's called Mike the tastemaker.
Mike and his tastemaker role.
I will, okay, can I tell a funny story about this
that I think is, I think I know what happened
and I think I confused a couple people.
So Jason called me tastemaker a couple weeks ago.
Anyway.
So this was in Bar Rescue with Griffin.
Griffin Newman, yes.
But, so very quickly after that, I went
and I talk about this sometimes.
I go to the smokehouse to see Jimmy Angel,
89 year old rock and roll singer.
And I'm standing in the back with my parents
who are there with me.
This guy, the ultimate tastemaker.
He gets his parents in.
With my parents.
Oh, he's got his elbows on its table
eating a New York strip with his hands.
My dad likes Jimmy Angel maybe more than I do even.
Loves Jimmy Angel.
Generationally, that makes sense.
Probably correct that he should.
Like my dad is still like 30 years.
He's still not the generation of Jimmy Angel.
Yeah, Jimmy's 89.
So two people stand up from their table.
They're leaving the done eating.
They walk over to me and the gentleman says to me,
we're here because of you.
Wow, wow.
And I get so excited, obviously.
I go, oh, really?
Wow, that's great.
And here's the mistake I think I made.
And I think I confused the shit out of these two people.
I had mentioned Jimmy Angel on Doughboys recently.
That was the most recent.
And I believe they're Doughboys listeners,
not podcasts, they're ride listeners.
So what I said to two people who I was thinking
podcasts or other centers, I said,
I am a taste maker like Jason said.
They looked at me like they had no clue what I was saying.
They smiled and were polite and nodded.
And they said, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, great.
We just met another Hollywood weirdo.
And they go, oh, yeah, so then whatever.
We said something and they left.
They think Jason is your mean stepdad.
It's possible, yes.
Let's see, I'll show that Jason.
I was just like talking.
People do like me.
I am going to make stuff out of myself.
I will kiss a girl.
Yeah.
So then they left and I took a second and I went,
I think I know these are Doughboys fans
that recognized me, not podcasts, the ride listeners.
So I think I confused the hell out of them.
But I did.
So that's a little bit of me looking like a fool.
But also I am a taste maker in this situation as well.
They came, they said they loved it.
They had such a good time.
This, can I tell a story?
Can I tell an embarrassing story of this nature?
Sure, yeah.
Because of just not understanding the moment,
assumed some podcast listenership that was not there.
So I went to a children's birthday party and-
I like how this is starting.
And I walked in and I was on the earlier end
and there were only a couple of people there.
And I was introduced to somebody who said,
oh, you just went to Bass Pro Shops.
Or asked a question, did you just go to Bass Pro Shops?
And I was like, how do you know that?
And I said, oh, do you listen to the podcast?
And she's like, what?
And I was like, oh, and then I looked down at my son
and he was wearing a Bass Pro Shops hat.
Then I remembered myself and the top of my own head,
which was also clad in a Bass Pro Shops hat.
This was being said because two people,
had man and child, had both walked in saying,
both walked in wearing Bass Pro Shops hats.
This was made slightly more embarrassing by the fact
that this was the first time that I was meeting somebody
who I am a fan and admirer of,
the great actress, Kristen Schaal.
Really?
I'm a little thrown because I didn't think
she would be at this thing.
I like her very much.
I'm a big fan of hers.
I immediately put my foot in my mouth and say,
the only way you could be saying this is that somehow,
you know, you'd have to be a second gate subscriber
to know that.
Right, right, right.
But I truly, it was not, but other people there thought,
were like, you think she listens to the podcast?
I was like, no, that's not what I think.
That's not what I think.
I forgot that I was wearing the hats.
That's why it was not an ego thing.
It is fine.
I am perfectly calm and collected here.
This is fine.
You got to do the finger thing for that.
If she didn't do the finger, like point down pointing,
you got to do like, oh, you guys just went to Bass Pro.
So you're blaming her for not.
I'm saying if she didn't, you know,
I could see that you could get confused
and you were meeting someone you admired.
And isn't that the worst thing?
That's what you don't want to happen.
That would sit with me for a while.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I knew I could not keep that in my brain.
Now you, the listener, knows this as well.
That, the story I just sat with me for like a week or two
of like, oh God.
And then I forgot even there's another extra part
is the woman, I guess I'm assuming probably a wife,
asks the guy, she goes, oh, you want to photo with him?
And he goes, no, I'm all right.
Nice.
Which is always the funniest, which I like, you know,
you don't have to take a picture.
But they knew who you were.
They did know what you looked like.
Oh, it was a video.
And in just a week or two, I was on a double
and there's a nice chunk about Jimmy Angel on the episode.
So I maybe, look, if they're listening now
and I'm incorrect, let me know.
But I'm 99% positive that they were Doughboy's people
that did not know that Jason Sheridan
called me a tastemaker weeks prior.
And I said it enthusiastically as if,
I am a tastemaker.
These must be listeners.
Something they don't know.
Like Jason said, something deeper they don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, incredible.
Well, when I do other shows, I say,
I host a show, Scott and Mike, you know,
I always say everyone's names, you know,
just in case someone was hearing me for the first time.
So I don't know.
I don't know if that would have even rectified.
No, I didn't know what was, I didn't,
I don't think I figured out what was going on
until they were gone is what I'm saying.
I didn't put two and two together just because I was like,
oh, I bet, I bet they're Doughboy's people.
Cause I forgot I had just, that Doughboy's episode
had just come out with a chunk about Jimmy.
You were out of your steak case.
You were grumbling, eating your cream spinach
cause you're like, I don't like it,
but I know it's good for me.
I like cream spinach.
I didn't understand that last part.
Are you saying the smokehouse menu
with the cream spinach are you talking about?
Well, I was just assuming that's a common steakhouse side.
So I was like-
It is what we're talking about.
Maybe you know if you went to a place that served,
I don't know, a combo of items
I know what you feel about steak houses.
So I've been trying to get you out to Jimmy for a while.
And you've been saying it's one reason,
but maybe now it's because it's a steakhouse.
Is that why?
Do you have a problem with steak houses?
No, I don't have a problem with steak houses.
I don't eat steak that often.
Sure.
Yeah.
So if a place has steak, that's fine.
And if a place has bourbon, that's fine.
Yeah.
But combined.
I just thought it was a little like a kind of bland,
So you can have the things.
Bland but aggressive advertising.
But if the smokehouse changed its name
to The Steak and Bourbon House overnight,
they would become a bad organization?
Well, it's a historic landmark.
They shouldn't change it.
Well, we can agree on that.
Yeah.
No, they should not fuck with the formula.
Hypothetically.
OK, let's talk about this a lot.
So the victory of kicking in was tremendous.
It was nice to have this moment of brotherhood.
Beyond that, it's just such a great sequence of ride
combined with music.
Obviously, you've got to do a cut down.
You've got to chop it up a little bit.
And I think they did it in a masterful way
where it doesn't feel like a radio edit
or you're missing anything too important.
Obviously, that's a pretty long song.
And it's got two, I think, remarkable solos.
And you don't have time for all of those
in a ride version.
Yeah.
But the cut down really does get you
a lot of the diversity of the song.
You know, it gets you verses and choruses
and bridge and solo.
Maybe you don't get, there's probably no bridge.
You don't get the, there's a room where the.
There's a room with hands right there.
I don't think so.
Maybe towards the end, maybe you.
It's also hard to watch on YouTube.
This is another part of me hyping it up.
It's hard to tell on YouTube
because it's just so hard to capture the audio
in a clear way when you're watching a YouTube
ride through of.
This is some of what has haunted me
about this attraction is that there are some.
There's some attractions, you know,
like I found myself watching Rise of the Resistance
a lot during pandemic, knowing that we were
really far away from being able to go on that thing again.
Yeah.
And there's videos that capture it pretty decently
and that at least give you like, wow,
when those cannons go back and forth,
that is so stark and scary,
even if I'm not there in the room.
This is impossible to watch a video of.
Yeah, you really don't know,
but you have to be like an expert photographer,
I think, to get the like the balance right,
to get the exposure right.
That room with the celestial where you do the big turn
and where everybody flips and the whole ride vehicle
becomes inverted and you're in the front.
Now you're in the back and vice versa.
That room looks like shit in any video that you watch.
Yeah.
You might watch it and think,
hey, Disney really cheaped out.
Yeah.
And in person, it's unbelievable.
It's just impossible that, you know,
like Space Mountain is never really going to translate,
although I think it's worse.
I think Space Mountain,
it is maybe understand better in a video than Guardians.
It really doesn't come through.
Yeah, yeah.
The mix of, yeah, the mix of the lighting
and just how fast in different directions is just,
it's impossible.
I wonder if they even have a good ride through themselves
because like they put out Tiana's like,
they'll now put out videos to get ahead of people
doing it during.
Oh, yeah, which I love.
It's nice to like see a really polished,
like a well shot ride.
Yeah, I think it's also to prevent like universal.
A lot of it, you have to empty your pockets
and leave your bags in a locker.
Yeah, yeah.
So I think like them strapping in a camera is safer.
Well, that's true.
And more reliable.
Don't film it where we have one.
And you can make the ad revenue from that too.
There's a lot of people who probably make like really
like a load up ad revenue wise just by like filming a ride.
And becoming the main way to watch the ride.
Yeah, there's a great Velocicoaster on ride
from universal that I watch a lot.
That one's really good.
It's really good and really gives you a feeling of it.
It might be the only way I experienced it.
I don't know.
We'll see.
I watched some epic leaks.
So I couldn't help it.
Well, no, I also, it's like the first opening summer of a party.
You never know what you're actually
going to be able to get done and get on.
There's no way I'm doing it for the big ones we missed
for Ministry of Magic.
And what's that?
Is that right?
Actually, is it called Fight for the Ministry?
Is that the name of that?
Battle of the Battle.
Yeah, OK, I'm going to do it.
Well, Jane sent me a leak monster ride.
And I said, no spoilers.
Oh, yeah, me too.
I did not click on it.
Well, and then later that day, that's only like can't fit.
Later that day, the full one.
Did you watch all of it?
Yeah.
Don't say a word.
Don't you dare say a word.
But there's a lot of darkness.
Sure.
Because it's scary monsters.
So you're not able to communicate similarly.
Well, I guess it's a spoiler in that now I
know that the monsters aren't all in a meadow by a rainbow.
That's true.
I know that it's not about the monsters going to a park.
You were hoping there was like a Pride and Prejudice,
like kind of like a guy crossing a long field.
Oh, yeah, maybe just a little shoot.
Like Frankenstein's Zeo-ly lumbering.
Sound of music, but it's with the Wolfman instead.
Yeah.
All right, well, spoiler, the ride has darkness in it.
It's dark.
Got it.
I did see the first glow.
I saw somebody playing it.
OK, I haven't done it.
I haven't done it.
I don't want it.
We're going back.
We're doing it.
We're done.
Yeah.
But OK, where does this take us?
I mean, everything's like remarkably paired.
It works so well.
Then immediately, the emotion of it is clear.
I start having something come over me, which I was surprised
by is that it starts to feel like a concert to me.
And I have the urge to sing along with it.
I can't say that I've done that on any of these
or on any other ride that plays a song.
A roller coaster, your inclination
is not to sing along.
But it was hitting so hard, I could not help but do it.
And it felt great.
I'm trying to think of I like to sing Monsters After Dark
on the monster.
Sure.
Overlay.
Yeah.
Monsters After Dark.
I like that.
Yeah, I don't know.
Other than that, I guess on Rock and Roller Coaster,
I don't usually sing along.
Although when we go for the last time, I will.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, right.
And how many Aerosmith songs are on Rock and Roller Coaster?
I should know this.
I'm not the person.
There are only two.
It mostly clips, isn't it?
There's like, yeah, they just change.
Quick hits.
Yeah, but is it the same loop every time?
I don't really.
I feel like it's not.
I don't know.
I'm going to try to get all of it next time.
OK, walk this way.
Dude looks like a lady.
Sweet emotion.
And back in the saddle.
And then love in a roller coaster.
And that's at the end.
Yeah, that's always at the end.
Is that all of them?
Yeah, something called Young Lust.
F-I-N-E spelled out.
Those are in the ride?
Yeah, Young Lust goes right into Fine.
I don't care for this.
I don't care for this one.
But I'm glad they're getting this.
The song Pink plays outside the ride.
It's insane.
It is insane.
As long as I keep that and a Muppet sings it, it'll be fine.
Sure.
One of the Muppets sings the song Pink.
A number of them are pink.
The Muppets are pink.
Mike, you don't ever walk down Main Street USA and find yourself singing Bicycle Bill for Two?
Not all of us have the old cheap music.
If Bicycle Bill for Two starts and I'm walking and you're there with me,
I'll pat you on the back like Scott did to me and I'll get so excited for you and then
we'll sing it together.
Is that your favorite of the Main Street songs?
Bicycle Bill for Two?
Is there a song from Hello Dolly?
Long Way to Tipperary.
Well, I like Long Way to Tipperary.
Sure.
There's the song for, yeah, build your ultimate.
What's your ultimate pairing of Main Street and Old Tiny Song?
I do like the song from Hello Dolly.
I don't know the name, but it's the same.
It's the same that's in WALL-E.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I forget the name of it too.
The 60s Hello Dolly.
There's Married Life from Up.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's a nice little thing that fits.
That's one of those where like, I wonder if I heard that song on Main Street like
seven times before I went, oh, this is from Up.
Put on your Sunday clothes.
Your Sunday clothes is from Hello Dolly and they play the instrumental.
Okay, okay.
We got to get you, you got to put a Main Street playlist together too, I think.
DJ, oh, Jason's DJing again at a club in Orlando.
You know it's all going to be this old timey bullshit.
Long way to Tipperary.
Oh, he put on the Caldo Adventure again.
Has Pitbull ever sampled Long Way to Tipperary?
He really should if he hasn't.
I don't know.
Run out of samples.
Wells Fargo Wagon is a song they play, it seems like.
That's Music Man.
Daisy, is that like Daisy, Give Me Your Answer Do?
Daisy, Daisy, yeah, yeah.
Okay, all right.
Well, stuff to explore there.
More about the music loops, area loops coming up in the future, I think.
But so, really hidden.
It was like a concert, you said.
Yes, really hidden at the chorus.
And then, and around that time, I had a revelation.
This is like, this is like a, this feels like being in the song.
And not just like Congo was probably that too, but I just don't care about Congo.
If you look at the list, if you look at the list of like these six in Mission Breakout
and these six in Cosmic Rewind, I would say everybody wants to rule the world is the only
one that is like emotional.
Maybe some of these songs are, but they're all more like upbeat rockers, right?
Which this is too, which is what makes it perfect.
It's like, it's like highly energetic.
But I think it's the only one of the list, anyone correct me if I'm wrong,
that you might feel like a lot of emotion.
It's like the saddest, it's not really a sad song, but it's like a bittersweet song.
It's a heavy song while also being upbeat.
Iran is a little moodier too.
I guess so.
But not as, yeah.
But everything else is pretty much a party song, I would say to some degree.
Yes, and this could be too.
That's what I think is what makes it a perfect choice.
The fact that it has the emotional weight and that it's a song I've listened to and
really felt a lot before, I was just like, oh my God, you know what's happening?
This is what Sphere must be like for people.
The highest caliber of technology is allowing me to experience this music that I care about
in this ultimate sensory way.
And I still have not been to Sphere.
I still haven't found the right candidate of a Sphere show that I think is going to make me
really feel it and live it.
Wizard of Oz coming soon.
Maybe this remix, they're doing a cut down of Wizard of Oz that is
formatted specifically for Sphere.
And then another movie that they announced, Backstreet Boys are coming.
Eagles are staying always.
And The Dead seems like they're staying too.
I think they're just there forever.
The Dead is just going to be hanging around for a while.
I mean, clearly this thing is having a Drew Carey effect on everybody for sure.
And now I'm just like, oh, I see what, I just don't have the connection to those
U2 songs that you have, but it must be, it's got to be a similar thing, right?
Just like, I can't believe technology and the might of man that allows me,
this song has been around and I've been able to listen to it for 40 years,
but never like this.
I've never been able to experience it like this.
You've never gone inside the song, which is what it felt like and what Sphere feels like.
That's like, that's what I want.
And maybe this ties into just my love of Jelly Rolls and cover, like cover bands.
Go on.
Is that I think that like, I am, I am on a constant search to immerse myself in a song.
I'm not saying this even is in a jokey way.
I do think I'm always like, I want to just feel one with the song.
And I described this when I went to LCD sound system last year,
and I hadn't been to a concert in forever, that I was alone.
I had a half of a drink in me.
Dad is in the back.
It's got half a beer.
I wasn't dancing.
I was just kind of moving and I was just like, I'm like, I'm in it.
I'm in it.
I want to be in it.
And I'm always, it doesn't matter.
I mean, it does matter.
Obviously that's a stronger experience.
This is a stronger experience.
Sphere is a stronger experience.
Than Jelly Rolls, you're saying?
Than Jelly Rolls.
But I do think it's like-
Than hearing two guys on pianos cover, Lose Yourself.
Yeah, that was my favorite.
Ironically, it didn't make you lose yourself.
It didn't make you lose yourself.
Although I saw another person at Disney Springs covering Lose Yourself.
So I don't know what's in the air with Lose Yourself lately.
It's been like over 20 years.
One week.
Oh, I was going to say it's been over 20 years since it came out.
So it's like an anniversary maybe.
It's an oldie.
Yeah, it's a classic now.
But I believe if I recall my Oscars history, it was not performed that year
because he didn't want to perform it.
It was like that's a weird song to try to cover.
That would have been calamitous for someone else to do Lose Yourself.
But Orlando performers are willing to do it anytime.
Look, that is literally another episode of what works and what doesn't in a piano bar.
But all that to say is just I'm searching for different ways to have these experiences.
And this one did it in a new way.
This ride mixed with a song.
And it is because it's a different energy than just a party song,
which it's fun to be on the roller coaster with a party song.
But just the smooth, especially the smooth movements of this new technology
with this type of vibe.
Yeah.
And it really did live up to what I thought, where it was like you can feel like
you can feel floaty.
You can feel like you're drifting on the same movements felt different.
They felt more peaceful to me.
Right.
I felt such calm.
It felt so meditative, even though it's the same thing that where the last time
it was like I felt a little nauseous and I was yelling so much.
I blew my voice out.
This was just pure tranquility.
I couldn't believe this music choice made it such a different experience.
It's like Joker and Dark Knight head out the window kind of a vibe
of just like that's what you're looking like.
He's so he's so peaceful.
Joker so peaceful in that moment.
You can finally have the peace that Joker feels.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
Finally, no one had considered sticking their head out of car window before that moment.
He just looks so nice.
He's not a thing that dogs do every day.
Dogs love it, too.
They do love it.
But yeah, it is it was like if somebody somebody could have lied to me and said,
oh, you know, if you really like the the ride itself is mimicking
like a piece of like the music chart of the notes.
And like, yes, we analyze.
Yes, we created a path based on the way the notes
move through the lied to me and said that that was actually
if you took a look at actually the map of the ride itself,
it's actually bouncing up and down the scale.
It's it fit.
Yeah, close.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, you could completely tell me that.
The other thing that I think makes it fit so well is thematically like just like yes,
the lyrics, which I won't pretend to know exactly what are going on.
I think you could like apply them to anything, but I think they've they've spoke.
Spoken of it being, you know, like a Cold War era influence, a Reagan influenced song.
And I think you could apply it to, you know, to world events and scary stuff to this day,
to current times.
Yes.
But you could also apply it to Eason.
The scary alien bad guy, Celestial.
But he's not he's not a Celestial, which is who lives it.
Those are the inhabitants.
Those are not Celestial.
They live in Celestial Park.
Celestials don't live at Celestial Park.
They live at Guardians Cosmic Rewind.
Yes.
But in a similar way, it's like, yeah, it's if you take it very literally thematically,
it's a big scary alien bad guy.
He wants to rule the world.
And similarly, Grand Theft Auto Vice City, it is an open world game.
And you are trying to break up breaking money and take over stuff and rule the town.
So it sees it sees it back for for your ends.
Yeah.
I think I mean, beyond just the stupid nature of it's everybody wants to rule the world.
Then there's a big world at the end.
Yeah, that's just also it is like I like what I like the air that it casts onto the story
of the ride, which is sort of like ignorable a little bit.
You just know something's happening.
You know, he's never you know, Eason's never winning.
Yeah.
You know, the Guardians have got this covered.
But that was part of it.
I think I said right after like it's like it just it put me at such ease that I was like,
I'm not even worried about it.
They got it.
The Guardians Star Lord has this.
He has it under control.
And Eason thinks he can rule the world, but he can't.
Yeah, like the song is telling me that what he's trying to do is futile
and just don't even be concerned about it.
Let it happen in the background.
And you enjoy this moment.
Enjoy this ride.
Enjoy the song.
Well, if you want to extrapolate it out into like a lesson of living your life.
Yes, I do.
That's exactly what I want to do, which I think is what you're getting at.
It is really, you know, to take a moment and ignore everything that's whatever you
in a moment when you can afford to ignore what's going on in the world and in your life
and take a moment to feel peace and to feel that everything's going to be OK.
That is kind of what no joke the ride feels like.
Like that's exactly what happened.
That's what this and not a lot of rides.
Nothing to do with.
Don't do that rocket raccoon, unfortunately, as much as I love rock.
And I'm just glad YMCA is not on the ride because I'd be flashing right to the world's problems.
Well, that's true.
That would have been a direct reminder with one of our leaders favorite songs.
Yeah.
But no, this was like, you know, it doesn't it feel like almost a little subversive in that way?
It does.
Yeah.
And yeah, to some degree, having a party song while there's a big fight going on,
it's similar to the opening of Guardians 2.
I believe you would like the opening scene to Guardians of the Galaxy 2.
OK.
It's little baby Groot dancing to Mr. Blue Sky
while there's a big fight going on in the background.
And he little baby Groot doesn't care.
Mr. Blue Sky would be good in this mix.
Yes, I wish they had put that in either of the rides.
Yeah.
Not sure why.
You have to wonder with this full list.
And this is where, you know, let me ask if anybody out there has inside intel
or you know about the process or you could and we won't talk about it on the show,
but if anybody just wanted to do us a solid and pass us like the I have the list,
I have the hundred songs that they narrowed it down.
Oh, I would love to hear.
You know what?
They did want Mr. Blue Sky, but Jeff Lynn said no or whatever it is.
I think it's in the is it in the it's not in the queue
because are excuse me in the exit queue.
Surrenders in the exit.
Surrenders in the exit because none of the songs from the movies directly are on the rides.
None of the they all they are.
These are all the first association of guardians with these songs.
I believe so, unless there's maybe one on Mission Breakout, but they're mostly not.
Well, that's what I think we've talked about before.
That still is a big draw for theme parks to me.
And that's when I was younger, certainly even more.
So do go to these places.
You get an experience that you can't get on VHS or you can't.
So you're saying the new song is the new.
Yeah, it's unique to this and a video of it is never going to.
Even if like even if you synced up like perfect sound of the song
with a ride through the song, it's not going to be the same.
It's not going to do the same things.
The big songs.
I mean, I'm off the top of my head from Guardians of the Galaxy.
Hooked on a feeling from the second movie is Brandy.
That plays a lot of my favorite songs.
Brandy, Brandy, really?
Because you have because of the line about your love is the sea.
So he likes the song Brandy, but he probably wouldn't like a song called bourbon.
That's true.
Well, if the sea was made of bourbon, it depends.
But better to drink on this.
Too sweet.
A little sugar boy saying it's too sweet.
Well, got to save those sugar grams for candy.
For candy and cake.
For candy and cake, yes.
Turkish delight.
So yeah, those are not on the ride.
So I think they just decided.
I don't know.
It's great that it's its own thing.
It's not just like it's got to be these songs because people know these from.
Yeah, it makes like fully original experiences.
I'm trying to think of any moments also that just hit hard within the ride sequence.
I mean, not that I don't know.
Like I said, I thought the cut down was great.
However, it lands where when they tell you you did a good job,
that last tunnel that I think kind of blows Space Mountain out of the water.
It's a great ride regardless, but it was really hidden with this soundtrack.
You know, I also had the thought, I don't know if it was on the rider later,
is that this must be what going on Knights in White Satin was like.
Yeah, talking about a ride with a song that is a moodier song.
This is, of course, the ride from the Hard Rock Park.
Yes, there only existed a short amount of time, but people really dark ride.
Yes, the band, the Moody Blues.
People talk about the ride.
No joke in fun terms.
It's hard to tell when you look at like there was a YouTube video.
I think we've tried to find years ago.
Sally Dark Ride put up an official YouTube ride, but it's still hard to tell, right?
Like what the experience was like.
Yes, it's hard to tell, but you can get the basic gist of it.
And that is what I have watched.
I feel like that was what I watched during the pandemic.
Does it read at all?
I feel like I looked at it and I was like, I kind of know,
but the way people talk about it, it feels impossible.
But I also, I mean, this is an app comparison and probably they were
trying to get some of the emotion that this thing gets out of you.
But like also, didn't it just kind of like putt around?
That's not the same ride system.
Certainly to move, make you literally feel like you're floating like this.
Yeah, I agree.
I don't, I don't think it's the same experience.
I'm just, I was just trying to think of a parallel of something
that was a moodier song.
That Meow Wolf one you did in Colorado.
Yes.
I think similarly like, I mean, that was all different
sculpturists and artists and stuff doing it.
So certainly different from Knights in White Sand, but both kind of
not really doing a straightforward A to B story.
Sure.
Yeah.
And that left me thinking maybe A to B story is fine.
Sometimes it's okay.
I got no, sometimes got no problem with that.
Seems like a lot of that day, your luck was, luck was not on your side.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess it's, I guess it makes sense.
I can't over-intellectualize that a day at Epcot Center
is going to be better than a day at Elitch Gardens.
Maybe it's not all luck, but still you can have
even in theme parks we love, you can have very unlucky days.
Right.
Just like I made that wrong decision and I got out of this line
and I would have gotten through it if I hadn't bailed right then.
But this was just the manifestation I think of the fates being on our side.
Yeah.
It felt heavenly after.
I think we both were just like in this bliss state.
It was wonderful.
Yes.
I was thinking too like most things, most rides are,
we've talked about this before, chills and thrills.
Oh yeah.
You get a little scared on the lift hill.
You get a thrill when you go down.
Oh yeah.
So what was this?
But I'm trying and I don't have a good, we will have to pitch on this is what is this?
This is a different thing.
And this is what I've been talking about for a while.
More feeling emotional, more feeling sadness, melancholy.
It is what human beings need sometimes.
As I said, I said this recently, you need it to be extracted from you sometimes.
Yeah.
That's at least I do.
My emotions extracted from me.
It's what music really helps with for sure.
And it's what music does for me and what other things can do for me.
Mostly music though.
And it is a different, it's chills, thrills and something else.
And I do think-
Well it makes you feel like you're on pills.
Good pills, yes.
But I think this needs to be out there more.
I think this idea needs to be in the ether more.
Can you cheat and say fills, but you mean feels.
You could.
We could.
Is there a way to say that?
Can it sound like cool and slang?
If I-
Thrills, chills, and fills.
Feels.
I mean we can make it mean whenever we want.
We are taste makers as well.
Yeah, that's right.
Well you know, this mission was inspiring.
And now maybe I feel inspired to go on the mission of embracing being a taste maker.
You're a taste maker.
Embracing you being a taste maker.
We all have our own things.
We've directed.
People do say sometimes I went to this place because of you.
No, that makes me feel-
And that's fun.
Right, yes.
Yes.
Yeah, I had that experience recently with the Casa Benita.
Yeah.
Whereas somebody I'd never met despite friends in common and he said I'm going to Casa Benita.
It's like, oh, I have this podcast and he's like, why do you think I'm going?
Oh, okay.
It feels good.
Well that's good.
It feels really good.
So that one-
Because I think we all have the thing where we are just kind of unbridled,
excited about certain things and want to make sure to shine a light on Casa Benita being one of them.
I would also, I mean, that's how I feel about this.
I want to tell everybody go on this ride and get Tears for Fears,
but that's not really in your control.
It's very hard.
I guess just, you know, keep going.
Go to Epcot as much as you can.
Pay Disney as much money as you can.
Because you try to get, try until you get this song.
Could you do, could you put in, would AirPods stay in your ears if you just did it yourself?
Depends on how good, like-
How good the things are.
They fit.
Have you like taped, duct taped them around your head?
Like my right ear stays in really good.
My left ear is always falling out.
You've got a sloppy left inner hole.
I got a sloppy ear hole.
I've got a sloppy left ear hole.
Well, that's yeah.
Now, as long as you know that, then you shouldn't do it.
What did we call the pecs earlier?
Was it sloppy?
Sloppy pecs?
Sloppy pecs.
Give me a sloppy pec near my sloppy ear hole.
I got curious if this was a just us epiphany.
I don't know what has been landing as the agreed upon favorite song across the Epcot world.
But I decided to take it to our listeners.
I put this up on the Patreon.
I did a poll asking what's the best song.
And sure enough, everybody wants to rule the world.
Number one with a bullet.
Pretty handily, I would say.
Currently, with 1,200 people weighing in, everybody wants to rule the world at 35.
September at 28.
September seems to be...
I was wondering if September was people's favorite.
And I'm a big fan of that song.
And I'd be excited to get that song.
Sure.
Wake me up when September ends.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Yes.
No, you got it.
No, it really unlocks the perfection of that song.
Yeah, actually, the order is kind of like exactly what they rank it.
Our listeners collectively rank it at everybody wants to rule the world.
September, Conga, Iran, which I'd be interested to get one way or another in Disco Inferno,
all the way at the bottom.
I think there's a time and place for Disco Inferno.
But I think some of these are just like a little deeper cuts.
I don't know.
And I'm just I'm happy to hear that we're not crazy.
And that people are feeling the feelings here as are we.
I got a couple of people in Orlando when I was mentioning that.
I don't remember if I mentioned we did it or we're going to try.
But they were like, oh, yeah, it's the best one.
Really?
I guess it is out there.
I don't think I knew what was landing.
I didn't know either.
Yeah, yeah.
I did not pick this to be one of the crowd.
I did not do it to be popular.
No, no.
We had this locked and loaded.
And really quickly, by virtue of us posting that,
there were a couple of interesting comments just to run through quickly,
some of which shines a light on some of these other songs
and what's good about them or bad about them.
Emily A.
I have never paid attention to whatever story is happening on this ride.
I only vibed to the music and enjoy the coaster.
Everybody wants to rule the world as the ultimate ride experience through this method.
That's totally what I've been saying.
I agree.
It honestly made me forget that Marvel was even part of it.
You guys were talking about Marvel.
Cover your ears, Jason.
And I was like, oh, no.
Why are you talking about Marvel, though?
We're talking about Choose Your Fears Ride.
I did.
I did have to go back.
It's the first time we rode in and now watch video
because I couldn't track the story when we were being ripped around in conga.
Doesn't matter.
That's what it is.
It feels like these big dicks are going to fight.
They're going to do whatever they're going to do.
And all you can do, all you can try to do is be at peace and tune it out.
Don't stop having moments that you need to have.
Even with that, I kind of like that.
It's like I truly I hear a voice.
I think that's Chris Pratt.
I think I think that's Rocket.
I don't know.
Fake Rocket.
That's fake.
I think that's fake.
I think it's not Bradley Cooper.
It's no way.
Here's here's one from Joe Martin to give some shine to the last place in the poll.
I've only been on the ride once and I got Disco Inferno.
I'm too young to have experienced this, but it made me feel like I was roller skating
backwards at a roller rink in the late 70s at certain points.
That's fine.
Yeah, about that next time I don't want to.
Brian, I ran is the only one that sounds like it could have been written for the ride.
The guitar strum delay at the beginning is the perfect complement to the Big Bang launch.
The pace of the song matches your speed throughout the lyrics idea of running through space.
It works on several levels.
I think I really enjoy.
I could see that being very good.
Yeah, yeah, it's interesting.
And I definitely the people who put this together had these thoughts.
They knew these these were moody.
These were different types of songs.
I mean, I just love to know the process and they tested them and what were the what did
they not do?
If you're serious, if you're in there and you know anything and you can tell us anything,
let us know.
Zach Wolf says, I know people love September, but as a wedding photographer,
that song is triggering lol.
Yes, I could see I could see that.
That might be kind of the downside of a Disco Inferno or something.
I think that's some of the that of all of these, everybody wants to rule the world is the one
that's like, but that's not that's that's a song that might make you sad.
It might make you feel a little something.
Zach would say, don't wake him up when September ends or wake him up.
No, when September ends is what he wants.
Oh, he does when he wants to sleep through the song, not the month.
David, I do love screaming body.
Ah, when I get September, more people singing along.
That's fun.
But that ethereal intro, everybody wants to rule the world just feels perfect for this ride and
its story.
Thousand percent.
Yeah.
Madison Lane, not to be corny, but everybody wants to rule the world is the one that makes
you feel truly transcendent.
Yeah, that's completely how I feel.
I've been trying to not worry about being corny in this episode.
I may have been, but I that's yeah, there's got to be a time to listen.
I worry about listeners have never been embarrassed for us before.
I'm sure before this.
Seven years of macho steak and bourbon guys, real steak and bourbon guys.
They're so cool.
Masculine, high tea, high tea motherfuckers is what people generally consider us.
I bet if they met listeners who likes their stuff, the interactions would go
calmly and normally and they would not be thinking about how bad the interaction went.
Yes.
For weeks later.
Megan Temple Club 3 polling has conditioned me to be skeptical that this isn't somehow about
bug main.
I understand.
I know it should be.
People were suspicious in general.
Yeah.
And I understand that.
I would say it was nice to have a poll that wasn't people fighting about bug main.
Well, in six months, we'll get there.
Yeah, yeah.
Five or six months.
We'll finally be free of this.
And then this I like too in terms of suspicion.
Ryan O'Reilly, I can't wait to hear which episode this comes up in and why Scott and
Mike are arguing over it.
Oh, interesting.
I'm really glad that we proved Ryan wrong.
That is true.
A lot of music oriented sparring between us for episode after episode.
So it's so nice to go have that big piece of musical and ride harmony together.
Quite the opposite, Ryan.
I'm happy to flip your expectations.
But Ryan, I'll say this.
If all goes to plan, you'll get some of it somewhat soon.
You'll get some of that arguing soon.
Jelly Rolls, you're saying?
Possibly a Jelly Rolls episode if all goes to plan.
Yeah, this song was great, but I think the ride would be perfectly synced to
two guys playing lose yourself on pianos.
Perfectly synced to a cover of We Don't Talk About Bruno.
Last minute cancellation on my part for Jelly Rolls.
I get too distracted thinking about delicious jelly rolls.
And I don't make it.
While you're listening to Jelly Rolls.
You walk up to the door and you say, yes, I'd like three.
Three what?
Do you forget the name of the establishment you were in?
What are all these people sitting in here for?
I thought this was a grab and go establishment.
You sit by the water and eat your delicious rolls.
Think about your life.
Anyway, that's that.
I was glad to see it win.
I'm glad to see people are in sync with us here.
I also really quickly want to mention about the song itself.
Maybe some of the reason that the world syncs up with it so well is that in some ways,
we aren't even realizing that it's taking us back to the mid 90s.
And we're getting excited for a brand new episode of Dennis Miller Live to begin.
I think we all remember that at the start of each Dennis Miller Live,
before the ranting started, that Dennis would walk into a pool hall,
walk up to a billiards table where all of the balls were little earths.
And when this song was playing, these memorable notes are playing.
And then he would draw back the cue and then get all but one of the balls in on one attempt.
But then one would just be teetering right at the edge because even Dennis Miller ain't perfect.
Wow.
Believe it or not, I don't remember that.
You don't?
You don't remember this being HBO's Emmy winning?
This was the last week tonight of its time.
My dad would watch it.
I would wander out into the living room and see him watching it and be like,
well, this is an adult show for sophisticated comedy fans.
And I would leave.
And that's really all my perception of Dennis was.
I saw him on Weekend Update a little bit when I watched the reruns.
Yeah.
But still, I was like, well, this man's too smart for me.
Well, he shows it at the beginning that he comes out.
He's the one wheeling and dealing.
This guy's got to know about politics.
He can make all those earths go into these holes.
Also just want to say I had never listened to the full album that this song
comes from, 1985, songs from the big chair.
I listened to it when we were on the flight back.
Perfect.
Perfect album.
It's so good.
All the hits are from that one.
Shout is from that album.
Head Over Heels is from that album, which is also,
I feel equal to Everybody Wants to Drill the World,
incredible song, moving song.
And on the full album, it is really great paired with,
it's like part of this suite with another song, Broken,
which it is in the single of it, too.
But I didn't realize it was part of a movement.
And that zone, especially, was wonderful.
And Tears for Fears are great in general.
Also really good covers of this song by Ted Leo and the Pharmacists,
which they did for AV Club.
That's excellent.
When AV Club was a single, Undercover, bands would come in
and crowd into this room, and they'd have to cross off from a list.
I think Ted Leo might have chosen early and gotten this one.
And he says at a time in his life, this was maybe his favorite song.
It's an excellent cover.
That cover might have helped me years ago,
start to really see the song in a new light and really love the song.
I was very engaged in this cover series.
Maybe I have seen that.
There is an excellent, they might be Giants cover of Tub Thumping,
where the entire office comes in.
I've seen that.
I watched that earlier today.
That is fun.
Mayor Hawthorne, one of my favorite guys, does a great cover, too.
It's also been covered by Lorde and been covered by Gru.
Oh, Gru.
Yeah, Gru did.
I love to see.
Upcoming, up-and-coming artist Gru did it in the Little Known
film Despicable Me 4.
My daughter is finally requesting to watch the Minions on the TV.
Wow.
After just knowing them on T-shirts at Universal City.
Things she point at in the park.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, she probably has the attention span for the shorts,
which I think are all on.
She's watching the movie.
Oh, she is watching the movie.
Yeah, she's good.
She identifies with the girls with Agnes and company.
I don't know about that.
With the stellar writing of Evan Susser and Van Robichow, of course.
That's what's resonating.
That's right.
Yes.
Anyways.
So yeah, I was also looking.
I was trying to figure out if there's any other experiences like this in Rides.
On the emotional side of things.
Yes.
Because you've said, this might have been a mail back or something.
We went on a tear about emotional media and you were talking about
wanting Neil Young after the gold rush or something.
Yeah.
There's something to that.
It is like this is the version that actually ultimately,
I think you're never going to get moody.
You're not going to get Joni Mitchell on a roller coaster.
But this does feel like, well, this is because it's driving
and it is close to party music, but it works on the other side too.
Yes.
Probably, yes.
Probably not some sad.
I mean, you did come up when we were talking about
Smashing Pumpkins Replacing Aerosmith.
Like a tonight tonight would work.
That would be pretty cool.
And as a driving.
I think it would be an extremely strange move in 2025.
Well, if they completely rebranded the Aerosmith.
Yes, the Smashing Pumpkins.
I agree.
But in a grab bag ride potentially, just that song could maybe exist.
I had a lot that I cut from things that I was going to bring up
while I was gone from the Scott Free episodes.
But you were talking to Cardona about, you were telling him
that they should redo the ride with Rolling Stones and Kiss.
I said I wanted older men.
You wanted all even older men.
Yeah.
Man, I align with Cardona a lot.
He's your guy, I know.
Yeah, he kept going, gah, what, ah.
And then you brought up, I don't know, I guess you could do Taylor Swift.
But then you said she's not high energy enough.
First of all, I was like, good, did Mr. Trump take over the podcast for a second?
But secondly, I'm like, there's not one Taylor Swift song
that would work for not a single one.
Well, there was a Taylor on Jelly Rolls.
The second night I was at Jelly Rolls, there was a Taylor Swift song.
Was that high energy enough for the high caliber of Jelly Rolls?
It was fun.
Yes, it was fun.
It was an early.
It was, I forget, why can't I think of it?
What song?
I'm trying to think.
Kind of obscure one.
One that wasn't even really released.
Whatever that one is.
It's not so high energy.
I'm still worried the Muppets aren't high energy enough for that ride system.
I don't know.
But either they make up a new song or they-
Well, I think they're going to be covering song.
That's what I'm guessing.
I still think that's what it's going to be.
Just tell me, it's not Disney songs, is it?
Oh, I don't know about that.
That's possible.
I do think it's like Meghan Trainor and Miss Piggy singing a new song.
Where are you pulling that from?
Because they said there would be current artists with Muppets.
Is Meghan Trainor an actual one?
Or are you just saying-
No, that's just because she's always on this stuff.
I don't know.
Jesus Christ.
Here in this episode, we have a lot of musical blissing.
I don't know, but there's a lot of singers out there.
Jelly Rolls?
Disney, if anyone's listening, you need to look
further than the people who are on your goddamn specials every year.
I am not one of these people who, unlike some of my co-hosts,
you can take out Aerosmith and I don't give a shit.
But if you replace it with Meghan Trainor, we have a problem.
Sabrina Carpenter grew up in the family.
She's too bawdy now it is.
Too big, too bawdy.
Too popular.
Too popular, yeah.
Yeah.
Jason, any other songstresses top on the charts these days?
Boy Genius?
No, no, no, not that.
He does have a Boy Genius though.
Like any young singers.
Chula.
Haim.
No, no, no, not a blonde, but a redhead.
Lucy Dawkus is black.
God, we're never getting there.
Can you see a ball?
We're never getting there.
Redhead?
Oh, he's not in the time that I want it.
He's not giving it to me.
Brandy Carlisle.
Geez.
You're messing with me.
So I was trying to figure out what other rides could have songs that are sad.
And I, of course, RIP Ride Rocket, the ride that Jason has been on,
but we have not been on.
And I have pledged that I will do it before.
A Universal Floral Opera, which has like a secret menu that you can dial in.
In a regular venue.
If you're in a phone booth.
But a regular menu as well.
A regular menu as well.
Yeah.
And I don't know this list very well at all.
You did a dive.
Yes, I have it in front of me and there are a lot of options.
So there are, I don't think it's going to be, it's going to hit the same way
because it's an outdoor coaster that no one seems to like.
Yes.
And it's not like an incredible light show and like, yeah.
Maybe at night it'll be better.
It's got the unpleasant vertical slow launch that I absolutely hate.
It's my least favorite thing.
Yeah.
Seems like the opposite of this, the instantaneous launch
with the magical first notes of the song.
Yeah.
You got anything that you think can be in terms of not thrills and chills, but fills.
So they have, they do have, and this is of interest to you,
Ride Like the Wind by Christopher Cross.
Which would be interesting to be on a coaster.
Okay.
Because that's got a nice, you obviously, you know, it's a nice little vibe groove to it.
Yeah. You got to crank it.
That's still, it still is a little soft, but I think.
Yeah. Yeah.
You crank that baby up.
Could be interesting.
I'll tell you, it's great on a pontoon.
Of course.
That's what it was written for.
Yeah. Yeah.
They have rainbow connection that you can get on the secret menu.
That's strange.
It is strange.
And I don't think it will work.
I just think it's like almost like two, unless, depending on the version of it.
That's like putting a slow kid's song in a scary movie trailer.
Yeah. I don't know.
It's meant to be the opposite.
We'll see if I can go on this more than once.
Also played at Jelly Rolls.
Because I would like, yes, that is true.
Ride Like the Wind was played at Jelly Rolls, I forget.
And a certain red haired singer's song was also played.
Who? Can anyone name her?
Lucille Ball.
She's usually named.
Yeah.
Lucille Ball's song.
Now what I thought was interesting on this list is that they have,
well, where is it?
It's My Everything by Barry White, which I'm like, I don't know how that feels.
It's a very romantic, groovy song, which I like a lot, but I'm like, I don't know.
So there's a lot more.
There's a lot more like mystery to some of these.
And especially how they're going to be playing at a
coaster that doesn't seem to be very popular.
Although some people are like, it's fun, whatever.
The thrill is gone by B.B. King.
You can select.
Why are these on here?
There's like a hundred of them.
There's so many.
There's so lose yourself is on the list.
That sort of makes sense.
Yeah.
Any of them time out remotely, right?
I think they can't.
There's just no way.
Yeah.
Maybe unless I'm completely wrong, but still Rock and Roll to Me by Billy Joel.
I mean, it's not my favorite song, although I kind of like it as far as
the Billy Joel like pop hits.
It's closer to what I like, but still, how can you throw any shade at any Billy Joel
when you love Jelly Rolls with every fiber of your bit?
This is Billy Joel.
Jelly Rolls is a different thing than Jolly Rolls.
Did you get for the longest time or?
We are Piano Man.
Well, really not a place where you can hear Piano Man.
That's right.
Is that when everyone's leaving like a last call playing piano?
Oh, that's like that's early in the set.
That's full.
That's the opening set.
They've got Immigrant Song by Led Zeppelin.
That makes sense to me.
That's a high energy.
Crocodile Rock seems really fun.
Are these all secret ones?
These, I think, are all on the secret list.
But you're like Crocodile Rock for sure.
Well, that's not a set.
Taylor does not have anything close to Crocodile Rock.
I'm talking about Rip Ride Rocket here.
Not Rock and Roller Coaster.
Different coaster.
Crocodile Rock couldn't cut Muster on Rock and Roller Coaster.
I don't know.
Does it get close to whatever the song was about young girls that's currently on there?
There's a lot of sketchiness.
I think on the regular menu, Intergalactic is available.
The regular menu, if I recall, was a lot of the biggest hits of 2009 and 2010.
Don't Funk With My Heart by the Black Eyed Peas.
There we go.
That's going to do it.
Oh, I want that song.
I want the Will.i.am Mick Jagger song.
You guys know that song?
Yeah, I do know that song.
You can go hard, hard like a rockin' roll.
Explode!
Rob Thomas tried to give Mick Jagger the song Disease from Matchbox 20's third album,
and Mick Jagger said, no, I don't want it.
But then he did the song with Will.i.am, and I think Disease is a better song than that.
So I don't know what Mick was thinking.
What song could possibly be better than Go Hard or whatever it's called?
Yeah, I don't remember.
Baby, baby!
Highly recommended, listeners.
Will.i.am x Mick Jagger.
There is The Black Parade by My Chemical Romance, which is a song I like,
and what I'm trying to do right now is let's decide what am I picking for my first one of all of these.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah.
What do we think that should be?
Should it be Black Parade?
I think that's what I'm leaning to, honestly.
I think the Rainbow Connection is too.
It's not even going to register.
It's like the banjo.
It's weird.
That is probably the best way to what Jason was saying in the era that it was.
Vogue by Madonna?
I don't know.
Lose Yourself?
No, I'm not doing that.
I feel like My Everything or Black Parade is what I'm leaning towards.
My Everything sounds interesting.
I don't know that it's going to make me ascend to a higher plane.
I don't know.
Do both.
I don't want to do this once.
I don't want this vertical climb.
Do they still have Kanye on their hair?
Oh, God.
They might.
I don't know.
Is it too loaded or is it too complicated to remove?
Where it's like, ah, we're leaving it.
We don't have access to that machine.
This whole thing's run on a Pono, so we can't really do much.
It's only the religious stuff.
They play out of the Christian events.
Oh, I forgot about the Christian era.
For listener, what Christian song would be the most,
what would make you have more of a religious epiphany on Rip Ride Rocket?
Our God is an awesome God.
There's hella good on here.
Speaking of Christian people.
Oh, right.
Anyway.
With arms wide open?
Is there any creed on there?
I would do creed in a second.
Not with arms wide open.
I would do my sacrifice.
I would love.
Well, that was one shot around the corner.
That would rule.
I don't like creed.
I wouldn't like going on that ride, but I recognize that the combo.
That could be, you know, as we've been saying, like, look, weird combinations.
I like a Marvel ride a lot.
This is where it happens.
Yeah, you have to tailor it to.
I mean, that's a perfect marriage right there.
Yeah, that would be if it exists.
I don't think you can do it, but that's I would pick that if you could.
So right now, I'm leaning toward my chemical romance.
Well, listeners, throw your creative experience.
People that have been, let me know.
Yeah, yeah.
Have you done?
Which one's better?
Barry White or Mike?
Have you been on this ride enough to do both Barry White and my chemical romance?
If so.
And boy, it makes you wish that we had little dial buttons for this ride.
I think you're missing two big ones on here, Mike.
Oh, go ahead.
Bring me to life by Evan S.
Oh, I did just see that.
That's borderline Christian.
Rolling by Limp Bizkit.
Oh, that's good, too.
A new contender.
Yeah, that's in the mix.
Yeah.
Limp Bizkit roller coaster.
I think I love break stuff, too.
They had break stuff on there.
That would be my ideal.
Does that have a big influence on second level?
We covered it.
You covered it.
Yeah.
You covered break stuff.
Yep.
We sure did.
I had to learn all of break stuff.
Sabotage.
I mean, that's legitimate.
Sabotage and Intergalactic are good ones.
Yeah.
There's a Ferg- Glamorous by Fergie.
How about I get a Fergie now?
That's so thrilling to me.
That could be me.
Yeah.
There's Flowdown by Modest Mouse,
which would be interesting on The Guardian's coaster,
I feel like.
That's kind of a fun little-
It's funny that you liked playing breaking stuff
because I know that in breaking-
I like playing break stuff
because I know that in your childhood,
you would have never been allowed to break stuff.
No, it was cathartic to do that in a different way,
to talk about breaking things
and beating a guy up or whatever the song's about.
I'm going to pretend not that it's my mom.
That's too far.
I'm going to pretend that I'm beating up my mom's rules.
Take that rule.
Break your fucking face tonight.
Mike, Vertigo by U2.
Yeah, I know.
It's not my favorite.
But this is what I think is so great
is that they have this odd confluence of things
and the James Gunn and as much as this would be-
and now it suddenly becomes like
there's a weird way that you can go
on the Modest Mouse roller coaster.
That would never happen.
That would never be built from the ground up.
I just really love and value that
through a weird confluence of events
that you can ride on a pretty goddamn perfect
Tears for Fears roller coaster.
There is no world where suddenly they're like,
guess what?
Universal's been talking to Kurt Smith's camp.
Just because of a certain events
that landed in the right way.
Just as our day played out right up until the end
where this was a great day for me and Epcot
and music, music that I like very much
because- and this is where I have-
look, I have no right to throw shade at you musically
because of how much I goddamn enjoy
getting to see a five-song set by Jason Scheff.
Jason Scheff, if you don't know and you maybe don't,
is the guy who took over as the lead singer
of Chicago from Peter Satara.
Great set, great- everything I could ask for a chef
from a chef set.
Along comes a woman.
What kind of man would I be?
Just you and me.
Hard to say I'm sorry with Get Away, the ending,
which is one of my favorite pieces of music.
That's my hype of music.
That's what I listen to.
Anything that's making me nervous, I will like,
let me get in the groove.
It's a song that Aaron and I play when we're arriving,
if we're pulling into Disney World,
if we're pulling into Vegas, we listen to that.
Hard to say I'm sorry is a fine ballad, whatever.
It's like a cousin of You're the Inspiration,
but Get Away.
When it gets rocking at the end
with Koki, David Foster energy,
and I got to hear it in Epcot Center,
under the shadow of the American Adventure
and next to a sign for George Bush's paintings.
That's the darkest.
That's really-
America.
Being, being, yes, and I've said it many times,
that World Showcase really is the draw.
When you ever think about maybe just packing it all up
and going down there and you go,
there is a World Showcase
and you could be there like five nights of the week.
You could be there so often.
Wouldn't it be weird if you lived there?
You'd be there and there'd be great concerts every night.
Although I think there's a break in concerts
when we were there for the live shows.
I just looked this up.
There's Garden Rocks ends
and then Eat to the Beat hasn't started yet.
Oh, okay.
These are different.
Dark Weeks, unfortunately,
because I was like, oh, who's there when we're there?
Okay.
It doesn't seem, maybe I'm wrong
or there's a different like filler acts,
but I was a little disappointed that we didn't get
because it's so fun.
That's one of my favorite things to do
because I texted you a couple of weeks ago
of who was there.
I couldn't believe.
And you were so thrilled.
Yes, I don't.
Look, it's hard to defend,
but Chicago ended up meaning a lot to me
from my dad, from my wife,
and getting a blast of 25 or 64,
ending every single set of the three.
You did the exact same set every time.
So yeah, I don't know.
That's what Epcot rocks.
Epcot rocks.
And we will post,
we'll post photos of you and I contemplating life.
Oh yeah, we have those.
Having spiritual moments along at the Epcot Lagoon
right after this had transpired.
But thank you for letting us come back
and try to bring this joy, spread this joy.
You survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
Jason, will you go on Rip Ride Rocket with me?
Uh, I don't, uh, maybe.
Sounds like a no.
Will you, okay, how about this?
Will you eat a steak with me in Orlando?
In Orlando?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Beef hasn't really greened with evil
in the last couple of years.
Answer the question.
That much.
Can we just get.
He's been so happy.
Just say yes even if we don't do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Lie to me, lie to me.
And now say the name of the singer.
What?
Oh, uh.
Say it.
Phoebe Bridges.
No!
Oh, all right.
I shut it down and forget it.
9-11.