FOREVER!
DOG!
Spaceships, mountains, fairy tale kingdoms.
Theme park creators can take us to these places without even breaking a sweat.
Who cares?
Our question?
What craftsmen, what artisans could dare to show us?
A desk.
A cup full of pens.
A little plant.
To shine a light on our actual day-to-day work lives via a little lamp.
Then glue that lamp to a desk so guests can't steal the lamp.
If you're listening to this episode at the office, prepare to be transported to a bunch of different offices, which are fake.
It's the Fake Office Final Four on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to the phony workplace war zone.
The ultimate debate of deceitful desk dominance.
It's the Fake Office Final Four here on Podcast The Ride.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
Hello there, yes.
And I am rocked and ready to go.
I am rock hard.
Excuse me, I meant to say I'm rock hard and ready to go and debate.
I am rock hard and no one will notice as we are all behind desks.
That is some of the benefit of talking about desks.
You can be as rock hard as you want.
I think I meant to use rock as if it was a paperweight for an office.
Something you would find in a fake or real office.
Either or.
I'm as rock hard as a paperweight.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi.
I'm sporting more of a half chub under my desk.
I'm a little more distracted because my fingers are like really raw and bleeding
because I kept trying to steal post-it notes and pens and other off supplies,
which is my usual M.O. working in an office.
You slice yourself up with a paper?
That's not the M.O.
Stealing is the M.O.
Stealing, I don't think I've bought office supplies since the late 2000s.
Really?
I'm still going, well, I buy pens if I see a sale of cool pens or I have a coupon.
Cool pens sale today you'll see on a store and then, ooh, in I go.
But besides that.
I'll tell you, I got a coupon from Staples once.
It was $10 off $10.
So I bought $11 worth of pens and I was like a pig in shit.
Audience on their feet right now.
Staples coupon talk right out the gate.
They're bringing out the big guns.
Garcinia Wall Show in the early 90s right now.
Everyone calm down.
We'll leave three minutes.
So let's just like kind of do nothing for three minutes while they calm down from the cool pens Staples talk.
Just trying to get me off his five.
Real quick, just a real quick question I swear for Jason.
Have you bought blank paper in a long time for a printer or otherwise?
No, I still haven't properly configured that printer our friend Andrew gave me like two years ago.
Configured?
Set it up, connect it to the Wi-Fi, buy ink cartridges, find my blank paper.
Plug it in I guess would be step one of the configuring.
Plugging it in, finding space for it.
When was the last time you bought computer paper?
At Target maybe like two years ago.
OK.
Because you know what I was doing?
I was going to Fry's Electronics.
One of their services, you could take an empty ink cartridge and they would put a syringe of ink in it and filled up.
They would shoot it up.
Like a heroin needle.
They'd just like go right into the heart and just really?
Yeah, it was like a third of the price of ink cartridge.
I can't anymore.
Wow.
This just like fill up like a top-off station of ink.
Reusable, yeah reusable ink.
That's interesting.
Yeah, I don't know.
Some places might still do that.
Hmm.
OK.
So you have bought supplies recently.
Yeah.
Jason, you got to remember I had an office day job 2010 to 2017.
I know.
So I'm used to replying all on every email telling people this is done.
Look at the cockiness.
You know?
Look at this.
This is like a wrestling problem.
He's coming in.
He's going to win this thing.
I know the competition isn't between us, but if it was, Jason is going to win.
He does reply all.
I just still have office brain from working in the office.
From how long ago?
Mike, every now and then you reply to logistical email, like ad emails or something emails,
but you don't reply all.
Sometimes I don't.
And I'm like, whatever happened with that?
And you're like, oh, I took care of that a week ago.
I don't want you guys to have to deal with some of the emails.
So I just go, I'll deal with it.
I love done email.
Oh man, my old job.
You talk about your email being full all the time with different ads.
You miss all our work emails, you say.
I'm taking some all to a month.
You guys are my important email.
I got the star.
The star comes up from Mike and Scott and Jane.
They do.
You claimed that they fall through the car.
You were claiming a little while ago that you lose emails because you have so many.
So I corrected that.
I starred you guys and my mom, my stepdad, my brother.
Oh, that's since the discussion.
Since then.
Okay.
So from now on, reply all.
I will never just reply because I think I can take care of a problem quickly.
You knew about this?
We're going to get caught for so long in this story.
I made a mistake.
But the reply all, you know that Mike has not failed to do reply all on podcast business.
That's something you know about.
I don't think I was aware of that.
Only because we've discussed it.
It's never something huge.
Yeah, it'll be something from the podcast network and it's like, do you approve a pencil ad or something?
Sometimes I'll just say, I'll just reply.
Do you approve this ad for a pill that gets you a half chub?
Yeah, exactly.
And we'll say we do because actually we wouldn't be comfortable with the full chub.
But knowing that it's only going to lead to a half because we're only.
I would roll that one by you guys if it was a half chub pill.
Although I should have just said, yep, but only Jason's willing to do the ad for it.
And it's some weird, that gets disguised.
Like, are we comfortable endorsing Xanthan X?
I don't know.
What is it?
It's that half chub pill.
It's a half chub.
They try to dress it up with a fancy name.
Well, every now and then there's ads about, you know, products for children.
I step back.
Well, I don't want to say we'll do that.
That's on you guys, you know?
Yeah, but you're sitting there like, come on, we got to do this ad and make that money.
I don't care about those kids.
You're sitting there hoping I say yes.
Well, yeah, I'm chomping on my stogie.
My apartment smells like shit because I'm chomping on stogies all day.
Right, yes.
So Rick, this is a runner on the show.
Your hatred of stogies.
I've never heard a word said with more dripping, maybe bourbon and steak.
But besides that, you have such malice for the word stogies.
I've got a real sensitive sense of smell, Scott, and I've got real sensitive eyes.
Especially in allergy seasons.
Okay.
So you resent, have you walked into a room that was loaded with stogie smoke that ruined you for the season?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Well, then he's done a good job successfully avoiding stogies.
Trying to avoid it.
Yeah.
The beaches at the Jersey Shore, there was always like-
A stogie guy.
A big dad would post up with his nasty cigars, cigarillos.
And the sea air would take it right there.
The wind would bring it right to you, you know?
And you'd see a seagull pass through, just choke and fall to the sand.
Yeah.
I don't know, they're a little wild there.
They'd probably try to eat it.
They'll eat anything.
You've never seen a Jersey seagulls sucking down stogies.
Smoking stogies while they fly on the shore.
Last couple years-
No, you've never seen a stogie being smoked by a seagull on the shore.
Oh, a seagull?
Last couple years, there's been falconers walk around the War Walk with falcons.
Oh.
Because they-
Like, for photographs to be taken, or are they hunting something?
No, they release the bird to scare away other birds, and then it comes back to him.
Oh, okay.
And then the falcon sometimes.
Are they paid by the state to do that, or they just do it?
Probably paid by the city.
The city.
They employ falconers to scare birds away?
That's interesting.
Yeah, they get a little out of hand.
They should pay some people to scare the stogie smokers away.
Yeah.
Caw, caw.
Some of those birds-
My grandmother had a half of the sandwich once, and she was talking.
And the bird just swooped in and took it away.
That would have been a great story if it had just ended at half a sandwich.
My grandmother had half a sandwich one time.
But there was more there.
Those diagonal cut peach sandwiches hit different, brother.
What's in there?
What's in that sandwich?
Maybe a tuna fish, maybe a simple peanut butter and jelly.
Do you think there's a chance that-
One minute, one minute.
The bird steals a sandwich out of your hand at City Food?
Too windy for birds up there.
The birds get blown away.
No bird could navigate.
They save money on falconer.
Too noisy with all the construction, too.
Well, lately, you're saying.
Lately, yeah.
Yeah, there's a lot going on up there.
Okay, but there's a lot going on here.
We should get to the premise of the episode.
Today is the Fake Office Final Four.
This is exciting.
I think we haven't done one of these in two years.
We missed it last year due to the City Walk stuff.
We are back with another competition this year.
This is not the only bracket-based premise in comedy podcasts,
but it is the most ignorant of how sports work.
Correct.
We're really excited about that area that we've carved out for ourselves.
That's what we can really lay claim to.
Some of this has been gone over a little bit on the Patreon
because we did a little bit of a pre-show this year over on the Second Gate
where we figured out the rules.
We got settled on some of the opponents, but not all of them.
We'll still do the reveal here in this episode.
But this kind of came to us because we were talking about the newish ride,
Tiana's Bayou Adventure.
We were remarking how much we like Tiana's office in the line
and how often theme park queues have weird little offices that you go by,
possibly in cages, at the very least behind velvet ropes,
things trying to prevent you from reaching into the office,
from trying to steal office supplies, as Jason might want to do.
Because they can't watch and ensure that people cut themselves on the sticky notes.
That stuff's valuable. They can't afford to lose it.
Oftentimes, the office supplies bolted down or glued down.
This is true.
You can't take one of the fake croissants from the Daily Bugle office.
No, I can't take the excess tech memo on the collector's desk.
Collector's desk.
Anyway, we like our weird little offices in cages.
We realized in the episode this might be the way to go,
and we did manage to narrow it down.
Well, you know what? Not quite narrow it down to 16.
We are entering this one not fully secure,
even despite having done a pre-episode.
That might have only slowed us down, created more questions rather than answers.
Before we get into the official list and the official divisions,
apologies to a few that didn't end up making it.
The Ghost Town Sheriff's Office in Knott's Berry Farm did not make it.
We, I think, determined that Officer Zizek's little pod was not...
I think there's an argument to be made and justice to be had
for little security consoles for aliens or robots.
Do you consider those offices and desks?
But I think none of them made it this year.
And we did, of course, in the episode over on the second gate,
determine that despite Jason's question, which I liked a lot,
Madame Leota's table, Madame Leota's seance room,
we are not considering an office for these purposes.
Some, look, some big schools often get knocked out.
Yeah, despite their best efforts and despite being very cool.
I mean, I almost wish it was in.
If we're feeling overwhelmed by one of these,
we could certainly knock one out and put Leota back in just for fun.
But let's see how we feel as we go down the line.
Can I apologize about an office that's not in the bracket
unless you guys light up and we want to throw it in?
We decide to put it in.
What do you think?
Dock on Dars little cage office in Batu,
something I did not think about until today.
He's got like his like bean counter on the back wall.
He's got a little desk.
He's got little trinkets.
It's clearly, you know, its own thing from the actual store from the from.
So so it is his office.
Right. My knee jerk was no, that's a store.
But you're right. He does have.
He's got an office, a little booth.
It's kind of like where, you know, Danny DeVito or Louie was in taxi,
a little a little caged off this batch.
I'm trying to get a good view of it just to I mean, I'm I'm into it.
I just don't know what goes.
Yeah. What if what if he's on deck?
What if he's on deck in case of injury?
I would like a case of boredom.
Sure. And I would like to declare this.
This will flaunt the rules of a traditional bracket like none of the other
final fours we've ever done.
OK, yes. Now, what do you mean?
You mean that we are going to anything is on the table here.
I mean, we're not going to we're not going to fit into your little 16.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
We're going to get crazy with it.
We can. And don't yell.
We're going to yell at us.
We're going to configure this thing crazier than adjacent printer.
This thing's going to be wild.
More complex than hooking up a printer in the year twenty twenty five.
I am stunned by the Canon company.
You know, what do you mean?
It's I have to try to put it on Earth.
Yeah, I know. I just haven't gotten around to it.
I haven't made space for it.
Look, I got limited energy a lot of time.
My hands hurt like one of my eyes.
You know, are you got to prioritize holding space for the printer?
I am holding space.
Very good. Yeah.
It's made it to the office.
Do you think it be do you think that Ariana and Cynthia's long fingernails
would make it easier or harder to use a Canon printer?
It might be it might make them more precise with hitting the buttons.
Like, I don't know.
You wouldn't miss aim like us and our our big chunkers, our half chubs of fingers.
You would have to.
You would have to. Yeah.
Like if you had long nail, I'm trying to imagine it right now.
But maybe like better.
You know, it'd be good for like answering telephones, like being an old telephone
operator like Lily Tomlin.
Oh, that would be fun.
That would look fun.
So you just got to be careful with those long nails, because if you hit something
on the wrong angle or wrong force snap, it's gone.
The whole thing's off. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mm hmm.
I would hate for that.
All right.
Well, Doc Gondar on deck.
And I think just anybody call it as you see it.
I like this thing being a little loose, a little chaotic.
Yeah.
If we need to draft candidates in.
And we did organize these things kind of in little divisions just because I thought
it might be a good way to highlight the types of fake offices that we run into in
theme park attractions, mainly cues.
When you add it up, it really is places that either that you are walking through
or like the things that are entirely walk through attractions where there's not a
lot of offices in rides.
I think that it's always like it's waiting areas.
It's on the way you're seeing them on foot usually.
Yeah.
I wonder what that's about.
Maybe I guess you're on a ride and you want to go somewhere more interesting than an
office.
Yeah.
There's a thing.
I don't know.
This is not too big of a tangent.
I've always been fascinated by doing a ride that would really simulate reality in a
way.
So the idea of a ride in an office, maybe something fantastical happens, but maybe
it's just the office ride, the NBC show, the office, or it's something that ends up
being more fantastical.
So I am fascinated by what you're saying.
There's very little of that in the actual ride.
It's almost insane that there is not enough.
What if you, the vehicle, was going on the wild one shot journey of making one of
those music videos they would make all the time?
Maybe it's just one scene.
In my head, the office was doing flash mobs.
Every episode, yeah.
By season six.
There were twice an episode flash mobs.
It's possible.
It's sounding more like OK Go, what you were talking about.
OK Go treadmill video.
They would make OK Go style videos where everybody pops around and slides around.
And you, the vehicle, are the winding path of the one shot cameraman that this paper
company uses to make fun videos.
I think that you do it.
I got surprised.
It seems like we will definitely.
The future portal in Epic Universe.
Scranton.
Well, because there's a new one coming, so it's ripe.
World of Scranton.
They would dress it up.
It couldn't just be the office.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Enter the Dunder Mifflin verse.
I don't know how you dress it up exactly.
I see you make it a bigger thing.
Yeah, I don't know.
I haven't even really crunched it.
We can figure it out.
Have you guys been to Scranton before?
Have not.
No.
OK.
He's really cocky today.
Yeah.
I'm winning this thing.
I'm just trying to stay awake.
Hey, cockiness keeps you awake.
Great.
Yeah.
When you're thinking of Scranton, it shoots your body full of excitement.
Well, it's just funny to me that it's like, this is the no rules bracket.
I thought we were going to come in with a locked bracket and we'll keep this thing tight.
And you guys are like, no, we're flying by the seat of our pants.
And I'm like, all right, let's do it, brother.
Let's go crazy.
So it's not a problem for you.
No.
Yeah, I know.
You seemed mad at the beginning there.
I thought we were locked, and now we're not.
Well, we can start getting into it.
I think we should get into it.
Yeah, let's get into it.
All right.
So this first area, the first division, this is what still requires a narrow down for us.
But this is one of the biggest areas of fake office in theme parkdom, and that is jungle makeshifts.
We ran into so many of these.
We figured make it a division.
And here is the list of five that needs to be narrowed down.
The Indiana Jones office from the Indiana Jones Adventure, Expedition Everest, Jungle Cruise.
And even in that, there's discussion of what is the Jungle Cruise office.
The Adventureland Treehouse.
And what's the office there?
In my head, going through it, and I haven't been there in person.
Maybe you can help, Mike.
The Daughters Observatory is an observatory.
That's where you see a desk.
That's kind of the most like art designed, like room for work.
And finally, Journey to the Center of the Earth.
There's a classic caged office in the queue for that in Tokyo DisneySea.
Okay.
I think maybe the most efficient thing is that we all, before we even get into it, vote for one of these to go.
Jungle Cruise.
Okay.
Everest.
Jason.
Jason, what goes?
What goes?
I'm going to try to move this along and also say Jungle Cruise.
Wow.
Jungle Cruise is out.
Jungle Cruise gone.
Why the immediate thought for that?
I just think it's a little ad hoc.
It's more queue than office.
I don't know Journey to the Center of the Earth.
I haven't been to DisneySea.
So I didn't want to vote that one out.
And I didn't want us to come to a three-way steal.
Well, some of it for me is just that when I think of these as having a lot of personality, I like, by the way, this is no knock against the Jungle Cruise.
But the other four, I have a stronger feeling in my mind about their identity.
With the Jungle Cruise, I like the aesthetic, I like the line, I like the stuff I'm seeing when I go back over the queue.
But the other four just stand out.
And there has to be a loser here.
The fact that we don't know.
That's part of it too.
There's a different one in my head from Disneyland and Disney World.
If it was that, one of them is the radio room.
But what's the radio room?
It's good.
The radio room's good.
Don't get me wrong.
People are already mad right now.
But I say don't be mad at me.
There's so much character.
It's playing my Spotify top five all over the place.
Yeah.
There's old-timey music.
And yeah, this is a tough competition.
All right.
Well, that was good and efficient.
And no offense taken that you were against me there.
You got to do what we got to do.
Okay.
I have entered the candidates into a randomizer.
So we didn't know the pair until now.
So right now the debate is between Adventureland Treehouse,
the Daughters Observatory, and Journey to the Center of the Earth.
Yes.
Okay.
So the Daughters Observatory, I think this is a very lovely room.
You know, you've got a lot of like celestial art on the wall.
You've got kind of a, is this like a makeshift telescope?
Is it made out of a barrel and stuff?
It's like a fun Gilligan's Island professor making something out of something.
And then this wonderful, what would you call it?
Like a mobile.
Yes.
That is like, you know, and I haven't been, I haven't seen this in person,
but it's like a solar system mobile that seems like lit up with special gems.
I mean, this is the right, I will say the right family landed on this island
because they are craftsmen.
I don't know how they managed to get this done with just a bunch of rocks and coconuts
because this is a beautiful place.
Yes.
I was skeptical about this one.
And then when I looked at pictures, I'm like, this one has a lot of character.
It seems practical.
And I think it's got something that the other ones don't have.
A lot of natural light.
You can't work in the darkness.
I think this is going to come up in other categories.
Now, I think there are probably some very cool offices that have no natural light at all.
We should respect those for what they are.
Sure.
Especially like a villainous character might want no light whatsoever.
But I do, part of me is factoring into these decisions.
What office would I want to work in?
Maybe that's not fair, but it's in my head, you know.
It feels like it needs to have qualities of a space that would be, you know,
that would leave me with an open mind, that would make me a free thinker.
You know, where do I want to sit and get some work done?
And I totally would in the Adventureland treehouse.
I think going with your gut is fair, Scott.
I think that should be on the table because you think about people playing basketball.
They're making split-second decisions of like, do I go to him or him?
You know, like, oh, my gut's telling me this one and oh, he made the shot or oh, we missed.
Oh, well.
On to the next thing.
Look at that.
See, I didn't spot one error in there.
We do know plenty about sports.
Wow, yeah, he's right.
Journey to the Center of the Earth is a very, this might fall more into the lab category,
where other offices that we have seen and will see are kind of more spare and like tidy and organized.
This is absolute chaos.
There is stuff everywhere.
There's supplies in a big net up at the top.
It's a tiny space and there could not be more packed into it.
This is the workspace of somebody furiously frustrated at being unable to tap into their theories
about what the hell is at the center of the goddamn Earth.
So many crumpled up papers, tons of test tubes with different colors and supplies, a big hatch door.
Yeah.
Cool space.
Definitely a cool space.
Anything you want to highlight about it?
Yeah.
Here's the thing with me that still keeps this very strongly in the mix for my affection or my decision, I should say.
I love beakers.
As a kid, beakers with different color liquid in them, obsessed with these.
Sure.
The idea of not, even though not thinking about it as a kid, I think I always thought they were potions.
I didn't think they were like chemicals that would hurt me if I drank them.
So obviously there's a kid element to just imagining what's in those beakers and bottle, what the experiments are happening.
Sure.
So the idea that there is a room, which I think, is there a room with more beakers?
Well, maybe one.
I think, I don't know if there's a room with more unusual beakers.
Yeah.
More unusual colors.
There's one we'll bring up later.
So I'm just saying this is a, from a kid's perspective, from a kid's playground, I am very excited by this.
Yeah.
And it's very striking when you're there.
It's very striking.
It's a hell of a cue.
Great cue.
And you got that like sort of steampunk aesthetic, which I now, it's not fully Dr. Toosome-ish.
You know, I shouldn't, that shouldn't be my frame of reference for steampunk now.
But I do like the copper.
I do like...
Oh, copper's a good word to highlight.
Yes.
It's really...
Good crystals.
Yes.
And there's a...
There's a frenzy in this place.
And the character of who works in here, I think, is on display.
Yes.
Now, the problem is, because like, you know, there's this picture of it where it's like,
you can see into it from the cue, and that looks cool, and there's a little mystery in there.
A little claustrophobic in there.
It is a little claustrophobic.
And I think I am tying in, part of my affection is from the ride itself, steampunk aesthetic itself,
a lot of other factors.
And yes, the office, just independent, is probably less beautiful and pleasant as the Treehouse.
Yeah.
I mean, you almost can't expect it to be.
It can't be.
I know, I know, I know.
That's not the story that they're telling.
But when we think about, if we do care about, is this a space that you want to be in, I
don't know.
I think, I'm going to go with my gut, Jason's style, basketball style, and say Adventureland
Treehouse.
I am as well.
I agree with you.
Wow, that's a three-way.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, you know what, and so we're a little bit of discussion, because I think if we hadn't
highlighted the pleasantry of it, that mobile is just wonderful.
It's great.
Yeah.
I think the key to being in an office five days a week or so, or even a few split working
from home, is personalizing it, is making it comfortable for you.
Uh-huh, absolutely.
And that's why, what amenities have you recently added to the research for it, that make it
a place that is fun and not oppressive?
Oh, let's see, lots of water, the tower of morning, lunch, evening bedtime pills, trying
to stay on top of filling that up.
Great, all right.
Do you have necessities in there?
No decor, you haven't made a little origami bird that's dangling from the top of the fort?
No.
Okay, well that's an idea, maybe be inspired by the treehouse, by the decorations up on
the roof.
Trying to clean up, you know, I get a little addicted to iCloud tabs, I've got tabs on
the laptop, the iPad, the phone, and it's like, sometimes when I'm scatterbrained, I'm
just open it tabs, I'm never actually reading, you know, defector articles or like watching
videos or stuff that I put aside.
Well, this isn't, yeah, don't just open tabs, look at them, actually see the tab.
Anyone can open a tab, not everybody can enjoy what's in the tab.
No, no, I got a baby at home who can't do either, frankly, so we should appreciate what
we have as adults.
That's right.
Okay, next category, Expedition Everest versus Indiana Jones' office in the temple.
Wowee wowee.
Okay, Everest, what are some details of Everest?
This is very early into the queue of this attraction in Animal Kingdom, I see, I'm going
to be honest with you, I'm going to Indiana Jones right here and now.
Wow.
Yeah, I'm going to do that too.
There's photos and it's fine, it's fine, but I was just gearing up to like really give
the hard sell on this and you know what, I got to vote with my heart right here and now.
So if you guys are passionate about Everest, I will leave it to you to, what's that you
do?
You just voted for Indy.
Yeah, I just gave it to Indy.
Oh, that's all right, well that was fast.
Do you want to make a declaration?
I guess I was going to, I probably would have said Indy anyway, but I just, the Everest
queue and the office and everything, I think I've said this before, the first time I had
been back to Disney World in many years, look, I knew that was a line for a ride, but they
had made it so authentic that there were part of me that was looking at the things on the
desk and on the wall and going, oh, is this some of these real?
And then finally I'd get to, like for whatever reason, the Joe Roady touch gave that an authenticity
that I feel most fake offices and queues don't have, so I just want to highlight that.
But Indiana Jones, fair enough.
The detail is amazing, but Indiana Jones is a close personal friend, just like Spider-Man.
Now I would say perhaps everyone's affection for the man is doing a little heavy lifting
here.
It definitely colors it because we can imagine, this is an office that Indiana Jones has worked
in.
Famous man's office.
We don't even know, there's no characters that we know from the Everest ride, so yeah,
it's hard to unsee that.
I also, though, think it's a pretty foundational office in terms in this category of jungle
makeshifts.
I mean, I think it caused a lot of the other jungle makeshifts to occur, and it also occurred
to me that is Journey to the Center of the Earth right?
That's not really a jungle, whatever, too late.
It's already named that, and we're already through it, and that one's already out.
We can't edit it now.
No, there's no way to do that.
So at jungle makeshifts, it becomes Adventureland Treehouse versus Indiana Jones office, and
as we start to make it through, by the way, the spacious 16, we're in the spacious 16
right now, it'll get a little less spacious as we go.
The next area, another big area in terms of fake theme park offices that you run into
is Toondens.
Now, I said dens to keep it kind of tidy, but you might also call some of these studies.
I don't know exactly the difference.
I think there might be a subtle difference, but I think it could all fit under one umbrella.
Toondens, I have randomized the pairings.
Here are the pairings.
Well, you know what?
This was not a matchup that you wanted, Jason, but the randomizer gave it to us, so I think
we're stuck, unless you insist that we don't do it this way.
Mickey versus Minnie.
Wow.
Mickey's Den versus Minnie Mouse's home office.
Holy crap.
Holy, sorry, excuse me.
Holy fucking shit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't swear enough.
Sorry.
I apologize.
Well, hey, it is what it is.
We landed where we landed.
Mickey's Den is, I think we've put a lot of shine on.
We have made famous via the show and via a clip that we're fond of and that I trimmed
out and highlighted on our YouTube channel just to capitalize on all that viral traffic
of people looking for Mickey's Den.
But there's a special where he gives you a tour of his house, and this is in Mickey's
birthday land in the Magic Kingdom, which is no more, and he is pointing out different
rooms of the house, which are more functional than they are cartoon fun, as exemplified
by him ultimately saying, when I need to make a telephone call, I use the den.
Weird fake Mickey voice in a fake office in fake Mickey's house.
This actual place, I don't know if anybody's looking at photographs of it.
I pulled a few.
I got Mickey here.
I think what's interesting about this version of his house and this office especially, this
is not a silly cartoon place.
This is an office that conceivably Walt Disney himself could have had.
It's all real.
None of it is fun.
It's not like a big piece of cheese.
It's not like gigantic ear muffs that would fit over his head.
It's real items, most of which are like 50s era, including the phone that he uses, which
is a rotary and the kind where the earpiece is separate from the, now he needs this kind
of phone in 1989.
Or did they just determine this is better for a gigantic mouse's head because the only
way he's going to be able to make a phone call, he's stuck with the old technology.
But you see a globe, you see a light, you see framed photographs and there's a key to
a city or something up there.
It is not fun.
This is important to note.
This is where Mickey goes to make telephone calls, get work done.
Is there a cartoonish notepad or legal pad by that phone?
Not that I see.
It's all just, it's just like ledgers.
It's just like.
Got my chiropractors in here.
No, I've, look, I leave my, I leave the funny business on the screen, all right?
When I'm here, I'm here to work.
The whole fun colors.
Get those pinks and purples out of here.
I don't want to see that shit, it's not a birthday cake, it's an office.
Can I speak on Mickey's, Minnie's, Minnie's, excuse me.
Yes, because Minnie's is extremely different.
This is, now this is a different era.
This is pure Toontown.
We are in full cartoon territory here.
Yeah.
Um, it almost reminds me and like Downton Abbey, the valet's room, with all the clothes
and stuff.
But I think the thing that has me leaning towards Minnie is, similarly to the phone,
it is now anachronistic, I feel like, but that bulky beige desktop computer.
Yeah, I'm seeing it as pink.
Whatever version I'm looking at is bright pink.
And what Minnie has here, Mike, you brought this up in the, I think this candidate is
here because of you in the pre-show that we did.
Yes, thank you for giving me credit.
And yes, of course, well, you're looking out for your girl, and I respect that.
The photo that you showed before was a little bit further away, and now that I've seen,
I haven't been in this room in a very long time, and now that I'm seeing into the contents
of Minnie's computer, I notice a couple of important things.
One, it is shaped like a heart.
It is a custom type of screen that no other computer screen is.
Yeah.
Gotta give points for that.
It also is a magic clueless before clueless type outfit customizing machine.
There is no, there are no letters.
There's no QWERTY on this keyboard.
If she wanted to type a letter, she couldn't.
This computer exists for you to design an outfit for her, and the keys are just eight
giant keys, just like here's blue, here's pink, here's stripes, here's classic Minnie
polka dots.
This is a fine machine.
This is a quality machine.
It's awesome.
Yeah.
And then you say the computer is heart, but other things in the office are heart.
The mirror is a heart, and the dressing, whatever you call that thing.
The board that you only used in 40s movies where actresses would change backstage and
drape the dresses over the...
A screen.
A dressing screen.
Minnie's dressing screen.
Yeah, so that's a heart as well.
So she's got an aesthetic.
There's a little heart at the top of the, what would you call it?
I can't think of anything today.
The shelves.
There's a little heart.
So she has hearts everywhere.
I don't think any of us have truly designed an office because we don't know the names
of the things that would go with them.
Desk, a dress.
It's a desk with a shelf above it.
Bureau.
Bureau, no.
Well, that would be...
So her little area is awesome, and in a different picture, she has a chaise lounge there too
as well.
So she does her stuff.
She does her business.
She does her work there, and it's a ton, obviously, more personality than Mickey's boring office.
And I also think maybe that office of Mickey's is showing his true personality.
It's all business.
He doesn't have any whimsy.
That's all bullshit.
That's all an act.
He doesn't give a fuck about whimsy and fun.
The writers write this stuff.
Yeah, they tell me who I am.
A bunch of nerds.
I had a bunch of guys on goofballs.
Funny stuff comes out, I guess.
A team of people to put all this shit in here.
I don't know what half this shit is, I don't know where it is.
I just like to see this with Minnie, because it's more what I think Minnie is, and Minnie's
true to herself.
I think Minnie is more who she is on screen, which is what I like to know and to see.
Totally, but I have to be true to myself.
I frankly am too fond of this den.
I feel like this is something...
This was a thing I got locked in on and brought to the show.
I can't possibly vote against the den.
I would not be mad if it went the other way, but I think I'd be betraying my friend Mickey,
who is also being true to himself.
His hard-edged, all-business nature.
He doesn't need an outfit customizing machine.
He's got one.
His suit.
He puts on his suit.
He goes to his desk.
He makes a phone call.
He gets the job done, and that's why I'm locking in Mickey's Den.
Wow.
Mickey's Den.
But it's not fun.
I'm going Minnie.
Yeah, I'm going Minnie too.
Wow.
I knew it.
It was kind of a protest vote in a way, but I'm also not...
In the broad scheme of things, I am not at all upset to have this Minnie computer.
I was more sold on the computer by the time I described it out loud than when I started.
If Minnie's job is kind of modeling or being stylish or being fashionable, that's labor.
In women's, what is traditionally called women's work is undervalued.
Certainly from the ball and chain, I've learned quite a bit about styling.
That was one of the best moments.
You're talking about how styling is good to be nice to her, but then you called her a
ball and chain.
That was the best combo ever.
Well, I was trying to be...
I meant that affectionately.
You've been married for several days.
I thought, yeah, I've been married for seven days.
She's the ball and chain.
That's a little bit of what Fred Mertz would use to describe...
Yeah, I'm true to myself, goddammit.
You're in character.
That's your model of an ideal marriage.
My beloved wife has taught me so much about the ideas that are communicated or stories
that are told with how you dress and stuff, and I read the menswear guy is always dunking
people on Twitter and learning about the history of clothes.
So I'm very interested in this.
Sure.
Well, I agree that Minnie is doing work.
You never heard me say otherwise.
And it's fun.
She's got her own place.
She's her own woman.
You have never heard me say otherwise.
I've never heard you say otherwise.
I am on the record.
I know.
He voted for Minnie.
For years.
I voted.
If anything, I need to be scolded.
Yes, Scott needs to be scolded.
Mickey tells stories, too.
Here's the story.
Dumbo's asking for more money.
Oh, really?
What's the name on the top of the Walt Disney Productions?
And what built that empire?
Me.
These big ears.
Not your big ears.
Stay in line.
You're saying Mickey.
I'll ship you off to Fleischer.
These lights are too bright in here.
Take the bulbs out.
I want to be in the darkness.
The guy who designed this thing.
Get the old light bulbs.
Are you trying to get me migraines?
I want the ones that last three months and then they just explode.
I don't want this new LED shed.
I want a hole in the floor that can open up when I hit a button.
And I don't want things powered by windmills anymore, okay?
All right.
Windmills, ooh.
They kill birds.
They kill everything.
I like that about them.
They kill Clara Kluck.
Can't you hear me?
I can't hear you.
I can't hear you, sir!
That's why I don't see her in the cartoons anymore!
What are you saying?
I was just a good woman!
He made love for many years!
We get it.
Mickey does not have a good work-life balance.
He sure doesn't.
But we all benefit from it.
We all benefit.
We get to have fun in his places.
He's kind of, he does it for our sins.
He's kind of a Christ-like figure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mhm.
It seems like good art to Christ.
Jerky Christ.
I'm sure art that exists, Mickey.
Yeah.
On the cross.
Okay.
I classified both of these as studies. I think that's fair. It's mr
Toad's study from mr. Toad's wild ride and it's Bowser's study from the queue for
Mario Kart
Koopa's challenge. Is that what it is? Is that what the name of the ride?
Is it Bowser's change isn't it somewhere isn't it? But isn't it weirdly Koopa somewhere?
Yeah, well, it's called Bowser's challenge in Japan in Japan. Oh was challenge. So I'm not pulling that
Things like we're Eggman is the name of the villain in Japan and it's Robotnik here inside. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I think so
Yeah, all right. Well, I'm glad Bowser's challenge is here. Yeah foolishness now. I think in the episode
We were talking about this as if it was a Badger's office
I mean, I think that's how it was suggested to us, but on reflection it you're in Toad Hall
It's got to be Toad's office and there's paintings of Toad on the wall
Badger's just in there leaning on one of those
Yeah bookshelf ladders the lie on wheels and having a hard time of it. He's holding too many books. He's slipping around
Mr. Toad's paintings are
Fantastic. There's one where he seems to be unless I'm just looking at it from a weird warped angle
Maybe it's our maybe it's of relatives or something. I feel like I'm looking at a Parisian Toad
With like a with a goatee. Yeah a little with the mustache and the little then the little wispy beard
And then I look more of an English more of a stuffy tea drinking
Monocle wearing Toad. Yeah, this is a very nice room. It's the first room that you enter in the ride
It's where your madcap journey begins. It's a very well decorated bookshelf. There's lots going on on there
There's a ship up at the top. We got globes
There's a lot of items we're gonna see throughout and that might the devil might be in the details here
We might have to we might find ourselves going which is the best globe, which is the best telescope?
Yeah, he's also got a pile of papers that have stacked up presumably because he's out
Show boating and racing around instead of getting his work done. Whatever that is
I don't really remember much about mr. Toad and what he does besides go on wild rides and take you to hell
Is badger mr. Toad solicitor? I
Couldn't tell you a lawyer maybe oh, maybe oh, yeah. Oh, that's a good question. I don't know
He's obviously in the in there doing some sort of research. She's pulling books off the shelf on the big ladder. Yeah
So he's obviously working in some capacity for mr. Toad. Yeah
so
Did you have a reason why you were asking about this? Well now I was just trying to figure out why he's in there
No, I mean, I guess it could be some sort of recreational thing, but I don't it doesn't seem like it. Mm-hmm
Yeah, it's just the feeling I get I think he makes other people do his dirty work
Yeah, I mean, I think boring stuff
Everyone's sort of annoyed with Toad because Toad is the one who acts wild and they have to reign him in
You know, like everyone is sort of in like everyone is lower than Toad status wise
But that's the frustrating thing is that he's reckless. Well, and he's a fool. Well, yes, it's a reckless fool
Mm-hmm, but he but he gets his and a lesson that we all learn
Right when we when we are taken to hell just like in in real life. Mm-hmm. All bad people go to hell
That's right. You know this we believe
then we move to
Bowser's
Study office, whatever you want to call it
I think that we have been pretty rough on this ride and I think that this ride has been rough on us frankly
Yeah
So it would be kind of a change of heart to give some shine to something
From the Mario Kart ride and it is very tempting to do so because every
Picture you see of this I've only been in this room once because I try to avoid this line and frankly the ride
I've gone back to this very much
I got to do it in like a single rider way where I'm skipping a lot of this stuff
But Mike you and I did it one time and if you're gonna get stuck in a theme park room for a while
This is a good room to get stuck in it is great
I've maybe never seen maybe not never but like it's right. I think it's rare to see
Q with this many details with funny jokes with nods to the vast rich Mario universe
There's so many great book titles. Yeah, he's got blueprints on the wall. You get to see where Bowser
Creates his minions like you get a sense of his process of how he designs a bullet bill of how he designs those wind-up toys
like
Like and it's also and he does it all from like a almost religious feeling space
It's like somewhere. It's it feels like a castle obviously, but it also kind of feels like a temple
I mean, it's it's remarkable and I don't think a space that you've I have no idea. There's been a lot of games
Maybe Bowser's office has been shown in the games
But it's not instantly familiar to me, but it answers a lot of questions
It tells me a lot about Bowser's character and I just really like this room. Yes, you're right
I mean, there's something that very cathedrally about some of the like windows in there. Yeah. Yes, it is
It really shows off his character as you're saying like there's a there's a pen. There's like a quill there
That's how he writes. Mm-hmm. So like he is a he's a
Dinosaur writes with a quill exactly so you are getting which is important
I think some for the office what Jason was saying earlier you make it your own
Shows your personality off. Mm-hmm, and I think you're absolutely right
You don't get this glimpse into Bowser's life
And if you just went through the queue of the Mario Kart ride, you would go. Oh my god
I'm but this is about to be the greatest ride of all time
Yes, so detailed such a usually with a long detailed queue. You're gonna get a really good ride very rarely
I feel like is there a ride with this good of a queue that
That not good of a bum people out. Yes. Yeah, perhaps a superior queue to a ride
I
Don't want to prolong it. I mean, it's just it's a hard competition
It's a very detailed office, you know, you know a world of IP that I love I'm going Bowser
Yeah, well I the thing about Bowser. He's always kind of monofocused on his goal
Yeah, right taking over the Mushroom Kingdom. Mm-hmm
Uh
Wooing the princess
Invading a nice way to put it. Yeah, he's using his office a lot. Mm-hmm
He's he's got a lot of business perhaps more than Mickey. I think they have similar workloads
I think they would actually get along very well. I
He's the kind of guy you want on your side not to be an enemy maybe new CEO for Disney Bowser
What do you think replace? I?
Need a firm and you know, you need somebody doesn't take shit doesn't create her to the woke mob
Traditional values of being openly evil somebody's mad and they criticize just get the airship and fly
Yeah, I don't know what do you guys think
Bowser
Well, I was gonna yeah, I agree Bowser I was gonna say toad toads office isn't crazy enough for toad honestly
Yeah, it's well, I think I think you get there, you know, there's it's similar, right?
Egotistical character but that is more evident in the exterior in the building
Made in his image where his image is shown very much and in the statues of him
And then the grandeur and the pomposity right is you know, they actually these are well paired
They have a lot in common both green as well
But ultimately I think Bowser's is a more is just a bigger manifestation of the egotistical character
design wise I think toads office is
more
library than office
Yeah, does that make sense?
I even had the question putting it in who is it an office and there is a desk so it ends up the desk ends up
Being kind of the you know the deciding factor
As it might be in some of these and this is another one where we might have to knock one out before we go
This is very competitive. But by the way, the next matchup will be
Intune den's minis office versus Bowser's study. Wow, I like that pairing. Holy shit
so
This area I call sci-fi and labs and this is extremely competitive
I would say we have the MIB headquarters from men in black alien attack
We have the collector's office from guardians of the galaxy mission breakouts in California adventure
We have what I keep calling the cool girl lab from spaceship earth
The representation of computer science in the 60s and 70s you have the professor's office
From Kingdom of the dinosaurs kind of a little kind of a sleeper
This is the first scene in this defunct dark ride from Knott's Berry farm
Right before time travel begins and then you have
one of the grandest labs ever made
the laboratory in flight of passage
in Avatar in the world of Pandora
So one of these has to go
Do we have to reason it out or do we just pick one? Hmm. I
Hmm, I've got two that I would put on the chopping block. Okay two on the chop. Okay
The
Professor's office from Kingdom of the dinosaur. Mm-hmm. I love whimsy, but I just I never saw I just don't know it as well
It's hard. It feels hard like doomed. But also when we discovered it in the episode, it's just like it's a fun silly place
It's got a time machine. Yeah, he's a kooky guy teetering in a chair. Yeah, I do wish I knew it more but he sounds like this
He's one of these guys. Oh, no, the time machine's not ready and there's a big dial and there's shelves
I you know to me. It's a little more of an office than
Pandora than avatar which is so clearly a lab
It's just so I know that we're allowing labs, but it's so much more
Other one it's more lab than office and we spend so much time in the second gate. Mm-hmm
Like scratching our heads about this one. I know I know
but well
One move could be deciding now
Labs are out because I don't know that you'd even call it a lab in the in Kingdom of the dinosaurs and you put in doc
on dar
Like just make it fair
And all labs are out
Yes, all labs are out labs are out. All right. I like the less. Okay, so what this has now become is
And apologies to the lab, but I do think it's a different category and it's you know
We got through an entire episode without realizing it perhaps making that episode a waste of time
No, but now that we're here. No
Like every episode it's not erased it there is an office in there's another office in
There's the makeshift garage office in in spaceship. I was thinking about that too. Yes. There is the pseudo Steve jobs
Well, this this throws us for a loop. I mean, I like it and I I think it's a very peaceful zone
Yeah, I don't want it in here, but it is if you don't want it in here
Then it shouldn't be in but I like that
I like that he has a Fleetwood Mac poster in there that is that makes me have it's nice to see very nice to see them
In a dark red. Yeah. Um, okay, so flight of passages out labs are out. This is now sci-fi
Not labs sci-fi it is and let me throw it into the randomizer so we don't have time to overthink these pairings
This is a very important step and we now
Throw it in and we get this
Okay, the first pairing is men in black
Versus doc on dars little room in his den of antiquities
Okay. Well, you know the thing about the doc on our one you go to a small business
Especially a knickknack shopper an antique store if they got the door to the back open
You're gonna see a little desk with a stack of papers
Probably an eight-year-old Dell computer and they got to do payroll, you know, they got to pay rent
They got to do all this stuff
That said men in black alien attack is so elaborate
It's a giant bullpen. There is a break room as you exit
Mm-hmm
There is technically a lobby even though it's a swerve
Yes, true, but I think I think you got a judge judge it for office
And I think mainly and you could take these other things into account, but I think you mainly have to
focus on that main
room where the most desks are and where there's announcements from ripped horn and
You know like arrivals of
aliens
And that room is a pretty spectacular room. That is a tough one to deny
What do you think Mike is the one who brought doc on dollar into this very recently?
I think there's a lot of things like the little alien break room that
Technically if you're considering the whole thing in office
That's part of it and look the design of men in black and the way that the office looks is really cool
And they've recreated it in a perfect way
But I think the details and doc on dar if you really take a look
There's little trinkets. There's things on the wall. There's like these cool weapons that are behind him
He's got like a big book that he looks through when he's looking for the prices for things
I just think this little zone is one of my favorite parts of Galaxy's Edge. It's the promise of Galaxy's Edge
It's a new character in the Star Wars universe, and you're it's just a gift shop
There's no he doesn't need to be in there, but I love peering in here
For a longer than your average
Park-goer when I'm in doc on dars and I think
That this was we as we're saying you get a character you get his personality
You get what he's all about even though he doesn't really talk. He just looks over and I love it
And I think I would vote for doc on door over men in black Wow
Well, let me throw out this the men in black bullpen a lot of desks a lot of papers
cups with pens and pencils and that cool oval screen
The cool again aesthetically very cool and a lot of it
I think for is the excitement of oh wow it's the office from the movie, which is a very well-designed office
Yeah, but it is
sterile and
Yes while impressive I just there's there's not as many details in it as you're getting from the hominess of
the doc on dar space
I agree with everything that you said in you
I like that we have taken some time to highlight this particular space with it that the den itself is great and the little room
In the den is the highlight the space is wonderful. I appreciate the passion that said not a chance men in black
Wow, yeah men in black as well
Potentially go although I really favor I just it's of course everything you said was right. There was not one error
I'm glad that he got some time on this podcast, but there's no way men in black so cool
I agree men in black so cool. I just got aliens to one more. It's also a unique
It's like he's in like a you a little UFC cage or like a UFC cage in the middle of his gift shop
I am glad you highlighted. There's like a weird like abacus thing going on
System of counting that I mean you're I'm gonna end up talking myself and you focus on even everything else
I mean like that's sort of above it the different lights the different details
Yeah, it's cool, but it's isn't well. Maybe it's more of a of a pen and a den
It's certainly a pen, but it is his office
That's where he does all his work, and it is lived in and it's and you know what it feels like very
Classically Star Wars does everything Star Wars you want Star Wars to do with like an entire world is
Implied with it with it isn't really they don't tell you everything it's just like here's cut to this
This feels so real and lived in one of the tries things that still to this day hold up for me as far as galaxies
I just concerned yeah, but the sterility of men of black
I don't think we've seen sterility a lot and isn't that a big element of
Real offices, but I also don't find all that sterile. We'll have to well
You know let's get to it in the next
Different type of sterility we're talking about we'll see what if it ends up against something more whimsical
Which it undoubtedly will via the next matchup, which is the collector's office and guardians and the professor's office from Kingdom of the dinosaurs
We could good we could do this for a while or we could do I mean it's pretty obvious
I'm really happy Kingdom of the dinosaurs is in there, but it's the collector's off. Yeah
Yeah, no cotton. I'm sorry professor. I really like it
People have asked for a little while about a kingdom of the dinosaurs episode at least on the second gate
I'd love to do that. Yeah, I'd love to hear this guy's voice more. I'd like to watch the video
Where Gary Owens goes through the ride?
with some other guy
We'll we will give proper shine to this professor, but come on. It's yeah the ends unfortunately
This is a tough. This is a tough category so men in black goes up against Guardian
Collectors office, which could be a I mean that that feels like it could be the final right there
Well, it's gonna have to get decided before that so that leaves us with kind of the unclassifiable with the grab bag
With the leftovers, but that's no way to put it because some of these are
pretty damn spectacular
And so I will throw these into the randomizer. Yes one especially. I think we've all been salivating
over a certain one of these
So let's do it. It is going to be I think it's the same order that I put in
All right
Here's the well. Let's just do the first two
Tiana's office in the line for Tiana's by Tiana's bio adventure and
Bluto's office from the line
For Popeye and Bluto's build rat barges is that correct it is
Now something funny about this because this was suggested by a listener
And this came up in the pre show that we did on the patreon and something that I thought was very funny
Was that I just described it because I couldn't get the photo to load
I just said oh, you know what Bluto has an office you guys didn't see a photo sight unseen when I said
So is it in yeah, it's in no. That's in that'll be in the pop
I love is so strong you didn't even need to see a photograph to know with absolute certainty
Bluto's office it could have been in like eight inch by eight inch drawing in like a little like portal or porthole or something
And it's just like you've peered in and I would have yeah. Yeah, it's in
Bluto's office
Doesn't matter could have been a scrambled tiny photograph 50 by 50 pixels
It's not what it could have been literally an announcement while you're in the line
Describing the office that you never see and I would approve it being in this
Like here's what he has. He's got a desk and he's got a telescope and well
Let's now that now let me show the photo which isn't much better than the quality that you're describing what I did get my apologies
I don't have it in front of me what a listener sent this but here's what is in
Bluto's office a classic cage off as we find in a lot of these lines. Yeah, we have a desk we have
Framed photo of himself. Yeah, we have a big yellow trophy
we have a
Treasure chest and then a bunch of loose treasure
That is piling up and then we have a cannon as a cannon. That's really good
So it is really really good. Yeah framed photo of yourself in the in an office is kind of
Psychopathic. Mm-hmm. He's bluto
Yeah, he is a traditional keel you want to see him lose you want to see him eat shit the original American Psycho
That's right. Yeah, that's right. You would say it. Yeah, Patrick Bateman
I hear they're remaking American Psycho with bluto in that role
but still
Still with Christian Bale. He's he is dick Cheney style
Going to style himself as blue. He's slowly turning himself into bluto
No gaining even more weight growing a big beard no one asked him to do that they hired they said no
This is a voice role. Yeah, you will not be seen
Who is in the new America? Did they and is it Austin Butler? Is that right?
I don't know is it I thought they were remaking or maybe like there was chatter with it
Is there a casting or did you see like more Jacob a little Josh Gadd? I believe did you see some like a I add on
Facebook that no, no, I thought it was a dead. It might just be in development
I thought maybe there was just names turn around there was a musical too. I don't think they're adapting
There's an Austin Butler announcement. Oh for American Psycho suck. Yeah, okay. Wow. Yeah, I could do yeah, you know
I'll go a little psycho. Yeah. Yeah, that's right
so
Bluto's office is pretty it's pretty strong. I have to say it is from saying those items. It's very good
Tiana's office inspired this entire thing and reminded us that we like this area. We're not be here without Tiana
It's a very there's a very simple just stylish chair. There's a typewriter
There's a good amount of space despite it being you know, a little corner. It's a solid desk
It's she's got framed photos of of other people people that she cares about
She's got a there's a little table with a box of chocolates and ginger ale aka Jason's go-to lunch
Tiny cans
so it's almost on par with the
Treehouse where you're just like, oh what a perfect space that I a human man
Yeah, I'd like to sit in and work of all the of a lot of what we've talked about
Yes, this would be high on the list of what I would like to where I would like to go what feels like a
Productive space right just well chosen a very appealing color of wood
Nice splash is a color and the queue is one of the the things that I think improve
On Splash Mountain. I think the key of Tiana's is better than Splash Mountain
Exterior of the queue and this office is a huge part of it
Yeah, natural light or at least the simulation of natural light
With artificial lights and the bright. Yeah
This might be highest on my list of where I think I where if you had to be nice to work out
To do it get a little bit of work done. It might be here
Pluto I am even I was calling to me
I
Wasn't where I started thinking about I like what like when I was staring at this matchup, I'm like it's well, obviously
It's Tiana. Let's let's be adults here. But then I don't know once I said
The randomizer putting this together. Yes, there's treasure. There's a big can. Did you were you about to vote Tiana? I
Actually was you were about to betray Popeye. I was you know, T
Well, no, I was gonna defeat Pluto's so if anything I'm honoring
Where does wimpy's allegiance lie when it comes to Pluto hamburgers?
His god is hamburgers
He's office and it was just a drawing of wimpy's office. You would have voted wimpy's office, right? Oh, yeah
Yeah, or even if it was um, oh god, what's a cook's name hard?
Rough house rough house. Yeah, if it was rough houses kitchen. I would went kitchen off kitchen is office
It's it goes to rough house. You're mad at Pluto. That's partly why you don't want him to win
Yeah, or where does the goon do their business?
I know look we can list all Popeye characters
We know when we could hypothetically we could it does sound like the kind of thing that would happen on this podcast
Yeah, yeah might have happened already
Yes, but keep in mind the longer you go within I'd say five you would ruin it
You would run into one that is completely wrong and those years would comment that you are wrong about this pop
Okay, see Hags we work
Great. There's something there. Yeah, so blue. So yeah blues. I
Don't know the thing I was about to say is gonna would tip a potential other matchup. So I won't even say
Yeah, no, let's save any you know, it's hard that there's a can there's a cart and here's also important
Yeah, it's not a practical looking cannon. It looks like a drawn cannon
That's the thing that makes it extra appealing is because so much of this is rendering things from a cartoon in real space like Bowser
It's like yeah, they actually made it look like to scale of what he looked like in the real world
This looks like a cartoon cannon a cartoon treasure chest and in the same way that Minnie's office is so appealing
This is so appealing. This is why I'm voting for Pluto realism kind of goes against
I don't know. Sometimes it's not not the most fun to boat. He's got a big trophy, right? Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's great
He sure does I'll make sure that this photo is distributed. So you all have it in front of you, right?
But we move now to the next one
Maybe the most interesting matchup in the entire affair the daily bugle from the amazing adventures of spider-man and island islands of adventure
versus the
oval office in conservative pollsters
conservative pollster Frank Luntz's house now if you didn't hear the pre episode
You might be very confused as to how we got here. Well, we got here because the the spider-man ride
I guess a lot of people like and then obviously Frank Luntz's house was right sure shot from the beginning
We there was a discussion of I threw out at the end of the of the pre episode on the second gate
Do we need to honor that across this country?
There are a lot of fake oval offices exact recreations of oval offices typically in presidential libraries
There's a number of those it seemed like a good category to honor Mike
You somehow had the fact in your head that conservative pollster Frank Luntz has an oval office in his house
Do you had that locked it you had that somewhere back in the recesses? Yeah, of course. Yeah, it's something
I don't know when I learned about it
there was definitely a period of time when I watched a lot of like MSNBC and
I guess to some degree CNN and Fox News to see what was going on
It was very I knew all the players
I still seem to know a lot of the play
I don't watch a lot of that anymore because why would you watch any of it? But I
Yes, Frank Luntz is a guy who is on these shows
He's he's on Fox News a lot and then he's on that he comes on the liberal ones to like once in a while
represents the conservative POV
Yes, and I feel like he often does those very annoying polls focus group
Yes, does he do the folks?
Yes, where he's sitting on one side and then there's ten people and and you are reminded that the median voter in America is insane
Like someone like an old woman will just come out and go like there should be universal income. We're a country of plenty
Also, every teacher should be fucking strapped every teacher should be armed
But we should all have government health care and you're like what?
What what is your life? Yeah, what are you doing now?
This is it is on us more than ever to try to take away
The character of who's in the office because in a world where we've got
Indiana Jones one of our favorite characters on earth and it's kind of impossible to untangle here
We have a guy who frankly I didn't know about before
Now the thing I made a point of not learning more because I don't want it to be about him
I want it to be about his office
We also learned in this episode that there's a number of unusual things in his house
I kept going and looking at more. Yeah, one of them being
that
He has a bunch of written accounts of from people who were physically present when babe Ruth
Called his shot when he pointed and then hit the home run where he pointed
He's got a bunch of people and then I looked up and I saw he pointed and I said why what for was he pointing out?
A criminal stealing a purse in the crowd, but sure enough knows where he's gonna hit a home run
And sure as hell he did seems like should be in a Library of Congress
Indiana Jones would say they belong to me
I wish this was the matchup. Maybe we can get it. I was gonna say if he wins
if the
Indiana Jones versus Frank Luntz
All right
Here we go
Daily bugle. All right, let's go through the daily bugle
This is a full not just an office but an office building one that has aged
Properly when it started it was a newspaper
Office in the 90s then newspapers went out of fashion and now it's a perfect
Anachronistic setting of late 90s newspapers and you got file folders
You've got the newspaper bullpen. You got a darkroom. You've got loading. You've got everything in here
including one of my
Unseen holy grails that weird silver statue of J Jonah Jameson in the overflow queue
All right. Well, I can make lists too. You've got Kennedy's desk
but Obama's chairs and George W Bush's side tables and
Every president since Truman is represented in this greatest hits oval office
It's kind of the oval office that never was he's even got a buck stops here sign
When you enter the room a curtain opens up and hail to the chief plays
This is and keep in mind, you know, they have to dress things up for us in a theme park
They've got paying customers in there, but you know Frank, this is his home. He didn't have to do that production value
Right. He's just having run-of-the-mill folks over, you know, like Clint Eastwood Warren Beatty Tim Allen and Tony Blair
He's just having salt of the earth people over maybe just to have a dinner in a chat and he gives them a little show
And makes them reflect for a minute about the great history of the great men who run this country
That's something this is a dangerous
He should go to the El Salvador prison. We cannot trust this man in the light society
Well, it seems suddenly you you all don't want to talk about Tim Allen as much as he usually do
well, that's I do but
He also you know 45 minutes out of episode, you know, obviously there's like fun whimsy and spider-man's cue
But obviously Frank also like in his area has Colonel Clink's outfit from Hogan's heroes
So he's a fan of movies TV and music as well. So it's you're getting sort of an else world's
Where Colonel Clink is hanging out with the president's?
You might say in Frank Luntz's overall Frank Luntz has his own universe
Okay, the Daily Bugle has my other friends Betty Brandt
Robbie whose last name I forget Ben Eurek J Jonah Jameson
Yes, but but that's the office
I want to visit and live in but Frank when his mother died
He thought about how in his rise in politics
He was never able to take his dear mother to the Oval Office despite all the access that he got
And so when she died he thought what better way to honor her memory than to do a full-scale
Multi-million dollar recreation of the Oval Office in my house. Wouldn't mom be proud?
Troubling it's trouble. Okay, it is troubling
Political views are wrong. But I tried I don't even know what they are. That's how much I am lock it
I've locked myself out of whatever the hell this guy's like a decorum Republican guy. We're like mr. Trump in his rudeness that being said
Yeah, he likes still he's just just to trump to you know, you're like a Lincoln project
Fully Lincoln project, but that's another discussion as a man who has a big collection me
Michael I have to appreciate
the effort into
recreating something you love
not with a budget of a theme park, but a
budget of a humble pollster a humble
Humble newsman Brentwood living
pollster yes, is this the episode where eight years and I finally burst into tears
Mike Mike and I are mostly talking to each other while we do this and then we will turn over and see Jason's face and
Your face is like shrunk as we like so much are you scrunching that it feels like your features are smaller in your head
Because you're glaring so much. I already have the deal like social media this year has been like oh and then wicked wicked
Okay, that could be dr. Doom could be wicked launching and the defying gravity on the Incredible Hulk coaster
and that is that's like
Rotten Disney brain of like just call them rotten to even suggest that dr. Doom becomes
I think doing a hit move like box office hit of the year and
transforming
26 year old watt rides is insane when they're full of expansion pads at Universal parks
That's my thing, but I'm like the thought of losing my friends spider-man and the X-Men. I'm like
Might be the thing that
Start going falling down
You know, I don't want to I don't want to cause that
Manipulate me right now into voting for spider-man without working out my feelings about Frank Lutz
He is holding me hostage right now with his mental health
Yes, it is I think it's it's insidious quite frankly
Yeah, yeah the hobgoblin in that ride for whatever reason I'm doing
Keep guests like girl boss to you
Trying to get what I want
That is what he's trying to do and it's we've never had a situation in a Final Four like this before where I am being
manipulated into not
Express I'm just expressing thoughts. We needed to work this out in case Frank Lutz doesn't go any further
We have to do we need this this needs to be a safe space for holding space if that terms even still allowed
Or if it needs to Frank goes against your expansion. I
Unlike are the present I will honor the votes of this election
So, you know, I'm throwing my hat in for the Daily Bugle you guys can say whatever you want and I'll honor it
Okay, whether win or lose the balls in our court now Frank
Chicken Frank Luntz and J Jonah Jameson are similar types of people in a way
I think they would appreciate each other's impact in the measures of spider-man right, but politically I bet they align
Let's be honest at least on a lot of issues
You know run for office in the past been mayor of New York the Kingpins been mayor of New York
Matt Murdoch's been district attorney, of course, of course
Yes, so I don't I don't know where he lies
Probably more median voter J. Jonas Jameson probably would be in the type of Franklin's focus groups. That's probably right
There's a lot of great little
Things about spider-man, you know, it says like Ditko place, you know, there's little references
Spider-man's creators only match up in on earth
I think where you would not be just like frothing with spider-man excitement. This is the only this is
Like how did it land here? I don't know. That's just the happens. That's happenstance
Look Mike's role on the show. One of them is he's just asking questions
Yes, I am. Yes, and I try to work things out
I don't want it. I don't always want to just go I you know what you guys are going with your guts today
I'm not I'm going with my brain. I'm going with my thoughts not my belly. So what are you gonna go with?
Now look now the curtain the curtain slides back choose your favorite Michael
Scott
That doesn't help yeah, that's a one-way ticket to Huntsville I am being emotionally manipulated here
Frank Jones owns a recreation of Monica Lewinsky's blue dress. That is true again
Doesn't he own something that the Beach Boys used to record pet sounds? Yes. Yeah. Yeah some filth some box. I don't know
Equalizer imagine you could record an amazing
Classic album in the Oval Office that is well, this is changes the rule like that changes
The scenario it's not just the president's it's it's the different thing. Imagine they record a Beach Boys album in the Oval Office
That's reality in Franklin's most likely to happen in 2025 and it's ever been before
They record it quite a bit in the Oval Office. It's called the Nixon tape
Listen to my wild-haired brother Dennis, I like what you're saying dick aren't as good
That guy knew Manson can't trust him lock him up. I
I think the spider-man ride is held up
Just amazingly the updates they've done to it. It's still one of the top three five rides on the planet Earth
He just won another award. It's such a good legacy
The queue isn't as fun as though like the queue is really good
The ride is amazing. I love the ride
But how crazy are we
How crazy are we is the question
Just gonna stare each other in the eyes figure it out. Normally I would edit out this long
Are we gonna go no, no, this is but I know that I think is it's real. This is real
It's real. This is I gotta look we gotta look each other in the eyes
Jason is racing as if his plane is going down. He's holding. I think the audience is too
I think the you will never see a bigger turn
Well, as we talk Scott now as we talk I start to feel powerful
I'm starting to Mike is like
Finally John Cena turns heel on Cody Rhodes. Oh, he'll Michael power flowing through my body right now
I
Is like the rock and he's just dragging his finger my eyes are closed
My eyes are closed and I am ready to ascend to a higher plane
As I make one of the most important decisions of my life, not just this show
What am I going to choose?
Frank Luntz's
oval office recreation or
the spider-man queue for miles of adventure
Which one
Which one air dripping with tension, so it's all I choose
This is gonna be the final I think either way the final two the final two
It's just we just have to make the toughest call
We're gonna breeze through the rest, but we're making the toughest one the toughest call right now, unfortunately
That's just how this works. Sometimes when we do these I
I
I'm going to choose
What do you think I know what you're gonna say you're gonna say Frank Luntz's
That what do you think I'm gonna say I don't think I know either
Jason thinks I think I know chance that you last-minute beer that you see you
Since Spidey in your heart and I think you've been wearing that hot stuff the little devil t-shirt a lot
Mmm, and some of his wiliness has rubbed off does Frank Luntz have a life-size hot stuff the little devil in his offices
I don't know. We don't know. Oh, yeah, I'm gonna take his collection and stuff out of there. You gotta think so
Yeah, it's all in the office. You can't bring things from his other rooms in you can't bring his babe Ruth letters in here
Yeah, cuz doesn't have a mini mart or a supermarket or yeah
No, and Frank's market doesn't count and Frank's diner doesn't count either all the things in this bad man
's house
But he could bring things into the office and then they're part of it it's here's the thing also
It's not static like these other offices. He can move things around that gives an advantage to more likely to yes to update things
Items from you know, each each new horrendous president who is elected
Coke button or the or the basket of poise right that makes it special that makes it modular that makes it a different
Type of experience that's unlike any of the other experiences on this list and an experience will never have unless
This episode causes us to get invited to Frank Luntz's house. We are going to the house
Once this episode comes out. No one has talked about this dumb office as much as we have
It was a Hollywood reporter article from 2016 and no one knows dormant ever since right and for some reason I know I saw
News show where he's giving a tour of it when oh my god
And then you said the phrase and I've just been in love ever since there's been little heart the hearts of
Hearts of flutter next to my head ever since this magical phrase was said but I'll say this we've talked about it
so much so that I think I
Think the chunk we've done now on it is enough to get us invited as I vote for spider-man Wow Wow
Well, then I will say to honor all of this
That I I think like I will use my vote to honor not Frank Luntz the man
But Franklin says oval office okay his house. It's not about him. It's about the desk. It's about the horse riding statue
It's not about his American flag shoes, which are unfortunate
And I think if I'd shown you that right before I would have
Deeper into spider-man viewpoint might call those a very
disrespectful
Flag every day
Trump requires America. He wants people to have red white and blue in their hair
That's the preferred uniform these days that must boy took a shit on the carpet go go scoop it up with their
Alright well that finally completes the spacious 16
It was certainly spacious in the amount of time we took to talk about it. I Mike I thank you for creating that tension
And friend for you know giving this the strange discovery a little bit of shine
But I think we call for breaks in the episode if we were gonna
Yeah, we can't break let's put one here, and when we come back the ergonomic eight
Okay, we are back now
fake office funnel for for the
ergonomic eight
Nice and pared down. You know we're not as spacious as it was and I I like where we focused
I think this is a very strong
You know all jokes aside. I think this is the right group of eight. I feel good about it
I do think that we should do the mental exercise in the other categories
Could lunch have beat it I I know yeah question
We can ask of a number of these because it would just it would just be interesting to know
I agree, so let's start with back in the territory of jungle makeshifts where we landed it the daughter's observatory and adventureland treehouse versus
Indiana Jones's office
Okay
Let's I think now we really got to put in the end of the microscope and details
Become important and that's something people liked to point out
When this was brand new was the life magazine is a life magazine from the 30s with Mickey Mouse on the cover
There's you know with all of these with the jungle makeshifts. It just kind of becomes. He has a lot of stuff
Yeah, maps they sure do got maps there. They are
Is there a telegram or a message from?
What's this?
Sala or the guy in the white suits that always show up in them like his
His guy is minder is fixer. I'm not sure I'm not sure Paul
The character in the first movie what are we talking about Paul was the guy who plays Ivan ooze
Yes, actually all freeze you don't know Paul free no no
I can't think of his name. I don't know Paul something right I have a news. Yeah, I think there's something like that
Paul Freeman close
Fre I was completely wrong you've got a crate that says delivered a club obi-wan the outches
Temple of doom yes, they yes not a club our wars reference, but with the meander in
Anything goes performance yes, yes, right yeah
Let's see you know you got a you got maps you got bulletin board you got stuff in that that Mara temple language
You know a lot of details good easter egg II stuff his professorial side is represented
Meanwhile adventure land tree house just like just such a relaxing space real sense of wonder there
Yeah
It's uh
Yeah, what can I say? It's just it's it's just really nice
Splashes of color that I think me I think the color makes it stand out among the other jungle makeshifts
I think that's why I sort of cut through yeah past everest and the like let's talk about vibes though
I mean, Indiana Jones. Yes, the office might have a lot of interesting things in it, but
Looks a little depressing to actually maybe work there
It looks cool from the context of it being in a ride or a movie, but if you were actually using it as an office
It's got dim light you'd want to put out more lights in there. You want to organize things a little bit better
Mm-hmm eventually tree house is ready to go ready to use you could walk right in there bring your computer start working no problem
Mm-hmm, which I think is a strike in its favor and to
Observe the stars and I don't think I realized how many telescopes
We were running to Bowser has one this has one and a fun
Gilligan's Island one right as if a professor and
Invention and I don't know. It's it's gonna get it's inventive. Yeah in Indiana Jones. It's got that old fan there
Well, it might here too
I don't know where this tree house is meant to live but that could be an incredibly humid jungle atmosphere
But maybe I don't know the canopy might be just right. It might be the most comfortable room in the house
From what I could tell again, I haven't been to this in person. Did it strike you at all?
When you were there or was this just like a room that you walked through among others the whole thing
I strikes me and this was one of the specific rooms that I liked
Okay, especially when you do this walk through this this tree house at night at Disneyland
And you get to see how you can you see the views of Disneyland which are perfect if you get a nice sunset
That's even better
But then you get to yeah look at the different rooms and I this one specifically did did stand out to me on the
Couple times that I've done it. I am willing to right now say it's the observatory in the tree house and I'm surprised
That I'm saying that because I just didn't know it and I'm glad it was
Suggested I had to like go on a little thing for what is the office but it's this and maybe observatory
I guess labs are out but observatories are in I'm fine with that and I think it's very nice. I'm going with that
Hmm, I just think even without the presence of dr. Jones
His as the kids say aura is so strong
the vibes are so good and you think about how Indiana Jones like whips out books or maps or
Diagrams and doesn't even hesitate just so confidently uses stuff and that's why it's all laid out as it is
Mm-hmm. Well, it's just it's uh, it's not there's no real rhyme or reason for the layout
So I think he brings the rhyme and reason
He knows exactly what he's looking for and where it is makes sense in his head
I mean, I like the idea of a character being
Evident in the way that they have set up their office
I think you find that that you know, the whatever takes it all the way that might be a facet of it
so I
Think I have to go with Indiana Jones
But I know I'm waiting a lot of the what do they call it the intangibles?
I'm gonna pull that sports term. I only have understand the intangibles
Are in play at Indy's make sure you can't quantify or qualify. Yeah vibes
Yeah, I mean kind of like Frank's office. Yeah like Frank's office
Yeah, big good vibes in there if it was Indiana Jones was Frank's office. I would have voted Frank's office. What about another one?
I'm voting treehouse treehouse
Interesting about that. I think it's the way to go
I think actually, you know, sometimes you want to vote for like a
foundational office in the area like in jungle makeshifts as I said, but this feels like a good evolution like a
You know it shows what they can do now and how good this the set design and production design of these spaces is when they let
Imagineers in the town of people who work there go nuts
People love it when a 16 seed knocks out a one seed, you know, that's right. I think it is Indiana Jones a one you think
Just from the fame of the occupier maybe
That's true a neon Jones a very famous character the daughter. Is this is it Swiss family? Well, it's
Inspired by it's not it's a different family different family. Do we have names here? I don't think so. I forget though
I don't remember specifically if there are interesting. This is probably in a three ring binder on a shelf in
Imagineering there's a whole better story
Yeah, it better be just like there's pages and pages of port of entry lore that may be lost to time
Mm-hmm. Well, well why you got to break into Universal creative and get your hands on it
You have to pull in Indiana. I need to grab a box of floppy disk
Then I need to find a floppy disk reader that I need to find a floppy disk reader that can convert to USB C
Oh, man, if taking you so long to put that printer together, you know, get that floppy disk drive Michael
That's what I'm saying. I'm fucked. Yeah, I'm gonna have to go back to Pennsylvania and get my college desktop booted up
Does that still exist? Oh, yeah, it's still got the snakes on a plane background
Three custom backgrounds for your desktop
I don't think get snake fever
I don't think the countdown clock to snakes on a plane works anymore because it's long release
You won't want this mother bun mother bleepin desktop off your mother bleepin a computer
All right, that's so winner of jungle makeshift
So eventually on tree house kind of surprising but I really like it once you when you really look at it when you study
It and that takes us to tune dens
Minnie's office versus Bowser's study God who um, I
There's there like
Let me just shout out some other
Details in Bowser that I think are neat if there's just good books throughout
A brief history of Moo Moo Meadow jumped out at me
It's a lot of it's just like he's like not only is he just trying to win at Mario Kart he is like
boning up on the entire history of it despite like he must have been like fundamental in the like
Making of it, right? Maybe not. I don't know what in the creation of the
Official what race organization that Mario Kart is a part of? Yeah, you would think I mean, he's always been one of the one of the primary
He's always been in the in the eight in that elite eight. He has that's true
But I guess he could just have be an invited guest to compete in it. It's true
That's true doesn't necessarily mean that he's part of the board. Yeah, I
Probably not know they probably try to keep him away
But maybe there is a sort of a peace offering to him to allow him to compete
That's the way I'm thinking about it off the top of my head. Yeah, but I don't know
But I just like that it's that there is a vast library with so many like
These are rare rewards in a truly punishing line not in terms of detail and cool stuff
But in terms of length and if you're gonna make people stand in a line like that, and then the only ride they get is meh
Then you know these books are a real treat the art of balloon battle why good things happen to bad people
I like that. They're all big old thick ones
They are these aren't half chubs. They're full chubs of books and it's
Yeah, it's it's just I don't know into as far as this this queue. I think really competes with
Mickey minis runaway railway in terms of stuff details
Yeah
Stop and look at that are worth taking pictures of that make it worth actually doing the queue at least once right?
Yes, is this throne is that chair in the office or my my geography wrong?
There is a throne
I'm looking at a really specific photo the one I'm looking at as a big like creepy
Furnace that kind of has a face and tusks and I like that one like the furniture when they can get like the decor of
A place to feel like the character and they definitely do here
Big throne. I'm not sure there's a bit like there's a big like work desk
I just love that they like that it elaborates on the history of that he that he he's the god of all of these
Villains, yeah, he made the I was okay. Help me out. Who are the little characters from Mario 2 who wear the little masks and cloaks? Oh
Oh great question. Not the shy guys. No, no shy guys guys are in the other unless I think I'm there
You're shy. I think are you thinking of shy guy?
Well, here's the I what I wanted you to regardless of who I'm thinking of
I wanted you to say shy guys and to help me out because I swear to god
I was about to say try guys. I was so close to saying and Bowser created the try guys
These are the shy guys. I think yeah, that's what I mean. Yes them. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, wait. No, wait
Oh wait, show me again. No, you're showing me
You're showing me three guys on a couch making the scariest apology video you've ever seen in your life
No, that's not from that's a different one shy guy that was filmed making out with Birdo
Who was a food bird? Oh, how could he resist that big luscious mouth?
Who doesn't want to spin with Birdo?
Birdo, um, they were at a they try to think they were at an Iggy cut. They were at an Iggy Koopa concert
How could they resist
Many okay, there's not as much room
Sadly because there's so many details in Bowser
So many just doesn't have the luxury of space there. I will like to point out that on the screen
I don't think we talked about this
Of Minnie's computer her heart-shaped computer you were saying it's a lot of it's done for fashion like her fashion work
But on the computer it says Minnie's email
Oh
Now this I made an assumption here
I thought that this was a fashion design thing or like it's because it's for literally it's for kids like to for to paint her
Right, but what is it? Wait, show me this again. So it says Minnie's email
Yeah, and it'll have her friends Mickey Mouse Donald Duck Goofy
Daisy duck, I almost said Daffy
Chippendale Uncle Scrooge and Roger Rabbit. Those are the characters on here and then you know, she's deleted that email
Nobody taught we don't talk to that guy anymore with Roger
He's spielbergs
He's blocked the email does say mouse look instead of outlook
Look
They're trying to get kids accustomed to working man get them into the office early
Neon
I like that tone. I like that bit. Yeah, so each each character has a different color and or pattern
Correspond so that is also how Minnie's computer works. It's a good idea. By the way, it's a color code of friends
right, so she's got like
Roger is green Uncle Scrooge is blue is darker blue Goofy's like blue
Chippendale are stripes her technological innovations
Make me want to give her more right and she's also got a picture of herself
Like like bluedo does she has a picture of herself on the screen for some reason
Waving I don't know why
She would does that mean an empty inbox?
Is that he cleaned it all out I think this is just the address book part of the email
Did Minnie invent her own clippy that is her?
Oh, maybe because if so, then this is one of the most innovative computer systems ever made. Yeah
So I just want to yeah
So so she can do all sorts of work with that interesting keyboard is what i'm assuming from this
Okay. Well, thank you for the correction and for the enlightenment. It is not just for fashion design
It's not just you can email scrooge mcduck. That's right. Um
I also want to shout out this little area which is like the shes lounge by the window here
That is a nice little area. Yeah as well because like but now let me let me say this though
That's that's true
But we're now we're a little bit more in like she fits some home office into more of like a parlor a makeup room a bedroom
Perhaps but now but this is also we you know, this was pre
Zoom this was her carving out space for a home office where there wasn't necessarily space
So she was kind of a pioneer in that way. Yes
so
Ultimately
If minnie had the real estate that bowser does I feel like she would handily beat him
But sadly because she doesn't I I you have to give it to bowser. I think okay jason
Uh, i'm thinking bowser too again. He's very mono
Focused on what he does. He's got personal attachments. He seems to be working on bettering himself though
So that reading educating that's endearing him to me. Why do good things happen to bad people?
You know, there's kind of like it's not just he's not just treating it like a race like there's um, you know
There's a psychological study in it for him. Yeah, if we think of office is as
Where people are doing their business doing their thing
I think it's bowser because minnie like mickey
um
Might be kind of a cipher in many ways
You put up those are fighting words like no like she can do any
She's a scuba diver then she's a model then she's an explorer then she's a you know you paint
Stuff onto
these characters
You know bowser do multiple things though too bowser can do multiple things, but he usually comes back to center
Back to his normal his true love his true life of villainy something that something I think we should all love and admire about
many is her versatility
Well, yeah, that's true. I for one celebrate that but maybe that's just me
That's just me too. I just I celebrate many and all the different things. She's all right. All right
You have maybe that's just how I see things and how I view women
But I like that they can do whatever they put their mind to
Yeah, so I but I look at bowser. I have to go with bowser bowser
Bowser crushes mini
I didn't expect it coming in. All right, we yeah me neither. I know I didn't think I had to even go like there is a
Office in there, right? And once you meditate on it, it's pretty it's pretty undeniable one
Okay, we go to the sci-fi category men in black versus guardian collectors office shit
Yeah, tough one. Definitely tough one. Um
okay, we kind of we didn't say a lot about guard obviously guardians is a
Extremely well themed room there. You got a lot going on on the shelves. Oh, yeah
Uh the walkman that is eventually stolen by rocket
Um great stuff on the desk you you pointed out this excess tech
Detail that I forgot about it's a real good chair. It's not big like a throne, but it's ornate like a throne
Yeah, he's got a quill
um
He's got a big chalice
Like it's sort of a I don't know you get a sense of the character. Yeah, there's a
Grandeur just just enough
Sci-fi and comic book to it
There's two different kind of slightly different versions that you can get to in the actual queue itself
With slightly different are they different from each other really?
Oh one of them is agent colson's big gun from the avengers in it and the other does not
Um, so I like the variation there and i'll say this about being in this physical space
I
My enjoyment of being in this little room is as high as it ever
Going on at the 50th time is just as fun being in this little room than the first time
Yeah, I have to agree this fucking room
You know what it has and I feel like you brought a lot
Brought it up a lot in the past
Intimacy, that's thank you. It's warm. It's it's cozy, but it holds a lot of people but it's still very intimate
It's very intimate and I mean like we're not even counting the fact that rocket the animatronic stuff happens in here. I guess technically
Does that count?
Well, that's just bad opsec, you know if he can get in that easy and snatch stuff
So might be a strike against it
I think you can't count it because the the collector doesn't want him in there. I know he's not supposed to be there
Yeah, but but it is something that happens. Obviously. It's the main thing that happens in the room, right mark in its favor
Maybe the only one but one that's referred to a lot
As the collector's office, is that right you mean they specifically say
That they call it an office. Yeah
um
yes
Now, but let me let me throw out the like
Like does anybody really want to work in here? This is a pretty oppressive space. I mean, it's cool
But like just in the office or in the whole building. No office the rest isn't an office. The rest is uh, uh, what is it?
There's a museum or something. Yeah, it's a fortress fortress
well mike and I have both made offices surrounded with knickknacks and creatures and
Books and comics, you know dim in there, but I do think you can get the light
I bet it's more adjustable than that indiana jones, which is like probably single light bulb or something hanging
You'd have to like bring stuff in I bet there's like a dimmer switch in the collector's office when it's just him
He's probably
Like yeah, he brightens it up a little bit. He's trying he's trying to scare and intimidate all the guests
so it is a it is
Like it is a little too dark for me and it would be nice to have open air and windows
but
my my collector brain
Likes the way everything's laid out and the little things that are in there
So I find it I would find it cool to work in there
Yeah, he boy he needs uh the brutalist himself laszlo toth to come in and get some more light in that place, huh?
uh mark against men in black
Personally, I hate open office spaces
Oh really? Yeah. Yeah, I think they're oppressed. I think
It was meant to be like hip and cool and we're all just hanging out
But also there's nefarious like and we can all keep an eye on you
That's yes. Yeah. Yeah, that's a good point. Um, but I think it's a different because that's not that's not like cool
moderate, you know, it's like it's
You know, it's more like a like a police officer government office in that way
It's just like, you know, there's only there's there's yes, there's lots of space, but you know hundreds of people
it's like a detective's bullpen like
Yeah, or a newsman like the daily bugle or i've been playing through la noir on the switch and you start every mission and the detectives like
You know assignment room and it's big bone pain kind of thing. Um
It's also not oppressive like an open office
Concept because the furniture is great. Yes
Uh, uh, you know you like
Somebody said sterile. I wouldn't say that because this of any these are probably the desks that I would want
There's this I wouldn't say sterile. I'd say minimalist. I'd say mod
Um, just the the brightest white the sleekest white. Um, the chairs are fantastic
Um awesome like 60s plus that this like round googie kind of style
um, I really like the
the big pillars I really like uh, like the
Like kind of the the big unmovable like this like the steel fixtures with the you know with the circles
Uh, uh very bright into them. Yes, bright white and I feel like they keep up with cleaning that white
Those those crazy chairs that are like bulbous
kind of like
ballsacky
After the idea in lack of a better term
Uh, um like there's there's kind of like a little like lounge area that's under one of the catwalks and the catwalks are cool
I love the perspective that you have on it. I love looking down
Um, you know, obviously there's uh, there's this fact that you can ask people to go take a tour potentially
I don't know if that's still the case
But at least at some point in time you could ask a universal team member
Can I go look around there and walk up to the desks and it's cool from that vantage point as well
Uh any view of this you have the big console is great. The two aliens are great
Uh, the screen is great the big big cool egg that they watch all the arrivals on
Um, it feels very lived in I I don't I don't think sterile at all
I don't eat I don't like because I I like I sense
Uh, I sense some hustle and bustle. I sense activity, you know, it's fun to work at the men in black
It seems like it would be fun to work at the men in black and I look you won't I hear what you're saying
There's a lot of truth to it
But let me put this out there as a collector as a collector of things
And you know, we're talking about the collector's office. He's a collector of things
Let me read some of the other things he has in the office
because ultimately what I find in my real life
Is when i'm working I like to be
working next to a big wall of shit that i've collected and the shit has to be stuff I like because
Of what you're trying to think of something you're trying to finish something you look over at your shit and you go
Ah
You should make that noise in your head
So I think that the collector in the office has cool shit that would make you go ha
So it would appeal to me now, obviously it's his taste if I was in there
Maybe I would add some things to it if I was working but he's got
The head of tom morrow a robotic the robotic character from rocket to the moon and interventions. Wow. He's got
A mickey and mini vintage toy, which i've never seen in person really that's listed on there
Uh, he's got a book with the hollywood tower hotel bookmark inside
He's got the super soldier serum. Wow
Um, he's got there's a couple there's a bunch of these things. He's got some book. That's a reference to joe roadie
Uh, he's got a vintage map of disneyland. He's got a head from the doll a doll from small world
These are these are things I want
I want a little vile and I want a doll from small world's head
Yes, but sometimes all that shit
Gets a little oppressive. Well, that's another conversation to be having that I don't want to have right now
Yeah, so what you what you own ends up owning you they say this is why he doesn't allow his mom to see his shelves
That's right
Because she'll say this is too much and he's still both delighted and nervous when his daughter is like doing laps in there
Don't touch that and don't touch that. I've had a super glue many a toy at this point
Because of breaks from my daughter it like the theme park rides you've had to lock it all down
We go in and play we were playing this morning. She was playing with leather head the wrestling leather head from mega toys
She loves leather head. All right. All right, so there are some toys to play with
Okay, let me say she's to play with i'm not insane. She plays with everything. It's only some toys are super glued
But resentment can build
I resent her. I
Resent my two-year-old. Um
We're foolish all of this all the arguments you're making are great, but this cue is great
It's like when we had this idea when the list was quickly made when jason was up the list the shot of joy
I got thinking about this bullpen. Yeah, it's great. Yeah, it's wonderful. It's men in black. It's men in black
It's great, but i'm going collector. I went back and forth a lot
I wasn't sure I was one than the other than the one I gotta go with scott on this one. Yeah
Wow, yay
Do you know what jason i'm mad
Jason now i'm mad that I didn't vote for franklin's. Okay
Well cheer yourself up
By going to nod your head black suit
Jason thinks that's the superior song of the two. It's pretty fun. No, I didn't say it's
I like it. I don't I don't say it's I might I might put it like because one is just kind of like an
Overplayed hit of the time. Yeah, the other was so audacious in its like
Mythology and this chick serlina, right and the way that it didn't really take no matter how much they aired it on mtv
I think I would choose to listen to black suits common though
It's not the better
But if I if you made me if you put a gun to my head and said
Which man in black song do you want to listen to i'd say what that's the gun to the head challenge
The video has those things they're flying on and they're soaring the video's not better than the first video
Well, I didn't say it was better
Yeah, he does dance with the alien weren't you like working out
Yeah, it was I was doing an early part of it
Nod your heads fell in love with a girl. Is this it?
Uh nelly for tato. Yeah, I think you were listening to philly nelly for tato
You're listening to nod your head and fell in love with a girl is really good
Is it a treadmill or an elliptical?
Uh, like one of those ones that had a resistance band and it swung the pedals back. So I think
Yeah, yeah
Swing swing
I'm like a bird one elliptical away from like
7 a.m
To 10 before programming started vh1 would just loop music videos and you didn't know what you're gonna get
A great blend whether you're a teen or a 50 something. Yeah. All right
Well now we land back at the grab bag, which has become another cartoon
area perhaps not surprisingly
um bluedo's office and
conservative pulsed
All right. Sorry. I was pretty careful. Yeah, I think I was just like I was practicing in the mirror for so long
Earlier morning that I was just ready for it. So let me oh, what is it? All right, the daily bugle
Right amazing adventures. You knew what you're doing. You were being a scam like my girl
We know what jason says but it is seemingly she should be conflicted
I think because it's popeye and it's spider-man this well
We have it's two it's islands of adventure against islands of adventure
A true sophie's choice for jason. This is a tough one
Like implying any faults in anything in islands of adventure
It's a very difficult thing. Yeah for him to do
Uh, but you do have to pick a favorite
I that makes me interested to start with jason's thoughts here. I'd love to start with jason
Yeah, because you'll be the most conflicted here. I think well, yeah, but
Except one is spider-man. Yeah, that's what
I like popeye and bluedo
but
I love spider-man if popeye marry
spider-man
Uh kill conservative pollster franklin's
Sorry, it's not what I do
Well, maybe so maybe there's no conflict then I guess not I guess it's spider-man for jason
Yeah, I think it's got to be spider-man for me. I mean, it's so detailed
And so officey. Yeah bluedo is like a nice quick hit but it's a gag more than an office
I'm a little surprised that it made it as far as it did it being like the tiniest caged office
But I think it really is just a virtue of
That yeah, he's got a trophy treasure. Yeah, it's got the cannon and he's got treasure. It's pretty good
It's pretty good. But yeah, I gotta say spider-man. That's come on. It's spider-man. It's dealing with like
This is where like obviously this is correct
I just wish it hadn't been because let me ask you this mike bluedo versus
Uh franklin's
Hmm looks interesting
I
Don't have time. Yeah, I know we can't go back to ones that were time. This is about uh, uh, yes making choices
Uh, not doing rematches that can't exist. We have to keep plowing we have moved from the ergonomic eight to
the
What I call it the feng shui four
A little cleaner than the fax machine four
Oh
But this is the wait, this is the final four we have made it to all right, so
That means that what we can see at least per these matchups the best four fake offices in theme parkton
the observatory from adventure land tree house bowser's study men in black
Headquarters and the daily bugle. That's a really good list. I think that's an excellent list
Um, and I and I now I like that we've got some like diversity in style because the very
uh realistic
Uh, and you know tropical
Adventureland treehouse goes against bowser's study. These are two extremely different vibes
um
Now mario kart in the final four of any. Yeah, who would have thought is a real shocker?
I
uh
Hmm, I got I have no immediate thoughts here. I'm working through it
Um, but we need to do it while we record that's I can't just you can't turn you cannot tell me to turn the mics off
No, we can't that's not how we worked. Does anyone have a strong knee jerk
Either way or an angle on one of these that was not already had
It's a good question. Um
I think that
Hmm, we just do in the first two. Yes. Okay treehouse bowser
The young girl's hopes and dreams
versus the ultimate villains
Den of villainy. Yeah place where he creates weapons of war
And cute if harmful
The thing bowser does everything it is cute. That's the that's the problem and I guess look that is also
you know part of
You know in real life too if somebody is is nice, but evil
If they they say things if they have decorum, this is a big argument
you have sometimes with somebody like a frank luntz who ultimately they
You know, they agree with the same evil principles and and viewpoints
But they want the politicians to do it nicely
They want to say it with a smile and don't you think bowser in a lot of ways by making his weapons smile?
And making them cute he's doing a lot of the same things that a frank luntz
Would do they want a similar they have a similar approach bowser really is modern american politics, isn't he?
That's what i'm saying do it with a smile, right? Wow. So maybe
maybe
We should not be swayed
By the cuteness of bowser's office and we should not overlook
the destruction
That he will no doubt. Yeah
Reek and that a vote for bowser is a vote for kind of this gross faux masculinity
Like if you went to a restaurant that served steak and that's the ultimate height of it. Yes
Don't you dare if arthur and sons had an office we don't we so we have gotten a glimpse of arthur and sons the soon to be
Open downtown disney steak and bourbon restaurant. I didn't see a glimpse
I didn't see an office like a themed office there
To add to this because I would I would probably pick an 11th hour
Or I would make an 11th hour choice to replace the daily bugle with the arthur and sons office
But it hasn't happened so our yet. Look we already we already had franklin's game. That's too many things bad enough
We're talking about bowser's office where he goes to stew
After he betrays his friend of decades the innocent kyle glass
You know
Well, it's kyle gass first of all, but you're saying because he thought was yeah
That was a lot of levels to get to a joke with
With a very wrong name jack black is bowser in the movies
Yes, and he sings a silly song broke up within that brief time where he said a thing about um
so
I just want to make sure everybody understands what we are voting for or against here
because it is
A lot more insidious than it seems sure. Um, I pulled up a video of the queue
And I immediately landed on a close-up of a big book that says dental hygiene for chain chomps
I am choosing bowser's gun on that alone. I love every one. These books are so good. We were so
Like we've been so mean to this land
But every everything in here if it was all like this like rich details
For a kid who grew up playing mario
And even that I think would be fun if even if you just vaguely understood the character
Yeah, you know and the mythology
um
Yeah, and it's also grooming the motorways you get friendly landscaping. That's so good. You gotta give it to this ride also for
Showing you something about bowser that you cannot see
Elsewhere it's creating new. Yeah, you really get into his head. Don't you?
Oh, and then there's a little animation. I'm voting for evil as well. All right a vote for evil
Jason, do you want to do that that gives it to bowser?
But do you uh want to cast the vote essentially?
Do you want to do oh, yeah, I was gonna say adventure land just because I think it's cute and it's got lots of natural light
That's nice. It is very nice. I can't disagree with that, but I can't disagree with your guys
You know affection for this place. I can't believe final two. Our embrace of evil. Geez. Yeah. Yeah
um
Let's see. So that takes us then to this is a heavy hitter for sure
I kind of yeah seem like a place that it all might go men in black
versus daily bugle
They oof. These are my yeah, these are my guys
I mean jason knows
Let's be honest. I mean, it's still daily bugle for me. Okay. All right, so it's just so it becomes that we talk about it
um, I
Mike i'm going to show you a photo. Yeah, go ahead
the
Not to just cut to the photo. Um
Something that is clever about the daily bugle
Styling is that it is painted like a comic book where you know
Foreground details are more fleshed out and then background details just kind of fall into more simple color
And I think that's cool and clever
however
Uh, you end up with things like this
a bunch of gray
Donuts and fruits and weird
Uh croissants that they haven't repainted gray croissants that are
Chipping away their paint. Yeah through the years. Yeah, this image. This is not a good image
I'm not saying that i'm not going to vote for it
But come on this this like what is this gray hamburger? What is this?
Well, doesn't that reflect the decaying of the newspaper economy in america
Surely, that's what they were thinking. I like your rationalization, but it did there were a bunch of weird gray donuts
At this place in 99 too. Yeah. Yeah, there was some gray
Huh, okay. Hmm. Do you know what you're voting for?
You don't have to i'm just wondering if you do not not totally locked in
Okay
Here's what i'll say
About spider-man
It's great. I'm a huge spider-man a huge marvel fan. Okay
They are trying to recreate comic book art in real life
now more pop party than the kind of
Grays and browns of the mcu. Well, yes
Yes more like a comic book versus actually what it looks like with the
What the slop the background cgi slop looks like oftentimes on the movies in the movies
um
I think that I have been shown through toys and through other different
themed environments
That the way in which they've made sort of a cell shaded
environment
It the spider-man to me looks a little outdated at this point
And I looked
And I remembered that there's a south korean cafe
That has tried to recreate its space to make it look like like a comic or a comic strip
And like it is so cool looking
like wow
They have come a long way and this has come this well what you're showing us is essentially just black and white
They just completely limited about color palette. I think there are but there's a woman
In full color obviously because she's from real life, right sitting in an illustrated black and white world
That is really neat. I would like to go to this really closer to like your black and white
Graphic novels or art comics, right? And I think they're i've seen a sort of more colorful versions of this and I could I could look
um
but
I
Do think there's a little tiredness to the spider-man
Q after all this time can you barely look at jason you barely look at it
You were scanning the room of where to put your eyes and even though like I voted kind of against men in black
The other two times I do think it's probably
held up
In a stronger way in some ways. This perfectly looks like the movie and
I think they could plus that spider-man q up by giving it some new paint paint would help making it look a little fresher
And they don't have to necessarily go this hard with cell shading
But i've seen so much good cell shading just on my toys
My toys are amazing that style of turtle that you have. I don't know if that's what you're talking about
But the style that's more cartoonish
Um, yeah, that's that's meant to look like it does it great. Mondo does great spider-man and x-men
One six scale cell shaded animated series style to this point now where the technology is whatever
Technology the artistry has gotten so good
That it does make me
As impressive as it used to be and I think i'm voting men in black. Wow
Wow, even after you just sent me the artist adam cubert showing
How he had max his son's name in the ice man. Well, but that's not the i'm not that's outside
That's outside. That's fine. I'm not gonna disrespect adam
One of my but it weren't my heart
Who hid my heart i'm not saying wicked needs to take over marvel's superhero island. I didn't say that
I do think it's possible, but I don't i'm not saying I want it
It's been a rumor for many years. Look. Yeah, it's all different things. Do I love
The song hero by chad skroger featuring josey scott. Of course, of course I do
If we're talking 2001 era music, that's the top of the top. That's the best anyone ever did it
But that's not this hold on hold on no, well is hero or vindicated
Which is your choice? No hero is oh always
I don't you don't really know what vindicated is is that dashboard confessional for spider-man indicated. I am selfish
I am wrong. I think i'm right. I don't know. I'm right
I swear I knew it all along and I am i'm doing like the long but it's not really
What a good little concert I just got yeah, yeah
You got some emotion out there. I do. Yeah, I don't know the spider man
Three song and I don't know the men in black three or four songs
Uh chris, that's the guy's name. I've seen dashboard confessional twice, but i'm not a fan of them
You're not a fan of them. All right. Yeah
Uh, I okay. I have not locked in my vote. I want to give a shout out to the fact that the daily bugle
Uh has adapted with the times. Yes, they make newspapers, but they also have their own
internal use
Internet called bugle net
That helps them track villains and where they are great and that mythology I think is spectacular
Uh, and i'm glad they have it and I like that. It's kind of 99 era clunky desktops, but the devil's in the details
Uh, I don't like these gray croissants and i'm locking in men in black
Oh my gosh
Wow final two
Wow, so that brings us jason just took a swig of whiskey a bourbon
Yeah, it's oh, no things have gotten so bad. He's uh
I prefer he's resorting to the devil bourbon. I prefer my sugar and chocolate. No my beverage
Okay, so that gets us down to
the
Uh, the tidy two. Whoa, we're down to the tidy two a head-to-head
Universal studios takes it entirely. This is too wild. Yeah is out. Disney has been out. I'm so sorry
What was mike's vote?
No, it's black men in black. Oh, okay. Oh, yes
He blacked him out. He wasn't even reacting to the
The loss of spider-man he wasn't paying attention. You didn't definitively say yes. He did. No, he didn't
Um, no, that's that it's men in black. Uh, so that brings us wow, it's all universal
That's really something they do good offices. They do good offices. Um, so browser study versus men in black
Uh, is it hard or is it easy? Is it hard or is it easy? Um, yeah, I don't know. I don't know
Uh, is it?
We've got one that is full of detail. They're both like really great
Worlds like the the world of nintendo versus the incredible
production design
Of men in black now, this is it's obviously not
You know
If you watch a scene from the movie of the real setting that this is portraying and then you look at the actual space
in a youtube video
it is much smaller, but they do a really good job of just of like
Maximizing space and making it feel giant and the way they send you in via catwalk
It feels huge even though it's probably you know, like a fifth of the size of the set maybe less
um
I also in thinking about men in black was reflecting on the
Awesome. I mean in general
The production design of the men in black films and all of the all of barry sonnenfeld's films those including adam's family
Um and remembering that it's all that all of that is one guy bo welch who is also tim burton's guy same guy
Same production designer like for if you took just one of them legend
Uh, but both burton and sonnenfeld some of the best
Uh production design movies ever and I forgot this guy
Mr. Catherine o'hara
They met during beetle juice. Yeah. Yeah. Wow what that's one of the greatest couples
Ever to exist true icons in their field
Uh both incredible
um, so I like that there is
I don't know. It's just it's great movie aesthetics that's portrayed
You know mike you said yeah at some point you said like maybe an argument of something else
Yeah, it looks like the movie and that is you know, I guess invention
Is good bowser's office a space that we have not seen before versus recreating a movie
But it's not like it was just recreating the movie. They had to do it with a pretty minimal space
Yeah, and make it feel bigger than it is
um
And I don't I mean i'm i'm very impressed by both. I like these I like the tidy too
Jason, are you are you okay? First of all? Yeah. Yeah, no, i'll survive. Okay. I will say a very strong memory in the year 2000
of uh going down to florida with my family
And my brother kind of was mostly doing smaller rides with my mom and my dad and I
Went to islands of adventure after I had a day of rest because I woke up and I'm puke because I was so stressed out
uh
But you were you were that way then too
As a freshman in high school, yeah
I uh, but back then it could be stressed and just walk into alfredo's get a big plate of
Fettuccine alfredo calm down can't do that anymore
But the one day me and him went to universal and it's like we're getting one park ticket. Which one?
And men in black had just opened I think
And I was like, I really want to do that ride
But I want to go to islands of adventure for so I made my choice
I went that was all to say you didn't go. No, I didn't I eventually did and I wrote it again and again and again
On men in black. Mm-hmm. So I have a lot of affection for this
In the mid 90s after having an nes
I switched to genesis
You know, what is this what for what what what you're saying you change opinions I switched to sega genesis for you're saying
You could switch away from islands of adventure. That's what you're saying. What's that?
What's the point you're trying to make about the genesis? Uh, I have more affection for the men in black ride than mario
paraphernalia
Oh, I see got it. I didn't really get back on board
I mean I fiddle with my brother's game uh game queued every now and then fiddle. We did have we did
I did too I do a fiddle sesh, but I was mostly playing like goldeneye. Uh
Poof, uh, so
I think my vote is men in black because I like it all so much the building we've been talked about the building
That we haven't talked about if buildings count
Yeah, we didn't even go over that they it's kind of weird because it's not it doesn't look like an office from the outside
Yeah, it's kind of a I don't know if it factors in
um
Hmm mike, are you do you feel conflicted here?
I do feel conflicted because I really i've grown more affectionate for the office as we uh bowser's office as we talk about it
and it does really
Satisfy a lot of things a lot of needs you would have from a space like this
Especially attached to a character like this. There's so much character in it
Yeah, so that's why that's where the conflict comes into where i'm like, yeah
I guess of all the different characters on the list
His office does feel the most fun now, maybe I could argue the collector but he's out of the running
But he really is with all apologies to indiana jones. It's like yeah, it's indiana jones office. There's maps in there, right versus
Uh bowser with the hundred
Jokes and details. Yeah, not that indiana jones doesn't call for that, but you know what sure I do fleshed out
Yes, it's so fleshed out and it's so yes fun and design. So that is where my conflict comes in
Is that I just think it's like the best possible version of something like that
Um, and it's cartoony it represents the it did come down to cartoon versus realistic
Yes, and it is cartoony too, which I like which is you really want it to transport you somewhere
You know, which obviously whatever men in black, but it's more real world, of course
Um, so that's what that's what i'm weighing in my head right now
Uh with the two of them
Yes, um, okay by what I want to say details are my favorite part about maria cart
However
men in black detail game strong something that you want out of any of these offices are just like I keep wanting to say
Freeze frame gags, but that's not it because you don't you're not freezing a frame
It's you're walking through a space but kind of like blink and you'll miss it kind of details. There's a great
Signs implying other offices and other areas of the of the headquarters
I think are like then these are so good in men in black like there's a there's a directory that points you to
Fingerprint removal urban legend archive oxygen free zone human resources alien resources
Child and spore daycare excellent sign. Those are good. This is a great. So so everything that's that's the caliber of
Detail that is in bowser. I also want to point this one out
I said that you know
You can ask a team member to go give you a tour and like you have to walk on the floor and look at the
desks
And the desks here's something you can't tell from up there
On each of the desks in the men in black bullpen is the paperwork like immigration papers
of other alien characters
in
Universal studios in that park specifically for example bumblebee
Broken at like formal forms. Yeah with last name and then first name so seeing b bumble
And then the best one the best one
for sure
Is uh, there's immigration paperwork for king from the simpsons
And in the section that says other names or aliases
bob dole
Perfect, that's a good that is a good this is an office that is like
Down to like the tiniest detail you can't even see that you can only see if you ask somebody to go see it
A great reference to a great episode. Yeah, there's nothing to do with men in black
We're not even in the men of black
But the fact that it's taking going down on the floor and then it ties together all of universal studios aliens
Really wish et was in there et sure, but that's what that's literally what et is is immigration
Well, you're an oveille
Well now I want to get down there and see if there's a kodos one that says alias bill clint
I'm, not sure. I don't know. I only saw two desks in this video
You're making my frank lund's argument from earlier about the different unit the shared universe
As far as like
Tying in different mythologies bringing hogan's heroes in with with bill clinton with the presidency
Yes, george wood now. Here's a question to either of these does frank lund's knock out either of these
If it made it to the final two
There's another universe where it won all except jason would have always protected spider-man for sure
Yeah, yeah spider-man all the way to the end, right? I think so. Mm-hmm. He's loyal
My final four would have probably been
frank lund's dot gandhar the collector
and um
uh
Walt's apartment walt's apartment not fake. That's the problem fake
Although I guess you could say frank's is kind of not fake if he does his real office. Yeah, that's true
I guess that's points against it. Yeah, so
Yeah
Would do you would either of the bowser men in black would not have ended up in your final four?
Um
No, wow, I don't think wow so that puts you in a strange place. So you kind of have no allegiances
I'd say I don't know because I also think it's a little bit like
Man in black is so big. They have such a luxury of scope
And that's just something that most of these places do not have the luxury of
Like if you were to expand out bowser with that real estate
It's no contest. Sure. So that's what that's where i'm trying to weigh the size of a mat. Yeah
Size there's nothing that big in in the whole bracket
Yeah, so
It's unfair because if you put the same love
Times whatever the size is times five of bowser in
I think it's bowser all day
Sure, the fact but the fact that it's limited to this room and the rest is not offices
But it's a fun surprise that there's an office in this castle, isn't there?
It's a great surprise learning that he reads learning that bowser is a reader and that he plays big and dumb
But maybe it's all calculated right, but let's extend out. That's okay. Let's imagine the entire queue
Of bowser's castle is an office. Yeah, just a hypothetical to try to get us on the exact equal footing, you know, yes
I think you're in the you're neck and neck. Yeah as far as cool details
You're kind of doing a handicap here and yes putting them putting making the size of the same exactly
Because there's so much other cool shit in that queue
so I cannot just
Deliver a victory for something because it has the gift of of size
To me, it's not size to me. It is certainly great details. I'm not saying that's all it is
Yeah, I think if you had less space, I think I might still go men in black
I think it's a great it feels it feels lived in which is something we need
Uh details are great, which is something we need
Um, you know you sense character in there
Uh, yes all that's true and and just great and maybe I might also be I just like the 60s
I like that aesthetic a lot as well. What if men in black was the size of bowser though?
What's in there?
What goes in there?
Well, you know what stack them up
You have a little glimpse of that because you see that break room that those alien that the sure the worms or whatever are working
In that they've taken over and they're being gross in and that's a room
You don't even get to go in you just that's like one of these little cage offices and that's great
I'm not grading it on that but that shows you what a small version of it is like it would be still detailed still fantastical
Doing it. God damn it men in black alien attack
Locking it in I will decide I will give my dissenting opinion my supreme court justice dissenting opinion that I believe bowser
It is bowser for you. Wow
Wow, I'll pen a multi-paragraph dissent
That I will publish to make it known in the history books
Yes
That I dissented that which will do a lot your note of dissent frank lens will have a copy of it in his oval office as well
just for posterity just for
Preservation sake from babe ruth letters to mike carlson rants about why bowser should have won a fake office contest
I'll be on the record for that bowser did not win the men in black won men in black
Has taken it also maybe i'm i'm also maybe skewed in like
Though i'm happy mario kart made it all this way something that we have trashed
It is really hard to say that mario kart is the greatest theme park office of all time
It doesn't feel right feels like you need kind of I think that's your you're letting you see
I think you're revealing that you're letting the feelings of the ride
Into this which should not be part of it. I know but I think I prevented as long
Hey, I got it into the final two couldn't I that's true
By the way, uh my plus up for the men in black area you a very tall man
Doing the vincente anafrio sugar and he's walking around in front of the building and two like men in black
Agents have their like guns in their hoof in their way after it
How is that not a walk-around character in universal studios sugar vincente anafrio sugar
I feel like so like have such a bad headache by the end of the shift
That would be so
I can't imagine doing it now
But I feel like i've only seen more and more online appreciation for that performance. Oh, it's great
No, that's one of those. Yeah, it looms larger now than it did at the time. Uh, yeah
That's great to see
Um, well, uh, i'm happy with this
Is everybody happy?
I don't know if everybody's happy because it probably would have been spiderman for you and it probably would have been franklin's for you
I had a feeling it would come down to men in black her daily people. So
5050 i'm satisfied. All right. All right
Um audience, are you satisfied? Let us know. I hope so
I hope it's not like the vehicle one where we knocked out indiana jones early and people were mad
They might be mad here because maybe people like this indiana jones one more than I don't know. I can't tell
These always provoke a lot of divisiveness. I feel but you know, I yeah, I wonder what consensus
I don't know. We were talking about earlier how like, you know, we throw the rule
You don't necessarily follow the rules of this and you can sub things in and out. I'd like to just real quick
Um, can we sub out?
the winner men in black for uh collector's office
Can a collector's office win?
Can we sub can I do that you want to you wanted to jump multiple rounds? I just wanted to win could it win
That you're you're asking us. Yes. You have to say yes or no. No
Okay. Well, I just want to try. I just want to try
Just because I wanted to flaunt the rules a little bit because maybe we didn't flaunt them hard enough. Yeah, I don't know
potentially
Nope, it's too late. It happened
Yeah
All right. All right. Whoa an elliptical just materialized out of nowhere. Jason's going nuts
I'm gonna hop off my flying elevator to hop on
My qvc purchased elliptical
I feel I feel good about it
Uh, I hope you do too and I hope you like it. I as always curious about ideas for what are you playing?
No, no boo vindicated
Vindicated
You are not vindicated you're not vindicated you try to do one last minute slide out
This guy's breaking the rules trying to cheat the system like frank luntz's cronies
What a look this guy's got this lead singer lately of dashboard. Yeah. Yeah, you should do you should do it
You're trying to look young and hip try to look like this dashboard guy, which show me the look
I mean, he's got a real like
I don't know if this is photoshopped his beard and he looks you know what he looks like
He looks like a cool because it's such listener. It's such jet black hair and beard. He looks like a cool emaciated bluedo
If bluedo, he's kind of got like an old hat. He's emo bluedo. You know what bluedo would say about this
I'm excited to see
Jason got his phone out
How long will it take to get to the part jason wanted
minute 45
And also he should move the phone closer. Definitely should do that
In front of it probably it would help
He would say so bluedo would just say sweet haven that's what he would say
God must love us
Why it's that wasn't that wasn't him though from the robert altman, we know what it is
No, we know what it is. But why would he say that because he would say oh sweet haven he loves the town
No, he doesn't he's mean to everybody in it
Yeah, he's the biggest jerk in sweet. Hey, lots of people have conflicted feelings about their hometown
I guess that's true. I can't deny that. All right. Well, thank you for that. You survived podcast the ride fake office final four
For three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our vip tier club
Three, you'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride
Really quick on the way at the door. I don't want to lock this in as next year, but I do want to throw it out
Mike and I had an idea while we were out and about in the recent past. This idea was
The fire for yeah the fire for here's what this would be
Two sides maybe still maybe still 16 one half fake fire
We're talking end of pirates. We're talking big thunder. We're talking the burning of rome the other side
real fire
mummy
The epcot fire after during illuminations that peter newnes saw as mcfodur. Yes real
Yes
The fire that killed king kong the fire that peter newton from hermans hermits noticed at the american adventure stage when france was on fire
Is that right france? We didn't actually talk about this on the show how to play out what happened?
He well peter new was singing mrs
brown you've got a lovely daughter on the stage at the garden rocks at epcot in front of the american pavilion and
He looked over in the middle of maybe the chorus and he got oh france is on fire and he went back to singing
There's like a cooler fire or something. I think everyone was okay. Luckily patch of grass lit on fire
Oh, I don't know the official reason. Yeah, I mean that it's it'll be a year out and therefore less topical
But we can keep it alive if we can devote a lot of time to the oval office in conservative pollsters
For the bolster frank lunce's house, that's true
We can within one of the candidates in this could be peter newnes fire peter newnes noticed fire
I want to do a whole episode on peter newnes. That's well, that's possible too. That's frank lunce has a fire for
uh good governance
That's true
He sure does and the resolute desk reminds him that this is possible
Uh, but anyway the fire for real fire versus fake fire. Yeah, which division wins. I think it's a strong idea
Do you have a better one leave it in the comments or leave it in your head?
We think of the ideas. All right, that's how this show works. Whoa, bluto got here. No, no
Whoa, sweet haven
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson
Jason sheridan scott gerdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on facebook
You