FOREVER!
DOG!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, where we love theme parks more than Maya the Explorer and
her navigator, Captain Kakao, loves scouring the cosmos for new candies and confections
to share with the Celestians.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hello.
And I will also say, but I don't know why, it was a more calm, it was like a nicer one.
That was you feeling calm and back at home with even the reference to Captain Kakao.
I was taking a deep breath from that, like not saying it's mealy-mouthed or complicated
in its mythology, it's just right.
It's perfect.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi, I learned about Maya the Explorer a few weeks ago and I've been wondering about her
background, her motivation.
Oh sure.
So, that you answered it in one sentence, I feel a sense of relief.
Yeah, I guess the motivation is scouring the cosmos.
You should make the noise too, go, ah.
Yeah, nice.
It feels good.
Yeah, we should remember to breathe in these things, we don't have to just flap our gums
all the time, we can take deep breaths, center ourselves, which is something we're going
to have to do in this episode because a lot of excitement has occurred.
We got big stuff to talk about here, via our social media you might be aware that Mike
and I took a whirlwind last minute trip to Orlando, Florida, recently, primarily to check
on the progress of a highly anticipated Orlando attraction, Taffers Tavern, on iDrive.
We gave it a good look, see, I mean it was maybe going to be just that in and out, just
peer in that window, see how it's going, answer if you're curious, not well, seems like there's
nothing in there.
Seems like it's really behind, he was making posts about that, we're opening soon, and
then we looked in and we're like, this doesn't look soon.
Define soon.
Yeah, what?
I see on the show he does these things in like four days, but here we are looking into
a window, and I don't, how can you have a bar when you don't literally have a bar?
John Mayne, clock's ticking, you got a lot of, you're going to have traffic coming in
from new theme parks and you're not even going to be opening time.
They're running previews, aren't you Mike too?
We very, pretty late, not so late, but kind of late at night, just had to wander in front
of this closed, never opened restaurant, and no one was around really, except like a couple
stragglers, I feel like.
Well people filing out of a, there was some like kind of martini bar feeling thing, was
it the bar or was it just the mall in general, which I believe is called the Point Orlando,
where was playing an old wrestling theme, was that coming out of the bar or was that
just on the speakers of the?
So I forget the name of the actual song, but the Monday Night Raw theme song, like my generation
across the nation, like that, whatever that one was, they were just playing and it sounded
like it might be coming from the mall, but I suspect it's coming from the bar or club.
That has not been the theme song for like 25 years.
Yeah, that's an old Monday Night Raw theme.
Wow, old wrestling theme, but there's, that's some Orlando shit, Orlando bars pumping an
old Monday Night Raw theme that rules, and that was also around the time as that was
playing.
Then we looked in a store window where we saw a couple of great signs, do you remember
them offhand?
You took a photo or video.
Yeah, I posted it too.
What do you, like, what were the ones that lit us up?
Do you mind taking a sec?
And then we'll get into.
I'll take a look, yeah, no.
This is very us to be more excited about some random signs we saw than the brand new theme
parts.
I truly thought that was from Margaritaville.
No, no, these are too bawdy for Margaritaville.
That's why I was surprised, I thought like, whoa, Florida Margaritaville plays by a different
set of rules.
There was one that lit us up a lot, and then there's all of them though are pretty good.
So there's a really Margaritaville looking like parrot with sunglasses and a cocktail
or a margarita, I guess, carved in a piece of painted wood that says screw the crackers,
Polly wants a cocktail.
I missed that.
Then under it, there's like a kind of just a wooden sign that says bitch's kitchen.
And then there's a sign under that similar sign, just kind of basic white and then with
sort of black letters kind of thing.
Dear laundry, don't be sad, nobody's doing me either, which I don't know why you would
put that up.
And where would you would have to put that in a place in the house that faces the laundry?
I guess.
Does that mean the machine or does it mean your hamper?
To make sense, it would be your hamper.
It's hamper, but would the POV of a hamper be, would you have to put it on the ceiling
so that it would have a view of, how does a hamper see?
How does a hamper see?
It's a very good question.
If it has a lid on it, I guess you can draw a couple eyes.
Yeah, but if it has a lid on it, it ain't seeing no signs.
You know, that's true, that's true, the laundry thing.
That song, how does a hamper see, you know, that was going to be in the live action Tangled,
originally it was going to be in gigantic, but that got canceled, so.
It kept passing from movie to movie.
It kept passing from movie to movie, you know?
A little in somewhere, don't give up song.
And then the winner, I think is.
Oh my God, best sign of ever, it's the winner of best sign ever made.
Right, it says, we don't skinny dip, we chunky dunk.
Which, I don't know, we all LOL'd at that, I'm still LOL-ing at it later.
From the other side of the country, that just got seared in my mind like a cattle brand.
I sent it to you in GEO right after that.
And I think hopefully you guys enjoyed it as much.
There's a couple other ones that got cut off here,
because I kinda took this photo quickly, but it is just,
it feels so good to be in Orlando, Florida.
Yeah, look, headline number one, it was great, it was great,
it was wild to do it in such a concise way.
It didn't let us do a ton of what there is to do there,
but it's really, I think what you've always dreamed of, Mike,
which is just quick pop-downs, just make Orlando your Vegas,
and it felt pretty good, it was fun to do,
even more fun than going chunky dunking.
Yo, sorry, go ahead.
No, no, I was gonna say Jason did not join us
for various reasons, among them being your marriage,
that occurred while we were, yes, congratulations.
I don't do anything really whirlwind nowadays,
but also I was busy getting married.
I was gonna comment on the video,
this is why you couldn't make the ceremony,
but we didn't really do guess.
Well, we should be clear, we were not being derelict
in any sort of way, we were not asked to be groomsmen
a year ago, and then we said, whoops, sorry,
Epic Universe, gotta go.
We were just doing, we've been talking about this
since October or November, and we missed,
we were gonna do it on our anniversary, March 14th,
and then we just got delayed for any number of reasons,
so we were able to do it like two weeks later,
and it was just us and the, it's not a justice of the peace,
she had some weird title, but she was really funny,
she was really fun, and then our friend, Andrew,
came and took some wonderful pictures
that we've been kind of rolling out,
Andrew, the guest on the horror award show
on Second Gate?
Friend of the show, Andrew Grissom.
Yeah, he comes up, said what a good man he is,
and he did a good job taking photos for y'all,
so congratulations. Yeah, thank you.
But anyway, we were not, let's be clear here,
we were not bailing on Jason.
Because, I will be honest, multiple people thought that.
What?
Strangers, people without the information.
People that didn't know what was going on.
Or maybe not friends.
Some friends, some were texting me, wait a minute,
were you at the wedding?
And I go, no, no, no, no, it's a whole thing,
so we were, there was some, I had to do some.
We were trying to make it not a whole thing.
Well, it's okay, I'm not, it's okay,
I squashed the misinformation.
Yes, thank you, and we'll have an update on that stuff.
Some people wondered if it had happened in Florida.
That is very funny.
Because you guys are in Florida, so wait a minute,
and then some people, some friends of ours texted me,
and they were interested in the timeline of everything.
You got, yeah, at the top of the Helios Grand.
And you're where, yeah.
Or, like, you know what would be the thing to do now
is to get married, like, bride and groom are in different
cars on Sky, Sky, what is it called?
What's the racer ride?
Stardust Racers?
Stardust Racers, yeah, that was starting to go
Skyfall Racers, that's not correct.
Not a James Bond ride.
But you go on, you do it as a duel on Stardust Racers,
and you, like, exchange vows at the part
where the coaster cars get the closest.
Because you could put the ring on each other.
I do, I do, I'm trying to toss it up.
Oh.
Nailed it.
Yeah, the cross, yeah, that cross, that was hard.
I was gonna say, yeah, we got married, we timed it,
we were the grand opening festivities
of the Terra Luna Hotel opening.
Oh, yeah.
Which, I believe, Terra Luna,
you cannot walk to Epic Universe.
We know.
But Stella Nova, you can, and you cannot walk
between Terra Nova and Stella Luna.
Did we go to Stella Nova?
I think we did.
It was the one with the tiles, which one is that?
They both have tiles.
Well, we popped in.
We popped in to see if there was a fun bar or something.
It's kind of a functional scene.
I think that somebody said the walking path wasn't open,
so perhaps it is Stella Nova,
but the walking from Epic Universe is not available yet.
Okay. Okay.
Gotcha. Right.
Yes, I also heard that Helios Grand, the fancy hotel,
it is essentially in the park, is that the parking there,
if you're just visiting the hotel, the parking is $135.
Yo! Because they're trying to,
they're trying to chase people out of the,
they're trying to make sure you don't use that
as cheap parking for the, if you stay overnight,
it's a more reasonable amount of parking.
Yeah, I don't know, $20 or $40 probably.
Yeah, they should have just gone full till with it.
If it was gonna be just a scare people away parking fee,
it should have just been like $7,000.
Have fun. Yeah.
You're setting the rules.
Have fun with it. Right.
And I thought 45 at the Beverly Hilton was a lot.
I was wondering how long it would take you
to start complaining about the parking
at your wedding hotel,
because you did before the wedding.
I, the historic ones, they hit you with a lot of fees.
I knew parking was going to be.
You paid for that history.
I think they hit you with those
at the non-historic ones, too.
Well, the non-historic ones,
you can park on the street, you know.
Well, depending, depending.
Yeah.
Welcome to our wedding dream suite.
What if we park on the street, just hike it in?
We'll save it, we'll save it.
I was gonna say, we'll save it,
we're gonna talk about this.
We have to save it because we've,
here we are dancing around and around
and not saying the big thing that needs to be said.
And the thing that needs to be said is,
Mike and I have been to Epic Universe.
Yeah.
We have been to Universal's.
Holy crap. Third.
That's right, I said it.
Gate. Third gate.
As far as I'm concerned.
Yeah, we've been to this park.
It feels crazy to say that.
It felt, especially right after
and given the whirlwind nature and then jet lag,
like truly the day or two after,
I was like, did we?
It feels so weird and we've been talking about it
for so long and anticipating it on the show forever.
Yeah.
And now we can say that we went, it's wild.
It is and what you're saying about it being surreal,
really like, you know, when you go to some place
when it's in previews, I suppose they would call that,
as if it's a Broadway show, it's in previews.
Yes.
Obviously stuff is, they're ironing things out.
So sometimes stuff, you know,
you don't get on the ride you were trying to get on.
So now when I think about it in this surreal way,
it does feel like sometimes you have
that like frustrating dream where there's like one thing
you're trying to do in your dream.
You can't quite do it.
You're right there and it does, ah, but I, ah.
God, you're right.
So there are things, there's great stuff.
There's, of course, because we're frustrating things.
Specifically, I'll even just say right now,
like I got to walk through the queue of the Monster's Ride
twice, but I didn't get to go on it.
So this is specifically what I'm referring to
where you're like, did that happen?
Did we actually go to Orlando for a short amount of time?
And then, oh, it feels in my mind like I had a dream
where I just couldn't get to the thing.
Just behind a door, as opposed to like,
my baby's back there and I can't help him.
It's instead, it's Victoria Frankenstein is back there
and I can't see her.
I came all the way across the country.
Yeah, that's a good caveat to say.
At the top is that like, you know,
we by no means could consider this a fully exhaustive,
expansive view of the park
because there were big, big old things
that we did not get to do.
And yeah, we were lucky enough to get this opportunity
to do it in kind of a preview period
in which you very much get the caveat of, you know,
not everything's gonna be open.
It's, you know, they were very strict about no photography
because there were things that weren't finished.
There were odds and ends where you're like,
I know that's gonna be glistening when it opens in May.
What is the day?
May 22nd.
That's pretty damn early.
And but, you know, yeah, we're like, oh my God,
this like wall isn't quite there.
The window's not quite there.
And it was very fun to get to see a park in that state.
Yeah, I was gonna say that's kind of one of the dreams
for theme park enthusiasts is like an in progress,
you know, walking through a live testing,
live construction site.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
I mean, I like, I was, when I shared with my mom
that I was doing this, she went straight to,
oh, you remember when you were a kid and we went,
we got to see, we were just in Universal Studios
and we just went near the building of T2 3D
and then suddenly people were going in.
And it wasn't scheduled open for a month or two
and we got a preview of it before it.
Like, I don't think then I knew that was even possible.
I don't think I knew that was a thing that they did.
And that really, I was so lit up about it
and my mom's thought about it forever.
So she was like, oh my God,
getting to do it for an entire park.
That's really crazy.
I think the stats also, I was thinking about
the headiness of getting to do this,
of like been theme park fans forever,
doing the show for nearly eight years.
This is the first time,
certainly that we've gotten to go to a park pre-opening.
It is the first time we've gotten to go to a brand new park
in Orlando since we were teenagers.
And I feel like if you told us back then
that we would have this opportunity now,
like how blown would our minds be?
And then if you added the fact that,
okay, you are gonna get to do that
and also you will be doing it
with a light jelly rolls hangover.
You at 40 will have hit it a tad hard
at the dueling piano bar.
I think, well, then you just go,
wow, you're sure that's 40 and not 17?
Seems like we really got it going on, don't we?
You'd be like, is my life perfect?
Did we win the lottery?
Are you a millionaire?
How, what?
My goodness.
Yup, yup, hey, pretty good.
Living it up, living it up.
Jelly rolls, why at 14, 15,
I'm not even allowed to go in there.
That's true, you only can imagine what it's like.
Let alone getting hung over.
What's the excitation?
Well, again, we'll get to this stuff later,
but I spent two nights in a row at jelly rolls
while I was in Orlando.
And I spent. Two separate nights
in a short short trip. Half an hour.
I think it really does illustrate,
we'll save it for other, but like.
That's by the way, jelly rolls is the dueling piano bar
on the boardwalk right by Epcot.
Soon to close.
Which is part of, must have been part of you
fitting it in.
Absolutely.
Yeah, it is very like, you know,
we get a pretty tight amount of time in Orlando.
How do we play it?
I did a bunch of wandering of mostly empty hotel spaces.
You did two jelly rolls.
Two. Evenings.
Two jelly rolls with two separate groups of people.
Wow.
So it wasn't even, I didn't even intend to do it too.
Just that's how the nights lined up.
That's what the different parties.
You did not enter the first night thinking
that that's what it would be.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it worked out.
That's the thing.
It's like, as in a family vacation,
everybody gets what they want.
Everybody gets their own flavor.
I'm very happy with mine.
You were very happy with yours.
I was thrilled.
I had a ball.
Well, let me ask you guys a question.
How much time did you allocate for Islands of Adventure?
Well.
Jason, I got bad news.
I got bad news.
I have bad news as well.
It doesn't always work out.
Yeah.
I walked by it.
Can you even fathom going to Orlando
and not stepping foot in Islands of Adventure?
Oh no.
He's dying.
Save him.
Oh, I mean, I went in.
I went in and I went on all the rides.
I went in and I honored each and every
very special location at Port of Entry
and thought about its history and mythology.
I smoked a pack of cigarettes at Islands of Adventure.
Don't worry.
I smoked the longest cigarettes
that I could possibly find.
Yeah.
So, no, I did not make it to Islands this time.
I ashed right on top of a cinnamon roll.
Yeah.
I did go, I did hang out at City Walk, though.
You did City Walk, but not, I don't think I knew that.
I spent a little time at City Walk, yeah.
My God.
I did wander the hotels as well.
There was the awkwardness of, like,
not every day getting to be a park stick
because two of them were traveled.
Yeah, I mean, I did it as fast as humanly possible.
Tried to be there for as many bedtimes back in LA as I could.
Yeah, my travel got delayed heavily the last day,
so then I ended up spending longer around the hotels
and City Walk than I expected.
I guess I should have, in hindsight, just, you know,
bought a ticket to Islands and gone.
In hindsight, I think I would have done that
if I knew it was going to keep getting
pushed back.
Sizeable delay, big, little delay.
Let's not delay too much further the talk of the park.
I mean, this is crazy.
It's like, it is almost overwhelming the amount
to talk about again, I would say.
Let's take the pressure off ourselves.
Let's take a deep breath, and audience, please,
take the pressure off of us to fully cover this play
because we'll be talking about it a ton.
Jason, you'll get the chance to go down,
and we'll be piecing off Epic Universe then,
but just think of this, I guess,
as just kind of a, like, I don't, I mean.
Overview.
A preview, a preview, as we got a preview,
this is a preview of our full thoughts about the place.
Why did you guys bring in the 12 foot sign
that says the Roast of Epic Universe then?
If you're hedging your bets.
All right, let's crack those knuckles.
Let's get into it.
We've got a lot of, we got a lot of.
Maybe it should be called Mid Universe.
Please welcome Tony Hedgeglove.
Yeah, we spent a million dollars
to get Tony Hedgeglove here to roast.
I assume that's how much he caused
because he's so famous.
He has Trumps here,
and he's trying to get Celestians deported.
Right.
No more safe harbor for Celestians.
I'm excited to learn about Celestians.
I didn't know there was a whole crew.
Yeah, okay, so, first of all, I'll say this.
Like, I don't want to spoil everything or anything,
but I guess if you really want to go in cold,
don't listen to this.
If you truly don't want to know anything,
I don't have a lot to say.
I don't think that's not already kind of announced.
Yeah, there's stuff that's out there.
A lot of my thoughts are gonna be like this thing
that maybe we've even talked about on the show.
I liked this, this thing, I wasn't sure.
Like, yeah, I don't intend to ruin experiences
for anybody, but if even this is too,
even if any dipping into it is too much,
check out one of the many great other episodes of the show,
especially at patreon.com slash bug guys, they're right.
Yes, so yeah, so Celeste, I will say this.
There wasn't as many Celestians walking around as I hoped,
but I don't know that.
Again, this is where you're in previews.
You know, they're adjusting things to live performances.
So, I think we'll be able to learn, hopefully,
fingers crossed about Celestians more when we all go
for our upcoming live shows in June.
Which, by the way, we have not mentioned
here on the main feed, one of the perks of the Patreon
is that we give you extra early heads up
about if we're doing a live show or anything.
So, we made the Patreon folks aware of it,
of the two shows that we're doing at Tin Roof,
which is in early June.
I don't have the date in front of me.
Yeah, June 8th.
But we'll put the link in the show notes.
There is still standing room, how about that?
We're at the standing room point,
but if you're gonna be in Orlando,
if you wanna come to Orlando,
there is still standing room available,
which is not crazy, it's a comfortable and fun place.
It's back by the bar.
Yeah, yeah, and not that far.
You could also probably, it's not that long
of a little trek to see the empty,
I would assume empty still by then in June,
Taffer's Tavern.
Sunday, June 8th, and we're doing two shows.
So, yes, grab some standing tickets if you want.
How far is Taffer's Tavern
from the world's largest McDonald's?
Oh, I get turned around around there.
It's by car, maybe I'm probably gonna get it wrong,
but like 10 minutes by car, eight minutes by car.
But it's on the same strip as Tin Roof and the Orlando Eye.
It's all in beautiful eye drive.
Which we, there's so much eye drive we gotta get into.
I mean, that's a real show extender by the time you.
Oh, yeah.
But anyways, where exactly to begin here?
I mean, a part of me just wants to step through
the day a little bit, but also we don't have to do that.
We could just start calling out highlights.
Is there anything that you have been aching
to get off your chest right at the get-go?
I mean, here's what I, you know,
just because I brought it up and it is
at the forefront of my mind,
is yes, the Monster's Ride was down.
So there's, you know, this Monster's Unchained,
the Frankenstein experiment,
that was running in previews is what I saw online.
And then it was not really,
maybe it ran a couple times that day and then it broke down.
And that was obviously the thing,
the big thing that I was hoping to get on.
But I will say this, and I don't,
this is a very fun thing I got to do,
is that they were opening the queue to people
since the ride wasn't working.
So you could go in the queue.
And I got to go in the queue when a thunderstorm happened.
And I got to hang out outside the Frankenstein Castle,
sipping a drink, going into the queue,
and then lingering and taking my time
with the entirety of the Frankenstein queue.
Not many people in there, which is really like,
that's not gonna happen anytime in the next so many years
where that queue isn't gonna be packed with people.
Yes, well and what with my skippable queue feelings
and all that, it is like,
it really throws things for a loop to think like,
but would you not at a leisurely pace
with less people wander around this queue
because it's like a extremely cool walkthrough experience.
And that for sure, I didn't know,
I didn't get to do the queue.
You're the only keeper of the secrets of the Monster queue.
So I, yes, so I don't know, we'll see.
So yes, you were off doing something else
just because we got, our schedules got a little off.
We were not doing everything together on the day.
And I ended up just in the Monster's land alone.
I went to the Burning Blade Tavern.
I saw the fire.
You did go to the Burning Blade Tavern.
Yes.
I was recalling what is where,
and I forgot that I watched the preview video
and I recalled that it's, yeah,
there's the windmill that lights on fire
and that there is a bar in there,
which is different than the steakhouse.
And there's a bar in the steakhouse spelled S-T-A-K-E,
that kind of steak.
So I didn't realize, ooh, how's Burning Blade Tavern?
So Burning Blade, I'll say this is,
the outside of it is unbelievable.
Like the windmill bursting into flames is amazing.
That is as cool as anybody expects.
Yeah.
Inside is pretty simple.
It's cool, it's like dark.
It has like limited seating
like you can order something I think on the side,
just like a to-go window basically.
So inside it's not the most themed thing in the world,
but you know, it's cool to go in there,
grab something and come out.
And just cause I was talking about it,
it's like I'm hanging out.
I'm like wishing this ride opens.
And then I realized the queue is open
and then a rainstorm starts.
It had been fine weather-wise all day and all the whole trip.
And then it starts coming down just in a large amounts.
People are soaked and I'm kind of as wandering around
a little bit buzzed.
And then the Frankenstein Castle has a,
spoiler alert, has a little bit of a show that it does
when like the electricity turns on in like the whatever,
the top of it, the, I don't know, that attic,
but there's like kind of like coils at the top of it.
The Spire Tesla coil.
Sure, something like that, whatever.
And then that's happening during the light,
lightning storm, basically.
That's awesome.
And I'm just sipping and I'm like, this rules.
And then I go inside like, ah,
I'm like holding my coat and I'm soaked.
And they're like, hello fellow traveler,
welcome out of the, come in out of the rain
to the Frankenstein Castle.
And I'm like, okay.
And then there's nobody in there.
There's a few people, but I'm in rooms alone now.
Being in Frankenstein Manor with a thunderstorm going on,
that is something I never considered.
I didn't consider it either.
I didn't consider it either, but I was like,
cause I was out, I was like looking like,
well, this is the next best thing to not going
on the ride early is getting to sort of hang out here.
So I mean, I can say like, it's awesome.
There's a big staircase.
Should I mean, there's, I, okay, I'll say this.
There's, I saw the two pre-shows or two separate pre-shows.
Wow.
Maybe we're sort of in spoiler territory.
Maybe.
Yeah.
You were gonna maybe skip ahead a little bit.
So I guess skip ahead.
I don't know.
I'm conflicted.
35 minutes.
Skip ahead a minute, I guess.
Okay.
So there's sort of more of a video pre-show with Igor,
who we ran into in the land as a human performing
or character who's awesome.
And then there's a pre-show with two robots.
Wow.
Robots in queue.
Victoria and spoiler alert, Frankenstein.
Wow.
And it rules.
And I will say it got me so psyched.
I was like, ah, no.
He's a big boy.
Oh, he's huge.
He's huge.
He's great.
So I mean, there's other little surprises and stuff,
but that was really fun.
And I left, I got out of there,
and I went right back into the line again to do it again.
Neat.
Cool.
And then you know what's funny
is that I'm going through it again,
even more of a leisurely pace.
Obviously I'm hoping something, a miracle happens
and the ride opens or whatever.
But then they stop us right before the pre-shows
and we're waiting there for five, 10 minutes.
The park's gonna close very soon.
And they say, no, something's wrong.
You can't see these two pre-shows.
So we get a pass, a front of the line pass
for Epic Universe for every ride.
Like it could be for any ride other than Ministry,
I think Donkey Kong, and then something else.
And I have it with me still.
Wow.
So I'm gonna try to use it when we go back in June.
Does it work on other days?
Yes.
Have you checked the fine print?
It does.
Wow.
Yes, it does.
And I was told, even though it might technically expire
a day or two before we go, they will honor it.
I've been told that.
Really?
So I now have a fast pass for Epic Universe.
Geez.
Which may be key.
Because I'd rather keep talking about exciting stuff
than get into the weeds here.
But certainly I think our experience made us
a little afraid of like, oh boy,
how are these crowds gonna be?
How are these lines gonna be?
I think that is a powerful weapon that you wield
being able to skip a line at this place.
Because for everything that's cool about it,
I am certainly nervous about what are these queues gonna be.
Well, depending on the crowds, yeah.
It's like the Frankenstein family's secret to life itself.
It is very similar, yes.
I did read something, I think it was in Attractions magazine.
One maybe theme park insider, someone was talking about,
it seems like Universal is limiting day ticket sales.
Okay, yeah.
To allow like, I don't know what the numbers are,
but like 20,000 people in the park at a time
as opposed to 40,000 people waiting
in three hour lines complaining.
Yes, that's what I've heard.
That's probably smart.
You don't wanna, Universal probably haunted still
to some degree by opening day 1990
of Universal Studios Florida proper.
And then of course the bad first day
of Disneyland looms large.
You don't wanna, and by virtue of that,
it is the year 2025 and how much has been learned
and that they do this long preview period.
I think that prevents things from truly being
in a disaster state, but we know.
When you're dealing with ride technology
that's unprecedented and when you've got things
that seem to be sort of in the rise of the resistance
neck of the woods in terms of technology,
or Tiana keeps shutting down.
It's definitely going to be a thing
that stuff is not fully up and running
and that there's frustration and not everybody's
gonna be able to dial it in the way we were able
to measure our expectations once the doors are open
to the public, I don't know if that's gonna be
fully possible, so they gotta be careful.
And I think capping capacity is a smart way to do it.
And more recently even, every time a Potter thing opened,
it was multi-hour wait, like four to eight hour waits.
Eight, god.
That might have been when the land first opened.
Well, I think that's definitely on the table
for the Potter stuff because Ministry of Magic
is the other one that we did not get.
I don't think any, there was maybe,
at the time we had heard about a brief window
of people getting it, but I think that may have even been
like a VIP, sort of like a, that's not everybody.
So we weren't expecting that or certainly guaranteed that,
but I think that's gonna be close to the bone enough
that yeah, I could see that being completely
in the territory of that long of a wait.
Yeah, I waited three or four hours
opening summer for Gringotts and.
We waited four hours plus for Guardians Mission Breakout.
Wow.
Yeah, with very ad hoc switchbacks.
Geez, that is a lot of time to commit,
especially in like, the Florida park hours are not crazy.
I feel like I'm used to, you know, that a lot of the time,
Disneyland is open from eight to 12,
from eight a.m. to midnight, and then you go to Florida
and like, some of these are like 10 to six,
what do you mean? Seven o'clock, I know, it sucks.
Like that might be only enough for one line.
And that wasn't the case.
I know, the old days. In the 90s,
they used to be open really late,
extra magic hours would go to like two or three
in the morning. I know, it sucks.
And I was in Epcot at like two in the morning in 2021,
but it was only because we were staying
in Beach and Yacht Club,
and there were specific extra magic hours
if you were staying at Deluxe.
Like there were so many asterisks.
Okay, yeah, the Potter ride did not,
that was another where we got queue, but not ride.
Yeah.
That queue, holy shit.
I mean, it was built up to be holy shit,
and then sure enough, it is holy shit.
They have released images of this,
so this isn't particularly a spoiler,
but I like, this might be after,
but I hadn't seen the concept art for like,
it's the ministry of magic itself.
And I also have not seen those movies
as many people possibly have not.
So I didn't, I was told about a moment
that feels akin to the resistance,
the doors opening and you see all the stormtroopers
and everything in the scope of that room.
I was told something like that is coming,
and sure enough, the one corner that you round
is such a jaw dropper.
I don't think you've ever seen
just such a gigantic room in a queue.
Just the volume of space and the height of it.
I ended up looking at concept art later
and thinking this might be a case
where the reality is better than the concept art.
When does that happen?
When does that ever happen?
We've, there's been a lot of concept art letdowns
in theme park world in the last decade,
and this is like, I just, I don't wanna,
I will just prattle on and on
if I try to describe what the space is.
But as somebody said before we got to do it,
the tile budget alone, what does it take
to keep those tiles polished?
It is like, if you're a fan of tiles,
if you wanna see tiles sky high,
but inside a giant room, get ready.
It's four stories, basically.
Wow. Yes.
Which is, that's the scope of everything
in this Ministry of Magic world.
Somebody said the fact that the, what is it,
the tallest building in Diagon Alley
would be the smallest one here, completely insane.
Yeah, so beyond that, I don't have a lot to say.
Also, there is a room that I think
would have handily made it extremely far
in the fake office Final Four.
Oh yeah.
But I realize we have ignored a lot of potter
in that area in general.
Maybe some of that is the virtue of us paying less attention.
The current 2025 reality.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know,
paying a little less potter attention
because fuck that lady.
This land is funny due to current unrelated hate monger
events, but current studio events of like,
ah, it's like France from the Fantastic Beast movies.
And Warner Brothers has gone like,
we are no longer making the Fantastic Beast movies.
Yes, the most cursed group of actors
and people involved in general.
I think there was, there was definitely a world
where this was all called like Fantastic Beasts land.
Ah, yes.
So like, it's still like the remains of some of it.
And they shied away from like,
let's make that the centerpiece.
I mean, what I was thinking just from walking in,
I mean, there's probably a little bit of backup
that we should do and maybe reminding people
that the premise of this park is portals,
this four major, there's a portal you walk into,
the Kronos to enter the park at all.
From there, you enter this connective realm
called Celestial Park, then it's your choice
of which portal of the main four that you head into,
which are very effective and cool,
much like the pipe in all the Mario lands
that kind of limit your view and then open it up wide again.
And I don't think there's a better iteration of that
than Ministry of Magic, than entering their depiction
of France, which you almost could just take
the potter out of it.
And like, the Fantastic Beasts and all,
it doesn't really matter, it is just Magic Europe.
If that was the name of it,
I'd rather it just be called that.
Now you're going to Magic Europe.
And it's kind of cheating, it's splitting the difference.
Like, it's Magic France, 20th century,
and you get transferred to the British magic ministry.
Don't worry about it, you're here for a ride.
Sure, no, no, no, yeah, I didn't find myself confused
terribly, despite not knowing any of the mythology.
That is also, it's a holy shit in that queue,
but it's also a holy shit seeing the scope
of those buildings and how, I was telling you,
Michael, over there, how a number of theme parks
have gone for the vibe of Europe,
even gone for the vibe of France.
And we'd been in World Showcase just the day before.
Like, it is not unfamiliar to do a Parisian vibe
in a theme park.
This is unreal, though, and no previous depiction
of France has made me bug out of my skin
and think I'm actually there.
It's so, it's just like, yeah, light years
beyond any depiction of a country or vibe, or I,
yeah, it's just insane.
And the level of detail, the signage,
to be in a place that is so new it's not even open
to the public, and yet it feels 1,000 years old.
You just really appreciate the art design
and the craft to it, and it's a true magic trick.
Yeah, no, it is so good.
I think on some level I took it for granted
because of how, I mean, I haven't been to France,
but how well it is recreating a very lived-in
over hundreds of years place.
Sometimes you take it, you're like,
oh, yeah, yeah, I'm just here.
You don't even think about it in the way
that when you're seeing the how to train
your dragon land or monsters, which are obviously
a little more unusual for you to come across.
Yeah, they're not trying to depict a type of place
that exists, you have nowhere to set your expectation,
but again, to go back to the dreaminess
that you were feeling, it was just a bug out.
I felt just weird jitters in my brain,
how much it was transporting me across the world
so realistically.
I think that an interesting thing
about theme park location design is like,
yeah, film sets communicate the place
the film's taking place, but then editing
like layers and layers of filters and camera cuts
and all that stuff, you have that at your disposal
with filmmaking, but theme parks need to make
the place look like the final product.
Yeah, sure, from the get-go for one unbroken shot,
as it were, and it's just, yeah, it's jaw-dropping.
I don't, without having been on the ride,
I'm in no place to say if this is the best
of wizarding world, but I do know
that that initial reveal is like,
I just wanted the most impressive sights
in any universe park or any park, I'd say.
I'll say this too, going back to the ride,
this isn't, I guess I don't have to say specifically how,
but they did the King's Cross station thing
where you see the person go through the wall
on the Hogwarts Express.
The way they do a magical transport in the line
for the queue for Ministry of Magic is the best.
It's so cool, I went backwards and did it again.
Oh, you did, of course, yes, you should,
because the way that the King's Cross station one is like,
you see somebody go through the wall,
so it's almost like the illusion isn't happening
to you, actually, the person,
you're just seeing someone in front of you.
So you go, oh, that's cool,
it looks like they went through the wall.
This, the way they do it now, or in this ride,
it happens to you.
Yes, yeah.
You get to experience it, and it's a very, it's.
I went back and I'm like, I just gotta do this
with like arms wide open again, I just have,
I gotta like, no, you didn't take it in,
you didn't really do it enough.
It's simple too, it's not like,
I don't know how they did it,
it's just, I was very impressed with it.
It's a cool thing to happen to you.
Just a cool thing that happens to you
right before the big reveal.
Yeah, yeah.
I almost want to, and we don't have to fully veer away
from Potter, certainly, but I'm almost like wanting to
go elsewhere just by, for the sake of,
because we know it better, because we got to do other stuff.
Yeah.
If you don't mind hopping over to Nintendo.
Oh, sure.
Which was, was that the first like actual portal
we went through?
I want to say. I think so, yeah.
Well, I mean, I did, I did Stardust Racers first,
but that's not a portal.
We can talk Stardust Racers.
I don't care.
By the way. Either way.
Well, let's, yeah, why not talk Nintendo a little bit,
because that's, you know, Nintendo, we know we have it here,
we've had mixed feelings about some of the offerings,
but we, of course, made a beeline through the portal,
which, what's best portal?
What's best portal?
You mean, well.
It's yourself, regardless of what you see
when you're at the end of it,
because we ranked what we thought they were going to be
in an episode.
I want to say that was on a second gate.
Now that you've been, favorite portal.
You mean the literal.
It itself.
Walking through the portal itself.
Yes.
I mean, I think it's probably.
The design on the outside,
but what happens on the inside,
because some of them are longer than others.
I think all have like screen components
that kind of make it more magical.
I think it's Nintendo.
Yeah, I thought so too.
I thought it was a little leading that I asked you
that question at this moment.
I mean, I knew what you were going for.
But I, because I, the others are great.
I like all the portals very much.
Yeah.
But the escalator, the fact that you got an escalator.
Spoiler alert, there's an escalator
that takes you into.
Well, I like that.
It's really neat.
I love an escalator.
Well, it kind of, and it kind of makes you feel,
it feels a little vagacy.
It feels like you're going into a Mario casino.
That's a good point, yeah.
Yes, yeah.
Is it an escalator or a speed ramp?
Escalator.
It is steps, okay.
Yes, yeah.
Yeah.
So it definitely builds up that reveal
of the Mushroom Kingdom.
You get more music then too,
to really build up the reveal.
Yes, true.
You get a little hyped up.
And then, you know, obviously cool to see
the fully fleshed out version of Nintendo World
that is not really what we have here.
It has like the extra dimensions and room for Yoshi.
But we go pretty quickly straight back to Donkey Kong
and to Minecart Madness.
Yes.
Where to begin with Minecart Madness?
Well, there was a little bit of question I'd say.
I think we, I brought up the possibility
that maybe this thing was gonna be a little lacking,
a little underwhelmed.
I was concerned from ride through videos that I watched.
Yes.
We had really though, we were hanging a lot on this ride.
Yeah, I was.
One of the first things we wanted to do,
and it might have like set the tempo.
Yeah.
You know, if we really liked it,
if we didn't really like it.
Feelings?
It's really fun.
It's really good.
I really like it.
I can see there's a look, some of the,
there's a little like parts
where you really get jerked around.
But I don't know, it's fun.
It didn't bother me.
That's what you're after though.
You're always, you're wanting to get to.
I want to be handled in a certain way.
That's true.
And I want to get fucked up.
This is a new way.
This is a new sensation of being handled.
So I haven't gotten used to being handled that way yet.
And maybe I will completely grow to like it.
Now I will say, spoiler alert,
a lot of these rides at Universal crush my genitals.
Many of them, including Donkey Kong,
got pretty close to crushing my genitals.
I'm a tall guy.
The way I sit on these weird seats to point up.
And then I try to get away
only putting it down a little bit.
And then nine times out of 10,
an employee comes by, jams it right down on my penis.
Nine times out of 10, that's what happens.
And I believe on Donkey Kong,
I made it through not pushing it down.
But then on one of the jumps,
the thing ratcheted down anyway.
So I got crushed anyway on Donkey Kong.
Wow.
I was going to bring this up later.
I was going to address this in the curse
of the werewolf zone,
which is a spinning coaster in the monsters area.
Because we were seated next to each other there.
And it was at that point that you confided in me
that you seem to believe there's some kind of conspiracy
at Universal Studios specifically
to get your crotch as crushed as possible.
Yeah.
It certainly seems like it.
You said Diddy Kong looked at you and said,
even you cannot escape original sin, Michael.
It's being punished.
You're being punished.
I'm being punished.
I don't know what the deal with that is,
but something's going on.
Yeah, what is it?
Well, is it somehow related to the more serious size issue
that is complained about a lot at Disney?
To some degree it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That curse of the werewolf, my legs,
I had to cross my legs.
The employees were like,
you have to cross your legs for it
to be kind of comfortable.
My God.
So yes, talking about size-wise,
as far as just, I don't know, girth,
but height as well seems to be,
is that what I should say that's appropriate?
I don't think so.
Keep going.
I'm gonna see where this goes.
I'm just saying it's size-wise.
The roller coaster crushed my girth.
No, I didn't mean that.
No, no, no, I was saying that for people of size,
there's issues getting on the right.
Larger folk.
Yes, I'm not talking about.
He was not, I see, he was not taking an opportunity.
No, I'm not talking about his little soda can.
Oh God.
His full chub.
Now I have to leave this in, though.
No, I was just speaking to,
that's obviously the number one complaint
that people have is that they make these rides
for smaller frames or whatever,
but I also like, it seems like their ideal person
that gets in a ride is 5'9", 135 pounds.
Yes.
It's weird, I don't know what, I don't know why.
They want a roller coaster car full of chalamets.
They want a bunch of slight little guys.
Yeah.
That's not how the world is.
I can clear half of one of those.
Okay, well you're halfway there.
I can clear one of those, so.
Yeah, so it is something about it.
I mean, I noticed it first going on the mummy out here
20 years ago or something, where I was just like,
this is an odd angle, and if I don't,
if I'm not perfectly in before I have,
like there's a pressure that gets on you
when you're trying to get all your stuff,
put it away, clamp it down,
and especially if you haven't been on the ride yet.
So like, I need like a two minute prep time.
To settle in.
To settle in and make sure I'm sitting at the correct angle,
not to have one of these restraints come and crush me.
You would say you need a little foreplay
and a little aftercare to recover from those.
Is, be careful how you handle my girth.
Is, is aftercare a real term?
Yeah.
It is.
I was hoping you would say yes,
because I don't know what that.
It's like, cuddling and.
Oh, okay.
And patting, and being affectionate.
Now this is now, I don't,
despite this being questioned in the past,
I have been having sex for a long time.
And.
Yeah, it's pretty fun.
I've never, yeah, well this is what I found is
it's a great way to connect with my partner.
Yeah.
But when I, but I,
and yet the word aftercare is brand new to me.
Care?
I've never heard aftercare before.
Is this something the kids say?
I, I.
How long have you been saying it?
I, I haven't been saying, I learned about it.
I feel like a while ago.
Well, that's a while.
Five years?
Yeah, five years.
Maybe four, five years.
Five years of aftercare.
I mean, it's just.
Because I'm familiar with the concepts.
It's just politeness and.
I'm familiar with the concept that you're not supposed
to make love and then go see you later.
I know that.
Yeah.
I'm not totally out of it.
I know the cuddling is good.
I know that, but aftercare is new to me.
Oh, okay.
Well, you learn something new every day.
Yeah.
Not AppleCare, that's different.
That is different.
Oh, boy, they got me on the hook for that.
I don't care for that.
I never, I never, I never go in on the aftercare.
Just too, just too expensive.
I'm just, I'm a cheater, this guy.
Seven dollars a month for this goddamn watch.
So, so I guess what I'm getting at with Donkey Kong is
I was not sitting in a great position on Donkey Kong.
So some of the jerking around.
Well, from what it described,
from what you've described,
we ended up on the same flight,
and it sounds like a plane ride is this for you.
Oh, God.
Let alone, and you're not getting
your girth crunched on that.
Not unless you buckle your own seatbelt
in a very bizarre fashion.
No, plane ride in basic economy is hell for me,
knees-wise.
Just brute, like, it's, and then even sometimes
if you pay like a hundred dollars
to sit in the slightly better seats,
that's, you got, you're talking like four inches better.
That just turns you into me.
And now it becomes like the still not.
Right, it sucks for you.
It doesn't become first class.
It just becomes like you are bumping the seat
in front of you instead of squeezing
the high angle, your lanky legs.
So I need to really, I need to,
I need to prep better next time when we're in Epic.
I need to prep for all sorts of different ways
that my dick will be crushed.
I think, so that's a, if you are a fan of dick crushing,
then this is the park for you.
Well, yes, and that is a fetish.
I've heard of this.
Jason, you've heard of this, right?
Is there a name for it?
I don't know.
Cause like, you know, the, like,
in my mind, it's like a Wall Street guy.
He's really stressed out and he, you know,
he's into some dark stuff.
So he pays. Step on me.
He pays a lady with a high heeled shoe
to step on his penis.
It's like the cold open of the first,
the pilot of billions.
Oh, is that right?
Is that right?
But yeah, Paul Giamatti is like,
Dominatrix is beating him up and peeing on him.
And I believe that actor is eventually the woman
he would go on to marry.
Whoa.
Well, that's nice.
That's a nice love story.
Wow.
So yeah, no, I don't.
How did you meet?
Any rollercoaster just turns you into,
I'm trying to find the name really quick.
Chuck.
If you are,
God, like you get off these rides saying,
God, what am I?
US attorney Chuck Rhodes Jr.
If you are, if you are a day trader
and you're spending 10 grand, 20 grand on a mistress,
no, no, no.
Go down to Orlando, go to Universal Studios.
Yeah.
And you can get 150 bucks.
You can get your dick crushed all day.
And you're like, is this some weird,
is there some club I gotta know about?
No, no.
Oh, there is.
It's called Universal's Epic Universe.
For just a slight cover charge,
you can have, you can totally fulfill
all your crushing fantasies. Splurge for that express pass.
What's $200 to a day train?
You know?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, then you can speed through all the girth crushings.
But, but-
Poor Mike, poor Mike.
Donkey Kong was really fun.
I mean, I don't wanna put down-
But despite the dick crushings,
the children's roller coaster is a lot of fun.
No, it's, it was great.
I don't, I can't speak to how,
I think I had the concern, like,
how effective is that jumping feeling actually gonna be?
And I might say, not terribly,
it's not like the illusion was ever like,
wow, I'm jumping track.
But that, but maybe that's not what it's about.
It was a lot of fun either way.
And things that I, that seemed like okay in a video
were a lot more exciting in person.
A lot more exciting, yes.
Dixie, I do, despite having me not played these games
for a long time, I consider them my friends,
Donkey and Diddy and Dixie.
I was really excited to see Dixie, wow, Dixie!
Dixie Kong, yeah.
And then, and then Donkey Kong animatronic at the end
is massive. Rules, rules.
He's a big boy, he's great.
It is, and even in the land, the land you go in,
and it's playing the Donkey Kong country theme.
Yeah, exciting, very exciting.
And it's exciting to hear Mario and stuff,
and some especially like the Mario 64 castle music,
which they play when you kind of go up the escalator.
And that's nice, and there's great Mario music.
But for some reason, in a park setting,
the Donkey Kong country theme hits hard.
It really does, all of that, donk, donk, donk, donk, donk.
Yeah.
It is, it's so fun just being in an environment
that's that big piles of bananas
are just so aesthetically pleasing.
I just wanted to, I know that they would just be
rock hard, and I wouldn't just tumble into them
and get to roll around in them,
but I did want to just pounce backwards
into the banana piles, they look so nice.
Seeing those letters throughout the land,
K-O-N-G, like in the game.
And then also, I realize that it must especially appeal
to you, and me too, because I do like,
despite having complained about the food,
I do like the vibe of Margaritaville very much.
And you kind of do get, it is kind of like
cartoon Margaritaville.
Yes.
Like, because you do have sea planes,
and you do have island rhythms,
and it is a new, it shows you how
they cannot just, they can't just cram a thing together
and say that's the Nintendo theme park presence.
There's so much to do there,
because Donkey Kong feels entirely different
than Mushroom Kingdom.
Yeah.
And better, cooler, liked it.
Fountain, fountain, water gushing out of the mouth,
the big head on the temple, really cool to look at.
Yeah, the temple itself looks awesome as well.
The ride itself in the temple looks really cool.
And in a lot of ways, that track jumping looks cooler
if you're not on the ride.
Yeah, yes.
It almost plays better.
Cool decor to, this is so appealing.
I can't wait to have it in Los Angeles,
assuming that's where things are heading.
Yeah, really neat.
Now, I am worried, especially this one,
it is like, if this becomes two hour wait,
I don't know how you feel about.
I feel like I have the ideal wait time in my head
that aligns with what is a good Disneyland day for me.
You know what I mean?
Where this one, ideal, I'd like to be,
I'd like to be through Indy in 35 or something.
Sure.
And if that's an hour, I'm like, yeah, shit.
And I think this park for a long time
is gonna be like, excuse me?
What does this wait?
Yeah, maybe, it's a good question and point
because I think once you're past,
especially, I mean, the first couple months,
I do think your average park goer will have,
they know that this is not gonna be easy, I think,
if it's opening week, month, opening year,
I don't know, six months.
They might not, we might be breaking this to them.
Listener, if you've been planning to go,
I would count, if it was the way it was in preview,
maybe that's misrepresentative,
but my guess would certainly be
that these lines are gonna be outrageous.
That's gonna be very,
I mean, Donkey Kong's gonna be so popular.
People are gonna really wanna do that.
And rightfully so.
Yes.
But it is interesting because I wonder,
I wonder, I mean, this is something for a Lentesta
to figure out, how crazy does the ride experience
have to be to make you feel
that an hour plus wait was worth it?
I don't have this equation in my head,
but for instance, when we first went on Spider-Man
when I was whatever, in whatever year, 1999 or whatever,
we waited, it felt like four hours,
three or four hours to go on Spider-Man.
And we got off it and we're like,
it was worth it.
We did think that.
So it will be interesting to see if monsters in ministry
are the ones where, if people get stuck in there
for two hours, those things are so cool
that ultimately people are like,
well, I think it was awesome, though.
I think those are the only ones
that are really gonna happen.
It's possible, yeah.
Because Dunkin' is on the shorter side.
It definitely is, yeah.
And I could see, I don't know,
I was just on the lookout for what are the things
that are gonna tip anything into bad review territory.
And I think that could certainly be one.
Wait time wise, yeah.
Another one that I think is a bellwether
for what morale is gonna be like going through this park
is not far, and a thing we didn't get to do
because it's not in LA, Yoshi's Adventure.
I think that is one.
I'd had my questions about this, too,
in watching videos from Japan.
I have thought, is it like, I don't know,
like, it's a little dinky, right?
And if like, what if you waited 45 minutes for this,
I think you'd end up mad.
I think that you could see some lines that long
for Yoshi's Adventure, which I'd be worried about.
Now we got to do it, I think we did it twice
and one at the most, it was like 20 minutes.
I would like to go on record saying
I'm a big fan of Yoshi's Adventure.
I don't know if I'd be with a longer wait,
but as it is, it feels very Disney in its fantasy land type.
It doesn't promise much, but it really delivers
on the not much that it promises.
I think it's a key, I think it is the biggest error
by far in Nintendo in Hollywood
that they left this thing out.
It is like the thing, much like,
everybody talks about the Bantha thing
in Resident Resistance, for sure Yoshi
is the little, fun character, like the cute ride
that becomes weirdly the most important part
and the most fun part.
It makes me so mad that I can't take my kids on this thing
because I could take my little one,
I could take my seven-month-old on this thing.
That is truly a ride for everybody.
It's so cute, so fun, so successful at hitting
the kind of low bar that it sets for itself.
I really like this, I'm like very,
I don't know if I'm just like dad cute aglow
over this Yoshi ride, but I wanted to take my boys
very much.
I wish that, yes, I could take my daughter on this
because there is a really good big room,
big-ish room of robots that represents a lot of-
The show scene is a good, yeah.
I mean, it also makes me not upset,
but a little bit disappointed that you could have just
tripled the size of this ride.
It's not that big and had a really great-
It was like people mover length.
Well, that would be even better.
It's just a 10-minute jump through the entire-
That would be unbelievable, that would be unbelievable,
but I don't, it seems short-sighted to me
that you wouldn't put a actual kid's ride in Nintendo Land.
Like this.
And we've said before, I think some people with Mario Kart
like Mario Kart, but really, we would be fine
with a Mr. Toad Mario Kart.
We would be fine with a small dark ride Mario Kart as well.
It doesn't have to be Cars Land.
Much more fine, I think, with that, yeah, absolutely.
But so it is disappointing, I'm like,
this is such a fun, slow, good kid's ride,
but it gives you what you want,
a bunch of really big, fun robots.
Seeing baby Yoshi, would you call it baby Yoshi,
or would you call it like-
Well, they're like that.
It's like pre, it's like Yoshi Mach 1.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Before they eat stuff and then get big.
Super Mario World Yoshi, when he hatches
right out of the egg, but he's not big yet.
The ones that have to get carried around and fed.
Yeah, you've got a few to three berries,
and then he grows up into regular Yoshi.
Yeah, that too, you saw me with those berries.
I like stopped-
You got very excited about the berries.
I just like hugged them.
Seeing the Yoshi berries-
He did hug these physicalized?
I'm not making that up.
I did hug them at one point.
No, I saw it, I'm not making it up either.
He hugged the berries, I saw it.
I thought I did, like I blacked out.
What'd I do last night?
Did I hug a bunch of Yoshi berries?
Mike sent a picture of you at Jelly Rolls,
and you still had Yoshi berry all over your face.
Yeah.
I'm never watching this face again.
Hey, sounds like some of this land
already got hit with Donald Trump's tariffs, huh?
What?
Why?
In what way?
Well, I was trying to connect it to-
Now explain.
Nintendo delayed the pre-orders for the Switch 2.
Oh, okay.
Just this morning.
That's because of-
I didn't know that.
I just thought you were maybe like a berry-
Yeah, yeah, because it's gonna have to be imported.
Okay.
I thought you were doing like a berry delivery,
because you said the land,
so I was thinking like berries were-
The berries are a thousand dollars a bushel?
Yeah, I just got greedy, I don't know.
I know, I saw him-
And you threw a drumph in there too,
which just really threw the whole-
I didn't go, I'm just trying to contribute.
I like your sitting there.
That's the most defensive thing ever said.
Well, I'm not mad at it, I just wanted to be clear.
Yeah, I'll workshop it, I'll workshop it.
Just kidding, yeah, yeah, get the clubs.
I'll workshop for the live shows.
If you can edit, well, if you wanna come up with it
and then re-record the joke on your own,
I'll insert it in the show.
Just dub it in, yeah, yes.
Do it like ADR, okay,
you gotta drop it in exactly the same amount of time.
And then Scott and I will do
our own live reactions at home and I'll edit it all in.
Okay, put a cup, pot of coffee on,
get me some long cigarettes and I'll get to work.
Long cigarettes.
Oh, can I say something about your show too
before we move on?
We've touched on this on the show briefly,
but if you haven't been on this ride,
and you probably haven't,
because it's only in Japan,
to the public until this place opens,
it is a little kind of omnimover,
everybody gets the different colors of Yoshi
and you get to explore rooftops that,
technically you could see from a lot of places
in the Super Nintendo world,
but you get a special vantage point and little fun scenes
and one Yoshi chomping the other who blew up a balloon
and he's riding them around,
and you get a talking toad instead.
There's a lot of cute things you can only see
from these vantage points,
but there is a light,
I don't know if you'd call it a story,
I don't know if you'd call it a game,
but it's kind of a task that you have,
which is finding all three eggs of different colors.
Let's say, I don't remember,
I wanna say it's like spotted eggs
and it's like red, green, and blue.
The ride ended the first time,
Mike and I both failed to find all of the eggs.
We both just got a big old F
on the children's spot the egg game.
The children's word search kind of game.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, with big bold buttons.
Yes, no, it looks like the worksheets
that my son is bringing home from TK
and we got a two out of three.
I mean, that should be nicer, that's a D.
We didn't get an F, we got a D.
Well, look, we were taking in everything, you know?
Yeah, not so goal-oriented.
No.
Just trying to be there, be in the moment,
take a deep breath, but I felt very stupid
that I missed only three eggs, but less stupid
because you were also the same amount of stupid.
That's true, yes, we must have both remarked
about something we liked at the same time
when that egg passed.
It's just gonna be a cadre of millennial parents sobbing
because they see Yoshi and then a generation
of iPad kids going, what do you mean
you didn't get all the eggs?
Because they've spotted.
It's the easiest game ever made.
Yeah.
I've been playing things more complex
than this since I was four.
You put me on Fruit Ninja when I was three months old.
Yeah, no, I think about this all the time.
My daughter, one of her favorite things
is to watch me play video games now.
I've never played, I have been playing video games
the most in the last decade ever since she's been born
because she loves video games, but can you imagine
what she thinks a video game is
versus what we thought a video game was at five years old?
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
And then when I play Mario Odyssey and he turns 2D,
she goes, no, no flat Mario.
No, she doesn't like old school.
Yeah, she does not like old school.
She likes the bright 3D.
Well, then she would hate the portal
and the Kronos itself where it's like a coin
that flips around and it has kind of classic current Mario
but also 8-bit, which made me happy to see flat pixel Mario
but your daughter would freak out.
No, but not my toddler.
She only likes Mario in three dimensions.
Well, you just had to sit her down and explain the context.
I did.
Maybe put on some YouTube documentaries.
I have, I said, this is how daddy played the game
when he was your age, not your age,
but a little older than you.
And then she said her first words, shut up, daddy.
Bored, daddy.
No, she kinda says that. Daddy sucks.
She kinda says that.
Yeah, back to your Donkey Kong concern specifically,
I did pull out the Fastpass and it does say
it's not valid at the ministry and Minecart Madness.
So that must mean they also are concerned capacity-wise
because they don't wanna hand out a free
skip the line pass to Donkey Kong.
So I'm sure that-
They chose those two.
Those are the only two that you're restricted from buying.
Oh, so you can use for monsters again.
Use it for monsters or stardust or.
Interesting, that's weird.
Well, yeah, maybe it's less that they're considering
the e-ticket and more of a capacity.
This is, it's also really like, as we said about Yoshi,
now imagine Donkey Kong and it's double
and you really get cooking and you really get fast
on that thing.
That becomes one of the best rides ever made.
100% it does.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, there's a few things at Epic that do feel like
if you doubled this, it would be top ride in the world.
Yes, there's definitely a number of, oh, and we're done.
That does happen a lot, unfortunately.
Yeah, so, right.
So yeah, as far as the quality of the robots
and the quality of the jumps or the scares
or whatever you'd like, there were a couple of places
where like, ah, like I did go, like it got me for real
on Donkey and yes, it is,
Nintendo is so good and it feels like
with just a couple different changes early on,
it would have been like unbelievable.
Yeah.
Overall.
Yeah. With everything.
Well, it's just been crazy watching all of this migrate
from like, you know, okay, so these like AR helmets,
okay, well, it sounds like, boy,
that could really be interesting that we try it.
Oh God, not good.
Weird, crazy, then like it's like the common talking point
with like, you know, like other parents at school
if theme parks come up or like, or my mother-in-law,
that like, well, you know, I just tell the kids
just take the helmet off.
It's like, gone from like, it's something
we the theme park nerds know too,
it is the common talking point.
Yeah.
Those are people who just,
anybody who goes to the parks,
like the Mario Kart ride is fine if you don't have to wait
and you don't wear the helmet.
That was like the point of doing it.
What happened?
How does it land there?
I think it's still well received
by your average park goer in some ways.
Yeah.
Supposedly.
I know, I know what you mean.
I don't, and the fact that it'd be hard for them to say,
like, it's a failure because the lines are so crazy long
and it made it to the tidy two
in the fake office Final Four.
I mean, it has back and forth for it now too.
Yeah.
Like, you wanna talk about spoiler warning.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm sorry, if you hadn't listened to that.
You have your draft kings, like I...
How much you betting on this week's PTR?
How much are you betting on the PTR fake offices?
Can we go real quick?
I forgot.
I wanted to say, spoiler alert,
say the name of the drink I got.
I don't remember what was in it,
but in Burning Blade,
I really like the name of the drink.
Yes, what is it?
The name of the drink is My Only Weakness,
which is really fun to order on My Only Weakness.
That's really good.
Maybe a good time to pivot to some other food stuff
because actually the first thing we did when we came in
was get a bite with a group that we were with
and this gave you the opportunity.
First of all, what was that restaurant?
Was that called Oak and...
Oh yeah, Oak and something Tavern, yes.
Oak and Star Tavern, where I did not eat,
but every piece of food I was looking at on the table
looked pretty good.
Was yours?
It was, yeah, it was a little like,
I ate a barbecue sandwich for lunch with brisket.
Yeah, great, great.
But it was good, I mean it was good
and they had the Coke freestyle machines.
And in there, something very special
and that's what I wanted to get your thoughts on.
Oh, sure.
This is in How to Train Your Dragon, Isle of Berk.
No, this is, no, confusingly from that name,
now we are in Center of Park, Celestial Park.
Well, here we are.
Maybe there's a lot of, definitely it's like
the food and beverage place,
it's where sit-down restaurants are.
And we'll get into it.
Since you said Coke freestyle,
I forgot until we were there
that something very special is in there,
a very special beverage is in there.
Would you like to explain?
Yes, I think it's called the Celestial Spritz.
Jason, have you seen this?
No, what is this?
It's a soda that is only in Celestial Park.
Or only in the park in general?
Is this an Epic Universe specific soda?
It is, but it's not the only Universal,
Epic Universe specific soda
because I had one in Monsters as well.
Wow, wow.
So I just, I didn't know that until later,
but Celestial Spritz to me tasted like
you had like a peach soda
and then somebody dumped a bunch of water in it.
I wrote down, you described it as watered down Fanta.
Yeah, sure, yeah.
That's not a good review.
It wasn't my favorite thing I've ever had in the world.
It was okay, but I was excited to try it.
Yeah, all right, I'll try it.
I'll try all the different sodas.
Yes, but, but later in the Monsters land,
I tried Screaming Berry, Screaming Berry Zero
to be specific.
That has Mike Carlson written all over it.
And that was good.
Screaming Berry I'm a big fan of.
So I had one hand my only weakness
and another Screaming Berry Zero.
You were, so in the sandwich,
you were double fisted.
Carlson, one is alcoholic and one is far from alcoholic.
Correct.
Perfect cocktail.
And it's in that neck of the woods
that you're getting a little buzzed,
you're seeing a windmill light on fire,
real rain comes in.
It's a downpour.
It's a downpour, 25% of each drink was Florida rainwater.
That's a lot, yes, it's true, it's true.
What did Screaming Berry taste like?
It tasted like, you know, mixed berry soda of some kind.
And it wasn't so unique maybe,
but it was a good taste, I liked it.
Okay.
So I adore Screaming Berry.
Okay, okay.
Maybe not, I wish Celestial Spritz was better.
I know, that's, it would have been
a really victorious start to the day
that the Celestial Soda is a big hit.
Yeah.
I guess you can't say that it is.
That place, the theming,
the, just like, just the craft in the bar itself,
in the bathrooms. Yeah, it was really.
This was, they have really gone wild
just getting these restaurant facilities
looking real sharp, really well-adorned.
I was pretty blown away.
The place that, you know, you might think of like,
as being like, okay, so that's like
just the pizza place, right?
Yeah.
Pizza Moon.
Pizza Moon. Pizza Moon.
Jason, are you excited, do you know about this?
I know Pizza Moon, it like has the early film,
the moon with the rocket in the eye.
Well, that's the thing.
It's like, in any other restaurant,
any other theme park, this would just be like,
you know when there's a place to get pizza
and the pizza's fine, and I can't really,
I had a little bit and it seemed like
better than average theme park pizza,
which we've been talking about is typically very bad.
The theming and the design in this thing,
yes, it's full-on, I mean, the more clever reference
would be like old school trip to the moon,
but I went to the thing that tributes it,
Smashing Pumpkins Tonight Tonight.
You are in the Smashing Pumpkins Tonight Tonight video.
I thought you were gonna say Hugo.
Hi, Vart.
Oh, Scott's beloved Hugo.
Yeah, yeah.
It might be like stepping into Hugo.
Like for, all right, now open the door
to the pizza restaurant.
Dear God, crazy Disneyland Paris Discovery Land
level theming, like living dioramas with moving parts.
It is like so much cooler in there
than it has any right to be.
Pizza Moon is pretty wild, I gotta say.
Great, yeah.
I didn't spend, we walked through Pizza Moon,
you were in there a little longer than I was later,
but yeah, it is for quick service pizza.
It's not like a sit-down, you know,
you're not waited on or anything.
For quick service pizza, it's pretty crazy
that it's that detailed.
Yes, pretty astounding.
Then I was, oh yes, go ahead.
Is that where there's the little tongue?
Remind me.
There's a, like the Pizza Moon has a little tongue
and he goes.
On the outside?
I believe so.
I think so.
I think the moon has a little tongue.
A lightly upsetting moon tongue, yes.
The Pizza Moon tongue moves, and I was thrilled.
I was really excited.
Does it kind of back and forth?
Yeah, yeah, like he's like hungry.
You know, like when Jason gets hungry for a meal.
He goes.
I know it, I live it.
It's what he does in the steps before the aftercare.
Yeah, right.
My God.
Why was that so crazy?
How is that a level beyond anything that's been said?
Jason's offended for the first time on the show.
He fanned himself, like he had a fan on a porch.
He's just thinking about pizza.
My word.
He's just thinking about that pizza moon.
I'm thinking about the piece of grease getting everywhere.
It's quite the name, it's a lexicon.
I then got to sit and eat at the Atlantic,
that is the name of like the big sit down.
Yes, yes, yes.
Very early as you come into Celestial Park
with like grand views of the entire place
in the lake and the fountain.
Food was fantastic, really good cocktail there.
I think everybody was really happy.
It was during previews, however,
and it's hard to not say that it took 90 minutes
for the food to come.
This was sort of insane.
Granted, we were warned, like it's a little crazy in here,
but when you get to 90, you're like,
oh, it's more than a little crazy.
I don't mean to be a complainer.
This is a cool thing to get to do,
but you had a certain point.
So I don't know, all I can say is they gotta get a bit
of that before it opens to the public.
Fingers crossed, yeah.
Got a lot of very unhappy people.
I split off from the group at that point
because I had a feeling, I didn't know 90 minutes,
I just had a feeling like there'll be shenanigans
at a sit-down restaurant in previews.
No, you were right, you intuited correctly.
Yeah, I was like, you know what?
I think I'm gonna not do it.
So yeah, I wandered at this point.
But it was kind of like, as far as how we played the day,
I think there were no regrets on any end
because you didn't have to do food hijinks,
but I was like, what if we're sitting here forever
not getting our food and then suddenly they open Monsters?
They did not.
Well, sure.
As we're checking, we're watching ride after ride
go down as we're sitting and not getting our food.
We're like, what's happening?
This has just melt down fully in this place.
Again, our experience, I don't know if this is how
it's gonna keep going, might have been only that day.
Theme Park previews, interesting, I don't know.
Just never gotten to do it.
It's wild to hit points of like, whoa, what's going on?
This is getting crazy around here.
Yeah, it would have been fun to hang out.
I mean, I mean this sincerely.
It would have been kind of fun to hang out
and go, oh my God, it's taking so long at this restaurant.
I wouldn't have had a fit or anything
because going in, that's sort of the whole thing.
But I just get, I'm a little regular with my eating.
I'm kind of like, I need a piece of bread.
That's the sense I got when you went to do it
is that you needed to eat.
Yeah, right then and then from there,
I waited and waited for this.
Yes.
Yeah.
No, not great, didn't play out great.
I wandered to the show, the Harry Potter show at that point.
Oh, right, yes.
Which I don't wanna, I guess I really
don't wanna spoil that.
Yeah, I know, I like it and I recommend it.
I almost don't wanna go further.
All I'll say is that that, go see it.
And I am very impressed with them making me confused
about the geography of where I am.
I know where I entered.
I know I could get back there if I was in the park.
But I couldn't draw on a map where I was
once the show happened.
Because basically, and this'll be,
I think this is a good way to talk about this
without actually spoiling the show
is that there's a little tent.
You probably see pictures of it.
It's a little tent like, oh, a little show, come on in.
Because it's a circus.
What is it?
Circus show or whatever.
Is it Cirque Arcanou?
Yes.
Is that the right word?
I believe Cirque Arcanou, something like that.
Cirque Arcanou.
Yes, and there's a, spoiler alert,
there's a guy that does talks like this, which is great.
Maybe there is in the movie, I don't know.
That might be a good story.
Never seen it.
Don't know.
I don't know about the Cirque Arcanou.
Never gonna see it.
There's a tent, there's a tent.
And yeah, and you go into it and it's a very small,
this is operationally, I'm wondering how they will do this
because there's not a queue to get in the tent.
There's just a big clump of people all being funneled
into a very small tent.
And I was like, oh, this is gonna be interesting
on an opening week or whatever.
Because it felt very chaotic.
It felt like, ah, people didn't know where they were going,
whatever, and we're funneling into a small tent.
And then you go in this queue that is really intimate.
There's really kind of small, just like,
and I'm like, I don't know anything about this.
And then ultimately you filter into another room
and you filter into a theater.
But once we're in the theater,
I was like, where are we in the park?
Because it doesn't give you any hint
of a full big theater show.
So you obviously, you're somewhere backstage in some ways.
It's a real, I wanna say it's like a Russian nesting doll,
but that doesn't feel accurate
because those get smaller and smaller.
This is like, it's like an inverse.
It gets so, I was there a bigger doll inside.
It's an opposite Russian nesting doll.
You see, you get it?
Great.
It feels like The Masked Magician,
a lot of the tricks on Masked Magician,
it's like, oh, they've actually been doing this
for like 100 years.
It's still just trickery and it still works.
All it really was, I'm sure,
is they just funnel you backstage.
Yeah.
It just doesn't, the way you kind of wind around
in that initial line, then go into the pre-show
and then go into a theater,
it just, like your brain just doesn't quite know
where you are.
And I would, it'd be interesting,
I didn't try this yet to go on Google Maps
and go, oh, here's the theater.
Figure out where the actual facility is.
Because I'm just, it's a very effective way
at disorienting you.
It makes you think you're getting something
that's smaller scale than what it ends up being.
Yes, exactly.
So, and then, yes.
Then you go, oh, wow, this is a bigger thing.
I thought maybe the pre-show was actually the show.
Yeah, yes.
For a half second.
Because something fun happens.
I'll say this, you see the show,
you're like, oh, it's gonna be one of these
and that'll be fun.
And then there's something else happens
and you go, oh, okay, okay.
No, no, bigger, yeah, yeah.
You got some bigger scale scope.
Yeah, it's almost the most spoilery thing.
It's, it is hard to talk about.
Yeah, I don't wanna say it.
I won't say it.
So, here's what I would, I'm gonna, you know,
I touched on the negative,
the way that this food situation worked out.
And here's where, Jason, I don't wanna,
I don't wanna break your little heart here.
But there is, I wanna touch on a little bit of downside
of the trip.
I think Mike may have already warned me
about where you're going.
Yeah, yes.
And I don't wanna break the audience's little hearts either.
But there's, you know, I think there's been a lot of buildup
in the pre-materials about Celestial Park
and about this, like, that it's, you know,
it's not really like an entrance area and just that.
That it's not, that it's like Main Street.
And then it just ends.
That it's like kind of this connective tissue
that is a land in and of itself.
I don't know if it's working.
I'm not sure that I currently feel good about.
Now, granted, this is previews.
And granted, there were people who were saying,
oh, you know what, now those trees
and this and this and this,
that wasn't here a couple weeks ago.
So by the, when we get to May,
things might be really humming here.
It'll be interesting to see.
But I would say that one, Celestial Park, for me,
was the biggest disconnect between how it was built up
and what was shown and what it actually is.
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna be negative.
All I'll say, well, not all I'll say.
All I'll kinda say.
All I'll say is 10 things.
There's a lot of concrete in Celestial Park.
Yeah.
So I don't, we'll see.
I'm very curious to see what happens in two months.
Because yes, it felt like there weren't really
any walk-around performers.
Not as much green as I wanted.
No.
And it felt like walking long distances
on concrete between worlds.
Where you want, in my mind, I was like,
we're gonna be on the planet Vulcan,
like the most beautiful part of Vulcan.
Philosophers, everyone's in robes,
people coming up to you.
There's beautiful.
As if you're on some sort of incredible
creative, philosophical retreat.
That's what I pictured, yeah.
That you were in a mind-bending place.
Exactly.
But instead it feels a little bit like,
this is a particularly nice mall in Newport Beach.
Yes, and the architecture for the buildings is amazing.
Don't get me wrong. And what's in there is amazing.
And then there's a Mario gift shop outside of Mario,
and that has stained glass and statues.
There is beautiful stuff to see everywhere you go,
and yet there's not a lot making me go,
Celestial Park is magical.
It's really the long, big,
it's just how much pavement there is.
Yeah.
Open pavement with no shading.
And it just becomes like,
I'm annoyed when I'm in Celestial Park,
because it's really far from here to there,
and I wanna be over there,
and right now I got nothing to look at.
There's not even a design on this concrete,
which I thought there was gonna be.
It seems like they have to pack a lot more trees in.
I think so.
Which might also be like. Grass would be nice too.
New growth tree,
like I've watched a lot of videos about Lost Island,
the park in Iowa, I think?
And that seems like it has some trees,
but some of the trees are very young saplings.
Okay.
That will not grow and really bloom.
This is a newish park?
I don't think I know about this park.
In the last couple years,
I think it's the one with the original Sally Dark Ride
volcano kind of creation.
Okay, okay.
This is like,
if I have complaints,
it is things along these lines,
and it is like,
not really knowing what it's like to be
in a fully brand new theme park.
You can feel that thing.
I'm sure being in Disneyland in 1955 felt like,
this is it.
There's plots of it that are just kinda nothing.
I know that these things grow and evolve,
and that tree growth is a massive thing.
I have no doubts that in 10 years,
this is gonna be immaculate,
that all of it is gonna be,
but I think the way that they've been hyping it up,
I was thinking,
oh my God, are we talking,
is this Disney Sea or something?
Yeah.
And there is something about the grounds and sight lines,
and again, maybe they're not done.
I don't really know. Well, they're not done.
Okay, okay.
But I think that maybe at night,
because we ended our preview at 7 p.m. before stuff.
I have a feeling maybe at night,
the wow factor of Celestial Park and everything else
will be there.
I'm guessing just from the things like
the bioreconstruct pictures you see at night.
It looks so great from the sky.
But I'm a little disappointed by how it feels
on the ground.
I think the vibes,
hopefully, fingers crossed, will be strong at night
to the point where you go,
wow, this is incredible to see
all the different lights everywhere,
and the hotel lit up,
and the different built.
I bet it achieves its mission there.
It's just that I wonder, yes,
if they can make the magic happen during the day.
Because it definitely felt like
a concrete jungle of some kind.
Water features, fountains, stuff like that.
That wasn't on, really, was it?
No, I mean, fountains were going.
But there wasn't a big show, though.
Those weren't exactly shimmering,
beautiful, Pandora way of water.
There's something, it felt a little bit,
somehow, chinchier than what I thought
from the concept.
I'm sure everyone knows.
So I'm so curious to see in two months.
That is, honestly, kind of what's fun to see.
We could be so far off base.
I could be dead wrong, I mean.
And this isn't, I've read in the trades,
not the trades, the rumor mill,
that they've subbed out entertainment already, as well.
So there was.
And I guess, you know what,
I talked to some people who did a preview, as well,
that got to see celestial entertainment that was roaming,
that apparently has been scrapped.
Oh, man.
So I think there are things happening.
This is powering some galaxy's edge territory, uh-oh.
And I don't know if it's scrapped because of a budget,
or it's just scrapped because, okay, that's not working,
let's try this.
Oh, maybe, maybe.
Yeah, so I don't wanna make it seem like
I think they've cut the budget, or maybe they have,
I don't know, but like, stuff is changing.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't wanna be like a,
you know, like they show early cuts of movies,
and I don't wanna be the audience member going,
there's one part where it's just green behind the guy.
Are you gonna fix that?
I hope I'm not that.
I hope that I'm not so just ignorant of like,
yeah, they're gonna fix that.
I don't know.
But I would say Celestial Park is the area
that made me the most nervous as far as this being like,
truly next level versus like every nook and cranny
of this place.
I also think there's something up with,
and maybe this will slowly get addressed too,
I think that this plot of land
is not a particularly magical plot of land.
You know how in theme park concept art,
it's always like, here's the land,
then it just kinda like casts off into trees and stuff?
And Disney World is like, they're very lucky there.
That's such ideal land because it does feel like
past space mountain and contemporary,
it just turns into forest, right?
Here, it's extremely clear that it's like,
then over there is the road.
Over there is like where they deliver shit.
Like everything around it is not particularly,
you could feel that this was just like industrial land
seven years ago or whatever.
And I think that will kind of like go away,
but it does need some like,
they gotta like plant some trees and cover some shit
because there are parts where you're in the queue
or on the ride and you do see like loading docks.
And again, this is not so like,
we've all been going on test track for decades.
Test track is a ride that takes you through a parking lot.
It's not like this is specifically a universal problem,
but like, I don't know,
there's like a little bit of magicing up,
I think they still gotta do.
I think that universal fans,
three of us certainly are universal fans.
I think there's certainly a desire
from the public at large to want universal
to get a couple shots in on Disney.
Yeah, we want it to be way better, yeah.
Right, we do desire that.
And I think people,
because people are a little bit annoyed with Disney
for many, many reasons over the last so many years
that I do think you can see it online
where it's like, oh my God, Disney killer.
Some people are a little over-hypey about everything.
We've heard plenty of stuff and that's just,
people's personality tends to wanna do that over-hype.
I am guilty of that sometimes.
And you're an online person and you wanna go
greatest thing ever or worst thing ever.
As opposed to what we're doing here,
which is kind of like, I like this,
this is a very gray area kind of discussion.
Yeah, so honestly, somewhat expectations
have to be tempered in general.
But I do think the first impression
going into a park is very important.
And all, Jason, all joking aside with Islands of Adventure,
we did a very controversial Port of Entry episode
a year or two ago where I was joshing around a little bit.
Some people thought that might,
I was maybe being serious that I didn't like Port of Entry.
But Port of Entry is legit music-wise, architecture-wise.
You do go in there.
You're a character pretty immediately.
There's a lot of character, you see the whole,
why can't I think of the name of it?
Ferris Lighthouse?
The Ferris Lighthouse.
You can't think of the name of it
because none of us knew the name of it three years ago.
That's maybe why.
But the lighthouse, I should've said the lighthouse.
Recreation, one of the modern,
the wonders of the ancient world.
Well, of course, now I remember everything about it.
As opposed to the modern world
where we have like the Bass Pro Shop pyramid.
Right, but that's one of the wonders of the world
as far as I'm concerned.
Sure.
Dream destination.
When you talk about Tokyo Disney Sea,
you walk in Tokyo Disney Sea,
you go, holy fuck, I've never been in a place like this
before. Yes, yeah.
Which, and we're holding it to the best of the best.
And that's an insane standard.
But also, let's go back to Island's Adventure, too.
Yes, it's Port of Entry and all that,
but then it delivers you to this grand lagoon.
Which, even though it is nothing, right?
It is water, there's not a bunch of,
they did go in a different direction
by not making it a big body of water,
which is a great way to fill a bunch of land
and make it feel very lived in.
So it is kind of like risky and different,
what they've done, that it's more like,
there is some water that it ebbs and flows,
and then there's a lot of just open space.
Yeah.
But it, yeah, I don't know that it's a holy shit,
and you know, I'm so sorry to say this,
with all appall-
this is not one of these spicy takes that I revel in.
I am not proud as I say this.
I don't know about that Kronos.
I don't think that Kronos is like,
it doesn't top Ferris Lighthouse, I'll tell you that.
Yeah, I think you're more-
Not by a long shot.
I think you're more down on the Kronos than I am.
I'm not saying it beats the lighthouse.
I'm not saying it beats it.
It wasn't running, it wasn't really running.
That hurts it.
And from a distance, we saw some night effects
after we were on the way.
I'm reserving my Kronos judgment for opening day.
I'm gonna wait-
For the two hour Kronos episode.
Yes, we're gonna do a lot of Kronos,
maybe one episode per Kronos.
Per medallion.
Per different, yeah.
Are you talking about per portal or per,
there's only one Kronos.
No, I guess you're right, yeah,
But you're talking about each portal
with its own Kronos-like structure on top.
We could do an episode about multiple Kronoses
because they are taking, and if you don't know,
this is like the entrance of the park,
we should say, the tower that you walk through,
the very first portal that you enter for the day.
They're doing a tour of a Kronos replica.
That's fun.
It's going city to city.
We're taking it on the road.
Yeah, yeah, I forget where.
It's not LA, but you can go to Chicago
and a couple other cities
and see a slightly smaller Kronos.
That is fun.
So, I hear what you're saying
and I don't disagree with the instinct,
but I wanna wait a second before I make my ruling.
I mean, I like getting our thoughts out in this way
because, and not in a negative way,
because I am interested to see what they do in two months.
I do find that fascinating.
I want people to say Scott was a fool.
A creative decision.
He judged early.
He didn't understand that the sound wasn't mixed yet
and they hadn't finished the color correct.
And that's why he was judging the, I hope that's the case.
It's possible that will happen.
So yeah, I do wonder how it will shake out
by opening day and then a year from now,
because yeah, I want,
I did have my expectations high for getting in there
and seeing Helios Grand and seeing everything
and wanting to feel like that land,
because I think you've been saying,
oh, that land is maybe my most desired location.
That's the one I wanna go to the most.
Well, I think it's the Monster's Ride in Celestial Park
were high on my list and then everything else
is kind of great,
because I don't know how much I'll be able to get done
when it's officially open.
So, there's something needs, something that's needed there.
Maybe they're doing it.
I hope they're doing it.
Maybe they'll do it.
I'll say this.
We were talking about sight lines
and the area in which the park was built.
I do, and maybe internally they've thought of this
and there's just, they can't do it,
but the number one thing I think Universal needs to do
is fight against the Disney bubble
and the Disney culture of hotels and things to do.
I kind of think that's the magic sauce to Disney World,
because we always have these arguments with people.
Disney World's better.
Obviously these are people that don't go as often as we do,
but what they're talking about
is the trees covering the hotels, the sight lines.
They're talking about that.
They're talking about the multiple hotels.
Whether they're saying it or not,
their memory of Disney World is based on the Disney bubble.
You're fully immersed and especially if you went as a kid
when it was vastly more affordable to stay at
Grand Floridian or Polynesian or Contemporary,
that if you're, like, you know,
because we can talk all day.
Stella Nova's interesting, it's like a building.
You know, that's how Disney builds things now, too.
But not to say it's a pretty decent building,
but if you went to Disney World as a kid, as we did,
and you enter a magical world for the day
and then you go back to the hotel
and the hotel is also a magical world.
I'm in an island paradise.
I'm in a sleek structure of the future.
I'm in this, like, Victorian grand, you know,
like, high status place.
Yeah.
I'm in the wilderness lodge.
I'm in nature.
I'm, like, that it doesn't end when you go back to your room
and then for adults and for parents that, like,
oh, and then there's, like, actually good restaurants
and there's good drinks and, like, this stuff.
Because you're right that Universal has some of that,
but what it has a lot of is, like,
and then technically we do have a little bar
and it's, like, very bright and not a lot to look at.
Right.
And there's kind of, like, a cafeteria there.
Well, one of the criticisms of Universal Hotels I've heard
is, like, it's a Lowe's Hotel.
It's just endless hallways.
It just keeps wrapping and wrapping.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, certainly.
And, yes, so.
Disney has always had magic to the grounds
and some of that is that Walt bought, however many make,
he bought, you know, bigger than Manhattan
and so it just is, like, some of that is just what they got
and a lot of it's literally undeveloped.
And, but, whereas Universal has piecemealed it
from these odd, all right, let's buy this from Lockheed,
okay, we can buy a hotel over here
and you can take a bus and, like, they've had to do it
in this piecemeal janky way and they've done a great job.
Everything they've made is great.
But, yeah, there's not, you could, I think, say,
with a fairly straight face, you know,
I just chase that Disney magic
and I don't think anybody says,
I just chase that Universal magic.
Yes, and what, again, somebody might tell me
that it's impossible to do what you're saying.
Just the size they have, the land they bought for cheap,
the trees that were already there,
because that's, it's just impossible.
But that's actually the thing that would flip,
I mean, obviously, prices could flip people's vacation habits.
But that's the thing if people started feeling
like they were going into the little magical world
of Universal, whatever version of bubble
they could construct, that is the thing that I think.
And they have it a little.
They have it a little.
Yeah, like, as we've, we talked so highly
about those boats and getting, what we,
for as much as there were, there were problems
with forcing ourselves to live at City Walk, essentially,
for a little bit. Yeah.
The part that was good was like, wow,
this system of canals and getting on the boat
and getting a little ride at the beginning
and the end of the day. Yeah.
And some of those hotels have magic.
I think when they made that switch from
Universal Studios is a parking lot
and you walk up to it and that's your day,
to it's this world of waterways
and there's a zillion things to do.
They got some of the way there,
but it's the challenge of we built a park down the road
is like, well, how do you make a bubble
when you gotta go out on a real road?
I know. It's enough.
Yeah, I mean, the first thing you're describing
is it requires a huge capital investment.
Oh, yeah.
But it also, to some extent, there's design priorities
because Island's Adventure felt pretty lived in
even the first two years.
Certainly, yeah.
And I think they did hide the real,
there is a high school right behind Island's Adventure.
Right, right.
But you might not know that, you know?
Yeah, there's something, I don't know,
it feels like there's more of a burn moon
if there is a little. That got hit better,
but then like- Yeah, but now there's I-4
if you're building down the road.
And Volcano Bay, if you're waiting in line up the stairs
on one of the water slides, there's just houses,
you could see, you're just like,
oh, mother of a road and houses.
I'm in my bathing suit on an elevated platform
looking into somebody's house.
So- Yeah, kind of close to what like Knott's Berry Farm
kind of uses their advantage of being like,
oh, it's a neighborhood theme park.
Right, so again, they're gonna,
I'm sure someone will tell me it's impossible
to do more of what I'm saying, and I get that,
but it does feel like, oh, Stellaluna,
or whatever the hell the name of it is, Stellanova.
You know, you peek your head and you're like,
there should be like one cool, unique thing in this hotel,
whether it's the bar or something that you could go into,
and you wanna go and look at the hotels of Universal.
You wanna, and maybe this is a 10-year plan
that there's gonna be a walkway from these hotels to Epic,
and Epic will start its own little location
that has maybe a city, I don't know how much they own there.
What if they, also if they, you know,
some of that, not an insignificant amount
of that Disney World magic is monorail,
and now Skyliner, and that the ways you get around
are magical, too.
Yes, right.
If Universal could figure out something
that isn't just buses, it would be, I don't know,
like if they're little magical potter carriages
that can take you from, or that's part of it.
It's not crucial, and this is really,
we really are like, we went to a brand new theme park,
but we think also that the buses should be neat, too.
I don't mean to be like a little complainy toddler,
but I think, you know, I think we are,
what we want is Disney World's magical and immersive,
Universal's magical and immersive,
like both have it all, and they all,
it's all perfect, and they all fight,
and they make each other better.
Yeah, I think in Florida, the main requirements are
the buses are reliable and cold.
So that's bare minimum.
As long as they do that, you're honest.
I wanna get to stuff we haven't touched on yet.
Isle of Berk.
Oh yeah.
You guys saw it already.
Isle of Berk.
Loved, Isle of Berk.
I think Isle of Berk is maybe the best land.
I think it's maybe the winner.
There's, I think, yeah, there's something about the like,
the lower expectations of like,
what's this, how to train your dragon, why,
who likes that, well, obviously lots of kids like it,
and it's gonna blow up even bigger than it already is
with the live action coming out, and like,
but it really, you know, with this thing that we've hit
over and over through the years of,
we don't care what the IP is,
as long as it's rendered wonderfully and magically.
I don't know anything about this franchise,
and I thought it was so great and charming.
And you don't need to, it almost reads to me
as just an original theme park world.
It just, like, Vikings plus dragons, wonderful, cool.
I think with Nintendo, you have, and especially Donkey Kong,
you've got a very, like, that's the fantasy land,
or that's the Toon Lagoon, and I think it's like,
that's like the kid place, bright, colorful poppy.
This is kind of the, this is like,
I think the really successful family land,
where everything is stuff that you can do together.
Just aesthetically, without even getting on anything,
I think, all this, just the placemaking's really neat.
And there's a lot going on, too,
because there's a lot of meet and greets with the dragons.
I saw the Boston Dynamics, like, robot dog
dressed up as a dragon, walking autonomously.
What? I didn't see that.
Yeah, so there was just a dragon walking around,
but it was the, like, Boston Dynamics dog, basically,
that robot dog that they used for Dr. Toothsome.
Toothsome's dog.
What was his name?
Widget?
No, it was...
Coco?
What was it?
Was it Coco or Truffle, or?
Let's call him Truffle.
I feel like it was a chocolate-based one.
Maybe it was Truffle.
Bon Bon?
Bon Bon, let's call him all of them.
2020, I don't particularly remember
limited run theme park attractions.
It's Bon Bon, but it's the O's or zeroes.
That's how you make it a robot.
Well, that's good.
I was gonna call him Dollar,
but I think that's Richie Rich's dog.
I think Dollar is Richie Rich's dog.
I'm gonna go ahead and say that's Richie Rich's dog.
I got Richie Rich on the brain, I don't know.
Well, I was gonna say, I don't know what's going on.
I know what's going on, it's my brain.
I got Richie Rich on the brain.
Finally firing up that live-action Netflix series
12 years later.
With the weird 12-year-old maid robot one?
That's weird, it's a weird show.
I've watched one episode, but not classic Richie Rich.
That's good and pure.
The comic strip, cartoon, you know.
Yeah, the Harvey, yeah.
The Harvey comic book.
We're all thinking about it.
They should build Richie Rich world at Epic Universe.
All right, all right, calm down.
At the very least, the Harvey comics portal.
I wanna see their laser carved Mount Rushmore
of the family spades.
That would be awesome, that would be great.
John Larrick Kow attacks the monkey.
Casper Lee.
So, Isla Burke from Marks too.
Yes, and there's a meet and greet.
It might be with Toothless.
I know one of the dragons that's the big dragon
is Toothless, the dragon.
Toothless is the black one that's like that.
I know him from posters.
Right.
I know him from, there is a meet and greet,
and I'm watching it.
Again, I've never seen these movies,
and I will, these movies I will probably see.
Sooner rather than later.
There's a meet and greet with Toothless,
and there's like a handler, and they play like nice,
I don't know, sad music.
I don't know, like sentimental music
while the kids are going up to meet the dragon.
I tear up so hard, so quickly.
It wasn't even like I'm sitting and watching
multiple kids go through.
Literally, I walk by, I see a kid meeting a dragon.
I don't know if it's because the dads left their kids
behind on this trip, and that's part of it.
I'm sure it is on some level,
but immediately I tear up seeing kids hearing this music
with Toothless with these characters
I have no connection with whatsoever.
So I go, well, I guess this works.
I guess this is doing well.
I had a similar reaction.
You sent me that longer Superman trailer
that I'm assuming is from like CinemaCon.
Yes.
It came out.
With crypto, yes, which I showed my daughter.
Crypto's jumping on him like a real dog.
Like I was freaking out.
You know what, I'll say this about that.
They showed the five-minute scene from Superman.
They showed the trailer, and I was like,
ah, is this gonna work?
And I see that they did the longer one
where crypto's like beating the shit out of,
already beaten to shit Superman.
Because he's excited to see him.
And I was like, well, this is kind of good, I guess.
I guess I kind of like this.
Okay, huh, Superman hope.
So yeah, so I was like, oh man,
these meet and greets are gonna be awesome
for kids and for parents watching them.
You know, I wasn't paying a lot of attention to like the,
I don't even know if it was all open.
There's like a kid run around area in there,
kind of like a rope and climb zone.
Oh yeah, yeah.
And then I actually don't know if they were running
like the boats that you like fire.
They weren't.
Okay, okay.
And that looks awesome too.
But yeah, they weren't running.
And it felt like full of life without even those goings.
So I can, I just, I feel like this is just like,
families will really post up here for a long time.
I bet the weights are gonna be bad
because it's gonna be very popular around here.
Yeah, yes.
We popped into the, like their quick service
and that was like a little like mead hole.
Obviously they don't, maybe they serve.
I didn't go in there.
I would have liked to, it looks cool in the concept.
The show wasn't running also,
which I've heard very good things about.
There's also a show in that land.
Which is also, it's in Beijing.
It's in Beijing, okay.
Yes, so you can see it online too,
but like, and probably everything's online
by the time we put this out, but.
The main coaster there, Hiccups Wing gliders,
which does not stay in my brain,
me not knowing these movies at all.
I really was like, is Hiccup a dragon?
Main guy.
No, Hiccup is main guy.
Hiccup is.
What's his name?
Jay.
I'm so ignorant of this thing, Jay Berischel.
Yeah.
Yeah, Hiccup, I'm Hiccup, it's Hiccup.
But I, this I think, I think we all had this reaction
because you only see bits and pieces of it
as you're in the line and as you're in the land.
And you're thinking, okay, family coaster,
Goofy's Barnstormer, sounds good.
Well, I'm here, I'll do it.
I don't think I realized this is like,
as somebody in our group described it, like Hagrid's Jr.
Yes, absolutely.
It's so fun.
This is a little sneaker-upper.
Yeah, it is.
It's not, you know, obviously like, it's a coaster
with multiple launches that they meant to be cool
and high-tech and fun.
But I was not prepared for,
and I'll sort of leave it a little spoiler-free, I guess,
and maybe I already did too many, sorry.
Just like, hey, don't sleep on Hiccup's Wing glider.
I don't know.
That is a good ride and a good like kind of trainer ride,
you know, maybe for me to take my children on
so that they end up launch queens and not no launch queens.
I was happy.
I was like, oh, good, maybe I take my wife on this
because after Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind,
I'm like, all of these new rides,
she's gonna get off and run to a trash can and puke.
Well, Werewolf, maybe.
Werewolf, maybe, okay.
Although it's short.
It's short, yeah.
Maybe, okay.
Okay.
Yeah, I think this would be totally fine.
This would be fine.
The fun fake-outs, show scenes,
things you don't expect it to do.
It's, yeah, no, just caught me off guard.
High on my list, very high on my list.
I agree, and what's fun about it too is that
they use the actual land itself as the show scenes
in most of it.
Oh, great.
There's some stuff that's hidden that happens
that you can't see from the line or from the land,
but it's like using, it's like as if the fantasy land
had a ride that used fantasy land,
the backdrop and the castle for the show scenes.
Yes, yeah.
Which I think is cool.
And it's kind of a similar effect in Donkey Kong Country.
Yeah, to some degree.
And a little bit Curse of the Werewolf as well.
You kind of explore the grounds a little bit.
A little bit.
And you might think, well, it's a ride
that just takes me through all the other stuff in the land.
That seems repetitive.
But actually, no, it gives you new perspectives.
It's economical.
You get to see things in cool, new ways.
But I think having not gotten on the e-tickets,
my big headline, and when people have been asking me,
I just keep saying it's like trilogy
of not that intense family coasters
that are all pretty remarkable.
I think those three.
Yeah.
That's great.
Yeah, Werewolf Kong and this.
I think that's a design trend I am very fond of
is like augmented reality or gamification.
It's like, I don't know if those have the,
can stack up.
Yeah.
Like using the landscape to see a different perspective.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, no, cool and clever.
And also just like being on some like smooth new coasters
feels really great,
which maybe loops us around to Stardust Racers.
Stardust Racers.
Because I'll cop to it.
I chickened out.
I didn't do it.
It was the first thing everybody went to Ridewise.
I just, I think when I learned
that it didn't have a harness mommy,
that there wasn't a thing that I could hold.
This has become my,
I will go on things as long as I can grip that.
I can grip that.
I can give a big pillow a big hug.
But I, yeah, I don't know.
There's things on the sides maybe,
but that would have been uncomfortable to grip.
Yeah.
The crotch restraint.
Oh yeah, how'd your crotch do?
It was mildly crushed.
Mild.
See, I find that comforting.
Like on hot sauce ratings.
From mild, medium and hot crushing.
Yeah, give us the Scovilles.
Mild crushing.
It was not as bad.
I mean, the worst crushing was
Twisted Colossus at Six Flags,
but that was a purely lap restraints.
First time I've ever done it.
I am so interested to do Twisted Colossus again now
because I've done Velocicoaster's only lap,
Stardust's only lap.
So I wonder if-
You're liking it, you're into it.
Yes, I wonder if now I go on Twisted Colossus
and I'm a pro at these,
and that first time on Twisted Colossus
freaked me out badly
because I just wasn't familiar with that type of coaster.
You should do it.
I've seen it suggested as a second gate.
I think there's probably a lot to the history
and when it was just Colossus and the Twisted Colossus,
step-by-step opening, obviously.
That's the one, right?
Oh, so yeah. It is, yeah.
But you know what?
It'll be the best episode it can be
if you go on and brave a crushing again.
I'll brave the crushing.
I think you should go on Velocicoaster
before you go on Stardust.
Wow.
Just because, there were definitely more moments
on Stardust where I went, ah!
In a way that just made me go, ah!
Like, I swear with Velocicoaster,
and I didn't do it this time,
but Velocicoaster, literally,
I was just euphoric the whole time,
even though it's insane.
It's so intense, but.
And that might override it for me.
Maybe. I mean, you're still not gonna like it,
but I think it will be more of a pure.
I got a wall still.
I mean, we're gonna see.
There's gonna be a lot of pressure coming.
Fast and Furious Coaster literally opening
within this next year. I'm really, well,
James out on that, right?
I mean, there's no way.
I don't think you're tripping on that.
I don't know what I've been on.
I'm scared of that thing.
That's gonna be Velocicoaster that flips around.
Like, that's gonna be intense,
but it's gonna be staring at you every day
you're driving around the San Fernando Valley.
Yeah, I know.
I'll be thinking about it all the time,
but I'm on Guardians going like,
I think I'm like one wrong look away
from this being too much.
Like, I'm thinking about it.
I'm on it, and I'm like, this is a performance.
And if you make one false move,
it's like I'm doing a figure skating routine,
and the tiniest thing could just unravel every,
one bad landing.
Yeah, I mean, Guardians, they had trash cans everywhere,
and they were so fast with hand towels and waters.
Puking is a different.
They do this a lot, yeah.
Again, I feel 5% sick after Guardians,
but I don't feel queasy on Starduster Velocicoaster.
It's not like that for me.
It's literally my motion sense.
So there's a possibility that if Fast has the,
Fast and Furious coaster has the flipping cars
that I feel ill on it.
Maybe the difference between real landscape
and filmic landscapes, or like special effects landscapes.
A possible, I think it's literally just the same
kind of principle where you're having a 3D movie
and your body doesn't quite know where it's going.
It's like when you get sick in a car
when you're looking at your phone and you're not driving.
I shouldn't be driving looking at your phone,
but you know what I'm saying?
It's because your body is experiencing movement
that your eyes aren't experiencing.
Like, it's the disconnect between the two.
This is the dumbest way I'm sure to explain this phenomenon,
but it's like because Guardians flips you around,
your body doesn't quite know where to look.
There's different things, big asteroid or big planet,
but your body twists in a different way
and you're moving and it's not lining up
with your vision and your body.
That's the dumbest way I possibly can explain this.
It's not one fluid experience.
Anything's mismatched and not dialed correctly.
Exactly, you have to be dialed in with your vision,
it has to know where you're headed
and your body has to feel that way.
And I think when it gets off,
apparently body wars initially made people sick
because it didn't have a point to look at.
You want to, I guess in a 3D movie like that,
to have something that the audience has their eye trained on
so everybody's looking at a specific place
so your stomach doesn't get messed up.
That's why I'm nervous about Fast and Furious
because I'm like, the whole city,
you have the entire city to look at?
You got this whole San Fernando Valley?
Yes, and it may be, I could potentially
get sick on it in that way.
So I'm just saying there's a lot of pressure
and there's gonna be new coasters
replacing rip ride rockets.
I mean, one of these days,
you may have to do one of these is what I'm saying.
One of these days you may have to graduate yet again.
Yeah, no, I know there's another level for sure.
There's another level.
It would be good, it would allow me
to experience cool need rides.
Yes, and so I would still say Velocicoaster,
I think you should do because it's just so much smoother.
Stardust Racers is really fun.
I have heard that they're still adjusting,
they're figuring speed out apparently on it,
which is also something you never really think about
because in my mind these days,
you would plug in new roller coaster on a computer.
It would tell you exactly the speed to go.
It would tell you like, all that stuff in my mind
should be just like worked out and they know it,
but I guess it makes sense that they're like,
they run it with some people and people go,
ah, that was a little, that hurt.
I don't know this firsthand, I'm just saying.
Wow, still dialing it in.
So there's still, and this is not uncommon.
I think every coaster goes through this,
I don't think Velocicoaster landed perfectly.
Well that one especially has a couple crisscross moments.
Stardust, you're talking about?
Yeah, that they probably need to time out.
Yes, they have to time that,
but I think more of the speed adjustment
is just because some people felt like it was too rough
maybe when it was faster.
Oh, interesting.
Because I would say my experience
going on whatever this speed,
I don't know the specific speed,
but my experience on it was you definitely round
whatever a top hat type situation,
which is that big curve that Velocicoaster has.
You definitely round a top hat thing like that,
and there's definitely a moment where you go boom.
It feels very much like you're kind of banging
into your restraint a little bit.
So it's not, Velocicoaster for some reason
doesn't make me feel like that.
It makes me feel like I'm flying over it
and then sort of more of a smooth thing.
So there was more moments of like kind of that thing
where you hit into your restraint
on a big whatever hill or something,
and it's still really fun.
It's just not quite the same,
I feel like I'm Superman flying like Velocicoaster has.
Now, as you just said,
there's a soundtrack to the ride
that's really good from what I could hear,
and there's a moment where both,
so you're launching at the same time,
two different long trains, two long roller coaster trains,
and there's a moment where basically both coasters
are in the exact same spot
and your heads are looking up at each other as you,
I don't know, I can't even,
I'm trying to think if you're going straight up
or you're going, I don't know what direction even it was.
I really should look.
But you can like lock eyes with your equivalent.
Yes.
It's a completely mirrored track.
So let's just say like one track is up
and one track is down,
and you look up and you are looking at a mirror image
of your car with a different set of people in it,
and the soundtrack helps make this feel
like it's Matrix bullet time,
which is what definitely like the highlight
of the whole thing.
It's toward the end,
is that you feel like when you look up
and you're just like looking
a bunch of other people in the eyes.
Who are you?
You're like, I'm a man of an entire life
that is not mine.
It's a ride that allows you to Sonder.
Sonder, stop and Sonder.
Bullet time and Sonder.
This was an original selling point to Dueling Dragons.
Yes, right, right.
But at the time, Universal didn't send you
through a metal detector and make you put your bags away.
So everyone's shit was flying out of the pockets
for a decade, and then they're like,
oh, we gotta do something about this.
A quarter sliced my eye.
You get an iPhone right in the nose.
I think someone did get injured by a flying cell phone.
I'm sure they did.
And it cost.
So now you bring things into the selfie stick era.
Oh my God.
We're talking decapitations.
Well, selfie sticks should just be for boat.
I'm glad they, yeah, the theme parks took a stand.
They had to.
My last point of inquiry, merchandising.
Did you like the merchandise for sale?
Yeah, yes.
I didn't get a ton of time to look around at merchandise
just because I wanted to do more of the actual stuff.
There wasn't a ton of Celestial Park stuff.
I did bring Captain Cacao home for my daughter
who was happy but confused to who this was.
You don't say.
There's something confusing about it.
Because I swear we had an entire conversation on this show
about Captain Cacao, this original Epic Universe character
before I realized that it was a bear.
Oh yeah.
I think I was in the park and you were showing me
Captain Cacao and I went, it's a bear?
Yeah, yeah.
And we missed that point.
Yeah, he's got a little hat and a little star.
He's cute.
He's a cute bear.
He does seem cute.
But I could see he's not immediately understandable
to a two-year-old brain.
Yeah.
I will say this about the merchandise in general.
It is just, I didn't see a lot of next level
theme park merch.
There's some Isle of Berk stuff that's really striking
in its different graphic design.
Yeah.
But mostly, you go Harry Potter,
it's the same Hogwarts aesthetic clothing, wands.
Monsters, there's some cool stuff in Monsters
but nothing so striking to me.
So I didn't do such a comprehensive look
at all the merchandise but it didn't seem like
theme park merchandise basically
and nothing that stood out to me like,
oh my God, I have to have this or that.
Well, the ideal goal, I think, of theme park merchandise
is to bring a little piece of the park back,
to bring a little feeling of what you experienced
back with you.
I can't be there all the time but I can,
in this little way, do something or see something at home
that is something I could do there.
And to that end, as we talk about what are the big headlines
of what you can do in Epic Universe,
I feel like what they should offer
is miniature crotch crushers.
There should be some little item or toy
and I can't speak to this, I think Jason would be the guy
who could maybe help us figure out
what the item would be like.
But just a little bar that you can bring back home
and just give that little extra team member press
that makes you, that gets you ready for that ride
and feeling, the universal magic, what that is for you
is the numbness you feel in your crotch
when the ride's about to start.
That's right, yeah.
It's not something you feel in your heart.
No, I feel it in my loins.
It's something you feel in your chub.
Yeah, well I think you get a little Kronos
and 80% of the time it holds your pens in your home office.
But that 20%.
And then the 20% of the time it's a very restrictive,
like chastity, like a cage, you know?
Yeah, I do know, I do know.
Ooh, this is a portal to somewhere extremely interesting.
Yeah, it's true.
All right, well, hey, free merch tip.
They'll be really glad we got to go when they hear this.
Oh, Mike, you went to Citi.
Did you go in the preview center at all?
Oh, I did, it's awesome, yeah.
Yeah.
You've seen pictures of the model
but it's much bigger than you think.
Part of me is almost as much more excited
about the preview center than the actual park.
I love a preview center.
I also ate like a B minus turkey club at Margaritaville.
Oh, why, why did you do that?
I knew you'd end up back there.
I knew there was no way.
You suggested it after we went, or we could,
Margaritaville, and I said,
or we could go to any other restaurant in this city.
So we went to Disney Springs, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, well, fun stuff.
What an experience, so cool to get to do it.
Sorry you couldn't join us, Jason.
We'll get you down there.
You will get your Epic Universe experience,
or at least your Epic Universe preview experience.
But if, maybe that's all you want.
Hey, well, depending.
No line for that.
Preview center to boat,
and then you can buy some merch at the preview center.
Hey, you know, I'm a simple man.
It's a pretty good day.
That's a pretty good day.
But we had a pretty good day in the place,
thanks to anybody who helped this happen,
and you survived Podcast the Ride.
For three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride, The Second Gate,
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast
the ride, including on The Second Gate on Wednesday.
This, we really wanted to be focused on Epic Universe,
but we did fit in some Disney World time
while we were down there as well.
And on Wednesday, Mike and I are going to talk about
what we are positive was the most cool,
transcendent experience we had during this little trip.
I'm excited for the drop of what the episode is
and what the title is,
because as soon as it happened, we were like,
is there an episode there?
Yep, I think so.
It might seem like, you might not get it when you see it,
but I think when we start blabbing,
you will see, you will go into a portal into our hearts
and hopefully experience what we experienced,
because it was really, I don't know,
I hope none of this is like a slideshow of a vacation
you didn't get to go on.
Jason, is that how you feel?
Are we just showing you?
And then we went here, click, click.
Then we went here, click, click.
No, not really.
That's good to hear.
Even as a child, I would have been excited for that,
because I've been like, oh, what things did they do?
What did they prioritize?
Can you summon a relative who went to a place
who showed you postcards or a slideshow of a trip,
an eight-year-old you is like,
wow, I didn't know that was a factory tour you could take.
I don't know.
I feel like my Aunt Betty went to Florida a lot growing up.
Disney World Florida or just looking at botanical gardens?
Oh, Disney World.
Oh, yeah, Big Disney World.
Oh, okay.
That chunk of the side of the family, yeah.
I was hoping it was just like,
and they had a sunflower exhibit.
There were sunflowers as far as the eye could see.
70 sunflowers, I believe.
Then we went to Gator World,
and boy, there certainly was a lot of them.
He went on all the trips.
He didn't have to be told.
Oh, yeah, he knows.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.