FOREVER
DOG
Warning
The following podcast may contain
combative principles
immersive barrels
and an oppressive amount
of Billy Joel
Mike and Scott hit Hill Valley and The Enterprise
at Universal Hollywood's
new FanFest Nights
with special guest Paul Scheer
on today's podcast The Ride
music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
a podcast about theme parks that you guys
aren't ready for yet but your kids
are gonna love it. I'm Scott Gardner
joined by Mike Carlson. Are they
Are they gonna love it?
Oh, I think so.
Oh, I think all of the, you know,
the references to William Frawley and-
We're pushing it with people our age is what I'm saying
when it comes to old TV references.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, and you know, the recurring specter
of the puppet madam that like increasingly,
I think you were-
Whelan Flowers and Madam.
Whelan Flowers, soon you will be the oldest living person
who remembers this reference.
Yeah.
And then we're, but I don't know,
but also maybe it'll all be so foreign
30 years down the line that there'll be a novelty to that.
That's a good point.
That'll be the appeal of the whole thing.
So the young people will look up to me in a lot of ways.
Yeah, yeah, well, you know,
if we get into the nostalgia neck of the woods,
which is certainly what we're dealing with today
with this thing that we got to go to.
Yes.
Jason Sheridan is not with us, unfortunately.
However, we're gonna have a good time here
because we're gonna talk about a really fun thing
that we got to go to.
The Universal Studios Hollywood has been doing it,
they're trying out that we were the guinea pigs for,
the first ever test subjects for.
Basically, yeah.
We were prepared for danger and brain damage
and anything that could've,
I assumed the shit was gonna go down at this thing,
but we were safe, we're able to come talk about it now.
FanFest Nights was the event.
It's a separately-ticketed after-hours event
that they have just begun
that celebrates different worlds and IPs and fandoms.
They encourage costumes and cosplay.
The big stars of this show,
Back to the Future, Star Trek, Dungeons and Dragons,
those are the big things that they're pushing.
It's kind of like an attempt
at a new Halloween Horror Nights.
It doesn't have to be stuck to Halloween.
But very few scares.
I would say so, thankfully for me.
I was worried about scares in this one zone.
Instead, it was nothing but delay.
I was, honestly, and this may be,
you sound this alone, sick,
but I was kind of hoping there would be some scares for you
because obviously, as listeners know,
Scott has not done Horror Nights yet.
So I was hoping maybe in a way,
it would be like a little bit of exposure,
be like a booster of that scene.
Taking a little bit of the virus to, yeah, yeah.
Exactly, for the future Horror Nights trip
that you, I think, are going to go on still as of this moment.
Well, we'll see.
Maybe we'll talk about how this went
and then we'll see if we're willing to do it.
But I'd say in broad strokes, a fun time was had,
especially because of our guest who joined us then
and who joins us now, an old pal of the show,
a good pal of the show,
writer of the book, Joyful Recollections of Trauma,
soon available on paperback, it's Paul Scheer.
Guys, I am so excited to be back, back here.
Yes, we're back.
It's been a long time.
For fan, Universal Fan Nights,
something that I will tell you in my circle of friends,
when it was first announced, I got a lot of emails.
You see this, it's happening,
because I think Star Trek, you know,
connects me to a lot of different people
and it felt like this was going to be a special
Star Trek celebration.
And immediately, I was excited, but suspicious.
What could it be?
What could a fan night be?
Because it really is like building a new experience
in Universal, like horror nights, you know,
you got these mazes, I get the idea of it,
but this felt to me like, it was a big swing.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
And how do you possibly, just saying Star Trek
will be at Universal Studios
doesn't answer a lot of questions.
There's so much, there could not be more
that defines Star Trek,
so what does it all get boiled down to?
As a fan of the Vegas experience,
and much upset that that has closed,
and I feel like it has just disappeared.
There's no, it didn't go anywhere, it just done, right?
There's no quark spar.
Well, the funny thing is, it all still,
maybe not anymore, but for a long time after,
it still did look like quark spar,
it just became an unthemed space,
including the place where you could go
to have meetings about time shares.
Just all was inexplicably like,
space stores, and yeah, yeah.
I was excited about this,
because I feel like there's a turn right now.
All these theme parks are trying to figure out
how do we capitalize on the new way
that theme parks should be,
and I feel like Galaxy's Edge was an attempt to be like,
it's immersive, it's interactive,
and in my opinion, all of these parks have failed
to capture what I think people like about escape rooms,
or these really seminal immersive places,
sleep no more and stuff like that,
because it has to be corporate,
and you have to bring in thousands of people, right?
At the end of the day, it's thousands of people,
so I always feel like I'm always,
I'm interested that they're going in this direction,
but it seems like immediately at Galaxy's Edge,
it was like, you bring your phone,
and you're competing on things, and you're getting points,
and then that seemed to not be a part
of Galaxy's Edge anymore.
They always opened very strong,
so I like this idea that Fan Nights is coming in
a little bit softer, softer and trying
something a little bit different.
Yes, not over-hyped.
If anything under-hyped, I mean, maybe not,
I mean, I was certainly aware of it,
and I'd been to Universal Studios,
and they'd put a flyer in my car for it,
but it didn't, like, that doesn't tell you.
They handed it to you, though,
they didn't just sneak it in when you were parked.
No, no, no, they didn't force it on me,
or just put it on my windshield.
Okay, like save the clock tower, it wasn't.
Oh, yeah, yeah, uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah, yeah.
Some odd cults is trying to get invested.
Did they call this number to sell your car?
Yeah, yeah, no, it was all on the up and up.
However, it really, it was just like
Universal Fan Fest Nights three photos,
no further information.
Then I think more photos were added
as the anime properties started to become part of it.
Well, I was under the impression
that it was going to be, like, each weekend
a celebration of one of the things.
Like, there's a Star Trek night,
and then there would be a Dungeons and Dragons night,
and that's how at least it was,
at least I envisioned it
when I first had read the information about it.
I thought the same thing, yeah,
and I found it confusing to realize
that it was gonna be these, like,
disparate fandoms all thrown together.
That remains kind of a funny thing about it,
that you're like, get ready, geeks,
the ultimate celebration, the things you love,
Star Trek, sure, Back to the Future, yeah,
Dungeons and Dragons, more different Harry Potter,
the general existence of Yoshi.
I mean, those are five things people are nerdy about.
One Piece, I mean, One Piece is really like,
I think that One Piece was that late edition
that became like, ooh, we need this
to pull the whole thing together,
because ultimately, look, I'm a huge Star Trek fan.
Mike and I had texts about Star Trek things
on the side over here, like, hey, you know,
but that's not gonna be,
I don't think that's gonna be fueling the night.
Dungeons and Dragons, like, I feel like I love that movie.
I don't know how wide that movie goes,
but the property Dungeons and Dragons, big,
but you are, like, I feel like the One Piece
was the one, the biggest thing that pulled it all together.
Harry Potter, definitely, but Harry Potter
really wasn't doing anything different
besides having puppets. Little shows, yeah.
Yeah. Oh, right, we ran into,
late into the night, we ran into a dragon
that is not usually there. They were like three creatures,
one like a wraparound dragon, one like a little,
like, very cool, like new creatures,
but it wasn't, it wasn't anything,
and that's already a very immersive land.
That could and should just be there.
Yes, it should. Always.
So a lot of the things they did just should be there,
always, I think. Yeah, yeah.
Yoshi could be there always.
I don't think anyone would notice. 100%, yeah.
I don't know, only the top tier Nintendo nerds
know the name Yoshi, kind of a deep cut.
But I will say the, what made it hard about Yoshi was,
like, Yoshi was there, but, you know, to see Yoshi,
you had to collect stickers on a head, like a headpiece,
to then get into a giant line.
So it was really like a lot of barrier to Yoshi, you know?
I mean, like, you had to spend about two hours,
and that was, I think that's part of this night.
It's like, what is this night?
Because I think when you go to a Star Trek convention,
it's really fun.
You see, obviously, Star Trek leading,
and then there's a lot of, like, sub pops of nerd culture.
But there are people here that were like,
I am fully dressed in Back to the Future,
I am fully dressed in Star Wars,
I am fully dressed in Dungeons and Dragons,
and One Piece, and seeing them mix around.
It didn't, it felt like somebody drew, like,
three giant circles of fan bases.
It was like, I think this covers all of nerddom.
Like, I think in some, like, I might like Dungeons and Dragons,
and I might like Back to the Future,
I don't like Star Trek, but I do like one,
like, I feel like if you were to, like,
what do you call that, like, those, like, the circle?
The Venn diagram?
The Venn diagram, yeah.
But it did feel like Comic-Con in a lot of ways.
There's, like, a big mix of people getting together
to do stuff.
So you like that, you're a Comic-Con person.
I do like that, yeah.
Did you find that exciting,
that it's kind of like a different vibe
than day-to-day Universal Studios?
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, when they play, like, pop and rock and roll songs
when you're walking down their main street,
I do always like it, it feels different to me.
It feels like it's a different experience.
So I did like all of it.
Part of me was like,
because I had a lot of people also,
who were like, oh, I'm going to Star Trek night,
and I was like, it's not just Star Trek,
it's the whole thing.
But part of me is like, oh, was it maybe like,
should they just do a Star Trek weekend,
a Back to the Future weekend?
Well, that's what I kind of think,
but I don't think that the park can handle that.
Like, they need to have everyone going
because, you know, as we saw,
the Star Trek experience in general
was about, like, little less than 10 minutes
from start to finish.
I mean, you know, like, you know.
That's not enough for a whole thing.
Yeah.
But I would say for like a ticketed after hours event,
like Disney charges for Star Wars nights.
Yeah.
They charge for whatever retro night, 90s night.
They charge, by the way,
much, much more than Universal is charging for any of this.
And all that really is, is like meeting Yoshi.
Right, it's photo ops, right?
So if you factor in the fact that you're getting
like all the rides at Universal,
and you're in like most of them.
Which is also an odd choice.
The fact that Transformers was not open,
and it is open during Halloween Horror Nights,
and is often one of the best stops on Halloween.
Well, I was very upset because I wanted,
I said, you know, may as well go on a quick Transformers.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, and the last we were with Paul,
you proved the case forever, permanently,
that Transformers is better than Resident Existence,
so you wanted to, like, enjoy your spoils with the two of them.
Right, I was gonna gloat the whole time we were on it.
See, that was better, right?
Have you seen this part?
He told you he's proud of you.
Oh, that really hurt our backs, huh?
That was awesome.
Kind of fucked you up,
but that's what you want, is to get fucked up, right?
Yes, Mike, yes, you're right, Mike.
We know, Mike.
But that was, like, that's a perfect encapsulation of,
I feel like this was a successful night,
but that's an imperfect encapsulation
of the question marks I have of the night.
Why close that ride?
Like, because the experiences, the three experiences,
are all, I mean, I guess we will save some,
we'll get into all of them, obviously,
but Back to the Future is probably the longest,
but you need more things to fill it up
until two in the morning.
It's up until two in the morning.
Yeah, it's a lot.
Which none of us made it all the way.
Like, we all, we were there pretty much
at the start at seven.
Right.
And then, like, yeah, I was wondering,
like, do we go for it?
And you, like, proven that you can still go.
I want to prove it.
I prove it a lot.
That I can still go.
I had to go, I had to pull back.
I was upset, I want to go, I want to go,
but I don't think I got it done until two, I don't think.
You missed seeing both of us
hit our relatively new parent wall.
You missed both of us.
I think we saw each other,
the light go out of each other's eyes.
Yeah.
And that is it.
We have no, we'll talk about maybe where it happened
and why it happened.
It felt like, you know, in Mission Impossible Four
when he's got the glove that won't work on the wall
and it keeps, like, shorting out.
I almost was like, no, wait, what?
You're, like, this tired right now?
Like, it's, ah, come on, work, stay awake.
That's a parenting thing that you can't fight against
because the other part of it is we're like vampire.
New parents, parents in general, are like vampires
because you're gonna wake up at a given time
no matter what.
Right.
So you can burn that midnight oil,
but he can get you on the other side.
And I knew the next morning,
I had to go relieve my nanny,
but I had an 8 a.m. soccer game
I had to get my kid to the next morning.
I was like, well, this is, even if I pushed it,
yeah, I'm, there's no, there's no rest for me.
I'm gonna be.
Then that's gonna be a terrible soccer game.
Yeah, it'll be awful.
You'll be, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anything kid, it's a true punishment.
And I came off.
And let alone, like, sleepless, bad, hungover, never.
Oh, never.
Hangovers are no, parenting is the ultimate hangover cure.
You can't, if you do it to yourself,
you're out with your mind.
I did it once, it was a terrible experience
to be hungover as a parent.
How bad, was there like a, was there like a leave to vomit?
Was it that bad?
It was, I remembered distinctly that my wife and I
were both just like down on the ground with our kids
and being like, we're just gonna hang out
and play on the ground.
Like we were just very, it was, it was for a wedding
and we, and yeah, we just missed it.
We, again, lesson learned, never again.
And yeah, it just, it just knocked us on our ass.
And it was just like, the hangover is a rough spot.
But thankfully, we didn't have to worry about hangovers
because FanFest, it was impossible to get a drink.
I don't understand why it was impossible to get food
or drinks at this place without waiting for,
the longest rides were for food and drink.
And it felt like they staffed it as if no one was coming
on that part.
It's like, well, I don't think anyone will want these drinks.
Like, and I, and I did do a lot, I did my research.
I watched a lot of bloggers and people that were there
had the same exact complaint.
Like everyone was getting off the lines
because they're like, it was like,
I'm not gonna wait 45 minutes to get like a themed drink
that it probably hasn't even had that much alcohol in it.
Like, but it really is a bummer.
It's like, I wanna, I wanna go to, you know,
I wanna go to 10 forward.
I wanna go eat the Dungeons and Dragons, you know,
hot brownie, whatever it is.
Yes, and it's our obligation.
It's our job, quite frankly, to try the special things.
And you got to do it, but at some point I was like,
I want a dessert.
There's literally no line for the basic soft serve.
The unthemed soft serve, you did the same for a churro.
I got a churro from the front of the mummy ride,
which has no theming, but it was very good.
Apparently- It's not special.
It's always there, but very sad.
I loved my basic non-IP dessert.
Well, you know what I think they should do?
And we were lamenting this as well
in the Back to the Future ride.
We, it mainly takes place in the courthouse square.
There's no food down there at all.
Yeah. And there's most famously a diner
in the courthouse square in Back to the Future.
They did recreate that diner
in a different part of the park,
which I also thought was weird,
but like at the Intuit Dome where the Clippers play,
every food station is the same.
So you don't have to like go around for the sushi.
It's like the sushi is with the,
and I feel like that's what they should have done.
They should have had a fan night's,
I don't need to like, so like when I go get something,
it's like, yes, I can get my back,
I can get my Biff burrito,
or I can get my cork sausage or whatever.
Or rain pasta.
Now I will say that I was upset with what you ate
at the corks bar.
That was upsetting to me.
What, the way you're looking at it, really?
Are you talking about the credacean dog?
Yes.
Yeah, well, and you bailed on that pretty quickly.
I sure did.
Yeah, well, this is in the genre.
This has come up here and there on the show
because it seems like it's from a location
that has previously been like a Chucky restaurant.
Well, that was a bar.
That's the bar area.
Oh, okay.
Although, no, excuse me, there was a diner as well.
Isn't that a food counter also?
Because I've gotten caught on that they serve an item
called like Chucky's Macassacre and cheese.
They have the straight, it's like impossible
to wrap your head.
You can like stare at it for five minutes
and not know how to say it.
So it's from, and I know they've also,
they've trafficked in this genre
of like corn dog that is insane.
And that's pretty much what you did, right?
What was the variety in which it was insane?
Well, it was literally visually this big, I feel like.
Yes.
This thick, really thick.
And not straight either, it felt curved.
It felt like an eggplant shape or something like that.
Yeah, it had a weird.
Yeah, the old Bill Clinton curvature.
Yeah, that's what I thought of.
Most famous weirdly curved junk in history.
Bright red Cheeto dusted Bill Clinton thick.
That makes sense.
You think of a different president.
Oh, well, it's a lot of ways
it was a mashup of all the presidents.
Yeah, it was like Cheeto red.
And then it was like a giant hot dog or broad of some kind.
And it was just like deep fried.
Yeah.
And it almost felt like there was like,
I know it wasn't an inch,
but it almost felt like there was an inch,
like an inch from hot dog to deep fry.
I was watching you eat it and at first shock
to know it was a hot dog or a broad.
Like I was like, oh, I thought this was maybe corn.
It looked like Mexican corn.
And then I was like, oh, it's not Mexican corn.
And I was like, well, it must be some sort of dessert.
It wasn't that.
And then when you did cut into it,
it was weird because it looked like
it was a layer of the earth.
It was like, there was the fried layer
and then there was some space.
It wasn't together.
It was like sometimes a corn dog is like together as one.
It did feel like there was like atmosphere between the two.
Oh yeah, a hollow zone, sure.
Right.
It felt like they like meet.
Where the dark universe takes place apparently.
Oh.
Where the Godzilla and King Kong hang out.
Yeah, right.
The upside down, the hollow earth in a lot of ways.
Yeah, I did feel like they maybe like made,
I'm sure they did fry it, but maybe I'm not.
Maybe they made the casing first and slid the hot dog in.
I don't know.
It was odd.
It was, I will say,
as somebody who was most excited to go to Quarks,
a very quick theming of Quarks.
Like, where were that place?
The chunky place.
It felt like a little slap dash.
They did have like the fountain drinks,
had like names on it.
It was like cart, like Bajoran.
Bajoran Plo-meek.
Yeah, it was like they threw up.
Orion, seemingly on their little label,
spelled with one zero and one oh.
So that's a good little Easter egg.
And then it's just green goo.
I assume the same green, yellow, and red goo
they have all day.
I think probably.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not sure what that is day to day.
They feel like they were definitely trying to make it pop,
but I don't know if these recipes were tested with much.
We're first night out,
so maybe this is gonna be a corn dog
that's gonna get better, I don't know.
I mean, might be optimistic.
I'm looking at,
I don't know if you guys caught this detail,
but also in that kind of service station zone
next to the space drinks,
there's just this kind of weird green,
like spinach green, like a ketchup bottle,
but with green to like beige goo in it.
And then it's like the goo is pouring out everywhere.
And in my photo,
I mean, this is like some science experiment gone awry
and in the photo, the label says don't squeeze too tight.
And then it seems like an explosion has occurred around.
This is not an appetizing thing to see.
No, this is what I will say is that I think that they,
and I looked at a lot of the food,
because again, we couldn't get to the food.
So I went to try to look at people's reviews of the food
and the food they had.
Felt like everything was kind of normal
with an aggressive color on top of it.
So in the Harry Potter world, they had churros,
but then they had these like yellow,
like little bow ties of sauce in the middle of the churros.
They also had meat pies,
which I don't know if that was specific to the knight or.
I don't know if they do always have that there.
I don't know.
It feels like. That's a set familiar.
Universal feels like in normal times,
it has a chicken sandwich, a hamburger,
and then a salad with iceberg lettuce.
Yeah, that feels like three things that they have everywhere,
except for Harry Potter, I guess,
which has a slightly better, more variety.
Now, next to your Cardassian dog,
and I see the picture here.
I want to ask you about this.
They had a very basic thing
that didn't feel themed at all to me,
which was, you can describe it here,
what the other dish you ordered was.
They were fritters.
And now I'm trying to remember what alien race
is responsible for these fritters.
Vulcans. Vulcans, okay.
Oh, it is the Vulcan symbol there too.
Not to be confused with the Klingon targ legs.
Thank you. I thought about it.
I thought about getting the Klingon targ legs.
Which would be nicely paired with Klingon blood wine.
$22 Klingon, that's inexpensive.
Yeah, these drinks are gonna cost you some cash.
Yeah, yeah.
Was there strong jealousy and desire?
Because you guys are the Trekkies,
blood wine's a big thing, right?
Were you like, kind of itching to try blood wine?
Did you ultimately look at that?
I wanted to get to that Deep Space Nine,
but I really wanted to get in there and see what they had.
But then I also equate it with,
well, this line is so long.
And then the, like,
you can get me to spend money if I can get it spent fast.
But the minute that I'm,
the minute I'm on a line for like 10 minutes,
I'm like, do I really need, you know, the Earl Grey cold?
Probably not.
And then I can walk away very, like,
I'm like, I've made a business decision, yeah.
Anytime.
You start to be too logical where you're like,
it's not really what Baccarat drinks.
Right, exactly.
This is not really from a Klingon planet.
Yes, they just took ingredients
and named them arbitrary things
that are related to properties we like.
And in my case, where it's not a property I care about,
like, I might bail instantly.
That said, my Seti Eel margarita was pretty bangin'.
I really like this.
Yeah, yeah.
I like my cocktail.
And I did have the,
I had the Earl Grey.
Wait, oh my God,
I drank something with White Claw vodka in a margarita?
Wait, that was the,
why was it a margarita if it has White Claw and vodka?
You can make a margarita,
I guess, with White Claw.
I'm so in love.
I feel like I failed some kind of taste test.
I'm not a White Claw person.
You look upset.
I am.
I'm really distressed.
I got tricked.
I have seen people that have,
you can mix a margarita base, I think,
can really adapt to,
because that White Claw vodka is not gonna be,
like, it's not gonna have that much flavor to it.
Yeah, yeah.
So the margarita base is where I probably suck up all,
you're tasting all that flavor
of whatever they're pouring in there.
There was a ton of other stuff.
A jalapeno syrup that was really strong,
but my favorite thing,
the little gummy Seti Eel in it.
Ooh, I like that.
It just looked more like a little cockroach.
That's what crawled into the ears.
And to check off here in Wrath of Khan.
Oh, really?
Okay, so that's the historic.
Have you seen Wrath of Khan?
You've seen Wrath of Khan, right?
I think I have seen Wrath of Khan, and my apologies.
The only one that really resonates
and, like, is loud in my ears at all times
is the Whales one, which I'm very much about the Whales.
I think I, because this is consistent,
and consistent with my love of Back to the Future,
that of all the fantasy worlds that I could ever be sent to,
where I really wanna go is the mid-1980s.
Oh, I mean, look.
That's the one that gets you there.
I wanna talk about Back to the Future desperately,
because, by the way, I mean, look,
I would love to have a FanFest nights
and go to Eddie Murphy's Beverly Hills Cop
and just walk around Beverly Hills or Detroit.
I would do any of those.
Yes, that's a great idea.
But the Star Trek thing, to me, feels like it has the most,
the most fan night,
you can build a night around Star Trek, ultimately,
because there's fun rides, there's fun food,
there are bars there, it's organic to the place,
and it can feel different.
And I feel like they definitely tried to do that.
I feel like the 10 forward bar,
I will give a note on the lackluster enhancement
to the area, it felt like a lot of this was set up
to be Instagram museum moments.
So it's like, if you step out from the frame
in which you took the picture,
you're gonna be a little disappointed,
but that picture is gonna look A plus.
Right, yeah.
Well, we sat and had a drink
at the one light up little counter that they had,
and then the reverse literally on my left,
you can't even see any Star Wars,
it's just an awning, yeah, Star Trek,
it's a fountain and an awning, and the White Claw logo,
is White Claw canon?
Maybe, like, my virtue of it being in all of these things.
It's from space, it is from space,
White Claw is from space, yeah.
I imagine some character has a White Claw.
I was gonna say, Kirk defeated White Claw
on an early episode.
Okay, so that is where the name comes from.
To bring their delicious alcoholic beverages to.
Right, it's really the blood of a creature
that he slayed. You may love
to White Claw's wife, too.
It's a really famous one, you should know it.
I will say this in defense of all the Star Trek,
I am shocked, even though Star Trek,
there's shows on the air,
I am shocked that we got something themed to Deep Space Nine
and Next Generation in 2025.
Right. So I am, I will say this,
I am grateful that we got some scraps thrown to us
in regards to just a quark sign,
like who would have thought we would get a quark sign
in this year of our Lord.
I believe that that is the Star Trek that,
we talk again about what's the age for this.
Well, our age, and our age is that kind of Star Trek.
I am on a Star Trek show, a Lower Decks,
which is a very fun show.
Very fun show, it takes place in that era as well, right?
So I feel like that was the right choice to make.
I feel like Deep Space Nine has had a real
kind of resurgence in recent years,
but then the ride itself, or the experience,
and we should talk about this, there are no rides,
there are experiences, and they are kind of like,
walk through shows, it's not,
I think of Immersive as, you are a part of the show,
I felt like this was like watching a stage show
in which you walked through it.
Sure.
Instead of the set being changed in front of you,
you get to be in the set changes.
Yes, and this is maybe, we'll get into certain elements
of it, but I wanted a little bit more,
okay, we need to do this, you man that, you do this,
and Dungeons and Dragons, we had to touch something,
but, or I did, I got lucky enough.
You were the only one with a task in a room with 50 people.
They said at some point, they said like,
man in the cardigan.
Cardigan wizard.
I also.
Touched a ball like that, it was literally.
Oh, just like is in the room with us.
It was right there.
Yeah, there it is.
You feel right, wow, you're flashing
right back to Friday night.
Holy shit.
It was amazing, they just pop up around you, I guess.
I was also, she's so like, the wizard,
we're like, single, do you want,
I go, oh, the wizard must recognize Paul.
No, no, but your proximity was just near the ball.
It was just near the ball.
It had to be you.
Yes, and, but that was the thing that I wanted,
and this is where I feel like these bigger theme parks,
they have to fail in a way because
you need to get a bunch of people through,
so it's like, I thought the actors did a great job.
Like, I will say that 100%.
Across the board, every one of these things, yeah.
Costumes look great.
The way they built the, the red alert is the ride, right?
The Star Trek red alert.
Yes.
Experience.
Experience, yeah.
We are going to the Star Trek museum,
which is a big part of Picard season three.
Yes.
And we are getting to kind of take a tour
of the enterprise.
There's some logic that I will,
like, we're going to a museum,
but it did seem like the enterprise
was fully manned for battle,
which was also a choice that I was like,
oh, okay, these didn't seem like tour guides.
It like, like the medical technicians,
the engineering, like they were fully at work.
I wonder if, I wonder if that was like,
because we talk about like recent theme park stuff
where like it feels like logic.
Sometimes it's too heavily like
they're trying to logic out a problem.
Like, well, if it's Star Trek,
but like really we know the enterprise
is on this new museum for Picard,
that's what Canon is now.
So it wouldn't make sense if you're just on the ship.
But then they also be like, we can't really,
I mean, then they'd be like,
well, we can't really have Picard,
but then you could because then back to the future,
they just embraced the idea.
They just did everything.
Yeah, yeah.
And I want to be clear because I will,
and I think we all will point out logic problems
in all of these things.
It doesn't mean that I didn't like it.
100%.
We're still going to do it.
That's why I do think Galaxy's Edge,
they should just put all the characters together
all at once.
Will all the nerds complain?
Yes.
Will they keep going back anyway?
Of course.
Some of them will though.
Even I think some of the hardcore nerds won't care.
Yeah, because that's what you want.
You want the experience.
And I think that like for me,
it was a really cool recreation of the enterprise.
Again, I have,
Yes.
Oddly traveled to very different places.
Like that used to be right by Man's Chinese Theater.
There used to be a,
like a place where you could get in,
like they had the Cheers Bar
and they had the enterprise set.
That TV museum.
Yes.
It's an LA fitness now.
And it was one of the coolest things ever
because you could actually touch these sets.
And then, and I've been on the Paramount tour
and the Paramount tour has elements
of the Star Trek sets as well.
So I love it.
Like I want to walk around in it.
That I felt like they did a pretty good job
at capturing what that is.
Again, in a main giant like maze kind of situation.
Like we have to walk through it.
Yes.
They clearly did a good job
because for you two who know it
and I who do not,
I walk into a room and I'm like,
there's a bunch of barrels in this room.
Right.
And they're like,
that's what it is.
It's barrels.
There's so many barrels.
The barrels, anytime you're in like a shuttle bay,
there's all these barrels in Star Trek Next Generation.
I don't know.
They just were like,
we need something to fill this space out.
It's such a great like prop designer going,
we have a big bay, we need more barrels.
Right.
But yeah, I loved all of that.
I felt like they really treated us really good
as my character is the lead engineer on,
chief engineer I should say on the Lower Deck Show.
I was excited to be there and I wanted to really razz
that engineering crew.
Actually play your character in real life.
That's how I grew this mustache just for fan nights.
To match Billups.
Desperate attempt to be recognized.
You asked us to point at you constantly.
Billups, anyone?
Notice it, notice it.
Touch the ball in Dungeons and Dragons.
I can touch something here if you want.
Touch whatever you want.
I'm good at it.
I have experience.
I will say that of the three experiences
that we experienced,
that was an original idea,
the Star Trek Red Alert that I thought was executed
at least from a point of view
if I understood what was happening.
Like from beginning to end and I was not confused.
Which was good.
Although it felt slightly lackluster
in the sense that you're like,
oh my gosh, an alien is attacking
and you're like getting to battle positions.
Ship is going down.
And can I give a spoiler?
Can we talk a little bit?
I think so, yeah.
And then the result is they were friendly.
Yeah, that's good.
It was one of those nice ones.
Once we talked to it, yeah, they were cool.
I was also torn about that
because that is a classic Star Trek resolution
where you like learn a lesson
that of course the alien, oh, it's peaceful.
Like what are you doing worried about?
This could be something that you're overreacting to.
But as a fan of haunts and scares,
I wanted the fucking Borg to burst
through those turbolift doors and scare the shit out of us.
And you wanted me to piss my pants.
I wanted you to piss your pants
and I wanted to be assimilated into their collective.
Well, now here's the thing that I couldn't quite figure out.
They have built this ride.
They have built a version of this ride
in Vegas that we talked about.
Why not just take that?
They had the Borg, they had the things.
I mean, not the actual pieces, but just take that story
because that story is a really fun story.
You're just a part of the assimilation.
And then you got the guys with phasers.
Oh yeah, we did it, we figured it out.
And then I wanted some more stakes too
because really at the end of it,
then again, no flack to this captain who did a great job.
But she's like, yes, we nailed it.
And it felt very like this is the way it was written.
She did say yes, and kind of like we do one of the pump fists
and I was like, oh, I didn't feel like a star.
I get what you're saying,
because it is a Star Trek kind of story,
but it just felt a little lackluster.
All right, bye, see you later.
It felt as easily solved as turbulence on a plane.
Yes.
Like, oh, well, they warned us
and then a minute later it was fine.
Yeah, and that was it.
And yeah, that was my only complaint about it
is I wanted some danger.
Yes, I agree, I wanted danger as well.
I mean, I wanted to live there.
That's also the thing.
Can I sit in Riker's chair?
What do you think?
Would it be okay if I?
Right, when you get that close to the bridge,
it's like all you want to do is touch it and see it
and feel it and to their credit,
they do have a great photo op
where you can sit in Picard's chair.
But I mean.
Yes, it's out by the water world.
But it's also, yeah, if you zoom out too wide,
you see the sign for water world,
the live sewers, particularly.
It's also like, I understand logistically,
they did give us more than you would get in a normal maze.
Of all of these things.
You know, is that true?
See, I don't know.
Not having done mazes yet.
Yes.
In terms of like getting ample time.
Because you did Dungeons and Dragons for sure,
like a lot of time and everything.
Yeah, you motor through Horror Nights maze.
That's what I was telling you.
You should do that one first
because you were in a single file line,
you were just rolling.
Well, I want to make a very strong case
to not bring you to Horror Nights first,
but to bring you to the world's biggest horror maze,
which is maybe like 20 minutes up near Calabasas,
which is in an abandoned mall.
Oh, yes.
And that is one of the most fun.
I'm down for you had me at abandoned mall.
That one is one of the most fun experiences I've ever had
because they worked that right level of people
to scare ratio where, because sometimes in universal,
like it's just like a line and it's sort of like,
you've seen the scare already,
and if the timing works out,
you will be scared,
but sometimes the timing doesn't work out.
But this, I felt like because it was in groups,
we had our own experience.
I really liked that we were like,
we were in the medical bay, we were in engineering,
we were like, we went as a group.
It wasn't like at our own discretion,
like we were going with the story.
Yes, I mean, it would have been a real bummer
if we just marched into the bridge and then marched out,
but it did feel like, come on,
isn't like a kid dressed as Q going to pop in here
and try to put us on trial for something.
Yes, in a world of villains,
in a world of villains and a world of characters,
to have none,
to have zero recognizable characters and villains
was a bummer to me.
They said the blue face guy and Dorian show up
with a big fake rubber chest,
like Ricardo Montalban in the second,
or by the way, but you just said it perfect.
Like you could put a guy,
a guy can pretend to be John DeLan,
we're going to talk about in Back to Future.
There was a guy, they recreate everybody in Back to Future.
So just put a hat and a red robe on somebody and be like,
I'm Q and I'm challenging you all.
We need to figure out this puzzle.
And then let them figure out the puzzle,
but we feel a part of it.
Look, I would have done it for free.
Just let me be Q.
This is, when we're complaining to some degree,
even though I really enjoyed a lot of this,
I do think that I bet if we were to talk to people,
they would be like, look,
here's the list of what we couldn't do with this maze.
Here's what Paramount said we could do.
Here's what they said we couldn't do.
And I do wonder if it was like,
you cannot have somebody playing Picard.
We just will not allow it.
Universal owns Back to Future,
so maybe there was a lot more room to do stuff.
But it seems like if they're leasing it out,
they definitely are.
Look, again, this all being said,
I loved that experience because it was fun to,
like that was an immersive environment
that was very familiar.
So you got to walk within a thing
that I thought was really, really fun.
And it's just, I want it,
the idea of it going away is upsetting to me.
Now that I know it's there, the carpeting is there,
I can walk by the panels.
I saw it in a picture of that panel.
Tear down Hogwarts as far as I'm concerned.
That's my Hogwarts is that Enterprise-D.
Well, by the way, so the whole way home,
I was thinking about this to give you like an old insight
on where my mind is going.
I was like, you know what would be awesome
is if they built a really kick-ass escape room
that recreated the bridge of the Enterprise, right?
And you have to solve mysteries
and you get these communications on the screen
and somebody has to be the captain.
It would be so much fun.
There is something.
I think escapology, is that the code?
Cause that's the one moving into Universal at CityWalk.
There is one, I think they have a start.
It's not the Enterprise-D though.
I do think there is a Star Trek escape room somewhere.
I would love, why not?
Why not?
Cause I think that's what I want.
I want to be like in that bridge,
touching and feeling.
With a problem to solve, you have to go to warp.
You want to go to warp, you want to do this,
which is not warp in the Millennium Falcon.
It's like this, you just slide up on a touch screen.
That's what data would do.
So it's a less exciting gesture, but that's more exciting.
But if you're the captain, you can also like.
Oh, you point.
Captain, you point like this, then you do this.
And then like if you're in Counselor Troy's chair,
and you have something, you can interpret things.
Cause she's baited so that she can feel things,
that's an eight person escape room.
Because you have enough positions
to actually be effective in the escape room.
I mean, whatever.
This is just free ideas for fans.
If it doesn't exist, yeah,
it does feel like it should exist.
People go nuts for it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And by the way, I think what's been itching
in the back of my head is, for whatever reason,
my Instagram account has been getting a lot of John Wick.
The Continental just opened in Vegas.
And that seems incredibly interactive.
I don't know about this.
What's the John Wick Vegas thing?
Oh, it's a whole immersive like bar,
and they don't even allow cameras in certain things.
And you get to really jump into the John Wick-a-verse.
Suit guy, everything.
Yeah.
By the way, if that comes on the thing,
I will gladly make a trip to Vegas with you guys
to check out the Continental.
Well, couldn't we all pair this
with cause Universal's opening the Horror Maze in August.
Ooh.
So I'm already like adding things to that trip perhaps.
And Summer League is happening in August.
So that's great for me.
I can make a real case for this.
Or another pitch is, do it any time that isn't August,
due to immense horrible heat.
That's a bummer, you're right.
But then Backstreet Boys, it's Sphere also August.
Oh, I would love to see that.
So there's a lot of things throwing in this pile.
If we're rounding it, I mean, I know,
there's a lot of air conditioning around.
We can, as long as we can-
Yeah, just don't leave the buildings,
which is fine, we're talking about all indoor activities.
Yeah, as long as we don't make the mistake
Eve Anderson made of walking from a casino
to our live show in August.
Oh, no, no, no.
I walked outside of the NBA Summer League
and just waiting for an Uber was awful.
And I didn't even walk, I guess I was waiting.
And that's, I guess we don't have to,
because even I went to Liberace's house
when we were in Vegas as well.
Which we really never did an episode on,
we just talked a little bit at the live show.
We could have dug in a little more on that.
I know, well, every comment section
and every episode we've had since, Liberace, Liberace.
This is the people who want the Wayland Flowers
and Madam comments.
That's true.
Where do you land on the, as somebody we can detest,
I can attest that the last,
maybe ever since the last episode you did,
I think Wayland Flowers and Madam
has come up every single episode.
How easy, and by the way-
It's an infestation on the show now.
You know, at this place, I mean, we need to keep it alive.
We need to tell, we are the storytellers, you know?
We need to keep that story going.
Yes, that's what I feel as well.
If we don't pass it to the next generation.
The griots or whatever they are.
All right, Madam escape room.
You're in Madam's dressing room
and you have to escape before she makes too many body jokes.
Your ears will start burning.
That's a room in the future podcast,
The Right Immersive Halloween Horror Night's Maze
that I would want to make.
With a Madam operated by you.
Yes, I will do that room, yeah.
From behind one of those dressing room walls.
Yeah, throw one bowl over. By the way,
as you're talking about the Madam room,
I'm thinking, you know, another,
because we were talking about this too,
like universal fan nights,
they'll probably change it every year.
Muppets would be a great one.
Go through like the backstage of a Muppet show.
Sure, sure. Is Disney gonna let them do it?
Well, who knows? If they're not gonna do
something better, although we keep hearing
maybe someone's going on with like,
I might not have to say. There's a lot of rumors.
Yeah, there's rumors of more.
Well, obviously we know the rollercoaster,
the electric man. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I know it'll be.
They want to screwed universal.
I feel like they're not in a mode right now.
I'm not saying it's a good idea.
I'm amazed that Paramount played ball
because Paramount isn't playing ball with anybody.
They're fucking with 60 minutes and they're all this stuff.
But I feel like Star Trek is like a property
that can be, you're right.
But there's no Paramount Park, right?
Yeah. So and I guess like Netflix,
they must have had to make some sort of deal
with Netflix too, right?
Or maybe not, because One Piece can exist
outside of Netflix.
I don't know. I don't know.
But yeah, I don't know who owns them.
There is precedent for Star Trek at Universal
because they had the. Right, that was the.
The tape, you get a tape.
Oh yeah, it's the return of Star Trek.
While you're buttering up Paul for different experiences,
this might be your best chance to get a buddy
to go on the cruise.
Oh, the Star Trek cruise.
One of the things I really wanted to do,
have you ever seen this?
I've heard of this.
Because like there's a Star Trek cruise
and it looks like the biggest like just messy party ever.
Well, see, maybe I could get on there
and get some VIP treatment.
I am looking at a list of people.
Tawny went on there.
Tawny Newsome and Noelle Wells
that are people from. Yeah, yeah.
If Eugene has been on there.
Somebody who's gonna fish,
somebody who is not your wife
is going to fish to be a plus one.
And I hope that maybe.
We know somebody who works on the cruise from Orlando.
Oh really?
Oh is that right?
I'm not sure.
But you got Shatner this time,
you got Frakes this time.
It's almost sold out.
Do we need to buy it right now while we're recording?
Maybe we should buy it right now.
Yeah, do they Shimmerman is gonna be on it?
My guy Armin, yeah.
Do they fly them in?
Because I've heard rumors
that sometimes the helicopter will come to the boat.
They don't do the whole time.
Whoa, they like helicopter Shatner in and out.
Yeah, in and out.
We know he's amenable to, you know,
little craft, little aircraft,
such as going into space.
Right.
Yeah, a little shuttle craft.
You know, you put a little, yeah.
He's gonna blue origin out of there.
A special arrangement for him.
I just watched the clip,
if people haven't seen it,
of Shatner like haunted by his experience.
Oh, I love that.
It's so bizarre.
It's so bizarre, he's haunted.
He's trying to express to Jeff Bezos
what he's seen and what he's learned about living,
what humanity.
And Bezos just pops a cork on champagne
in the middle of his like profound statement.
It could not be a better encapsulation of him.
Yeah, yeah, who cares?
Let's party.
Now, let's get into the meat of the thing,
which is, I mean, I think the one thing
that everyone says, universally, no pun intended,
is the best part is the back to the future Hill Valley.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, destination Hill Valley
is the official naming mechanism of it.
So this does the thing that a lot of mazes have done
at Horror Nights over the years
where you board the world famous Universal Tram
and it takes you down to the lot
and drops you at this particular part.
But it's an area that is-
And I will say, before you even get to that,
we have the Save the Clock Tower lady.
Oh, that's right.
She is at the base of the thing.
And what I found so interesting
about the Save the Clock Tower lady,
who looked great and was doing her part,
people were actually giving her money.
And I was like, where does that money go?
Because people were putting money
in the Save the Clock Tower.
I saw real money go in there.
Maybe she got it.
Hey, look, not bad.
That's for, there should be more opportunities for tips.
I can tell you that during the training,
they tell you people might offer you tips,
turn it down.
I did, one time, somebody gave me a 20.
I took a 20.
Look, when I worked at the container store,
in Chambord, Illinois, which is filed for bankruptcy,
I'm a little worried about that.
Oh no, PTR Curse.
It's a PTR Curse, talking about it for eight years,
finally destroyed it.
They would tell you if someone insisted twice,
you should take it.
But that's the only time.
At Home Depot, when I get my Christmas tree there,
they can't take tips.
But then they show you how you could just pop it
into their little thing.
So you gotta treat them like,
you have to slip it into it,
which is a little bit more uncomfortable, honestly.
It's also like a strip club or something.
Yeah, I know, I was like, all right.
Here goes, this is for you.
You get yourself something special.
But continue, so yes, we get on the tram, we go.
Yeah, it's one of these experiences
where the tram takes you down somewhere,
but in this case, it takes you to the real courthouse square
where scenes from all throughout the trilogy were filmed.
Oh yeah, sorry, yeah, good, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Although, is any of three there?
I could be wrong.
Is there any proper courthouse square?
I'm not sure.
But you know what it is.
But yeah, it's a location you get to see
on the tram tour, obviously,
but I don't think they've ever done anything
where you get out and walk around,
other than for VIPs.
So I was excited about this,
because this is one of the only areas
that I'm super nerdy about, and I've always been,
and I've gotten to when I was a guide,
we got to do a tour down there, and I ran around,
and I stood under where the Jaws hologram comes out.
Then one time, I had a general meeting on the lot,
and I realized that I could exit via the path
that made me have to drive the path of the DeLorean,
which I did with so much gusto.
I think I turned on the score.
I found it on Spotify, blared it as I went past
where the lightning strikes.
I sang it real loud.
I super durked out.
So getting to be there and hang out for a long time.
I love that.
I love that square as a, yeah, that movie,
that's like, these are playing with big parts
of my emotions.
I want to be in that town square.
I loved it.
It was crowded, but not overly crowded.
I think that where Star Trek brought you in in groups,
this kind of allowed a crowd to kind of form.
Now, for better or for worse, we could talk about it.
But what I did like is it didn't feel like
this was a theme park-based area
because you're walking on grass, like real grass.
That's a functioning part of the lot.
That's not a...
That they use a lot, we were talking about throughout.
In some cases, we were being a little nitpicky
of like, it doesn't look exactly like in the movies,
but part of that is because they do redress it
and use it all the time.
Then that was...
That's what I loved and hated about it,
which was like, it was so cool to be there
and there's everything.
But the theming was like someone going like,
oh, we can make this look a little bit
like the Back to the Future.
It wasn't the exact stores or things,
but it felt adjacent to it.
But then I'm also like, but you have all this stuff, right?
But I guess I can't really decorate it fully.
And I'm sure it's another thing
where somebody would be like, we wanted to do it.
Right.
They wouldn't give us the 50K.
But what is the reason why the sign would not be right?
The fan night, that's exactly what a fan
is gonna pick apart immediately.
That kind of drove me the most crazy
because that to me is either have the exact recreation of it
or have the original one and put some,
because they did actually have like Biff's car
and they had like, those were like real, the real cars,
but they had the locked off so you couldn't touch it.
Lyon Estates billboard.
Yeah.
But that was a recreation of something
that wasn't a replica of it.
And that was bumming me out.
Like I was like, give me the thing that is the,
like you have that, you're so close.
You're so close.
It is interesting because I think it being the actual place
where they shot the movie is amazing
to get to do a fun immersive thing there.
But then the limitations of it being a working studio
also hurt, there's probably various reasons
why certain things aren't the way they are.
Probably if they do a recreation of this
for maybe Orlando, maybe UK,
it'll be what we're talking about.
It'll be more perfect than this is even able to be
for some reason we don't even.
Well, because they're building it from scratch
and the courthouse will look exactly right.
It does look like, I don't know,
it looks like more of a standard city hall kind of,
I don't blame them super.
You could feel the vibe in the space.
It was, this was, I would have loved
to have spent more time there.
I think the issue that I had with it was,
so where Star Trek was a unique experience
that was unlike anything from the films,
this was a chance for you to walk around
and interact and put that in quotes
with scenes that are happening from the first film, right?
That's what's like, that's really what's like,
they have multiple scenes happening simultaneously.
So it has like a sleep no more vibe.
You can follow one character into another character.
You can go over here and you'll see how they all wind up.
And I actually thought that was a really cool idea.
The only thing missing for me personally
was I would have loved to have seen Marty McFly
from Back to the Future 2 skulking around
to be watching some of the things happening.
But that's a new thing.
And if they're hiring tons of Marty's for this experience,
then yeah, make one of them just work around
and try to be avoided and not answer your question.
Maybe they just assume there would be enough people
dressed as Marty with the hat on.
Right, they'd feel like,
we're so many Marty's in the red vest.
That is a really funny aspect
that you're trying to keep your eyes peeled
for Marty McFly and then you keep seeing the vest,
there he is, no, there he is, no, that's a woman.
Like, I think at any given time,
because I watch videos of it and then being there live,
like I think there are 13 Marty vests
and then different Marty modes.
And I think I saw a leather jacket Marty,
there's a bunch of different docks.
There's every type, there's a bunch of Jennifers
running around.
Well, yeah, that's the one costume
that I think a lot of people can put together very quickly.
Like, people may not have a Klingon costume at the ready,
but you can put together a Marty McFly costume pretty easily.
It definitely felt like Rick and Morty,
like the amount of Rick,
I mean, Rick and Morty is based on Back to the Future,
but I mean, having multiverse Marty's running around,
like 50 Marty's, like where's Waldo of who the real Marty was?
Knowing that that's kind of a fulcrum point
in the space-time continuum,
that's a good way to think about it,
if I were to do it again,
is that since that's an important date and time,
what if too many Marty's have shown up for too many reasons,
now there are 13 all with different tasks and goals,
bunch of docks too.
I don't like, I'm just not into cosplaying necessarily,
unless it's for like a show or something,
but I would be almost like,
if we go back of next year or whatever,
I'm like, maybe I dress like Marty too,
maybe we'll all dress like Marty.
I'm down to dress like Marty.
Everyone should be Marty.
Well, I do love that, I love Halloween,
and not Halloween Horror Nights,
but I love the Halloween thing that Disneyland does,
where you can dress in costume.
I think it's really fun,
and I love the idea that people could dress in costume
for this, it felt like it made it a lot more fun.
I will say that,
as you're going on this tram ride down,
it was the first night that we were there,
we could tell that the tram driver, the announcer,
was kind of still figuring out the script,
and kept on really imploring us to dance.
You're gonna get down there.
Oh yeah, that got said so many times.
And you're gonna dance.
Make sure that you feel the music to dance.
I was like, I don't wanna dance.
I also don't feel like,
I don't feel back to the future as a dance thing,
but I think that they were like,
we have a live band there,
and we wanna make sure it's okay for people
to feel like they can dance,
because that town square gets very crowded very quickly.
They did, again, it's a tight square,
and they have this,
I think they messed up two things in my opinion,
which is like, on the left-hand side,
this very cool thing.
It's the spinning license plate,
and the flames from the tires as the DeLorean is gone,
but it's going into the movie theater,
which is not there,
it's just a poster of a movie theater.
And that was awesome.
It was really cool-looking.
It's lit so well.
I've seen multiple people's photos of it,
all of our photos.
It looks so great.
That's such a victory,
that cool line of flames.
That was beautifully designed.
Now, on the other side,
now again, you only have a certain amount of space.
The other side, they built,
and this is classic universal,
they built like carnival games.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Nothing that has ever been in the back of the future.
Everything.
Detailed.
Again, I know I was nitpicking about the,
oh, the signs aren't the right, whatever,
but carnival games were never a part
of anything in Back to the Future.
Except in the Old West when he learned
he does a shooting gallery,
and he learned how to do it at 7-Eleven.
That's the only time. Exactly.
But that's not the 50s.
That's not where we were.
And so they have this carnival game thing set up
to win something,
but that's so tightly packed into a picture,
a photo op in the DeLorean with Einstein,
not a fake Einstein.
A real dog.
It was there.
They cast Einstein.
Which is, blew my mind as well.
That dog didn't seem,
that seemed like a wild choice to be like,
we're gonna have a dog here to pose for a lot of photos.
Dogs are comfortable meeting hundreds of people
at a time in quick succession.
They do it with Max during Grinchmas.
You see, so that's, yeah.
They have experiences.
But they must have tons of Einsteins.
There must be a whole bunch of cages back there.
Well, that night they had four Mardys.
I saw multiple things with different Mardys.
I liked our Mardy a lot.
Our Mardy was good, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But that's another one of those Rick and Morty paradise.
We've entered a world where there's so many Einsteins.
So many Einsteins.
What are they all here to do?
I would love to see the back.
The kennel is great.
There's a bunch of Einsteins.
Show me the Einstein room.
Like one Einstein doesn't wanna go on.
He's like feeling.
I can't do it.
I don't like this Mardy.
I don't feel the connection to this dog.
Now the thing was,
I feel like they could have opened up the experiences
a little bit wider,
because when you walked over to that carnival area,
you immediately got in this.
It was like carnival,
the only place for food,
non-themed food,
which is also odd.
Yeah, eat a regular ice cream bar
in Hill Valley in 1955.
Yeah, and it's like,
why are we skimping out on the theming here?
Like just call a biff water.
Give me something.
Yeah.
And then you have this recreation of Doc Brown's lab,
not his 1950s house,
but his 1980s house
with the DeLorean inside.
And that's where Einstein is.
And isn't there something with all the speakers?
I missed that entirely.
Peter from Slash on Post did that.
That's where Einstein was.
The amps blown.
Okay, okay.
So that was,
Einstein was like,
that was like a little tableau,
but it was so hard
because once we got into that area,
like people were like,
come on, move around.
It's not a,
we got ushered by a universal place,
but it was like,
but you've literally walked us into a dead end
where there's three major things going on,
including a biff who is harassing people
at the carnival games.
That is a good move,
that he's trying to miss people.
I like that.
That he yells at people
to get them to mess up
when they're trying to hit the buzzer.
I like that.
I like that a lot.
I like that the actors in that were fantastic.
He was running around yelling at everyone.
Yes.
And you could really hear him.
I would say we,
I mean, we'll probably get to it,
but like some microphone issues would be good
because sometimes you wouldn't be able to hear
certain performers in different places.
It's outdoor.
And they're getting on the courthouse steps.
And I guess they want the community
of this gather around
and gather around and you'll hear it.
Now, I don't know how you guys feel about this,
but when you arrive,
you might arrive at the,
it's on a cycle, right?
It's on a loop.
Yeah.
All the way to the end of the first movie.
We, I think, arrived actually at a great time.
We arrived at the beginning of the story.
It's up, but I talked to some people
who arrived at the end.
And then you're kind of waiting for it to recycle again.
I didn't know how you guys felt about that.
I felt we had a great experience.
We saw it kind of play out perfectly.
It turned out really well.
I almost didn't realize the extent
to which the events of the film would start playing out.
I do have the nerdy objection of,
they tell you, you watch a video on the way down
with a fake Doc Brown,
something that we've always enjoyed,
a guy playing Doc who is not Christopher Lloyd.
And I will ding the one thing about that
is his background, clearly CGI,
he's in front of giant satellite dishes
from the movie Contact.
I'm like, well, this is, why would he ever be here?
Just put him in the backdrop of his lab.
Why are we putting him outside
in front of satellite dishes?
Those little choices are like, what?
You know me, my famous experiments with satellites,
with time travel satellites.
You built it on the, just put him in front of a clock.
Give me something.
Oh yeah, wait, they've recreated his lab.
Why don't you film him in his lab?
There's, and I believe the guy we saw on the tram,
we happened to get the, I think it was the same guy.
I think that night, I think.
Oh, who was running around the actor who was running around.
But anyway, that was like, I was a little like,
what the, like that's where I feel like
there are certain,
and because they clearly own all the footage.
They do everything.
They can even take a screen grab of the backdrop
and just have him stand in front of it.
Like it doesn't.
Yes, something recognizable from the movie.
It is a lot of weird little nitpicks.
Also the fact that like, how are we getting to the past?
We were bemoaning the fact that they,
why don't they just call it a time tram?
Yeah, we're on the time tram.
We'd be so excited.
We'd be saying time tram nonstop this whole episode.
And all you need is like, they go,
this time tram, there's some, and again, I get it.
I love this part.
But it's simple, like these are the little tweaks
that also feel like it's a first year thing.
It feels like we're trying to figure it out.
But they're like, the time tram travels so fast.
You don't even realize that you've time traveled.
You know what, give me two strobes.
We'll walk by and go, this give me like a little strobe
pass as we're driving by.
Oh, that's right.
Right when you pass by the big mannequin of Ted,
right after Ted just flashed some lights at us.
Ted should have like some like weapon,
kind of like a time travel weapon
that shoots a light at the tram as you go by him on the lot.
And then you travel like right,
it's pretty close to where you end up off.
Make Ted part of it.
We know, we know already that Doc Brown
is part of the Seth MacFarlane universe
because of the, he appears in the Western.
What's that called again?
Once Upon a Time in, or the West.
A Million Ways to Die in the West.
How the West was horny or something.
I don't remember what it was called.
But Doc Brown's in it.
So Doc Brown's allowed to be in Seth MacFarlane things.
Yeah, have Ted do it.
It just felt like that was, again, we're time traveling.
And one of the coolest things about this movie is
that when you're in the car, the lightning, your time.
So we are not getting that experience.
Now meanwhile, we get that experience in Star Trek
when you're on, we get the, we fly in
and we get the warp speed, we get the turbo lift feel.
They give you a little mist, which at least, you know, works.
Yeah, yeah.
Like to kind of.
No, that was super cool.
If you go through mist, you do transform or you.
I like a mist, hell yeah.
It's something very cool in Epic Universe.
You got a great light and a great mist coming your way
over in the Potter zone, yeah.
It's the best light slash mist thing I've ever seen.
Yeah, very good mist in Epic Universe.
And then, you know, just push through that.
But we're in Hill Valley, it's awesome.
It's not exactly right, but then I think, look,
we need to be brought in as advisors on this
because I think where we're pitching here is not even.
Right, that's expensive.
Yeah, we're.
No, it's the littlest tweaks
that would just like tie it all together
because everything, there's a lot that is great here.
Performers especially.
The band is great.
They're doing the Enchantment of the Sea dance, great.
Yeah, absolutely.
And the way it all times out where like a character
might be talking to you and then on stage
at the perfect time a minute later
to make story points happen.
But if you're gonna call it fan night,
here's a place to come and like geek out
about a property you love.
Why are you gonna tell me on the way down
that you're going to the night
where Doc discovered the flux capacitor,
but then you get there and it's all the events
of the night that Marty traveled back to the future.
Those are different nights.
Why would this Under the Sea dance be going on on that?
That's not, it's when Doc bumps his head
and gets the cash.
But when you first meet Doc or when we first met Doc,
he just said this morning he came up with,
he fell off the toilet.
But then the movie kind of progresses.
I know.
These are like, they're like six days apart, aren't they?
It's not very far apart, is it?
I don't think so.
It's like it's enough time to give Marty time
to like hang out and have to get his parents together.
As a nerd, I would have liked to,
it's seen the recreation of the table
made of like the exact replica of the town square
where like Doc does his like.
Oh yes, oh if he had had some weird,
like if his, oh that's one missing thing.
If his like little workshop had been something
that you could check out.
Yeah, just look at it.
And then Lorraine comes in
and they have to cover it up really fast
and you have to help cover up.
Yeah, because the DeLorean is nowhere to be seen.
I mean, there's a photo op DeLorean,
but like the whole thing culminates
and obviously to Marty going back to the future.
And the way they kind of do that
is everything is being acted out
until the final back to the future moment
where it is then projected on the clock tower.
Very cool.
They recreate the lightning from that moment.
That was awesome.
That felt like amazing.
And then culminating in when lightning strikes,
they represent that with the firework going off.
Very cool.
From the courthouse.
Yes, which I don't think anybody expected.
I don't think we saw it coming.
I've read get there before midnight
because past midnight for neighbors,
they are not allowed to do it.
So do it, do it first thing you go.
Which by the way, this is going between now and May 18th
if you're in Los Angeles, you're gonna be in Los Angeles.
Yeah, get to the fan fest.
And wanna check it out, which I do recommend.
Despite all of these, nitpick, nitpick, nitpick,
I had a great time.
No, this is awesome.
I will say the other thing that made me slightly
uncomfortable was seeing them play out
the Biff sexual assault scene.
That is, it's an interesting moment
because everyone's got their cameras out.
Oh, now everyone's filming it.
Yeah, and you're watching this great moment of George,
hey, you get your damn hands off her.
And then Marty is like with us in the crowd going like,
yes, yes.
And we were watching Marty while Biff
and while that interaction is happening,
he's like looking at the picture,
like he's fully in it acting.
Like, yes, okay, this is great.
I'm gonna go in and I'm gonna play the music.
But it was funny to watch that moment,
which is a great moment in the movie,
but it is funny to be like,
we're supposed to be interacting here, but.
They told us to dance,
but they didn't tell us to stop any assault.
We should all be getting involved.
We should probably, each and every one of them.
And that's a fan dream we've all had, I think,
is to prevent that particular famous movie assault.
Yeah, yeah.
100 people all at once.
Hey, you, get your damn hands off.
And that's what I was missing.
I do want, and I feel like this is all a great baseline
of where we could do it.
But I would love to have had some more,
we were watching, again, we were watching a show.
And yes, I think you could interact with them.
And I felt like we did.
We interacted with Gordy Wilson, the earlier.
Goldie.
Sorry, Goldie Wilson, who is gonna be the next mayor.
And he was great,
because he doesn't really have to do anything
in the story of Back to the Future.
No.
But just walk around and be like, mayor.
He directs Trav, he tells you about some things.
Yeah.
And I was like, maybe I should ask if there's food anywhere,
because he's dressed like a,
this was some of my situation,
is like, okay, go talk to these characters,
and I know who he is,
and I know he's gonna be the mayor.
But the people ahead of me had already spoiled.
They'd just done the thing of,
are you interested in politics at all?
Oh yeah, mayor.
You're obviously just trying to set him up to say it,
which the actor said, great, it's just like in the movie.
Yeah.
But then I'm like, why am I talking to this guy
who cleans up counters at a, like in story,
there has to be a reason I can talk,
I wanna talk to him.
Because he's just walking around town,
so he's not even in front.
Like again, it is a crucial part of the story,
like a lot takes place in that shop.
That's not there, that shop is not there.
Yeah.
And so he's just wandering around in his outfit,
out and about on this night of insanity, I guess.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
They also made an odd choice of giving Biff a friend
that was not dressed like any of his gang.
Like give me the 3D glasses, give me Casey Sermansko.
Billy Zane, Zane, Zane.
Yeah, I mean, they gave Biff a guy in a yellow cardigan.
That was not, that's not a recognizable character
from the movie, in my opinion.
Yes, he seemed, he had a fun, lackey energy.
Because you're nearby, it happened,
and you get to watch them break up.
You get to watch him be fired as a lackey,
and that's a fun moment to get to see.
Now, the highlight of it all for me, for sure,
was we're gathering to watch Marvin Barry,
and so the set is beginning,
the set that we know is gonna culminate
in Marty joining for Johnny B. Goode,
but I'm just trying to enjoy some good old-fashioned
rock and roll music, and then who should get in my face
with mean old Principal Strickland?
Yes, that was intense.
And he just, he chose me, out of nowhere,
he just rounded, like I had no prep
to be talking to Strickland,
and then he was just right in my face,
uncomfortably in my face, post-COVID uncomfortably.
But you stood up to him, you went, you approached,
as you approached Goldie Wilson with a lot of care,
you approached Principal Strickland as really combative.
Thank you, thank you.
You were like in a David Mamet play with him or something,
and the intensity of both performers,
we haven't un-videotied each other.
Yeah, I guess we had a close-up.
You're like, I want rock and roll.
You were fighting for rock and roll.
Rock and roll.
Right, and I appreciated that.
Yes, I think I unlocked my inner mic.
I was fighting for, and I was a little embarrassed.
I'll just get ahead of it by something
that I ended up saying to him.
When you're just in the moment,
and you're talking to an iconic movie character,
so you're not thinking about what you're saying,
and I think he's saying that rock and roll
is for no good-niks, and I said,
no, rock and roll is an amazing art form.
Rock and roll is the new wave, is what I said to him,
and then later I'm like, oh, good,
and you're gonna wanna post that clip.
Here I am saying rock and roll is the new wave.
But I felt like that was your character.
I felt like your character was trying to say.
Sure, sure, not just me.
You were being respectful to character.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Well, yeah, I guess I found a character in that moment
who cares about the music, and who knows the good.
We were told.
Rock and roll ends up doing over the,
I've seen all the many,
Strickland doesn't know about Live Aid.
No.
No, no, no.
How rock and roll has healed our planet.
Hard Rock Cafe, how much good it's done for the rainforest.
I had to fight for all that.
Strickland has no idea what's coming.
Well, we were told explicitly to,
these people don't know about Instagram.
They only have three tells.
There were good written jokes, I feel,
I don't remember any of them, but to these people,
TikTok is the sound of a clock.
Right, yeah.
Now, I will say that, again,
these are these small details that I'm like,
who's minding the mint here?
Because he's like, the shows that they're watching are,
and they list these shows, but famously,
the show that is a part of Back to the Future
is The Honeymooners.
Oh, that's right.
They don't say The Honeymooners.
Right, yeah, yeah.
Like, he references to other shows, and I'm like,
but we,
Dragnet.
Why are we, yeah, why are we not referencing
the thing that is a plot point of the movie?
He said Jack Benny program.
I was trying to think, like, is The Honeymooners, like,
owned by CBS, or not CBS, like ABC?
Is there a, they aren't allowed to say that.
Is there something, I don't know.
I think that might be, well, certainly why,
there's no Lucy mentions.
And if Jason had been with us, he would have said,
yeah, I'm, we watch these things today.
This is what I, I watch the Dumont Network every night.
Well, how is this different?
Exactly, yeah, so I wonder if that's,
I'm always curious about these events,
like, if you would get the real shit of like,
yeah, we couldn't say Honeymooners.
I know, and that, I think that there is some sort of,
but again, like, I think you can say these words.
You would think you could say them.
But there's somebody who's probably, yeah.
I think my Googling will either help me discover that,
okay, yes, I was gonna say, all right, CBS does own it,
so I think that was a good guess that might be why.
But I was hoping that from Googling, so.
Oh, but they are, they did,
so when they made a deal with Star Trek,
they should have made a deal to be allowed to say
Honeymooners on the tram tour.
Yeah, they should have thought of that as.
That should have been in there.
That should have been in the contract.
I will say the ending, like we said,
was a great ending, a really fun way to see it done,
because obviously, look, if I had my dreaders,
I would love to see a Waterworld kind of style car
driving down that street.
Obviously, you can't do that.
The fire in the street seemed like there was a lot
of security around that fire in the street.
A lot of people walking around there,
there's fire people out there,
be like, don't get anywhere near this fire.
But I think we all agreed that the one big plus up
would be to have a stump person, a la Tinkerbell,
from the top of the clock tower.
Sure, yeah.
Shoot down on a little.
It's much better than Tinkerbell.
That'd be amazing to watch a guy.
And it would have still worked perfectly for the moment,
because it's such an iconic moment,
and I feel like it would be,
it would just go from roof to roof.
Just go to, we don't even have to see land.
Just go roof to roof.
Oh, and then somebody, yes, and then somebody runs down
until like more of a face actor comes down,
tests himself on.
Well, send a dummy down.
100%, yeah. I would love that.
Yes, please, dummies.
They have those Spider-Man things now that they do.
Yeah, it's like just Stuntronic or whatever.
Oh yeah, just throw a simple Stuntronic.
Just throw a Stuntronic around.
I mean, overall, I really enjoy,
and getting to stay there for a while,
to be immersed in it, despite all these details,
and of all of the,
because I didn't want to wait in the lines
to do the photo ops and everything,
but that I ended up with,
of all the things, that I have a detention slip
written for me.
It was pretty great.
By Strickland.
I'm gonna keep that in my wallet
for as long as it'll hold,
and then checking it later,
like 3 p.m. Scott Strickland.
And my wife was very impressed by that.
She was like, what was this thing?
I was like, let me show you how not dumb this was.
I have a Strickland detention slip in my pocket.
And that to me was the thing that,
the Goldie Wilson and Strickland moments
were actually really fun,
because I feel like what I liked about that was
the thing was alive around us.
And I feel like I would like to have seen
even a little bit more of that,
because the main actors,
Doc, Marty, Lorraine, and Biff,
they have to be at certain places at certain times.
They're telling a story that is on a loop.
A couple more side characters around
for these interactions, I think,
would even be a little plus up.
Just a little, because it's fun.
I think I talked to a lot of people
who spent a long time there,
like two hours.
It was a great, that was A plus, A plus.
I mean, nitpicks put aside.
Yeah, if you could have gotten a hamburger
and a beer and hung out even,
it would have been even better.
But it's like, that's what I want from
the Back to the Future template
is what I want from almost all the immersive things.
Star Wars, you want just a loop of all the movies
character-wise going on in Galaxy's Edge.
Doesn't matter that they don't take place in Batuu.
I don't give a shit about it.
It's just Luke, he's looking for Aunt Beru and Uncle Owen.
Doesn't matter.
Look, they've already decided,
the new movies decided that the same things
happen over and over in Star Wars.
Just make it happen.
Just have it happen here on Batuu.
That's totally fine.
We'll complain about it for 90 minutes
because we got the shit to fill in a podcast.
That's right.
Doesn't mean we won't go over and over again.
And again, the iconic location is a big deal.
I think what you want is just,
I think it's really fulfilling.
We didn't get to interact with
any characters in Star Trek.
They're moving you through.
Very good actors, fun experience, all for it, aces.
This is really fun because I felt like
they really wanted you to interact
with the characters, but because they're on a timeline,
it's hard.
So I found when watching the Marty character
that we had who was great,
he does have to be like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, but I got a thing.
I gotta get over.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, very busy.
Whereas Strickland, I got a second with.
The goal, I feel like a lot of people were having.
Strickland has no plot points.
He had one cue to meet, which I was really impressed.
Oh my God, he was just in my face.
And now he's up here scolding Marty
for playing a solo that was too darn loud.
Yeah.
Which is also not- It is really
cleverly blocked out.
Not from that part of the movie.
Oh, that's true, yes.
It's messed in there.
He has to be Huey Lewis and Strickland at the same time.
It was fascinating because you know how like,
there's concepts that are tried to,
I've read about, you know, like,
if you were able to see space time,
if you were able to remove yourself
and see time and space all as one,
it would look like a single line.
It's almost like we were seeing Back to the Future
removed from linear time.
Oh, yeah.
Which I kind of found fascinating.
Like you were just seeing all of it happening at once
which is kind of how our lives would look
if you could see them from a certain vantage point.
Especially with a time travel movie,
I found that very fascinating that like,
everything is like folding in on itself
and we're seeing it and we can experience it
in different ways and you could experience
the same timeline in an hour differently
than you did before.
It was very, it's kind of a mind-boggling thing, yeah.
And the fact that they were even switching Marty
so you would get there and maybe see one loop end
and a new Marty begin is kind of crazy too.
Right, because that's a multiversal.
Yeah.
You would see a different Scott who loves haunts.
You would see different things and slightly different
or it's almost exactly the same
and it's like you just have a slightly different haircut.
Who knows?
I loved it.
I think it should expand a little bit.
If they bring that back as a kid,
that would be the number one.
Like these are the rides that I wanted
that I never got as a kid, right?
Like I wanted, like if this was a thing,
this should always be a thing.
And I feel like if universal was smart,
they should keep this.
As long as there's nothing shooting on that line.
And I think if the rumors are true
and the little hill valleys are going up across the globe
and universal parks all around,
this is a strong rumored thing.
And if they're testing the waters for that,
that like, because we can't do that ride again.
We can't go to 2015 and have the video with Doc and Biff.
So like just section off an entire other part of
Back to the Future and interact with 50s characters.
And it's a cool idea.
It's just a cool thing to do.
But by the way, in VR, I have done that
Back to the Future ride.
They have that ride in VR now.
You can do, it's great.
You can actually even put that,
give everybody a headset, put them in their room.
This is the, you've made the strongest sell
for me to get a headset, finally.
Yeah, you get to go on old rides
with old outmoded technology.
Because it's like all that stuff is built
for that kind of perspective.
It's kind of great.
Let's touch a little before we wrap up
on Dungeons & Dragons.
Which was, we were told was the highlight of the night.
Some people had really dinged that as being like,
that's the one to see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which I felt, I don't know if it was just
the quickly downed Isla Nublar IPAs talking.
We had to chug a beer because of the waiting in line.
What a nice thing of all to be my favorite beer to chug.
And then having that kind of hit and then be,
first of all, told by you that maybe,
I think this is gonna be scarce.
I think you're gonna be scared.
And I told you, I'm betting it will be.
And it was not.
So the relief of that hitting me.
And then also, I'm just getting a little floaty
while I'm being ushered from room to room
where I don't understand what the hell is going on.
I sort of love it.
Couldn't tell you anything that happened
in Dungeons & Dragons.
I was paying 100% attention.
Part of that was due to the lack of microphones.
Some sound bleed happening from the other things.
Oh yeah, yes, from room to room.
But I truly don't care.
I liked that I didn't know.
I'm just like, oh, this now.
Oh, what, this now?
I felt so dumb, but I loved it.
There was one part where they said a bunch of stuff.
Somebody said, okay, your mission is clear.
And then three things I didn't understand remotely.
Well, this is, so the,
I would say of all,
Back to the Future is a different beast, right?
Because Back to the Future is literally
an area in Universal Studios where they shot the movie.
You can't beat that.
But the props and stuff,
I think we thought a little lackluster.
Star Trek, pretty good.
But also, moments where you're like,
okay, it could maybe be better,
but it was definitely high quality.
Generic enterprise, good enterprise,
but generic enterprise.
Right, and certain parts.
This T2B, great design.
Fully, beautifully worked out, thought out,
looked like they spent a lot of money
on whatever this was.
Yes, I have a little bit of factoid
that was told to me that VIP guides tell people
when they're in this.
Some of the trees in this experience
are from the E.T. Adventure.
What are you talking about?
What?
I don't know which one specifically.
Now it's a true fan festival.
The thing I'm the biggest fan of.
Those were the old trees.
I mean, by the way, I love those trees.
The way you walk through the forest
and smell the pine like that.
They still have the trees
and we were seeing them and we didn't even know.
Why aren't they out somewhere all the time?
Well, get mummy out of there.
Put it back in.
Just put the trees in.
Supposedly the trees sometimes are used
in the Horror Nights mazes.
Apparently these are trees that are maybe often used.
I love that these trees are out.
You've sent me straight to watching
a ride through of this again,
just to see a purely tree spot.
A walk through.
Thank you, Scott.
Thank you, Mike.
Now I will say.
Oh, thank you, friend.
This is, again, I am,
first of all, I love this.
I love that we are catering.
I think that people are trying to figure out
how to make theme parks.
As magical as they were for us
and we went and continued to be,
but try to get people in, try to do new things.
I felt like each one of these experiences
had something that I really, really liked,
but it was almost like every experience had
two of three things, but it's like,
oh, but one would, this one, we walk in
and you are in these different spots.
You're wizards.
You are knights and you're clerics.
You happen to be a cleric when you could be a wizard?
We all got wizards.
We were the only three in the wizard spot.
But it played no part in our story,
nor what we had to do, nor was it ever referenced again.
It was like, and that was the thing that I'm like,
well, why go out of the way to say
that we're in the spot of the wizards
and we're on our block, that's the wizard block,
and then they keep on going, well, come with us.
And you think, oh, okay, well, the wizards
are going in this one room
and the clerics are going in the other room.
But no, it's just two doors that open to the same room.
So some people on the left-hand side,
some people are on the right,
and there's no difference because the performance
is in the middle.
By the way, I love this.
Don't know what happened in it,
but I felt like we're walking this line.
I'm like, I wanna, you're so close to giving me,
all right, all the wizards.
I would even go for, all the wizards go, yay.
All the clerics go, ooh.
Give me just something where I feel like.
All the rogues in the house say, hey.
That's what I think was missing in all of these things
is just the slightest bit of audience participation.
And it didn't have to be big.
I don't need you to give me a sword
and run out to fight things,
but just give me a vocalization.
Give me something like, you did it.
Your world opened up because you said something.
I was like, oh, I don't care.
You can just remember your color and point to it.
Sure.
Truly, there was not a thing. Medieval time style.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, there's these nitpicks with all of these things,
but don't you feel like this could all be
super solved next year,
and this could be a hell of an event.
I think it already is.
I think it's off to a great start.
I could just see a little bit more kinks get worked out,
and then this becomes a, you have to.
There's a whole new way to see
Universal Studios killer. I like a soft launch of this.
I think that this can,
I imagine the first year of Horror Nights was similar.
They're trying a lot of different stuff.
It feels like they're very invested in it.
I thought it was not done cheaply.
I think they were like, let's figure it out.
Let's build these experiences.
Let's make this a fun night.
We're celebrating fans.
And I think it's about how do you balance out
that many people making it unique,
and how do you get it beyond the photo op?
And maybe they're part of them,
which is like, that's the biggest thing.
The biggest goal for them is photo ops.
And I think a lot of people in those cosplay outfits,
to be in Picard's chair,
to be in the DeLorean with Einstein,
that's worth the price of admission.
And I've been to a lot of these events with my kids,
not these events, but Instagrammable museums.
To have those pictures, it's like, oh, that's the best.
It almost makes your night more memorable,
because here's a million pictures of what we did.
And I think a lot, we weren't doing that.
We were just kind of enjoying the rides and or the experiences.
I think they can make this,
I think this is a giant solid foot in the right direction,
and it will only get better.
Ding.
It's not the nitpicks, it's the food.
The food needs to be more accessible.
They clearly were not ready for the amount.
We waited, what, conservatively 30 minutes to get a beer?
Yeah, and that wasn't one of the fun ones.
That was the regular Isla New Bar that I like,
and I thank you all for waiting in that line.
Dad really wanted that Isla New Bar.
By the way, I was excited to have it,
but I'm also like, why have one person manning that?
I'm constantly making complicated tiki drinks,
and then go, yeah, that was strangely understanding.
And it felt like that's what happened
at the Dungeons and Dragons Tavern,
which looked really cool and themed,
and they had all these really cool things.
But it's like, there is something about,
and I don't know if this is like, maybe it's like a,
they have to just have them ready to go.
And it's almost like, pre-make these drinks,
and be like, you want that?
Boom, boom, and they're like, here, you want this?
Because it's like, it just felt like we were waiting
for Chipotle-level weights.
It's like, it shouldn't be this,
this shouldn't be this complicated.
It's not like bespoke food.
It's like, or they should have more vendors out.
It felt like they were understaffed, which is odd.
That's really the only nitpick of the night is like,
and maybe they'll fix that on night two.
They must have been like-
It might have been a random thing.
Yeah, maybe they didn't know how many people would show up.
I'm at least happy that there's a ton
of great performers employed and doing a great job.
That's a good amount of staffing,
and yeah, so many talented people did so great.
I might have one more nitpick,
which is the sheer volume of Billy Joel.
There was so much Billy Joel playing
that it could have been, here's Star Trek,
here's Doc Brown, here's Billy.
So much was that a part of the night.
I think they had like a half-hour music loop,
and three of them were Billy Joel songs.
I heard We Didn't Start the Fire three separate times.
When I was walking through City Walk,
I even heard of Billy.
My God, and I am a big Billy Joel fan.
I saw him here at the Intuit Dome
and he'd bring out Axl Rose.
Oh, right? Amazing.
Wow, wow.
Axl Rose singing Welcome to the Jungle,
and I was like, very impressive.
Not even a Billy Joel?
Yeah, no, I was like, this is great.
That's fun.
Yes, no, not even shade on Billy in particular.
It's just a high volume of one particular thing.
Then I went home, as I put on like,
oh, let me watch a live feed of what's going on up there
now that I'm back here on my couch,
turn it on, Marilyn Monroe,
straight to We Didn't Start the Fire again.
Why this?
Why this so much?
That's a great question.
We also, we didn't talk about this,
but I wanted to just mention it for a second.
There was also a new part of the park experience
that was going on where these coins
that were in these cases that we were scanning,
and if you scanned all four coins,
you would get some sort of badge or a pass.
We opted out after we realized that once you scanned it,
you had to log in to like a...
You had to have an nvcuni.com account.
Yeah, and that felt like...
That's the thing you do on day one of employment.
Yeah, it felt, and it didn't feel like a fun thing
to get a membership on.
It seemed hard, yeah.
Yeah, no, and it was just stations.
There was just a light, a circle with a question mark.
And the gentleman...
That's the fun medallion you gotta look for.
They're like, we don't even know what this is.
The guy who was speaking to us was like,
what I like is, I like when you're in these moments,
I'm so bummed I never got to experience
when Frontierland became that day
where they were doing immersive.
Oh, yeah.
People had sides and stuff like that,
and that was the idea,
like that might be what Galaxy Edges.
But he was like, yeah, we're doing something
really interesting.
We hid these all around the park.
Now, I did clock all of them.
It's hard to hide something that is a cylindrical post
with a rotating, glowing coin in it.
It's not hidden.
It felt like the guy was having to sell something
that even he didn't believe in.
Because I was saying out loud, what is this thing?
Why isn't it working?
I can explain that, why you see...
And then within one sentence,
he was catching the logic flaws himself.
And he was like, you just tap it with your phone,
and then I did, and he's like, well, actually,
maybe just take a picture of it, yeah.
That's gonna be a cleaner way to do it.
And then we all walked away
once we saw the additional login step.
Yeah, so all right, that's a note.
Maybe whatever that is, we don't need to do that.
I like the idea.
Just one Billy Joel song an hour
instead of three every half hour.
These are all nitpicks for what I think overall
was a fantastic thing.
Do we all approve?
Would we all do it again?
Or are we all for another year?
I kinda wanna do it now.
I kinda said I'd like to go back again
knowing what it was.
I didn't know what it was going into it.
I think where this thing needs to improve,
or not even prove, is to your point,
keep the theming going on throughout the park.
Horror nights, they got a million clowns
running around with chainsaws wherever you're going.
They know how to do this type of thing.
I think it's just about getting that infrastructure in.
Now horror nights may bring in a lot more money
and they can afford a lot more people,
so that may be part of it.
But it seems like there were areas
where we're just dead on theming Billy Joel songs
and then fully Star Trek.
But even the Star Trek area was Billy Joel songs.
So it's almost like, can we isolate the islands?
Can we?
That would be nice, yeah.
Because then when we were down
at the Dungeons and Dragons area,
it was that DJ who was doing wedding music.
He did Casper Slide, yeah.
Yeah, so they were like,
I just feel like there are these things where it's like,
they were trying to keep it a party vibe,
but it's also like, we're nerds, we're here,
we're in costume.
Play me some, you know.
The Star Trek First Contact score.
Yeah, give me that stuff, but we want that.
We wanna feel like we're in Quark's bar,
not hearing Sabrina Carpenter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can hear that back up at City Walk,
and we will.
Although it was kind of special to get a mashup,
as you noticed, of Party in the USA with Pitbull.
Yes, that was nice.
I love that.
That's all crafted for us.
And by the way, that's a real DJ, not a person.
They're not playing track,
that was the DJ that was up there doing his thing.
Yeah, I got the right idea.
But then mash it up into that ZZ Top.
Dun, dun, dun, do, dun, dun, do.
I love that.
Yeah, I wanna hear that all night long.
And I also think that they had an issue with spacing,
because we saw Back to the Future, it was awesome.
You get off, and it's seemingly like
there was a Back to the Future restaurant
that we did not see,
and there's also a Back to the Future band
called the Flux Capacitors,
and they're just doing full music all the time.
Really cool, but they seem all separate.
They're islands.
An island, yeah, away from the main attraction.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, there's one more thing on the way out the door.
We have not mentioned Xanathar.
Xanathar, the gigantic puppet who shows,
spoiler alert, although I'm sure you've seen it already,
if you've watched the YouTube video about this,
Xanathar is a gigantic puppet
in Dungeons & Dragons experience.
I think if Xanathar were in the park year round,
you'd become a new icon of Universal Studios.
It's one of the best things in the park in any form.
Well, this is what I'm saying,
like the money that,
whatever they did for Dungeons & Dragons,
and I thought it was really interesting
that they spent the most money,
clearly the most money on Dungeons & Dragons.
It's like, that's what I was so confused about.
I was like, you created this awesome thing.
The costumes there were great,
the characters there were great,
but just to take that away,
and somebody, when I posted a picture of that,
somebody was like,
oh, is that a Big Trouble in Little China attraction?
Oh, yeah, it looks similar.
Oh, yeah, it's a little shop of horrors, too.
I wonder why the money was spent on Dungeons & Dragons,
and I wonder if it's partly
because that's a new property for them,
they did that movie,
there's a new series that I think is coming out
that someone is behind.
So maybe they're like,
this might be something that we are investing
more time and money into,
whereas the rest is like,
ye nostalgia guys.
Yeah, maybe.
I feel like if it's gonna be a little bit scattershot,
it's little things that can tie it all together,
it would all work for me if,
as you're leaving for the night,
you meet one more Xanathar,
and he sings Harry Truman, Doris Day,
Red China, John D. Ricks.
Well, there you go.
That's a dream.
By the way, you have a very talented listenership.
They should take any videos from the livestreams and stuff
and just put that together,
and let's sing it together, and let's do it.
That is a mashup I'd love to see,
even more than Miley Cyrus and Pitbull.
But overall, good reports,
especially from the evening, a great time.
Great excuse to hang, Paul.
Thank you for coming.
I was thrilled to be there.
I loved it.
And I am excited for more of it.
I'm excited if next year is three different properties,
or you continue to build out more properties.
Alternate 85, different backstories.
Yeah, that's what we want.
And I guess there's, I'll say one more thing,
where they should also just embrace,
the Simpsons, obviously,
it's so beautiful, the Simpsons area.
That should be also thriving with Simpsons characters
during fan nights, right?
I mean, to a certain extent.
And deep cuts.
Yeah, the one-eyed baby should be walking around.
But maybe that's a Disney problem.
Oh, yeah, yeah, they're not gonna free up money.
I bet they would if it wasn't just for Disney.
Yeah, it's a bummer.
That's a bummer, because you are walking through these areas.
Well, maybe next year, you have Fast and Furious,
we'll get to bump into Kurt Russell's character,
to be at the Corona dealership.
I don't know these movies well,
and you have to tell us who you wanna meet
from Fast and Furious.
Who's the dream, who's the ultimate fan dream?
Look, I think you would, for me,
it's be Mamoa with the going around being crazy.
I'd love to meet any of them.
I mean, they're big personnel, big shoes to fill.
Of course.
Harder to cast, because it's so muscular.
Oh, sure, but they find, hey,
Waterworld's got a lot of Bloodjack guys.
They can, yeah, and save one Jack one
to do the Doc Brown slide.
And let's bring back some of that universal
old West stunt show in that night.
Let's have somebody fall off the building
from the Fast and Furious building.
Let's do some more stuff.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely, yeah.
Just don't go off the other side,
which goes all the way down the entire mountain.
Well, this was a blast to talk with you today,
a blast to do it the other night.
So much fun.
I'll sure you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for joining us again.
Yes, narrowly escaped, narrowly survived.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug?
No, that's it.
My book, Joyful Recollections to Trauma,
comes out May 6th, and every week for free on YouTube,
you can check out Rob Hubel and I
on a show called The Dark Web.
It's just.
Oh yeah, I've been seeing some clips of it.
Yeah, it's been fun.
Really funny stuff on there, yeah, yeah, yeah.
As for us, for three bonus episodes every month,
check out podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast,
The Ride.
Thanks today to Brendan, Lucas, and Kelly
at Frog City Studios, and shout out to Brendan's cousin,
who's in the flux capacitors.
I'm sorry we didn't get to see the band.
We've heard good things.
We briefly did.
We walked by them.
Oh, we did, okay, great.
I watched some stuff online
and I was like, that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
It reminds me of, and again, that's a great,
a great, smart, cool thing to do.
Yeah, very cool.
Like, it's not Billy Joel, it's the flux capacitors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah.
Little less Billy, but just a little.
Just a little.
Just a little, we need to see it last.
Definitely keep some Billy.
Okay.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.