Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcasts to Ride the Second Gate.
Turn in your passports at the door.
This is the Magic Kingdom.
You might not be allowed to leave.
I was going to say, what's your name?
I'm Jason Sheridan.
We were laughing very loud, so I wasn't sure what's going on.
He was letting the laugh die down.
I was letting the laugh.
But he was being polite, right?
And laugh, and laugh, and laugh.
And now he's serious.
We should do that more when I think I say something really hilarious and I go like, hold
on a second.
Let's let the listener at home catch their breath, or say it out, and hold for laugh.
I'm Jason Sheridan, and joined, as always, by Mike Carlson and Scott Gerner.
They're here.
Hold for massive applause, hold for huge applause, as everyone applauds when the hosts are introduced
when they are alone.
Everyone driving, please take your hands off the wheel and clap.
You had that line, so I let you do it, but I thought of a little song to kick it off
if you want to hear that.
Oh, please.
Sure.
Okay, here we go.
Disney fans, this new park's gonna save the company.
Abu, Abu Dhabi, authentically Disney, but distinctly Emirati, Abu, Abu Dhabi.
Hooray.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah, I thought so.
I wanted to do a musical salute to our new favorite place, a place that, okay, full disclosure,
I've only heard of this place for the first time right now, and I heard it after the name
Disney, so therefore I love it, and I refuse to look up anything else about it.
It's a great place, a perfect place, because they're hosting the Disney company.
That's all we need to know, and that's all we need to say.
I think, right, end of episode.
Yay.
Welcome to Abu Dhabi, Disney.
Everything seems copacetic about this.
Don't look to your left, please, let's go over here.
As long as you keep your eyes focused on Yas Island only, as long as we don't go looking
around other parts of the country or, you know, people who are being detained in basements
in different parts of the country, and everything should be fine.
That's right.
So anyway, here we go.
Yay.
Yeah, we're excited with no qualifications, especially because we've got, I mean, all
right, let's just explain the whole thing.
Disney's seventh resort is open, Disney's not resort, it's seventh theme park destination
is opening.
And it is opening in Abu Dhabi in the United Arab Emirates.
I got this information, this broke about a week ago, and I got it during a hotel stay,
I got to do an overnight for my anniversary, Aaron and I, 11 years, and it was a thrill
to get to go do a big old Disney day, and it was a magical, perfect Disney day.
As good as they come, we got everything we wanted, we got Guardians, we got Carthay
Manhattan's end of list, anything else is bonus on top of that list.
Yeah.
But it was like a magical one where everything worked out for us and luck was on our side,
and then just in all these little ways, everything worked out perfect, and it was like, wow.
The next morning, just like exhausted, but just blown away by how magical a Disney day
can be, and how perfect, we really got the best of the company.
And then I checked my phone, and I immediately saw the worst of the company, the sobriety,
the splash of water in the face of like, wow, we really did it, the company really provided
for, oh no, what has happened, what are we paying into?
Yeah, I had to double check to make sure it wasn't a speculation site or a rumor site.
Sometimes you also see those parody Disney sites now.
Have you caught this?
Have you gotten sent a parody Disney news site, like the Onion for Disney fans?
Oh, that's grim.
I've been sent this from my mother or something who thought it was real.
It'll be like the silliest stuff, they're replacing the water on Pirates of the Caribbean
with bubblegum or something.
It'll be like that level of like, but it's like, it's called, I shouldn't know the name
of it.
With the worst Photoshop or possibly AI art you've ever seen, I feel like I've seen one
of these, and the illusion lasted for me for 1.5 seconds, and I did not click through to
anything else.
You know what's funny?
I'm all off on tangents here.
I was in line at the grocery store, and I realized now, I overheard a cashier telling
somebody that they're turning Guardians of the Galaxy back into Tower of Terror, and
it took all of my strength not to interject and say, that is not happening.
That's not, he's saying the wrong thing, and the people in line were like, they were skeptical
too, but they were just like, oh, okay, or whatever.
So I feel like I'm battling misinformation a lot on different playing fields.
Excuse me, Mike Carlson, Podcast The Red.
You probably recognize me.
If you don't, if I must, I do host podcasts about this stuff, and I would have heard about
this.
Pull up.
Well, I had my badge at the ready in case I decided to say anything to prove it.
Did you have your gun?
Yes, I did.
Always armed, always on duty, the podcasters motto.
My Toy Story Midway Mania gun with the pull toy.
It's massive.
Yeah, I pulled that out of my pocket.
Excuse me, misinformation, stop.
Click, click, click, click, click.
Oh, my wrist hurts.
That's 10 yanks of a rope that tells you that this is false information.
Yes.
So anyway, that was, it was real.
The story was real.
Let's save it for, you know, the audience are the people at the grocery store.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
If you spoil all your scoops there, then they don't get what they pay for here.
Okay.
So, well, so, all right, but we can confirm that.
We're sure that's not happening.
That's, I don't know.
Maybe this person has insight info.
Maybe, maybe.
It would be surprising.
It wouldn't make any sense, but yeah, I guess it's possible.
I think we're all thrown, though, by this Disney Abu Dhabi news because I don't think
anyone had heard this rumor even remotely.
This is not leaked.
Yeah.
As far as I know.
I don't think so.
So it was quite the cut to that.
There wasn't even like, we didn't even get a moment of, oh, my God, they're going to
do this.
It was straight to Eiger, Demaro, the Abu Dhabi guys, the Yass Island guys, Mickey and
Minnie on a weird stage built into the beach with mouse ears.
And then concept art that is as generic as you could possibly produce, that is the least
committed to art you've ever seen.
Yeah, very blurry.
The castle is just some squares.
Yeah.
There are just some squares and diamonds and like what, like.
Could be a crystal cathedral.
It very much seems like crystal cathedral, it seems like, eh, this isn't European.
They don't like that shit.
So crystals.
Yeah, like glass is what we read.
Beach guy stuff.
Yeah.
So I mean, today, I believe even today was confirmed that it's all indoors.
I saw something like literally today, somebody confirmed that it's all indoors.
So I wonder if this is even representative of anything they're actually doing or this
is just sort of an abstraction of the idea of a theme park.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Yeah, because the heat there is, I mean, it's a desert.
It's terrible.
There's literally laws.
There are basic labor laws saying they cannot build between like twelve thirty and three
thirty because the heat and sun are so bad.
Yeah.
All right.
Will these rules be followed?
This we will see.
Yeah.
Maybe when Disney's in play.
Will any.
We're giving up.
We put mouse ears on them with a little brim, a little special brim that'll keep them.
No, I was curious about heat.
They in July last year, they hit one twenty three.
Yeah.
An average in July is like one oh four to one eleven.
So yeah, it's going to have to be.
It has to be.
Yeah.
Mostly.
But that's not reflected in the concept art, huh?
I don't think so.
I mean, it can't really tell, though, because they've they've figured out a better like
Universal.
We haven't talked too much on the show about the UK park that they've announced in that
concept art.
You can tell these are concepts that they've just done some light, either Photoshop or
some little tweaks to to try to hide what is pretty clear, like it's pretty clear that
Back to the Future Hill Valley is in there and they just maybe remove the top part of
the clock tower or something like they did.
They did some slight changes to to make you not sure exactly.
To abstractify a little.
What are the other big things with that?
Jurassic Park, I believe is the rumor.
Haddington.
I believe that there looks to be a Waterworld type like show in the back, but it could be
James Bond.
Yeah.
They mentioned James Bond.
They mentioned James Bond in like a press release or something.
Finally outside of that one thing.
That one.
Yeah.
Dominion attraction.
With only Judi Dench, that Judi Dench in the pre show.
Yeah.
And no Brosnan in the ride.
Sure.
No Brosnan anywhere to be seen.
So that's when the rules as established by Indiana Jones were not the star and back to
the future.
The rules used to be no star.
Pick your secondary character.
No star.
Yeah.
Now I think we may be kind of expect stars.
Right.
And it's interesting with James Bond.
It's like we're in the middle of they're in the middle of figuring out what the next one
is.
So I don't know who it would be.
Yeah.
So I guess maybe the next one.
I don't know.
Whoever is the next Bond.
It's up to Jeff Bezos.
It really is.
He could be him.
Yeah.
He could be on the tux.
It certainly seems like that's where he thinks he's headed with his his new look.
I'd be really excited if they bought it and then that was the direction that's what they're
doing.
Well, this new James Bond is hot and cool in his mid 60s.
He's not a dork who works in a computer on a computer in a garage for sure.
Do you think he does hair for that?
Or does he?
Yeah, hair.
Yeah.
The baldness is hot.
So he stays in my dream.
It's the most obvious wig of all time.
Yes.
Maybe.
Maybe he does the look that all the Trump A.I. photos are of like Trump should go grow
a beard and shave his head bald.
He looks so powerful.
He looked like Jeff Bridges and first Iron Man.
He did kind of look weird.
Like it kind of cool, I guess, in those photo shops.
Oh, Obadiah Steyn.
Yeah.
Regular Iron Man villain Obadiah Steyn.
I watched that entire movie and I didn't know his character's name was Obadiah Steyn.
Correct.
Yeah.
Obadiah Steyn.
So I saw this news and I I'm not an expert by any means, but I've been reading like I've
been reading news about the Middle East since college, maybe even high school.
So it's a generic statement, I suppose.
I mean, I guess technically I have.
There's a lot.
But I've been like, you know, it's hard to tell which governments have been overthrown
and replaced by Western or CIA interests.
But I let out a groan because when I saw it was Abu Dhabi, I was just like, oh, God, there's
so much money there.
And sure enough, I found an article in the Arabian Post headline, Abu Dhabi tops global
wealth rankings with one point seven trillion in assets.
OK, so that's why all those these companies are going there, because there is so much
money.
I don't know, though, because I heard Eiger and Damar saying that Abu Dhabi is the crossroads
of the world.
So I thought that was why, because it's crossroads of world.
Well, yeah, I mean, who are you going to believe?
Eiger, you're lying eyes, you know, I think it's almost one of the funniest aspects to
me is that it's straight to that, that it was just like straight to the big dogs.
There they are. They are there out there hustling us, selling us on this.
That had to be Abu Dhabi dream.
That had definitely had to be part of it, I think, because it does feel like something
that like, well, we even talk about how it wasn't so much publicity surrounding like
Tokyo, like Disney, see, like it wasn't like my family didn't know about that.
They didn't know Tokyo, Disney, see, existed or whatever.
I don't know that there was a big I obviously the Internet didn't exist.
But it's harder to say we were I mean, when it was planted, we were like 14.
So it's true. Yeah, but no, I know.
In my mind, it was like it was just there.
Like I say, it was one it was one link I saw on like on my sage.
Oh, there's a whole new park there. Right.
So it felt obviously it's different because of the Internet.
But like this definitely felt like a big flashy rollout for this thing.
Yeah. Well, it was a great photo shoot.
It's Mickey and Minnie giving big hugs to the people from from the morale.
That's it. Right. Right.
Well, yeah, that's how I was saying it.
I'm not sure that's wrong.
I think so.
I yeah, that's that's another one of my I always love.
You really know you're being sold something when a name is said.
You've never heard before. Yeah.
Disney to partner with Miral.
We love our partners at Miral.
Mickey is the most excited to give hugs to his new pals from Miral.
What's Miral?
So don't start saying that like I know what that is.
Why Mickey is here with his friends from DuPont Chemicals, DuPont,
just any entity, any company.
It's like, why? Yeah.
Mickey is here with the creator of the Remington rifle.
Tell me who I got a hug.
Just tell me, point me in the direction of the hug I have to give it.
I'll do it.
We have to get out of your questions.
Mickey and Minnie and me and Minnie are not married.
We're in kind of like a no, no kind of relationship,
which is illegal in this country.
So we got to get out of here before they kill us.
The rules are different for me.
I'm a star. It's allowed for me, right?
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, and so so it prompts you.
You just have to start asking the questions immediately.
OK, well, what is what is Miral?
And they are the people who have
are they are the people who have developed all of the theme park
entities that have been forming in the specific part of UAE
and the specific part of Abu Dhabi
that we that we now know and love as Yass Island. Yes.
Pronunciation wise, I've looked it up and seen.
Yes, I've seen.
I've seen more of a Z like Yass.
That's what I saw Iger do.
I'm going to follow his lead. Yeah.
If I get it wrong, it's Iger's fault.
And what has he ever done wrong? Never. Nothing.
Has anybody gone wrong following Bob Iger?
But anyway, I'm going to try.
I'm going to go with the Oz Island.
But whereas this is like, I think here and there,
maybe we have brought up the Warner Brothers Park there.
It's come up in fits and starts.
But now with this, we absolutely have to pay attention to Yass Island.
This becomes the addition of Disney to this area.
Now it is one of the like primary
burgeoning theme park zones in the world.
Yeah, for sure.
I maybe this is this is we should talk about this later.
But I this is I do get the feeling with the Universal and now this news
that we are maybe like on the precipice of like crazy,
rapid expansion worldwide as well. Yeah. Of everything.
Because especially in the last so many years,
as the movie business collapses and the TV business consolidates,
whatever you want to call it.
I feel like these companies are just like, these make a lot of money.
And yeah, if there are people or if governments are willing to pay,
we are willing to build and Universal, obviously,
is out front with more of it right now.
But are we not going to be able to get away with talking about new developments
that have shown up within a 25 mile radius where we live?
Are we going to have to travel across the world?
No, don't worry.
They're not going to build anything in domestic parks.
They'll just keep kicking that football down the line.
I know. I know. That's how it feels.
I mean, this whole thing feels kind of like a big middle finger
to the domestic parks.
Like, OK, well, you know, we got a new parade where we're which it's
it's now called light of dreams.
Celebrate a wish, not wishes of light.
Dream a celebration.
So you excited for that for 2026?
OK, anyway, entire new.
We are officially spending $10 billion in Abu Dhabi.
I wish that they would make it like they would by government
mandate in America, make it so that the parks were its own business.
Find independence of the studio, because that's like it just doesn't
even though they are building stuff in the domestic parks,
it's just never going to ever be the priority
when it's just like it's already making a ton of money.
They can put a little money into it to keep it like fresh.
But they're never there's no incentive to put like all these
likely cool things are about to put into this park in America.
Why, that sounds like breaking up a monopoly, Michael, that
never happened.
They're only now getting around to Google punishment for that.
It's just, you know, it's just divorcing it from the possibility of like
a bunch of movies bombing, although they've been on a roll.
They've been on a pretty decent roll, I think, Disney lately.
So maybe I'm damning the domestic parks
to a worse fate, if I say this.
Well, and they they said in the announcements for this.
And again, I'm taking them at their word.
They did say because they did like Iger did some sit downs
with CNBC and CNN and other places on the day.
And they reiterated the massive investment
in domestic parks that is, sure, supposedly coming and perhaps
already in progress. Some a little bit.
Avengers is being built.
Yeah. So that's that's right. Yes.
And they are the animal kingdom.
Yes. Yes. Some of the things they've said.
Avengers or new Avengers or Thunderbolts, Asterix.
I'm confused.
I think I think regular Avengers. Oh, OK.
Yeah, I wasn't sure.
I wasn't sure it was Thunderbolts, Asterix.
Do you not like that? Hold on.
Is that a question? No, I thought that was funny.
I actually did.
You're putting a lot of spin on that ball.
It made me feel like you didn't like that.
Oh, no, I was making fun of it because it's a little silly,
but it's the kind of silly I like.
Oh, OK. I just couldn't tell.
I'll jump in and say I don't like it.
That's fine. I knew the answer to that question.
I knew the answer already. They're driving me crazy.
You know, tough to slip out and see movies and stuff.
I still got a new little one.
And like it's the mockery of that when that asterisk
pulls up to me at an intersection, when a big bus rolls up
and right in my window is the big asterisk, like, what is it?
When am I going to know?
Now, was I annoyed that the real part of New Avengers
was that Spider-Man Wolverine joined the Avengers
and Sentry was kind of like a leader thing.
But I'll take it because it's more Sentry focused. OK.
OK, so that's more of a nuanced opinion.
Yeah, that's my opinion of comic books for about 20 years ago
that we all care about.
My opinion is, I don't know what Sentry is.
Sentry. He's Sentry.
That was helpful. OK.
Oh, yeah. He's kind of like a godlike Superman character.
They all just like copy the same character and they just put
a different name on it and a slightly different personality.
To me, for years, it's just been like, so what's his?
Oh, he can like make light shoot out of his hands. OK.
He can stop the other.
He can stop the bad light that's shooting into the sky. OK.
Most powers are they can shoot light and they're like kind of hot.
That's mostly the powers of all the superheroes.
They're all kind of hot.
They can shoot stuff out of their.
God, if you get into the movies, probably just see sinners or friendship.
That will probably be the most rewarding thing for you.
Oh, yes. Friendship.
I'm going to try to make it a friendship. Yeah.
Anyway, where did where to start with this?
I mean, one, I think one important thing to say
is that due to this partnership with Miral, what made the why Miral?
What made them partner with Miral?
Is it that Miral is paying for 100 percent of this project?
Yeah, paying 100 percent operating the park.
But then I believe still paying a licensing fee for the park. Yeah.
So it is very similar to the Tokyo
Oriental Land Company right arrangement,
which should get that.
You start getting excited about that because that leads
to some of the best parks in the world. Blank check. Yeah. Yes. Yeah.
But then you get start you stop being as excited
when you do any googling of UAE in any social issue of any kind.
It's not it's not ideal. No, it's not ideal.
No. Yeah.
Put it mildly.
It's definitely some Trump to who gives a shit.
It's like that's what I was wondering, too.
Is it no rule? No rules.
Like, do they like delay the announcement a year?
And they're like, I'm not sure it's going to happen.
If Trump is back, we can do this. No problem.
They were on a plane, whatever the day was, November 6th, the day after.
They were like, are we getting on the plane?
Are we going to Abu Dhabi? Possible. Yeah. And let's go.
Yeah. Daddy tomorrow had his formal bomber jacket.
Steamed and everything. Ready to go.
I would like to do a big I told you so about daddy tomorrow.
I this this announcement and these photos are exactly why I have been
needling this issue for a long time, because I swear to God, it's like
pandemic is kind of, you know, sort of winding down.
Not really. They are at least enough to open the parks.
And I just start seeing all these posts are like this guy.
I saw him. I was I was there on morning one and I I saw him.
And he was wearing he was wearing a mask with Buzz Lightyear on it.
And I thought he's he's one of us.
He's me. I am him.
And to have one of us running the parks and not just go to the parks.
I mean, this guy is and then cut to him,
shit eating grin with the morale people like. Yeah.
All right. Excited to do some work in the capital of no homosexuality.
Like I'm like, OK, this is. Yep.
You know, you're no executive is your friend.
This is the point. Yeah. Yeah. At the end of the day.
Besides, obviously, Michael Eisner would sit with no qualifies.
Yeah, he would have.
He would have navigated everything perfectly.
So but other than that, yes, I hear. Yes.
You would have got he would have gotten this done
and made them go change all their laws so that they're better now.
It is. Well, that's true. Yes.
Well, that yeah, that would have been fine.
If he could have worked that out, he would.
He's a master negotiator.
So likely he could have.
Yeah, I mean, it's really like it's just the world is is money.
The world is just money.
And that's what it is.
I mean, I think Carly pointed out, like, well, this is kind of
this seems like against the company's values.
Now, I am more cynical. Yeah.
I say, well, they have done something against their values,
like against the things that like the the product stands for.
Because if you think about it enough of when I say enough,
I mean, like 20 seconds, the the
the heads of this country are essentially the empire
or the bad guys in all the Disney stuff.
So like, what what are they putting in this part?
It is. Well, that's a good question.
But I was just going to tell your point.
It is interesting because there's people in the company
because it's such a crazy big company.
There are people in the company that do care a lot about this.
You know that we have seen people make the movies and whatever.
Usually it's not executives.
But like it is interesting where it's like you feel like some of the Disneyland
changes are like they're so worried about making sure they change things.
And sometimes I think it's a little bit of an overthink.
Jessica Rabbit can't wear a dress and any Disney anymore.
I'm like, it's a little bit over the top.
That was a preview of the device. Well, right.
This is right.
Most of those changes are made in good faith to try to whatever,
to to make things more inclusive or not make them whatever.
But yes, there's certain people, there's pockets of the company
that are concerned about things like that.
And then ultimately, the company is like any other company
that just consume consume at all costs.
It's got a dead sweet executives that they got to deal with.
Let's hear from the guys themselves.
They had just been announced and then they went on CNBC
and our two favorite daddies said some really cool stuff.
Why Abu Dhabi? Why now?
Money?
Well, first of all, let's start with the region and we'll focus on Abu Dhabi.
This, in many respects, is the UAE is the crossroads of the world.
About 500 million people that are income qualified,
meaning they can afford to visit one of our parks, live within a four hour
plane trip here.
And about 120 million people will actually come through Dubai.
That's the mess. That's the main.
OK, I'm sorry.
I wrote down income.
That's like the most dystopian thing I've ever heard.
Income qualified.
Yep, yep, yep.
Yeah, no, that's yeah.
He really should have gotten some more flowery language for that answer.
That was very dry and like robotic,
like people who have
strong enough imaginations.
Yeah, have big enough hearts like we like.
There's so many folks around here that haven't experienced the Disney magic.
And now that it's closer,
they'll be able to come and they'll be able to ride on the back of a rainbow
right into the new magic kingdom.
Like you'd be like, well, at least that sounds fun.
At least that's a more fun way to put it.
This is the first episode I think we've done in eight years
where I spent a lot of time on Human Rights Watch
unintentionally.
But the I mean, really, we all should have been doing that
when we were talking about David Copperfield's island.
Oh, well, that's true.
No island.
But Human Rights Watch says
you UAE based migrant workers
who form 88 percent of the UAE population.
So that means less than 20 percent are just like regular citizens.
And I guess I read something like this.
Yeah, go ahead. A lot of those regular.
I can't prove that he read it, too.
Anyway, go on. Huh?
I can't prove that he also read it.
Anyway, go on. I want to prove I was smart.
But like so that means like less than 20 percent of the population is like
not the workers who toil at the like slave labor wages and such.
Uh, but there's a lot of very rich people in the UAE.
Sure. Yeah. That's what he's talking about.
I feel like. Yes. Yeah.
You've been reporting this like this is big news several times in the episode.
Now, again, get buckle up.
There is money there.
But I think that's so 80 percent is like saying, yeah, migrant workers.
And that's also like an insane process where they lure people there.
The visa costs and the travel costs cost so much.
And then they put the cost to pay that off on the workers
and they pay them practically nothing.
So then they just get caught in an endless cycle.
Those sorts of travel costs should really be shouldered by the companies,
not the people.
Well, we haven't seen their plan yet.
Well, yeah.
Will they come on and tell us?
I I read a Guardian article when they were building like
because there's a Louvre and a Guggenheim on another Louvre.
Really? Yeah.
Louvre, too. Wow. I didn't know that.
Oh, and Sadiyat Island, which is a different
Abu Dhabi island that translates to Happiness Island.
Oh, you mentioned happy.
Yes. Yeah.
So and I think there was supposed to be an NYU campus.
I don't know if that ever got NYU.
This is they're just they're gathering,
gathering a ton of crazy stuff.
I look, they call American college, love
sending riot cops against college students in America.
So I can only imagine what they would do to them on Sadiyat Island.
I don't know. I don't want to talk about it.
What other miserable articles did you read, Jason?
I read a lot.
Well, I this is why, see, you get like, you know,
the the non mainstream media gets in your head
and they mess you up with all of these thoughts.
I let me present how my news sources,
how this was presented to me by the real media, by the true media.
Look how ABC presented the news the morning.
Who owns that?
Stop right now, because we have a brand
new announcement from our parent company, Disney.
New world is being revealed.
And it's an Abu Dhabi where Rebecca Jarvis is for us.
Whatever you whatever you're doing, stop right now.
Stop it now.
Get away from your children.
If you're trying to take them to school,
cease that, that doesn't matter anymore.
Our parent company has an announcement.
Yeah. You have to say it's for legal reasons. Yeah.
But they seem like they seem prouder than one other.
You know, yeah, sometimes you're reading like an article.
It's critical or something.
And then in parentheses, it's like we should say this is our parent company.
Right, right, right.
This is what you watch. Good morning, America.
They they love it. They were they embrace it.
George Stephanopoulos is smiling huge.
He loves the parent company. Right, right.
There's a lot of speaking of smiles, actually smiles
leads me into my next little section because I know how everyone is
being so open arms in this room, because if we listen to the parent company,
they are telling us that this is actually a time to smile here.
Oh, OK, good.
So this is the rendering we have.
I'm smiling because I'm smiling.
It's pretty much that's him showing the my smile program is activated.
I'm smiling because it makes me smile.
And that's weird in its in its own way. Right.
But then several minutes later into the same piece,
now we meet the guy in charge of morale.
What does he have to say?
Tell me a little about your company and what you aim to do with Disney.
Our company is based on creating smiles.
We're here to create happiness.
And this is what this is all about.
What I truly love.
Everyone got together.
Smiles the smile like what's what is something?
There's going to be some weird reaction to this news.
What's something you're going to argue against a smile?
See a baby smile.
That makes you happy, doesn't it?
That's the language I guess I was looking for.
Earl from the clip earlier.
It's just like, what are you doing here?
Trying to create smiles.
Yeah, that income qualifiers should be out.
Smile havers or potential smile havers or future smile havers.
You're a smile haver in the region.
Be our guest.
You know what? When people ask what I do for a living,
I don't say a podcaster, I say smile creator.
That's because that's what I'm looking to do for the listener is create a smile.
I like that. And people say content creator.
And that's so formal. That's not what it's about.
What is the goal of the content?
And it's always to make you smile, to make you smile.
I like to say, like I make people smile like that movie Smile and Smile 2.
Now I've only seen the first 10 seconds of both trailers.
So but I'm assuming those movies are all about smiles that you are thinking about
in the next Halloween season, watching 10 minutes of smile and then.
Or you hold on, hold on, just at least the trailer in the full.
Yes, baby steps.
Yeah, the entire trailer.
I don't know. I turned it off because something seemed to miss.
OK, like maybe they weren't smiling because they were smiling.
But I did like all those people smiling behind home plate at baseball games.
They were loving the good sportsmanship.
I don't know what that's referring to.
Is that in the trailer of Smile?
No, we haven't watched the first 10 seconds like you.
That was like live marketing.
When those movies came out, they would buy the tickets behind home plate
and people would be sitting there.
So the whole there, the whole game, huh?
The whole scary would have a couple.
Yeah, they will. They will be in and out in the game.
They will be behind on plate smiling.
Oh, interesting. Promoting the movie.
This is yeah, I'm seeing I'm seeing what you're talking about here.
Why would this they just they're they're creeping out.
Everybody at baseball games to get people into a movie theater.
And I think it was like the playoffs.
It was later in the season, I feel like.
If we stand up and look like Vincent D'Onofrio in Full Metal Chicken. Wow.
That is really funny.
It worked. It got a lot of coverage.
Yeah. Well, you're still promoting it three years after it happened.
It made an impression.
Twenty twenty two is the article about it. Yeah.
An impression enough to what?
Did you watch 10 seconds of both trailers or in in different years?
Or was or was it at the same time?
Was it in one sitting you watched 10 seconds?
Oh, I just keep revisiting it because I like smiling so much.
Yeah. Well, I just, you know, I live the gimmick of smiling.
Anyway, so, yeah, it's just a bunch of smile
makers who are going to go to an island and make a bunch more smiles.
Who could have an issue with that?
Do we? Yeah.
I was going to say, do we think it'll be like you think you'll be able to?
Is it going to be very expensive, is what I'm saying, to get into this park?
Like, look, will a ticket cost like 50 times what a ticket is elsewhere?
I don't think 50.
But I think it'll be at the higher end of what they are doing is already very.
I guess like Warner Brothers.
Warner Brothers world isn't, I don't think, too expensive.
Yes. But that's not the Walt Disney Company.
No, it is not. Yes.
They're they're always going to push things as much as they can.
Should we talk a little more about Yaz Island?
Yes. Sure. The kinds of because I think that phrase has been ringing in our heads.
I think we've you know, we've we've come across it here and there.
But that's it's yeah, it's now like a going to be such a giant,
crucial destination.
And I think it's all kind of risen up without us paying a lot of attention to it.
In 2006, there was no such place.
It did not. Right. Right.
There wasn't even the land carved out for it yet.
So that's when the development begins.
And then by 2010, they have something called Ferrari World.
Ferrari World boasts the fastest roller coaster on Earth.
Formula Ross Rosa.
It is it is one hundred and fifty miles an hour.
This is do you guys?
Is Velocicoaster probably the fastest coaster either of you either of you have been on?
For sure. For me.
Uh huh. Any any idea if you've done it and done anything faster?
I don't know if I've done anything.
Maybe start just a little faster.
Forget. I don't think it is.
I'm not sure. I could be wrong, but I yeah, I think.
What is that top out at 70?
70 is Velocicoaster.
So Formula Rosa is
twice more than twice as fast as the fastest ride anyone in this room has been on.
Yeah, I would do it. I would do it.
I think. I mean, I would do it.
Oh, man, I'd love to do it in that honey.
One hundred and twenty degree heat.
Yes, we have no choice. Yeah.
But you'd be going so fast.
I wonder is like the hot air even does it cool going that fast on your face?
Like in the wet, like out of a car window.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah. So fast.
Well, here's what what I read is it require it requires.
I guess this isn't a heat thing, but they do require passengers to wear goggles
because Abu Dhabi is subject to heavy sand and dust.
Oh, yeah. I was going to ask about the sand storms. Yeah.
They might still be running it in a dust.
If you're going to go all the way there, you still want to go on it. Sure.
Oh, man, when you're riding in a Ferrari car and you put your big goggles
on, it's a trademark of Ferrari.
You bring goggles. Yeah, of course.
I feel like you would like that because that feels like a turn of the century
thing. You're driving goggles. Oh, yeah.
It's kind of a throwback. Yeah.
Or burns. Mm hmm. Yes, exactly.
I know that's that also got me curious.
What is the fastest ride I've ever been on?
And I get and let me here's here's how to
I was surprised by the number here.
Do you know the fastest ride at Walt Disney World?
Do you know Walt is all the parks? Yeah.
You know what? I believe at least all the domestic Disney parks.
Do we know the answer to this?
Is it and you're counting just roller coasters, not like how fast
the Tower of Terror shoots up or something?
No, no. Yeah. Forward motion.
Is it guardians? The new guardian? It is not a guardian.
Is it a credit coaster? It is not a credit. Oh, OK.
Yeah. The answer is a little surprising.
I'm obviously I can rock a roller coaster. No.
Weird, right?
Can you even contract?
It is still test track.
The speed run of test track at 65 miles an hour.
It's funny. OK.
That's kind of surprising to me. Yeah.
And also and I.
Radiator Springs does not have an equivalent part that goes nearly that fast.
So test tracks still the fastest ride, at least in domestic Disney parks.
I think Disney parks and universal parks
always seem to put an emphasis on like the theming and such.
Yeah. Whereas Cedar Fair, Six Flags, those are always bragging about.
It changes every year.
But it's like this is a fast roller coaster in America.
This is the tallest coaster.
And then immediately gets topped by another project.
I think Cedar Point has it right now in America.
I couldn't tell you the name, but on the list I saw,
because I looked at a list and the list also had an asterisk on it
because Formula Rosa is going to get
dethroned by another ride
that's also going to it's like the not only the it's like the fastest
and the tallest, it's everything.
It's something called Falcon's Flight.
And this is in Saudi Arabia.
This is Six Flags, Kidia.
Oh, yeah. Which is an entire other fake place.
This is an entertainment city
that is being invented from an even bigger, faker place
that costs even more money.
Is that 70 billion dollar development?
Yeah. Does that start with a Q?
Yes. Yeah. I think it's Kidia. OK.
Do you know about Neom, the city that the tax city?
No. That's being built inside.
It's another like non thing.
Like, it's a thing that they're like, oh, in 20 years, this is going to be
there was all there's already been influencers.
They were like, we've moved into the dormitory apartments here in Neom.
It's so great.
And the cafeterias are wonderful.
And it's like, oh, that's a.
That's an op.
Like, that's that's a plant.
That's a that's not a real person.
You know, you mean the influencer, an influencer.
But you're saying that they've created the influencer to sway
like a public opinion or you're saying you're saying
it's not a familiar influencer to you.
It just it's it's like it's kind of bullshit.
If somebody's yelling at me at the beginning of a video
that I'm trying to watch with the biggest captions
that could possibly be on the screen, then I immediately trust them
and I take their advice on everything.
Oh, and I hope those captions get every fourth or fifth word wrong.
They often, yes, of course.
Yeah, the ones I trust the most get even more than that.
Right. You're lucky if you're you're lucky if half are correct.
I hope they're auto generated and I hope they never check them.
You know, it's all about it's all about that five second.
It's all about how much can you fit into the five seconds
because you're competing against people clicking away.
So but you can't like, hey, I just want to tell you about something
you can't the speed can't you can't forego the loudness.
You in being really fast, you also have to be the loudest man who has ever lived.
Yeah, that helps. Yeah.
It's a it's a difficult art.
I wouldn't even begin to put my my foot in that game.
Yeah, frankly, I'm just not loud enough.
No, I like the ones where like it's an ad.
And then you you realize like, oh, this person's insane
because they're talking about Satan being hitting it,
hidden in posters or degeneracy.
Sometimes if you wait, that's what happens.
That's what that well, someone reposted like a crazy person
going like Mr. Peace Logos.
They have the colors of the transgender flag.
They're trying to indoctrinate.
Yeah. And I'm like, oh, good.
Everyone's Alex Jones, Alex Jones now.
This is awesome.
And those ads end up just on everything.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
Oh, boy. Yeah, I'm on the Yas Island website.
Did you go on the website? I think I did.
Yeah. And there's a lot of way.
Maybe I didn't. I was on the morale website.
I want to know where all's been up to.
No, but they have like a like a tourist website
and they do have a list of all the things.
And it is like I didn't realize there was so much,
I guess, really, I'm getting at here.
Yeah, it's already bonkers. Yeah.
So much going on there.
And we've talked about the Warner Brothers world for a while.
Anytime you look at a video of Warner Brothers world,
it seems like there's nobody inside.
I don't know if that's true or not.
I don't have attendance figures, but it definitely seems empty.
So I'm wondering if they're like, we need a big thing.
And this is like why they put together an offer Disney couldn't refuse.
Is Warner Brothers world and its perennial emptiness
a visual representation of every streamer
and every movie that is watched by 70 billion eyeballs on every streamer?
It's possible. Yes, possible.
But they have Sea World there.
There is a Sea World there.
And I watched somebody somebody's video from there that was raving about it.
They loved the Sea World.
Apparently, it is like levels of theming way beyond
any Sea World that has ever existed, entirely indoors.
It is this like no orcas.
What's that? No orcas.
That's well, and that's the path to the future.
They can't orcas cannot be the future for them.
So and very few rides.
And yet this person was raving and raving.
I didn't check out everything that the raves were about.
But I know there was a show where you like when you're
again, who needs orcas when you can sit in like a stadium kind of crowd
and then watch drones that are fake
dolphins and turtles flying through the sky. Yeah.
That move in perfect patterns of swimming.
Like you're looking at sky turtles. Right. Right.
I mean, that's pretty undeniable.
I'd like to see some sky turtles.
Yeah. The Disney is Abu Dhabi is going to be incredible.
There's going to be the craziest technology you've ever seen.
But it's a check.
But but I'm worried about the technology.
Yes. Now, let me put the word Disney next to it.
Now, are you concerned?
Well, not as I mean, I just think that the money is going to be such
that there's a bunch of like concepts that like were deemed too expensive
for anything domestic.
So maybe they get like they get the good versions.
That's what I'm guessing. Yeah, maybe.
I mean, I'm just I'm just going off of the Disney situation where
they open a better Pooh Bear ride and that the Pooh Bear right here
is going to be insane.
You're going to get in the honey and it's going to be like your inner actual honey.
It's going to be sticky in there.
But then you're going to be clean when you come off.
You're not going to know how it happened. Wow.
There's going to be so much.
There's going to be weird VR honey sticky technology micro drones.
They're going to use hard light technology, hard light like that
shot out of the hands of all the superhero characters.
Scott goes like, what if that's right?
Yeah. Yeah. Uh huh.
Yeah. The real hard hand lights.
Yeah, that's very exciting.
Well, I got concerned, though, because then the guy,
the chairman of Moral and also the head of the Abu Dhabi
Department of Culture and Tourism, Mohamed Khalifa Al Mubarak,
just talked a lot about gamification.
And that's where I got concerned.
That's gamification and Disney.
No, no, no. Well, that man, has this worked out lately?
No, that's that's a problem worldwide, industry wide,
with the gamification, gamification, augmented reality.
Throw me in the dustbin, please.
That's that's a frown maker, not a smile.
Build some robots.
All we want is animatronics.
Yes. Yeah, I don't know.
That's the thing that we had in plenty in the 60s and 70s.
Yes. The things that we the things that we had no shortage of
when LBJ was president.
This is what we want now.
And yes, they've applied modern technology to them now.
And they're like, wow, guests are really responding to these.
Like, yeah, no shit.
Like what would be really funny, I think, is if they built some like
if they built a new Everest there
and then they made the Yeti even bigger and he worked, he would obviously work.
So like if they were do it, like to take the things that people have,
like as far as gripes of the domestic parks and then like fix them, make them better
and then only have it working there.
Yeah, that would be really like a slap in the face to the parks fans domestically.
Scott, I'm glad you said there are no orcas there because I'm like,
I don't even know if sea light can survive those temperatures.
I don't even know if metal can survive those temperatures.
We're talking about that roller coaster.
There's some sea life in there.
Yeah. Yeah.
So you got and what's crazy is all these places are right next to each other.
They're all kind of jammed together.
Ferrari World, Sea World, Warner Brothers and then some other.
That's that's not all. There's all kinds of things you've got.
You know, why kick your feet up at any one of our spacious
Yass Plaza hotels, which are different than the Yass Island hotels.
Right. Rent a boat at Yass Marina.
Catch some sun at Yass Beach.
Challenge yourself to hit a hole in one at Yass Links.
Shopping and dining are plentiful at Yass Mall.
And to get to all of these places, just climb aboard Yass Express.
Well, did you know there's a Yass annual pass, too?
For everything, for everything, for all things.
Unlock a year of unlimited fun with your Yass annual pass and enjoy year run
access to four record breaking theme parks.
Ferrari World, Yass Water World, Warner Brothers World and Sea World.
I didn't even say Yass Water World.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah.
So it's the only water park where the water evaporates immediately.
So, yes, it's dry.
The pools are dry.
It's mostly sand there in the morning.
Yeah. Yeah.
The fact that there is an annual pass that ties all this together
because it is all morale.
Do we end up with something that feels very un-Disney,
which is get a big pass for a bunch of shit.
And Disney is one of the things.
Well, they had that SoCal pass.
Wasn't there like a universal SoCal Disney pass
where you could kind of get both parks for a while?
Yeah, there was like a Southern California tour.
It's like you're coming to Southern California to do all the tourism stuff.
So they have partnered with PO.
They have done things like that.
So, huh, the version of it.
But doesn't it? And that speaks to me to kind of the bigger weirdness,
which is like is Disney Abu Dhabi or whatever ends up being called,
because it may not be the name.
Is it like leagues better than these other things
and it blows them out of the water?
Or is it just one of like because if it's just like
and it's about as good as SeaWorld Abu Dhabi, then that's weird, right?
If it's just kind of like one, like is there a kind of a cheapening
effect, potentially, if this is not truly Disney Sea next level?
I think it's going to be.
I think it has to be. But I could be wrong.
I think you got that.
I think you got pixie dust in your brain again.
Don't you think it's possible that it's just like a bunch of screens
that look good in promo videos?
And then you get there and none of it works.
And it's all very unpleasant.
It's possible.
I this is I've made up my own headcanon that like they're like, look,
this isn't doing quite as well, this whole area.
We need like a big, big draw and let's pony up.
Let's put the money up to make the craziest Disney park.
That's the number one.
They're going to do some crazy stuff and then we'll get fly
all the influencers in and they'll show out how crazy this is.
And this will bring a lot of tourism to the area.
You think that the same influencers
and the same smile makers out there would rave and rave
about whatever they put there?
Like, why does it need from their end?
Why does it need to be the best park they've ever done?
Well, I I think that there is a like, I think a lot of people
and I'm not saying that people didn't have a good time at the Starcruiser
because I think they did.
But most people I saw online liked it.
Most people said it was good.
But I don't know in the videos if it was conveyed to your average person.
Obviously, that was expensive to do it, too.
I don't know that there was an extra level of like the influencer says it's good.
And I can see in the video that I need to do this thing.
So I do think there is an incentive to not only have a bunch of people
say this is good, but also be like, here's the crazy thing
that you can see in here.
Here's the crazy point of like ride video.
And you can see you can't do anything like this in America.
That's my logic.
This is I would agree with you if it were universal
who's been making good on these kinds of things.
That's true. Disney have been big old Laurel wrestlers lately.
Yeah, but I think they could put up anything and people would be raving.
I think you're also miscalculating these people who can attend,
who are, quote unquote, income qualified.
It wouldn't matter to them.
It would be nothing to them to just fly to America or fly to Japan
to like visit the real Disney. Sure.
I mean, I guess the like people that are like billionaires
aren't necessarily going to be watching theme park vloggers.
But I do think that they're getting a crack.
I'm sure the money is insane. Yeah.
And I'm sure that the reason they're paying up
for Disney is to get a elevated level of quality.
I'm sure that's why.
Because like it's, you know, we've heard that this Warner Brothers world is good,
but you don't like nothing we've ever seen has been like
absolutely mind blowing from a video.
Right. Oh, and it's hard to tell if that Batman ride.
I mean, the Batman ride looks OK, might be good,
but it's still kind of even hard to tell.
I just think that they're going to have to have some things in here
that are so crazy looking that it drives
the type of tourism they're looking for here.
Now, maybe I'm being a little naive and thinking thinking that people
won't just come because it's Disney and it's what Disney Park.
But I don't know.
I think I think the money involved in here
is is making me believe that they are going to do some like crazy stuff.
That's that's my guess. Maybe that's naive.
I don't know. Yeah, but no one's cheaper than really rich people.
You know, sure.
But then they wouldn't pay for Disney. Huh?
And they wouldn't have paid for Disney is what I'm saying.
Yeah, but I think they're paying.
Disney's doing it for the free money and they're doing it for like,
though, we said the reputation with sports washing theme park washing,
whatever washing.
Well, let's get a guess here.
What are you are you expecting for like early
California adventure level of like OK-ness?
No, no, but I'm I'm expecting Shanghai.
Exactly. Well, which seems good.
But well, scenically, it's not Tokyo Disney as far as the layout of that place.
But certainly is some crazy big technological leaps and rides.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That pirate looks incredible. Yeah. Yeah.
I bet it's I I bet it's like that.
But more of that couple Shanghai Pirates.
I don't know if it's enough to draw people with a hostile climate.
Everything that like relationships between men and women
that aren't marriage are pretty much banned.
Women are second class citizens.
Homosexuality is outlawed.
Like that's so much stuff.
Let alone this is another thing from Human Rights Watch.
The UAE deploys some of the most advanced surveillance technologies
to erasively monitor public spaces, internet activity,
even individuals, phones and computers.
The authorities block and censor content that they perceive to be critical
of the UAE's rulers, government policies and any topic.
Shit, our UAE listeners are not even going to get this episode.
Oh, no. It's not going to be.
Well, how powerful is the Patreon paywall?
Maybe like that sounds pretty powerful, but maybe they haven't.
The Patreon paywall is it is probably more secure than what was its signal
that the Trump people were using to do war plans.
Signal is actually a pretty secure messaging website,
so at least they weren't using like WhatsApp.
They want to if they want to go, if they want to trade military secrets
in the comments of our second gate episodes, be my guest.
That's totally fine.
As long as you pay us the five dollars.
Yeah, I'm inspired by Disney's money grubbing.
If that's a secure place, just text emojis of planes and boats to each other.
Try to code it a little bit for your own purposes.
Yeah. Besides that, I don't know.
It'll be a fight. It'll break up the bug main comment.
Make sure to use that comment that that combo.
That's like the emoji fist American flag fire, because that is cool.
That's a that's a bad ass run of emojis.
I don't know what the the goals necessarily are.
What it looks what success looks like.
I mean, it's it's interesting because it's just you're trying to figure out
just as a consumer, as a person that's ethical, like what are the rules here?
What are you supposed to do?
But like you look at this island and it's like
Bill Burr is performing in Yaz Island and Trevor Noah is performing there.
So is that true?
Yes, it's true.
Every major act has been right.
It's not as if there has been some like wide.
We read and not go.
No, the list is.
By the way, I'm not dismissing the human rights situation.
I'm just saying as a person who's just trying to navigate the world
and navigate, you know, the companies that you pay attention to.
You're like, well, what are the rules?
What do we do?
It's hard to know what to do because you're like,
nobody knows that Jennifer Lopez is just playing concerts here.
Like, what is right?
What is so I honestly, I just don't know.
I don't know anything, really.
Well, I think you you said the other day when we were talking about it, like,
I think your phrase was like international waters.
Like Bill Burr and Trevor, they get like international.
They can say whatever they want.
They can do whatever they want because they're rich in fame.
You mean in there or in general when they're no, not
I've heard them on podcasts.
I think they say whatever they want here to have big balls.
Look, comedians are greatest truth tellers.
And we take that very seriously.
I pointed out when you were gone is that that's something you say all the time.
That is. Yeah.
Oh, I'm making fun of us and our peers.
I do.
No, we're not.
I don't know.
Our truth telling boasts.
No, but I think like, yeah, they don't.
They don't really get for like, yes, Island, they get
you know, a little more wiggle room.
Sure. But I know that's the draw.
There is just money.
They're not going to like say a couple extra jokes about Trump or something.
I don't. I think.
I mean, from what I've I was doing a little bit of research.
And I think there's people who are there, I think, not just for the money, but to
I just I saw this docu series about a guy who's trying to add
a whole lot of hearts to every adventure that he has on Yass Island.
And that is I'm talking about Kevin Hart.
Yes. If you guys if anyone anyone's been concerned about this place
or about visiting Abu Dhabi, I think all of your fears might melt away
if you watch the original series that Kevin Hart did for visit Abu Dhabi's
YouTube channel. Oh, my gosh.
Kevin Hart, as we know, is a he's very choosy in his projects
and in his endorsements.
And I know that's a face that's not going to appear next to just anything.
So when I saw that he went to Abu Dhabi
and that he was going to put his stick his neck out there
and become the world's first chief island officer.
Oh, well, figure out how to heartify everything about Yass Island.
I knew that I could finally trust this place. Sure. Yeah.
And I there's one that we haven't mentioned of all of the cool stuff
on Yass Island.
You can go to CLIMB, which is spelled CLYMB.
That is the it's the biggest wall in the world.
And he went he went to he did all of these things.
In this video, I'm going to show it's 52 seconds long.
He was the first chief island officer.
He hardifies it. He brings a little heart to everything he does.
And he takes it to a whole new Kevill.
Oh, Kevill. You think have a whole new Kevill. Wow.
So just if anybody's been worried about any of this,
I think this video will shut down everybody's fears.
That's a title card about how he's heartifying
CLIMB Abu Dhabi, because it looks good already.
But what couldn't be better with a little bit of heartification?
Yes, Abu Dhabi hired me to elevate every moment on the island.
But here's the thing. We don't do moments on Yass.
No, no, we do momentous.
Check out what your chief island officer just want to make sure that landed.
They don't do moments there.
And we've said a lot of stuff about this place,
but I want to be very clear. They don't do moments there.
They do momentous.
Have you guys look me in the eye and tell me you understood what he just said?
I yeah. Well, I can't look you in the eye.
Why are you looking at me in the eye?
They do momentous there. Kevin Hart told me so.
He's the chief island officer.
I glance at your eyes for a second.
Takes it to another Kevill.
Yeah, I know that Jason's with me. He understands.
He could draw me a map, a graph that shows me how Kevill's work.
I just double check.
Did you say they have the world's tallest wall wall?
I think it said that somewhere.
That's a phrase. That's a phrase.
Building literally build. OK, that's not right.
We'll build it.
They must mean world's largest climbing climate.
Yeah, I would guess because the Burj Khalifa is in the sea.
Yeah, if you if you consider those walls, I think they mean a wall within walls.
They mean a wall inside walls.
That's what they're saying.
I mean, look, he's he's swole, but he's jacked.
We know he's jacked.
He's tiny, but he's jacked.
He's a rock's best friend.
But he's not going higher than Tommy Cruise.
You know, I'm not sure that he even went on it at all.
But I don't think you have to be on climb to take climb to a whole new Kevill.
OK, good.
Look behind me.
That is crime. Abu Dhabi today in that building is the tallest wall in the world.
And I'm renaming that way.
That is where I got it from. Wow.
Well, Kevin Hart, it's the tallest wall in the world.
Oh, in that building, which is made of walls, is the tallest wall in the world.
Wow. That's interesting.
That's a real mind blow that something could be the tallest wall
and also be surrounded by walls that by the definition of walls
have to be taller than it to fit it in the walls. Right.
Scott, I wasn't doubting that you would hurt, but I was like,
I know someone said the world's tallest wall.
I was starting to doubt.
I was like, did I write something down that was wrong?
And now I've learned.
OK, no, we've established it.
It was established that it was not my mistake.
It wasn't Kevin's mistake.
It was no one's mistake.
It's the biggest wall in the universe thing I ever pondered before.
How many views on that?
That says a a completely real one point six million views.
Wow. That is OK.
That's I was I was thinking it'd be like five thousand.
This is this is a hit series.
It put that those numbers put it at the number thirty nine.
As far as Kevin Hart episodic series
produced in the last two years goes.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
Mount Kevin Manjaro.
That's something else he's doing.
He is taking things to a whole new Kevil and declaring that climb
is now Mount Kevin Manjaro. Wow. OK.
There's so I've only played half.
That's only in 30 seconds.
How many phrases did we learn?
How much information did we learn?
This is an exceed this blows Anthony Bourdain out of the water.
You know, I think Disney has already got a leg up on this
because just talking about this place, I am starting to experience
unreality ish and the world's biggest wall
in Mount Kevin Manjaro is not helping.
They already if what are they going to do?
They're going to build a new big thunder.
Is that going to beat Mount Kevin Manjaro?
I don't think so.
And then at the end, they tell you that you can book a vacation
that's hard to beat.
Wow. They've I think every frame of this has a new phrase.
Is something in the other like sort of Kevin Hart commercial verse
he uses or in like his is that or is that like a yeah,
has that been like a long time?
Like if yeah, I don't know.
I faintly recall that Kevin Hart at one point did stand up comedy
and maybe in that, you know, before he was like an investment broker.
But now, like so in that maybe Kevil was like a running
quote within. I don't know.
Confusingly, he had a special called Kevin Hart presents
the next level, not the next Kevil.
So, OK, not sure. Not sure.
All I know is there is a shot of him that is the same shot
in all 10 episodes of Chief Island Officer, the series that it's all done
in front of the same hotel wall and every in every one of them.
He is committed. He has fresh energy.
They definitely don't start with the energy of him being told, OK,
we got nine more of these to go.
So come on, let's make it.
Yeah, let's keep going.
Yes, I know that we hired me to.
So anyway, I reckon I recommend the whole series later.
I mean, if that one wasn't enough, there's another one where he
actually joins the Justice League.
He declares that he's going to change the face of funhaving as we know it.
Well, I'm interested in that.
Yeah, I love that.
That's what he's trying to do, too.
That's all everybody's trying to do is change the face of funhaving.
He also you guys appreciate this because you're comics guys.
He is he's naming, you're right, Superman and Wonder Woman.
Then he tries to come up with his own name and it's a heart dude.
And then he's like, he's still working on the name.
OK, so he's not sold on it.
No, but that's what he but he's he's brainstorming again.
When he was once a standup comedian.
So he changed the face of funhaving
and the rock changed the balance of power in the DC universe.
Here's the reason these guys are so good.
There is, yes, there's something only they get.
They are gods amongst men.
Yeah, yeah. And only only by taking things to a new kebel
can they get experience, any joy.
They've already done everything this world has to offer. Right.
Jason Momoa also did some time as the chief island officer.
Sure. A whole other series of wonders in himself.
Moa Moa was sitting down that road, too, nowadays.
I think, yeah, they better make some room in the car on their road trips
for for any item and any film.
Can I go back to Eiger or is there more Kevin business?
You want to know that's fine.
If after all that, if you want to talk about it, a chief executive officer,
it might seem like a letdown having talked about a chief island officer.
But that's that's fine and fair.
OK, the one thing in the promotional because like on the Disney parks blog,
they they kind of sum up what's coming.
And there's like a three minute video, which is mostly clips
from movies and a lot of marketing gibberish.
But I could not get past Eiger saying this park is going to be authentically
Disney, distinctly Emirati. Yeah.
Because that is just what they said for Shanghai.
This park will be authentically Disney, distinctly Chinese.
We were that is by that a long time ago.
That is so shitty to not come up with a new marketing phrase.
That's so condescending.
And there's also no video.
I think I know why.
There is no video of Eiger speaking Arabic or Mandarin,
probably because there's a lot of hate crime,
racist psychos in America who just loop it nonstop.
I yeah, that is that is very funny.
Authentically, authentically Disney, distinctly Emirati is exactly
the same phrase as I did the last time.
There was an account. I don't know.
I mean, I follow all these different universal accounts.
And I there's one account that's like was tracking the jet,
like the Disney jet, because you can track private jets online.
And they attract like they were like, oh, you can see that the jet was in
like Abu Dhabi a lot.
So like, obviously, that's what they were doing.
But then they've also pointed out the jet was in like Texas a lot lately.
They're like, oh, we know that was that.
Oh, that no, that's just where Tesla is in Texas.
Oh, yeah, there's a lot of it.
I mean, a lot of things are in Texas.
There were there. Yeah, there could be other reasons.
There's I would say one million other reasons to go to Texas.
Texas, I just knew it as a home of Tesla and the boring company.
And oh, well, and the comedy mothership, if that's what you're getting at.
Oh, well, the smile left and right.
Somebody was speculating.
Oh, I mean, because Universal, obviously, is doing is Texas.
Yeah, perhaps Disney.
So like, could they say, like, you know, this this new Disney
Texas park, hypothetically, would be distinctly Texan to distinctly
Texas by your cowboy hat.
Yeah. Cowboy hat is definitely there.
Boots cowboy boots.
Maybe Abbott presents him.
Yeah. Cowboy boots.
Sure. Yeah, I think so.
But I was just trying to imagine that you're going to use this phrase a lot.
And a regulation big piece of straw to stick. Yes.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. So they'll be measured like the length that they like it.
Right. Right. Mm hmm.
So it's like 11.5 to 13.5 inches.
The right length of big straw. Yeah.
I wouldn't be so I wouldn't be shocked if this phrase gets dusted off a lot in the future.
I don't know if it's going to be like crazy, like Universal expansion, but we'll see.
I don't know. Yeah.
I think these companies, especially Disney, is like these companies
cannot just make the money they make.
They need to make more and they need to build more.
So but that's also that's a phrase that could apply to everyone.
All companies always. Absolutely.
I'm just saying it's they're they're part of it.
So like I wouldn't be shocked if if Disney, Texas or something is on the table.
Other companies, other countries are on the table.
Texas, Brazil, I think, you know, the was discussed.
Oh, I feel like for a long time in the past, because, you know,
there's so many Brazilian tour groups that come to Florida.
It's like, what if we build it in Brazil?
Mm hmm. I want to look.
What do I mean? Do I want Disney Schomburg?
Yes. Disney Schomburg, Illinois.
The build next to Woodfield Mall, a full Disney park.
And I want it to be distinctly Schomburgian.
I want it to be. Well, how do you make something distinctly Schomburg?
Oh, the pizza is really big pizza, Culver's burgers in the park.
Um, the sausage, Italian sausage,
Italian bears, the Mike Ditka ride, probably.
Or might you haul up like a great moments with Mr.
Lincoln, but it's Mike Ditka.
Oh, which would be pretty good.
I think about it. I'm just kind of meandering.
It's like, yeah, I'm doing any interview with him. Right.
Disney can just have the white socks.
They're like a thread usually.
Yeah. Yeah. So throw them in with the deal.
I mean, yeah, generally speaking, that's in Chicago proper, but not.
But you can't but you count Ditka for you as opposed to Chicago.
Well, no, I mean, I'm just trying to think of something
that would at least make it this. Yeah, I guess you're right.
It should be more of a local Schomburg hero.
So it should be.
Who's the most famous guy from Schomburg? Is it me? Is it?
I feel like I need to look that up.
Do you think it's do you think it's even pod?
Do you think you're in the top 10?
Do you count Robert Downey Jr.'s
producer wife, who went to Schomburg High School?
As being famous, I guess she is.
She's probably married to one of the most famous men on Earth.
So I guess she's been photographed more than you.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, sorry. Yeah, yeah.
So she's above me.
Let's see a couple of actors who are probably more popular.
Notable people.
Hmm. Somebody somebody named
Shane Madej from Buzzfeed.
Madej. Yeah, I know Shane.
Let's see. Yeah, there were Susan Downey's in the list.
Kurt Kittner from The Bears and the Falcons.
I don't know. There's not 10 names in this list.
How many? Maybe you're in the 10.
I could be in the 10. Yeah, I'm number 10.
That's that's fun.
You know, the idea that I would be the top in the top.
Says you're right under the Green River killer.
What?
Pete, Pete Wentz is not from Schomburg, but he's from around there.
This is a weak list. I think I think you're.
Yeah, I think you're good.
I think I'm in the top 10 most famous Schomburgians of all time.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah. Well, you got to be right.
Well, somebody had Mike, I guess.
Yeah. You need the Wikipedia to begin with. Right.
Do you think podcast The Ride is enough?
Or do you like if you were going to like because I feel like some of these people
have two things in the list. Right.
You know, performer, professional Call of Duty player and the CEO of 100 Thieves.
What is your 100 Thieves?
It's a great question. Yeah.
Mansors format, one episode of Mansors.
Mike has Mike has had to bury his answers.
That's right. I know you're not going to ever see that again.
Mansors or just the the mighty
Akron, the work I've done for the mighty Akron.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Atticus, maybe.
Coiner of the term mighty Akron. Right.
So that's pretty good.
So I think that'll be I really haven't been invited back to the high school.
I don't know if they do that with high school.
So you get invited back to college.
Mike, you should be.
Disney should commission you to make some phrases
they should commit like what?
Well, you came up with mighty Akron.
Oh, right. Right. In that way.
It seems like mostly they make phrases nowadays.
They are phrase makers.
Stinkly like smile makers, phrase makers.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
Yeah. Is there some way to
tout Disney Abu Dhabi in an elevated way?
Yeah, I don't know.
How do you how do you phrase it?
How do you sell what you're imagining,
which is the craziest park they've ever done?
I say, check it out.
I say, hey, get a load of this.
I say, hey, whoa, look at that.
What if you combine a few of those?
Check out a load of this.
Nobody's ever thought to combine them.
It sounds a little weird.
Yeah. But you do that all the time.
You do. Yeah.
Once you say a compliment to a ride that's very sexual.
Yeah. But when somebody else says that, I don't care for it.
When it comes out of my mouth, it's good.
So if you had just said, check out a load of this, you would have liked it.
If I had said, check out a load of this, it sounds good.
Now that I said it out loud, it sounds good.
You just had to reset it, pretend you didn't hear it from me.
It says it in, yeah, when I say it in my own voice.
Well, then I'll just be the ghostwriter of the phrase,
check out a load of this.
That won't be on my Woodland Hills, California, Notable People section.
Yeah. I'll cede it to you because I'm that kind of a man.
I'm taking it to the next Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, yeah.
Carl, Carl.
Check out a load of this.
Taking it to the next Michael.
And I'll be a Wall Street raider,
so I'll just wait for check out a load of this to really drop.
And then I'll scoop it up.
Check out a load of this.
It's going to drop and scoop it up after it does.
Oh, no.
Hey, you said it.
I just I just love the phrase.
It sounds better when I say it out loud.
Yeah, it sounds better when I say it out loud.
Most most things do.
All right. Well, check out a load of this.
You survived podcast.
They're right.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to take things to the next kevel,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
And now I think we just plan, you know,
what it's our reading material and what are our snacks for many,
many flights to Abu Dhabi and remember, let's put a smile on that face.