FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning! The following podcast may contain
sordid tales of the Disney surveillance state,
the saying of names of original Simpsons writers,
and long-dead puppeteers,
plus barely-sourced speculation about the future of the Simpsons in theme parks.
Alan Siegel, author of A New Simpsons Book,
joins us to talk about a bunch of Simpsons stuff
in a perfectly-cromulant Simpsons episode on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, which like the Simpsons,
has characters who are yellow,
which in our case means cowardly.
I'm Scott Gardiner, joined by Mike Carlson.
It means cowardly, it also means maybe we had too much Taco Bell Caliente sauce,
because the sauce itself was made from an artificial yellow dye.
That is always a danger, yes, that you consume so much of that,
despite its prior effects on you, that you end up the color of the sauce.
Jason Sheridan, who struggled with said sauce.
Yeah, I was worried you were going to say we were jaundiced,
and I was like, no, jaundice is one of the health battles I've not faced.
You are not currently, yes, yes, well congrats, there's always time.
There's always, oh yeah.
Yes, we're happy to not particularly resemble the Simpsons,
but we are happy also to talk about the Simpsons,
and to revisit the world of the Simpsons in Springfield,
and the intersection of the Simpsons in theme parks.
We talked about the Simpsons ride with the Talking Simpsons gentlemen,
but today we're going to dive a little deeper.
We're going to talk about stuff that's beyond the ride,
the Springfield areas and Universal Studios,
and the theme parks they visited in the show,
and what we'll be losing, I was going to say if,
but I'd say when the Simpsons disappear from Universal Parks,
it's certainly seeming that way.
More, it's tipping towards when.
A grab bag of Simpsons stuff, and this comes to us courtesy our great guest today,
who's an excellent writer, who has a book that is available for pre-order right now
called Stupid TV, Be More Funny,
How the Golden Era of the Simpsons Changed Television in America Forever.
It's Alan Siegel, hello.
Hi guys, thanks for having me.
Absolutely.
Thank you for coming, thank you for making us aware of your book,
for sending us copies of the book, which we've been diving into already.
I think you had all of us at Golden Era of the Simpsons.
That's a starting point that we love.
But yeah, I mean, congrats to you,
and I'm excited to check it out and spread awareness of it here.
Thank you, I just got back from Orlando,
it was the first time I'd been there since 2001,
and there were a lot fewer Dick Tracy products there than I remembered
from the early 90s of my first trip,
and also Jessica Rabbit had a lot, you know,
there was no presence of her, there was no giant Jessica Rabbit sign
like there was in 1991.
That's right, Pleasure Island.
Yeah, there were still the lingering little,
it really did loom large, I guess.
Like so many props around, because it's what they had just done,
and they had to like populate that studio's park with something,
so it was all that.
Couldn't they leave Jessica up and put her in like a big coat, you know,
at Disney Springs?
Like they did on the ride, you're saying,
because there was an old neon sign,
and you're saying just amend it with a second neon sign.
Give her the big coat and put it back up.
Like put it under the, you know, Morimoto restaurant, you know.
Yeah.
You know, it's like, hey, it's like a weird, it's a funky thing.
It would fit somewhere at Disney Springs.
Right, that's what I'm saying.
And it nods to the history.
How was your trip in general?
This was a thing with niece's nephews?
Yeah, so it was my dad who's a retired engineer,
he planned this whole thing.
We took my seven and nine-year-old nieces to Epcot,
Animal Kingdom, and Magic Kingdom,
and we did pretty much everything.
My oldest, older niece managed to do Tiana.
It took some psyching up, but,
and the photo where I look like a psychopath,
I'm sticking my tongue out,
but she is like kind of like bending her head down,
and she looks scared out of her mind,
but at the end of the ride, she was happy she did it,
so we were happy too.
That's a huge one to get over.
I was much older when I did it,
and then I completely reset for decades,
so a nine-year-old is a better time to begin.
You mentioned that, well, okay,
you mentioned a little bit of like,
when we were talking before,
there was a little bit of like,
mostly went very smooth,
but a little bit of like tension of perceived space
at the end of the day,
like in the fireworks kind of zone.
It was very funny, again, as a childless adult,
things that I don't run into too much,
but we were watching the fireworks at the end of the day
on Main Street USA,
and we staked out a good spot,
and my dad, again, amazing planner,
wanted to sort of protect our little three-by-three space.
You're implied.
If everyone spreads out a little bit,
you can't put tape on the ground,
but you can just sort of try to convey a bubble.
And a guy sort of stepped in front of him
completely innocuously,
and my dad, again, is a very sort of rule follower,
and he kind of said to the guy,
like, oh, you're right in front of us,
and the guy scoffed very loudly,
and he's like, dude, there's 10,000 people here.
We're going to be fine.
And my brother kind of tapped my dad on the shoulder
and was like, all right, let's just leave this alone.
It was perfectly fine.
I was telling Scott that they,
my parents are 75 and 72,
and they walked, you know, three straight days,
like 10 to 14-hour days.
It was really impressive, and my nieces, too, were,
again, I think they just are on such a high
from being there that they were great.
Yeah, yeah, it's sort of like the magic of that place
and all of these places where you sort of, yeah,
you go, like, beyond your bounds of kids stay up later,
kids push it harder.
Yeah, your parents, I find that, too,
I'm always astounded by the step count at the end of it.
Like, I did what?
Where if you told me at the beginning of the day
to do that in my neighborhood, I'd say, absolutely not.
I'm going to get so tired, I'm going to get so bored,
but it doesn't happen.
It's not even possible.
It doesn't feel like it's possible in real life.
It only is possible in Orlando.
Yeah.
I have more energy.
Well, it's possible if you're, I don't know,
if you run, if you're in a workout.
I'm not talking about those people.
I'm talking about normal people, regulars.
Yes, like us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm happy it was successful and that the dad situation
didn't overflow into a worse situation
because another thing you mentioned
when we were sorting out this episode,
you alluded to some amount of issues.
You said that you have a tale involving the dreaded,
the place that we all avoid trying to,
that we're all good boys to try to avoid going,
which is Disney Jail.
So the Disney Jail story is actually secondhand,
but I'm going to build it up.
It wasn't your father.
It was mine.
No, thank God.
That's what I was wondering.
So it was a story told to me by my buddy,
who I used to work with at the newspaper
I started my career at.
And he mentioned it, I think, before he went on
a different trip to Disney World.
And he told this story.
So this was 2004, approximately.
So my friend went on a spring break trip
at the end of college with 10 other guys
in their early 20s to Florida.
And it was like Daytona, Miami, and Orlando.
And there was this one kid who had no money.
So he saved up for a plane ticket and then had nothing.
Oh, jeez.
So as young men tend to do, they were like,
all right, we're going to exploit this situation.
So they started having the guy with no money do dares.
Oh, no.
And so it started with, you know,
take a shot of Tabasco, get this girl's number.
I think it was like, wink at the pilot on the plane.
So they go to Magic Kingdom one day.
And well, let me back up a little.
This guy had no money.
So all of my friend and their friends
had to pool their money to get him a ticket
so that he didn't have to stay in the parking lot
the entire day.
Oh, you got grand old time, though,
ticket and transportation center.
You know, you're watching monorails go around.
Well, you take the monorail, you go to Disney Springs.
Yeah.
No, that is a free ride.
That's true.
Well, this was clearly the juncture point.
Should have just had a fantastic day at the ticket transpo.
But instead, a foolish decision.
They had their day at Magic Kingdom.
They had a good time.
And then they boarded the ferry from Magic Kingdom
to the parking lot.
So it's like the Seven Seas Lagoon.
Am I correct on that?
Yeah.
It's a big, crazy hassle.
It's like the transportation, as we just
found when we were there, like the transportation
decisions just to get over the moat.
There's a lot to work out.
A lot of second guessing on our part.
Should we do the boat?
Should we do the monorail?
That looks full.
No, we've got to do the monorail.
Never mind.
It's a real process.
So they're on the ferry.
It's nighttime.
And someone goes to this guy.
I'm not going to say his name.
He said, hey, why don't you jump in the lake?
Oh, no.
Oh, god.
And my friend said, this is my friend's mind here.
He said, before I could tell him there are alligators
in there, all of a sudden, this guy is gone.
He jumps in the water.
Oh, god.
And my friend looks back, and he said it was nothing
but a splash in the distance.
And my friend said that he was laughing the hardest
he's ever laughed in his life until he started
seeing sirens and boats.
And all kinds of like, I'm snapping here, immediately,
like within five seconds.
Wow.
So they don't know what to do.
So the ferry lands.
They get off.
The friends are all led to like a holding room.
And my friend said it felt like, you know, five hours.
And all of a sudden, a little while later,
their friend shows up.
He's still damp.
He doesn't have his shoes or glasses.
And he, quote, had to sign his Disney life away.
Whoa.
So they told him, don't ever try to come to a park again.
Don't go to Euro Disney.
Don't go to Disney Cruise.
Nothing Disney.
So let's tell you about the Vacation Club hotels.
Now, these are full of wonderful amenities for families
to visit, but not for you.
No, you cannot live in Cotino, a story living by Disney.
Yeah, no planned communities in Palm Springs.
We'd prefer if you didn't visit a Disney store,
but there's a lot of those.
It's a lot for us to honor.
There's no ticket, so we can't really stop you.
But still don't, probably.
So from then on, they kept referring,
or they kept saying that Disney was no longer
the most magical place on Earth.
And so my friend, when I brought this up to him,
asked the offender, like, have you been back to Disney?
And he said no.
And my friend said, you should try.
Yeah.
Because how long?
Like, how do they try?
They didn't, like, scan his face in some way
that tracks how he ages.
They're screwed.
They got nothing.
Yeah, I really doubt it.
But I kind of want to see.
I want to hear if he tried.
I would love to know.
Would they flag him if he signed up for Hulu?
Like, if he signed up for Hulu or Disney Plus
or tried to order a Mickey t-shirt on the Disney store
website, would they track him down?
Are you saying that that would help?
Or would it ease the call?
Would it be like, oh, he's a subscriber?
You know what?
All that's in the past.
No, it's certainly not in the past.
I'm just wondering if it's like, like, you know,
because it's talking about Simpsons.
Like, we're out of board license plates in the gift shop.
Yeah.
Will he immediately get pounced on by, like?
I suspect he will not be applying to join the Club 33.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
He will not reach the highest echelon.
No, the Disney Pinkertons, like, dive right for him.
But Universal welcomes him with open arms.
We have a new customer, you know?
I, there's a lot.
That's all fascinating in general.
I think it's interesting that they clocked the Friends.
How did, like, were there telephoto lenses?
Were they lip reading?
Were they like, we watched that conversation.
That guy said, you should jump.
Well, like, we know that the Friends were part of it.
I feel like Disney, like, employs technology that's, like,
that was, like, ahead of the Patriot Act.
Like, I saw guys, I was going to ask you guys about this.
Like, these mostly gentlemen walking around Epcot
in tasteful polos and khaki shorts
with their trash pickers and sunglasses.
And I was like, I wonder if these are security folks
who are trying to appear, like, as friendly.
Oh, and, like, a thing that would be around
that you wouldn't question,
but then the trash pickers can be, like, you know,
like, those turn into tasers.
Yeah, exactly.
There's different levels.
Like, there's the security guards you see
with, like, wide-brimmed hats and, like, nice clothing.
And then there's, like, plain clothes.
There has been photos of, like, someone got, you know,
stopped at a metal detector for whatever reason.
And then there's a guy, like, making a report
or talking on a walkie-talkie, and he's just in shorts
and, like, a Dad is Darth Vader t-shirt.
Like, there's plain clothes guys, for sure.
Here's one that threw me of the themed t-shirts
was the first Princess Security t-shirt I saw.
I was like, oh, shit, is this, like,
is this what the security people wear?
And I'm like, no.
And I saw, like, 400 of them around, you know.
What is that shirt? Maybe I haven't seen that shirt.
I think it's, like, you know, it's, like,
Girl Dad kind of theme, you know?
It's, like, a guy, like, I'm gonna protect my daughters,
you know, that kind of thing.
Yeah, Mike knows he's a hashtag Girl Dad.
That's true, yeah, and I have that shirt.
And I saw a shirt yesterday at Disneyland
where it was just the Godfather font
and it said the Girl Father.
And I was like, I'm gonna get that too.
That's badass.
It used to be, up until three years ago
when the term Girl Dad was invented,
it was embarrassing and shameful
to be the father of a daughter.
And, you know, though billions of people
had this experience, they all hated every second of it.
And that phrase did a lot of good,
and Girl Father, that's even better.
That's the next generation.
This was a guy with a big beard.
He looked like he'd beat someone up, too.
He looked tough.
He had two girls, though.
I don't know, can a Girl Dad be tough?
I don't know.
I mean, the shirt makes me think they can.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so lame.
It's possible.
There's one more thing about that story
I have to ask you about, which is that, like,
does the timeline imply that they forced the friend
to shiver for hours, like, lay in your own filth
after what you did?
No, we will not give you towels.
We will not help you.
So here's what I don't know.
That whole, like, elapsed time
might have been 20 minutes.
Sure.
Yeah, because, like, my friends were probably,
my friend and his friends were probably terrified or,
you know, but yes, I don't think he had a change of clothes.
No way.
They did not provide, I'd like to think
that they'd made it psychological torture
and that they, like, took him to, like, a sundry shop,
to, like, a place with a lot of towels,
or just to the pool area at the Contemporary.
Like, made him look at 500 towels
and then said, you can't have it.
I think, yeah, or they found a bibbidi-bobbidi-broke T-shirt
for him that I saw in Disney World several times.
It's like these guys who think that they're being clever
and they're definitely not.
And the guy who got in the water, he didn't.
Do you know if he tried plausible deniability of,
like, I lost my balance, I fell?
You know, that's a missing detail
that I will surely pass along to you guys
because when we're done, I will ask my friends.
You will get a fill on the gaps, yeah.
The railings are kind of high on those boats,
so it might have been, like, a camera caught him,
and he kind of had to vault over,
so we couldn't pull that excuse.
All of this stuff, it does tie together very nicely
into, you know, like, the biggest intersection
between the Simpsons and theme parks,
besides, obviously, their presence in the theme parks,
but which is the Golden Era episode,
Itchy and Scratchyland.
And, like, besides, you know, it's, obviously,
we've all been big fans of that one in particular,
and we were little park fan kids.
We loved that episode.
But it only gets, like, it stays so fresh and so true
because while it, like, it gets the Disney parks details
right, like, the public-facing things,
it's just so smart with its observations
about the security state
and the underground Disney World that you don't get.
And in particular, it really, like, it does, like,
Itchy and Scratchyland feels a lot more like Disney World,
where there is, like, the hassle
and all of the transportation that we're talking about
and the feeling of, like, being stuck on the campus
with no way to contact the outside.
That, uh, the combo of Disney World and Jurassic Park
that it found is so smart and continues to be funny
over 30 years later.
Can you believe that?
Yeah, and I didn't, this is a very Simpsons thing,
which is, you know, I didn't know what Westworld was.
Oh, right, right.
You know, in the early 90s,
so that's another one that it definitely sent up.
But the, like, glut of merch
is just something I think about all the time.
I mean, and I saw it in Disney World a couple weeks ago.
The, you know, the famous joke
is the bored license plate joke, as you guys know.
And a couple years ago,
I tracked down people who had real bored vanity plates.
And let me tell you how, A, envious I was
and, B, like, the delight in their voices
when they talked about it was so good.
Like, they, one guy was like,
it's probably not that funny a story,
like, basically, like, got let off on a ticket
because he had a bored license plate.
Oh, wow.
One, you know, one guy was afraid to put it on his car
because he didn't want somebody to steal it.
And...
Oh, yeah.
I mean, those at Universal, don't those sell out?
I think I've read that in places.
Yeah, I don't know, or I feel like I've been there
and seen that they were out of bored license plates.
And I thought, is that the joke,
that they always have, like, a permanent spot?
Or was it genuinely sold out
and I was watching the joke play out
in a meta way in our actual world?
Well, I have a very dorky story
that somehow I don't think I've shared before.
Ah.
But when the Simpsons ride
opened at Universal Hollywood
in 2008, I was working across the street
in office space rented by Vivid Entertainment,
the pornography company,
but they were making, like, Tabitha's salon takeover
in the rented space.
And I...
So you were not in the space being a performer.
No, no. And you...
Just a wishful performer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just hoping, like,
drop them headshots once in a while,
if you need me.
People would have to go up to the top floor,
the actual Vivid office,
to get, like, keys and key cards.
And I don't think I ever got up there,
but apparently there was a lot of billowing drapes
at the top, like, cartoonish decoration.
Anyway...
Just layers of hundreds of layers of drapes before you.
The show wrapped,
and then they let everyone go early,
and I was like, oh, my God,
the Simpsons ride opened yesterday or today.
So I drove up to Universal,
and I rode it,
and I immediately went in the gift shop
and started looking for bought license plates.
And then I went back a few weeks later,
and still they had nothing both times.
Wow.
So I ended up buying, like, a name keychain,
but the name was blank.
And I, with a Sharpie, wrote BORT on it.
And I carried that around for years,
long enough that eventually the gift shop
did start selling BORT keychains
and, like, license plate pins and stuff.
Wow. You had to take matters into your own hands.
What did you use to write?
A Sharpie.
A Sharpie, okay.
Look, I didn't have a lot going on at 22, you know?
I'd entertain myself somehow.
Yeah, wow.
He had the entire six minutes
to write the name on the license plate.
And then carry it close to my heart
until it eventually just got scratched off.
Oh, wow.
Not literally close to you.
It wasn't to, like, fend off bullets.
No, I don't tend to keep my house keys
on my upper chest area.
On your upper chest.
Yeah, yeah.
You could be smart if anybody's after you.
What a funny thing, though, that it isn't, like...
Yeah, it's in the world of the...
I was meditating on that joke on BORT license plates,
which in the context...
Well, it's BART looking for a BART license plate,
and they have every possible name surrounding BART
except for his own and including BORT,
and immediately a real BORT walks up,
and then later there's an emergency
that is the shortage of BORT license plates.
I think Barclay is an underrated step
of this joke sequence as well, for sure.
Oh, and don't forget the one beat
where the mom is calling for BORT,
and a stranger goes, are you talking to me?
She says, no, my son is also named BORT.
And it's really funny.
It's kind of just like a stray...
I mean, I love the episode for that reason,
that there's a lot going on in the episode.
There's a lot of story,
and there's a lot of themes to touch on,
but then they will still just stop down
and do kind of a free joke
that is not so attached to anything,
because it's not really...
I mean, is there a greater point about theme parks to it,
or is it just like...
It's almost just one thing
that makes the day more unpleasant for BART.
There might be people that probably have that experience
with their name that's a little more unusual.
Yeah, or being in a...
Somebody thinking, my name is a fairly common name.
How am I in this alternate universe
where you have this and you have this, but not mine?
Right.
Well, I know I've definitely seen people
or encounter, like, oh, they're out of Jason's today.
But even more, like, my wife is Jane with a Y,
and that's harder than with that.
Yeah, you're not gonna find that.
So that's pretty common.
You gotta get the Sharpie out for that name.
Yeah, well, I gotta get the Y.
They have different spellings of Caitlin
or other names that are escaping me at the moment.
There's always an Alan,
because every Alan besides me is, like, over 70 years old.
Well, this is the...
Like, I was gonna ask you about this, Mike,
now with children in the picture
and without revealing our kids' names.
You've been in these gift shops.
You find in your daughter's name in there.
Is it in the stand?
Never. I've never looked.
Oh, really? You haven't done this?
Wow, wow, no kidding.
I don't think...
You know what?
Maybe we looked at the Minions the other day,
but I think maybe she ran away,
and then we didn't finish the job.
Okay, sure, yeah.
It seemed like she cared.
She knows how to spell it.
She's known how to spell her name for a while.
Sure.
But she doesn't care.
Well, it'll be, like, a year or two
before, like, the seeing the name is, like, the biggest...
Yes, right.
Wow, my name printed out.
Both of my son's names are a little bit old-fashioned.
I will sometimes see my younger son's name.
Oldest never.
Really?
It has never happened.
But, like, yeah, you might think,
due to it being, like, kind of traditional,
quote-unquote, that you would run into it,
but I think they don't, just in that, like...
It's just not on the short list of, like...
They're like, come on, nobody under five
is gonna be named this.
Go ahead and guess, I guess.
It's all...
So, listener, guess what you think it might be.
Zachariah?
Come.
Ulysses?
Abraham.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They don't have your son's name,
but they have a million variations of Jaden, Kaden, Aiden.
It is, I know, if it, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If it's an Aiden, really, yeah.
A Zaden, a Zaden with an X Zaden.
Harley.
Yeah, yeah, plenty of those, yeah.
You're both kind of out of luck at the Minions shop,
because it's all just Kevin, Bob, Kevin, Bob, like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's really unfair.
Stewart.
Sticky in those lanes.
So, I have a question for you guys.
When you were first going to Disney,
like, how into the merch were you?
Because I feel like I was obsessed
and, like, pissed my parents off in 1991
to, like, fur a stuffed animal,
whereas my nieces, like, I think they got,
they each got one souvenir.
I don't know, like, the pull of that stuff is so strong.
Yeah, right.
You guys remember it.
Oh, tons and tons.
I wanted, I didn't want big stuff.
I just wanted a million little pins and flashlights and pens.
And then I just kept, I have so much, like, paper products,
maps and coasters and matchbooks, you know.
Well, those are free.
You're describing free things.
Oh, yeah.
You can grab as many of those as you get.
I, like, every time I was packing my duffel bag or suitcase,
like, to leave Disney, I would, like,
take the biggest Disney gift shop bag
and just throw everything in.
All the maps, all the pins, all the stuff.
This feels like a part of the Disney World tradition,
is that, like, needing to make, like, checking the,
making sure that the airport,
your airline's policy is, like, personal item.
And go, well, how big can that personal item be?
Because that personal item might be, like,
a full-size monorail box that I'm bringing in
with, like, you know, seven other shirts stuffed into it.
I don't know.
Yeah, big merch thoughts for yourself.
I mean, I wanted everything, yeah.
And I was, the stuff that looms largest
is getting, like, the goofy stuffed animal
one of my first trips.
And then I was just always obsessed
with getting one of the Disney characters,
generally one of the big five or six,
a plastic head of theirs
that was full of tart and tiny candy.
And I have a goofy one, I think, still somewhere.
And then I think I have a Mickey one as well.
And that, I was obsessed with it.
The amount of tart and tiny's you would get in this big head.
And that, like, that, for whatever reason,
is, like, those are the two exciting,
the most exciting things.
Of your entire childhood.
Of my life, my entire life.
Is that where the tart and tiny fixation came from?
That's where I got my tart and tiny fetish.
Yeah, well, because we've been at,
there's a candy store in Burbank,
up the block from the movie theater.
And Mike once got in a fairly long conversation
with a clerk about tart and tiny's.
Well, because I was, I learned online
that tart and tiny's were back.
Like, out of commission for a while.
I don't think, I think somehow in all these years,
I haven't heard tart and tiny's specifically.
Really?
Tart and tiny's.
Yeah, they're these little things.
They eventually had candy coated tart and tiny's,
which I still liked as well.
But I didn't like them in their original,
I didn't like those as much as the original.
Can I say this?
They look like crayons.
Crayons?
Yeah, so what I'm looking at,
yeah, they look like crayon stumps to me.
Probably taste like it too.
That's what I'm wondering.
I mean, they must not, if they were so.
They do not taste like crayons.
Were they a little?
Well, that's good.
Were they chalky?
They're chalky, yeah, like sweet tarts in a way.
Yeah, so another company picked up the lucrative IP
of tart and tiny's a couple years ago.
For feature films, you're saying?
For tart and tiny's the movie.
I own the rights for that.
I own the rights to the tart and tiny movie.
You were both at each other's throat trying to get
the script duties for tart and tiny.
I've heard about it a lot.
I was only in the game just trying to dethrone Mike.
I didn't care and give two shits.
That's why you ended up winning.
You had the passion.
Right, right.
It says on this tart and tiny's website,
pucker up, we're back.
Which is gonna be the tagline of the movie.
So yeah, no, I got very excited tart and tiny's were back.
I went to the candy store in Burbank,
and I think I said something about tart and tiny's
or asked or they had them.
I forget what it is, but then the guy who owns there
was like really into the tart and tiny conversation
because I think he's owned that candy place for many years.
So he knows the news about candy.
So I really was talking his language.
Well, they also like sneak candy in a movie theater.
I feel like they don't care now,
but that candy shop will give you a discount
if you show a movie to them.
Yes, now I believe we have mentioned that on the website.
This is absolutely the time or more that has been said
on the show.
That is my favorite.
The only downside post pandemic
is they don't let you scoop anymore.
Where everything's like kind of pre wrapped.
They don't let you scoop in this particular,
but you can still go to the American.
They don't let you just put your hand in it,
walk into a movie theater.
As long as you can hide it in your fist,
no one will notice.
Because you want a lot of chocolate covered pretzels,
but you might only want one or two gummy sharks.
Scott, you know what this is like.
It's really, they're pretty sizable.
Do you have candy predilections in this?
That's not the right word.
That's a creepy word.
How about candies you like?
I like any kind of Reese's or in my Boston accent,
I call it Reese's or any kind of Reese's peanut butter stuff.
I like Sour Patch Kids and Sour Watermelons.
Those are my.
Nothing wrong with those.
That's my predilection.
Sure.
Well, thanks for using the word.
I'm going to do a talk show transition now.
I'm going to do Byron Allen transition now.
In your book, which once again is called Stupid TV,
Be More Funny,
is a great Simpsons reference.
This isn't as clean as Byron yet.
Hold on.
There is one of the first licensees of Simpsons products
is Butterfinger.
And that relationship, God, is it still going?
There still should have been a speaking of candy in there.
You needed one more thing to make it.
What do you mean?
The transition wasn't until the end of the thing.
Well, I got very excited.
Also, the Byron Allen transition is so.
You like Butterfingers?
That's the Byron Allen transition.
I see you wrote about Butterfingers in your book.
I just wanted to shout out his nice book.
Well, I appreciate it.
And Byron Allen.
Well, that's good, too.
The crazy thing about that license is that
Simpsons was advertising for Butterfinger
before the show started.
It's like when the shorts were on, which is insane.
It goes back to that.
I was doing research, and I thought,
I couldn't believe that it was actually true,
but that's quite dramatic for this fact.
But the New York Times was reporting it,
interviewing Matt Groening in 1988 about it.
So they had the license for a while.
It went away, and I think it came back for a while.
But it was really funny interviewing the writers
just about the gobs of Butterfingers
they would get in the office.
I mean, okay, you guys have all been there.
They would put them in a gumball machine
when it was those Butterfinger BBs,
those little balls.
And they would pour water in it,
and then it would get moldy,
and they would throw it at the ceiling.
I mean, these are very mature guys,
but I remember John Vede, the writer, said that,
I'm not sure if this actually made the book,
but he said whenever they were pissed or cranky
about Fox or the show,
they would take a shot at Butterfingers.
Oh, wow, wow, that's funny.
Did the writers room, or is it still,
or what's the deal?
Because my understanding has always been
that even in the success of the show,
I think you allude to this in the book,
even in success, that they kept the writers room
kind of shitty on purpose.
Just kind of like, let's keep it just this humble,
kind of bad place,
as if to just connect to the roots,
or just like, I don't know,
there's a humbling quality to it.
Yeah, they definitely liked having it
like a dorm room for better or worse.
I mean, they would sit around,
and I think George Meyer told me this story.
There was a pool cue that they had
in the middle of the floor,
and nobody knows where it came from,
and they would compete to see who could unscrew it
and screw it back together as fast as they could,
because they would just be there for hours,
and most of them didn't have kids,
so they were there for 12 hours a day.
And yeah, it was just like a dump,
and everything, their whole day was basically based on lunch,
and that was the only thing they looked forward to.
Oh, sure, yeah, yeah,
the biggest variable in the day.
Yeah, I recall hearing like the Oakley-Weinstein era,
season seven and eight, that it would just be,
it's like, it's past midnight every day.
It's just like, they all live to be there.
Yeah, in a pre-kids time,
you can just pack it full of jokes upon jokes upon jokes.
Yeah, Oakley had a line that like,
he said that he would, I think, drive into the Fox lot,
and he would like see like a valet Parker,
and he would be like, I wish I was doing that
instead of putting the show together,
which I know, he's self-aware.
I just thought he, have you guys heard the,
I'm spoiling my material in the book,
but the famous Simpsons lunch Conan O'Brien story?
That was really funny.
I can get to that.
Maybe.
So they would have a PA every day get the lunches.
Oh, I know, yeah, yeah.
And so people would put in their orders,
and it'd be like Pavlovian,
the PA would come up the stairs,
and people's mouths would water.
So one day they hear the PA coming up the stairs,
and then all of a sudden they hear a scream,
and they hear the box just tumbling.
And so people are like, oh fuck, is he hurt?
And also our lunches, what happened to our lunches?
And they fuck.
So they go outside, and it's Conan O'Brien
with a box full of garbage
that he had just thrown down the stairs
to fuck with them.
And one of the writers was like,
it was like a devastatingly effective prank
because that's all they looked forward to.
Everyone pledged to the absolute worst.
And they would go, the other story,
Bill Oakley is saying like, yeah,
we would order so much food,
like you would just order an appetizer
and an entree and dessert,
and the anecdote that when he left the show,
he quickly dropped like 65 pounds.
Yeah, it's wild.
I mean, there are stories like they would,
this is a very LA reference,
but they would order like whole pies from Apple Pan
and just like be eating, you know, out of,
which is like a famous greasy spoon here.
So yeah.
Delicious pie.
Multiple entire pies being split.
So Jason's getting a lot more motivated
to try to get into a writer's room.
Thinking about starting this writing thing.
Yeah, the like one talking head
for documentary interview did,
I got like a free granola bar at craft services.
That was the most fancy.
Yeah, I don't think, yeah,
I think everything's pretty bare bones
most places these days.
Do you chalk up the quality of these seasons
that we all really admire?
I mean, I think especially through eight
seems to be the magic number people refer to.
Is it like the dorm quality
and just that all these brilliant people
are hanging out all hours of the day
and packing everything full of stuff?
Or was it like, was there something special
also maybe to like the lack of the feedback loop
that we're not like, you know,
getting obsessed with what the audience is saying yet,
that they're a little bit in a bubble
and they're just doing what they want to do?
I think that's a very good point in question
because so the show kind of became
at least famous among comedy writers
for like the no notes rule.
So because of James L. Brooks,
they were allowed to,
like the executives didn't have creative feedback,
but one of the writers said that it's kind of misunderstood
because he said that the, you know,
people think that the perception is
that all the notes were shit.
They were really bad, stupid,
but he said that's not really what it was.
He would get good notes sometimes,
but it was the fact that notes took time to respond to
so it was really just to not have to worry about that
in your day.
They had more time to, you know, like you said,
sit in the room and go over every single joke
over and over and over.
And I mean, again, it's a cliche,
but they sort of talk about how the best joke would win the day
and it was sort of competitive,
but not in a way that like SNL was
where the writers were sort of fighting
to get their material on the air.
Oh yeah, because it's a different thing
because you're all building the same thing.
It's not like you're not competing
for three minutes of Simpson space.
That's another, that's chilling as you say that
because of the things that I've worked on,
it is like the amount of effort that goes into
like getting this step ready so that the people
who need to approve it can take nine days to get it done.
And then as soon as we get it back,
we have to hurry, hurry, hurry to get all of their thoughts.
Like it's the wrong thing, drive it.
Wow, that's interesting that it was just like purely the,
just the time saved.
We'll make it better for us.
And then it's, and then it's all of these episodes
that we, everyone devout and that haven't aged a bit.
And 30 years later, we're still now,
we appreciate them as adults in a different way
than we did when we were kids.
It's like insane, the timelessness.
I was, I watched like three or four episodes yesterday
and I was laughing so loud.
That the police were called by your neighbor.
Yeah, normally it's just a polite chuckle
and they thought something was different.
They could tell something was different.
It screams, oh no.
But I, the sins I got reading the book
was that a lot of the original, you know,
for lack of a better term,
a lot of them were just different flavors of weirdo.
Like they were all complimentary,
but they were different, like George Meyer
and John Schwartzwell, like they were all different
in the way they approach stuff.
Yeah, and they all had weird obsessions.
I mean, it's sort of what you're saying.
Like the, John Vede, who's another really good writer,
I was sort of asking him,
because you know, the lore of the show
is that it's Harvard Lampoon guys, which it is.
And I was like, well, what made the Lampoon
like a good breeding ground
beyond just a bunch of smart nerds?
And he said it's like,
it would be the best place to procrastinate on campus
because instead of studying,
they'd watch like a Brady Bunch episode 12 times in a row.
And like dissect every aspect of it
and what made it good, what made it funny, what made it,
and you know, that also caused like a,
or created like a meta sense of humor for those guys.
Like they love things like both ironically
and earnestly somehow, which is pretty impressive.
Yeah, the give and take is like one of the things
that seems to make those golden era Simpsons really work,
you know, and appreciating it on different levels.
Like when I was a kid, I was just amazed by it all.
Like, and I spent a lot of time at the Jersey Shore
growing up in every souvenir shop, knickknack shop,
half of it became The Simpsons at some point.
That's funny because there was a writer, Jeff Martin,
who maybe I've mentioned before,
but so he had a Disneyland annual pass
in, you know, late 80s, early 90s,
and he had a small, I don't know if it was a newborn,
but he had a kid, and he would push the kid around Disneyland
and he said in 1990 there were more Bart Simpson T-shirts
than Mickey.
Yeah.
At Disneyland.
I'm sorry, at Disneyland.
Yeah, well.
It makes sense, like they sold, I keep repeating this,
but they sold 15 million Simpson shirts
in the first year of the show alone, which is insane.
Which is like, if you go to a vintage store or flea market,
you'll see them on sale for like 50 bucks, 70 bucks.
They are so expensive, like original Simpson
or like Black Bart Simpson especially.
Very expensive.
The bootleg shirts.
Yeah, there are, there's Black Bart.
I mean, there are two, there are like inappropriate,
I mean, not, you know, inappropriate ones.
There are like anti-desert storm,
or rather, no, I take the pack, pro-desert storm.
What's the ayatollah ass hola is like a Simpson joke
that seems like, oh yeah, your shit
was getting modded and bootlegged.
Yeah, like it was, there's one I saw for like over a hundred bucks
at the Silver Lake flea market.
It was like Bart hitting a bong.
And I was like, I should have bought that, but I didn't.
There's no way to make that now.
There would be no way to recreate it.
I was, I'm trying to find ones that I can read.
I mean, here's one called Ram Bart,
and it's Bart, very strangely drawn,
Bart kicking Saddam Hussein in the butt.
And then another one, Warren the Golf, 1991.
I was there, dude, and it sucked.
I don't think I knew about this particular slice
of insane bootleg shirt.
Wow.
It was the voice we needed in the Desert Storm discussion.
His name is escaping me, but there was an attorney
who was sort of famous for helping Disney secure the land
for Disneyland, for Disney World,
who was involved in like trying to police these things for Fox.
And so there were literal stings.
I couldn't stop laughing.
I found a report, it was like, Operation Dizzy Fox,
like yielded 30,000 Simpson shirts in Washington, D.C.
Next to the Keep Off the Grass marijuana shirts.
Oh my God, what a waste of time.
But doesn't it not, didn't it in a way,
just like, well, now people are walking around,
like so many people are walking around with advertisements
for our show, even if the design is wrong.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, yeah, that's a...
Yo, Saddam, I'm Bart, and I'm pissed.
Geez, I'm starting to want one of these.
Well, you talked about in the book that the rise
of graphic tees being like such a huge thing,
and you chalk that up to like stores like The Gap
selling their logo and Hard Rock Cafe
selling souvenir shirts, but also Simpson shirts
just like taking it to the next level.
They were so ubiquitous.
Yeah, and I was, again, I found this really funny.
So the big one, like the two in the late 80s
were Ninja Turtles and the Tim Burton Batman merch were huge.
And there were articles in like early 1990,
just as the Simpsons were taking off, again,
about Disney's hoping Dick Tracy products
will be the newest hit.
And there were a ton of them.
They were ready.
It worked on me.
Same, I have a photo of me with,
there was a charity event in my hometown near Boston.
It was like me and my brother next to Kevin McHale
of the Celtics, and I have a Dick Tracy shirt,
and I look very sad and pissed off
because we were waiting for Larry Bird and he had to go.
So we only got the second Hall of Famer on the team.
Kevin McHale.
Wow, wow.
That's, wow, but Dick Tracy.
Yeah, that really, yeah, they were ready for it.
They were like, well, all right,
we have watched this phenomenon happen of the Bat logo
and we are ready for it to come to us.
Here it is.
And it wasn't a failure by any of me,
but it's just as fast as time goes on.
Yeah, you don't put that, it's not the big four.
No, I don't.
I don't, it's also funny, like Disney executives
watching these dailies with kind of sleepy Warren Beatty
as Dick Tracy and going, I don't know if this is it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have to imagine.
So it's like they had the plan
without even stopping and thinking
about what the movie would be.
Yeah.
All right, now let's see.
What's that?
It's like this big, exciting action,
and then he's kind of mumbling.
You're like, is this the same thing
as Michael Keaton and Jack Nichols?
I don't know.
This all where the marketing for these,
the old comic strip, 90s movie adaptations,
worked hook, line, and sinker on me,
because I loved Dick Tracy.
It was like second movie I ever saw in theaters.
I had the shadow toys.
I went to 7-Eleven to get the Phantom,
the ring with the skull on it
that Billy Zane punches people with.
They had Phantoms at 7-Eleven?
I remember the ring being available.
Wow.
Did I have the ring too?
The ring was available a lot of places,
and I'm sure they sold it purple.
And you saw shadow in the theater?
No.
No, I never saw it.
But you had the merch.
I just had the toys.
I just thought it was cool.
What about The Rocketeer?
Oh, I love The Rocketeer.
Yeah, that would fit along.
Yeah.
You were a 40s boy when you were five.
I was a 40s boy.
A big part of that, besides Disney, MGM Studios,
was Simpsons reference.
I would pick up stuff from The Simpsons,
and sometimes I would just like the parodies
and the jokes,
and then sometimes I would hunt down
what that was a reference to.
Sure, sure.
Sure.
That actually brings up something
that I found really fascinating,
because you guys have all worked in comedy,
and you're trying to reference
a lot of different stuff.
It's like they were trying to reference
the works of Diane Arbus
and the movie Sorcerer in 1992.
Oh, yeah, way to Mr. Plow, right?
That's one I didn't understand
until a couple years ago.
I didn't get that until I saw that
at Los Feliz III a couple years ago.
I was like, oh my God,
it's not a cliffhanger reference?
Yeah, I always thought it was a cliffhanger.
Yeah, absolutely.
Kind of a hard movie to track down,
even until a few years ago.
They would send PAs to the Warner Brothers archive
to get stills of whatever movie,
and it's insane to think about
in terms of time spent.
Yeah, yeah, it's crazy now
that everything is at our disposal.
Similarly, I just remember hearing
about how for the Saturday TV Fun House,
for Robert Smigel to do a parody
of the Harlem Globetrotters cartoon from the 70s,
you had to sneak a camera
into the museum of TV and radio.
In fact, that was how committed you had to be,
and now you could tell AI to do his stuff,
which is not better.
The love that Smigel had going,
it's very evident in that piece,
how hard he had to work to get it right.
That's what we're going to have to do
to find that King Koopa's Cool Cartoon episode
that's in an archive at UCLA,
because we were given a tip
that there is a full episode in there.
Oh, I forgot that.
We're going to sneak a camera in
or something and record it.
This is lost media, kind of.
This is a Saturday morning show.
Nintendo licensed.
This is insane.
I, of course, did a story
on the Super Mario Brothers Super Show.
Oh, okay.
I guess I remember watching,
was the intro of the Koopa show available on YouTube?
Yes, there's clips of it.
He's leading a bunch of rowdy kids down this,
and it's very like,
ah, gong, gong, gong, gong, gong.
Yeah.
It's so janky, even jankier
than the wraparounds for Super Show.
It was just a bozo show hosted by an angry man
playing King Koopa from Mario.
It's starting to come back.
I think all told, there were six minutes that existed,
and it's all starting.
We have a second gate on this on the Patreon,
but then I guess I'll give the big reveal away at the end
that we don't believe necessarily.
Do you remember this?
That we don't believe.
Wait, I don't know.
Well, we were skeptical of the claim,
is that Michael Eisner got it canceled.
Oh, right, right.
Oh, I forgot that.
He's the one who got it pulled off the air
by calling someone and saying he didn't like it.
Yeah.
It seems odd.
Why would he care about a local...
It was on a local affiliate that they owned,
or that they didn't own.
I don't know that they owned it.
He just thought it was bad.
Yeah.
That's where it was a weird,
yeah, there wasn't a lot of detail in there.
This is the most name-dropping I'll ever be,
but I interviewed Michael Eisner once about...
Oh, Jason, make a noise.
This is the place to drop that name.
...about BoJack Horseman.
Oh, okay.
He was a...
And Raphael Bob-Wicksburg, the creator,
had a funny line to me that he's like...
It took him a little while to realize that Michael Eisner is just a guy.
He has this image of...
I don't want to hear that.
Yeah, I know.
Not us.
I think he called BoJack maybe the best show he's ever worked on,
which is pretty crazy considering all the things he's...
I mean, better than the show he was on,
The Magical World of Disney,
where he gave the greatest performances ever given by any performer,
with no offense to BoJack.
He has to say that.
He has to say it.
It's his current project.
I didn't ask him about soaring, even though I wanted to.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, I figured it out.
That was a little bit of journalism I did,
that it is, in fact, not him.
Did you see somebody posted on our Reddit,
Quartzide at the Clippers game, game four?
Oh.
Did you see this?
Yes, with...
Eiger and Eisner together, sitting Quartzide.
Proof of life.
We haven't really...
He's getting up there.
He's in his 80s.
We haven't been sure.
Right.
So seeing him at an event was like...
He looks great.
This is a nice thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Some people might be excited to see Jack Nicholson show up at a game,
or at SNL 50.
We're just like, oh, he's Eisner.
He's always there.
Not lately.
No, less and less.
I think it was very...
A real rarity that he was at SNL 50.
Yeah, he's not...
Yeah.
So, Alan, here's a question.
You've gotten to talk to so many of these brilliant writers from the classic era,
and probably the drive for the book was to talk about, you know, the show.
That's pretty important is the show and the episodes of the show.
But the theme park presence of The Simpsons,
how often did this come up or do any of them give a shit at all?
So, I think it means a lot to them.
Like, Jeff Martin, the writer,
remembers going to Simpsons land at Universal when it first opened
and seeing, you know, Cletus's chicken shack.
And he just was dumbfounded because Cletus was his little league coach.
Oh, Cletus.
And he came up with that.
And, you know, I think these guys, and it's mostly guys,
have been so successful and done so well that they are not at all bitter.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I do think it's an honor to them to have this thing that just, like, lives forever.
I mean, the story that he also told me was the Dapper Dans, the...
Disney acapella.
Yeah, the acapella barbershop quartet.
He said people...he talked to those guys at one point.
I'm sure there are several groups of them,
but people will come up to them and ask to sing...
ask them to sing Baby On Board from The Simpsons episode,
Homer's barbershop quartet.
And they can't because of some copyright issue, which is really funny.
Now it probably is not a problem.
But that's the reach of the show, I think, that I was sort of delighted to learn about
and I want people to enjoy.
Well, yeah, I think you do a good job, from what I've read so far,
of, like, just highlighting that the...I think it's the...
like, of course there are, you know, subcultures within fandom of particular...of shows,
but it's almost that The Simpsons gets so granular that there's an entire world of stuff around...
yes, around that song that people like, around Steamed Hams, around Bortles,
but, like, the amount of sub sub subcultures is so insane.
Like, what other show could...like, one joke out of 500 in an episode
have such a, like, this deafening chorus of fandom about just the joke, let alone the show?
It's like a show with a thousand secret handshakes.
Like, if someone...
Oh, yeah.
The Bort license plate one is a perfect example, I think,
and I just don't think that's been replicated at all.
Well, that's...you talk in the book about not being allowed to watch The Simpsons,
and that happened to me, too, but yours was the, like...
the go...there's Princess Cashmere, the belly dancer.
Mine, I went yesterday, I found the episode, and it's in Lisa the Greek,
and it's not even the gambling stuff, because there's a big...
They kind of predicted, you know, they couldn't have had any idea
how much sports gambling is a thing now.
Oh, without having to call a guy on the phone.
Without having...
You're Barton.
You're opening an ESPN bets app, which still makes me laugh,
because Disney owns that, too, but they don't want any gambling anywhere near Disney parks.
But when I was...
Would you rather? Do you want gambling in the Disney parks?
I love slot machines.
But he wants a penny slot so he can spend about $10.
And he goes, ah, damn, I'm down 49 cents!
Cleanest!
Son of a bitch!
I almost had nine cleanesses to trigger the bonus.
Do you want them in the parks? Do you want the slot machines?
I've said that I believe slot machines will be in Disney parks in the next 25 years.
That was my prediction, I think, on the show.
Yeah, yeah, I believe that. Yeah, yeah.
But what got me not allowed to watch The Simpsons in Lease of the Greek,
Bart is melting an army man, a toy soldier, with a magnifying glass,
and he says, I'll see you in Hell, soldier boy.
And my family was watching that, and my mom just turned that right off.
Just in that mere profanity.
And that was about first grade, and then come seventh grade,
everyone's talking about The Simpsons, because it's on every weekday.
Like, the best ones are on syndication at that point.
And I'm like, Mom, I'm old enough to watch The Simpsons,
and I'll be a social pariah if I don't watch The Simpsons.
And that's what I remember from seventh grade,
is watching Simpsons trading comic books and doing plays.
And punching villains with your phantom ring.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and getting that phantom ring.
Take that, see?
I think one thing that's funny to me is,
I don't think people now realize how edgy that show was considered.
Oh, yeah.
Which is hilarious, like, it's on postage stamps now,
and it's this institution.
And now, I mean, back then, you know,
the president of the United States was calling it out on the campaign stump,
like, multiple times, so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, more like The Waltons, less like The Simpsons.
Exactly, yes.
That it was even, I feel like, you know,
Beavis and Butthead probably kind of, like, you know, took the heat.
Took it up a notch.
Not long after. Yeah, yeah.
And then, like, crazy Jackass, whatever, really crazy.
Yeah, but it is strange.
Oh, yeah, it is, like, a big distance from,
that it's a thing that people bring their families to in theme parks
when there was a time where both of you, me to some extent,
I think I had the thing of, like, I think they thought,
my parents thought, as good Catholics,
maybe we shouldn't let them watch The Simpsons,
maybe we should watch it, too, so.
Which is, what a beautiful thing, what a great, like,
that it was, like, they couldn't deny it, even.
Yeah, my parents, like, gave in very fast.
I think it took a couple of months, and they were like,
all right, this is okay.
And, you know, it's been a part of my family since then, so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I, it's been nice for me to be exposing my oldest son to it.
We watch it, and God knows, there's five,
you know, it's just going over his head,
but it's really, like, just watching, like,
just basic stuff, kind of, just, like, I don't know,
the look of a, he just got really fixated on Sideshow Bob,
and it really helped him with some ride bravery,
because he was avoiding anything that's even,
like, was a remotely rocky ride,
anything where the lights go down,
anything that's, like, 2% a ride.
He was becoming his dad in that way.
But being able to tell him, this is a ride about Sideshow Bob,
it's not even just a Simpsons ride,
he would ask for those episodes specifically all the time,
and it really helped him get, like, you know,
the lure of you get to see Sideshow Bob on this thing.
That's funny.
And then it led to a nice thing,
and just, like, in terms of these, like,
these little subcultures and odd, you know,
mini Simpsons experiences,
something I, like, I never clocked it
until he got interested in Sideshow Bob,
but I didn't realize how many people in Universal Studios
would be in the Sideshow Bob wigs.
You go down the starway,
and you're passing by a few at least,
and I'd never thought of that as some kind of new mouse ears
or anything, and it isn't,
but you see more than you think.
I think because it is a prize in a carnival game,
and with a lot of cheating for this five-year-old,
who can't exactly pick up a big heavy mallet,
we did attain a Sideshow Bob wig for him,
and he wears it in the house,
and he has so much fun with it.
Here's maybe the point that I'm driving to,
is that, all right, we know that the Simpsons days
are numbered at Universal Studios,
and you think, okay, well, this happens all the time.
You take a ride out, and you put a new ride in,
but the footprint is gonna be so much bigger than,
like, something like that, that, like, wow, you look around,
and there are a lot of these wigs,
or there's a lot of people with the Homer donuts
or people at our window, like, you know,
like, the amount of merchandise, Homer slippers, whatever.
It feels like, because it's not just the ride,
but also, like, the Springfield surrounding area,
it is gonna leave such a massive crater
that has to be filled by whatever property
it ends up being that replaces it.
You know what I mean?
It's a little bit more than just,
like, it's more of a seismic change, I think,
than just changing up the ride.
Well, it's not at this level,
but you're saying, along the lines of, like,
the amount of times you see people in, like,
wizard robes now walking around,
something like that would just disappear
if that presence wasn't there.
You know that's never gonna happen,
but it is, like, I don't know,
it's just, like, physical footprint,
amount of stores and restaurants.
They're, like, to make these change-outs
at Hollywood and Orlando
is gonna be a pretty major operation, you know?
Yeah, it's gonna be interesting to see,
because, yeah, they do have a big, like,
food infrastructure, like, situation going on.
They're both of them.
Because they're, I assume,
I assume they're gonna just replace the restaurant.
I don't think they're gonna tear everything down.
This is based on nothing,
so I guess I don't know why I'm saying it.
Okay, sure.
But, I mean, you could,
I guess you would re-theme, like,
Cletus's chicken shack to, like,
Glinda's chicken shack or something,
or what a wicked character.
What was the chicken before that?
Was it like Doc Brown's fried chicken?
Yes.
It was Doc Brown's.
Supposedly, it's the same recipe.
The same not very good recipe.
The same delicious recipe.
Well, people, it has its fans.
Oh, come on.
Like, everything.
I swear to you, I swear.
Who?
That as opposed to any other theme park fried chicken.
Well, I don't know.
I feel like my son wasn't even into the,
like, you like chicken tenders, right?
Can I not have these?
I gotta ask, does your son know the Sideshow Bob rake gag?
Yes, yes.
I thought that was the funniest thing in the world
is kids Sideshow Bob stepping on all those rakes.
No, I know.
He's imitated it.
It's wonderful to see.
And we've tried to point out that Stinky Pete in Toy Story 2
is the same voice.
Like, this is the same voice in things that you watch.
That's a heady thing for kids to understand.
They don't, like, voice actors, they can't.
They're barely, like, getting their heads around reality
in general.
Alan, let me ask you this.
Have you been up to, well, like, okay,
we already talked about the ride.
We can touch on the ride a little bit.
But have you, like, have you been up to
The Simpsons stuff at Universal?
Is there anything you especially,
anything you like up there in terms of big experiences
or just, like, that little detail is a great thing?
I like Moe's a lot.
Yeah.
Yeah, and the, like, Flaming Moe.
I mean, it's, you know, it's a little,
it's hard to translate the animated world, like,
into the real one, but I think they do,
they do a really faithful job.
And I was gonna say, I think, you know,
if and when that area closes or changes,
like, I do think they'll lose, you know,
the, I don't know, 30 to 60-year-old visitors
will be less.
Like, I don't know, like, I feel like people our age
maybe go to Universal for The Simpsons.
I'm not sure, though.
It's fun, and it's done really well.
I mean, I remember specifically taking a trip.
When Moe's was open, I remember, like,
that might have been with you, Mike.
It was.
Yeah, right, well, we gotta do,
let's get drunk at Moe's is what we'll do.
That we ran into Evan Susser coming up
and doing the same thing.
And then I think we all just stayed.
I think we were about to leave,
and I think we ran into Evan Susser,
and then we all just stayed.
Wow.
Well, to have the experience, you know,
the glamor, the fun of Moe's,
that's kind of a funny thing,
is that we would all like, yeah,
we get to be in Moe's, the saddest place,
the place where people go to get drunk.
We have a photo of it.
Where people frown at each other
and don't speak for hours.
I guess there's times where Moe's is fun.
Yeah.
You know, when Barney wins the contest
and gets the Duff Man package,
and then he can't participate in it.
But mostly, it is just a funny,
like, there's so much subversion in The Simpsons,
and a lot of it does have to go away
once you're in a theme park.
You do have to like, Moe's is just a fun water and hole,
where you can grab yourself a great couple of beers.
It's like, cheers but miserable, you know?
Yes, yeah, yeah, that is what it is.
It's tricky because it's not a place that makes,
like, it doesn't immediately lend itself
to being what a theme park needs
for something like that, where it would be like,
it needs a lot of seating,
it needs, like, to get people in and out.
Like, Moe's is a place you just kind of want to go in
and hang out, but I feel like lately,
I don't really ever do that.
I haven't done it in a while.
Yeah.
I will grab Duffs.
Sure.
Like, whatever they frame as Duffs.
I don't know if that changes in and out,
but I am always satisfied by whatever I...
It's gonna be Glinda's beer now.
Now, is this, yeah, do you believe
that this is becoming, is this a strong theory?
You know what, I don't actually think that.
I have, my guess is that it becomes, like,
some sort of, like, English city or French city,
and that leads you down to the tram loading,
which will be Hogwarts Express.
That's my theory based on a ton of rumors I've seen.
Really?
So you don't think Pokemon?
In Orlando.
Oh, okay, yeah.
That's different.
Orlando, yes, Pokemon is the rumor.
Oh, it's not the rumor here?
No.
Really?
Not enough room.
Oh, not enough room,
because there's gonna be a whole new ride system
for Pokemon that's, like, supposedly Scoop style
transformed into Spider-Man.
Oh, so does that mean that in Orlando,
the simulator ride that we know that's been back,
that building's gone?
Burned to the ground.
Or maybe they keep some facade or something,
but wow.
That's the word.
I mean, that's good, I think,
because how many more times are you gonna be able to do...
Yeah.
Re-skin it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and be, like,
it's already a little bit weird.
You're in a theme,
but you're in a Krusty the Clown carnival.
Now, go into this weird little room that shakes.
Be trapped in there and watch a free show video.
The only thing that gives me pause with that theory,
because then, like, okay,
you could make a bunch of, like, I don't know,
quick service English Harry Potter food, I guess,
in the place of Springfield,
and then demolish the ride
and put up some cool-looking buildings,
and then you go through to the, whatever,
the railroad system.
The only thing that makes me think, like,
maybe that's not it, is the fact that they just dumped
a giant Fast and Furious warehouse
right at the start of Hogsmeade.
Yeah.
So it's not like,
because in that way, you'd be like,
oh, man, then they can perfectly create
a little Harry Potter thing up there.
Yeah.
But there's a big warehouse now dumped
right when you enter Hogsmeade,
so it's not the end of the world if it's there.
That was the only thing that makes me think.
Well, you could kind of transition monsters,
like, universal monsters.
You could, but I don't know where you put the big ride.
Yeah.
Is the building not big enough?
The Simpsons building?
Not at all, no, no.
Oh, okay.
That's not big at all.
And you're going off a cliff.
Yeah.
You couldn't build past that.
You couldn't really.
Maybe, I don't know,
because they're doing stuff
with the sides of the mountains now,
so it's possible you can put a little bit all out.
Yeah.
Kind of hang it a little bit.
Yes.
Universal Hollywood has a unique problem
that many theme parks don't.
Cliffs.
There are a lot of cliffs.
You've got to deal with the cliffs and the hillside.
So I went back through my Instagram,
and I found, when they opened Springfield in Orlando,
this is me with a Duff Beer in 2014.
And that was the first time I had it.
And the thing that sticks out,
because I think the bartender took this picture,
because I was like-
You were alone.
I was not alone.
I was with family.
But I was very excited about the bottle.
And they're like,
they poured out the Duff Beer into a cup,
and they're like,
you can't, the bottle is glass.
We cannot allow you to keep it.
Yeah.
But we can take a picture of you with it,
but I need that bottle back.
And that was before,
they're like,
maybe we should just put these on tap.
Oh, okay.
That was before they built the Duff Garden,
the Beer Garden,
which is on both coasts, I believe now.
That's when you see those,
you see the seven Duffs,
you get Surly,
you get the gang,
that's nice to see.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, that's a good,
being one of the theme park episodes,
that they get some real estate in the-
Yeah, that's great.
Yeah, yeah.
The Duff Gardens,
I was shocked to learn that was season four,
and Itchy and Scratchy Land was season six,
so Duff Gardens came first.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I think Itchy and Scratchy Land
just kind of dwarfed it
in terms of like,
yeah, cultural-
I mean, look, Jason,
those of us who watched it from the start knew.
Yeah, this is what you were missing out on
when you were a social pariah.
Don't, don't even.
From episode one,
the family, Carl Saffellini,
was locked in, okay?
Don't you dare.
My mom still quotes the original episode,
but when they got sent us out,
but when they got sent us a little helper.
Yeah.
We knew, we knew.
But I have to think,
there were some Simpsons writers
who were from Southern California,
and until the 70s,
there was Busch Gardens Van Nuys
by The Bottling Plant.
Oh, yeah.
So I'm wondering how much of those memories
like leaked into that script.
Yeah.
Well, that's, yeah,
that's why, yeah,
they cover different areas.
One is more like the local park
and the beer-oriented park,
and one is the like,
insane, scary compound
that is itchy and scratchy land.
Here's a question, I guess.
It's like, well, first of all,
like, okay,
so we will maybe miss Moe's,
if Moe's goes.
I mean, I will,
I'll go do a final Moe's.
We all have to do a big final Moe's,
if that's what happens.
Yeah.
So we'll miss Moe's.
Do we miss anything else up there?
Or do we view that zone as just like,
well, it's, you know,
it's nice to walk around
and see, you know, yeah,
reference to Cletus,
or here's the, the,
the Androids dungeon,
or the, you know,
like, like,
you know,
that is a nice, like,
that area is a nice chance
to, like, see references
and recreations of King Toots
and whatever,
and things that I like.
Or do we feel like
that's had its time
and we're, we're good?
The Krusty Room
is the thing that I will miss.
The Krusty...
Like the Palm style.
There's the one special room upstairs
that is like the Krusty memorabilia room.
It's got the big gabo on the wall.
Have you been to,
have you been to the special room now?
Oh, yes.
Yeah, and this is what I've said
for many years now.
With the caricatures.
I would buy a gabo like that
if they made it.
No one has done this.
Although, um,
Jack's Pacific is making
Simpson's stuff
and I have the Krusty evil
Krusty plush doll
with the drawstring.
So maybe we'll get to gabo doll,
I don't know.
But that I will miss.
Did, is, um, uh,
did Krusty buy gabo
in a way of, like,
owning and crushing his enemies
in the way that,
uh, like a David Copperfield
would, like, buy all of his rivals things
and then put them on display?
Is, is if he vanquished them?
I think that's probably right.
There should be, like,
For him to have a gabo,
you think, Krusty probably views that
as, like, I'll put him in a glass case
as if to suffocate him.
Right, right, right.
No, you're probably right.
I mean, it should be like,
he should have, like, at least, like,
one, like, punch through his head
or something to signify
the Krusty.
Broken teeth.
Gabo.
Get some anger out on gabo.
Gabo, the creation of likely influence
by a recurring topic on this show,
Jerry Mahoney and Knucklehead Smith.
These little gestures
you're doing to each other,
you're so proud.
And that's it.
That's Jerry Mahoney.
Well, when he makes a good point,
I have to gesture to him
to signify that he's being right.
He's being correct.
Alan, do you know what this is?
Have you ever heard this reference?
You gotta fill me in.
Oh, okay.
So you're saying that Jerry Mahoney
is not a very common reference.
I mean, for me, it actually,
I am surprised that you guys have referenced
something that I don't get,
because normally I do get the references.
You are deep.
This is what I'm saying,
that even for a deep-cut pop culture person,
the Jerry Mahoney is not something people are saying
all the time.
We're trying to educate people.
We're trying to make this more known,
because the great Paul Winchell,
who did Tigger's Voice, of course,
had two ventriloquist dummies
that were very famous.
One more famous than the other
named Jerry Mahoney.
What happened?
Why were?
Why not today?
Well, some kids just don't appreciate
sort of the finer comedy of yesteryear.
That's what I would say.
Comedy that you yourself played on the show,
that all of us just stared at,
all of us just glared at in silence, even you.
That's true.
Well, maybe it wasn't the best clip for a podcast.
But you can appreciate...
We stepped into a long-running argument.
You can...
I mean, the argument is settled,
as far as I'm concerned.
As soon as we talked about it,
we met, someone sent us,
like right after we recorded,
or the episode came out,
you sent me a text to a video clip
and said, shit.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
And it was Paul Winchell and his dummies
on The Lucy Show.
And Lucy Ball, like, flirts with Knucklehead Smith.
But these were dummies
that also people were behind them
with, like, human arms.
So it is, granted, a little unsettling, but...
Why the shit?
What do you mean, shit?
Like, we missed it.
We missed him.
We should've brought it up.
We should've talked about it on the show.
It's behind the paywall.
You gotta pay us to get that good content, folks.
I'm sorry.
This is like the Podcast the Ride 4D experience,
and I'm loving it.
Like, the Podcast the Ride.
Genuine argument about Lucy and puppets break out.
It really does happen.
I think you were working at the time,
but for Mike's birthday,
I did get him an 8 by 10
of Jerry Mahoney and Knucklehead Smith
and Paul Winchell, and I framed it.
Yes, he did do that.
Congratulations.
And now you feel like your life is complete?
Complete? No.
Not until all the children of the world
know about these two glorious dummies.
He needs more cursed objects in his home.
Yeah.
Look, I just want that Gabbo that's up at Universal.
We should try to steal it before...
You want that Gabbo?
You have to have that one?
Well, I don't have to, but I'm saying...
I don't think you're gonna get it, unfortunately.
I think that's owned by Universal Studios.
Of course it is.
Well, maybe it's owned by Disney, technically.
I don't know, at this point,
what the ownership situation is.
But that's gonna go away.
I don't know that I missed the upstairs eating area
of Cletus's Chicken Shack.
No offense to it.
Okay, sure, sure.
It's like a spider pig, but I'm not...
That upstairs room, though, is...
I watched this video,
and I don't think I had even clocked this,
that this upstairs secret room
has become a place for Simpsons artists
to draw characters, and they're allowed to sign it
in a way where most Simpsons art out there
is signed by Matt Groening alone.
But it's become this weird secret museum
where somebody can draw Troy McClure
or whatever it is, and they get the credit for it.
Yeah.
So that's a neat thing,
that it's become this organic...
Is it still the artists go up there
and just like, all right, I'm gonna draw a character?
That's a good question.
I would save that room over Moe's,
no offense to Moe's,
but I think that's the coolest room of all of it.
I won't miss the Krusty Burger.
I haven't eaten a Krusty Burger in many years.
Okay, if I find myself up there,
and I really want chicken fingers or a burger,
I feel like, for whatever reason,
surrounded by all the Simpsons stuff in my mind,
it's just like, ah, this is better quality
than the fake American graffiti Mel's Diner
that has made me ill multiple times.
Is it?
I don't know.
Well, if it hasn't made you ill,
then that implies that it's better.
But yeah, it is not.
It is not a thing.
It's the same.
Yeah, I watched my son who eats,
that eats any garbage burger or chicken.
I feel like he was underwhelmed by the burger
and the chicken fingers.
It is like the Simpsons joke
where they sphere gray meat,
and it's just from the same vat,
and it goes to different restaurants.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
The food jokes on that show, it's wild.
There's a reference to the Good Morning Burger.
It's 18 ounces of ground beef soaked in butter.
But that sounds like something Guy Fieri would have now.
It's a different world.
Yes, now that would be an upscale food challenge situation.
Also, the way writers talk about the lunch breaks
being their savior in these incredibly long days,
sometimes when they talk about what they were ordering
or eating, it's disgusting.
It's so gnarly.
Yeah, I think Oakley's word was aggressive or vindictive.
They would order caviar spreads,
which is a joke from The Simpsons,
the American excess or whatever.
That seems like it happened a lot
where they would joke about something
or satirize something on The Simpsons,
but then people would adopt it at face level.
They didn't intend to give Bart so many catchphrases,
but kids repeat stuff they hear on TV.
Sure.
Yeah, the writers would say that it was like Sam Simon
being like, well, these are things Bart hears on TV,
so he's just repeating them, and it's a bit.
And then you think about it though,
and it's like, well, we don't see Bart picking that up on the show.
No, we don't.
But at 7, I just see Simpsons merch everywhere
saying, don't have a cow man underneath my shorts.
Were you saying it even though you weren't watching it?
I wasn't really saying it.
But you were saying not the mama.
I was saying not the mama, yeah.
But you were watching it.
So I was repeating, yeah, so I was repeating.
Yeah, which it's funny because in terms of,
oh, I can't let my kids see this,
it's like, well, Simpsons was a little more thoughtful
than dinosaurs.
How so?
What was the problem with dinosaurs?
What do you mean?
Well, no, it was just kind of like a B sitcom.
Oh, sure.
Like Simpsons is a better show, you're saying.
Yeah, Simpsons was a better show,
but I don't think my parents picked up,
like, oh, it's all these Harvard nerds, Harvard books.
You should have told them about the Harvard connection.
I didn't know about that until I was much older.
Do you know, can I tell you about where the writers were educated?
Mom and dad.
Dad, you like Letterman?
A bunch of these people came from Letterman.
You're five years old.
I wish.
I was.
This was a pre-IMDB era.
I don't know how you were going to find that out.
Well, you just had to have a giant phone book size,
like history of movie, like movie reference books.
Oh, I remember stuff like that.
Yeah, here's a big book that just lists every movie who's in it.
Yeah, you did need stuff like that.
We had a couple of those.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I had a lot of them.
Roger Ebert's Guide to the Movies,
we had one or two of those.
I had a lot of those for comic books,
which as soon as that book came out,
it was immediately out of date
because he just kept publishing more comic books.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
It only goes up to a certain time.
Okay, let me ask this.
Also, this like Simpsons inflection point that we're at.
If we lose it, Universal Studios,
if we no longer have a Simpsons presence in those parks,
now the ownership is with Disney,
and this is why it probably needs to go away
because we're at the two corporate umbrellas that get along the least.
Disney has done polling about
would you like to see Simpsons characters in the Disney parks?
Would you like experiences, rides, attractions?
So there is the possibility
that Disney does a second round of Simpsons stuff.
I guess two questions here.
One, do we think this will happen?
Two, would we want this to happen?
Feelings either way, Alan?
I think, well, I know I'm going to throw it back to you guys,
but first of all, could Disney deal with the mild subversion of the Simpsons?
What's the closest property they have in the parks to that sort of theming?
Muppets, which is going away.
Deadpool.
Oh, yeah, yeah, true.
He did a little show where he was subversive.
Yes, but they have not invested in a subversive or offensive permanent Deadpool attraction.
That is a very good question to bring up.
I mean, I would love to see a ride.
I mean, it's funny, I, of course, did my homework about this.
My best friend, he is an 11-year-old,
and I kind of polled him, like, what kind of Simpsons ride would you like to see?
And he said, like, a roller coaster that's, like, escaped from Burns Manor or something like that.
But see, my pitch would be, and this is sort of inspired by going to Disney World,
like some sort of, it's like Guardians of the Galaxy and Tron both sort of inspired this idea.
Oh, great, yes, they're good ones.
Basically, you're, like, on a skateboard like Bart.
So, from the perspective of Bart, I don't know how you would do that in a, like,
I was thinking of, like, the Tron light cycle or something like that, but, like, something to recreate the idea of being.
You have less support, but maybe there is something that you could sort of, like, position yourself on.
A skateboarding simulator ride is a diff, that's, like, that's its own good idea, even, regardless of Simpsons.
Right, but almost like a coaster simul-, like, a combo.
And so, the opening credits of the show is about a minute long, and it's full form.
So, basically, you would be Bart going through, like, the ride through Springfield or something like that.
That would be my ideal.
Going out the window. Yes.
There's a different chalkboard gag on a screen every time you ride.
They change out a zillion.
And it didn't, it doesn't have to be the exact path of the credits, but, like, that would, like, you start with the clouds opening and,
that would be, like, the best ride.
That would be, like, the best ride.
And I do think a, some sort of movie or, like, Muppets-like presentation would be really cool.
Like, I don't know, the Simpsons characters in the Disney park and, like, a 15-minute movie.
So, those are my pictures, yeah.
Wow, opening sequence, yeah, yeah.
And, and I would, I would require that they stick with all of the very season one stuff in it.
That he, like, that it's, you're Bart and you narrowly miss Jacques, the, uh, Marge.
Is that the bowling?
Yes, yeah, the bowling.
Yeah, Albert Brooks.
The Albert Brooks bowling structure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, uh, uh, or the, who's the, like, who's the belly dancer?
Princess Cashmere.
That was the, that's the, that's why you couldn't watch it.
Yeah, for, for a while.
Because of Princess Cashmere.
She is kind of, like, uh, became, like, a Simpsons, like, side, or, like, Blinky, the three-eyed fish,
where after the episodes that directly address them, they just kind of are in the periphery of all the characters.
They're not around as much.
But never do anything again.
Yes.
Marvin Monroe.
Sometimes you'll see Mindy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, it's been 36 seasons.
Maybe Blinky and Princess Cashmere get their own arcs.
If you told me that there were 15 episodes about Princess Cashmere at this point, I would be like, oh, yeah, probably.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
No, I, I, I assume that by the, you know, I, yeah, I'm just not as versed in, you know, the recent seasons,
by which I mean the last, uh, 22 years.
So, yeah, I, no, I assume that every single marriage combo has occurred.
Has been tried, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's what happened, like, the X-Men and stuff.
Well, like, Wolverine's with Storm now, and you're like, okay, let's see how that works.
Yeah, they had tension over the years.
Sure.
Well, they all did.
Yeah, they all did.
Well, the X-Men, especially.
But, uh, yeah.
I had tension with all the X-Women, too, when I was growing up.
Well, sure.
One-sided tension.
Yeah.
Uh, the, um, oh, God, I forgot what I was going to say.
I threw Jason off.
Which X-Women was popping in your head that distracted you?
Well, like, when I was a kid.
Who was it?
Was it Jubilee?
No, Jubilee was my, like, friend.
Okay.
Like, Jubilee and I were just friends.
Who was it?
No, Psylocke was too ridiculous.
Jean Grey.
Maybe Jean.
Jean or Rogue.
Rogue got that cool jacket.
Mine was Rogue.
Yeah.
That's, that's definitive.
Anyway, you got your back on track?
Yeah, I stayed with the Simpsons, like, into high school.
Like, a lot of people capped a lot earlier, but I think, like, the behind the laughter,
like, that could have ended there.
Like, it's season 10 or 11.
Behind the laughter's, like, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there's some good stuff in there.
I think you got some spotty stuff on the way to behind the laughter, for sure.
Sure.
Yeah.
I think the Poochie episode would have been an amazing finale.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's just, like, a good capper of, like, what, you know, basically the fans fighting
back.
I ruined my, in high school, I ruined my guide to our favorite family, the big book, the
Simpsons episode guide, because we were, I was in a class where we were doing screen
printing, and we projected an image up on the wall, and then you had to trace it on
paper, and then you cut it out with X-Acto knife and screen print it over that.
And the heat of that overhead projector killed the glue that held the book together.
So it is, I still have it.
Did you keep putting it on there to trace different characters?
Well, and then I tried to screen print Poochie.
Easier said than done, he's got a very complicated plaid shirt on.
Oh, okay, okay.
It takes a while to draw those lines.
And then I, the next section, I just did the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, the little
circular guy that used to be on the book covers.
Yeah, much easier.
I'm making a googly eye face, so much simpler after the Poochie debacle.
I was going to say, as far as rides are concerned, like we've talked a little bit about this
before, like there's other stuff that I think is a higher priority than getting the
Simpsons into the Disney parks.
I'm not going to be mad if they do it.
Yeah, that's my, you know, this question came up in a second game mailbag episode, and
we were both like, I guess so, but I feel like with Disney, I'm like, well, as long
as you get to like 13 other things, but if Disney's only going to do every like a couple
things, should one of them be Simpsons?
I don't know.
Is that like, is that a weird thing to, do I seem like a Fairweather fan?
I know, I feel bad saying it like that too, because I don't know that I'm, like the thing
I would want is some sort of like kind of retro ride, which is something we kind of,
I don't know if we've touched on this lately, where I've been thinking like, it would be
fun if Disney built like a Mr. Toad ride in this day and age.
And I mean that by like a small ride.
Yeah.
Like something that is not even like, cause they even build like a new dark ride and it's
Ariel's undersea, which was a big ride compared to the old Fantasyland dark rides.
They don't truly do little dinky rides anymore.
That's true.
And I guess like if they built something new and then they advertise that people might be
upset by that, like that's maybe their thinking is that like, you can't do that anymore.
It would be a let down, like too minor of an attraction.
Right.
I feel like the Ratatouille ride might be an interesting model for it.
Yeah, yeah.
Like in and out of a physical space.
Yeah.
Some is practical.
It's not, it doesn't necessarily have to be super scary or have a lot of thrills, but
immersive.
Yeah, yeah.
But like fun and wild, quote unquote.
Where were you going somewhere specific?
A little, well I have my, I have a pitch for it that will never be made is that like you
do, it's like the size of Mr. Toad or Pinocchio or, or what, whatever.
And it's basically just robots and it's small.
And it's based on one of my favorite as a kid, Simpsons video games, which is funny because
all the Simpsons video games were like about the Simpsons beating people up, which is
hilarious.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Marge assaulting people with a vacuum cleaner.
Right.
With a big heavy old vacuum cleaner.
And the Nintendo game, which I played was Bart versus the Space Mutants.
It was Bart fighting aliens.
Bart.
Bart or Bartman?
There was Bartman in different, oh maybe you turned into Bartman in that one.
I forget which one.
Yeah, you might have done both.
Or was it El Barto?
That's the thing I think is funny.
I was just watching, I was watching like a walk through the places I haven't been in
Universal Florida, Springfield.
I was like, it's funny that they, El Barto really looms large.
I'm like, has there ever been like anything like big with El Barto on the show?
It's just what he writes on walls and it's, it's just his graffiti.
Yeah, yeah.
But I feel like theme parks end up, and you know what we'll do is we'll have El Barto
everywhere.
I'm like, that feels like a season one not relevant thing.
Did not catch on.
It's like set dressing, like Blinky the Three-Eyed Fish.
Oh, sure.
You know?
The nod to the roots.
But like yeah, Bart, you remember this at all?
Did you just play this?
Yes, I do.
It was punishingly difficult.
Oh, it was very hard.
Yes, very, very hard.
It was very hard.
But more fun, and I see people talking about like, they need to put this out or they need
to remaster it.
Simpson's Road Rage?
Road Rash?
That's later.
It's later.
Yeah, it was in like high school.
But it's like one game, I think.
Grand Theft Auto, essentially in Springfield.
Might be a good ride.
Might be a good ride too.
But I would pitch as a tiny little dark ride with a bunch of robots where like Bart and
aliens have invaded Springfield and it's just static figures basically.
And you're going through in a little Simpsons car and you're coming, the stuff is coming
and you have Kang and Kodos can be there too or whatever.
But it could be more themed to the actual show.
You see Lenny and Carl.
You see Snake and Pony.
Yeah, yeah.
So like just a little dark ride and like Moe's with a beer garden seems like, oh, that might
not be so expensive.
You could put that in Hollywood Studios somewhere and you got a little Simpsons there.
I like a little modest, fun little, not high pressure.
Right.
There's merchandise there because Simpsons will never stop.
So you may as well sell Simpsons merch forever, I guess.
Something smallish but still has a fun little ride.
That's an interesting, I see a unique way to do it.
You know, I was thinking in terms of what could they do that they haven't already done
and that the original Simpsons ride does not already accomplish.
And I feel like, I think you would have to get the Shearer characters.
That's like the only way that they can, because I was watching some video last night where
somebody said, so why don't any of his characters like Burns and Smithers appear?
Well, it turns out he was unavailable for the recording.
And I'm like, you poor, you blindly optimistic vlogger.
You don't know what's happening here.
Wait, is that what, the reality is probably just he didn't want to do it.
The reality is he hates the show and doesn't want to participate any more than he could
step away from Lay Show for a minute to record some voice.
Must have recorded and set up his whole busy building more floors in his home from Simpsons.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Proceeds.
While being extremely furious at what funded the floors.
No, but I think Disney would have to shell out.
And you would have, because like, I was like, okay, you know, yeah, we go to Moe's.
We go to Krusty Burger.
You go to so many places on the ride.
The place that is not really represented is the power plant.
And then in tandem with that, you're, wait, your niece or nephew.
I forget who you asked about.
Oh, yeah, my nephew, my friend's son.
Yes, yeah.
So that also Burns Manor is definitely, I think, to like do something with a big Burns presence,
because those are like, those are grand spaces, scary spaces.
And it's like a very easy sort of Disney good versus evil scenario.
Yes, absolutely.
And you can kind of put any ridiculous thing in Burns Manor, and it would make sense.
Yes, well, he has like a thousand rooms full of nonsense.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So behind any door could be any craziness.
If there was something that could like take you from, I don't know, like Homer causes a meltdown
and you experience it in real time and have to escape, you know, like there truly is like giant plutonium,
you know, the kind of thing that makes the whole plant grow, glow green or whatever.
Yeah.
And you have to, you've only got seconds to escape.
Which kind of tangentially happens on the ride, but it's not no Burns or Smithers.
Yeah.
It's subbed in for, Krusty is subbed in, Krusty and company is subbed in.
Oh, as kind of as the corrupt businessman.
Yeah.
But yeah, I mean, I think getting to see like, and physically Bill to be in a queue of big, scary, Gothic, imposing Burns space.
And I also want animatronics.
I think that is the only way to justify doing new Simpsons because we've already done, we've done screen ride and it makes sense.
It's an animated show. You do screen ride.
But getting to see like physical eyes, like a Mr. Burns physically in the room.
Yeah.
Taking you to task, throwing stuff at you, throwing items, throwing paperweights in your face.
I think that that'd be the thing.
They're going to look weird, though.
Yes.
They just will have to, there's just for whatever reason, it's really hard.
I mean, the closest I've seen actually is this company, Super Seven, which makes Simpsons.
I don't make them now because of Disney, they lost the rights.
But they made these Simpsons, Super Seven toys that are the closest I've seen to 3D Simpsons looking good.
But I just like, oh, like anytime you ever see the like 3D Simpsons, it's always odd.
It is, yeah. But I'll tolerate.
I'm for it. I'm for it.
I just want to know what they would do.
Don't get me wrong, I'm for it.
I just want to round a corner in a physicalized.
Yeah, they're always scary as mascots.
They're so scary.
They're weird in the park.
They're as weird in the parks as they were on the ice capades 35 years ago.
It's just, yeah, it's strange.
I'm imagining like the Yeti in the Expedition Everest coaster.
It's like Mr. Burns looming.
Oh, that would be nice, yeah.
Oh, that'd be awesome.
Yeah, yeah.
Are there giant characters?
I mean, like a sci-fi, I mean, you were like, you were like a huge king in CODIS.
Huge king in CODIS, yeah.
And they have, obviously they have that spinner in Orlando.
Alan, I'll shout out, mention in your book again, because again, I really enjoy this.
But the mention of Homer fantasizing about if he wins the lottery.
And his fantasy is he is giant and covered in jewels.
And gold too, right?
And gold, and that's such a weird joke.
And then years later, I feel like there's a different Homer fantasizing about coming into money
where he's sitting on the porch of a solid gold house and twirling a revolver and marches in a bikini go-go dancing next to him.
Yeah, if he robs the Kwik-E-Mart, I think is the, oh yes, that's the life.
But the writer, I think the Homer growing and being jewel-encrusted was a Swartz Welder joke.
And another writer was like, it doesn't make sense.
Like, why would being rich make you grow?
Like, why would it make you grow?
But doesn't Lenny kind of get those?
And I think that they love that Swartz Welder would come up with these jokes that were like, they made sense, but they made all the sense.
They made no sense, but somehow made all the sense in the world.
Some operation you could get, presumably with all the money in the world, there's something that could widen your bones while keeping your same physical structure.
He doesn't want hair.
That's not part of the equation.
He will still remain bald, a much easier surgery to get.
He just wants to be giant and gold.
I've read a couple of his books, Swartz Welder's books, and it is a thing where I need to take a break when I'm reading, because it's joke after joke after joke.
And they're all good.
You're laughing so loud, you start concerning your neighbors.
I'm concerning my neighbors, but they're all so funny.
And he is, I mean, he's the best kind of weird.
There's like one profile of him in The New Yorker from 2021, and I feel like all of my comedy group chats that day were like,
Swartz Welder, Mike Saks piece, The New Yorker, it's so long, because he's such a recluse.
Yeah, and that interview was done over email.
So what was crazy about it is if you read it, it's like you're reading a Simpsons episode.
It's his voice. It's crazy.
He sort of crafts these answers that are in ways that you can't really do if you're just speaking it.
Oh, like it's hyper written.
Yes, exactly.
But in a good way.
That's cool.
I bet he knows who Jerry Mahoney is.
Oh, I absolutely bet he does.
100%.
Very well, then that's the key to being relevant today.
He doesn't do a lot of interviews, but could we get Swartz Welder on to talk about Jerry Mahoney?
Does Swartz Welder know the pandemic happened?
I would hope so.
I feel like I always just hear like, yeah, he's just in a house in the Hollywood Hills smoking in the diner booth he bought.
I think it's funny because some of the writers said they wouldn't call him a recluse.
They would just call him someone who doesn't do interviews.
But then George Meyer was like, it's OK, he's a recluse.
But I think he loves baseball and will rent out Safeco Field in Seattle to play games.
It's crazy.
Perfect story.
Well, God, anything we've missed on the way out the door here?
I mean, another like, all right.
If the modern Disney company, if they really they want to have Simpsons representation, but they truly don't have the money to do it, which feels very current Disney.
I would settle for of all the part of any like anything theme park you to recreate on the newly in a theme park, Homerland.
I would I would happily take Homerland, which is, of course, when he buys a trampoline and then flashes to an expanded operation with the trampoline as the base.
But that also includes Muckville, USA, which is just a bunch of mud and then Fort Adventure.
It's a bunch of soil mattresses.
If there is a perfect kids play zone of Homerland.
Yeah.
With the same with that graphic design and that did smell.
I think I would accept that.
And I actually I think my son would be crawling around there all the time.
I you could leave your son at Homerland and then all the millennial parents are by the photo op by the barbecue grill that Homer did not successfully build in that one of us.
Oh, yeah.
I have real.
I just had a thought.
Sorry.
This is a different idea to get Simpsons in Hollywood Studios is that we canceled that Muppets rock and roller coaster thing.
While you're trying to get rid of that anyway.
I'm trying to get rid of that.
I'm still going to try until it's gone.
Mm hmm.
But we replace Aerosmith with Simpsons Aerosmith.
The Simpsons version of Aerosmith.
This you will allow.
That keeps.
Yes.
Yeah.
The Flamin' Mo Coaster.
Well, it'll still.
Well, it's still called Rock and Roller Coaster featuring Aerosmith, but they just look like the Simpsons versions of themselves.
So it's the same.
Alan with a pitch that's fun.
And you're like, no, no, because I need Aerosmith to be in the title.
Let's not go crazy here.
I'm so sorry.
I'm in the zone and I'm so creative right now.
I respect it.
The man loves Aerosmith.
What can I say?
But yeah, there'll be some other Simpsons references in the rock and roller coaster at that point.
Simpsons, David Wayne, Simpsons.
Who plays their manager?
Simpsons Camerino is what you're talking about.
Oh, yes.
Simpsons Camerino.
Sorry.
There's a dozen people.
Ileana Douglas.
Simpsons, Simpsons.
Simpsons, the Ileana Douglas.
If she hasn't been already.
Just get them all.
I assume there was a full state reunion on there.
With zillions of episodes, that must have happened.
But a lot cheaper than whatever this Muppets thing they're doing is.
It's a lot cheaper.
So to have them do their iconic performance of their animated performance of Walk This
Way where Mo joins them, you would accept this?
Would you let Mo be in there or is that a little too much too?
When you said it, I kind of winced.
I just prefer they keep the tracks the way they are.
And it just still reads the same because it's Aerosmith.
Would you want it to be like the show where they are animated into it with their manager
at the time, which was part of the deal of them being in the show?
Do you know about that?
It cuts to them at a booth at Mo's and then there's some guy.
Why is he there?
I think they initially turned down a different episode because they didn't think it was cool
enough, Aerosmith, and now they're on a roller coaster at MGM.
Or, I'm sorry, Hollywood Studios.
Wow, that dated me.
No, no, no.
I will never stop calling it Disney MGM Studios.
We're cut from the same cloth.
I could not have predicted as a child that now when I was saying MGM, it would be Jamie
Foxx telling me all about Bet MGM.
You know all the bet apps.
I know all the bet.
I know all the commercials.
He's getting ready to be on that and be putting up those 40 cents a day.
That's how much he wants to hit the gambling bricks.
You can do the gambling casino from Springfield in Hollywood Studios.
That is true.
When Marge has a big leak problem.
Yeah, the Burns casino.
Well, there's another massive scary mystery.
Yeah, okay.
We can do that.
I want all the Burns stuff.
You could flip the Hollywood Studios Brown Derby to the Simpsons fancy restaurant pretty
easy.
Oh, that's true.
The Gilded Truffle.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah.
But my pitch is very doable and less fun, but you would do a Simpsons after hours event.
Photo opportunities, all the songs in the Key of Springfield.
Well, you're speaking Disney's language.
Walk around characters.
Exactly what it would be.
So it's $180?
Yeah.
That is data collection to save people like it.
It's like live, real-time data collection to see if people would accept it, you know?
What is?
You mean to get it something more permanent?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, to see like, is there still enough interest?
Have our shorts where like Maggie meets Baby Yoda on Disney+.
Has that kept the Simpsons in the public spotlight enough?
There's a good chance that's more popular than all the stuff we've been talking about.
Possibly.
A good chance that that's more relevant.
Well, we all know what it's going to be, which is just they take all the theaters they have
that aren't playing anything and they start playing this Simpsons in plus-aversary.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Disney plus-aversary shirt.
So they can implement that day one as soon as Universal loses the license.
Well, but it's nice to brainstorm.
It's nice to think about.
Nice to think about.
Nice just to talk Simpsons for a while.
So thank you for being here to do that.
Alan Siegel, you survived podcast The Pride.
Much appreciated.
This is a good time.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Anything you want to tell us?
Obviously you have something to plug.
We've been referring to it the whole time.
Anything else you want to tell us about Stupid TV?
It'd be more funny.
Well, first of all, thank you guys for having me.
I feel like I'm sitting with my three podcast brothers talking about this stuff.
So it's a blast.
So Stupid TV.
Rod and Todd.
The characters we most resemble.
Two rods and a Todd.
Someone asked me who would you be and I'm like a combo of Milhouse and Lisa.
That would probably be Milo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of Milhouses in there too.
So the book Stupid TV Be More Funny is out on June 10th.
You can pre-order it.
If you don't want to use a giant online retailer, you can go to bookshop.org.
Great website.
And that connects you to a local bookstore if you would like to buy it that way.
Wow.
Okay, that is a very good specific plug.
So yeah, for sure, do it that way if you can.
And from what we've read already, such a great book and such a great deep dive.
And I've enjoyed your writing in the past.
So congratulations on this.
Yeah, great work.
Thanks, guys.
Absolutely.
As for us, for three bonus episodes every month, check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And then I propose that we end like a Simpsons episode, which is, of course, with
I forgot the shush.
The shush comes first.
Mike edit the shush.
I'll do it.
Don't worry.
Okay.
And then you'll edit all this that I'm saying right now, right?
That'll be cut out.
Okay, thanks.
I know.
I could trust you as an editor and as my brother and as my friend.
This has been a Forever Dog Production, executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at ForeverDogTeam, and liking our page on Facebook.