Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate.
I'm Torque, joined by Outlaw.
I'm pointing at you, Outlaw.
Me, I'm Outlaw.
That's right.
Embrace it.
Own it.
Outlaw.
I was going to call myself, like, Young Man or something.
Well, that's fine.
These are suggested.
But that's better.
That's more of an actual American Gladiators name.
I'll call myself Outlaw.
Outlaw.
And over there, it's Throb.
Oh, Throb.
I was going to say Scuttle, and then I realized that's a little...
Scuttle's a little mermaid.
Yeah, that's why I was like, wait, there's a Disney thing named Scuttle, and then I remembered.
Yeah, scuttling isn't a tough word to scuttle around.
What about Engorge?
Sure.
Or Jason?
Well, Throb Engorge.
Scuttle kind of made sense to me because you've got to scuttle between the barrier.
You've got to dodge the balls and stuff.
You've got to be crafty and high.
I guess you could describe that as scuttling.
Scurrying?
Scurrying is what you're thinking, I think, more.
You're thinking about scurrying, I think.
And over there is scurry.
Technically, an action verb.
Well, to each his own.
I just wanted to come in with a couple of suggestions.
And by the way, mine is Torque spelled with a Q, not like Peter Torque.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for making that distinction.
For our audience.
Yeah, yes.
Well, for at least one person in the room.
Just wanted to make sure you didn't think I was making a monkey's reference.
We're talking about the Torque as in the, is it a motorcycle movie from the early 2000s
with a young Adam Scott?
Oh, right.
Yeah.
He's in Torque.
He came to Funny or Die once and made a video about his experiences on the set of Torque.
Is that true?
Yeah.
It was something about an assistant director who was making him do something dangerous.
And it made him feel unsafe while making the movie Torque.
Oh, oh dear.
I forget the name of that.
And Ken Marino is in it playing a backstage role, much like in the rock and roller coaster
attraction.
It's the part he was born to play.
Yeah.
But we are here to talk about something I've been wanting to do the deep dive on for a
long time.
This has been on a, this has been on a literal to-do list for a while, and I'm glad that
we've, we've landed here.
Today, we are talking about American Gladiators Orlando Live.
However, I would like to overshoot that proper title and refer to it as what it is in my
heart, which is the American Gladiators Dinner Theater.
This is something that was in Orlando.
And you know what?
The building did say American Gladiators Dinner Theater as well.
There's a bit of branding confusion throughout this thing.
So I'm going to, I'm going to use the most descriptive one because that's what this is.
If you don't know this, American Gladiators, the smash hit pop culture phenomenon syndicated
televised pseudo sports show of the late 80s and early to midnight, 89 to 96, this thing
ran.
We can talk about the show a little broader, but you know, very popular, like insane, garish,
show with, you know, crazy bodybuilder types performing stunts and sports that were made
up for the show specifically, memorable theme, you know, just like a vibrant, great 90s memory.
When the show petered out and stopped airing on television, they wanted to do more with
the brand and the Gladiators wanted to work and people involved in the show wanted to
keep going in some way and someone had the idea to take all of those desires and to
thrust them together, to throb them together with the rather big at that time and maybe
still a little bit, the world of Orlando dinner theaters.
And I say dinner theater, not so much as like who done it to mystery type dinner theater,
but you know, medieval times, pirates, dinner adventure, these dinner arenas really would
be the proper way.
Yeah, dinner in a show, I guess is what medieval times would say.
Yeah, yeah.
Big, long piece of entertainment where you're not in the dark, you're eating, you're lit
up to, you're eating a big piece of chicken.
You're eating the worst chicken you've ever had.
You're cheering on your guy against your opponents.
And it does, these things do sort of align.
You can certainly see why on paper American Gladiators becoming a new current version
of medieval times.
Makes sense.
Yeah, I mean, it is, I'm trying to think of even a better way, like dinner in a battle
is really the way these specific dinner theaters should be described because it is pirates
dinner adventure.
It's medieval times.
It's this.
It's probably Dolly's Dixie Stampede or whatever it's called now, but you're watching fighting.
It's like, it's like you're in the Coliseum, which was also, by the way, a great idea for
an Orlando dinner theater is when you're in like a Coliseum and there's gladiators.
Has that been done?
That feels like that's no, I don't think that's a ripe, that's, you know what, as I discovered
doing this, I think I'm virtually every other type of theme and era was done.
And I'm kind of surprised that somewhere in, well, I guess by the two thousands, they figured
out that this area is not as fruitful as and guaranteed financially successful as anybody
thought that it was.
So I was going to say, like, you'd think maybe the movie Gladiator would prompt more
of that stuff, but I guess not.
And will the new one, will Gladiator, will the success of Gladiator 2 lead to the dinner
seum or the food seum?
What's the, what's the, for the cuisine of seum, what's the cleanest way to combine those
words?
The coleslaw seum, because that's one of the dishes you get.
Right, right.
This is only, this is related, but I'm realizing now that when we were in Orlando and I drive,
I noticed that the body show that's at the Pirate Dinner Adventure in Buena Park, Tietro
Martini, which closed in Buena Park is still in Orlando.
I saw a sign for it.
Wow.
So I don't know if they move.
Is it's own venue and does it not share with the Pirates?
That's what I'm wondering, because there is a Pirates Dinner Adventure in Orlando as well.
Yes.
The sister cities of Buena Park and Orlando.
That's why I think of them.
That's why, yeah.
And that's why Buena Park is so high in your heart.
Right.
It's one of the greatest cities in the world.
It feels like there should be a portal to Orlando, not you don't have to take a plane.
It's just like there's a magic hole in Buena Park that you step through and you step out
into Orlando.
That's how it feels.
It does feel like it's like you're not that far, like one minute you're in downtown LA
and then maybe, you know, 25 minutes later, if you're lucky, you're in the silliest place
you've ever seen.
Right.
Yeah.
It doesn't feel like the rest of the city, not even Anaheim.
It feels like singular.
Yeah.
From Anaheim.
You show up next to the Big Wizard gift shop or the empty lot where the Florida Project
Motel used to be.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, the location of this gets us close to one of these like roadside looks like something
kind of places, which is a gift shop that looks like a big orange, near the big orange.
This is, I was showing Jane to the building to see if she recognized it from living in
Florida.
And she's like, I can kind of picture the area.
And she looked up in this, the building this used to be in is about 10 minutes from Pop
Century.
Yeah.
It's not that, it's not that far.
Hey, look, this, this should have been a point in its favor that it is fairly close to Disney
World.
I think that I, you bring up iDrive, you bring up International Drive, like the big crazy
stretch, you know, near Disney and Universal where every single corner and block, it is
like just one, it is just a murderer's row of every crazy two story chain restaurant
and weird pseudo themed thing.
And at one point in time, a lot more of these dinner theaters, which I'll bring up a few
of these kind of in history.
But I, that was some of what spurred me to push for this episode finally is that, you
know, you and I made it down there, Mike, and I was like, iDrive, we got to explore
some of this crazy iDrive stuff, like the American Gladiators dinner theater, but looked
into it, not iDrive, not iDrive, different area.
As you said, as Jamie pointed out, pretty close, like 10 minutes east, but it's actually,
it was on a stretch in Kissimmee, it's very close to Fun Spot Kissimmee, if anybody's
been there.
Kissimmee St. Cloud, the center of all the action.
Throw a dart, throw all the darts.
It might be, because we did the, I'm too excited to sleep, the Kissimmee St. Cloud
archery ad might be worth examining.
Well then maybe you get into some other what the hell was going on in Kissimmee, because
I think it's the episode Kissimmee St. Cloud, obviously with a strong focus on darts, or
arrows?
Arrows.
Yeah, arrows, I think, it was a big archery target.
There's Sea World.
There's Universal Studios.
I believe Pirates, Dinner Adventure, and Teatro Martini are in the same, at least.
In Florida too?
Yes.
It is a shared.
I believe it's shared, but it might be two different buildings next to each other, I
can't tell from here.
Okay.
And do you have any sense of if the Florida one does the seasonal show Vampirates?
Very good question.
I can look into it, and I will right now.
Great, great.
And can you befriend someone in that show as well?
What is one of the odds of a Vampirate talking to you in Florida?
In Florida?
Honestly, probably pretty high.
We might know a Vampirate.
Yeah, I know.
Because I knew a Vampirate in Blana Park.
If the show had kept going, we might have known a Gladiator too.
We might have.
That's true.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
We might know the Hot Soup Pitcher Company if it kept going.
One of the greatest inventions of mankind, the Hot Vegetable Soup Pitchers.
As if you're getting a pitcher of Coke, but it's a bunch of soup in the pitcher.
You'd think that they would use the same ones, but first of all, you don't want the
cross-contamination.
You don't want the vegetable soup in the Coke, although I've combined those things, and
they're excellent.
But you need the hotter pitcher.
It's got to be thicker in order to have the soup in it as opposed to the cold cola.
Scott, when I tell you I had this same conversation in my mind a few hours ago, about whether
the pitchers could be the same.
Do the pitchers get, are they one pitcher used for everything?
I'm like, oh no, that Hot Soup Pitcher has to be temperature safe.
It couldn't be the Coke Pitcher.
I chose the character of somebody who thought that there should be specific, because you
mentioned the Hot Soup Pitcher Company as opposed to the cold one.
I guarantee it's the same pitchers.
This is some of the worst food on the planet Earth.
I thought mine was, this is one of my revelations, I thought the food was fine.
God.
I just never.
The Doughboy's despised by a steer of hatred for one of the worst places they've ever been.
Maybe the worst meal Aaron has ever had in her life.
You guys.
It is the worst.
We come from different worlds.
There's no doubt about it.
I don't bake chicken a lot.
Mike Carlson is saying this.
It's some of the worst food on planet Earth.
You've got to listen when Mike Carlson's saying it.
I don't know how you can say that it was pretty good.
The salad is like wet newspaper.
The chicken is just like an odd texture that I've never seen before or felt and then it's
dark in there and it's like, it adds, it's like when you're like, you were a kid and
they put like spaghetti in a box and you put your hand in there and you're like, it gives
me that feeling.
I don't know.
Touching the chicken.
They had that lobby, they're like touch a zombie pirate and then that's someone's chicken
on tray an hour later.
They just serve it right up.
Yeah.
Yes.
With hand contamination.
Who cares?
We've got to move these babies.
You will not find worse food than a pirate's dinner adventure.
Geez, Mike.
Some sanity has been reached food wise on the show after many, many long months of avoiding
it altogether.
Something that we'll learn in this episode also is that this, I mean, it shouldn't be
a surprise, but the food being extremely cheap is absolutely a part of the model.
Oh yeah.
It was extremely on purpose and I can point to the specific person who pushed this model
and you may be surprised, you may not be surprised who this source ends up being.
There's a very good Orlando Sentinel article from 1995 and it was giving good details and
then right at the end, it hit like two things where I was like, oh, of course Scott's all
over there.
Yes.
Credit to Orlando Sentinel really like unlocked it because there's not a ton of info about
this thing.
So some excellent articles that sent me down some rabbit holes.
I had so much fun.
I don't want to build it up too much.
I just, I know I loved learning about what I learned about and dare I say, we're hovering
around something, a word that we haven't said in a while, strangely, this word that was
really looming over the podcast and I don't know why, maybe we've just picked more benign
topics lately, but today, guys, guys are on the menu.
Oh yeah.
There are definitely some guys in the picture here and welcome back guys.
I had a feeling, I had a feeling just reading, just seeing some of the names.
I was like, oh, these wonderful names.
I don't know what it is that's speaking to me about them, but I will say the article
that I read, which was kind of a rundown of how this started and came together, no mention
of food.
Yeah, no, there's almost no information.
I can't vouch for how much better or worse it is than the pirate's food.
I would guess same or worse.
That's what I'd throw out.
But anyway, as far as location, not I drive, but on a stretch called Erlo Bronson Memorial
Highway.
I feel like I've come across the street in Orlando Travels.
I think maybe part of Erlo Bronson Memorial Highway maybe connects all the way to Disney
World itself.
I think that is possible.
And I just in seeing it on a map, I got curious who Erlo Bronson is or was, and I'll say was
because he has passed, but he was an old guy in the Florida House of Representatives.
He was a massive Florida landowner who sold some of the land that is today Disney World.
He made Walt's dreams come true, sold for like a hundred dollars an acre.
I don't know how much he had, but you know, Erlo was one of the guys that Walt swindled
when he came into town, but he got a street named after him, so it all worked out.
And you know, it's maybe fine because would you believe that a Florida representative
in the 1960s and 70s engaged in a lot of segregationist and McCarthyist tactics, some not good stuff
along with a bunch of his fellow representatives to where Erlo and his whole gang, they all
got a kind of a group name together.
They were referred to in the Florida House as the Pork Chop Gang.
Okay.
Yeah.
Which is, you know, I guess refers to that whole, that government pork and that spending
stuff.
But I hear Pork Chop Gang and I think like the old gang Jason was in when he was a little
kid with a bunch of other friends of his, an off-brand reboot of the Rascals that some
straight to video enterprising filmmakers tried to get off the ground with a, I was
going to say an eight-year-old Jason, but it could have been like it was all eight-year-olds
and then a 30-year-old Jason.
Yeah.
Mike and I had already done an improv team at UCB and then I fell in.
Well, you know, if you go down the store with bulk candy, inevitably everyone scoops it
out into bags, but you know, one or two pieces fall off and those are no man's land.
So you got to grab those single pieces.
Was that your audition monologue for the Pork Chop Gang?
Yeah.
Well, that's, that was a tip I gave them and they're like, that's a great idea.
That's a great idea.
Tall boy, you're in because I was taller than all the only time in my life I was ever taller
than the room.
Why the hell they listen to you?
So the, the, the place itself, well, how else to go about this?
I mean, like, is there anything else we need to say about American Gladiators?
I think, I feel like people probably know what it is.
It's, you know, it's crazy red, white and blue costumes.
It's the most fit people you've ever seen, kick-ass theme with the ultimate like films
at Universal Studios Hollywood with the fountain in the beginning of the show.
Although it wasn't always filmed there and moved to CBS Radford at some point, but the,
you know, just a watch to this day that goes down smooth.
It's not like I'm watching a lot of American Gladiators, but it was the like cable era.
If you land on that and I think there's a Pluto and all that, it's like, you love it.
You love these and all these, you know, they're all named something crazy.
It's ice and saber and blast.
It's, it's, it's just a lot of fun.
It's definitely in the wake of rock and wrestling, WWF at the time, Hulk Hogan.
It's definitely in that zone where like, and kind of capitalizing on like bodybuilder mania
post Schwarzenegger.
Yeah.
But if you've never seen it, it's like adult guts, adult Nickelodeon guts.
That it's like, well, we're probably on the episode about guts that we did with Mo herself
or an episode about Nickelodeon Steels, we were like, if you've never seen guts, imagine
like a kid, American Gladiators.
Right.
Well, it works the other way.
All of this came first.
This was years before.
Yes.
Imagine adult guts.
American Gladiators has a lot more high powered nerf cannons.
Yes.
Things that would be dangerous for kiddos to use, things that the pork shop gang would blast
each other's heads off with.
Did you watch the video on YouTube?
The video about this?
Yeah.
The infomercial?
The 30 minute infomercial.
Oh, I sure did.
Oh, I didn't catch that.
It's really a tremendous 30 minutes.
It's kind of the best piece of material that exists about this thing.
Yeah.
It's a, we should have passed it around.
You learn a lot.
And I was just going to say, yes, you could, if you're listening to this and you really
want to know before you get into the analysis of Podcasts that Ride, it tells you about
the different events that you will see at the dinner theater, which also were on the
show.
Which that's, you know, that's a good way to go about it maybe in terms of what this
was a little bit.
And yeah, because they did all of these like invented kind of hyper, what's the like, they're
all like a roller ball, like scary future sports.
Something in American Gladiators would be in a dystopian Verhoeven movie of here's what
sports are in the future, but they make it very friendly and fun.
Yeah.
And they try to, I mean, they definitely hype it up as being, I think it was at power, like
one of them is called Powerball, which is really funny now in hindsight cause they said
less the lottery if you didn't know, but I think they refer to Powerball as like the
deadliest sport on this infomercial.
They hype it up as like, this will kill you.
Yes, they are hyping it up to that degree and then the ultimate musical hype up that
you could do, which is in the background during Mortal Kombat.
Yes.
Which lasts for a while and they keep looping, I feel like, Mortal Kombat as well.
But then isn't Powerball, that is mainly like, it's sort of like a fast pace disposing of
your lunch items.
Yeah.
It's a bunch of cans.
It's like four basketball hoops on the ground and you got to run and throw your basketball
in them fast.
And you got a big scary guy or woman coming at you.
Sure.
And I'm sure that is very imposing and difficult.
And by the way, everyone, also the premise of the show is that there are the weak, there's
the staff, right?
You're, it's, you know, think of it as a beat the geeks.
Think of it as a more obscure thing than this.
But here's the ones who are always there and then it's outside opponents come in and try
to take on the gladiators and those outs to even be there, you got to be a fighter fighter
or former military or something, you know, like the immense shape you have to be in to
even try to do this.
There was apparently the premise in the show that the winner of the season would be asked
to join permanently as a permanent gladiator and then they lost that premise between one
and two when they realized they didn't want to keep anybody or something.
Right.
Yeah.
You get sort of the greatest hits in this dinner theater show of the real things that
they would do, such as Powerball.
Do you have other favorites?
The assaults.
The assault.
That's the first one they talk about the assault and you're like, it's not, it doesn't sound
so fun.
It's not a word that today you want people saying assaults.
So like, it wasn't then either, by the way.
Yeah, yeah.
It goes from assault to Powerball, which is really funny.
In 2025, I feel like something's really awful sounding and then something sounds fun, like
you can win some money.
What's the, I'm blanking now, the joust.
What's the joust called?
Is it the joust?
Yes.
Joust is the thing where they're up on the platform.
That's the iconic, I think, the most iconic of all the American gladiators events.
Well, there's that, but there's also where they're rolling around in the balls.
Yeah.
It feels iconic to me due to the Simpsons joke when Luanne Van Houden, is that her name,
is dating a gladiator?
Pyro?
Pyro.
Yeah.
And they leave in his ride, which is one of the big balls.
But kind of a big hamster ball or something, hamster wheel, but that actually moves around.
That may be too big and expensive of equipment to do at this gladiator dinner theater, which
if you haven't started guessing already, this is a little lower rent than the television
show.
Yeah.
It's just basically a staff with like cushion pads on each side.
It's like a big Q-tip.
Patriotic Q-tip.
And you're trying to knock each other off your platform.
I think it was maybe the main event or on the cover, there was a Nintendo game of American
gladiators.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, right.
Yes.
I would love to do the joust, I think.
As long as it's like softish on the bottom, I think I could still do the joust.
How long you think you're holding up in the joust?
Who am I against, though?
The weakest gladiator who ever did it.
But they are a gladiator.
Yeah.
What event are we planning?
It's me, Mike versus Scott?
Possibly.
Okay.
Well, if it's the weakest gladiator, let's call him Spudder.
I think I could last 30 seconds.
Maybe that's generous.
I don't know.
That's very generous.
Yeah.
I think you're getting hit three times.
Spudder now?
No.
Because Spudder is 65 years old now, probably.
You're fishing for people exactly like you or that it's old gladiators.
I think probably an old gladiator, unless they're very injured, I think is probably
still got a good shot.
I would like to take on an old gladiator.
I think a lot of them are in great, you know, because there's this documentary which gets
into this thing a little bit, and I think a lot of them are in fantastic shape to this
day.
There are competing documentaries, which I forgot about.
Is it Netflix is one, and then there's a 30 for 30 on American?
Oh, I forgot this, yes.
I forgot my friend John Katz, who I don't know if he still works for Absolutely, but
he did for a while.
And he's involved in Santa Monica Democrats, Santa Monica political issues.
He was my boss on the American Gladiators remake, my college classmate, and hired all
of us on the incredibly disorganized 2008 one.
And just listeners, you may have heard this before, but if you don't remember, Jason was
one of the 2008 American Gladiators.
Yeah, I was Spudder.
He was Spudder.
I was very callous of you.
I would prefer not to take on my current state, but okay, if it's for the glory of the gladiators.
Yeah, do you think we have, we don't have any gladiators listening in the audience,
do you think?
Any of the group who, how many gladiators, honestly, how many people can officially call
themselves gladiators?
The answer to that depends on if you count the people in this show or not.
I do.
It's a fan website that certainly does count them, but I think by that point, my guess
is like 30.
Wow, that is low.
I was thinking 50, but yeah, I guess it would be.
Well, I don't know.
Well, then the new people, 2008 people, your pals Wolf and, do you remember the other?
Wolf and Phoenix.
Phoenix, okay.
Right.
Gina Carano.
Was Gina Carano one of them?
Yeah, I believe she was.
What was her name?
I don't remember.
I don't recall.
In the original?
No, no, in the 2008 agreement, the writer's strike filler version.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I think there's maybe more than 30, but maybe I'm wrong.
No, I guess maybe it's closer to 30.
She was crushed.
Wow.
Gina Carano was crushed.
And today she's crushing weak, woke minds with her defiance.
If you search American Gladiators live, you will find also there was a live touring version
of Gladiators in addition to this show having live in it.
Okay.
Oh, which I think planted the seeds of, well, this has worked on the road, so why could
there not be a permanent version?
And would that not be a good deal for some of the real Gladiators?
You don't even have to go on the road.
You got a family.
You bring the family.
Bring the family to Disney World.
You're 10 minutes away.
This certainly will not become a seedy, sad development that ends the franchise for at
least a decade after.
I might've, maybe I under did it.
I'm looking at a pretty big list.
You know, I got ones popping up.
I've never seen Raider and Rhino and Rio and Rocket.
I see Zap.
I see Khan.
Ooh, Khan.
Like Spalltow.
How?
Like Wrath of Khan-Khan.
Oh, wow.
Uh-huh.
Not C-O-N.
Not C-O-N, no.
You're starting to get to maybe a few dozen Gladiators?
Yeah, and also apparently there's a BBC version.
We can't.
American Gladiators.
Well, they talk about the British one in that video.
Oh, okay.
Because one of the guys, Thor, the guy Thor is from England and he kind of shits on the
English Gladiators.
He's like, you know, America's where it's at.
That's really what he, no offense to my British counterparts, but you know, America's wherever
the real action is.
Geez, wow.
So it wasn't bad, even though you're closer to the roots of jousting.
You would think.
That doesn't make for more quality jousting.
Yeah, but was it called England Gladiators?
English Gladiators.
That's such a different vibe.
Yeah.
That is such a more like, there's like, you get hit in the face with a glove to start
the match.
Maybe just, I believe, okay, it looks like just Gladiators.
I see that now.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
There's a whole list of those Gladiators, too.
It also inspired another show called Ice Warriors.
Oh, there was Gladiators in 2024.
Wow.
That's a British one?
It looks like it.
Yeah.
Wow.
So there probably is a whole new crop of Gladiators.
I'm also getting, not to get distracted here, I'm starting to get interested in Ice Warriors.
Gladiators type, it was on, it was like Gladiators, but on an ice rink and they all have even
cooler names because the names are longer because they do like Viking type, Krell the
Tormentor.
Wow.
That's great.
Morka the Fireblade, Thorgon the Beast, Zalan the Serene.
Wow.
Oh, nice.
Well, there's room for serenity in here, too.
I didn't know the ice ones.
I really like the martial arts.
WMAC Masters.
WMAC, yeah, what does that stand for?
Is this another syndicated?
It was on Fox.
After Fox Kids.
And it was like ninjas in a battle dome of some kind.
Geez.
But it was also kind of WWF storylines behind the scenes.
This was maybe a Saban related.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there was some Power Rangers elements to it.
Geez.
Filmed at Universal Studios Florida.
This is what I'm going to, I think what this episode will become is kind of like its own
little gladiator match within topics to like see what rises to the top as something we
want to keep talking about because there's more.
There's so many things that I'm hearing about for the first time via like especially other
dinner theaters.
Right.
There's a lot to unpack here.
Maybe we should start diving into the real, into the thing.
So anyway, so here's the idea.
We'll do like a greatest hits of the best and also cheapest to recreate gladiator.
They did the wall.
They didn't do the wall at the same size.
So they say as the wall on TV, you know, things look bigger on TV.
Probably should have done it bigger because it's in person.
Right.
Yeah.
But they also they had something that the show didn't have, which is a really tall American
flag.
The tallest, most patriotic flag you've ever seen.
Isn't that nice?
That's I think it's very nice.
So you know, what else?
Yeah, they had the wall.
So you know, it culminates in this in the same way.
But so, you know, definitely makes sense on paper.
Orlando sent an old article, you know, they bring up the gladiators to tour several years
ago and the live concept went over very well, said Steve Scarano, who brought together the
investor group that financed the dinner show.
You can watch it all with a meal for $39.95.
That's still the price.
Yeah, you're right.
That is still how much Pirates Dinner Adventure cost, I'm pretty sure.
So that's expensive for the time.
Yeah, seemingly.
But also the second show at the night was just the show, No Dinner.
That was $27.95.
This is what I would do at every one of these.
If you give me a non-dinner option, please, do any of them do this?
Do they all do it?
And I don't know.
The food is precisely what I want.
But I don't think there's food with Teatro Martini.
I don't know about that.
I bet there's a version of it.
I think there's options, but isn't it kind of in the outer lobby stage area?
Well, at least in point of part, we just said it's closed.
So I don't know what the Orlando setup is.
I'm seeing now this, I swear I paid $40 for my seat at the Vampirates, but I'm seeing
This is one of those things where there's 10 different types of discounts to get, depending
on what it's just like, whatever.
If you're like a, if you have low patience for finding deals, you'll pay $60.
But if you do two Google searches, you will easily find it for 25 to 30 to $40.
Anything in the Groupon range, they have to, they rely on things like this.
Groupon or what was the other one?
I don't know.
There was a Groupon competitor.
I don't know if it's still around.
There were a few, I think, but I don't recall.
Anyway, the, okay, so Scorano wouldn't say how much money he and other investors put
into the venture, but another producer, Blaustein, said it was up in the millions.
The show employs 213 people.
In classic chain restaurant endeavor kind of thing that we talk about, they're instantly
out of the gate talking about, we're going to do a ton of these.
We're going to do one in Vegas.
We're going to do one in London.
It's always the best.
That's the guy, the multi-city hubris.
That's the trademark of a guy too.
It really is.
And I'm not sure which one, I don't know that they're, the people talking right here
don't seem like guys, but there are guys, guys do come up and the guys might help
influence that thinking.
Yes, it's just guy.
It's typical guy thinking, whether it's said by a true guy or not.
Yeah, us on the cover of a book, typical guy thinking.
Typical guy thinking.
And it's, and there's like, like crooked martini glasses.
It's the book cover that every Chelsea Lately guest got.
That's going to be a best seller typical guy thinking.
Anyway, another person said, we liked it from day one.
We felt that the TV show is very popular and that Orlando needed something as an
alternative to other dinner theaters here.
And this is sort of the point that I was making.
And this is the rabbit hole that I started going down due to these Orlando Sentinel
articles is other related dinner theaters, including the one that occupied this theater
before American Gladiators came there.
So this space was not built for American Gladiators.
It was, I don't know if it was built for this, but this is what was there.
Something called Fortune Feast Dinner and Game Show.
This lasted less than a month.
We've come across some bombs in our time and this show you would consider American
Gladiators because it only lasted a couple of years, but I mean, that's that's
seeming like a global phenomenon compared to less than a month.
Yeah. Yeah.
I always I'm always mystified when I learn about Broadway musicals and stuff.
That like last less than three months.
And it's like that took years to mount.
That took so much money and so much manpower.
I didn't even make the six months.
It's got to be so broken to not even just like to sputter, sputter.
Yes. The headline from the Orlando Sentinel article, it says, and now, of course,
I just got an ad which took a Fortune Feast closes for some fine tuning.
Such as Entire Concept, Entire Business Plan, this thing.
So this was a little cheaper for only thirty five ninety five.
Here's what the OK.
Let me explain.
For Fortune, Fortune Feast Dinner, maybe Game Show.
Huh? OK. Here's what it was.
Was you're in Sherwood Forest.
It's Robin Hood and it's Merry Men and it's stealing from the rich
and giving to the poor, but stealing the rich and giving to the poor.
Couldn't we make that an interactive concept like a game show?
Like, let's make a deal.
So this was a Sherwood Forest Robin Hood game show.
Man, I am so in the weeds like I forgot all these details.
I was like, oh, OK, it'll be like a Jeopardy stage and you eat chicken or beef.
Mm hmm. And I'm like, no, it's Sherwood Forest.
It's gamified Sherwood Forest.
Yeah, gamified, gamified Sherwood Forest.
You mean like that they fight the king? No, no.
They you play games of skill and memory and chance.
You do fun games and it's what's behind door number two.
That is what happens in this Robin Hood thing. Yeah.
I we're talking a combination of let's make a deal
and all hell breaks loose in Sherwood Forest.
It's roast chicken and Robin Hood.
And then it was described by the guy who started it.
Bahram Korsandi, as I was trying to find a theme
that nobody had the rights to and take from the rich and give to the poor.
Went with my idea for a game show.
The audience can come in to eat and leave with a new car.
So in the search for something that no one if he is right,
no one had ever thought of it. Yeah.
And it is funny because I guess you could have done like,
let's make a deal live.
Yes, but that might require the rights to let's make a deal.
Unless you just have to change enough words.
Let us let you and I consider forging some kind of arrangement
that you could do.
Do we know like was Friar Tuck involved?
Don't know that. No, I don't know that.
It depends also on Robin Hood has been public domain for for a while,
I would think. OK, yeah.
And then I think the answer lies there.
I think if if Friar Tuck is public domain, then yes, he was in it.
OK, if not, like we could do like Sherlock Holmes was on the table,
probably I'm guessing he was probably he was he came to your table.
He was at this to he was also Sherlock Holmes is there.
Help Sherlock solve a mystery and win a Ford probe.
I don't even remember that car.
I don't even know.
I know I've never heard that in my life.
You may have made that up.
I don't know.
Ford probe. 50-50.
A glamorous Ford probe.
It's just fine.
Latchback. What year was that?
I don't know. They stopped making them 97.
When did people stop? That lasted less than a month.
That's way into but that's way into like alien stuff
where people just thought of probes is going up someone's rectum.
Yeah. That's too.
That's too recent for calling something the Ford probe.
That's bizarre.
If you want to go exploring uncharted territory,
find yourself deep in dark uncharted
territory and get yourself a probe.
Buy American for your probes.
Listeners, I don't know if you'd believe this, but
a lot of this stuff is not well documented or preserved.
No, not terribly.
But I did find a post on the Orange County Regional History Center.
And it is the cast and crew windbreaker.
Great. That was donated as a piece of history.
Yes, donated as a piece of history by.
Oh, I don't want to spoil your fun and say this name.
I'm sure you're going to get around.
Peter Blaustein.
Yeah, it was Peter Blaustein.
Well, the fun wasn't saying the name Peter Blaustein.
I'm a stupid. Yeah, but there's some details about Peter Blaustein.
A ton of details about Blaustein.
Let me first close out Bahram Korsandi
and say that I was curious, is there anything else about
Orlando game show entrepreneur Bahram Korsandi?
What happened to him after Fortune Feast and Dinner and Game Show went bust?
Well, apparently he was also involved in American Gladiators Orlando Live.
And I found this out through a deep Google where I discovered that
somewhere in him doing business with American Gladiators Orlando Live, he
he was arrested at Miami International Airport
in connection with one hundred and sixty grand not paid in state sales taxes.
My God. He pleaded no contest to a single count of theft of state funds.
Wow. So this is an you know,
the guy number one.
And it's a it's a mini guy because there is literally no more information.
But like one of the first names you encounter is a guy like here's
there's what we know about this guy. Robin Hood Game Show. Great.
Next thing we know about him sent to prison.
I mean, I'm sorry, not set to be arrested at the airport.
Forced to pay one hundred sixty grand.
What? Because he stole from he was robbing from the rich.
He was robbing the rich to give to the poor.
Himself is a poor, who I suspect is not maybe that poor.
But, you know, the same idea applies.
Could we win back the money we spent on these tickets for dinner in the show?
Oh, no, absolutely not. You'll never see that again.
Well, I was thinking about this like I do.
I envy these people who just can make something stupid happen.
Yeah, because it would be fun to have a bad dinner and see a show.
And you would be responsible for that, creating the whole thing.
Make it what seems fun.
But the inevitable amount of like the amount of money it takes to put this up
means you're going to have to get the money from weird places.
And then that means that you're probably a little bit looser with laws.
So probably a lot of like being mired in funding and people who fund things.
Right. You're going to get really tempted to start stealing.
Right. So much money.
And then you just that that money becomes meaningless to you at a certain point.
And then one hundred and sixty thousand is just like, whatever.
But here's the thing is that if you can successfully make the switch
to being one of these people, you get to do it into infinity until you die.
Well, you get to be the president.
If you get to be. Yes, obviously, the president is the biggest example.
The most famous example of this.
Another crowd. All right.
One more chance, but we'll see.
Yeah, we're also seeing it with it.
Like somehow people are giving money to the fire festival guy.
Yeah, right. Every right everywhere that it's supposed to.
Every every city he's saying he's doing it in saying he is not doing it here.
There is no thing.
I just watched a thing about this last night and like, you know,
you could go on a TV expedition with your favorite rapper.
People make phone calls. No rappers are attached.
There is one football player who has been somebody.
Forget who was on a Super Bowl winning team.
This is the music festival.
FireFest has booked one act and it's a football player.
Oh, it's an XFL play. He hurt me.
But he's loved. I'd go party with him.
And I'll be honest or whatever.
He's going to make a bunch of money again. Yeah.
Like, yes, it just that's how this works.
I don't understand it exactly. Yeah.
But he's one who went to jail.
Even if you're what?
Maybe especially if you're one of the ones who go to jail,
you get to do it again as many times.
And it's just a matter of like because I don't think you or I could get away with it.
I think I don't think so.
You have to you have to like just make this sweet.
You have to become this person fully.
Yeah. If you do so, you get 12 cracks at that bat.
Yeah. Before you go to jail and at dinner theaters,
we go to jail for two weeks and then get out and do another 12
and we'll go make all your contacts for the next time you do it.
Yeah. No, I know.
It's really we should try to put together like a comprehensive list of guys,
of like people who seem to have this ability to just either
scam people or at least just thrust their terrible ideas.
And I actually I'm very glad he is alive is a good idea.
I don't want to trash.
No, this one actually makes sense.
It's this is more an execution that it falls. Yeah. Right.
So there there was a guy going around the Internet the other day,
and he's like, when you drop out at Stanford after your first day
and then a month later, your most cracked out friends
join you to start building your startup.
And it's just the nastiest room full of like guys on MacBook Pros.
One of them has their shoes off and their feet up.
And then at some point, some of the most damning detail I've ever heard.
The guys are you just saying?
No, I've seen.
No, I this this was a thing that was going around.
And then at some point, it's like, yeah, we had an engineer.
He was passed out one day from working.
And so we had to put in air safety reminders
because it's just like everyone's like, I don't know what the ventilation
like is in that room to have a dozen people like working out of like
a one bedroom apartment, a studio.
We got drive. We got we got the juice.
We don't need air.
We got Riz.
Who needs heroin? You got Riz.
We're smelling this guy's feet.
He's got his feet out.
And it's like the fire festival guy where it's like, oh, they made one
app for credit card processing.
Or it's like this is a new kind of credit card.
And it just holds a lot on that a lot of events.
But you're like, I haven't seen him talk about the credit card in a while.
Jason, we should after we're done with this, you get your shoes off.
And we got work to do.
We need to start getting on our shoes off.
Mike, shut off the air.
All of us scramming in the closet over there instead of the lightly
bigger room that we're in.
Someone turn someone turn one of these monitors vertically for some reason.
That's good because we're thinking different.
We're flipping everything on its side script.
Yeah, I agree.
No, it's we got to figure out our scam.
After years of pitching perfectly good theme park
ideas that no one is taking, it's time to start doing it our way,
which is by stealing.
Yeah, I know.
If I had no like if I didn't have if I was like a single guy
and I had like nothing to lose, it does seem fun to try to be a weird scammy guy,
doesn't it?
It does.
You definitely see many people really seem like the type from the way
that you were raised to suddenly become a major scamster.
But then wouldn't that be fun?
Like that would be fun to go completely against your programming.
There's no one would suspect it.
No one would suspect it.
That's true. You have good cover.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I'm not doing it.
I think this guy's scamming us.
I listen to this podcast where he said all the stuff that his mom made him do.
Right. That would be that would hold up in court.
Thought a poster was going to land on his head and suffocate him.
Yeah. When I was like 10 people, I told I took five million dollars
from 10 different people and they were all suing me together.
And we would play clips of that.
And they would say, well, this man is innocent, Your Honor.
You know, like 10 years ago, the like
early streaming of 10 years ago in different websites and you know,
there was so much money flying around that some people just pocketed and disappeared.
Oh, yeah, of course.
It's all it's all.
That's what anyone was trying to do.
That's all it was, was being in the cash hurricane.
I grabbed I got a 20.
Yes, money, money, the Internet was just money laundering.
Comedy websites were money laundering.
But not happening, not like the fruitful,
trustworthy world of Orlando dinner in the 1970s and 1980s.
Now all of these now we start getting into people who I who I kind of like.
Peter Blaustein, as you said,
he was the producer of the show as far as the entertainment.
It seems like maybe do we all go down the rabbit hole of this person?
Because the rabbit hole of this person leads us to some people we really like.
Peter Blaustein was a longtime Disney guy.
He put together the opening ceremonies of Walt Disney World in 1971.
A lot of stuff for Disney program shows and stuff for them.
But at some point, he left Disney and went to work
producing dinner attractions for the company Orlando Entertains LLC.
He produced a show called King Henry's Feast.
He produced a show called Mardi Gras.
These were all on iDrive and Orlando Entertains LLC.
That name might not mean anything to you, but the guy who ran it
might mean something to you.
The name is Robert Earl.
Oh, the famed restaurateur.
He's always here.
The famous man who makes great sandwiches
for construction workers to fill up their hungry bellies.
It all started with King Henry's Feast.
You can feast like a king here in Orlando, Florida.
Yes, you can.
I'm going to make so much money for loud
Hawaiian shirts from King Henry's Feast.
Robert Earl is here.
So this guy is a this is a Robert Earl acolyte.
So the Robert Earl was not involved in American Gladiators, right?
Dinner. He would have made it work, I think.
Yeah, for three years longer than it actually is.
They're building the third or fourth location of the Earl of Sandwich
at Downtown Disney at this point.
And it's like a like finally like a dream campus.
Yeah, we're like a bar on the top of it or something.
This might be one of the best spots.
This is going to be fucking awesome.
I'm so excited about that in the portos.
Downtown Disney is where it's going to be where it's at.
Yeah. Thank you, Robert Earl.
We're all have sandwich briefly in the old La Brea Bakery space.
I think at some point was in like a temporary trailer.
Yeah, well, still is.
You can get you can get a sandwich on the way out by the ESPN zone.
But you also can get it at La Brea Bakery.
Well, much like Walt Disney Animation, which was shoved into a couple of bungalows.
Yeah, maybe everybody thought it was on the way out,
that it had lost the good graces of the Disney Corporation. Right.
But instead, it went there, it grounded out and it did its best work.
And just as then Disney Animation rose from the
rose from the ashes like a phoenix and made Beauty and the Beast in Aladdin
and entered its golden age, so will Earl of Sandwich
with its glistening new two story location.
It's going to be great.
Robert Earl wins again.
Would you describe the sandwiches as great? No.
Yeah, I was going to say that was really that did confuse me.
It's going to be great. The food, you mean?
No. Fine's a good
once in a while, you get a good one.
And usually it's fine.
Eight bucks or something. Nine dollars.
I still, by the way, I'm like, you know, there's a lot of like
and they got portos now and they got Dintai Fung.
I'm putting money on these ending up the worst portos
and the worst Dintai Fung in the entire organization.
That's a good point.
I don't that Dintai Fung looks cool, though.
I haven't had it there.
Oh, and I'm sure it's good now.
Well, sure.
Like if any location was going to start to lose the shine.
Yeah, it would be the downtown Disney.
But I could counter is Disney Springs.
Our rest, like the boathouse is still apparently where it's at
as far as like the quality hasn't dipped.
Now it's not a chain. Yeah, yeah, sure.
So what could could the magic be sustained?
I don't think Disney Springs is as bad as downtown Disney or City Walk.
Either. That's probably right. Yeah.
I think there's something that there's something
a more inherent quality going on.
Portos, Dintai Fung.
There's another place coming soon as well
that has different kinds of food and drinks.
I wouldn't I wouldn't get in.
It's like there's a lot of things.
Everything's under construction.
Stuff takes so long.
I just think there's so much vibrancy coming there and life will be injected
that I think I'm very optimistic about the future of downtown Disney.
Sorry, I looked at photos of it again.
And one of the photos that they've released is a chef
drizzling vinegar onto a bunch of tomatoes.
The place that you say is the most toxic.
No, I didn't.
Masculine. I didn't.
I said the market and like these signs.
But they've only released three pieces of marketing.
And one of the pieces of marketing is a man pouring vinegar onto tomatoes.
Yeah, it's just get image, probably.
Right. No, it's no, I don't.
You're accusing them of just buying.
I'm just saying that's very generic.
No, what you said is that it's faux masculine.
Is the faux masculinity in the vinegar or the tomatoes?
Which which part of the equation is the faux?
I thought just the black and gold.
I like I don't know.
It just it just drives me the wrong way.
I don't know. Leave me alone.
Look, it is my unfortunate to tell you that I will never stop
thinking about this opinion that you've asserted.
And I have one thousand questions.
I listened back to people sent me similar things.
It's it's something about when you just plop it down on butcher paper
or like a silver like just that.
But do we know that's what the restaurants like?
No, I just said that we only know the name and a picture.
And one of the pictures is a man putting vinegar on tomatoes.
And I like that.
Although I mean, we do like one of the three things
and we do like steak, but we don't like.
I think, well, I will write.
OK, I will write a list of things.
I have to collect my thoughts on this discussion.
And then we'll do it.
We'll do it on the Arthur and Sons episode.
I did not mean to open a can of worms.
Of course you didn't mean to.
But when you say things like that, cans of worms are open.
Here's what it was just funny, because you said it was very masculine.
And all we knew that it was called Arthur and Sons.
And there was a picture of some meat and a picture of a drink.
And I thought it was funny that out of context of like the aggressive,
like barbecue lifestyle with like menswear and this without any of that context.
I thought it was funny to refer to that as like faux masculine.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, sure.
Versus like the aggressive, like, hey, we have barbeque.
We have our smoker out here and the guys got the apron and they're doing the whole thing.
It felt very it did feel more generic, which is, I think, what you said.
The second. Yeah, I think that's what I was aiming for.
Yeah, I do tend to like barbecue.
I think there's more craft involved.
I think there's usually more flavor involved than just a regular thing.
What you just said is we got the smoker and then you said you like barbecue.
When is now? Why is barbecue the problem?
Look, it's not the problem for me, unless you're a vegetarian.
And I'm just saying if you have a smoker, that's basically a military weapon.
Look, Dean Norris has a smoker.
I'm excited about it.
Everyone's in full support of Dean Norris.
Of course we are.
I'm just saying that's more of the aesthetic
that I see a lot of where it feels like kind of aggressive in the way it's marketed.
Arthur and Sons feels very, very nothing.
It feels like nothing to me.
But a steak and bourbon to me is a good nice treat once in a while.
You know what I'm saying?
I would agree. It's all just opinions.
I just like a sloppy pile of pulled pork.
I don't know. What do you want to know?
Well, you're not. You can like that.
You can like. Yeah.
Do you think it's insane that people like steak and bourbon together?
No, I was just saying.
You can't deny that this is a combo that people have.
I don't really like those things that much.
That's fair.
It was stated as if like it in and of itself was a problematic combo.
It's just seemed a little generic to me.
It just kind of rubbed me the wrong way.
I've not really explored. Not like a nice dry rub.
That's rubbing you the right way.
I like a mustard base or a vinegar base.
I think usually from the Carolinas.
Here's what I think.
I think Arthur and I think we're all going to get a meal we really enjoyed.
Arthur and sons, bourbon and steak.
I think when you find when you realize that that's not the only things that they have.
Well, here's the thing.
It's going to be a nice meal because we're at downtown Disney
and it's going to taste at least a letter grade higher,
especially if there's like a porch or something.
And if there is any problem with it, it will be due to the fact
that it is a restaurant at downtown Disney. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. This is the greater enemy.
And maybe we even like had a nice little time at the patio
part of Earl of Sandwich before we go to Arthur and Sons.
The future city walk.
I have more of a mystery about what it's going to be either.
But I think downtown is going to be good.
I am excited about the future of downtown Disney.
No, no one wants to get in on this with me.
I'm a little more skeptical. OK.
Well, the I feel like one of the best meals we have there,
Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen within just a few years.
It was stripped of like.
Well, the personality of that person definitely sucks.
Yeah. Personality of the place certainly was stripped.
I agree. But we don't know if the food is bad.
We don't know if the food got worse, do we?
One thing I know is that the big rolling hills,
like the big grassy area that they put in is one of the biggest hits
in recent Disney history. Yeah, it is.
There are so many children.
Yes. Running, having the time of their life.
Now, does this go against some things that I said about,
I don't know, certain types of things you put on the ground?
Gras, you might say.
Oh, that was referring to different grass.
You know what? That grass, that was a photo of grass
that was very tiny and it's mainly used for stroller parking.
Yeah, this grass is rolling and giant.
Yeah. And there's like there's dimensionality to it.
And I got no beef with this grass.
My son had a lot of fun on the grass. Yeah, no, I the grass is all
we've we've had a lot of fun on the grass the last year or two of Disneyland.
Yeah. So my daughter.
The grass is good. The grass is green.
It sounds like one that they did deliver based on the concept
or there was a lot of grass.
Yeah, no, it's absolutely true.
And so the future is so bright.
This is the most optimistic I am about the country.
It's just specifically at downtown Disney.
At least one that's the only zone of several blocks in this country.
Yeah, it's going to be better than it's ever been.
Yep. OK, back back to all this.
So now we're dealing with a guy who used to be in the Robert Earl
enterprise.
Now I know about King Henry's Feast.
Now I know about Mardi Gras.
And where all this ties together is that Peter Blaustein went
to go work on a new show for Robert Earl.
And all of this information is on the website of a guy named Ron Schneider.
Ron Schneider was the original actor who played Dreamfinder in Epcot,
the face character, the walk around guy.
He also played a character who's come up on the show before.
Old C.L.
Whomp Hopper. God bless him.
This guy is back.
A man who is Dreamfinder and who is C.L.
Whomp Hopper has entered the world, has entered the domain.
There was always a crossover that we didn't know about between C.L.
Whomp Hopper and Robert Earl.
And here it is. It happened.
So this guy's friend leaves Disney to go work for Earl.
He's starting a new concept.
And he asks Ron, are you ready to maybe
hang up the big purple hat and join?
And and he went and worked with Peter
and Robert and made a third I drive dinner show called the Fort Liberty
Wild West Dinner Show.
All of these on the same stretch.
You can go to every one of them.
Can you eat each meal?
I wish you could eat like breakfast, lunch and dinner at different
theater shows on I drive.
Spend your entire day, the whole day, all three meals.
Yeah. Three great shows.
It all only costs you one hundred and twenty dollars.
Yes. Assuming that they don't get you with extra add ons.
What a time.
I mean, I don't think I really like how much Robert Earl made I drive.
And it's all still in his shadow.
You know, right.
Is there there's there's a book of De Beppo there. It's all there.
So here.
So this guy, none of this is central to American Gladiators.
I just I'm so excited that there's more restaurants we know about.
So here's quote Ron Schneider.
I'd seen King Henry's Feast and was wary of working for Robert Earl.
The food was OK, but I'd found the show to be rather dull.
I thought King Henry's Feast was beautifully produced,
but too authentic and stuffy.
If I'm going to create a show from scratch, I want it to be exciting
and truly funny with a good plot and audience participation integral to the story.
So with the first time that former Dream Finder
and Seal Mom popper meets Robert Earl, Robert says,
Ronald, I need you to understand one thing about me.
I charge people twenty eight dollars for a meal that costs me one fifty.
I put on a show so they won't complain about the food.
Quote Ron Schneider.
Do you mind if the show is good?
Not at all.
Then we'll get along fine.
Cool. That's a scene I want to film.
I want if there was any desire for.
All right. Guess what?
Guess what, Hollywood Studios, we're making Robert Earl the movie.
Oh, we are finally telling the story.
And who's that now?
He runs restaurants just up the streets, up at the top of the studio.
What is that now? Oh, God.
Is that place still open?
Yes, it is.
I've why me and the host of a show I do and the listeners of the show
talk about it all the time.
So if that's a random sampling of the American populace,
everyone's thinking about Robert Earl and his restaurants at all times.
You sure it didn't just become a grocery outlet, bargain market,
because I swear I know most things did.
I know most things did.
It's it's so funny, too, that he's just like,
oh, I feed these little piggies slop.
They don't mind because they're distracted like doesn't matter.
He's really like that is such a like a shitty evil thing to say.
Yeah, yeah. The food is awful and they don't care.
I put a little dose of OK sauce on top of dog food
to where you can't tell that it is dog food on first bite.
You will buy the sixth bite.
But by then, you're engrossed in this show and you want to know
all that King Henry's feast.
I need you to remember the acronym SFS slop for slobs.
Is that a real one?
No, because I would have believed that.
Yeah, you can imagine it, right?
That was a secret.
Someone's listening who is in the organization
and they're picturing the poster and they're like, my God.
Yeah. How did Jason know?
I'm going to get a cease and desist because they trademarked the term.
Or Robert is going to like hire you.
Because he's impressed.
You get it. Someone gets it.
Brilliant. Brilliant young man.
Yeah. But then what happened to him?
We're like, we put on a show so you can't tell that the food is terrible.
Years later, Bucatepepo, there's no show.
I think everyone's left to figure it out.
Yeah. It's looking at the head of the pope in a glass cube counts as a show.
Yeah. Any number of podcasters, they just come and spend money
and they want to sit in the pope room by the deformed statue
of Pope John Paul's sack.
Also, by the way, in an episode, I don't know, like a month or so ago,
I asked if anybody pre-gamed Conclave
at the Universal Cinema by going to the Bucatepepo
and asking for the pope room and that I never heard anything else about that.
And I forgot that I said it.
And then all of a sudden, last night, friend of the show,
past guest Joe Quazzalla texted, I did it.
I did conclave pre-game in pope room or I tried, but we didn't have enough people.
So they turned us down.
I pulled over to the side of the road to tell you this.
I could not wait to tell you this.
Wow. So one hero out there.
That's great. At least tried.
Were you getting maybe I'm getting ahead of you.
Did you see what happened to King Henry's?
Are you going to get there? No.
What happened to King Henry's?
It turned out it's an olive garden.
Great. Great.
Yeah, I think all of I think Mardi Gras is a Walgreens.
None of these exist.
None of these, even if Orlando locals are listening,
maybe you remember them faintly from long ago.
But none of them exist today.
On Stage Entertainment, Inc. of Las Vegas, the company best known for the legends
and concert impersonator shows, more guys,
acquired King Henry's feast, blazing pianos and wild bills, dinner theater,
including for liberty from then owner Orlando entertains.
But on stage ran into financial difficulty, sustaining major losses
from the now closed Daytona Beach
and Toronto shows of legends and concert on December 9th, 1999.
Whatever the mortgage holder on King Henry's Theater
obtained a foreclosure judgment against the company after late and missed payments.
And poor old Henry, old King Henry's was subsequently dethroned.
And then on June 22nd, 2000, the feast ended and the castle closed.
The valuable I drive real estate kingdom on which it sat
was redeveloped into a less kingly olive garden.
So the olive garden, I guess, is the olive garden still there on I drive?
I bet it is.
Probably. It seems like it would be.
Olive gardens don't seem to be having a lot of trouble.
No, they do. Yeah, they they thrive.
Good margins. Yeah, yeah.
Let me tell you, the olive garden food costs 125, but we charge 29 for it.
Doesn't that take some?
Don't you want to think that on some level, Robert
Earl was like, I want to give good food to the people.
Like, I want to believe that on some level he believes that the food is good.
It's that he's now he's like a Kraven supervillain.
I don't know. I guess I'm not surprised.
I mean, I guess I'm not surprised either.
I just want to know.
He is like synonymous with restaurants that are uniformly bad.
Yeah, we ever is.
Are any of the Earl restaurants any good?
Yeah, good question. Probably not. Chicken guy.
Chicken guy's not bad.
I mean, yeah, we liked I don't know how it's doing now, but it's a more even
handed that guy influence. Right.
Cut me a deal. Got to make the food good.
Olive Garden, yes, is still there.
OK, well, we should all honor its memory as we pass by that all good.
You met this time.
It's just this time where like there is a fort.
There's an old West Fort and there's a castle.
And yeah, sure, half of that stuff is still there.
But I want all of it to be there.
And it's yes, the world's largest McDonald's is there,
but it doesn't look nearly as stupid as it used to know.
This was the stupidest street in America.
There is so much what happened.
Decay and it's so decaying now.
When you draw like parts of I drive.
Yeah, because I walked a big stretch because my plane kept getting delayed
on that Monday and I ended up walking all the way down to the Hooters,
walking all the way back.
You're just walking along I drive.
I did. Oh, I walked so much that Monday.
I was at City Walk.
I walked through the hotels and then I ended up on I drive.
You want to walk up to the Hooters, open the door, closed your eyes, said,
you all should be ashamed of yourselves, slammed the door and marched away.
Yes. I saw the seafood place
that had like a big three different cars that deliver
seafood with giant crabs.
Did you see this? I posted this on Instagram.
These photos were insane.
I'll show you these. Talk amongst yourselves.
OK, it's crazy. They were crazy.
Like I drive is I mean, we just there's a lot to learn about it.
There's a lot about its history is a lot about what it is today.
I think we could do a trip where we only do I drive
and don't go to parks.
Oh, God. A Boston lobster feast on I drive has,
I guess, a fleet of vehicles that look like this.
Wow. A giant lobster on the lobster is bigger than the car itself.
Yeah. Is that street legal?
I know they're like VW bugs.
That looks like an accident happened in a in a parade in a crazy movie,
like Jingle All the Way.
Yeah, he was driving through Lobster Day, the parade.
And then like and then it ends up attached to his car.
And he's like, ah, if you order seafood from there,
I think you get it delivered in a VW bug with a giant lobster
attached to the top of the car.
It looks like the the red VW bug is being delivered
like at like a baby by the lobster. Yeah, it does.
And I was so excited.
Mike, I know you want to be optimistic,
but those kind of look like 20 year old VW bugs
that have been moved in a long time.
You think they're just parked there for 20 years?
Yeah. No, I think that they look like the paint looks sort of new.
Orlando listeners, let us know.
Have you seen this proud fleet of lobster cars?
I mean, maybe you're going around your neighborhood.
Let us know or if not, send them your way.
Order Smith, place an order and watch this armada arrive in your house.
A lot of this thematic decay that you're talking about
kind of reminds me of family friendly era Vegas.
Yes, where a lot of stuff is still standing
and a lot of it has been torn down and the stuff that's still standing.
Some of it is begrudging, like begrudging
that we have to run a knockoff medieval times and Excalibur
that we have to do with.
Do you think it's begrudge? I bet people like that.
I know. I think people like I think guests like it.
Mm hmm. But you think that would you think that would tell is like,
let's just put a cheap gastropub in here.
Just like throw some stencil art up.
Yeah. I'd have to pay all these performers
or like the roller coaster in New York, New York.
And it's like we could take this stuff down
and have another room of slot machines and make the same amount of money.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Yeah, yeah.
Yes. Well, yeah, that roller coaster is begrudgingly kept up
like the like the person doing the repairs, I think.
I was barely fine.
I'll fix one of the five screws.
It was unpleasant like 19, 20 years ago when I went on it.
So I can't imagine now. I don't think it ever worked.
Anyway, none of this has anything to do with America.
Just I guess it's it's all to say the pedigree of people
who were putting this American gladiators experience to get a guy,
an acolyte of Robert Earl himself, a friend of C.L.
Whomp Hopper, a Padawan of Robert.
This is the story of Dorff Plagueis, the wise
and a guy who I consider a roguish Han Solo type character,
Barham Korsandi, who marches to the beat of his own drum
and doesn't care if his game show idea doesn't make any sense
or if he ever gets caught at the Miami airport for stealing from the state.
These this is the rogues gallery putting together this remarkable thing.
And that's not all, because the real stars of the show,
I think we've got a name.
I'm just going to say all of the gladiators who you could see at this show.
Some were from the TV series.
Some were new additions just for Orlando.
And here is the heart of the show.
Dallas flame flash hawk ice.
Jade jazz laser quake saber siren
sky tank Thor Titan tower man in tower turbo viper
Cobra rage raven electra and Tigra.
Yeah. Yeah.
That now that that's like a like a list of random words
that I would say into a computer so that now I could be scanned
and used as a forever. Oh, yeah.
Just just put all that in and you can steal my voice after I'm dead.
So that's the group.
Now, I don't remember who exactly is from the show
in this infomercial that you referred to, Mike.
You definitely meet some people who were from the show.
Let's see that.
I know that I'm going off the Netflix documentary.
Sky is original TV American laser ice.
Someone named Dan, I don't remember what his gladiator name was,
but Dan came for several shows and then
realized it was shady and got out of there.
Would be great if you saw Jade and laser and
turbo and then Dan.
He's proud of who he is.
He doesn't need to impress you with a fancy word.
He loves himself.
Zap did not go, quote Zap in the documentary.
I didn't go. I'm so happy I didn't go.
That was a debacle.
And it's hard to tell exactly what made it a debacle.
This is what's a little mysterious.
I guess we can go off of that infomercial a little bit
that shows the promise of what it was and what it could be.
You meet some of the newer gladiators.
They get some sit down time with the host of the infomercial, John Romano.
There's a sit down between John Romano and a guy named Tank.
I love Tank.
I'm really glad we got so much time with Tank, so much more than the other
gladiators that you meet.
Tank tells you during his interview, I strive on excellence.
It's not I don't think of the word.
He I don't want him to be smart.
I want him to be strong.
A couple of things in there where I don't know that he's using language correctly.
It's not so far off.
No, I know what he's going for.
Yeah, they follow Tank to jungle land
where you see exactly the kind of man Tank is.
He meets up with Jeff Quattrochi.
I regret not writing that down.
Thank you for catching that, Mike.
So Tank and Jeff Quattrochi
start looking around at all the wild animals you can see at jungle land.
I guess another Kissimmee attraction.
And Tank decides it's not enough just to look.
He wants to wrestle.
He wants to get in there and get up close and personal with some gators.
And he like, yeah, he's like he touches him.
He's like got him by the mouth.
He keeps like being like, I'm not going to hurt these.
Don't worry. I'm not hurting him.
Then he's like he's like shoving his chin to force an alligator's chin
close, like an alligator's mouth closed.
And you're like, guess you're not hurting him.
Well, you got to be annoying animal.
Yeah. Animal doesn't need you doing that.
Yeah. Yeah. The animal probably wants to.
Yeah. The gator wants to be able to open and close its own mouth.
Gator jaws closed gently, right?
As far as I know. OK.
That's what Tank believed, at least in filming this piece.
Tank also then he climbs on top of the hundred and twenty six foot
alligator that is out front of jungle land.
I want to know more about jungle land as well, quite frankly.
Then at the end of the piece, he tells you, I'm not the prettiest one,
but I can guarantee I'm the craziest one.
So Tank, Tank, Tank's great.
You meet Titan, you meet Dallas, you meet Thor.
You meet Flash.
Flash touts his own agile-ness.
Yes, I caught that as well.
No, they're not really the word.
Yeah. I found out Flash was hired to be a referee for the show.
And then original series gladiator Viper got sidelined.
And before you know it, this guy became Flash.
Yeah. You're in Flash.
The most interesting of the.
I don't know. Tank's probably the most interesting.
But eventually you meet a female gladiator by the name of Siren.
You get a bunch of time with Siren.
John Romano, the host, seems especially eager to talk up Siren,
seems really fawning over Siren in particular and telling you all about
Siren's life story and how Siren went deaf very sadly when she was very young.
But that did not stop her from becoming exceedingly strong
and winning a lot of bodybuilding competitions and getting into America's
Cup, the yachting competition.
And you're kind of like, why are we going on and on?
So I mean, this is all nice, but like there's an energy here.
And then he says, and she's probably got to be one of my favorite.
Let's say my the favorite, my favorite of all gladiators in the show,
because I happen to be married to her. So he goes, she I think he goes,
she's my wife or something like he gets so like cute.
He gets like so like mushy all of a sudden,
because I actually didn't know where it was going.
I'm just like, he's really talking about her a lot.
And then he also goes like, she's my wife.
Maybe I shouldn't say that, but that was the vibe.
That's what I remember.
He got all like, like that.
That was the energy all of a sudden.
This is the toughest, toughest gal you're going to see out on the floor.
And also.
So then I start having a lot of questions at this point.
Don't get me in this interaction.
Everything seems fine, but I'm also like, why?
Why is this guy the host of this?
And I thought I saw him in the documentary clips, too.
He's the host of the live show as well.
He's the person who introduces the gladiator dancers is the kind of thing
that tells you maybe this won't be like as good as the show if they are killing
time with dancing and if they are killing time with something
that Siren gets to do, which is because she's deaf.
She does a performance of Heal the World of Michael Jackson's Heal the World
using sign language, yes, sung by the most questionable Michael Jackson
impersonator you've ever and all of this.
Like, well, like, all right, that's that's nice and fine.
But also you're like, what's the show, though?
Like it's so why is that gladiator?
Yeah, it seems like a lot of extra stuff.
And then, like, I'm there to see the thrust or whatever.
I'm not here to see John Romano.
Who's John Romano?
And there's there was just enough
shadiness to this guy that I started having some questions about John Romano.
I do some googling about John Romano.
I discover that he became because I was like, is he part of it because he's
married to Siren or did they meet doing this?
Like, what what brings him into the picture?
And it's that he met her when they were both bodybuilders.
And he said, I'll become your manager.
And also, let's get married.
The best arrangement that you can have.
If you're looking for a manager, choose your significant other.
Oh, just a little bit of basically I just all right.
Let me just like look up a few interviews with John Romano, bodybuilder,
pretty quickly find an interview where he's saying a bunch of stuff about how,
well, I ended up in Mexico because my wife kidnapped my child.
That's where he is today.
He runs a gold's gym in Mexico.
He also started talking about another bodybuilder.
And they said, where did you meet him?
He said, in prison.
This guy also did some jail time.
He was a commodities and stockbroker.
He went to jail for wire fraud.
OK, a lot of like a lot more white collar crime this episode than I was expecting.
I know with gladiators you think it's like I went to jail for jousting a guy's head
off, that it's all the boring reasons to go to jail.
Why did you go to prison?
Because I wouldn't rat out the group of guys who were ultimately culpable.
I was the one exposed.
It was me. I was a hero for going to jail.
So, I don't know, a bunch of weird stuff.
And I was like, wait a minute.
So he was married to the gladiator.
And then so they must have had a kid together.
And then something shady happened and she
left with the and then I kept going, no, married a different gladiator.
He was married when this started.
He was married to Siren when it ended.
He was married to Electra, had a kid with her.
Isn't that always the way?
So this was gladiator on gladiator cheating.
This guy is still around and I have a number of questions
just about him and Siren, who had a very sad life.
And I have questions about what happened there and comments lead me to believe
that's not good, but also this guy, I think, is a proponent of steroid use.
So I don't know if I want him coming after me.
Just we may have a guy on our hands if you watch this infomercial.
Is he the guy that wrote this cookbook called Muscle Meals?
Why, yes, that is one of his claims to fame.
I also saw the cover of Muscle Meals.
Describe the cover of Muscle Meals.
Well, he is shirtless.
He's got a big whisk.
It's a big whisk, too, like a really extra big whisk.
And he's got a big chef's, a big, tall chef's hat on.
And it says a cookbook to build muscle and lose fat.
It says Muscle Meals, delicious, low fat, high protein recipes by John Romano.
The giant chef's hat and the giant wick.
And he is so muscly and so shirtless, because shirtless as you can be and kind
of oiled up, it's a hell of a cover. It's a very good cover.
He also is so much thicker today than he was when any of this was done.
This is a massive man.
He's like, I guess, like Stallone is really big at age 80.
So and like seems sometimes bigger than he was when he was younger.
Yeah. So, yeah, similar situation.
It's a strange.
I just don't. It felt very like you guys must come across people like this
in the wrestling world. Really? Who is it?
Is he one of the guys? No, he's like a promoter.
But now why is he on camera?
And people are just kind of like, oh, yeah, fish their way into things.
And what it leads to ultimately, there's this clip in the Gladiators
documentary that's kind of showing you how this whole thing was the nadir of like
you've just heard one of the Gladiators say the whole thing was sad.
And, you know, you go from like you're
on TV and everybody's cheering you in a TV studio to now you're on a dirt floor
and people are eating pork chops and and then they play a home video clip.
And I think that's this guy, Romano.
And he says, all right, thanks for coming out, everybody.
Remember tomorrow, the Gladiator Grand Christmas Buffet from seven to eleven.
The Gladiators will be there.
You should be too. Drive safe, everyone.
I just remember a thing that stuck out to me in the Orlando Sentinel article was
the phrase, a number of the people have moved their families to Orlando
because ended with the justification of like, well, look, Gladiators only tapes
a few weeks of the year, so it's actually better.
So everything got to go somewhere more work.
This is better than the show.
We they should be glad that they're here.
Yeah, we give them the extra pork chops.
I want to move my family to Orlando, so I'm jealous in general of it.
I feel like clock's ticking on that one.
Yeah, I can feel it. I know the days.
I think I say to a different person every day in the last two or three weeks.
Yeah, well, we could move to Orlando.
I when we were down when we were just down there at some point, I told Aaron,
Mike's going to do it.
I just could feel it.
If I look, if I had no connection to any family or anything else.
Yeah, I'm gone.
Well, you got to fix that.
You got to sever your connection to that family.
My wife better not kidnap my child.
Then I'll be able to go to Orlando.
Then I'll be able to go to Orlando guilt free.
So it actually, you know, it actually worked out because, you know,
there were some disagreements with my wife, but I was able to come down here
and finally achieve my dinner theater dreams.
It's something I've been talking about
on this podcast that I stopped doing. I got rid of them, too.
And I came down here.
I gained 100 pounds in muscle weight and I and I run this awesome dinner theater.
I feel like I served the shittiest steak
in the shittiest bourbon to a bunch of a bunch of dudes.
It sucks. The food sucks.
I spent 25 cents per meal, the lowest quality steak and lowest quality.
But it's protein.
Fucking animals will eat it.
They don't give a shit.
You want to say, hey, you want to tell me there's anything full about this
masculinity, rip your shirt off, flex.
I'm bigger than John Romano now.
It's my new life.
Mike weighs 360 pounds.
I do feel like 10 years talking about wrestling.
We're out of connection.
I feel like Mike was like, you know, you know, you can buy creativity or like
human growth hormone when properly administered.
It's G or what's the one that's good for your joints and skin?
It's just powder, your collagen, collagen.
And a lot of questions for Jane about red lights.
This is we're going to come to we like at some point, Mike is going to leave.
We're going to go visit Mike.
He's going to have the home that is seven times bigger than what we have combined
here. And he's going to he will live in it alone, but he will be alone.
He'll be essentially like a human refrigerator size wise.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
I did find and jaw wise, you'll be as square as a refrigerator and I'll be young
looking to Jason Scott.
Oh, my God. It's been a minute.
Why is your hair that color?
Why is your hair so white?
Come on. Can I get you guys anything?
Twenty raw eggs.
Anything.
And this is Jason.
You come around on that yet.
You will. I'll make you do it.
I know the good stuff.
And I got black and gold in the office here.
I want you to enjoy the aesthetic.
Makes me feel good.
This is outlaw.
This is I go by outlaw now.
It's funny. You gave me that name as a joke in that one episode.
And I thought, huh, I can see that I can really see that.
I'm talking to a couple of guys that I met overseas about investing in a couple
of different restaurant ventures.
You guys want to end?
There's a lot of.
Everyone talks about the hair science in Turkey,
but the cuisine science coming out of there.
I'm also marketing a new line of hair growth tonic.
I also what I figured out.
So I'm talking to the Ninja Turtle guys to try to get the rights.
I think they're going to come around.
But if they don't, it's just it's just they can't copyright the word turtle
and they can't copyright martial arts in general.
So it's the it's the turtle martial arts dinner theater.
You root for whichever.
And we know we're prepared to use different Renaissance painter names if we have to.
Yeah. And look, I got look, I can fall right back on Battletoads.
I got the guy who owns the Battletoads.
He's ready to go. He wants to get in on this.
He's going to invest in my hair growth tonic, too.
And so he's really like, I'm in my back pocket.
No problem.
You guys make yourself at home.
What do you want? You want the guest room over here, Jason?
There you go.
This is all future builds to the karate
tortoise grand champions dinner explosion.
Yeah, that is a water bed, Jason.
Now it's
the tortoises live in the bed.
They like it in there.
It forces them to seal their jaws shut.
This is what they they prefer, actually.
I take them out to wrestle with them.
Then I put them back in the water bed.
I'm not hurting them. Don't worry.
I'm training them to not be able to use
that snapping jaw to give to veer to pry that mattress open with their mouth.
We lost a couple.
No, they didn't die.
It's just law. I don't know where they are.
Remember, a turtle's tail is also its dick.
Keep it in mind.
Keep it in mind while you're playing with them.
That was another thing. I always ran from that.
And then I looked then I looked at that Leonardo one day.
I saw I saw a big throbbing hog and I said, that's what I need to be like.
I like not like him.
Like the hog is tilled.
It is green and green like dollars.
That's that's all bad for me for me outlaw.
I see green everywhere I go.
I see Everglades green.
I see green dollars.
I see green karate tortoises.
Hey, Jason, come on, make yourself at home in the bed.
Why is he only talking to me?
Jason, Robert Earle's fucked on that bed.
I got a camera in there.
I got it from the love sponge.
He comes over here sometimes up from Tampa.
Give me his sex cameras.
I got tape of Robert Earle, man.
You want to watch it?
I'm not going to name names.
But I remember we wondered once if the Gladiators ever listened to the show.
Well, don't know about that.
But I've had sex with three of them.
I got the tape. You want to watch them?
You want to watch the tape?
I got the tape here.
It's all shot in Bubba Vision.
Jason, come on.
It looks like you're going to throw up.
You're not eating your steak.
My life coach is coming over in like an hour or two.
He's more of a guru.
Do you remember Rick Flair?
He's got this energy drink.
He's 95.
One more match.
We're going to do one more match.
He's only wrestled 20 times this last year.
The old guy wrestlers get super strength when they punch.
You guys seen my daughter around?
She driving by now?
No, I think she's 10.
Cars don't.
Also cars. You don't need to drive cars anymore, man.
It's the future.
I choose to.
It burns as much fossil fuel as possible.
Yeah, I'm an old school guy for a lot of things.
Old cars powered by coal.
My politics are old school too.
2025 politics.
Got Trump on my podcast.
He's 95 too.
Hey, he's fucked on the bed too.
God, it's water bad.
It's really sturdy.
It must be all the tortoises.
I didn't film that one just to be safe.
But, you know, if you're wondering if there was a little white lotus action.
Yeah, I might have done a little raise your hand.
Go to the bathroom. Is that what you're about to say?
No, no, I was going to talk about.
You were about to raise your hand.
I was like, oh, Jason, go to the bathroom.
But we're on a roll here.
No, I was going to talk about some remnants of American Gladiators live.
Yes. Yeah.
So the building is still standing.
The building sure is still standing.
Is it called?
Correct me if I'm wrong, but the name.
Is it the Church of the Rock?
It's the Rock Church.
The Rock Church is that.
The building closed and the building.
This dinner arena is has since the closure of American Gladiators been a church.
It has been a church for so many years,
for so much longer than it was ever Fortune Feast or American Gladiators.
That this, if anything, could inspire me to start going back to church.
If this was my local church and it's where it's where Outlaw will go.
I go to church, I go four times a week
and they left some of the lifting stuff backstage.
So
well, I mean, the hunkiest priest you've ever seen.
Chaplain.
In the chaplain get down, we lift.
I was not.
I could not tell if it was like Jesus is my rock or if it was a rock and roll church.
Oh, no, no, no.
Although that would have been a very good idea for a dinner theater experience.
Another one that Outlaw could try to open while he's down there.
No, it's well, the sign still says Orlando Arena on it
as if it is the main arena in the town.
But in fact, Orlando Arena equals the rock church.
And then you can like, OK, here's what's this.
It was this way during American Gladiators, too, is that it was a mixed use venue.
So this footage of it in the Netflix
documentary and it is like, I mean, I love it aesthetically.
There's like a light, the lightest art
deco, the worst art deco you've ever seen.
And kind of some Miami style, just like pink neon stripe.
Really like it aesthetically.
But then it's because like they built it to where like, oh, and we can charge for
stores that are underneath that are in the same.
So there's like at the in the 90s, it was a T.C.
T.C.B.Y. yogurt and then just like a liquor store.
And today they're like, here's the sign, the rock church.
There's a nails place, Indian restaurant, Farmer's Insurance.
So Farmer's Insurance is just built into this mega church.
Yeah, there's a Dippin' Dots,
the brick and mortar store next door.
I heard about Dippin' Dots.
Yeah, I saw that.
Have you ever been to a Dippin' Dots brick and mortar store?
I don't think so. Always just dance.
And you're a Dippin' Dots guy.
I love Dippin' Dots.
Yeah, yeah. This is an episode.
I know, we've been talking about that for a long time.
Let's do Dippin' Dots.
There's as of 2023, there was another remnant.
Oh, I found there's a YouTube short, a vlogger went and there is a
I've never heard this phrase before,
like a souvenir shop kind of adjacent to the Church of the Rock.
And it says everything to $2.49 or less, that's $2.49.
And on the wall of hats,
there is a line of pristine American Gladiators Orlando live hats.
Wow.
So you may be able to still find a brand new hat.
You can find this is an Orlando vlogger I've seen before, Mr.
Nooks and Crannies.
It was a funny day.
We use videos and I stayed at a lot of hotels.
I've looked up, you know,
but I get Mr.
Nook and Crannies over Travis Waterman.
You can get a swole.
So, yes, so if you're in Kissimmee,
pop over to the $2.49 or less souvenir shop and you may be able to find
an American Gladiators live hat.
Wow.
I would like that.
I mean, that's like for a year.
That's all I knew about this place,
that there was briefly an American Gladiators thing and that it quickly
turned into a church and I've like I've looked it up on Street View before,
like long before we did before there was a podcast.
It's just like, what does that look like?
And there's a little, there's a little art deco thing.
Like they tried to make it look cool and hip once.
But now it's just and it's just a couple of stray details on the way out.
Because like another few other things you notice in that old footage where it's
up above the liquor store in the TCBY, it says American Gladiators dinner theater.
And it's in a logo that resembles the font of the show, but is not the font of the show.
I was watching this with Erin.
As she pointed out, you never hear that theme song.
You hear Mortal Kombat and other songs they probably don't have the rights to.
But they probably the one that they had to and we could use the song, right?
No. Whoever that was.
That's like a great composer.
I forget who wrote the
Bill Conti or something, Gladiators theme.
Bill Conti, yes.
Al Nathot in one.
I want to say.
Yes. Yeah.
Rocky Square composer.
Batman too.
Did he also? No, that's a different guy.
Anyway, sorry.
But yeah, the original man.
Yeah. Who's Neil?
Neil Heft?
I'm confused.
I'm confusing Hefty and Conti is what I'm doing.
Is that his name? Hefty?
Neil Hefty.
Anyways.
But so, yes, no theme, no.
So it's this weird where they have the rights and they have some of the people,
but like not exactly so good.
So it's all a little bit wrong.
I know that's some of the bit where it's a little bit.
It's kind of a copy of a copy.
Something's wrong with it.
Is this sanctioned or not?
I also like that in the infomercial, the number to call to get information is
one eight hundred battle four.
Yeah, they keep saying that.
And they make people say it's a tank.
Where can they go to?
And they make sirens sign it.
So everybody's got a plug one eight hundred battle four.
And there's not like there's not much more to.
Nobody went and filmed the thing.
I know YouTube.
So that's I can't speak to the quality of it.
The only thing as far as what it was
or the aftermath of it is that all the gladiators, it basically it has the slot
in the gladiator documentary that OJ in Miami and Vegas has where it's just like
and it's oh, it's all it's coming apart here.
This is where it gets shady.
And I don't think anything horrible happened while everyone was dead.
But it was just like absolute misery for everyone.
It made them realize this chapter is over.
We can't just cling on to this lifestyle that we like.
The show is done.
We've got we got to move on.
We have to see who we are now.
And a number of the gladiators seem to have like unlocked a new chapter.
And they're and they're still friends in their heads.
So there's some like happy stories.
But the this weird dinner theater just served as the wake up call of like it's over.
That's a real hard pill to swallow once you moved across country.
Yeah. Yeah.
Brought the brought the family.
One guy notably said it's hard, man.
You know, it was hard.
It was hard to be away from the family.
And I'm like, oh, so you didn't bring them.
Yes, Mark. Yeah, very possibly.
What else? Anybody desperate?
They called it sad.
They called it I oh, another thing about it is that
they had the same competitors every night.
So there's the gladiators.
And now all right.
And now meet, you know, Michael Jones.
But they put Michael Jones.
They can't find a new Michael Jones every
night to be like a new regular guy to fight the gladiators.
So those were like ringers.
And they say in the dock, like, we've got to be friends with those people.
You don't want to go out, kick their asses.
I see them every day. I like them.
Yeah. So you lost the like cold gladiator
defeating their enemy, dropping them off the wall.
Yeah. I think the action wasn't good.
I think there was too much
music and bad Michael Jackson impersonation going on.
Yeah. Again, no information about the food.
If I had to venture a guess, it was probably not so good.
Yeah.
And yeah, I don't know.
Like, unfortunately, this thing lights me up in concept and then just something
about it, it was just a seedy affair.
Is it because they would compete for real
in events like it wasn't a stage show like Medieval Times is or Pirates Dinner
Adventure? Yeah, I don't know.
Wait, are you asking?
Because this is a question Aaron had.
It was like, was it fixed?
Well, that is the overall question that I'm not sure about.
Yeah.
Jason, you worked on the newer version.
Was anything fixed?
You know, I don't have that question about the show.
Yeah, I don't think this.
Oh, right.
I think the dinner theater, they could have gone like, you want to win tonight?
Michael Jones, you in? Yeah, well, that's true.
Yeah, that was a thing where I'm like,
did they pull like athletic dads from the audience?
And I'm like, no way.
There's no way they're filling up a dad from like Tampa with clam chowder.
And then they're like, get up there and joust.
Well, I was planning on sipping on
sipping on pitcher soup tonight, but I suppose I could climb the wall.
I've had five Miller genuine drafts in the lobby and I am ready to fire the cannon
at the audience. It's terrifying.
You son of a bitch.
You puked on Dallas.
They didn't make it to the cheesecake that night.
It's like a boxing match.
So it's like a prize for like a boxing match could end in the first round.
You might not get as exciting of a show with boxing.
Yeah. Oh, you know what I'm saying?
Like it could just they could be having
kind of an unexciting night if everything was legit.
Oh, and that's why you need to build why
Robert Earl needs to weave a narrative in order to like sustain the again,
to distract people from the food, like exciting things.
Right. That's why you in the third act, you need a bunch of aerial silks.
This show didn't.
This is the rule of successful dinner theaters.
Aerial silks while people are getting dessert.
Yes.
Or else they'll notice that it's very hard cookies.
In pirate, it's in pirate's dinner adventure that you got to do.
You're in the air with some like pieces of cloth.
So that has to happen of the human body.
So it's more beautiful.
We saw it at at the Santa's Secret.
There's nothing makes me feel more alive than somebody spinning around on a ribbon.
Anyway, I it's yeah, it's it's too bad.
This just didn't work for whatever reason.
I think it opened around Christmas 95 by November 96 and it filed for bankruptcy.
But it was one of those files of bankruptcy where it's like, well, it's actually
it's good for us. It's good.
And it's to help everyone that we're doing this.
And then it did stay afloat for two more years.
But that was that.
And then they gave it over to God and and we lost our our opportunity to hang
with the gladiators, to share a soup pitcher with Hawk.
It was not meant to be.
Jesus, take the wheel and our debt.
So RIP dearly departed.
It was as fun to talk about as I thought.
I don't know what all gets promoted to episodes.
I'd say Dippin Dots.
I don't maybe there's not there's not a ton of information about.
But I'll show you guys the flyers really quick for King Henry's Feast.
Oh, yeah, I know.
I saw those in Fort Liberty, one of which was in Mercado, Mediterranean Village.
I have questions about that.
That sounds interesting.
There's no end to the amount of I drive that I want to know about.
And I know there will be no end to the amount of I drive nights that outlaw
hot on the town, newly unencumbered is able to
is able to scrounge up.
Yeah.
And I just get like four or five chicken breasts.
Kissimmee St.
Cloud, the center of the action.
Yeah. Dippin Dots.
Yeah. WMAC Masters.
My mansions literally in the center of the I showed them the ad with the bullseye.
And I said, where can I be in the center my whole life?
I've been on the side.
I've been just watching the action.
Not anymore, baby.
I'm the action.
You understand? I'm the action.
And he throws Jason out his balcony,
which is a big deal because it's four stories high.
My Mike paid 250 grand and got the biggest shoddy mansion has ever been built.
Floors two and three are not finished.
And you know what? Neither is floor four.
I also died, but I just stepped wrong.
I've been building. I've been putting it together.
They just dumped all the pieces on the lawn and I've been assembling it.
But I can do this. I put toys together.
I do Legos.
This is like ultimate Legos.
Yeah.
Jason, I also sleep on the tortoise bed.
So just a heads up.
I'll be in here later.
I do a lot of sleep punching these days.
I'm going to be farting this room up like
there ain't no God.
Creatine and chicken breast don't make a good combination.
And remember, we've got to set our alarm for 6 a.m.
We got to go to the Rock Church in the morning.
That's right.
I'm playing lead guitar.
We got to atone.
Oh, I've been saved, by the way.
I do most of Frankie Valley's hits.
I mean, he's still out there.
He's still out there performing, but I
in a tribute to him.
I hold him up.
I got baptized at the the lazy river at H2O Live, the Margaritaville Water Park.
Yeah, that's no that failed years ago.
Another church bought it.
They had the whole lazy river blessed.
So you could just crank through baptisms.
You could do 50 an hour, you boys in.
If not, I'm going to have to ask you to go back to Sinners, California.
Most of the church bought up a lot.
I drive, honestly, at this point.
It's half more than half religion owned.
All that olive.
It's still Olive Garden, but the never ending pasta is all blessed.
So it's the same as eating the hosts.
Spaghetti, the old spaghetti factory is a factory.
Hey, Jason, Mr.
Trump brought a bag.
Hey, Jason, after you're done eating the bowl, the never ending pasta bowl, you
put our keys in it.
You want it, you win.
You know what I'm saying?
You take the bowl home, you put your keys in it.
Then we go to church next morning, though, to a tone, so don't worry.
None of that happened since we walked through these doors and it raises all that.
Dip your hands in that holy water, brother.
We're clean.
I know where they've been.
We call this sizzling scene, sizzling scene.
All right.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us in our VIP Patreon tier club three, where
you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
We do appreciate your support.
Your dollars are the initial seed money that turn Mike into Florida Mike.
Thank you, outlaw.
Granted, it's really going to kick into
overdrive when he starts scamming people for three mil a pop.
If you could all change your pledges
to 10 grand a month, that would really help us or me specifically.
If you've ever been like, I like Dr.
Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, but I wish it was just Mr. Hyde and he was crazy.
I thought you were going to say Dr.
Jekyll, Mr. Hyde, dinner show where they fight the one brain.
All right, Team Hyde, let me hear you.
The hard side, you're green.
That means green for the monster Hyde.
And where is my Jekyll eaters at?
Now everyone come together over your shrimp skewers.
Just like crushing up pills, snorting
lines, say is the energy to do four shows a night of Jekyll and Hyde live.
Oh, yeah. Oh, God.
Fucking pumped.
Let me at him.
I'm at six more shows and get a four a.m. going.
Are you not in Gorge?