FOREVER!
DOG!
Welcome to podcast the ride a theme park podcast where we remember that Tommy used to sing on the
Tommy used to sing on the boardwalk but Disney raised the rent and jelly rolls left it's tough
So tough
Gina worked the door all night collecting twenty two dollars the price was more than fair
It was fair
So fair
She says we've got to hold on to nineties Disney World stuff
It doesn't make a difference if we like it or not Michael Eisner okayed it and that's enough
Now that jelly rolls is closed
I'm sure Michael is somewhere distraught
Oh the world is unfair
Oh I'm sending out a prayer
Hey there God make it reopen somewhere
Oh to make Michael Eisner not despair
Hi I'm Mike Carlson joining me as always Jason Sheridan
Well I liked it and one of our guests liked it
Okay good I'm glad
That'll be the standard division for how this is gonna go I think
I was in such a moment I was feeling it so much I didn't even notice the reactions I just I was connected to something bigger in me
Scott Garner is here as well hopefully he's connected
Yeah well you know I mean I liked the lyrics that you were doing but the main thing when you started singing I was like I know that song
That's a song I know and when I hear a song I know and I realize the people around me also know a song I know I freak out
Cause it's like I'm alive and there's a song that everyone in the room knows and that's plenty for me and that's worth $22 to me
Well that's good I agree with you that's actually maybe not in the same tone how I believe it but that is basically a similar
What do you mean the tone was excited
Okay
I'm smiling it's an upbeat tone I don't know what you're referring to tonally
We're on zoom so sometimes the tone gets strange when you're on a zoom call I understand that so maybe I'm just sort of interpreting it wrong
There's a false sarcasm filter that comes through
There is we're doing stream yard now and there might be a false sarcasm filter that's what I'm interpreting
Yeah that's the problem when you're dealing with technology we don't always use yeah
Okay yeah so well look we're coming in hot today let's bring the guests in because I think we all have we're all really riled up today
In different ways but they're returning to podcast the ride from World Wrestling Entertainment it's Candice LeRae and Johnny Gargano
Thank you welcome back thank you for being here
I felt like I should have applauded them but then I was like are we not supposed to
Hey I just want to say up front Mike that performance was better than anything Jelly Rolls has ever seen
So I mean that was awesome
Johnny I love you you're my favorite guest in one sentence you're my favorite guest in history
We're just getting started guys
We're just warming up
I took notes I have a notepad of stuff here about Jelly Rolls just right up I can't see it on the camera
You don't want them to see it you don't want them to know
They're from me they're from my eyes only
Right yes
Does it have just to be just so we're clear does it have the amount of pianos is it one or two
Because I'm worried we're going to lose sight of the basics here
So everyone knows how many pianos are in that building
So everyone knows
Yeah oh boy
I can't wait I'm excited guys
I'm excited to dig in here
That's a great idea actually
Like tooling piano bars
You know the standard is two
But what if there were three
Oh yeah
Or if there's like just like you know
Dozens
I mean I was just a
Civil war of
What if everyone
Instead of a table is sitting at a piano
That's what I cast
Look I love that idea
Well you mean like the guests are just
That's what I thought okay I don't want to I don't want to spoil some here
But that's what I thought
Sitting there in the moment again I've been there once
I went there once just for this podcast
To be fair
You can kind of set that up there
Never ever ever go I was
Like I had accepted
It will never be a place that he's ever going to experience
In his life
And you guys did me a solid
So thank you guys
You're welcome
Thought process on Jelly Rolls like this is years ago
Years before I even know what the place was
So
Given my profession I have to diet a lot
So I go to
Disney World I want like a nice treat
And we're walking on the boardwalk and I see a sign
That says Jelly Rolls
And I'm like oh it's probably a bakery
That serves fantastic delicious
Jelly Rolls
It is not
Spoiler alert it's not that
They don't got that I think that that just put a bad taste
In your mouth from the beginning
I wanted a good taste in my mouth
It's false advertising
It's false advertising from the
Gecko and by the way as we
Get into what it is
This is one of those things I am going to require
That somebody says the basics
Because I do think
I still don't know
What's happening
Yeah so Jelly
Rolls is well
Was I should say because Jelly Rolls sadly has
Closed but it was a
Mainstay on the boardwalk
Over 30 years
30 years
On the boardwalk
Disney's boardwalk
Hotel that's the strip
That has like the abracadabra
Which we talk about a lot which is a little
Magic theme bar there's a now
What is it called the cake bake shop is on the boardwalk
Yeah
And there's a
That's good
We haven't been there yet
Jelly Rolls should have been
It should have just sold delicious
Wasn't Jason mad at that place because
Of prices? Sure
I understand that
I think a lot of people were
They did lower them at some point
They did lower some of the menu prices
Because there was such an uproar
Over the prices
I would spend $150
For one slice of cake
Then sit there and let the Jelly Rolls
Experience happen to me again
So
Jelly Rolls and K.I. in case you haven't pieced it together
And you don't know it was a dueling piano
Bar
In the style of a Howl at the Moon
If that helps if that's a place that you know
More well than
Jelly Rolls but you would get you would go up
And you would tip and you would generally
Tip and write down the suggestion for a
Song and hopefully they would get to playing
It on the piano there were antics
That also happened at Jelly Rolls you know
There was somebody would bring a saxophone out
They would do little dances
It was pretty it was a little more
Aggressive than just a quiet like
Piano bar so it would be more of a rowdy
Party like atmosphere I would
I would call it an aggressive
Place that plays a lot of Muppet songs
Aggressive is the word
You would use you will hear
You will hear an aggressive I'll make
A man out of you from Mulan
Which is an aggressive
Look good it's about masculinity right there
So yeah that's the kind of
They play a little bit of some toxic stuff a little bit
Right yes that's true
I don't know have they ever played toxic by Britney Spears
I would hope so
1000%
Obviously
Have they ever done a deep cut like toxic
Toxic might be a little too
Obscure for Jelly Rolls though that's all
I'm saying
I feel like though in the 30 years that song
Had to be popular enough that
Somebody would request it in that time
Right I would think so
You would have to yeah they would have
At least tried it one night to see
But I will say this
Personally I didn't know this
What this really was until like two years ago
And I think we talked about it on the show
Is that we were all hanging out at Abracadabra
And I was just like looking
And I think I maybe thought it was just a facade
I maybe thought that Jelly Rolls was just like
Oh that was just a fun yeah
Look I'm admitting my ignorance
I didn't realize what it was
And we went in there and of course I lit up
I was so excited by it
And I brought everyone around
Scott I believe did not go in that night
In 2023
Well I did because here's how it played out
I think maybe I'd heard of it
And then we you know we didn't go in
There's kind of like a
There's a little bit of a lobby
Area and a box office
And when I learned that the
Cover charge was 20
Dollars for me
And it's at the end of like a long
Very long Epcot day
With a lot of walking
And a lot of food and a lot of wine
So now
At the end of the day
I am
The premise is that I'm supposed to pay
20 Dollars in order
To go listen
To like all
Of the most obvious songs
In the world with a
In a room that seems
Like it is made to hold
100 people and instead there are
900 people
From the little lobby
I was stressed by the lobby
And then also knowing
That mere steps away
Are the masterpiece hotels
The Swan and the Dolphin
Where I could go and just walk and have some
Peace have a moment to myself
In the Michael Graves Causeway
There was just there was I mean like I think if it had been
Free possibly maybe I
Would have popped in but when I heard that cover charge
My jaw dropped like you're
Kidding there's no way
On earth that
That was like an insurmountable hill
For me in that moment and then later
When we when we returned a few years later
Yeah I you know I
Said 20 Dollars oh
That's a steal I can
I felt
I felt like we I walked into
Like a time warp cause it feels
So 90s in there and it's
Like I'm traveling to a place that I never knew
What do you think?
It doesn't feel 90s it feels like 60s
50s
I think it's the logo that
Feels so 90s to me that's like
That's on the wall there
And I've talked on the show
Before I really never went to Pleasure Island
And I'm nostalgic
For a life not lived in Pleasure
Island I'm nostalgic for
Going to mannequins
And I never did it but like
Reading through the Facebook group of the
Pleasure Island memories
I was like oh this would have been so much fun
To do if I was a young
Adult again but
I feel like going to jelly rolls is
Look I in general like
Singing songs loudly with
People even if they're the 20 songs
That everybody knows so but
I think there was an extra element of like oh my god
I went into a time warp and I'm
Back in time in Disney
Worlds and that also felt good
For me as well and yeah
You have to respect that
I mean Johnny you don't have to
Johnny feel free
Feel free not to respect that
You are allowed to not respect it
This is the logo we're having
I respect all of that
Obviously you see the back of
My background I definitely respect Vinded
But my
Collect your thoughts
Take your time
Vastly different
Than yours
Again I made notes
So I can tell you what the thought
My first initial thought was when I walked
In the building before I
Before I walked in the building honestly
The first thing before we're walking in
Set the stage for you
Our son
And his nanny are over at Hollywood Studios
Watching Phantasmag
So we do the smart thing towards the end where we're like
I'll go to Hollywood
Studios
People can go into Hollywood
Watch Phantasmag as much as he wants
Especially when they're show one and two
We can walk from Hollywood
Over to Jelly Rolls
So on this night
We did the walk
It was a nice walk
Great walk
Walk from Hollywood Studios over to Jelly Rolls
As we're approaching Jelly Rolls
My first initial instinct
The smell
It has nothing to do with actual Jelly Rolls
Right outside of Jelly Rolls
I wrote, smells like poop
I don't know the opposite of a Jelly Roll
The smell of a Jelly Roll
I think they were just replanting stuff
And it was a little moist out
And so it just smelled like manure
It smelled bad
It smells horrible
The back of it
The backside
Horrible smell
It's not coming from Jelly Rolls itself
It was a nice bakery
I'm just saying
Smell fantastic
Other end of the boardwalk
This is the entertainment district
As they call it
Put me in the head space
It smells like poop
That can't help
Can I ask a question just to back it up
Slightly here
Because it seems like where you guys are starting
Is that Candice has been trying to talk
Johnny into doing this for a while
What are you
Candice you're coming in with like
Have you done this place a lot
Are you a huge fan of Jelly Rolls
When I was living in California
There was a dueling piano bar
That was in downtown Fullerton
And I was like
Wow this dueling piano bar is amazing
And I loved it
So we moved out here
I just never really found the time
To make my way over to Jelly Rolls
And was like dying to go
So for my cousin's birthday
A couple of years ago
We were with our
It was me, my cousin, her mom and my mom
And our moms are sisters
And we're like well let's go over
And check out Jelly Rolls
Because this seems like a perfect time to do this
Like our moms are here, they love music
This will be great
It was amazing
It was like the funnest night
And since it was so close to my mom's birthday
She was a percussionist
So super into
Music
But anytime we go anywhere she's drumming on tables
She's picking up random things
And using them as like instruments
So we'd written on the napkin
That we would like
We requested that for my mom's birthday
They let her play a tambourine
Because she just kept talking about like
I wish I could just have a tambourine
They let her go and play a tambourine
She did Hey Ya
In our life apparently
Unbeknownst to me
She killed it
So it was like the most perfect, fun, amazing night
That you could possibly have
At Jelly Rolls
So my cousin and I went back like a few more times
But Johnny would not go
Which complicates me being
A frequenter especially with a kid now
So like
I would have loved to have been
This is interesting
So Johnny's against
The notion of it
You haven't even gotten a taste of it
And Candice is saying it's an incredible
One of the best nights she's ever had
That was not enough to
What were you fearing?
What was making you never want to try this?
Just the idea of it
Sounds like it's awful
But mind you
His own mother, if I took his mom with us
She would have loved it
That's one of my notes
My mom would love this
Not you
Now with some of that
That's just like the general vibe
Because you know the vibe of a dueling piano bar
Is any of it like me
Where you're like
I don't think I'm going to enjoy hearing
The 20 most famous songs that exist
Is that a wall for you?
Honestly I just think
I just don't get the point of it
And I was there
And I was sitting there
And I was like
Nothing is happening
People are having so much fun
What do you mean nothing is happening?
What is happening?
Everybody in that room is having so much fun
Except you
Who's just on your phone like I hate this
It smells like poop
First note smells like poop
Second note too loud
Too loud
I know what you mean
I'll accept
I want music to be loud if I'm at a concert
That I'm excited about
But if I'm not particularly thrilled
With what I'm experiencing
I saw O-Town in the 90s
I'm always down for a good concert
In O-Town?
Not in O-Town
It's not in Cleveland, Ohio
But Ohio, O-Town
How was Liquid Dreams that night?
Fantastic
Ashley Parker Angel absolutely killed it
Johnny knows what's up musically
That's not for sure
He was there
Hold on now it's a different story
Did you consider writing
O-Town
On one of the slips
With a 20
Did you see if they could play that
I ain't giving more money
That is fair
I have given my fair share of money
To this cause
But it's for the talent
You can't tell me that the pianists aren't talented
They are
So think about this
The second a song becomes popular
These guys have to learn
This song immediately
Immediately
Because it is going to be requested
A thousand times
And they have to play it
Here's where my head goes with all this stuff
Nothing's happening
Everything is happening
If you're going there
If you're going to Jelly Rolls
They're serving great food
And you're going to sit there and eat a nice meal
Eat a nice meal
Sure, no food
They serve popcorn
Popcorn is flowing like water
If you're going to get a fancy drink
Nothing is happening
You're sitting there
Letting these two guys
Let it happen to you
Playing this music
I view this like almost in wrestling
I like watching bad wrestling
So my head went to
To make this thing even better
Take the guys
Take the professionals out of it
Just let two amateurs duel
Then we see who wins
That's what I would do
He just wanted to see random people go up on the stage
One person goes up and plays a song
Fight it out in a piano duel
That's what I think dueling pianos should be
To be a fighter at some point
This is like Roger Rabbit
I wish
Johnny
What's the last concert you saw?
Music concert
Has it been a while?
I'm trying to think
Music concert, just to clarify
It is an old town
Well, it could be a
Different kind of concert
I don't think he's been to a single concert
Since we've met
We've been together for like 10 years
It's been a while
I honestly can't even remember the last concert I've been to
Do you ever stop and go
Where's my headset there?
I don't think he likes live music to be fair
I don't know that you even like
I feel like if you went to a concert
You would just be like
Nothing's happening
It would be an epic band and you'd be like
Nothing is happening
So this discredits you
Is there a band you would like
Say they were playing nearby
That you would make a point to go see them?
Even if they're dead
Even if it's the Beatles
You could go say the Beatles
Any band
I mean obviously that would be cool if the Beatles were back alive
Limp Bizkit
They have been sure done Limp Bizkit
At Jelly Rolls, right?
I mean they've had to play
They've barely played Roland at least once
At Jelly Rolls
If they played Roland at Jelly Rolls
Would you be like whoa
This is an argument that Mike makes
From time to time which is
They played a song you like
Two guys have never heard of playing the song I like
That doesn't help me
That's not the version I like
That does not help the argument to me
When we were there
I feel like
The Jelly Roll Gods were not on our side
How long were we there for? I set a timer
He set a timer because the deal was that
You walked in and I set a timer
I think we said originally
What was the time that we were
It was like 20-30 minutes
And I stayed extra
I stayed longer than that
Just to see are we going to play a song that I actually know
We did not
I wanted to request
Let the bodies hit the floor by drowning pool
But that would have been really salt
If I could request one song I can go back in history
I'm not getting any money
If I can request one song
It would be Let the bodies hit the floor by drowning pool
Do you think it might bring the room down?
Do you think the room might be
People would be like one nothing wrong with me
Two nothing
Somethings got to give
If that happens
Maybe
Let the bodies hit the floor
He played that song to my womb
You know how they say you should play music
For children while they're in the womb
Against the belly
It will help their mind
I played Let the bodies hit the floor by drowning pool
Wow
Is that your favorite song?
It might be
If anyone asks me a song
That's always my go to
Song
Any scenario
I think it works in any scenario
Wedding first dance
Let the bodies hit the floor
Did he play it at our wedding?
I don't think we did play it at our wedding
I did a weird L
For our first dance
Which weird L?
If that isn't love
I don't know what love is
I can't even remember what album it's off of
It's a love song
If that isn't love
Then I don't know what love is
It's an original L
Wow
That original L
It's just a really cute song
Because it's a lot of like
If you ate eggs
I'd still
I can't even remember all the lyrics
But I hate eggs
He loves to eat them
I'd still kiss him after he ate some eggs
It's in the song
We just didn't really take ourselves very seriously
At our wedding I guess
I came out to a piano version
Of Shawn Michaels song
Or I guess piano version of Macho Man song
So that's where we were
We're getting into that as well for a second
Just as a quick aside
Wedding entrances
Not fun
Coming from the world of wrestling
He got upset because he asked me
I said
I was going over, I was like what do we have the wedding party
Walk down the aisle to
And we did a piano version of the WrestleMania theme
And then he was like
I'm walking down the aisle too
And I was like I mean you just go
With the rest of the party
Like you go first I think
He didn't like that
I said you maybe walk your mom down the aisle
He goes no, I want my own entrance
I should get an entrance too
I'm trying to explain to
I'm trying to explain to the
Wedding planner
I'm like so here's the thing
Is that not only does he
Require his own entrance
But he wants to go right before I come out
Yeah it's our thing
Which complicates it when we're hiding
Each other
They're trying to hide me
So I have to like sprint down this long
Because we got married at the Grand Californian
Hotel in Disneyland
And in that little
You know where like the Monorail kind of goes over in the
Courtyard by the downtown Disney
So that's where we got married
And I had this like
Long hallway that I had to
Like sprint down
Just to like be there on
Time because he literally had to go
Right before me his own entrance
By himself and then
He had a gripe about it
I mean you think like again
Coming from the world of wrestling you do entrance and people are like
Yeah they're pumped up
No one makes any noise at a wedding
You just walk down to silence and it's like
This kind of sucks
Because my family and friends you think they would give me
A little something I don't know
But it made my wife uncomfortable
As well like she
Started walking and it was like the quiet
Hush of like oh the bride
Is here and she kind of hated it and she said
Like hey what's up everybody
And then that got a huge applause
And then it lit the room and then it was like oh now we're cooking
Which I found was wonderful
I was like oh that's her personality coming through
She doesn't want to be the like delicate
Maybe just kind of smarten them up next time and be like
Please applaud
It was a huge moment
I think this should change
I think you guys are onto something about like upping the entry
That said it does seem very
Inconvenient for Candice
To have had to
I don't know how it had to become a hallway
You being bright before me was very inconvenient
But we got there
Scott
What piano version
Of a wrestler's theme did Aaron walk down the aisle
To?
Undertaker
Well that'd be good
Well the entire
The entire wedding
Was scored to the
Hulkster rules album
Oh there you go
First dance was to Hulkster in heaven
There you go
That's fantastic
I want to check in real quick Jason Sheridan has not
Done jelly rolls and he will
I hate to be rubbing it in
You'll never do it
It's over
Oh no I'm not going to say that
But
My family
Stayed at the boardwalk once or twice
But I was like
A pre-teen and this is like
One of the places at Disneyland
Disney World
Where there is like 21
And up
And it's very funny that
They have that cause right before this
I watched a clip and they were playing
The Mickey Mouse Club theme
Oh so
But that's for the adults
That's for the child inside of all of us
That's true yeah
You need a place where you can listen to children's music
And essentially throw up while you're singing it
That has happened a lot there there's no way
It hasn't 30 years
How many throw ups okay that's all we don't know the answer
How many times has someone thrown up
At Jelly Rolls in 30 years
At least once a night
Once a night yeah easy
So it's about
200,000 pukes
I mean if not
In Jelly Rolls when they go outside
And smell the sewage they probably like immediately
Right afterwards
Yeah
So Jason though do you feel
You don't have to feel sad I'm not trying to make
You feel sad but what do you feel about
Never getting to do this
Yeah I don't know
I think it probably would have been fun
We did go to Hell at the Moon
The one time
For the City Walk Saga
And yeah
It was kind of
I think we went on a Wednesday or Thursday
And it was
I mean an experience
What a review
I had more
Fun than Jason that night
I was trying to get us all to dance and Jason was a
Hard no
I forgot about the dancing
Yeah you didn't want to go down there
Right but we had the big
We shared a big blue bucket
We shared a big blue
Bucket and it was
Like three or four dollar
Absolute vodka
So everyone's drinking doubles
And then we recorded
At like one
In the morning right afterwards
Yeah
But yeah I mean
I think it's impressive
That like the
Not just one pianist but
Two pianists can play
Like in tandem
And like kind of complement
Each other or
Race each other or something like that
Jason I hate to cut you off
It doesn't sound like you're that distraught
Over going to Jelly Rolls
I well
I said the entertainment district
It's okay if you're not
When I was like
In 2014 I was like
Oh that's
That end of the boardwalk is for
Adults and like I don't know
I guess
It's forbidden
It's still off limits to you in some ways
It is yeah
Have you been in the dance
Have you been in the dance hall
No I think anytime I tried to go
It wasn't open
But it seems a lot more open
Nowadays
That I believe is all ages right
Or is that 21 and 9
Did we have to show
We did pop in there last trip
Did we have to show an ID
I don't recall
Yeah that's another I guess if we're talking about
Yeah this district of the boardwalk hotel
There is Jelly Rolls and then right next to it is something called the Atlantic
Dance hall
Which when we popped in was hopping
Kevin Tully our pal and
Recent guest
He was excited to get me in there because
He's like
He's like this is now this is like a locked in time
I think you'll like because there's sort of
Some like you know 90s by way
Of 40s and neon and I was
Really digging it there
I and I think
He was anticipating it would be weirdly
Empty which I think it is a lot of the time
But in this case like
Really hopping I like
A ton of people out there dancing
To bye bye bye or whatever
We went up on the balcony where you got
A nice view of the Epcot resorts
We actually met some listeners up there
Had a good chat for a second
They asked where's everybody else I said
Well Mike's here but he's a he's over
At Jelly Rolls speaking of and then
You texted and your text was
Bad bad Leroy Brown
And I
Which as and this has become a recurring
Thing in the several times that we've been
And I have either gone and then left
Immediately
Or just not gone at all
Some of like you are trying to like
I don't know what you're trying that's a
Question what are you trying to do
When you text me bad bad Leroy Brown
Because it's not making me jealous
It's doing the opposite of that what is the
Intent when you are when you send a
Text of that nature
Okay let me analyze
Another one right after was
They're going ape for
American pie
And these things just make me like oh
My god I'm thrilled to be in any
Room other than that room
I think it depends
I think I know that you're
Probably not going to get thrilled by bad bad
Leroy Brown and I think
I think I'm sending that but I do think I've also
Sent since more sincere
Texts and I can't think of any
Off the top of my head of songs I think
You would like I think those
Two in particular I did find it
Funny I think really when that
When they start playing bad bad Leroy Brown or
American pie I do think
It amuses me how angry you
Would get I will I think that is what
It is so I think if he was physically
There yeah I think
I think I think I'm like laughing
At the idea of bad bad Leroy
Brown coming on and you're just being like what you
Turn the table over
So I think I'm like sharing
It for that reason in those
It is an attempted rile up
I because this tradition kind of began
Because a couple years ago when
A group ended up there which was
Kevin and Griffin Newman
And Nate Mr. Morrow
And when I departed
And did not join that group
Then for the rest of the night everyone was
Texting all of the songs
That were being played and this is a
Transcript this was Griffin
Leading the charge on our text
Thread Griffin
Scott this place fucking
Rocks
This may have been after a video
Of
Of a cover of Love Shack
Which was a to me
In rewatching it this morning
A nightmarish cover
Of Love Shack
But I guess Griffin felt differently I texted
Back I'm thrilled with my choice thrilled
Because at this point I'm sitting by the water
Staring at the Swan
Hotel I just went and sat on the grass
Put them in a real moment of peace
It was amazing and I'm getting
These texts what's that
Nature you're having a moment yeah yeah
Essentially yeah well nature combined with
80s architecture that's exactly where I
Want to be yeah you got that's part of it you got to know
What you want as Johnny does
So then
He keeps going then he then Griffin switches
To all caps Scott
They're performing the Ken song
Now
Barbie I'm just
Ken and then I what my
Response was I have never been
More confident in a decision
Number one this number two
Marrying Aaron
I put I put my decision
Ahead of my
Marriage
Sure I was I did not want to be listening to the Ken
Song well now the Ken
Song was only a few months old at that
Point so I bet that was a big hit
You know
To Candice's point
They are keeping up with the with the time I feel
Like they do it's like they know
Eight songs from the last
Year and then other than that you're going back
To pre 2003 that's
Kind of the what seems like the setlist
Here did any
Anyone get a
Fancy like the
Applebee's Applebee's
Date night song I feel
Like that was a big hit I feel like
They would do that I
Don't I would be skeptical that they would
Have ever played that fit song fancy
Like that you and I are big fans of
And that Applebee's used in a commercial
A lot of commercials
Was that
Was that a stump on Johnny and Candice
I think I know what he's talking about
And if that's the case
It's not getting played at Jelly Rolls
Candice that's my role on
The show
Jason's per episode
Stumping of everyone in the room
Walker I shout
This will help it was a song
Performed by Walker Hayes
Oh yeah
Yeah
Okay so now we're all clear
On what it is so we talked about
This this night that we had in 2023
On the show
And I feel like of there were a handful
Of people reached out Candice reached out to me
At this point and was so incredibly
Passionate about Jelly
Rolls like you were
Like oh my god I love Jelly Rolls
And then we basically
Right then and there were like okay well we have to
Do an episode on Jelly Rolls eventually
And I think the thought was
Oh we'll go there next time
And make a thing of it
And then of course in 2024
Very early in 2025 I forget now
Oh yeah it was it felt like it was
I felt like they were goofing on us
It happened after we were just like
This is gonna happen we were so pumped
And then they said
And they said no we're closing
Jelly Rolls
Closer announced yeah
I think it might have been even early 2025
So honestly at that point we were pretty
Sure we're going to go to Epic Universe
After it opened which now it's open
But like we'll be like it's gonna be at the end of May
At the earliest we'll be there
It seems like Jelly Rolls is
Not gonna happen and it did make
Me sad because obviously we were gonna still do an episode
But it felt like okay that's
It's gonna be a little bit of the episode that's
Just not gonna be as it's not gonna be as
Satisfying because we didn't get to go one last time
And then and it would lead to me
Never having done it
Because he never went in
But
A miracle happened
We were invited to a preview of
Epic Universe and yes
Epic Universe was really fun to go
To see it before it opens to the public
Getting to do that before the general
Public we were so lucky to do it we had an
Amazing Disney World Day in general
Where you know just because of the
Kindness of someone we were able to do
A lot of rides skipping the lines
That was amazing but
I was really
Really excited to one
Last time go to Jelly Rolls
It felt like oh my god this is
Going to be the perfect trip every day
Is packed with something super fun
And satisfying and then
Just by happenstance a friend of mine
From a long time ago was in there
Was in Disney World with her family
And she used to work at Disney World
During like the intern like college
Intern program and she
Was like I have to go to Jelly Rolls
One last time so I ended up
On like a three and a half day
Trip going to Jelly Rolls two out of the three
Days which was
Unbelievable
So I got
A short trip real estate
To spend in that Johnny what do you
I got to get your reaction to that
Please Johnny
Johnny let me have it let me have it Johnny
Be kind
No
So you went to Epic Universe
Fantastic new experience
Amazing rides all
Up to date technology
Just so futuristic
And then you cap
It off by going to quite possibly
The worst place
You can go to
You like ended the sentence
That was the end of that sentence
No qualifiers
I was there I was thinking about what
Would I rather be doing right now other than
This and the first thing that
Popped into my head because we went on that walk
That Scott was talking about of sitting
Outside looking at the dolphins by the
Water I thought
You know what would be better than this
Sitting by that water and one of those
Alligators just coming out and trying to
Attack me
That would be better than what I'm doing right now
Getting experience
I knew
Perhaps less
Annoying than that particular love shack cover
Yes
So
What do you think is better
Monsters Unchained or Jelly Roll
I'll give you
Options here
Hang on
Monsters Unchained was down when we were there
Oh you didn't do it
It's unfair how dare you
Which Jelly Rolls was down
It is down
It's down
Old Yeller
They've been dropping like flies
The Mama Melrose
Closed one of my family's favorites
Jelly Rolls closed
Do you know
You're not going to want to talk to me about this
Because I'm very much so
IP guy
Put some IP in there
Put some IP in Jelly Rolls
Do you have any ideas Johnny
Sorry
He thinks that anything that's like
Outdated should just be demolished
Plus it up
You think that they should just be gone
No plus it up
You're not the first
First cast to say that
You haven't announced anything right
There was a rumor that they're going to
The rumor that there's like a jazz club
Going in there
I don't like that either
There's music so much
I like jazz
I'm worried about that
Of a bakery
But there's the
Cake bake shop
You can never have enough bakeries
So they're dueling bakeries now
People are upset that the Muppets are leaving
How about this
Swedish Chef
Put him in there
He's making Jelly Rolls
It's not a music place
He just makes sweets
Swedish Chef
He just wants more food
Can I pitch you an idea
If it's a dueling piano bar
But all they do is play songs from
The 1995 Mortal Kombat soundtrack
Okay
I'm warming up to that idea
If it would be a specific
Genre of song maybe
I don't know if you're into the Mortal Kombat soundtrack
I'm just saying
Or the Power Rangers
The first Power Rangers movie
You're speaking my language now
What if the Muppets are playing the piano
The Muppets are playing the piano
That might be different
If you get the actual Muppets to play a piano
Just put some IP in there
And give him some Jelly Rolls
If you wanted to keep the
Dueling piano concept
Just make some IP people
Right
Who would you want to see
Who would you want to see play piano
In a dueling piano bar IP based
Because that's a new question
IP okay
So what famous fictional characters play piano
Obviously as you're saying
Dr. Teeth from
Electric Mayhem plays piano
But like what's a famous
I'm trying to think
I want the guy from Soul
Joe Gardner
Joe Gardner versus
Ryan Gosling La La Land
I forget if he plays piano
Done
With Joe Gardner in there
What if
What if he though plays
Don't Stop Believing and Living on a Prayer
Would that be still good
Like if he plays the same song
He'll do new
He'll find new
He can play whatever he wants
Joe Gardner
Oh he's got a brother
No it's dueling
You get Joe and you get Joe Gardner
And they're dueling against each other
I am glad
Someone had the name
Because I'm sitting here going like
What is that guy
That character is a very normal name
And I cannot think of it
And so I'm glad someone got it
I would love for them
To like lean in
My family
Has a lot of connections to
Atlantic City
My grandfather grew up in Atlantic City
A lot of my dad's family
Lived down there
My mom's parents honeymooned
In Atlantic City when he was on leave
From World War II
So I say
Make it like a full
Bootlegger speakeasy
But
But add Joe Gardner
Add Joe Gardner
And they play
They play Fancy Like
They can play the Casher remix too
You know
Switch it up
Jason's favorite song is just Fancy Like
By Walker Hayes
One song from this one Applebee's ad
Is the go to for
From 2022
It's 3 years old
It's 3 years old but I'm telling you that would bring the house down
If there were dueling pianists
Dueling jazz pianists
Playing
Yeah
The problem has been a lack of Fancy Like
That's been the problem
Yeah for me
NIP apparently
NIP
They played Why Should I Worry
When we were there that Saturday night
And I don't know that anyone there knew what it was
So I'm not sure that Fancy Like
Is going to light up the audience
I'm just a reality check
Sorry
I admittedly would have freaked out
If they played Why Should I Worry
You could have requested it
Maybe they would have known
If you were there you could have requested it
Do they know the Dear Radigan
Song from the Great Mouse Detective
I don't think
I know that
I don't think I knew there was a song
Jason would you sing a little bit of it for us
I can only remember
Dear Radigan
It's a drinking song
Yes it is
All the little mice are drinking
To the Vincent Price
Villain
First of all
I don't think anyone in that room would have known that song
I would have known it
They would have taken it
Right off the setlist after one play
I think
Because it wouldn't have gotten a huge crowd
I always wonder too
Because when we were there
We were watching all the napkins
Go up on the table
I'm trying to understand because there's two sides
If there was a napkin
They'd wad it up and throw it to the other guy
The other guy would open it
Who's deciding this setlist
Because there were so many moving parts
On the napkins
On top of the pianos
Each side had a list of them
How do they
How do they make their playlists while they're going
They do a switch at one point
You kept hyping up this switch
She kept hyping up
Every time I've been there
They've done a switch
It's been like a boy band song
Or like
Bohemian Rhapsody
You're getting these
Songs that are
A hit every party that you ever go to
That did not happen
On the night that we were there
They didn't even
Actually switch
They usually do
I just feel like Jelly Rolls really did me dirty
Or Jelly Rolls showed
What it really is
I went three different times
Three different times prior to that
That were very closely
Before that
Great
Performers were great, crowd not great
But still a good night
Then phenomenal
And then that night happened
I did write in my notes that
Some of these people's personalities
In real life
This is their whole
Personalities coming to this place
I'm worried about where they're going to go
Now in the future
What this means to their life
You're talking to one of them
One of them is in a box in this window
We're doing right now
Their whole personality is Jelly Roll
I feel like you found
Yourself there
In a matter of two nights
The first one a year and a half ago
Really set it up
By the end of those two
You know what I realized? It's your pink pony club
This was your
Where you discovered yourself
A place where you can be who you are
That's true
And Mike said they played that
Oh
You're right
You're right about that
I'm gonna keep on singing
At the dual piano club
Pointing at songs I've heard of
Down in Walt Disney World
I'm gonna keep
I'm a Jelly Rolls boy
Singing rap songs
Without the N words
Whatever
Let me ask
A question
I think I know the answer
Did they play
Power Line when everyone went?
No
I would have loved it
I would have been great if they did not play it
It is a frequent that they like to play
Do they do
Do they do both of the power lines
Or just eye to eye?
I'm trying to think if I heard both
Or if it was just
What the hell is the other power line?
Stand out?
Stand out a very underrated song
It is
Power Line Deep Cut
Yeah, there's only two
There's the hit and then there's the deep cut
So you know what we should
In terms of weaving this tale
I think something that we haven't officially laid out
Is that, okay, so Mike goes
You get to go
Your plan was that there was gonna be one with Candace
But you ended up getting a bonus one the night before
Do not change your plans
I'm gonna go back
I'm gonna keep on dancing
At the Jelly Rolls Club
We do it the next night
And the whole day there's the discussion of am I doing it or not
Now the biggest thing
Luring me into doing it
I was very charmed and honored that
Candace was interested in getting me
In there
And I think there was even the offer of the cover being
Taken care of
I believe Mike ended up doing it
Unless I'm confused about the
Because this was admittedly I was like
I will not
That is not worth it to me
Can we all agree that is an
Awkward amount of money
That's a strange amount of money
I will say that Johnny and my last time going
Was the first discovery for me
That pass holders got a discount
So we did not pay the full $22
We did get a discount
I can't, it was like
I can't even remember
I don't know
Maybe
Inflation
You're definitely
You're definitely paying Disney World tax
At Jelly Rolls
Because I don't think any other place
Like this is gonna charge that much of a
Cover
It's a weird amount of money for a
Concert that does not have name performers
You know what I mean
But people pay it
That room was packed
It was absolutely packed
Which is the thing that turned me off
But I was really
Happy that you wanted to get me in there
And I wanted to prove that I could
Do it for more than 20 minutes
You said three songs
Oh that's right yes
And I made it past the three
And I was proud that I made it past the three
And also I want to say thank you
For the jello shots
I think that was a spirit
Lifter across the board
Alright I'll stick around a little longer
I literally went to the bar and I was like
I didn't even know these still existed places
I'm gonna get this all
I don't think I've done it
I think over 10 years since
My last jello shot
I feel like I'm at confession
It felt
Jello shots just that also I think maybe
Part of it and that really was the perfect
Choice because I do
This does feel like I'm in college too
It does feel like I went to college in Norman, Illinois
And it's not that they had a dueling piano bar
But definitely we went to like
A bunch of places where like
Jello shots were heavily advertised
It's not something you're generally
Getting anymore when you're in your 30s
And 40s
So much so that we all looked
At them and went does anybody remember how
To take these jello shots
Yes it was really awkward
Only my sister in law knew
She's very nice I like meeting her
Yeah I was like
Because it comes in a little like
Immediately disintegrating
Little tiny cup
And I guess I just mush it
And I didn't get it all
I did not
It kind of defeated me I definitely did not
Shoot the entire thing
You kind of just pinch the bottom
And like
Make out with it
I got very lippy
For sure
The dogs eat like a frosty paw
Which is like a little ice cream cup for dogs
Where they have to like their tongue goes around
And they're really trying to get all the pieces
That's what it feels like trying to get all the jello
Out of that thing
Like a
Like a pup cup or a
Kong with peanut butter in it
Yes it definitely felt like we were
Having a kong with peanut butter in it
A big
Rubber kong and trying to get all the last
It's so weird
Yes
So it was definitely like I was honestly
The whole day I was like
It was a process getting you to
Go even like Scott I was like
It was really
I'm like every
I didn't do this like it wasn't so well
Timed but I was like every 45 minutes
Or every hour and 45 minutes I'll bring up you know
We should probably go
I think like casually
Is this a good time should I bring it up now
We went on a garage
He's happy
Hungry
I could really go for
Some popcorn right now
Oh you know
Oh Jelly Rolls has good popcorn
Actually if you're feeling hungry
I'm like really
In the mood for free popcorn
And like some shoe leather reporting
Like
Really getting on the ground
Like Christian I'm a poor
Kind of reporting you know
And I would yeah I was trying
I was hitting from all the different angles I was trying to make sure
And then you did get to Scott
Scott was he got a musical
High that day because he saw
One of his guys at Epcot
Oh yes
The second singer of Chicago
Jason Schiff
Who replaced Peter Cetera in the band
So yeah I got enough I got a bunch of songs
That I'm very fond of which kind of
Cushion the blow of Jelly Rolls
I would say I mean by the time
Once Jelly Shots
Enter the picture
And then it's just like okay well now it's like
Now it's a bar and we're hanging and we're talking
And we can sort of ignore
The show we didn't get seats
Which was actually good for me because
I'm like I'd rather mill around the corner
If you get a table now you're stuck in there
Now you're committed to it's like literally hard to leave
It definitely happened to us right after you left
Yeah we sat at a table
Yeah
Okay
So you got out of there while
You were safe
While I could roam free
Yeah absolutely
The crowdedness does that is definitely
A turn off
Doesn't it seem insane like that
Is too many people I can't believe
The demand for this play and if
That's what they were doing for 30 years
I don't really understand why
It's going away
It was so hot in there
And I like didn't sweat
I wasn't sweating at all the whole weekend
And I felt like I was in a zone
That was 105 degrees
While we were by the
Once we sat at the table it was better
But I was like oh my god I'm not
Really a big sweater in general but I was like
Whatever is going on I guess
It's just the human bodies in there
And they were not like the air
Was not working or it was not blasting
Anywhere near cold enough
The night before it was not
As crowded so it was not as bad
And we were standing over in the same exact
Area which is like to the left
But yeah
It was it was crazy
Hot and it's not
Not my ideal way to experience
Jelly rolls
You also can tell me cause we went right
When it opened ish
So that was the thing that also didn't help us
We went very like it was what
The last week of operation
We had to go
Early because we told our son
That we would make it in time for
Fantasmic 2 cause he went to see Fantasmic
One without us so we said we'd be back for Fantasmic
Cause I was convinced
Once that like timer went off
He was gonna be like alright let's go
I let it ride out I let it ride out
But because we got there so early
It was like I think the
Doors open at like 7 and then they don't even
Start performing till 8
So when we got there
It was still like maybe a half hour into them
Even playing anything
And there were a lot like the crowd
Was a lot
Like I don't even know how to put like they were
Like usually
When you're in there the age
Ranges all over the place
The average age was about 65
About 65
Was the average age
For people in there
I think what kind of did us in with some of the
Musical choices
Was that they were
Appeasing like the
Sure. Yeah. So like
What did it? What pushed
Johnny's buttons? That's what I'm curious of
I wanna know what songs were
Propelled. I can't
I didn't even know what songs they were
Like they were playing songs I've never heard before
In my entire life. They were making up music
While I was singing
They did play
So they played
The feeling 22
The feeling 22 song
That was our first song
Because it was someone's
Lady's birthday. She was turning 20 something
So they played the Taylor Swift song
Again I just wanna say for the record
If you're 20 something and you're spending your birthday
At Jelly Rolls then you gotta
Reassess what you're doing with your life
It's still early enough
You can change
They have jello shots
That feels very 22
Sure, sure
Other than that I don't
I can't name another song they play
They play the usual
Brown Eyed Girl
Did they play that one? Yeah they did
They played Brown Eyed Girl
Sweet Caroline
They didn't give us Sweet Caroline
That's never gonna help me
Can I say something that maybe illustrates where I'm at
In terms of like
Some listeners will hear this and go
They did play Brown Eyed Girl
Because I have it in my notes
Brown Eyed Girl got people excited for 7 seconds
Okay
And then it settled
And then we don't actually want to hear the verses
That's what you interrupted and told us
Make sure everyone knows that
This might illustrate
What I'm about to say
This might not be a good thing
Maybe I would have more joy in my life
If I was the kind of person who liked
What I'm about to describe
But I have to admit that in something like this
In an arena
At a karaoke bar
Wherever it is
When I am somewhere and Sweet Caroline plays
And everybody does the thing
So good, so good
I feel so bad, so bad
So annoyed
It's one of those
I'm like on the outside of humanity
I'm looking at people and I'm like
I don't know why everyone likes yelling so good
In that part of the song
Mike can you explain what's good about that
Or why it's fun
So good, so good
I will admit to you
It's not that I'm
Here's the situation
It's not that I totally disagree
With the take that I've heard all these songs
A thousand times
And then the Sweet Caroline, So Good
Which I don't even know where it came from
I don't love that
I don't
I don't love saying so good
There's other songs where
I'm much more on board with it
Even though I've heard a million times
And I am with So Good, So Good
But are people, if you like yelling
So good, so good, is that one of life's great joys
Is it like orgasming
Am I missing out on one of the finest
Maybe you should try it sometime
Next time you're somewhere
You should just try it
So I know from experience
I performed it
Sweet Caroline is like a famous
Boston Red Sox sort of thing
So they do that at the Boston Red Sox team
We had an NXT live event, you weren't on this one
We had an NXT live event in Boston
And one of the performers
He's from Boston, his name was Oney Lorcan
And
We were like, we need to send the people home happy tonight
We need to end the show on a great note
Like all the good guys were going to do something at the end
Like vanquish the bad guys
And we're all going to send the people home happy
What can we do? They're like, oh you want to
Perform Sweet Caroline?
And I was like, sure, we can try it
So the whole show
We had a guy in the face who's from
Boston, Oney Lorcan
Was on his phone, learning the lyrics
To Sweet Caroline
So we're like, oh it's a big Boston thing
They're going to love it
We vanquish the bad guys
Oney Lorcan grabs the microphone
He's like, there's only one way to end this show
The song starts playing
He immediately forgets the lyrics
People start booing
You're immediately
Very upset
He's standing there like, forgot the lyrics, he was practicing all night
And yeah, so
Having been on the end of
Kind of performing in the ring
Sweet Caroline
What did you do while this was happening?
I just laughed at him
You're bad, wow
Why didn't you just tell somebody that you didn't know?
He blew it
I'd love to see
A giant fumbled, Sweet Caroline
Sweet Caroline, So Good, So Good
Is similar to the salt part of
Margaritaville
I love the song
But I don't get so excited to yell
Salt, salt, salt
But in the right context
With a bunch of people who are excited
I think this is maybe the difference
I like being in a crowd of excited people
And sometimes it doesn't necessarily
Matter what it is
I can chuckle to myself that they're very
Excited
Like that, oh that's funny that they
Like want to
Live on a prayer, like they've never heard this before
This is so exciting
But once that goes away, I go, well
Now we're all part of this, now I'm living on a prayer
As well, I'm with them, we're all one
We're a team
It's a communal experience
This is what I would say, so yes
When I hear Bad Bad Leroy Brown
Which is not, I mean I guess at this point
I feel like I heard it a million times growing up on the Oldies
Station, I don't hear it quite as much anymore
It's not my favorite song in the world
But I do, like it does, I kind of chuckle at it
A little bit, because it's like
One of the 20 songs you would hear on Oldies 104.3
Growing up in the
Chicago area
But
That's maybe the difference
So I agree with you that I don't like
To necessarily sing the
Sweet Caroline part
But then I can get on board
I can get on board after a few seconds
The group that the magic of a crowd
Just can sweep you up and pull you in
You just want to be part of a happening
I want to be part of the crowd
Whether it's at Jelly Rolls
You don't want to stand out
You want to be a part of the crowd
I don't want to stand out
I'm trying
If they announce
Whether it's the song
Or whether it's them announcing
The new Blade at Hall H
I want to be excited
With everybody
That's a good way to put it
I get it
Even though intellectually I'm like
Some of these Marvel movies aren't going to come out
Most of them will be
B minuses
But like, hey
Somebody came out and put a hat on
A Black Widow hat
I got so excited in 2019
And here's what
I will say this
I was kind of shocked
That once we went to Jelly Rolls
And I started mentioning Jelly Rolls to people
The love for Jelly Rolls
Is so common
I was not aware
That it was such a thing
There are so many people I've texted
And when I say so many people I just mean
Of people I text with
Memories of Jelly Rolls
Somebody I know
Went to a wedding at Jelly Rolls
Whoa!
How does that happen?
I think maybe the ceremony itself
Was at the dance hall
But then the reception was at Jelly Rolls
Did they like rank it out?
Or did they all just go there and get it?
I believe so
I had an idea yesterday
And there wasn't enough time
To put this together
I'll just stick this at the end of this episode
Is that I'm gathering
People's memories
Of Jelly Rolls
And I will collect them
And place them under a bed of music
I was shocked to learn
That my friend Noel
From high school and junior high
Was like oh yeah we went there
And then she was like my mom loves Jelly Rolls
She's usually the one that tries to get us to go there
When we're on vacation
And there's new Jelly Rolls fans we've talked about
And then Mike Mitchell
A friend of the show, Mike Mitchell
Loves Jelly Rolls and he goes
They played Lionel Richie's All Night Long
And it was awesome
Mitch has done Jelly Rolls
I'm kind of shocked by that one
He said he just really liked Jelly Rolls
And that was his one memory
Is that they played that song specifically
I'm texting like
Seven different people
Who all have Jelly Rolls
Memories
So I was like shocked
That this was even such a thing
Like I really was surprised
Because even going once I wasn't expecting
I was expecting most people not to even know this was here
But apparently everyone knew it was here
And they were having a ball
In 2023
Esquire Magazine named Jelly Rolls
One of the best bars in America
No
That did not happen
There's no way that's real
I got the link right here
What else is on the list?
I was skeptical
But I went on the Jelly Rolls website
And they were touting it and I went
Is that true?
And I found the Esquire article
And they have different bars in different towns
That they really liked
And there's a paragraph here
The single best night I've spent in a bar
Since the start of the pandemic
Was at a spot called Jelly Rolls
Located squarely inside Disney World
It's a proper real boy
Joint to get a drink in after
I don't know, it's Michael Theodore Mouse Week
There's some flourishes
There's some flourishes in here
That sounds like a British affectation
It's a Pinocchio
It's a Pinocchio reference
No wonder I don't like this
It's a place for real boys
It's a great real boy bar
It's a bar for boys
I've peppered with Disney references this paragraph
But it says
You can hear a man who could be Billy Joel's doppelganger
Sing The Bare Necessities
And you hear that man just go ahead and sing Piano Man
As if he wrote it
So this person had a fantastic time
And you really
Right
And this is the best night in a bar
Since the start of the pandemic
2023, so that's a couple years
So I was blown away
By how much love
Jelly Rolls has accumulated over its 30 years
And there's more
But yes, I was just
So hopefully unless this is all cut out
And you won't hear this listener
There will be a fond
Maybe 10 minutes plus
Long
Jelly Rolls memory segment
To hear just
Send this place off in style
That's remarkable
I discovered this was happening
Because I texted Kevin Tully
And he said
Well, I'm preparing a voice memo
For a collage that Mike is doing
Oh, really?
So I don't want to step on anything he's going to say
If we hear him later
But he did text this while we were recording
And I feel like I have to say it
I will say, I have only known Mike for a couple years
But I've never seen him more emotive
And happy than in Jelly Rolls
You are like another
Person in there
Just wait for the Mad Tea Party episode
We did a Mad Tea Party
That's another thing
We've been debating about that
For years
We haven't done Electronica
Because I feel like they're the same
But also not the same
Very different vibes
Maybe Jason
Jason brought the idea up of bringing
Electronica back when the Leto
Tron comes out, which I think is a great idea
They could do it
There is that stage
Well, I guess they won't have the bar
But there is a stage here
In Orlando, in Tomorrowland
Where they just pop the band over there
Our dog is trying to break into this room
That's okay
He wants to do the
Bop bop bop part of
Sweet Caroline
Rough rough rough
Bark bark bark
This is another thing
I wonder if like
Is a big barrier to me
Connecting with more people on the planet Earth
That I don't have strong feelings about
Billy Joel
Would everything change for me
If one day I wake up and Piano Man
Hits me
Am I a different man
Do I suddenly
I'm one with all of humanity
And every person I see
The room smiles
I think it's a thing that's holding me back
And has for nearly 40 years
There is
No place I
More enjoy Billy Joel than
Jelly Rolls
I'm not listening to a lot of
Billy Joel during the day
During my life
But at Jelly Rolls
I enjoy hearing it
Now did anyone look up what the first and last
Song they ever played at Jelly Rolls was
No did someone
Did someone keep a note of it
They sure did
Did they come full circle and play the same
First and the same last
They sure did
My life by Billy Joel
So
Yeah
So that
So the place closed but I didn't see
I saw no
Footprint online
Again you were talking about all these people
Who loved Jelly Rolls
There was nothing
But would you say it was harder to find
People who loved Jelly Rolls
Or was it harder to find people who hate Jelly Rolls
Like when Lightning McQueen's Racing Academy closed
There was like a big hoopla
That's because you were looking at
That was all because
The internet was just showing you
What you wanted to see
You don't go to Jelly Rolls
The algorithm was not
Your algorithm was full of Jelly Rolls
My algorithm and my inbox
With Mike over here we were
In an uproar
Johnny maybe you're not on DisneyDining.com
Because they had a nice
Well then you must not be
You didn't see it
I think your algorithm
Disney Dining
Covered this
DisneyDining.com
They have to as journalists
They have popcorn
Popcorn
Jello shot kind of a food
Maraschino cherries
They cover the general beat as well of Orlando
I will say that like food and drink
Or at least
Drinks in this place
Not the best
I think they could have done better
So it's one of the best bars in America
But the drinks aren't so good
Listen
Here's the thing
It's great for the college age girls
Who are like give me all the sugar in the world
But some of us don't want all the sugar
Or for the north of 40 year old men
Who are like give me all the sugar in the world
Give me all the sugar
Beer and all the sugar
So for those of us
Would prefer just like straight whiskey
This was not the place for us
Yeah
I mean they had like a well
Whiskey or something there
I would argue if I was making a decision
I would say like if they said Mike
Should we make the drinks better at Jelly Rolls
They would have said no that would ruin the vibe
Oh okay
Okay that's fair
It's shitty college town
Vibes in there
I think that's just an excuse
You're making
No
Come back every episode
There's a lot of episodes that we could do
Where we would be very combative
Mike and Kayden are both just making excuses
After excuses for Jelly Rolls
We're making valid points
Look the music's supposed to be bad
The drinks are supposed to be bad
Wait till
Neither one of us ever said the music was bad
When you went
Neither one of us said the music was bad
You said the music was bad
It's better later at night
You were at the wrong time
There was no switch
We didn't get a switch
Wait for the switch
Oh that wasn't the right switch
I'm just saying
You can get a good night
Where they do hit like six songs in a row
Or something that you like
It will take you
It will take you from an A- experience
To an A-
So it can change
So A- is the floor
A- is the floor
That's as low as it's ever gone
Jelly Rolls never went below A-
And I think like Scott when you left
It was not the greatest stretch
When we were sitting Candace
You see this Johnny just randomly
When you were there it wasn't the best
Randomly when I was there it wasn't the best
It was pretty good when you were there
It was better when you were there
Because I wrote down some of the
Set that I got to experience
And just like
Can you maybe understand
Why I was not particularly drawn in
We got
Four Seasons Oh What A Night
Lose Yourself
We got
Gold Digger
With a certain word not used
By the white male
Piano performers
And the entire audience
All like consciously singing along
But making sure to say broke
Twice instead of saying
Another thing
And then you got
A tradition for them because there was like a
There were props involved there was a
Puppet involved because it was man
I didn't get no puppet so
Okay I mean I respect I guess the production value
Of that a puppet came in but yeah Man or Muppet from
From the Jason Stigl Muppet movie
We got a Muppet song
He didn't even bring a Muppet for me
You really got the shit out of the deal Johnny
They phoned it in
Maybe the right musician wasn't there
You needed to be there for at least three hours
Yeah
I just honestly think
We were there too soon after it opened
That's what it was
They were too fresh
But you can't stay 20 minutes
When you get there like they just started
Playing and people are barely coming
In it's all your
Whatever you said the age range
65 and 122 year old
Let them cook
Let the piano people cook and
At that heat level the 65 year olds
Are definitely cooking
But Mike how do you fit that set list
Can you understand why that
Group of songs and how do you
Put that or would you
Are you not going to tell me well no that wasn't the best
And as soon as you left it became very good
With Bad Badly Roy Brown
Well Bad Badly Roy Brown is better
Than Lose Yourself Now Lose Yourself was going
Around especially those
Weeks I don't know why there was somebody performing Lose
Yourself at Disney Springs I feel like
Somebody posted a video of a different
Performer doing Lose Yourself I don't know why
Lose Yourself was
So big maybe that's just been a big song for
Decades
I
I feel like Lose Yourself just doesn't get
Me in like a groove I mean
Oh What A Night is like I can enjoy
It Oh What A Night is like fun
And upbeat Lose Yourself is a little
Too I don't know intense for the
For the
Yeah
Yeah it's just too edgy
I was scared of it honestly
Like I gotta get out of here this is an
Uncomfortable place now yeah
So it's not my it was not my
Favorite I do think that Set List
The night before was better
Now what
Would they play the night before Michael
Well that was the Chapel Roan that was
The Mulan song and then
I did get their like greatest
Hits stretch I think I was there
A little later because we were doing
Epic she said like I would have stayed
Later that Saturday night when we were there
But we were doing epic that Sunday morning I was trying to be
Responsible so I think I kept
Saying to Candice I think I kept saying
All right I gotta go out on a big song
One more song and I think it happened four
Times and I
They kept playing a
Better song a cooler song after the good song
And then you're like you gotta go out on like a good
Song yeah
You remember what your last song was there well I had a really
Good last song but then I went back with you and then I was
Like oh no because
We hit the time and I didn't get to choose
What was the last song
What was your last song
So my good last song was hooked on
A feeling and I was like this is the universe
Telling me because it's
Guardians of the galaxy vibes
Our son's name is Quill I was like
This is what I have to leave on I have to
Leave on this song and then
We went back and I don't I have no idea what the last
Song was
He looked at me and he was like because I was like we just got
We have to leave on a good song and then it was like
A few not so great songs
In a row or just songs that we don't really know
And then he looked at me
And he was like we gotta go and it was good we
Left when we did because we had to make it for
Fantasmic number two
You guys are both for you guys the
Converted for Mike and
Candice that you're both like
God I would stay at Jelly Rolls forever if
I didn't have a preview
Of the amazing new theme park
The first thing in the morning I could stay forever
If I didn't have to go get my son
Like without these killers
You would just be in
Jelly Rolls for seemingly
Seven hours in a row
There is something
Yeah we would be there
We would just live if I could live
Multiple lives at once one of the
Multiple lives would be just a guy
Who like
Stays in Orlando I mean it is
Orlando we talked about him on the Patreon
So it's Orlando Mike
You know he's just a guy who like sort of
Lives his name is Outlaw he works at
The American Gladiators Theater
And he just goes to Jelly Rolls
Yeah we believe that if there's ever
A world where Mike ends up moving
To Orlando we think very quickly not only
Will his lifestyle change in little ways just
By going to parks all the time we also think
He's gonna start like juicing
Taking every bit of like de-aging
Drug or
Weird process that he's ever
Wanted to try he'll be bathing in red light
Every night and it's gonna slowly turn him into
A guy named Outlaw what's going on brother
Yeah it's really like if I
If I abandon my family
Completely
And I just sort of on my own I'm going to
Just try a completely different lifestyle
And that would be a guy I think
Who would be at Jelly Rolls every night
And I was about to say too that
I do think part of the
Jelly Rolls experience is being there
For a long time
Like you want that like you've been there
For two and a two hours two and a half hours
You're a little tired you're probably
More dehydrated than drunk
At that point
You get it you gotta be tired
It's kind of weird
There's this kind of thing
You wanna be a bar fly
You wanna be like nursing
Your tonic and gin like
In piano
Like the man in piano man
Maybe we just are fans of that like
That vibe
The kind of cover music
Cause they're kind of pulling from everything
Like you get a little bit little mix of
All different kinds of music and you don't know what's coming
Next and like everybody's there
They're happy they're having fun they're singing
They're dancing like it's like
Being at a party but I don't have to go talk to anybody
Else like I could just enjoy myself
In a corner in my little
Corner with my little group and
I'm happy
Yes and I think that like
John I'm making baffled faces
Everything that's being said by the way
You just like you find a new type of baffled face
He doesn't like live music hates live music
Doesn't want to be at the party
I just said so many things that are happening
Again I was there for like 45 minutes
I think I think 45 minutes
I thought you took a stopwatch
Yeah but then I just I just stopped
I gave up on it
That's what I made it to as well I was right around 45
Aren't you proud of both of us Candice
Both of the people you've tried to coax
In this place
An adequate amount of time
Over an adequate amount of time of being there
You hate live music so
But I can't imagine like oh once you're there
Once you hit that three hour mark that's when the sweet spot
Really is like I can't imagine that
If you are
There long enough they will eventually
Play pony by genuine
Oh
I bet they do do that
Right they have to do that
Maybe I've heard them do that I'm trying to remember
I don't want these dorks up there playing
Pony that's not going to be a good pony
That's not going to be a sexy pony
Scott did you ever have
Like a Richard Cheese phase
In college or me first in
The gimme gimme's
I downloaded some Richard Cheese you're talking about the guy who
He did lounge covers of kind of
Madden Dunn bodies at the floor
Yeah he did yeah he did
That's in the genre
Do you guys
Like Scott and Johnny do you guys
Feel like
You would prefer
And you have to pick one you prefer a
Karaoke bar over jelly rolls
Yes yes
We have a no and a yes
Because you maybe get
Like you get all the different like personalities
Coming through and what I really like
Is a private karaoke room with
A group and we're like
Where you're getting up there
A lot and kind of like group mania
Of the small room is fun
Yeah I'll definitely do you know
A karaoke bar
Yeah yeah you know cause like
Yeah first of all then I'm
Part of the show and I can pick a song
That I enjoy and maybe my friends
Wait so you'd prefer yourself be
The musician and
That helps and that there's like
The building up of the nerves
And like okay I gotta stay in it I can't get like
I can't get too sloppy here
Or maybe do get a little sloppy and then it's a
Funny sloppy but I wanna like
No some of the greatest moments of my life
Literally have been singing
Debarge's rhythm of the night in front of
A group of people a transcendent
Moments that's my
Jelly rolls were actually a karaoke bar
You would prefer jelly rolls
And that like everything else
Everything else is the same
But now it's a karaoke bar
But that also transitioned to my idea as well
So I mean I'm with him here
I think that the infusion of different personalities
And that like possibly I might go up
And possibly my friends might go up
And then there might just be some weird funny characters
Who you get to enjoy and then somebody
Who's like wow that person's really good and this person thinks
They're really good but they're terrible
I think that like you know it feels more like
Like a sketch show or something where there's
Like a there's a variety and you don't know what's
What's coming around the bend whereas
I think I get tired of the
No matter how good the piano players
Are I get tired
Of kind of the
Same deal over and over
Again again I said
Let civilians go up there
Just let civilians go up there and duel it out
I'm all about it
Let them try
Isn't like children going on stage
Now I will say now we covered this during
Our City Walk Orlando Saga that Mike
And I ended up being among the only people
By the end the only people at Pat O'Brien's
At City Walk Orlando
And that too I guess I
Look I just like what I like I don't
Respond to Sweet Caroline or Piano Man
For whatever reason but if I can throw out
The shit I like which that was
Wonderful for both Mike and I we were both just like
Let's let's just we have we
We these guys have to play what we
Want to hear because we're the only people in there
And that was Peridot getting to like
All right yeah let's say let's see if these
Guys can knock out Steely Dan
Deacon Blues let's uh
You know like you got a ton of Springsteen
You were very happy Mike you know you're
Very naked ladies and we all got
To explore our little things you know I made the guy
There play an eight minute Springsteen
Song a jungle land I was like
Let's see if he can do jungle and he
Goes yeah I think I know it and he did a really good
Job of it you know so
I think also I think
At my core also and I've said
This before probably on the show
I think like you know
I'm a normie guy at my core
Whether I want to be that or not
I feel like I grew up
In a very normie place I went
To college in a very normie place
So I maybe going to jellyrolls
I feel like I'm back
Among the normies
And I mean that in a good way I don't mean that in a
Derogatory way I think there is something
To that that I feel like
Oh yeah okay this is where
I live this is where
This is where I actually belong I don't belong in Hollywood
I don't belong at
The Largo in Hollywood with its
Snooty music and
Comedy I belong to
Jellyrolls performances and incredible
Talents and well curated
No thanks
No I've had good times at Largo but I
Jellyrolls is maybe where I was born
And where I should have always been
That's maybe at the heart maybe that's
That's tapping into something
In me when I go there
As much as I don't get at uncertain
Level it's you know you're my friend
I want to see you in your element
And isn't it crazy to that we're like
It's what I'm saying I'm saying it's your
Pony Club Kevin separately just
Texted I've never seen Mike happier
Than in this play like there really is
Something I you know it's
Like I guess it's like
How I'd have to be happy for somebody
Who you know like converted
To some deep Baptist kind of
Religion and I'm like it's not for me
And I'll never convert but they seem
At peace and I so I have to
I gotta support you know
Yeah and multiple people that I'm texting
With are from Schomburg Illinois as well that
Like Jelly Rolls too so maybe there is
Something there is something and not that we had a Jelly Rolls
In town but maybe there's
Something there was something in the water of Schomburg Illinois
Yeah I mean I'm from
Cleveland Ohio and I don't
Maybe it wasn't in Cleveland
I'm from Riverside California
And I too
I loved it
Well I guess there's no common
Element it's just either it
Hits you or it doesn't hit you I don't know it's
Strange I also think there is something
There's some I feel like some people were posting an article
And I forget the name of this there was a term of
Like when music itself
Like gives you like goosebumps
Maybe there is a biological thing
I have that just hearing
Live music like stimulates
Parts of my brain cause
Like my wife cause Lindsay will say like
I think she likes music a lot but she
Generally listens to stuff that she liked
When she was younger and doesn't listen
To newer stuff as much she's like I wonder if
You're just like it's doing something in your
Brain that's different and I do think
Maybe there's something to that
Because I do have my cover band great
A real cool band that's
Like cool and then I appreciate the production
On the album and I'm like oh
Shit this is like such a subtle way to
Produce like I like all that stuff
But you can just throw me anywhere
At a state fair or some like
Band in the park playing covers of
Beatles songs and I'm like pretty good
Like it's any version of it
I don't understand this thing to me I'm like
The more music you like wouldn't you end up more like
Discerning and pickier and you have just become
Like if music is being played
If a drum is being hit I'm happy
And it doesn't matter by you
Or for what
You're just you love any music
It's interesting it's probably better
I kind of
Understand that cause I have that for
Movies like even like
A movie that was just like oh it was
Okay it's like well I think I just like
Going to the movies
Like sitting down with a movie
Except for country bears
Yes counterpoint country bears
I didn't love country bears
But
For the most part
Every other movie in existence
All movies
Country bears
The other thing is
To a lot of people reminiscing
That you're talking to Mike
Probably experienced this
Like on
When they were on vacation
You know
So if the vibes are good
Like you know
They might already be prepared
For that sort of thing
Well they had to be 21 on vacation
We should remember that
It's not like they're attached to it
This is full adult
Your brain is fully developed
And you made a choice
I do think there is something to
And you can say this about movies
You can say this about a lot of different things
If you go into it
Not wanting to like it
You're going to find reasons not to like it
So if you're going to it
Wanting to absolutely love it
No matter how bad it is
No matter the situation
No matter the garbage food
But to be fair they walked by
And were like whoa
He thought it was a facade
He thought it wasn't real
So he walked by going I love this
This is going to be the worst day of my life
Then you already kind of polluted the brain
You said it smells like poop out here
You went into it hating it
You went into it thinking it was a facade
And went what is this magical
Joy and excitement coming out of this door
Right now
And I walked up to the door
I sensed that there were 500 people
In the room
I heard two piano guys playing
American Girl
That caused Griffin and Kevin to go
Holy shit I can't get my 20 dollar bills out fast enough
It caused me to run away
I don't know what
I was not coming in with any bias
I didn't know anything about
That lobby room I think it's really
That's a key spot
If you get a sense of it
The little pre-room
It really is
It did break me but it helped
Knowing that my fee
Would be covered and the jello shots
Helped once I was in there
Getting to chat with you Candace was all great
I will say it all
And I stayed longer than I thought
I would say it all exceeded my expectations
Though my expectations after the first time
Around were
Hovering around Johnny's
Poo pipe zone
What he walked in with
But it was better
It was better than I expected
Barely
We should say
They claimed that this
Is going to reopen somewhere in Orlando
I was looking and trying to find any
Information about it
It doesn't seem to be any further information
I remember seeing speculation online
That they were lying about that
So the performers wouldn't quit
I don't know
If that's true or not
I saw a video
I know this is a weird thing
That I just happened to notice
I saw a video when they were
Previewing a lounge
For the Disney cruise line
They were doing a
Preview thing and one of the pianists was
Playing piano at that
Preview
I think they're good
I think they're going to be okay
Wait until they find out they're going to get replaced by
Joe Gardner
Or Muppets
Muppets
Easy fixed
Jelly rolls
Block out the RO
Yeah block out the ROL
Jelly souls
There you go
Don't even need a new sign
Just block out
I hope so
And then you say hey we have a special
Guest tonight he just dropped in
Everyone please welcome
Rolf
Oh from Muppets
Rolf doesn't
He doesn't get enough
Play in modern Muppets stuff I feel like
This is true
He's not as appreciated
He'd like to see him for sure
Fingers crossed if anyone has
Any information out there let us know
If there's any hope
Mike and I have questions
We need answers
I will offer $5,000
If anyone has information about
Jelly rolls opening anywhere in the Orlando
Area
That's too realistic of a number
Should I say
Parody
I will offer $5,000
For anyone
To give me information
About the opening of jelly rolls
Or can I
I'm not going to be the one to reopen it I don't think
Maybe that's part of your Orlando
Move
Maybe that's what this is all about
Your life
My life's work
You're just at like a moment right now
I don't know anything about opening the Dueling Piano Bar
But I had to do it
I lost something that day
And I'll be damned if I was going to let it go forever
So I'm here
I'm fucking outlawed
I got my piano duelers at my side
Yeah I lived a lifetime
When you brought that up
I lived a lifetime in that moment
In my mind
In my memory
Outlaw Mike's is a Dueling Piano Bar
Located in Orlando, Florida
I think this whole episode is just
To watch you
Yeah
I could see it, it's how I felt looking at the Pleasure Island
Memories, I lived a life
Every time I read someone's account
Of their teen
Early twenties
Now maybe this is it for me
This is all about
All of Mike's variants
Are just at Pleasure Island
Or working the box office
At Jelly Rolls
There's only one
Multiverse universe
Where I'm living in Los Angeles
All the others, I'm in Orlando
Doing a variety of things
So many things
Working at different piano bars
Probably different Dueling Piano Bars
One's like a Medieval Times play
One's like a battle arena
One is a Dueling Piano Bar
One is just like a
All jello shots
100% jello shot factory
You're inventing new flavors
You're the jello shot scientist
In Orlando in another reality
When you bring the magic party out here
So that I can have it back
Oh yeah
The other I'm working is a bartender
At Taffer's Tavern in Orlando
By the way, do we know
I emailed Taffer's Tavern about opening
Because we're coming out there in a few weeks
Week and a half
And we don't have an opening date
And I was so hoping that that would be open
I don't know if you two have visited
The site of Taffer's Tavern on iDrive
Unfortunately the local news have not
Covered it whatsoever
Oh really?
Candice's lives don't revolve around the actions
Of John Taffer the way that are
Haha
Yeah I guess
We walked out
We did a little video in front of Taffer's Tavern
When we were there a month and a half or two months ago
So fingers crossed
From having been in front, do you think it's opening
In the next week and a half?
I don't
Sadly
It makes me hard to say it
No
What scares me most about it not opening
Is that I'm positive
It will be closed by the time we come back
I'm positive
That it will be open
And closed within like 6 months
So we won't ever get to experience it
That's my worry
It's iDrive
It's cut through
It's kill or be killed on iDrive
Businesses
It's open and out
You don't know what's going to last
Luckily Tin Roof where we're doing our shows is still there
Hopefully it doesn't close by the time we're there
During the shows
That would be a big problem
Everything you're really excited about
And gives you the most joy in life
Just keeps shutting down
I don't know
I don't know what that says
If I'm willing that somehow to happen
Including the bodies of 90 year old actors
Who you're obsessed with
What are you doing man
Most of them are still around
I don't want to say them out loud
Because I'll jinx it
Don't say them out loud
I'm thinking
Maybe you shouldn't even do that
Don't think about it
It's too late
I touched my head like
Professor X
Whoever it was
The next time you read about
An old celebrity who died
It was who Mike was thinking about
I don't want to force an ending to this
But now I'm aware that we have to carve out
Approximately 20 minutes of space
For people's fond
For voice memos
Jelly Roll's memories
Anything else that we
I don't know how you want to place that
In there Mike
I don't know if that's after we do all our business
I think after all the business
And now we send it to the memories
I'll do a real
Casey Kasem style
Talk up
He's already dead right
You didn't kill him by mentioning him
Remember his wife
Was carrying his corpse
Around for a while
Remember that
That's a whole
Too dark sorry I apologize
Luckily
We'll find out if the corpse
Of Jelly Rolls is being carried around
Or if it'll find a new permanent location
Somewhere in the Orlando area
Candice and Michael
How fast are you there once it is reestablished
Do you take
Our Epic Universe trip just to take a trip
To be there opening night
God I mean it sounds fun
To do that right
To go opening night
I want to present you
With a question
Epic Universe just opened right
So you saw all the open introduction
Ceremonies the opening live streams all that stuff
Like that in your perfect world
What does an opening
Ceremony for the new
Jelly Rolls look like
That's a great question
Great question
I mean outside of something like every
Table has a piano
Which I think is unrealistic
I would like it to
I think it needs to look even older
I think it needs to look
Have that retro vibe
I guess I'm not talking about the opening ceremony
I'm talking about the new location
I'm making a building in my mind
But that has to be part of it for me
Mike is imagining
A dive bar
And rotating it in his mind
But I think
I think they have to invite
Every theme park piano
Performer in the Orlando area
To come up and do their
Like three best songs
Of all dozens and dozens
Of pianos at the entrance
Of Jelly Rolls and all of them
Will be playing the most
It will be just like a medley
Of all these different songs
May what if it's
Like dozens
Of the Disney Springs
Piano on a bicycle
Yeah
Okay, yeah, I mean
What if Jelly Rolls
Wasn't even a place
I know Jelly Rolls is an idea
It's a concept too, but hear me out
You know those long
Bikes where somebody's pedaling
But we're all sitting at a bar
What if Jelly Rolls was mobile
I like this
Jelly Rolls cause it's
Rolling
Now I don't know if it's
I don't know if the person pedaling
Could also play the piano and sing
If that's too much
I would like to see him try as well
Maybe you'd have to have a piano player on the back of it
But I would like to see the person
Cause we're dueling
Or are the two sides
Like the bars
The two sides are pedaling and they're dueling
And you guys get the best of all the worlds
That we discussed
What if
Yeah, like if you and I are on this piano bar
We're sitting opposite sides
We're dueling each other
Yeah, that's my initial concept
But it's all the ideas
Everyone has a piano?
It's one big piano
Now it's a game
Now we've created a game
What if it's a bike
It's a long bike
There's two piano players on the long bike
And there's a piano on each side
One starts pedaling
And the other one is playing this way
And then as soon as the next song
The other one starts pedaling
And they go the other way
So people switch off pedaling and playing
So they're dueling on the long bike
And there's like eight people
Six people maybe on each side
I feel like you can afford this
I feel like this is something that you can afford
So maybe you are going to reopen
Jelly Rolls
If you can find
A roundabout way of surface streets
From Disney World to Universal Studios
And you just
Establish a route
So you're saying you would take
Like a four hour bike ride
From Universal to Disney World
Well
Because you're not going to be able to take this
Pedaled monstrosity on I-4
So you're going to have to
Take surface streets
But you can go back and forth
And by the time
Unfortunately by the time
Number three is rolling around
You will have arrived at your destination
But you will be
Equally as dehydrated as you would have
At the original Jelly Rolls
But you will have
Tired as part of it
Tired as we learned
Little dehydrated
You did it
You get the full experience
You'll be so pumped up from hearing we didn't start the fire though
You'll be so
Revved up from hearing it
And doing the parts
And you'll probably have heard it like three times in three hours
And then you could play
Limp biscuits, keep rolling
And it would be perfect
Rolling, yeah
Jelly rolling at the New York Jelly Rolls
Well this is beautiful
This seems like a viable business
To get the piano
To get mobile pianos and a bunch of
Like all the keys all out on the road
Really excited for you Mike
Put that
$5,000 to work
You got a little seed money to start
Yeah, don't give that away
Because that could be the $5,000 that started
Jelly Rollers
I hope you guys don't mind that the Patreon money
This month is going to go just to this
Idea
I did think the numbers
Seemed a little off when I looked at it
But okay
You thought zero seemed off for you this month?
Yeah
Well
It's going to a good cause
If it makes you happy, clearly it does
And it's been nice to hear the reports
Of somebody who this place made very happy
And somebody who it did not
Whatsoever
It takes all kinds and it made for a fun time
Candice and Johnny, you survived podcast
The Ride, thanks for
Zooming in this year, stream yarding with us
And being here
Truly fascinating, there can be that
Degree of difference
Even tight
Co-hosts disagree
But you're in a marriage
And yet you make it work, despite your Jelly Rolls
Conflicts
Let's exit through the gift shop
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Go ahead, plug your stuff away
You want me to plug your stuff for you?
My stuff?
Follow her on Instagram
CandiceTheRay
Follow me on Instagram and X
And YouTube and all that good stuff
I feel like you have more to plug than I do
I'm just a mom hanging out
We do a travel vlog sometimes, you want to see what it's like to be a wrestler
Watch that, it's on YouTube
We're on SmackDown
We're on SmackDown too, yeah, I guess we're on TV
Every Friday night, USA Networks
There's a lot of plugs out there
You did some Epic Universe
Did you do more?
We did, yeah, just recently
We've been to Epic Universe four times now at this point
We love it, fantastic
Way better than Jelly Rolls
I'd love to check out your
That heresy
That the new theme park is better than Jelly Rolls
Could be
Hey, as for us
For three bonus episodes every month, check out Podcast The Ride
The Second Gate, or get one more bonus episode
On our VIP tier, Club 3
You'll find all of that at Patreon.com
Slash Podcast The Ride
And just on the subject of music
I was referring to just maybe not liking a lot of the run-of-the-mill stuff
That you end up hearing at this place
I just want to say
In terms of the kind of music you like
And if you want to hear some real music
Some gritty music that makes you feel
And that's emotional and honest
There's a friend of the show
Named Kyle M
And some of you listeners might be familiar with his album
That he put out, The Real Me
You might be familiar with his former
Name that he's not going by as much anymore
Which is Kyle Mooney, because he sort of moved on from the comedy
Stuff that he used to do
Let's get into the music stuff
If I'm pointing to the music that I love
That I'd rather be hearing than Jelly Rolls
It's Kyle M, it's The Real Me
I just want to say he's going out on the Real Me
Fake Me Tour
His first big music tour
There'll be a little bit of comedy in there
But hopefully he gets through it quickly
And moves on to the music
Because it's very artistic and very creative stuff
And I was lucky enough to get to do some artistic stuff with him
I directed the videos for the tour
So if you end up
The Real Me
Is going to your town
With his unflinchingly honest show
I made some unflinchingly honest videos for him
And it was great to do that
So go to KyleMooneyLive.com if you want to see what he's cooking up
And what I got to do with him
So just a little extra plug there
Mike, now do we go into the
I think now
Now if you will
Go out to the store
Buy the cheapest beer you can possibly find
Pour it in a
Plastic cup
Buy some Jell-O
Put vodka in the Jell-O
Find a whiskey
That is so well that it doesn't even have a name
Unlabeled whiskey
Well it's labeled
It's just got three X's on it
Oh sure
It's name is XXX
Right
And I want you to sit
And tell anyone in your family to hush
To be quiet while you now
Listen to many
Many, many people
Share their fond memories
Of one of the greatest places
Disney World ever offered
Jelly Rolls
Please no laughing
This is very serious
Take it away
Take it away everyone
Who loved Jelly Rolls
Back in 2010 my friend
Had her wedding after party at Jelly Rolls
It was unofficial and there were none when
There were no guests there but her guests were
Basically running the place
My friend the bride kept running up on stage with the pianos
And the security guards kept scolding her
And chasing her off
Tuesday nights were free for cast members
You'd walk in and the place would be packed with all of your friends
It truly was like
Cheers for all of us that worked at Disney
You had to be at least 21 to get in
So that was where I spent my 21st birthday
And my friends got me on the piano for Uptown Girl
And you lost that love and feeling
So many amazing memories from Jelly Rolls
We go to Jelly Rolls with a friend of ours in town
From Pennsylvania
And we Jelly Roll pretty hard
And
Our friend Alex in particular
The next morning was like
Oh my gosh I'm so hungover
To get on an airplane this is crazy
He ended up being the sickest he's ever been
And I am 99% sure
That he got COVID
Before COVID was a thing
So I'm willing to go on repair to say
That Jelly Rolls may have been the site of patient zero
For
COVID-19 in the United States
The last two times I went into Jelly Rolls
I was actually with the BTR boys
Mike Carlson paid
My cover fee both times
Very generously
$20 each time
And the man is very generous
Don't let anybody tell you he's not
Jelly Rolls really brings out the good
In people I think because I return
The favor by buying a round
Of four Dos Equis beers
For me and Mike and
Mr. Morrow and Griff and Newman
And it's a beer I never drink
But I drank it that night because Jelly Rolls
Is all about diverting expectations
Really you never know what to
Expect and I'm really going to miss
That place I'm fighting back tears right now
So I better go over and out
I recently had the pleasure
Of spending two long nights in a
Row at Jelly
Rolls just last month right before it closed
And I really can't think of a better way
To end a day of park hopping there
You know especially with the Skyliner
When that was put in
I feel like Trader Sam's takes up a lot of space
In the hearts of theme park bands
And the Hoop to Do review has a lot of
Nostalgia that looms large
In the lore
But this may have actually been the true hidden gem
Of the after hours resort scene
And these pianists could banter really
Well with the guests and they have their standards
But they also were really willing to go
For it to give people like a special
Customer experience
For me though the real standout of those
Guys was this guy Michael
We saw a few different folks but he was there
Both nights we were just there and
And he owned that stage
He had all these great bits and enthusiasm
And like just a genuine stage
Presence and at one point on
One of the nights he decided
On a whim it seemed to do the entirety
Of the Main Street Electrical Parade
I do not know how else to describe it
Except as thrilling
In trying to think of a good
Memory about Jelly Rolls
I think the only appropriate
Response for me is
That my favorite memory
Was when it used to be free
For cast members
The day they got rid of free entry
It closed
To me that day
RIP Jelly Rolls
Home of probably
One of the best nights of my life
Let me say definitely
A great night with a great group of friends
But notably absent
One Scott Garrett
Went with Mike
Friends of the Pod
Mr. Morrow
And Kevin Tully of Telethon
We had a great time
We were all walking down
The boardwalk together and Scott bailed
When he found out there was a $20
Cover charge
We had an exchange here once we got inside
Mike very casually
Lowercase
Just texts American Pie
And Scott texts a photo
Of a $20 bill
In his hand
I believe looking up
At the
Ceiling of his hotel room
And Scott wrote
Underneath it just admiring
This $20 I still have
Mike texted
They're doing can you picture that
From Muppet Movie and Griffin is going wild
I can confirm
I gave it a thumbs up stamp even
I was indeed going wild
I was losing my god damn mind
And Scott said okay that's a good one
I'll give them that
And I wrote all caps
He did all the different voices Scott
I will say if any other PTR listeners
Cliffords
Are similarly mourning
The lack of available
Live rock piano
These days
On June 6th my podcast
Blank Check will be doing a live
Show at the town hall in New York
City that is a tribute
To King Ralph the largely
Forgotten John Goodman Becomes
King of England
Vehicle
Which is a movie that is
Largely centered around
Piano rock as much as it is around
The royal family
The tickets are still available on sale
Bit.ly
Slash Blank Check 25
I don't know why
It's 25 in the URL
I'm aware that this show is the same weekend
As PTR's
Live shows in Orlando
Perhaps some strategic
Errors were made I'm not asking
Our shared listenership to choose
One or the other
Why not do both
RIP Jelly Rolls
Gone but never forgotten
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog
Production. Executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner, Brett
Bohm, Joe Silio
And Alex Ramsey. For more
Original podcasts please visit
ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog
News by following us on Twitter
And Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
And liking our page on Facebook